Yo. Okay, so time for a new video. Okay,
so I'm going to title this video
LJ. Um because I think you know what, me
and LJ, we go way back. Yeah, we've had
arguments, but we've got this like
little lovehate relationship. Um, you
know, and yeah, I know he came to London
that, but you know, he was even around
back when I was 22 before, you know, he
even started showing his face and before
he, you know, had that brown avatar
instead of the portray of his face that
he has now on his uh YouTube now. Yeah,
I think this is a a good video uh to be
dedicated to you.
Every time um I've gone on your channel
um in the past, I don't really go on it
much anymore cuz it's just the same
people, same arguments, you always
promote positivity, positive mindset.
Women are drawn to positivity. They're
drawn to a positive mindset and that's
what gets people win uh women. Now, I'm
not going to sit here and pretend that
you're the only one guilty of spreading
this lie and spreading this rumor. It's
everywhere on the internet. You know,
you see people on multiple different
forms on the internet claiming how women
like confidence and positivity and all
of these stuff that does not match with
your real life experiences, so to speak.
So, I was actually sitting down
yesterday thinking, where did this rumor
come about? Was it just some guy that
lives in these mum's basement that has
never spoke to a woman that just made up
stuff and guessed what women like and
guess what women want and then he put it
out there and everyone just copied it
because from my experiences that seems
very very much um what what has happened
or something like that. So, I was
cooking some nice pork chops two days
ago. Um, and yeah, they're really nice.
But then I started to feel a bit ill. I
started to feel a bit dodgy, like I was
coming down with a flu. So, I went
upstairs to lie down. Now, I went on my
phone and I was looking at uh some of
these women's numbers that I've got over the past
four, five weeks, and a lot of them
didn't reply. Some of them did. I'm not
going to pretend like none of them
replied. Some of them did, but a lot of
them never. So, I thought, yeah, I want
to do this little experiment. I'm going
to see if I write a negative comment, a
negative message um to all of these
women. And the message was all women are
evil, just to see how quickly um they'd
reply back to it or how many of them
rather would um reply back to it. I
literally sent that message, mate, and I
was getting messages at 6:00 in the
morning, 8:00 in the morning, 11:00 in
the morning. Uh, even when I came back
from the butchers, I went to the
butchers to get some food uh food to
cook. I come back and I was still
getting the messages. That told me a lot
of what women hot actually like because
it's not as if you messaged 10 women and
three or four of them replied because
then we can just say, you know, it's not
a gender issue. It's these women. Maybe
they're young, immature, maybe like they
they're just not nice people because
they're not nice people, not because
it's it's women. But the fact by the end
of that day 90% of women were so fast to
reply to a negative message but to
ignore uh a normal nice one. It said a
lot about what they're really about. Oh,
so before sending that um message all
evil, it was only one thing I had said
before that like hey how's the hangover?
How's your day going? All of the
messages completely got ignored. Never
got back to me. Nothing. But as soon as
I wrote the negative message, bam, they
were there before you could say Jack
Robinson. Start talking to me, LJ. What
is really going on here, buddy? You
know, because my experiences, my life
experiences are showing uh completely
different. Now, we're going to get on to
what they messaged back cuz some of them
were funny. Um, but let me just start by
saying I was done with the dating game
even before that. I just wanted to do a
little experiment just to see. Um, I was
done. And to be honest with you, the
reason was it wasn't because the them
saying that I've got a boyfriend, I've
got a boyfriend, I've got a boyfriend.
Yeah, okay. It is annoying hearing it,
but you know, you're going to hear it.
When you go out, you know, drinking or
approaching, you're going to hear that.
And to be honest with you, it's the
quickest way to then just move on to the
next person. That's a minor that's a
that's a minor negative. That's just
going to happen, you know, whether you
like it or not. It was the fact when I
started going on these dates and the
ghosting, that's what really thought,
nah, I'm not pursuing this no more. You
know, this is this is this is too
negative. So, um I went on a date last
month. And you know, when I go live, I
get people on the chat say to me, "Oh,
like, are you making noises or are you
um making these silly voices when you're
going on these dates?" is basically
suggesting that I don't take these dates
seriously and I'm purposely messing them
up for myself. Let me let me let me give
you a picture. Right. So, I had this
foot injury here. It's 90% better now.
Um, and I had it for
literally 5 weeks and it's only just
getting better. Now, when that woman
said to me, "Oh, like you know, let's
meet up." Um, so basically she
approached me. She gave me her number.
She was texting back every 2 minutes,
wanted to meet me. So I was like,
listen, my foot is hurting. But at the
end of the day, as irresponsible and as
silly as it sounds, we can't afford to
lose any options in this country. When a
woman wants to meet us, you know, you
should meet them, you know, cuz it's
it's hard to even get a date nowadays.
It's hard to even get a response back,
let alone a date. So I literally had to
limp to that date, like because my foot
was like this. It was really painful.
was waking me up at 4:00 in the morning.
It was it was a horrible annoying
injury, but I still managed to make it
to the date and I went on a date with
her and she said and then was talking.
It was a Thursday, so I didn't really
expect anything. Normal vibing like I'm
a I'm an outgoing person anyways. I'm an
I'm an I would I would say I'm an I'm an
extrovert. And the vibe was good. uh you
know and she said to me half an hour I
think the date was like half hour 40
minutes I said oh well when do you want
to meet again sort of thing and she was
like oh I don't really feel the vibe I
was like huh I was in my head I was like
wait so you've approached me you've gave
me your number you've traveled an hour
to meet me yet you're saying on the
first date you don't feel the vibe let
me let me give you a better picture
right um or they'll say they don't feel
the connection. We'll get on to that in
a bit. Um that makes absolutely no sense
whatsoever. At the end of the day, my
interests are very universal. Um and if
you don't know what that means, I'm an
outgoing person with universal
interests. So, if I if I am to go on a
date with somebody, it would take more
than one date for somebody to claim they
don't feel the vibe like I've got. And
then you and when you get these
experiences, you need to look at things
like how many friends do you have? How
liked are you? Me, I've got loads of
friends. I have people that look up to
me. I have people that generally
disbelieve me when I say I've gone out
and I've had these women say they've got
boyfriends or I've been on a negative
date. They genuinely don't believe me.
That's like, what? You got a good
personality. You're outgoing. You're
decent looking. And that tells me it has
to be these women. Now, at the end of
the day, right, it's that one was just
wasting my time and her time. Even
though it logically doesn't make any
sense why she would do it, that is what
she did. I logical or logical, she done
it, you know, at the end of the day.
Because let's let's let's put the shoe
on the other foot. If you approached a
woman who was, let's say, let's say
average to above average looking and she
agreed to meet you and you was both
extroverts, you know, um would you be
saying how you don't feel the vibe? No,
you wouldn't. You'd meet her again,
probably meet her third time, give her a
chance. So, it doesn't really ring right
when there's an average guy to above
average looking guy with interests,
personality, and somebody claiming they
don't feel the vibe. Now, that's not to
say that I'm compatible with everyone
and everyone should, you know, like me.
No, no, no. Of course not. I'll give you
a prime example. Somebody that I
wouldn't vibe with, okay? Um, a
vegetarian who's an introvert who's a
bookworm. Me and that person would not
click because we're we're the polar
opposites. I like traveling. I like
going to places. I like all kinds of
food. I like, you know, I've got
hobbies. You know what I'm saying? So me
and that person would not click from the
get- go. But where you know when you're
an extrovert and you meet another or if
they're an introvert if you're if you're
an extrovert meeting another extrovert
and you've got similar interests that's
enough to vibe with over you know to a
second uh you know even a second date
and that's and then after that I was so
annoyed I had my foot hurting me. It was
the first day I remember this. like,
"God, I'm pissed off because of this."
Because it was to me it was a taste of
what my future dating life is going to
be like if I continue with dealing with
women in this um country. It was like,
you know, when someone cooks you like a
curry and you taste a bit of the chicken
before it's cooked. I don't like this. I
don't like this taste of this is what
the taste of my future date life is
going to be like in this country. And
what they what and I'm trying to figure
out what it is like you're a light
person. You're a normal person. you've
got universal interests, universal taste
buds, and I'm thinking that if it's
somebody in London that agrees to go on
a date with you, I would say they're
either using you or they're using you to
pass time. Now, I'm not going to say
that every single woman is wasting your
time on purpose, but um you know, with
the whole if they're in London, then
they're probably just using you as a
rebound or they're using you. That's
that's the only that's the only uh
explanation. Or the third one being,
which I have thought about this is
before these women go on these dates,
they've got unrealistic expectations.
Like they probably got a video in their
head of like some Romeo and Juliet type
situation and they want that and nothing
less. And if you don't give them exactly
what they expect, they claim they don't
feel the vibe. They claim they don't
feel the connection. Like, mate, I've
been all over the country. I'm outgoing.
I've got friends, you know, I have
people that look up to me as as as silly
as it sounds. So, it doesn't it doesn't
ring right. And even though I didn't
really like the person, it was like,
"Oh, this person is wasting my time. Oh,
my foot is hurting." Like, I put so much
effort into going on this date all for
somebody to just waste my time. So, I
was pissed off um to say the least. And
then I thought, "Yeah, I really need to
start thinking about Thailand now." And
then literally I booked Thailand 3
months after, which is 2 months away
from now. I was like, we really really
got to have a plan B here because it is
not working out in this country. Um, so
then I went out. I was, okay, I'm going
to take a break from this. So then I
went out 2 days, uh, sorry, not 2 days,
2 weeks after.
Um, and I met this woman. We were
supposed to meet on the Friday and
literally by the third day was talking
about our interest, seemed all right,
and then bam, disappear. You never hear
from them again. And I think that's the
most annoying thing with the dating game
is is the ghosting and the time wasting
on the dates. That's something that
really gets to me. It's not even so much
like the ignoring or like um the
boyfriend stuff. It it is the ghosting
and the time waste on the dates because
it's just like when is this this is just
this this going to end? And then she
just ghosted. I was like and I remember
being at my mom's trying to recover from
this foot injury. It was pounding me
this foot. I was like, "Oh no, not
again. Another one's ghosted." I was
like, "Yep, I'm looking forward to
leaving this country." So, yeah, like
that. And that's why I looked tired now.
Anyways, on to the boyfriend thing.
Yeah, it just popped into my head,
right? I'm so sick and tired of people
saying, "Oh, how do uh uh how do you
know they don't have boyfriends? How do
you know they don't have boyfriends?"
Okay, let me explain this right now.
There is 80% of men who are single,
struggling with women, etc., etc., etc.
Yet, 95% of women that you approach
claim to have boyfriends. The maths
don't add up, right? And even when I
used to go out drinking and going to
bars and going to clubs, I would meet a
lot of guys, decent guys, and they would
all say, "Oh, I'm single." Some of them
have never had a relationship. So,
you're meeting all these single people,
but yet every single not every single
woman, but most women are claiming that
they've that they've uh got a boyfriend.
The maths ain't looking right. And when
the maths don't add up, it don't add up.
Not only that, okay, if you went out on
the street right now and
you approached three women and one of
them said they had a boyfriend, I'd be
like, "Okay, they might have a
boyfriend. Yeah, okay, fair enough." Or
five and two or, you know, it's then
Yeah. Okay. Obviously, there were there
were some people in relationships, but
here's the thing, right? When you go to
a nightclub and you see women that are
dance around in very revealing clothing
until 600 7:00 in the morning claiming
that they've got boyfriends. Come on,
let's be realistic about it. What is
Jack the Lad boyfriend doing when he
comes home from work? What is he just
sitting on Netflix in front of the TV
watching popcorn whilst he's Mrs. is
coming home at 7 8:00 in the morning.
Why is it that in these nightclubs their
boyfriends are never with them? Because
bear in mind, they're probably serial
clubbers, you know, and I can speak from
experience. I've got sisters and they
rarely go out like rarely. Like I would
even say every 3 months. So if a woman is probably
probably going out every week to a club,
why is her boyfriend not with her? Is
her boyfriend gonna be happy about her
coming home at 600 7 o'clock in the
morning? It's not looking right. And
when something's not looking right, it
don't make sense. And when it doesn't
make sense, it's not true. So in that
context, you can say, yeah, and I'm not
saying that, okay, I'm not saying that
anyone that goes out for a drink
doesn't, you know, um, can't have a
relationship, you know. No, of course
people can go out for work drinks 6 7 8
and go to Weather Spoons and still be in
relationship 100%. But there is no way
as many women clubbed until the early
hours of the morning that they do have
boyfriends as much as they say they do.
Not a Scooby-Doo
chance. No way. And anyways, on to um
the replies that I got from the negative
messages that I negative message that I
sent two days ago. I had one say to me,
"Oh, um, I get she was trying to be
nice, but she was trying to be clever."
Like, this is another thing. Um, women
will seem to argue with you if they
think they're more intelligent than you,
and then when you show like an ounce of
intelligence, they literally just run
away or they play victim. They could
play victim. Um, that's another thing
they love doing. They're experts at
that. She was like, "Oh, I gave you my
number, but I didn't expect you to ask me out."
I was like, "What?" I was like, "You're
in a nightclub and you gave me your
number." Cuz I messaged her. I said,
"Well, it's funny how you reply to the
negative message, but you don't reply um
to um you replied to the negative
message, but you don't reply to the
positive messages." And she was
basically saying that um yeah, I didn't
expect you to ask me out. I was like,
"You gave me your your number." And then
she was like, "Oh, yeah. I was looking
for a room." So then I said, "Okay,
well, if you're looking for a room,"
which she said she was looking for a
room to be fair, and I just told her I
was a landlord. I said, "Well, why
didn't you reply to the first message?
It doesn't make any sense." And then
she's like, "Oh, I didn't want to get to
know you like that." I was like, "Who do
you think you're talking to?" Like, I
was actually eating with my friend the
other day and he was like, "Oh, come and
eat now." I was like, "No, no, who does
she actually think he's talking to?"
Like, if you don't want to speak to
someone or whatever, just write a
message. It was nice meeting you, R. and
just end or just say like you don't want
to take things further. That's normal.
That's completely normal. And most
people, unless they're a psychopath,
would be happy with that, you know, but
it's it's entitlement. Like, who do they
actually think they are trying to be
intelligent to? And who do they actually
think they're talking to? Cuz you're not
talking to me like that. Um about I
don't want to know you that way. Like
some of these women really need like a
reality check. Like I think they feel
like they're much better than they are,
you know? But um and then basically
yeah, and that was it. And then I just
told her like you need to basically get
that silver spoon out of your anus and
stop thinking that you're better than
people basically. Um but yeah, and then
this one was the funniest one. Yeah. So
I don't think I told anyone about this
on YouTube to be honest. No, I don't
think I did. I kept kind of started
keeping things quiet in case people was
like would find out the women I was
speaking to. Anyways, I met this woman
from Italy um about three months ago. It
was literally on the street like this in
central London and I was talking to her
and we spent about an hour together
walking around spend an hour together. I
was basically her tour guide. Went to
the Eminem shop. I said, "Do you want a
key ring? I'll buy you a um a ser a um
servette." Just trying to be nice sort
of thing. Um and basically she was like,
"No." And then we just went around
Chinatown. So there was a lot of there
was a lot of context before like
actually like me uh messaging her. It
wasn't like oh I got her number drunk
and then she didn't reply. Then she
didn't reply. Now I messaged her 3
months ago prior to this saying oh um
hope you got home okay. How's your day
going? Didn't even reply which I thought
is a bit [ __ ] like to spend an hour
with somebody and being nice to
somebody. I wasn't even expecting
anything. I think I weren't expecting to
see her again. I think I was just in a
good mood and she didn't even have the
decency to even write back saying, "I
got home fine. It was nice meeting you."
We would have never seen each other
again. She lives in Italy. That there
should tells you how entitled these
women are and how it's just crazy to
even want to put yourself in in a
position again when you're speaking to
women. Now, she was one of the people
that I messaged, "All women are evil."
And she literally replied within an
hour, and she wrote to me, "Oh," and
this is where she tried dictimizing
herself. She tried saying, "Um, oh, uh,
yeah, I didn't want to lead you on. I
was going to I was going to message
you." Um, and and that whole thing was I
was going to message you. When was you
going to message me back? It's been
about 3 months, mate. I think my message
got left in the [ __ ] in in in in in
the in the in a in a Mexico cartel
border, mate, because that was not
getting replied to, mate. It was just
stuck lost in the Mexico transit because
that was not getting reply to. So,
another one ignores a normal nice
message and a nice person, but then
replies to negativity. Now, how I acted
um with her, I'm I think I made a good
example and a good role model of these
men actually do exist. These men that
are not drug dealers, these men that are
not covered in tattoos, these men that
are not like domestic abusers actually
do exist. And I showed her that. Didn't
expect anything from her and she
couldn't even reply back. That that also
says a lot to be honest with you. Um,
and yeah, so I was like, well, you was
going to reply what what in another nine
months. It's been three months and then
you've not replied to the message. And
then she was basically saying about how
uh I didn't feel the connection. Rare
rare. And I'm thinking there was no
dating thing about it. It was I was your
tour guide. You just had to message
back. It wasn't a romantic thing. Not in
my head. I was thinking anyways. I just
thought being nice to someone, you know,
I'm bored. Let me have someone to speak
to. So, and her saying that she doesn't
feel the connection is actually
victimizing herself. Um, trying to
victimize herself because what she's
basically doing is she's trying to blame
it on something that cannot be helped.
See, I'm far more intelligent than
people think I am. I don't like it when
people underestimate my intelligence,
but I don't want to underestimate my
intelligence, but I don't think I don't
want people to think I'm this person
that just thinks they're more
intelligent than they are, because we
all know nobody can stand people.
Um, so basically what she means by she's
basically trying to blame something that
cannot be helped, i.e. the connection as
to why she didn't reply to that normal nice message
um that she ignored for 3 months yet
surprisingly replied as soon as I said
that women are evil. And um I basically
said okay why uh don't you feel the
connection? Let me just let me just hear
it because it's somebody that lives
international. Let's have a laugh. let's
hear what is it this time and she said
to me that when you asked for my number
initially initially at the start I felt
a bit uncomfortable now I I believe that
you've come to another country by
herself someone's approach you on the
street yeah I generally believe that
even sometimes I'm wary and I'm a man so
I don't think that she's she's lying
about that initially no I generally do
believe he was uncomfortable it's the
street it's London you're here by
yourself I I generally do believe at the
start you was wary and you was
uncomfortable about giving your number.
Yeah, that's that's the truth. But what
doesn't make any sense is that's nothing
to do with a connection.
What are you talking about? You giving
your number is not whether you feel the
connection or you don't feel the
connection. That's the whole point of
getting someone's number and then
meeting them again. I asked you why
don't you feel the connection? That
doesn't make sense. Yeah, you was
uncomfortable at first and probably for
the first 15 minutes she was probably
uncomfortable, but I feel like I
achieved my goal at the end that not all
women are kidnappers, not all women uh
not all men are the are words, not all
men are kidnappers, and not all men are
going to drag you on the street and put
you in their boot. I feel like I I fully
achieved that goal by the time that I
left her. Basically showing her that all
men are are not like the men that they
go for. I have to say that the men that
they go for because they generalize
these men, but these are the men that
they choose and and they go for, which
I'll get on to in a minute, but so
basically I feel like, yeah, you might
have been uncomfortable for 15 minutes.
Um, you know, strangers approach you on
the street. I fully much get it. Um, but
then at the end of the day when she went
back home or went back to Italy, I think
I met her 2 days later. This is an
example. you should have got the point
where I feel like I achieved my goal and
it's not what you thought it was because
everyone's going to be nervous at first,
especially if a man's approaching them
on the street. You did not even have the
decency to reply back to that message.
That says a lot about how selfish and
how entitled these women are. And I feel
like it is bad to ignore somebody when
the context is like that. It doesn't
matter if you approach somebody and
you're drinking, you know, that's if
they don't reply and they don't reply,
there's not much context for them to go
by. that that's rude, especially when
she was um uh she was uh she was sober
as well. Um and the other thing was uh
she then said, "Oh, um yeah." And then
this is a lot of what these women do as
well. It's it's like the same story over
and over again. I don't even know where
I am on so far. Um she said, "Oh, I
don't want to engage with somebody that
has this mindset about women or or
misogyny." And I was thinking, love,
that's the message that you replied back
to. The only reason that you are
engaging is because I sent that negative
message. So that does not make any sense
whatsoever. You're saying that you're
not going to engage with somebody
that says mis mis misogyny comments.
This very comment that made you start
engaging. And then she said, "Oh, I wish
you the best." I was like, "Thank you."
And I wish you the best and I hope in
the future that you don't have to feel
the need to only reply to negative
comments because that nice comment that
was never get that that nice message
that was never getting replied back to.
Oh, did you get home? Okay. And as soon
as I wrote something about women being
evil, bam, they started engaging. Bam,
they started messaging. Bam, they
started with their [ __ ] And then
this, let me give an example of what
they'll do. So basically anyone who's
watching this, say you go out right now
and you approach a woman on the street
and she gives you a number. So for
argument sake, and you message her, she
will ignore the nice message. She'll
ignore the normal message. And as soon
as you say anything negative, bam, they
reply straight away, and they'll be
like, "Oh, no wonder I didn't reply."
It's a form of victimizing themsself.
Even though she had no intentions of
replying to the first message
um to begin with, that's why she hadn't
replied in 3 months, but she was going
to get round to doing it, she said, even
though she hadn't messaged back in 3
months. Um they have no intentions of
replying to normal nice messages, yet as
soon as you send one
negative message, bam, they reply
straight away. Doesn't add up. You're
saying that you don't want to engage
with somebody that writes misogyny
comments, yet you are engaging because
of that comment. You have wrote me about
two paragraphs since I have wrote that
comment. So, uh, make it make sense. And
on that note, I'm done for at least where we
say about 6 weeks. And that's why these
breaks are very imp imperative, you
know. And let's just say anyone who's watching this,
let's not sugarcoat this. Dating as a
man is it it is it is a negative. It's
no different than gambling. It's no
different than alcohol. Alcohol alcoholism.
I don't think I've ever said that word
before. It's no different than eating
crappy food and becoming obese. It is a
negative and we shouldn't have to deal
with it. you know, at the end of the
day, the the rubbish and the negative
experiences um that come with it, you
know, it's it's actually crazy. Um let's
not sugarcoat it. It is a negative. And
I think people need to start, you know,
start understanding that. And at the end
of the day, right, um back I gave up
like 2 months ago and I was I was
feeling my best. No mood swings, no
pissed-off moods, no nothing. I was like
good as new. As soon as I started
talking to women again,
all the problems started again. Which
I'm going to end it on saying that
people say all women aren't the same.
All women aren't the same. Well, I'm 27
and I've never been shown any different.
I'm 27. Still relying on that person to
show me that they're different. It's
like people that say pigs fly. I've
never seen a pig fly. Just like when
people say women are different. never
seen a woman that's different. I
messaged loads of people, one negative
thing and they replied straight away to
it. And yet the positive message, it got
lost in the Mexico transit border. I
think that tells me a lot. And I think
it tells you a lot on about how many
women actually reply to it. They ignore
normal nice messages
for months and months and months, three
months. It's normal, nice, kindhearted people,
but then they reply straight away to the negative messages.
It's crazy, eh? But on that note, I am
taking a minimum I I personally don't
think I'll ever try again in this
country. Um, you know, with women, I I
generally don't think I just ever want
to engage with them ever again because
of all of these experiences. It's just a
negative. And when something's negative
in your life, what do you do? You get it
gone. Just like a normal person. I don't
think I will. And it's so bad. I
shouldn't even be saying this in case
some younger people are watching this,
but I genuinely think they've ruined my
sex drive. Like I I don't even get much
of a sex drive anymore. I used to get
like a really We're not going to get
into it, but now I don't even
I don't even get one.
It's crazy. It is actually a madness.
Sad sad state affairs. But anyways, LJ,
that's my video to you.