Okay, so Lord Jay, I'm cooking up a load
of old bell. And you know what? Yeah, I
thought I would do this video because
this is how I started my YouTube channel
when I was 22. You know, whipping up
some tasty pork chops. Now, the key to
make really nice pork chops if you
you've got to cook them really slow. You
know, it tastes better when you cook
them really slow. And I thought, you
know, I'd do this video showing you
because even though you want to put on a
front that you're big and hard and so
like your viewers, we all know, LJ, when
it all gets tough, right, you all run to
the boys and blame, you know? So I
thought what better way than to cook up
a load of old dill, you know, like yeah,
I could have had curries there. I could
have had KFC. Could have got any
takeaway of my choice really, you know.
I could have got 100 pound steak, you
know, from the restaurant. I could have
could have went to the shop. Could have
went anywhere. But sometimes you just
can't beat a nice plate of old bell, you
know, cooked very very slowly. you
understand? So, um yeah, and you know
what's also good about pork chops is
they're very uh they're very cheap. Very
cheap indeed. Very cheap. These were like £180, £1.90.
Cook these with a bit of mushrooms.
That's a meal for less than £3. So, you
cook them really slowly. You can't be
cooking up some nice old build RJ. So,
anyone who's thinking of like,
you know, whipping up a quick snack, you
know, just just pop to your local store and
get some piggies. Simple. Yeah. Yeah. They're nice.