Yeah. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ] it. H
Why do these people there?
Yeah, I a [ __ ] 20 football bet. It
didn't come in. Oh well. But yeah, bro.
I had this [ __ ] woman be wasting my
time again, bro.
Oh my [ __ ] god, bro. I don't know why
they do it. I don't know why these [ __ ]
Why these [ __ ] do it, mate? Honestly, I don't know
why. I don't know why they waste their
time and why they waste your time. It doesn't make
sense. Yeah, I just 20 pound on two
teams. It didn't come in. Oh well, I don't care,
bro. What could I do? Accept it straight away, maybe.
Not really bothered,
mate. I had a few people say to me
today, "Oh, we should go out." I told
him to [ __ ] off, mate. I actually told
him to [ __ ] off. I'm not coming at going
out wasting my [ __ ] time and money in this country
again. You know, [ __ ]
that for a very long
time. These [ __ ] are crazy, bro.
I don't know why they do this, bro. I
it. I'm actually speaking to Q. Q is a real
one. Q is a real
one. No, that actually pissed me off today, bro.
You actually pissed me off today, bro. I
swear. Why these people do
it? I don't know why they they they do
it, bro. I'd love to know the
answers. They waste their time and then
they waste your
time. What's the
point? You know, I should have stayed
out with my friend
yesterday. I kind of feel bad, you know.
I kind of feel bad for leaving him, but you
know, I thought I had to save money,
bro. You know what I'm saying? But
yeah, looks like I'm never going to be proven wrong.
Hey, I told Adman as well, when you're
back in England, I don't want to hear
about it. I told him straight, I don't
want to hear about it when you're back
here. Obviously, you don't say anything
now cuz you're not dealing with it. But
when you're back here and you're dealing
with these [ __ ] again, I don't want to
hear it. I don't want to hear
it. I don't want to hear these excuses.
I don't want to hear about other guys.
is I don't want to hear about me and
you. I don't want to hear about nothing, you
know. It just actually pissed me off
today, bro. I swear
down. Pissed me off,
man. Got to do I've got to do a YouTube
video. Uh, no, bro. I'm not even asked
about that. I'm just asked about this
[ __ ] wasting my [ __ ]
time. Huh? Today I'm going to get proven
wrong by one of these women. Okay, I've
got more chance of
[ __ ] I've got more chance of pig
flying. I can tell you what happened
now. Anyway, just can't [ __ ] me about.
No, I just lost 20 pound on the
football, man. Only on one bet. I was
talking to this [ __ ] woman on Instagram,
right? I was talking to this woman on
Instagram like three days ago. We was
messaging back and forth. I was like,
"Oh, let's do something um sometime,
right?" And then they gave me their
number. Now bear in mind, no. Yeah, bear
in mind we were speaking for three days
straight. Now, usually they lose
interest by the second day. If they're
interested the second day like they are
the first day, you're lucky. Anyways,
we're talking now and I said, "Oh, we
should meet uh this week." Well,
obviously she said she had like a
wedding and that. I was like, "Okay,
I'll come up there next week and that."
She said, "Yeah, that's fine." And then
um yeah, she was messaging, messaging,
messaging, like voice noting, messaging.
Then I go on Instagram now and I see
that I've been blocked. So I said to
her, "Why have you blocked me on
Instagram?" And she's like, "Oh no, I've
deleted Instagram." No, no, no. I was
like, "No, you've literally blocked me
cuz I can see it." Cuz I got my friend,
he deletes his Instagram sometimes. And
then he comes back a few months later. I
don't know why he does it, but he does
it. And then as soon as I told her that
I knew she was lying to me, she blocked
me. So you went through all of that
three, four days voice noting, wasting
your time, wasting my time, and you was
never even going to meet. That is a [ __ ] madness,
bro. Like normally they do it for like
20 minutes, 30 minutes, but I will never
be proven wrong. I will never ever be
proven wrong. This was a madness, bro. I
was talking to her like it was nonstop.
same age as me, same hobbies,
everything, bro. Nonstop. And what I
think the reason why she blocked you is
because you was going to catch her out
in her lie. Doesn't matter what she
looks like. But yeah, it's cuz you was
going to obviously catch her out on the
lie that she's not at a wedding today if
she puts stuff up on her Instagram. But
don't lie to me. I'm not some
[ __ ] And I text and I texted that
as well. Like don't you know what I'm
saying? because I cuz you know my
Instagram followers whenever I go on my
Instagram uh well I don't really gamble
much anymore so oh and another thing
yeah don't say that it was too easy
yesterday about how you're going to get
someone on my door I [ __ ] literally
you don't even know where I live and I
was going to bed
yesterday I was going to bed yesterday
bro get anyone you want now get anyone
you want now that's another thing I was
going to bed yesterday I was tired I was
[ __ ] drunk as a [ __ ] I saw
your comment when I ended the live
stream as well, but it was too easy, was
it? Get someone here now then, big
man. Come on. Come on, mate. Get someone
now. I'm going to stay
live. But anyways, bro, but what I'm
saying is, yeah, like honestly, all
jokes aside, bro, like that pissed me
off today, bro. Like, and I even had
people like invite me out and that, but
I was like, I'm not going out. I don't
want to deal with them. I don't want to
deal with them, bro, for the longest
time possible. I don't want to go out,
bro. I said to my friend, you can have
you can waste your
time, you know, wasting your money and
time. I'm done with it, bro. I'm done
with it. But I would have stayed out
with my friend yesterday, but it was
obviously I was actually trying to save
money. I didn't want to waste money in
case I had to go [ __ ] next week. So, but
yeah. Wonder why they blocked you on
Instagram and then blocked you on
WhatsApp. They were probably they were
probably eventually going to block you on
WhatsApp, but I was like, I know that
you've blocked me. I said, my friend's
right next to me and he's typed up your
name. That's what I said. So, how how is
that? I don't even know why they do
it. It's not even funny, Bob. Like, I
don't even know how people can laugh at
it. And I and I said to Ant-Man as well,
like, don't don't talk to me about it
when you're back here, when you're on
your little rants again. other guys do
this or me and you or I don't want to
[ __ ] hear it anymore when you're back
here. Yeah, I don't want to hear about
it, bro. It's annoying as
[ __ ] Don't tell don't talk to me about
I don't care, you know. It'll be your
problem when you're back here again, you know.
Yeah. Look, it's [ __ ] raining outside
as well. Imagine going out drinking.
pissing down rain,
lad. And there was no sex mention, no weirdness, no
nothing. Nothing. Obviously, there was
nothing cuz it was back and forth. But
I yeah, I just I just try not to expect
it nowadays because I hope one of them
will prove me wrong. I always hope one
of these people are going to prove me
wrong, but they always end up being the
same. Devious liars, [ __ ] time
wasters, you name it. They always end up
being like it,
bro. It's why there's no point in you
even going out anymore doing this [ __ ]
cuz even if you get numbers, you you
know what will happen. you see what will
happen. He's going to my mom's in 5
minutes. Oh, really? Good for him. Crack on, mate. Nobody cares. So,
yeah. Good for him.
This is really bad,
bro. So why do you think they block me
on Instagram then and not WhatsApp properties?
Oh, did he? Good for him. No one cares.
Um, that Arsenal Mark was trying to get
my attention earlier as well, pretending
to call me out again. Good one, bro.
Anyone without selective memory would
have known what what what
happened. I don't know. I don't know why she
blocked for like no reason. You know, we
had plans to [ __ ] I can put them,
mate. I can send you the conversations,
bro. Every single one of them. You want
to see, I'll send you it. And I was
saying to Q, yeah, the guy that I went
out with, he knows about what I've said
and that. I said, bro, this is why
people go mad. Do you not understand?
Like, I sent him these screenshots and
that. And I was like, this is why people
go mad in their [ __ ] head. Do you not
understand, bro? Yeah. Funny enough, he
hasn't blocked me or unfollowed me. He
just said, I'll read these in a minute,
bro. cuz you know how it is. It's [ __ ] mad,
bro. I don't know why they even What
What was the point of you speaking to
someone on Instagram, giving your
number, speaking to
them? YouTuber texting too much? No. No.
Stop making excuses for her. She's a
[ __ ] Simple. There was no texting
too much. She's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
You know, this is what a lot of society
does. They like to make excuses for
women. And in this case, there's no
[ __ ] excuse. You gave your [ __ ]
number. You speaking to me for 3 days. I
planned to come up there and what? You
just blocked someone on Instagram and
tried telling me how you didn't block
me. I'm not a [ __ ] I don't know who
these other guys are that you're talking
to, but it ain't [ __ ] me. You know what I'm
saying? And it wasn't texting too much.
Yeah. Yeah. Exactly, B. But like it was
back and forth, back and forth, back and
forth. Yeah. Good luck in a wedding in
Manchester. What? In this pissing rain.
Yeah. Good luck with your [ __ ] wedding,
eh? The madness, bro. This why I don't
care. This why I don't waste my time
over. This is why I went out with my
friend, had some drinks.
She definitely definitely definitely
didn't close her Instagram cuz I got my
friend to look up her name and it come
up. She definitely definitely didn't.
I've been using Instagram for years,
man. I'm not stupid. I wasn't born
yesterday. And then when I said, "Oh,
like I know you're lying cuz my friend
just looked up your name." She blocked
me straight away on WhatsApp. As soon as
I told her she was lying, as soon as I
told her like you have blocked me, she
uh she blocked me.
When they realize they can't manipulate
somebody and lie to someone, they run
away. Same as USA, Izzy. Same as all of
them. 2,000 more. Yeah. Good. Yeah. No
one cares. Anyways, yeah, that's it,
bro. Yeah, proper time
waster. And I was actually going to go
up there as well. It weren't easy for
me. Do you think it would have been easy
for me? I've got to [ __ ] travel 4
hours and then [ __ ] pay for hotels
and [ __ ] I wasn't having it
easy. So, it's like what did you have to
lose just by meeting somebody traveling
to you? It's [ __ ] mad, bro. It's
[ __ ] mad. Same with that French one.
Like, what what what have they got to
actually lose, bro? They're talking to
you. Yeah. You're going up there. You're
saying how you going to meet them? I
said, "Oh, I'll meet you outside the
hotel door the the the the at the
reception." Bro, someone's traveling 4 hours.
Yeah. What do you have to lose? You're
texting them every day. Why don't you
just come out? You
know, it's [ __ ] annoying,
bro. But I just said to ad man, yeah,
like when you're back in England, I
don't want to I don't want to hear
it. Like, I literally don't want to hear
I don't want to hear it,
mate. No, cuz when somebody closes their Instagram,
it you know, you know when somebody
closes their Instagram cuz it doesn't go
private and it doesn't give you that option to
follow like you know when someone's
privatized their Instagram. When they
privatize their Instagram, it will it
will still come up. You're following them.
Oh, just brunette. Just some brunette
like average weight person.
Yeah. Or we say deleted account. There's
no way a woman's deactivating her
account. Someone that's got over 3,000
followers with all them pictures. Don't even sound
believable. Doesn't even sound believable, mate.
I know when someone's Yeah, I know when
someone's deleted their Instagram, mate.
I've got people that sort
of cuz all of the other people that's
blocked me on Instagram like pe other
people. It all says the same thing as
hers. See, look, it comes up as deleted
user. See, when someone's deleted their
Instagram, let me see. No.
Yeah. You know, bro, you know, you just know, man.
Like something like that. One second. Yep.
Yeah, she was trying to say, "Oh, I had
to delete my account cuz I was getting
too many follow requests when I've like
wrote posts." I was like, "You'd be
loving that, mate. You'd be loving that
if that happened. You'd be loving
it. You'd be [ __ ] loving it, man. Madness in
it. Find someone that's actually
proper time waster, mate.
See, with men, right, anyone who's gay
or like anyone has to deal with men,
they don't play as many like these
games. These women just love playing with people's
heads. Nope. And you can [ __ ] off, you
little s. Oh, sorry,
White. Bye-bye, white
knight. Lack of life experience, mate.
See, these people on here, I'm not even
going to talk about these people on here
today. These little simps, these little
white knights, these little
rejects. Can it never be the woman's
fault? Not by any
circumstances. And [ __ ] send it. I'm
not wasting my [ __ ] money all my
time. I'm not wasting my money all my [ __ ]
time. [ __ ] that, bro. That's funny,
bro. But yeah, these people are such
white night little simps with no life
experience. Want to message the cunt's
family, but [ __ ] it. Who cares? YOLO.
[ __ ] it. I found him on Facebook anyways.
Oh man, this We ching
today. Just chilling, bro.
you get a lot of it, but not normally on
Instagram. Normally, it's people that you
approach. Normally, it's people that you
approach. Um, it's not really people
that on Instagram. You don't really get
replies back on
Instagram. Normally, it's when you approach people. [Music] [Laughter] Coming
in coming in,
bro. Oh god, they're trying.