Sorry mate, I just made a copper
[ __ ] and you changed your name as well.
So I just put how they've changed their
name because they were
pedophile. Cuz they were pedophile.
pictures as well. So, I'm going to make
some posters of
him. Try and get someone that aren't filtered. Hold
up. There we go.
Oh, is that where they are? Is that
where they work? I might go to where
they work as well
then. I want a more bank. I'll go there
then. [ __ ] it. I'll go to where they
work as well when I'm in Manchester.
Okay. Save some pictures. Okay. Going to
make some nice little posters of this
little [ __ ] Now it's my turn to [ __ ]
take the [ __ ] piss.
There we go. We got the bank as well.
They work at
lovely. Now it's our
turn. It's our turn to start taking the
piss out of these [ __ ] old little
westernized [ __ ] It's our turn now,
bro. It's our
turn. So, I thought I'll edit them later
on in the photo editor and probably get them printed
out. It's probably tomorrow cuz internet
caps shut. So, I'll get them posters printed
out. Never thought I'd be doing this. E
[ __ ] hell. And all I want was a
[ __ ] peaceful life. All I wanted was
a [ __ ] peaceful life. But I'm having
to do madnesses like this because these
[ __ ] in this country think they can
start taking the piss out of people.
So, it's mad how it has to
um be this way, you know,
That's Yeah, I'm I'm going up there,
bro. Don't worry. I'm going up there.
I've saved all of their photos as well
and I'm going to do some posters of him.
Yeah, [ __ ] this, bro. It's my turn to
start [ __ ] taking the [ __ ] piss,
bro. Like, you know, and you know, the
maddest thing about it is I just I just
wanted a peaceful life. Like, I've
already booked a hotel for Friday,
remember? Like, all I wanted was like a
[ __ ] peaceful life, but I'm asking to
go out and do [ __ ] like this because
people think they can take the piss. You
know what I'm saying? People that's not
been taught a lesson before. You know,
someone that's not been taught a [ __ ]
lesson before. So they they they need
[ __ ] teaching, bro. Do you know what
I'm [ __ ] saying? So the hotel's
already booked anyways for next Friday.
So it's all good, bro. I'm going to get
them posters done probably tomorrow, the
next day, and then I'm going to go up
there Friday, bro. Like [ __ ] I've had
enough of these [ __ ] I'm going to
write that she's a dirty little nons who
fingered my kid. That's why she had to
change her name. And I'm going to go to
where she works as well. I'm going to
put the postage up where she
works. Yeah. All around tra all around
Trafford Center. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you
think I don't know Manchester, bro. I've
been there many times before. I'm going
to do all Trafford Center, the bank that
she works at, everything, bro. That'll
teach you, bro. That will teach you,
lad. You know, they didn't contact that
girl on Insta cuz they don't know who it
is. So, yeah, they don't know who it is.
And this was after any This was before
anyways. But anyways, it doesn't matter.
I'm going Manchester next week anyways.
Um, I'm going to Manchester next week
anyway. So, it's all good. So, no
problem, bro. I already booked a hotel
cuz I was going to go up there anyway.
So, all good,
bro. No, they don't know who she is.
They don't know who the woman is. So,
that's impossible. And even if that's
true that she done all of this before
that. So, yeah. You
know, you think just because you're in
Manchester, you're going to he he with
your little friends and you think that's
someone, mate, I've been to Middles,
mate, for a name, but a name behind the
[ __ ] screen, mate. You think I got to
go Manchester again. So, you can sneer
with your little mates taking the piss.
Yeah. Thinking how you've gotten away
with it. Bro, I'm going I'm sending
posters and I put your number out there
as well. So, you're also going to have
to change your number as well. So, yeah, man.
It's all good in the hood, bro. It's all
good in the [ __ ]
hood. See you Friday,
[ __ ] No, they didn't. And not before
she done what she done. No. And no, they
didn't because they don't know who she
is, right? They don't know who she is.
And if they had done that, that would
have been after she already done what
she done. So, stop make stop lying. No
one knows who she is. Anyways, [ __ ] all
that. I'm going there next week.
Anyways, I've had enough of these [ __ ]
you know. I've had enough of these [ __ ]
and all I wanted was a quiet, normal
life. Just a nice quiet life. But nah,
nah. Nah, mate.
Nah. Yeah, exactly, bro. I know you're
taking the piss, Charlie, but I'm going
there. I am going there cuz I've already
booked the hotel. So, I booked the
hotel. I told her this as well on the
messages. I booked the hotel, so I'm
going anyways with these posters.
Yeah, you won't be I'll get the last
laugh, mate. Trust me. When you can't go
into work cuz of embarrassment and you
can't work and you can't walk around
that [ __ ] city center, you know, it's
not even the fact that I like them. They
were just wasting my
time. She um just
ghosting. She didn't No, no, no, no. I
was talking to her. No, no, no, no, no.
She was messaging me back, messaging me
back, messaging me back. And then I
realized I've caught on that I've gone
on my Instagram and then she's blocked
me. So I've said to her like why um why
did you block me on WhatsApp like you
know like uh sorry on Instagram like
what's going on? And she was like oh I
didn't block you. I just needed to take
a break because so many people's
messaging me um when I made that comment
on um some meme that we watch. So she
had so she so she said that she deleted
um Instagram and we all know girls don't
delete their Instagram. And I said,
"Listen, I'm sat next to my friend,
right? I'm sat next to my friend and
he's typed your name up. You've not
blocked me." That's what I said. Then
she blocked me on WhatsApp and then she
blocked my number. So that's it. I'm
going up there next week anyways. So
it's already booked. So yeah, but I'm
sick of these [ __ ] I'm sick of these
[ __ ] I am actually sick of
them. We was talking. We were supposed
to meet next Friday. It was all arranged
and all of a sudden she blocked me on
Instagram. I was like, "Nah, this is
dodgy, bro." She didn't know my name or
nothing. No, it doesn't prove that
people on her message. No, no, it didn't
because she would have blocked me on
everything. Stop talking [ __ ] [ __ ] you
know. No, it was her. No, no, no, no.
The people didn't ruin it. No, no, no,
no, no, no, no. She is. No one messaged
her. It's the girl. White Knight. It's
the girl. No, no, no. I never said that.
I said that she blocked me on Instagram.
That's what I just said. Yeah, she
blocked me on Instagram and then she
lied about it and I was still talking to
her on WhatsApp and then she tried to
lie to me on WhatsApp. Yes. Yes. It
doesn't matter. I'm going
there after I commented. No. No. Okay.
I'm not explaining this again. I'm not
explaining this again, bro. If your
brain does not work properly, I'm not
explaining this against you. She was
getting messages from people where she
commented and it wasn't anything to do
with YouTube. It was the same page that
we follow, not YouTube. [ __ ] sake,
man. God, does your brain not work properly or
something? No, she didn't tell you. She
said that loads of people meant Oh, I'm
not explaining this again. I'm not
explaining this again, bro. I'm not
explaining myself to brain damage
people. If you don't get it, I'm not
explaining it again. I'm not explaining
again. So, that's it. You're just trying
to make excuses for women like you
always do. I'm not have I'm not having
this conversation, bro. Simple. I'm not
having this conversation. She said that
loads of people was following her from a
page. Not YouTube, [ __ ] From a
page, because they're simps on
Instagram, [ __ ] Not people on
YouTube. People on Instagram that are
not from this community, [ __ ]
Because it's a woman and they're simps.
So, what she was trying to say, she's
sick of people trying to get in her
pants and following her. She decided to
delete her Instagram, which he lied
about. Do you not understand? Yeah.
So that's it.
Yeah. Exactly. Yeah. Yeah. So when she
said she had people messaging her, she
meant simps, not people from YouTube.
Just like generally like she said she
needed to take a break from YouTube.
It's all right. I'm going Manchester
next week. It's good, man.
That's it, bro. It's all right. No, I
don't need people on YouTube to give a
[ __ ] bro. I'm going to put posters all
up next Friday when I'm in Manchester. Simple.
And that's it,
bro. Yes. I don't care about Little
Lies. Grow up. You don't know who she
is. I don't care. You don't know who she
is. How can you contact her when you
don't even know who she is? You don't
know her name. You don't know who she
is. Anyways, I'm going to Manchester
next week. Anyways, I I'll finish it.
Simple. End of. I'm going Manchester
next week. No problem, bro. End of
story. I'm putting up these posters and
I'm ruining her life. [ __ ] that will
teach a little [ __ ] you know. One too
many [ __ ] times this this has happened, you
know. And that's it. I'm going and I'm
pulling posters. I've already got the
I've already got the [ __ ] hotel booked for
Friday. And make her aware if anyone
does fire her, she can bring whoever she
wants, whenever she wants. I'm not
bothered. I'm going to stay around the
whole city center as well.
Yeah. And stop making up lies that
you've contacted them and grow up. You
know, you've done this about a million
times. I don't care if I've never met
her. I don't give a [ __ ] Uh, she didn't
knock me back. Nice try, White Knight.
She wasted my time for three days. She
wasted my time for 3 days. Nice try,
though, White Knight. But, um, no, it's
the fact that she tried taking the piss
out of me and wasting my time for 3
days. I don't give a
[ __ ] No, they didn't ruin a
relationship because I've already
explain I'm not explaining this again.
I'm not explaining this again, bro. I've
already explained it about three or four
times. I'm not explaining it
again. Simple. I am literally not explaining this
again. Oh, I told Antman to let her
know. I told Antman to let her know.
Yeah, I'm not doing nothing. Harry,
we've all seen you in Liverpool, mate,
when I was in Liverpool. facts. You
never came out. Shut your mouth. We've
all seen you in Liverpool G when you
done absolutely nothing the whole time I
was there. Shut up, bro. Shut up. You
stop embarrassing yourself. Yeah, I have
been to the Northwest. I have been to
the Northwest many times and you kept
your simpleton mouth shut just like all
the other people from Harry. All the
Liverpool. I would have doxed her
already. Why am I going to dox her? Why
am I going to dox her, bro? I booked a
hotel for Friday. I'm putting up posters
of her. Why am I gonna dox her? Nope.
YouTube didn't ruin any chances at
all. Nope. Ruin did it. Nope. YouTube
didn't chances at all. Stop trying to
blame YouTube. Stop trying to blame
everything but the woman. You know,
you've got a masters in blaming
everything but the woman. Okay. What
about the French woman last week then?
What was that excuse? Okay. Okay. So,
this was over YouTube. Okay. So, what
about the French woman last
week? Okay. Oh, was that YouTube? Was
it? Okay. So, what about the French
woman last week
then? People didn't tell her to Google
because they did they don't know who she
is. Anyways, I'm going to stop reacting
to this now cuz I know what you're
trying to do. End the story. End the
story. End the conversation. Um, moving
on now. Moving on. Moving on. So
yeah, moving on now. Anyways, I'm not
going to answer any more questions about
this because I've explained it about six
times now and I'm not going to repeat myself
again. I'm not going to repeat myself again. So
yeah, he's moving on
now. Anyways, moving on now. Moving on.
Yeah, exactly, bro. I know I'm a lucky
[ __ ] I don't need to spend thousands
this time. So, I'm a lucky
[ __ ] But let me tell you this,
Charlie. Right. So, this one was over
YouTube. Okay. What about all the other
ones then? What was the USA Izzy one
then? What was the French one then? What
was the French one with the dress? Was
that all YouTube? Was that all YouTube?
She says she's sending your friend list
to that Trump channel. Yeah. Yeah. Good
for you, bro. Yeah. Okay. Good for you.
I believe it when I see it. You can keep
making up stuff that people on YouTube's
contacted her. No one cares. You don't
even know who she is. So, I don't know
what reaction you're trying to
get. So, yeah, bro. Good up with that.
You don't even know who she is.
So yeah, no problem, bro. Have you
noticed that Charlie? I love your name,
bro. It's mad. YouTube have ruined a
relationship. Yeah, good one, bro.
You're not going to get a reaction. So
yeah, has it really? Good for you. I've
already explained it about six times.
Yeah, you're not going to get a
reaction. This is not Timmy and this is
not Monty's channel. Yeah. So, do not
try to talk to me like I'm Monty Man or
Timmy. I find it very very disrespectful
that you're trying to underestimate my
intelligence. Is this the same law J
that said he was going to have somebody
banging in my door on my door in 10
minutes and he's been saying that about 100
times? Yeah. The same one that's going
to say he's going to have somebody
banging on my door. Has anyone heard
someone banging on my door all the times
I've been live? Bro, go on Monty mans or
Timmy Timmy's channel, please. I find it
very very disrespectful. You
know, I find it very very
disrespectful. Very very
disrespectful. You know what I'm
saying? Yeah. Yeah, I wouldn't wait. No, no,
no. I said I was going to sleep because
I was tired and I was drunk and you knew
I was coming off live YouTube and that's
why you've done it. Tell somebody to
come now then. Why don't you tell
somebody to come right now then? If
you're so convinced that someone knows
where I live and they're going to bang
on my door in 10 minutes, I will wait. I
will wait here and I will keep still.
Yeah. The other night I was tired.
That's why I ended the live stream and
you knew this. Yeah. Anyways, bro, get
someone here now. Get someone here now
then. Get somebody here now then, bro.
Bro, get someone here now then. It's a
Sunday. No one's working. Chop chop. I'm
not going anywhere. Yeah. I'm not going
anywhere. Chop chop. Bro, I'll wait 21
minutes if you want. Three times. Three
times the [ __ ] time different. Come
on, bro. Let somebody come and knock on
my door, bro. And let them get a hammer
through their head, bro. Come on. Come
on. Come on then. I'll wait here all
day. Come on. Someone's going to bang on
your door, bro. Ain't no one banging on
my [ __ ] door, bro. That ain't ever
happening. Yeah. Get with the [ __ ]
times, bro. I come off of live YouTube
the other day cuz I was [ __ ] drunk
and tired, you little [ __ ] You think I
can sit on YouTube all day talking to
spastics? I'm not moving
nowhere. I'm not moving nowhere. I'm staying.
Simple. One second. Hold
on. One second, bro.
got [ __ ] Ant-Man messaging her. I got
Ant-Man messaging her and
Sorry about that, bro. Somebody was uh
somebody was calling me after wait
until you lose a money b gamble. You
don't like getting rejected by on
YouTube where people contact these
women. These women don't contact any
woman that I know, Harry, because they
don't know any woman that I know. They
don't contact no woman because they
don't know women that I that I
know. You know what I'm
saying? Anyway, sorry. I was Someone
called me. One second. I'm I'm trying to
multitask. You don't have a bad word to
say about women, do you? Do you no bad words? One
second. You come and go.
And you know how you know it wasn't
anybody on YouTube? You know how you
know it wasn't anyone on YouTube,
Charlie? Cuz A, they didn't know where
she was from, B, they didn't know what
she looked like, and C, they didn't know
she was from
Manchester. So, there was literally no
way of them knowing who it was. Where
I've got so many women on my Instagram.
So, this whole thing, oh, people
contacted her. It's just another excuse to defend
women. Do you see what I'm saying, bro?
Because A, they didn't know where I met
her. B, they didn't know what she looked
like. And C, they didn't know she was
from Manchester. So what? You just
randomly just clicked one and got lucky
and started messaging them about me.
Exactly. I didn't I didn't Nope. I
didn't comment under her comment. So
that's [ __ ] I didn't comment under
her comment. I never done that, mate.
You're talking out your ass. You just
got caught out in another lie because
I've never ever comment replied to any of her
comments. You know what I'm saying? So,
I just got saw a comment and I messaged
her. No, I didn't say it. I said I saw
her comment on something and I messaged
her and added her. Messaged her and
added her. Yeah, I messaged her and
You know what I'm saying,
bro? Yeah. Okay, bro. Okay. Well, then
what's her name then? If you know her,
what's her name then? What's her name?
And what does she look
like? Do you know what I'm saying?
What's going on? [ __ ] all, bro. Just
Just woman who's wasting my time in
Manchester. wasted three days of my
life. So, I'm going up Manchester next
week to put up posters of her.
Yeah, it's all right, bro. out next
Friday anyways. Doesn't
matter next week. I've got the [ __ ]
hotel booked. Same hotel I always stay
at. Well, I'm not going to
Well, well, it it might seem like that
to you, but I feel like I've got to
retaliate. Yeah, stop defending women.
It's [ __ ] embarrassing. Oh my god.
Stop [ __ ] defending women all your
life. It won't [ __ ] get you nowhere.
It's [ __ ] embarrassing, bro. And I
won't be wasting my life because I'll
probably go out clubbing there. Maybe,
probably not. I'll probably just go
there and stay in the hotel for a little
bit and then go after like seven hours.
I probably won't drink to be fair.
Bro, can you stop bringing that weirdo
up on my
channel? Can you This is why I don't go
live anymore. This is why you don't see
me for ages. Because why do you keep
bringing this weirdo up on my channel
when I've asked you to not do it? I've
asked you several times, stop bringing
that virgin up on my channel and you
keep doing it. And this is why people
get blocked. And then Timmy says, oh uh
yeah, uh you got so many people blocked
on your channel, bro.
Stop bringing that virgin up on my
[ __ ] channel. Australian [ __ ] Dave. So
yeah. Yeah. He's not taking a piss. He's
a keyboard warrior. People can do
whatever they want, right? Yeah. Revenge
is never a waste of a life. It's never
Exactly, bro. You know it ain't. You
know it ain't. And it's not even it's
not even one person, Charlie. This is
what these people don't understand. It's
not of one person. It's all of them.
Like that French [ __ ] wasting my
time. Like that other [ __ ] wasting
my time. Now this person from
Manchester. It's an amalgamation of
things. It's not one person or one
thing. This is what people don't
understand. He's not taking a piss. He's
a little keyboard warrior. That's a
YouTube obsessed repeater man. There's
nothing taking the piss about that
little gay virgin, that little closeted
homosexual. So, I don't know why you
keep bringing them up on my [ __ ]
channel. Do you know what I'm saying?
Why you keep bringing this little
YouTube obsessed little virgin up on my
channel? Exactly, bro. It's principle.
Yeah. I don't blame anyone from [ __ ]
YouTube cuz Okay, it was people from
YouTube, was it? What about that French
woman? What about all these other women?
What about USA? What about all of them
women? What about all of them women?
Hey, isn't that mad, Charlie? How is it
that all of these women have done
similar devious, nasty, evil things that
we knew had nothing to you knew had
nothing to do with YouTube, but this
person is just so happens to be someone
on YouTube that stopped it all. Isn't
that a madness? What's the chance of
that? So, you've got all these women,
USA, Izzy, French ones, all of these
ones. Didn't know my name, didn't know
YouTube, didn't have them on Instagram.
So, we knew YouTube definitely never
[ __ ] this one up. But something tells
you with this one that YouTube stopped
the [ __ ] Mary go around. I don't
think so. I don't think so. You know
what I'm saying? They just love blaming
everything but women. Welcome to the channel,
Charlie. Man's like, I'm pissed off cuz
it wasn't even you. It wasn't even me.
He said it wasn't even me. He's like, it
wasn't even me and it's pissing me off.
Like, I get what you mean, bro. Like
even when I see these other men deal
with these shitty women, it annoys me
just watching it. Like even a I don't
even like watching it, bro. Like I'm I'm
the same. Like I don't even like
watching it happen to other people. You
know what I'm saying?
So yeah. No, no, not not necessarily.
Not necessarily, bro. Like no. If you
talk to someone and they ghost you the
same day, I mean no not not necessarily,
bro. But if they lead you on and then
get with you, then ghost you. Yeah, it
should be. It should
be. They're [ __ ] sat there laughing
with their friends thinking that they've
got away with it because they're in
Manchester. Mate, I'll go Manchester
next week. It's already all booked. You
know, I've done it enough times for
these [ __ ] You know, I've been to
Middlesbrough to try and meet someone.
You know, the [ __ ] never come out. I'm
in Newcastle. Bro, do you think
Manchester is really going to stop me?
They deserve it, bro. I'm just going to
pull up posters. That's all I'm going to
do is pull up
posters. That's it. You know, it's about
time someone [ __ ] these people need to learn, bro. You
know, they always love blaming YouTube,
blaming and you know this one. Yeah.
Sometimes they can say, "Oh, woman
change her mind." But this one blatantly
was taking the piss. Now, this one here
was blatantly taking the [ __ ] pissed.
Yeah, I know. I'm No, no, no. I'm pissed
off cuz I thought I found somebody that
was [ __ ] normal because we were
speaking for 3 days. Normally when you
speak to someone, Charlie, yeah, the
next day they're going to ghost you and
that's just like you expect it. You
expect them to be interested one day and
not interested in the next. But this
person kept texting and texting and
texting. But even though this is a prime
example of this person in particular
taking a piss, they've got no bad words
to say about women. I had somebody try
and say it was because I sent two exes
even though she was sending two exes too
and trying to say that I was like they
will they will do anything to defend
these women. No matter if it's an
approach, whether it's um a dating app,
whether it's [ __ ] you met them on
Instagram, even if you're right, you're
wrong. Even if you was right in like one
in 50 times, nope, you're wrong. Nope.
Nope. Nope, you're wrong. In their
minds, women can't do no
wrong. Women can't do no wrong in their
eyes. You know, there's something about
a woman that can't do things
intentionally, that can't be evil, that
can't be a piss taker. They seem to
think because they're a woman, it's
impossible for them to be any of that,
which it doesn't make sense. You know
what I'm saying? It's it's [ __ ] m
it's mental, bro.
You know, they don't seem to think
there's no bad women in the world. They
That's what they think. That's generally think. You
know, no, it's not even about hitting a
woman or not hitting a woman. It's not
even No, no, no. It's not even just
about that. It's they do nothing but
defend them. No, no, no. It's not even
just that. It's that there's they do
nothing but make excuses and defend
them. Like if somebody says, "Oh, you
can't hit a woman." Well, that's just
the way society is and that's just the
way the world works. Unless they hit you
first, then okay, we can live with that.
But it's they do nothing but defend
them. Nothing but defend them. Even when they're
wrong, they will never ever like even
when I used to tell people like the USA
Izzy story, they would never ever have a
bad word to say about her. There was a
few people that said, "Oh, I'd ruin her
life." There was a few people that said,
"Oh, if that was me, I would make the
[ __ ] pay." Like, there was like maybe
like 15% of people.
Um, but yeah, most people would just
defend them and make excuses for them.
And maybe this and maybe that, and maybe
this, and a woman don't owe you nothing.
And that's what they do. They want to be
equal. They want equality. But there's
no equality because well the only thing
a man can do that a woman can't do is
sleep around and not get called a slag.
If you've got a [ __ ] between your legs,
mate, the world is your oyster. If you
was born with a [ __ ] oh my god, dating
apps are easy. [ __ ] you can get away
with murder. You can take the piss and
people would defend you. Imagine living
life on easy
mode. [ __ ] hell. Sometimes I'd love a
[ __ ] between my legs, mate. You know
what couldn't you get away
with? What couldn't you get away with? You
know, if you had a [ __ ] in between your
legs. I'm still waiting for the day, uh,
Charlie, when somebody says, "Oh, a man
doesn't owe you anything to a woman that's
complaining." You never hear that,
though, will you? Nah, you never say
that to a woman, though, would you? You
say it enough to men though, don't you, mate?
And I'm not talking about every single
example. I'm talking about, let's give
two examples. USA, Izzy, and this [ __ ]
in Manchester. These circumstances, they
were in the wrong. But no one will say
that. Oh, you sent two
X's. Oh, uh, yeah, maybe he was a bit
too full on or, oh, maybe they changed
their mind. It's nothing in their mind
that this person could have just been
taking the piss out of you. They don't
believe it. They don't want to know. Any
point that you prove against a woman
being a [ __ ] they call you an incel.
It's like it's like you're treading on
eggshells. And that's exactly why I
didn't go out yesterday cuz I'm not
dealing with these [ __ ] anymore in this
country. I've had enough of them. You
know, I stopped going out to get away
with from it. You know, I met my friend
the other day to get a [ __ ] way with
to get away from it. That's why I stayed
locally, you know.
And that's it,
bro. They're [ __ ]
horrible. I I I I don't understand it.
They always say it when they do bad,
when they do wrong. They always say it
when a woman does wrong. They never use
it in the right context either. They
just use it to try to justify their
shitty behavior. But the thing is is
that they say that a woman don't owe you
nothing, but the women are the same
people that will message you asking you
for money. You I've had it many times.
You've probably had it. They will think
the world owes them anything because
they're so entitled. Yet we're told that
women don't owe us nothing. But they're
the they're the entitled ones. We're
only trying to find love and we're
complaining when we get [ __ ] around
with. But then you tell us when we get
[ __ ] around with how they don't owe us
anything. That doesn't even make sense.
You're not even using it in the right
context. But yeah, they they will do
anything to to defend a woman. You
know, I don't want to deal with these
people anymore, bro. I'm sorry. And it
weren't even just that one. It was the
French one. It
was the the other one as well. It wasn't
just um they talk they lead people on to
waste their time, you
know. They lead people on on purpose to waste their
time and take the piss out of someone.
That's what they do. A lot a lot of them do do
that. The only person I have ever met in
my life that was not like that was that
one from New
Zealand. And that says a lot. That says
a lot. With all the traveling you've
done and all of the women that you've
you've seen, been with approached that
only one of them is not like that.
That's a woman problem, bro. That is a
woman problem. I can't even count on one
hand how many women I've met that are
different because they're all the same.
Literally, they are all the same. And
and and when they get older, they don't
change either. Don't think, "Oh, once
they're older." No, they never change.
They never never never never never
change. Even when they're older, they don't change,
bro. They They never never never never
change. And you know, the thing is,
Charlie, it weren't even an easy ride
for me. If this person turned around and
said they would have met me, bro, I
still got to go all the way to [ __ ]
Manchester, you know? I'm anxious. I've
not traveled by myself for
ages, you know? So, it's not like a case
of, oh, you going up the road. It's far,
bro. You know, that's It weren't even
like it was an easy
ride. Yeah, but to be fair, I did say I
was going to meet her and I didn't meet
her again. Like, she had every right to be like
that. She didn't just disappear, bro. I
was talking about other [ __ ] when I
was with her. I was supposed to meet her
the next day. So, she's the only one,
bro. But all of the rest of them,
they're [ __ ] Uh my man uh my football
bet didn't win. No, I wasn't even asked
about losing the football bet. I didn't
even care about that cuz this [ __ ] in
Manchester was [ __ ] pissing me off, bro. That's
why go to a black guy, go to a [ __ ]
woman abuser. You obviously like them
people in this country, you know. I'm
not saying a black man's a woman abuser,
but I'm saying that they either like
black men, white people with tattoos, or
somebody that abuses them. Go with the
people that you like. Stop wasting nail time. You
know, I'm not going to lie to you, bro.
Oh my god. This [ __ ] thing on Valentine's.
Yeah. So, I met this woman from
Liverpool before in Birmingham. It was a
couple of years ago now. I think it must
have been about 3, four years ago. I
think it was the last time I went to
Birmingham. Oh, I don't give my number
out. Gave me her Snapchat. Been trying
to contact her on and off for years.
Guess what? She posted a snap on
Valentine's Day kissing a black
man. Oh my god, it was funny. I showed
Ant-Man. It was funny to be fair. You
have to laugh at it. They literally have
the same types. It's even It's like
Manchester as well. You know, everything
they do is either you you have to be a
white woman abuser with tattoos, a drug
dealer, a crackhead, or black. And
unless you're one of them, you stand no
chance in this country. And that's not
being racist. I'm not saying that that
the black people they get with are bad.
I'm saying that that's the kind of
people that they go for. Yeah. He was
kissing her and touching her boobs. I
swear to God, bro, it was some guy with
dreadlocks. I swear to God. Like, it did
make me chuckle a little bit. But guess
what's going to happen? She's going
to You can laugh at it cuz it's funny.
It is funny. It is funny. I did laugh at it.
It was funny to be fair cuz you couldn't
make it up. You couldn't make it up. But
when they go for white guys, they like
abusers. They like men with tattoos on
their necks. They like them kind of
people. Them kind of scumbags. They
don't like normal
people. They don't like normal people, bro.
Um, you know, they only like white scumbags and
crackheads. I don't even find it funny,
bro, to be honest with you. [Laughter] [Music]
Um, I just don't think she replied,
bro. I can't remember.
I think it's [ __ ] disgusting
me. I think it's disgusting me, mate.
Yeah, I think it's [ __ ] disgusting.
What do you think? And then there's one
I'm speaking to, but she's just too fat.
She's just too fat,
bro. She's just too too too fat.
Yeah. So, that's no good, of
it. When will I get proven wrong?
Anyways, I want to get proven wrong. I'd
love to come on YouTube and say I met a
woman and I was proven
wrong. Well, it will happen, just not in
this country. Well, it's already
happened, but they're not English.
They're Asian. So, uh, yeah, they're not
American. Definitely not
Yeah. So, yeah, I have met women that
were different. Actually, people that
are not from this [ __ ] country.
Yeah. That speaks volume though, don't
it? Whenever you meet an an Asian woman
or something like that, you never get
this problem. Isn't it mad? Isn't it mad
how they say that? It's not the women in
this country, right? Yeah. Any
westernized woman that you deal with
Australia, [ __ ] America, they're the
worst. England, it's all the same
negative Nancy experiences, negative
Wendy experience. But yet, as soon as
you get with like a Asian woman or you
speak to an Asian woman, um, you don't get these
problems. Isn't that mad? But it's
definitely not westernized women as
well. It's definitely definitely not
westernized women. No. No. That's why
it's always the same games, you
know. I know, man.
But I don't know what the problem is, bro. It's m
it. What can one do? Hey, what can one do? Really?
How would you even meet someone?
Charlie, I was speaking to my friend
yesterday. He lives in uh near
Liverpool. Um he went to New Zealand as
a kid, but he's back here now and he was
saying how depressed he is. I said, "Oh,
if you ever need to talk, come here or
whatever." Like I know cuz I'm dealing
with it as
well. You know, I'm dealing with it.
though, but not like I just said to him
like basically like I'm I said to him
like you're best off just going to
Liverpool and going for a drink and
sending it like I'm beyond that now.
Like I've tried more than anyone in the
world, but I don't want to tell him
that. So he feels negative. You know
what I'm saying? Like I just told him
like, "Yeah, you're in between
Manchester and Liverpool. You might as
well just go Liverpool and just send it
cuz these dating apps are no good for
you, man. I don't even know why people
use them. I honestly don't know why
people use them.
I said I just go for a drink just to
have a drink, you know, like I said to him
like we've known each other since for
years like since we were kids. So, and
he said to him
like, and the thing is it wouldn't have
even been easy even if this person did
meet me cuz I still would have had to go
Manchester [ __ ] miles away, you know.
But then they moan about where are all
these nice guys? Where are all these
nice guys that don't cheat on
me? You left them behind, bro. You
know, you left them
behind. What do you reckon would have
happened if I went out sending it yesterday, Charlie?
Good old trouble.
What do you think would have happened, mate? Yep.
But some for some reason people don't
have a bad word to say about westernized
women. Not bad
words. Not bad
words. He's He's surprised I've not
killed myself or killed someone. Yeah.
He said, "I'm surprised you've not
killed yourself or killed someone." But
I said, "Bro, I'm a bit different than
you." Like, I'm going to go and do these
posters cuz I know that if I do get
caught, like I'm not really going to go
prison for putting up posters. These
[ __ ] are not worth it. They're not worth my
freedom. Um, why was I back on dating
apps? Um, I can I can answer you. That's
a good question. You've been saying
dating apps are useless for years, made
videos, etc. Why was I back on them? I
I'll explain to you why I was back on
them. So, the last time except from
early in January when I was in Wales, I
said I would never use them. So, two
years later, it was this year. Um, it
was the start of January and I was like,
"Oh, man. I I don't really want to go
out and waste money. It's cold. I've got
the flu. Not not many people's really
going to be out. Now, let me try these
dating apps because it's been 2 years,
right? I swear I'd never go on them
again." And oh my god, they were [ __ ]
Oh my god. It led to porn addiction,
kiss taking women. I literally was on it
for like a week and deleted all the
apps. So the reason I was on them is
because it was January and people
weren't really going out, you know, cuz
people don't really go out January,
start of January and I got so fed up
with them that I just deleted them. They
were making they were driving me mad. So
just like a little tester in January.
Yeah. But yeah, that's the thing cuz if
you go out and you do madness, then
you'll lose your freedom because of
these women. It's not worth
it. It's not worth it. You know, no
food, no coke, no
nothing sat there without a [ __ ]
phone in prison cuz of these [ __ ] It's
not worth it. As m as much as crazy as I
am, right, you have to also be careful
at the same time. And these [ __ ] love
playing victim as well. So yeah, that's
that's why I don't use dating
apps cuz they're just the most pointless
thing ever. Unless you're a woman or
gay. Unless you're gay or a woman,
they're the most pointless thing. And
then that leads to porn addiction and
all these other problems, you know?
So, I mean, they're rigged against men.
Think about it, right? You're in a city
like London. Why would you go on a date?
Think of all of the competition there is,
right? Why would you even waste your
time? Piss taking women, catfishes,
[ __ ] competition, people pretending
to be women that are actually men. Like,
why would you even waste your time on
dating apps? It's [ __ ] stupid.
Yeah, mad is it? I I thought the
offering money thing would have worked.
I actually did think the offering money
thing would have
worked. I actually did think that was
going to work. That actually did surprise
me. Do you think it would work doing it
in another area? Nah. Nah.
No, it's not. It doesn't matter about
the area, man. There's poor people in London as
well. Well, I actually thought that was going to
work. I can't lie to you. I actually
thought that was going to work. But it's
probably best. I'm not trying again,
bro. I'm done. I'm done for a very long
time. I'm not trying again. I only went
out Friday because my mate went was up
the road and he wanted to meet me. He
come down from Manchester where he lives
now. Uh, no. I'm not trying again. I'm
done. I'm done, bro. For a very long
time. I'm not trying it
again. No, I'm not trying it again. I'm
not trying nothing again in this country
for a very long
time. No, my friend was like, well,
actually, he was a few, he was actually
a few stops away. I was like, listen, if
you come here, I'll meet you. And he
came here. That's the only reason I met
him cuz he went he was like 10 minutes
up the road. Otherwise, I wouldn't have
met him. I weren't traveling to meet
anyone. I weren't trying to do that.
So, yeah. No, I'm not doing it. I'm not
doing it again in this country. I've had
enough. It's not my problem no more.
Even though I'm still here, it's not my problem no
more. Cuz how many times does this [ __ ]
have to keep happening before you get
the before you get the point? You're
born in the wrong day and age. You're in
the wrong country. There's no one for
you. How many times you have to keep
doing this till you get the
hint? You know, the hint's not hard to see, bro.
I'm not trying it
again. I thought it would have worked
though. Did you think it would have
worked, Charlie? I thought it would have
worked. Genuinely believed it was going to work.
Yeah. Nothing's going to change in this country, bro.
faster than did it, bro.
See, if YouTube actually did ruin it,
we'd actually know why it happens. We'd
actually know why this [ __ ] happened. If
it was actually YouTube that ruined
these things, we would actually have an
answer for it. But it isn't, so we don't
have an answer for it.
bad, bro. It's very
bad and it's never going to change
either, you know.
So, this French woman said to me, "And
do you do you want to know what I said back? SW off.
remember them times I had to make
excuses when people used to invite me
out all the time. I used to say I'm in
Wales to see my nan even though I don't
[ __ ] have any family members in in
Wales. Do you remember that period? I
used to have to make
excuses. It was hard to keep up with the
lies as well. Like I had people invite
me out yesterday, today. I had to make
excuses saying, "Oh, like I'm out of
London." And yeah, it's crazy, bro. You
have to make excuses when you're very popular.
Yep. I know you're taking a piss, but it
is it is the
truth. It honestly I thought that money
thing would have worked.
[ __ ] Yeah, I actually thought that
money thing would have worked, bro.
I generally thought that would have
worked. I I'm actually shocked,
bro. I'm actually shocked. I actually
thought I would have won. So, you truly are [ __ ]
going out, bro, for a very, very long
time. So, there's no point in saying it
anymore. Go out. Go out, cuz I won't be
doing it, bro. For a very long time.
I've had enough of
it. Had enough of it. I've had enough of these
Yeah, I said it was my nan's birthday,
so I'm in
Wales. And think about it, bro. If you
was going to meet
someone, if you was going to meet
someone, met someone by
now, think about it. You tried more than
anyone in the world, bro. If you was
going to meet
someone, you would have [ __ ] met him by
now. Think about it
logically. You got to be logical about
it statistically, right?
Yeah, nothing will uh change in this
country. Well, at least I can drown my
to a nice KFC. Hey boss.
Yeah. So, what would have happened if I
went out approached on Saturday, Charlie?
How come is Manchester is the West Midlands,
Charlie? I kept saying to Timmy, me and
him should go to the black should go to
Blackpool in the West
Midlands. Blackpool in the West
What do you think?
Huh? I don't think I've been right since
my mama left me,
Johnny. I think since my mama left me.
I've not been the same since, have I?
Charlie, my mama left me.
Charlie since my mama left
me. [ __ ] Your mama left you.
Mama of him.
Sucks, isn't it, bro? [ __ ]
sucks. I'm probably going to eat once
today. KFC anatomy done,
bro. Just stay in bed depressed.
Oh, I just done that wrong media
channel. God, you're so obsessed.
You, you know, like you don't [ __ ] with
anyone's head. You little virgin. Like
everything you say is just funny now.
Like we all laugh at it, virgin boy.
Like you're obviously trying to be
pated. The skin big nose woke up with no
woman and no money. Even though we all
know that I've got more money than
anybody on this community. Like you're
not going to bait people for reaction,
bro. I'm not the one that had to
withdraw all of my housing benefit, all
one, 1500 of it to make it look like
I've got money. Do you know what I'm saying, bro?
Like it's it's just so embarrassing at
this point. Like you we clearly know
that I have got more money than 90% of
people in this community and I get more
money than 90% of people in this
community. So you're just really really
really embarrassing yourself like when
you're saying these
things, you know, and you're being
psychologically affected as well because
you can't come off you can't come on
YouTube every day without being
obsessed. So, you're the one who's
actually getting triggered because
you're the one that can't every day.
You're obsessed every day. You're on YouTube
obsessed, you know, like these people. I
don't even know how Timmy can get
triggered over these people, bro. It's actually funny.
self projected and YouTube
obsessed. Like everything that they say
is just about their own lives. So they
can't trigger no one. Like when they say
skin, lonely, virgin, [ __ ] whatever
the [ __ ] they're saying, it's just a
reflection of their own life, you know?
So this is why we can't even get
triggered over it, you know? A bunch of
people talking about themselves because
they don't know your life. They don't
know what you have. They don't know how
much money you get. They don't
life except from what you actually put
out there. You know what I'm saying, bro? You
know, like you got no teeth, you look
like a rat, you got a disabled
girlfriend, you get a proxy,000 a month,
and you think you can come on YouTube
and talk about
anyone. A grand a month. Imagine getting
a grand a month. I could live on that. I
could not live off a,000 pound a month.
And that's what this [ __ ] gets. Maximum
max skin. That's why he calls other
people skinned because he's skinned himself, you
know, a month, bro. [ __ ] that.
I'd be even more depressed. Imagine
living off that a grand a month. [ __ ] hell. Jesus
Christ. He calls people skin, but he is
the only one that is actually skin. Just
like a lot of these people. Look at all
them that I showed money. No one could
show me nothing. Like you are the one
who only gets benefits. You are the one
that has to show your house a benefit.
You are the one that is skin. You ain't
got a bed. You got no
teeth. You dress like a [ __ ] Like
who's the one that
really really has no money?
You. You're the one that has no
money. Like Charlie, you really think I
can't go to the ATM right now? Well, not
not the AT. Well, actually the bank's
closed. But you really think I can't go
to the bank tomorrow and withdraw
thousands and show these people? I'm not
showing them nothing. I'm not showing
these people nothing. You know,
simple. I'm not showing these people no
money, bro. Because why would you show
these people money? They're only talking about
themselves. You don't need to show them nothing.
Do this little self-reflect. Why do you
need to show these little self-p
projecting little gay lord [ __ ] bully
victims anything, bro? Come
on. just shows that when they keep going
about money as well, how insecure they
are, like how they're very very insecure
because they keep asking people to show
their money over and over and over and
over and over again. And they're the
ones that keep bringing money into it.
Like I never talk about money ever,
ever. Cuz I know I've got money and
these people don't. So I don't need to
keep going on about money. That's how
insecure they want people to show their
money. But they want you to go out, show
their money so they can laugh and say,
"Haha, we made you show you we made you
show us money." And then they never show
you nothing. And then they just ask you
to show the same amount of money
again. Nope. I don't even know who that is.
So if I'm skinn, how can I go out all
the time drinking? How can I eat KFC
every day? Think about what you're
saying. I'm not showing you nothing. [Music] That's it.
I woke up I wake up with no woman and no
money. Bro, you wake up with me in your
head every single day. Imagine that. You
wake up in your head every single day, you little
virgin. Uh, let's see.
Yeah, there's no video of me though.
Yeah, I'm on the channel right now.
Yeah, you're not talking about
me. Let me
see. Okay, I've seen it now. Yeah, who
cares, bro? That's just immature.
Like nonslegs is
obsessed. He's on YouTube every single
[ __ ] day obsessed over me. So yeah,
I'd rather wake up with no woman and
skin, as you like to call it, than have
another man in my head every day. And
I'm not skin. I've got more money than
you would ever have. Go on my videos,
then go on your videos. You literally
had to withdraw all of your housing
benefit to make it seem like you got
money. Insecure little virgin. You ever
catch me ever doing that? No, bro. No,
bro. He's not trolling. He's not
trolling, bro. He's an obsessed little
virgin. He doesn't know how to troll. He
doesn't troll. All he does is be
obsessed every day talking about
himself. He's not trolling. He can't
troll to save his life. He's a little spacker.
Definitely definitely not
trolling. Definitely definitely definitely not
trolling in like why does he still do it
without anyone catching him? Because
when you go to his area, I'm not a
fighter. I'm running to the place and he
never meets anyone. So that's why people
just got fed up of going to his area. I
used to always go there and the little
[ __ ] would never come out and then when
he's miles and miles away from you, he
pretends that he's trying to meet you. Yeah, that's
why he doesn't troll anyone. He can't
troll to save his life. Him and his fat,
ugly girlfriend with special
needs. Didn't this guy say that he was
going to get the [ __ ] police on
people or something? Yeah. Where were they
then? He said he was going to get the
[ __ ] police on people. Oh
yeah. But yeah, when I go to Manchester,
I probably won't even stay over, bro.
I'll probably just go there for like the
whole day and then just come back to be
fair, bro. Just do them posters and then come
back. It's only like 50 quid to go there
back. Just rail card. I'll just bunk it.
Yeah, bro. I don't want to stay there
overnight. Nothing there, bro. Nothing there, is
there? Just going back to a hotel, bro.
By yourself. It's
pointless. Just going back to a hotel by
yourself. It's pointless, bro. I'll stay
in a hotel for like six, seven hours,
get some tails, go do some posters, and
head back to London. You know, good old
Good old London,
mate. Good old
London. All right, Harry, why don't you
comment on nons legs'
thing? You should comment saying you I
think it's in your best interest to come
off of YouTube. Your obsession with
Peter Benny is affecting your mental health.
Somebody should write something like
that and be funny cuz he's blocked me on
everything. The little virgin [Music]
Yeah. Wait, hold on. Let me see what
this [ __ ] is
saying. Um, need to link. Has anyone got
a link for that Twitter post with a
million subs? I need to send it to an
innocent future victims of a skin nose
big nose who I'm in contact with. You're
not speaking to anybody on Instagram,
you little virgin. You don't know anyone
that I speak to. You didn't even know
where they were from or what they look
like, you little virgin. Like, nobody
cares, bro. They don't even live in the
same city as me anyways. So, why don't
you spend more time [ __ ] your ugly
fat ugly girlfriend and lose your
virginity instead of coming online being
an obsessed little keyboard warrior,
which is what you
are, you know? You are the skinnest [ __ ]
ever. The skinnest [ __ ] ever, bro. I
swear to God. Do you know what's so
annoying with this little virgin is that
he would never ever say anything to
anyone's face. Like even with Timmy.
Yeah. Okay. Timmy's a [ __ ] Yeah. But
he's had some fights and he's lost. But
he still met up with people like I would
say I have as well. But with this little
virgin, right? He has never been in a
fight in his life. He will never meet
anyone. He will never ever say 1% of
what he does on YouTube when he's
obsessed every day when I'm living in
his head. You understand? It's it's it's
[ __ ] bro. Like even Timmyy's met up
for fights. You know what I'm
saying? You know what I'm
saying? Go one whole day without calling
people skin. That's good, bro. That's
good. You know, your lives are [ __ ]
bro. Your lives are empty. I mean,
bro, you insecure little
virgin. Yeah, big nose. You need to stop
that big nose thing. It's getting
really, really boring, mate. I'd rather
have a big nose than look like a [ __ ]
ugly skint rat like you. And I've said
this many many times. I'd rather be have
a big nose than look like a rat. Because
at least with my nose, like you can kind
of, you know, you look like a [ __ ]
rat. You look like a Down syndrome rat.
That's why you have to get with
vulnerable disabled girls cuz you're so
ugly. Cuz you're an ugly [ __ ] That's
the truth. That's not me being
triggered. That's telling you what you
are. That is literally literally telling
you what you are.
Yeah. You know what I'm
saying? Yeah. But the thing is there's
no point though, Harry, because all he
does is run to the police. All this
little virgin does, this little rat ugly
face bastard is go to the police every
single time you do. And I'm not wasting
money on this virgin. He can be obsessed
all he wants. I'm living in his head. I
don't need to do anything.
I've done all of this before, done
posters, and then he he went to the
police. Oh, I'm not a fighter. I'm not a
fighter. Run into that place. We've all
seen it. We've all seen me having him
shaking and shivering when I've gone to
his area. I'm not a fighter. Where's
that place? So, what's the point, bro?
There's no point even going to this
little virgin's area. It's like you,
bro. You if you came on my door Yeah.
three times. And I didn't come out three
times, bro. I started running to the
police. Are you going to come back on my
door? You're not, are you? You
know, and the only skint one is this
little rat face showing these little
benefits off where we all know that he
is living in poverty. Think about it.
Listen, listen, listen to me, Harry.
Yeah. Look at all of my designer
designer gars. Class them as assets.
What does this little virgin have? He's
on a grand a month and he's got a fat
ugly girlfriend. That's literally all he
has to his name. Think about it, bro.
Think about it. Class them as assets.
Yeah. That whole [ __ ] wardrobe. Come
on. Yeah. This little virgin has got
nothing but a fat ugly girlfriend and a
grand a month to his name. Think about
it. A grand a month. A grand a month.
There's been there's been times where
I've spent 600 700 pound on a [ __ ]
night out. A grand a month, bro. Imagine
that. Imagine that, bro. A grand a
month. This little virgin, this little
ratfaced ugly [ __ ] with a fat ugly
girlfriend is on a grand a month and
he's trying to call other people's skin.
Really, bro? Come on. Come on. Yeah.
It's it's it's embarrassing now. It
really really really really is
embarrassing. You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, you haven't spoke to anyone. You
don't know who I've spoken to and you
know. Yeah. So, stop talking [ __ ] you little
virgin. You obsessed little
virgin. Bye-bye now. Bye-bye now,
virgin. He's such an insecure little
virgin. Oh my god. Like how many how
many women does the does does he do this
with? Yeah. How many women does this guy
try to stalk? It goes to show that he's
such a little virgin. Like when he does
all of these things. Yeah. It goes to
show how much of a virgin he really
really is. And he has got erectile
dysfunction. You know, he's never stuck
his dick up nothing in his life. Think
about it. He's the one with the fat ugly
girlfriend on £1,000 a month. Not me.
I'm on no [ __ ] £1,000 a month, bro.
Do you think I'm on some proxy £1,000 a
month like that little ratfaced virgin?
Have you ever heard of a thing called
[ __ ] housing benefit,
bro? Have you ever heard of a thing called housing benefit? No. No. You're
obsessed. You are [ __ ]
obsessed. You really, really obsessed.
You need to get laid. You need to lose
your virginity, you sad little virgin.
No wonder your mommy starved you and her
boyfriend slapped you up, you little
[ __ ] How the [ __ ] can you come on
YouTube after being starved by your mom,
almost starved to death, right? Coming
on YouTube like you're some kind of big
man, bro. We've all seen you getting
strangled by your mom's boyfriend. He he
had you up against the [ __ ] wall,
mate, and you weren't saying nothing.
And then you're trying to say how, oh,
the police was called on me 22
times, you little
virgin. You know what I'm saying? Well,
guess what? But here's the thing. Here's
the thing, though. Ding. You don't even show up
anywhere. Anyways, I thought you was
messaging me on Facebook, Jill. I
thought you was messaging me on
Facebook. I thought you was messaging me on Facebook. Oh
yeah. Oh, but
anyways, turning on my family. Oh,
really? Whoa. I mean, you can make a Snapchat, can't
you? I mean, you can make a Snapchat, can't you?
Yeah, I'm unstable now, man. I'm very, very, very
stable. Sean, do you even if you are
speaking to this woman from Manchester,
you do realize there's two things. A,
she's done all of this [ __ ] before you
contacted her. And C, tell her that I'm
going Manchester next week. Anyways,
look how obsessed this little virgin is
with my life. I live in his
head. Like, I live in his head, bro. Go
on his channel. Yeah. go on this wrong
in media channel. Every single post is
about me. He's obsessed with me. Why is
this ratfaced [ __ ] so obsessed with me?
I don't want you. Like, I don't want
nothing to do with you. You know how
your mom starved you to death almost and
she abandoned you. I don't want you
either. Like, your mom didn't want you.
Why do you keep making community posts?
I don't want you like your [ __ ] mom
that starved you never wanted you. You little virgin.
Virgin boy, I don't want nothing to do
with you. Why do you keep making
community posts? You're never going to
say nothing to my face. You lanky string
of piss with the fat ugly girlfriend.
You're never going to say nothing to my
face. You are your fat ugly girlfriend.
So why do you keep coming on here every
day with your no teeth, ugly rat face,
double chinned, [ __ ] ugly, greasy
hair coming on here every day when
you're never going to say nothing to
anyone's face. You are your fat, ugly
girlfriend. Before you keep saying,
"Yeah, people are triggered. Do you want
me to link your channel to everybody on
here now? I live in your head rentree of
charge, virgin boy. Just like when your
mom starved you." Yeah. Your mom starved
you to death. Yeah. And it and and and
it stays with you. Yeah. I live in your
head, virgin boy. Yeah. We can all see
in your comments. Yeah. You can stalk
all of my all of these women again. No
one cares. It just goes to show that
you're just this virgin who's never been
laid. Your fat ugly girlfriend. Your fat
ugly girlfriend don't give you no sex
cuz you're an ugly [ __ ] Truth be told,
she's probably cheating on you, mate.
You who what woman would want some lanky
string of piss, no money on a grand a
month, no [ __ ] shitty clothes, no
teeth. Who would want a [ __ ] skin
[ __ ] in Kent? Who would want some skin
version from Kent? Answer me that
question. Answer me that question. Oh,
because these people are because these
people are stalkers. That's why. Because
these people are stalkers. That's why.
Yeah. Yeah. Good for you, bro. No one
cares. I'm going to Manchester next week
anyways. Virgin, you know. Yeah. Good,
bro. I'll tell everyone on Instagram. No
one cares. Go and message her. Who gives
[ __ ] Nobody cares. You're obsessed. No,
it wasn't him who ruined it. She done
all of this before this. No, it wasn't.
wasn't. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Mate, listen.
No, it wasn't him who ruined it. He
didn't ruin nothing. The little [ __ ]
virgin with a fat ugly girlfriend. You
know, you found her post that got over.
That's how you found it. Yes, because
she told you that virgin. Yes, because
she told you that. Anyways, get a life,
you [ __ ] little weirdo. Go lose your
virginity. Get laid, virgin. If if you
actually got laid and you weren't such a
[ __ ] virgin, you little creepy little
skint [ __ ] on benefits a month, it
wouldn't bother you. It wouldn't bother
you. Yeah. Go lose your virginity, you
[ __ ] little virgin. Go get starved by
your mama again. You and your fat ugly
girlfriend. Guess what though? All of
this stuff you do online, you can never
say it to my face. I can say it to you
and your fat ugly girlfriend. Isn't that
mad? I can say it to you and your fat
ugly dowy girlfriend. Keep dreaming of
Morgan. You will never have Morgan. You
will never have Britney. You will only
have the big fat ugly girlfriend that
don't give you no sex. And I love it.
This is why I love Izzy and Morgan in
your head because you're a little virgin
with erectile dysfunction that got
starved by his mama who got starved by
his mama and he's still a virgin on a
grand a month. Hey, don't let me tell
you how much money I get a month. I
don't want to make you even more
jealous. I've already got my sloppy
seconds. Living in your head, rent free,
son. Living in your head, rent free. You
know what I'm saying? I don't want to
make you any more jealous. Listen, you
you your little money video is
so Yeah, she has PTSD and mental health.
Oh, I do. You know why she said that? I
can tell you why she said Why do you
think she said that? Keep bullying him,
Fruit King. We've gone to your area and
you didn't show up. Yeah, we went to
your area and you didn't show up. You
people don't bully no one. I bully you
every day when I'm in your head. When
I'm living in your head doing hoo, I'm
bullying you. When I'm in your head
every day and I can't get out of it, I'm
bullying you without even doing
anything. Yeah. And anyways, um she told
you that she had PTSD and mental health.
She never said that to me. I've got all
the messages. I've got all the messages.
And yeah, she would tell you she's got
mental health cuz she got caught
out. Never told me she had mental
health. Yeah, she's saying that to play
the victim. Dumbo, when did you when did
you start talking to this person? Oh,
let me ask you this question. When did
you start talking to this
person? When did you start talking to this person
anyways? Yeah, she would tell you she's
got mental health. That's what they all
do. Yeah, that's what they all do, lad. Yeah. Bye-bye,
Sean. Anyways. Yeah. Yeah. You should
have saw what [ __ ] thing he was
[ __ ] telling LT. Mr. [ __ ]
B. Vulnerable women. Sean, listen. You
are literally the one who's with a fat,
ugly, disabled girlfriend. Your
girlfriend is fat, ugly, and disabled.
You are on a grand a month. You are the only skint
one. You are the only skint one. No one
else, mate. No, you're not coming on my
channel. [ __ ] off. If you've got
anything to put up, you can put up on your
channel. He's in He's in the same That
[ __ ] virgin ain't nowhere near me.
That [ __ ] virgin don't live in
London. He's a Kent [ __ ] He's a Kent
virgin. He's nothing to do with London.
He's nothing to do with London. I'd
rather have a big nose than be a [ __ ]
rat looking [ __ ] like you with no money
on a grand a month. I'd rather have a
big nose than look like a [ __ ] lanky
rat with no teeth obsessed with people's
sloppy seconds. I'll take the big nose
rather than a rat face like you. Have
you seen your face? No, it's not
Southeast London. You're from Kent,
Virgin. Do you want me to put it back up
again? You're not from Southeast. You're
from Kent. You don't even sound like
you're from London. Stop begging it.
You're not from London. You're not from
London. And your [ __ ] nons ugly dad
baldy [ __ ] ain't from London [ __ ] So
stop saying oh self East London you are
no part of London. You are your [ __ ]
non dad. Understand rat boy ratfaced
benefit boy on a grand a month. Grand a
month boy living in poverty with no bed.
Do you understand that Brmley and Orton
is Kent virgin? It I'm Essex. I'm Essex.
Okay. Okay. So, I live in London and
I've been in London 26 years of my life,
but I'm not from London. You are a
little Kent virgin. You have lived in
Orington since we have known each other.
You are not no part of [ __ ] London,
virgin boy. Yeah, you're calling me a
[ __ ] boy. Really? Really? Was I a [ __ ]
when I was in your area and I made you
say, "I'm not a fighter. I'm running to
the place. I'm not a fighter. I'm not a
fighter." Was I Was I a [ __ ] then?
Sh was I like Was I a [ __ ] when I was
in your [ __ ] virgin Little India area
with a shitty fish and chip shop, you
little virgin [ __ ] and you didn't come
out? Was I a [ __ ] when I was in your
area? Was I was Was was I a [ __ ] when I
was in your area talking about your
[ __ ] ugly fat girlfriend and you
wouldn't come out? You [ __ ] little
Ken virgin on the ground among you
little [ __ ] Anyways, why why don't you
tell us why you didn't come out when I
was in your area three
times? Why don't you tell us? Why don't
you tell us why you did not come out
when I was in your area three
times? Huh? When I was in your area
three times, why didn't you come
out? You little [ __ ] virgin. I was
going to smash your ugly rat face. You
and your fat ugly
girlfriend. You You and your fat ugly
girlfriend. I'm gonna slap you up. You
ain't your fat ugly disabled girlfriend.
He can't tilt sack. Ruined nonse has
ruined PJ's life. Okay, I've got more
money than him. I get more money than
him. I'm better looking than him. And
I've literally literally never ever ever
resorted to dating disabled women. And
I've actually got a bed. And I've
bed. And I've actually got a bed.
This guy has literally never ruined my
life. What? Because he's speaking to
somebody in Manchester that ghosted me.
I don't live in Manchester. I can go out
and get another woman. You can't nonsex
cuz you got autism. You can't get a
normal woman because you are autistic.
You're diagnosed autistic. You can't
even function in a normal relationship,
in a normal environment, because you're
autistic. Bro, remember that time I went
out and I got nine [ __ ] numbers? I
could literally go out today and get
numbers if I wanted to. You know what
I'm saying? I'm not autistic like you. I
don't need to pray on the vulnerable.
Yeah, bro. You can you can message
someone in Manchester. I don't really
give a [ __ ] to be honest with you. They
done what they done anyways. But guess
what? It's not a big deal to people like
me because I don't have such bad autism
where I can't go out and get some more
numbers, get some more Instagrams. You
are an insecure diagnosed autistic
horrible little virgin. You don't love
Sarah. She You You're just with her
because you can't get nothing else.
Think about it. You've been with her 3
years and you're still a virgin. Does
that sound like love to you, lad? Does
that sound like love to you? You're
literally still a virgin. You've got
erectile dysfunction. This is why you
can't get Izzy and Morgan out your head
because your autism doesn't accept the
fact that other men can get what you
can't get. And that's why you do all of
these things. Like, he didn't sleep with
her. He didn't [ __ ] her because you're a
virgin. You have never [ __ ] You can't
get a normal woman. I'm having to say
this in this way so you understand this.
You are diagnosed autistic. You have
been starved by your mom and your mom's
boyfriend was called Philillip Campbell
of Leeds. Philip Campbell of Leeds. And
he slapped you up. And he slapped the
[ __ ] out of you. You weren't out to like
a big man when your [ __ ] mom mom's
boyfriend [ __ ] strangled you to death
and lied about how you got [ __ ] you
you got [ __ ] uh what was it? Arrested
22 times. You You want to talk to me?
You You really want to talk to me? Come
and meet me today. You want to meet me?
Come and meet me today. You want to meet
me, do you, Virgin? Bring you and your
[ __ ] fat ugly girlfriend with you.
I'm in a mood. I'm in a [ __ ] mood.
Come on, son. Bring that fat ugly
girlfriend with you up. I'm I'm talking
about your woman. You You You really
want to talk to me? Come and meet me
today. Come and meet me today. Okay, I'm
going to put my trousers on, right? And
I want to meet you today. Come on, you
little virgin. Bring your fat ugly
girlfriend as well. I'm going to [ __ ]
you both up. You ain't that fat ugly
girlfriend. And bring your disabled dad
as well. Bring your [ __ ] disabled dad
as well, you silly little [ __ ]
And you know, bring your [ __ ] ugly
dad as well. Your [ __ ] nuts dad and
your fat ugly girlfriend. Bring them as
well. Come on. I'll meet you. I'll meet
you. Come on. I'll meet you. Let's meet.
Let's meet. Come on. Come on. Come on,
son. Come on, mate. Come on. Come on.
No. Come on. I'll beat you up so much
that you're not an ugly [ __ ]
anymore. I will slap the ugliness out of
you. You won't no longer have that rat
face. Oh, one second. Hold on. Let me
Let me One second. Hold on. I need to be
a bit respectful here. Be a bit
respectable here. Sorry.
Sorry. Just give me a moment, please. Thank
you. One second, please. Hold on. Hold
I go for disabled people.
Sh. Come on now. This is ridiculous now.
Sh. What the [ __ ] Look at the state of
that fat ugly girlfriend. What? You're
taking a piss, bro. That ain't a woman.
That's a man. That's not a woman. That's a [ __ ]
man, you know. And this is why he's so
obsessed with Morgan. And is he? Cuz
he's with a fat ugly girlfriend. They
don't give him no sex. And he looks like
a little rat. Oh my god. This is why
you're so obsessed with Morgan. Morgan
and Izzy. Because I slept with him and
you never You're still a virgin. And
you're autism. Don't let you go out and
meet normal women. Cuz you're too
autistic. Ah, cuz you're too autistic.
You're too autistic to get normal women.
That's why you're jealous of Peter Belly
and you're still a [ __ ] virgin, mate.
Honestly. Yeah. I can take the big nose.
That's funny to me. I can go over
everything with you though. Double
chinned, can't grow a beard, ugly,
lanky, balding, greasy hair, no teeth,
mummy starving, autistic, virgin. The
list is endless, lad. Like, honestly,
the list is [ __ ] endless. What I can
say to you, I'd rather have a big nose
than have a big fat ugly rat face that
scare all the women away because I'm
such an ugly [ __ ] like that's not
autism, mate. I'm not all. You're
saying, mate, you're the one that's been diagnosed with
autism. You're [ __ ] You're the one
that's being diagnosed with autistic.
You're the one that's being You're the
one that's diagnosed with autism, not
me. Not me,
lad. So, you're trying to say that this
person has got mental health. And what
mental health do they
have? Yeah. Slowly, I mate, I'd rather
have a big nose than have a [ __ ] big
ugly rat face like you, you predator.
You predator a little nons. You're
talking about a big nose, mate. If if
big nose was only one was only your
problem, mate. I'm better looking than
you will ever be. That's why you can't
get the women that I've got. That's why
you're jealous of all the women that I
get with cuz you're too ugly and
autistic yourself to get anything. Yeah.
I don't want to let him on. I want to
meet him face to face. I want to meet
him face to face because I because what
he's trying to do, Australian Dave, is
he's trying to get attention on my
channel. If you want to meet me today, I
will meet you
anywhere. Anywhere you want, son. Yeah.
Simple. That's it, bro.
One second. Hold on. Hold on.
Sorry about that. You want to meet me?
You want to meet me Brmley South
Station? Okay. Okay. Go to Brmley South
Station and stay live for 1 hour. Okay.
Okay. Okay. I'll meet you at Brmley
South Station, but you have to stay live
for 1 hour. Okay. Good. Good. Good.
Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Yep. and
we will see if this virgin actually is
trying to meet someone. He says that he
wants to meet me. Okay, go to Brmley
Station and go live for 1 hour. So, we
know that this little virgin don't try
to run home. See, this is what he does.
He will go live for 5 minutes then run
back home. I know this little virgin's
tricks. You want to meet me? You You're
going to be in Brmley. Okay, stay alive
then. Stay alive then, you little
virgin. Stay alive, you little virgin.
Go on. Go on. You have to stay alive for
1 hour. Exactly. You've got no desire of
meeting me, but you're obsessed with me
every day and you won't leave me alone.
I live in your head. I bully you every
day, but you don't want to meet me. But
should we should we put this channel
back up? Right. Let's go on this
channel. Let's go on this wronging
channel. Let's go on this wrong wronging
media channel from this little virgin. Okay.
Community post, community post,
community post, community post,
community post, community post. You've
got a whole channel dedicated to me, you
little ratfaced, ugly, no teeth bastard.
But you won't meet me. Shame on you,
bro. You're the only one that looks bad.
I'm skin. Okay, bro. I'm skinn. Yeah,
I've shown more money than you. I've got
a bed. You're the one with no bed, no
teeth. You're the one on benefits, not
me. You're the one. Yeah, exactly.
That's ex No, no, no. Listen, listen,
listen, listen. I'm skin sh I have more
money than you will ever have. You have
no assets. You are skin. You got no bed.
You got no money. That money that you
showed the other day was your housing
benefit, your shitty little benefits
that you have to pay for your rent.
You've got no money. You've literally
got no money. You're skint. You shop at
the charity shop. You have no money. Why
do you go on like you've got money? You
literally have not a pot to piss in. How
long have you lived in that [ __ ]
Orington virgin bedsit and there's never
been a bed? There's never ever ever ever
ever been a bed. Yeah, I know, bro. I
love it. But you got no money. I will
always have more money than you. More
money, more women, better looks, better
food. I will always be better than you.
And that's why I live in your
head. Yeah. I'd rather be a big nose
than be a skin ugly little rat with a
fat ugly girlfriend. Skinn little rat
face like you. I'd rather have a skin
big nose than be a skinn little rat [ __ ]
that can't say nothing to anyone's face
like you. You little [ __ ] You know, at
least that's more than one. You little
skint rat with a fat ugly girlfriend.
See, look. I'm saying all this stuff to
you, but you won't say nothing to me.
You won't meet me. You won't meet me.
You will just stay a virgin on your
little grind a month from benefits.
£1,000 a month tops. That's what you
get. You get £1,000 a month's tops. No
bed on benefits. Ugly fat woman. Bro,
you're embarrassing yourself now. You
really, really, really, really are
embarrassing yourself. You really,
really, really are embarrassing
yourself. You will never know where I
am. And that's what I mean with these
people in Ali. They don't want to meet
you. They just want to argue with you
every single day. What's
up? There it
is. What do you think of Sean's looks,
Natalie? See, they they they want to be
a keyboard warrior every day on YouTube.
They want to be a keyboard warrior every day on
YouTube. Yeah, they messaged her, but
they messaged her after she had already
blocked me. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Listen, they blocked me. She They done
it after she had already blocked me.
Don't back out. What do you mean don't
back out? I've gone to his area three
times. I've literally tried to arrange a
fight and he's saying that he's not
meeting me. This is exactly what I mean.
It's the same It's the same atmosphere.
It was the girl's fault all along
because they only messaged her after
this. They messaged her after this. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, bro.
They messaged her after she had already
done this. It was her fault. It was her
fault. Yeah. Because she was still
texting. If if it was these people on
YouTube, she would have blocked you on
everything and not even wrote back to
you. No, no, no, no, no. It was these
people. It was definitely these people.
She It was definitely her. Sorry. No,
no. It was definitely hurt because if it
was these people, bro, think about it.
If it was these people, I will be there
if he goes live. Yeah, Brmley 6 p.m.
Yeah, go live. Go live in Brmley at 6
p.m. Stay live for an hour maximum and I
will be there. I will be there. Simple.
I will be there. And if you're not going
to go live for 1 hour, it's because
you're not trying to meet anyone. You
just want to be a little keyboard
warrior all your life. Yep. Romney 6
p.m. Go live and stay live. So everybody
knows when this little virgin doesn't do
it, he's not trying to meet anyone. Like
here's the thing with you people. Like
you have to be taking a piss. Like you
know that he will never meet no one.
We've all seen me go to the Virgin area
three times. I'm not a fighter. I'm not
a fighter. I'm not a fighter. But again,
you've got selective memory just like
Arsenal Mark. Yeah. Just like the
Arsenal Mark thing.
So, yeah, you have to go at 6 p.m. I I
said if he goes live there at 6 p.m., I
will go there. Okay. I will go there. I
there. Yeah. If you're that Bobby, he's
mugged you off. Okay. End the
conversation. I know what you're trying
to do. It's not going to
work. It's not going to work. Yeah, bro. Sorry,
bro. When he goes live in Brmley, I will
I will I will go there. I will go there.
End of story. Anyways, end of story. I'm
not talking about this no more cuz
you're not going to get what you want.
Anyways, end of story. I'm not playing
little keyboard warrior games. You go
live in Brmley and I will be there. You
go live in Brmley Station and I will be
there. End of. That's the That's the
deal. That's the [ __ ]
deal. Well, I'm telling you that is the
agreement, you little virgin. Because
otherwise, what's going to happen?
Because what's going to happen,
Greavves, is you're going to go there
and he's going to be like, I'm not a
fighter. I've got no intention of
beating you. I know this little Orington
virgin rat and I know what he does. I
know what this little Orington virgin
rat does. You know, uh, that's Sean's m
girlfriend. That's his fat, ugly
girlfriend, which explains why he's so
obsessed with Morgan. And is he? Because
he's never had such women, you know. Why
don't I go at 6 p.m.? Uh, Jill, it's not
going to work. Remove yourself from my
channel. I'm not Monty Man and I'm not
Timmy. Stop doing it on my channel.
Yeah. Again, stop trying to
underestimate my intelligence. You go
live Brmley Station for one hour and
I'll be there. We're not playing these
silly little games. I'm not playing
these silly little keyboard warrior
games. You go Brmley, you go live, and
you stay live. End of job done. You're
about 10 minutes away from there. Yeah.
You I'm not playing these silly little
keyboard warrior reaction games. I'm not
doing it. Yeah. You go live for 1 hour,
you stay live, and see what happens to
you. End of. Done. Not talking about it no more.
Simple. Absolutely simple.
Done. These people want you to travel,
bro, like all that way and not meet you.
That's why I'm asking you to go live and stay
live. You know, no one's getting
triggered. No one's getting triggered.
The virgin is not coming on my channel.
Get it through your head. This little
virgin is not coming on my channel. Get
that through your [ __ ] head until he
meets me. him and his fat ugly
girlfriend and he's got something to say
to my my face. He's not coming on my
channel. I'm not letting this toothless
little virgin coward prick on my channel
until he meets me. [ __ ] stop asking
it. Simple. You meet me, right? Yeah. He
didn't make me lose another
relationship. He didn't make me lose
another relationship. And he's never
made me lose a relationship ever. You
know, I've had more women than him. I
will always have more women than him. I
slept with Morgan. He never I slept with
his he never and he's jealous. He never
ruined no relationship. No relationship
on anyone's. Yeah. So anyways, you go
live in Brmley. Why won't you go live in
Brmley then? If you're trying to meet
someone, if you're trying to meet
someone, why won't you go live? It's
because you want to go live for 5
minutes and run away and say, "I'm not a
fighter. I'm running to the place." How
do I know exactly what you do, Virgin
Boy? How do I know exactly what you're
about, virgin ratfaced bastard? Because
we know that if you was actually trying
to meet someone, you wouldn't have ran
to the police when I was in your area
three times screaming you weren't a
fighter. Go live in Brmley and stay
live. That's the arrangement. End off.
And we will see if this little clown
does it. And if he doesn't do it, we all
know the reason why he won't do it
because he's not trying to meet anyone.
He's not trying to meet anyone. Go live
in Brmley and stay live for 1
hour. Simple. If you're really trying to
meet someone, you would do it. But
you're not trying to meet anyone though,
are you? You're just trying to be a
little keyboard warrior, little virgin
with your rat face, sticking your
[ __ ] ugly nose with your fat, ugly
disabled girlfriend. I've spoke about
your girlfriend today. I've spoke about
your dad today. I've spoke about every
your life today, brother. And you still
won't meet me. You still will never meet
me. You still will never meet me. That's
the maddest thing about
it. That's the maddest thing. Yeah. I'd
rather have no misses than have a
[ __ ] disabled girlfriend like that.
I'd rather have none. Yeah. Yeah. Tiger
ruined me. Um, actually I actually
defeated Tiger and Tiger will actually
tell you that himself. Tiger didn't ruin
no one. Stop repeating yourself. Yeah, I
slipped. Again, let me repeat myself to
you little mongos. Right. I slipped and
as soon as I got back up, I smashed him.
Yeah, I smashed him in his face. I lost
another relationship because of YouTube.
I've never lost a relationship because
of YouTube. And Tiger will actually tell
you. Tiger would actually tell you that
I'd done him. Tiger would tell you
himself that I done him. He even sent it
to Money Mike. So, stop talking [ __ ]
And no, there's not another relationship
because YouTube has never cost me a
relationship. Uh, no, he didn't. Bye-bye
now. You know, this is what I mean. This
is why I don't come on here much
anymore. It's the same atmosphere. It's
the same atmosphere every day. Same
[ __ ] same repeating people. But I
didn't lose no, there was never another
relationship to be lost because I've
never lost a relationship over YouTube
ever. All the people that these people
know about was one night stands. I've
never lost a relationship over YouTube.
Never, ever, ever. All of the women I've
met, I've literally got what I wanted
from them. I've never lost a
relationship from you because of
YouTube. I've never lost any money from
YouTube. I've never lost nothing from
YouTube. So, get your facts right, bro. Yeah.
Like I said, I didn't go out yesterday
cuz I can't be bothered. See, the thing
is with this little virgin, right? Let
me explain it to you. Let me explain it
to you. Let me explain it to you, bro.
Yeah. So, this person from Manchester.
Yeah. Someone that lives in Manchester.
But these people don't realize that I
could go out every day, Thursday,
Friday, Saturday, and just meet someone
else and just go this person, that
person. There's 9 million people in
London, but these people don't
understand it's because they're virgins.
They've got autism. They've got no life.
So, it's everything to them. So, people
like Shan, it's everything to them
because their autism don't let them go
out and socialize. Doesn't let them
function in in in normal environments.
You know, I can go to a shopping center
right now if I wanted to and get a
woman's number. Two women's number if I wanted
to. Yeah. Yeah. Of course. Anyways, put
it up on your channel, Sean. Put it up
on your channel. You're not coming on it
until you meet me. I don't care about
this irrelevant person. No one cares.
It's everything to you because you're
you ain't got a life. Oh my god. Listen,
do you know how many people I met last
week? No one cares. You
know, so that's it. Nodd legs. Come and
meet me, bro. And then that's it. No one
cares. Do you see how this is everything
to you? Like it's nothing to me. The
thing is it's nothing to me cuz I would
just go out and meet someone else if I
wanted to. Argument sake. It doesn't
bother me. No. Put it on your channel.
Go live and put it on your channel. Go
live on your channel and put it up on
your channel. You've got an You've got a
channel obsessing over me. You've got a
channel obsessing over me, you little
rat face, little skinn virgin. So go put
on that channel, you little rat face.
Simple. You don't need to come on my
channel. You got your You got a whole
channel obsessed with me, man. like just
put it up on your channel, you
know? Yeah. And it wasn't Yeah. It
wasn't him, bro. It wasn't him. It
wasn't him. You wish you wish you you
know you wish you wish you ruined a
relationship between me and someone. You
[ __ ] never. And they don't even live
in London. And I don't even live in
London either. Yeah. They don't even
live in London. So what, bro? Do you
think I give a [ __ ] about one person
that don't even It's everything to you,
Sean, because you can't
approach. You can't go out and meet
normal women. This is why it is
everything to you. But it's nothing to
me. This is what I'm trying to say. I
don't care. You know, I haven't even met
this person. You know, they don't even
live in London. You're obsessed. You
want some more Instagram contacts, you
little weirdo. And it wasn't someone
else on YouTube at all. So, anyways, I'm
done. Carry on. obsessing over PJs.
Um, yeah, sloppy seconds. They basically
are my [ __ ] sloppy seconds, aren't
they? So, yeah, you're obsessed. And
this is how you know, people, people
who's watching this now, this is a prime
example how you know that Sha's
girlfriend is disabled. Because what
normal woman would let their partner
start messaging random women all cuz
they're insecure and jealous? You really
think a normal woman would sit back and
allow that? Nah, bro. You got to be
disabled to. You know what I'm saying?
You have to be disabled
to. And that's
it. And that's and that's honestly it,
bro. Like, you're you're obsessed. I
love it. You're obsessed. You know,
sometimes I feel like just going out and
approaching women just to piss you off
cuz I know that your anxiety will never
be able to do it. Like, sometimes I feel
like doing it just to annoy you. You
know what I'm saying? Like, you know,
you know, one of them days like just
just to piss you off. No, I'm just going
to go for a KFC,
man. Bye-bye now. Nah, I'm going to go
for a KFC. Don't fancy a roast today. I
actually just fancy KFC. And I'm not
broke. I'll never be broke. That's the
joys of you not knowing how much people
have. You go on here every day talking
about people you don't even know,
brother. It's funny. You don't know how
much money people have, how much money
people don't have. You don't know
nothing. You only know about your own lives, you
know, and that's
it. Oh, he's waiting for me at the end
of the street. Oh, are they? Oh, are
they really? Oh. Oh, well that's not
possible because no one knows where I
live. So, I mean, that's not possible at
all, really, is it? Because A, they
don't know where I live and B, it's not
possible. Oh, I thought you was banging
on someone's door. Has it changed all of a sudden
now? Oh, has it changed all of a sudden
to banging on someone's door than um
than them waiting at the end of the road
for you? Oh, really? Bless
you. A bless you. You really are some
sad bastards, aren't
you? Oh, bless you. You really think
that anything you do is going to make anyone
scared? You actually really think
anything you do is going to make anybody
scared? Trying to feel bad, but I ain't
going to lie to
you. I ain't going to lie to you, man.
But LJ said no, he's just waiting. Oh,
is he just waiting? Is he? Oh, that's
nice, bro. But he'll be having a long
wait then cuz I'm saying like people
like you need to grow
up. I'd say you need to grow
up. When are you going to start growing
up? Considering like you people are like
a lot older than me. When are you really
really going to start like thinking
right and madness I need to start I need to grow
up. Do you say you Yeah, I'm going to
KFC. Not right now. When are you really
really going to grow up? When are you
going to grow up, man? It's boring now.
Boring. Come on, man. Like it's so
boring. Like the [ __ ] you people do
every day. Like you you kill the community.
You honestly kill the community. It's
boring. It is actually
boring. Get a kettle one, bro. Like, I'm
not scared of no one. Look at my thing.
My My finger is not even moving, bro.
You don't bother me. No one on this
bastard community bothers me. It's just [ __ ]
repeaters. So, yeah. Remember LJ said he
was going to
call Yeah. Yeah. He ain't coming to no
one's, bro. He doesn't even know where I
live. So, how where is he going if he
doesn't even know where I
live? Anyways, yeah, Sean, you're
really, really obsessed, man. You really
need to lose your virginity, you insecure little
virgin. And let's just say Charlie,
right, for argument sake that these
people in here [ __ ] this up for you,
which they never. I promise you they
never. Let's just say for argument sake,
right? So you was going to go to
Manchester. Yeah. And they [ __ ] it up
for you. For example, as an example,
bro, you can just go out and meet
someone else. You live in London. You
can go out and get numbers and message
other people. Other people
else. Do you know what I'm trying to say
to you, bro? Like even though they never
[ __ ] it up, nowhere near [ __ ] up.
But I'm saying, let's just say that was
actually the case or it was one person
from London. Yeah, it is a madness, but
it's never happened to me. Never
happened to me. Yep. It is a madness,
but it's never happened to me and it
will never happen to me. So
yeah, it's never happened to me and it
will never happen to me.
So, well, she's the one she's the one
that blocked me. It was nothing to do with
YouTube. It was nothing to do with
anyways. Someone you was going to marry
later on. I don't think so. Cuz if it
was somebody from YouTube, they would
have just blocked you everywhere and
wouldn't have messaged you back. Nothing
to do with YouTube. So, anyways, I don't
care. Like, I don't care about this
person. I don't know why we keep talking
about it as well. [ __ ] obsessed.
Let's get a
life. What post have I am I putting up
that she's a nons? That she's a
pedophile. That she touched my
kids. That she's a pedophile. She
touched up my kids. time
already. Just because she didn't want to
meet you, bro. This is not Monty Man or
Timmy's channel. I have to keep telling
you this. This is not Monty Man's or
Timmy's channel. Take it elsewhere. Take
your little weirdo trolling attempts
elsewhere cuz you're not going to get a
reaction on this channel. Yeah, take it
elsewhere. Like, take it elsewhere, bro.
Money will go live soon. Timmy will go
live soon. Like, you're not good at
trolling. You suck at it. So stop trying
to do it.
Yeah. [ __ ] white knight. So many
white knights. So many white
knights. Spray. Spray it. Yes. So
yeah, literally what he is, bro.
Literally what he is. And then when I
told him to go live in Brmley, he won't
do that somehow. Huh. Funny, isn't it?
Funny how he won't go live in these
places that he wants to meet
people. Oh my god. How many times is
this keyboard warrior going to be doing this for?
Yeah, that's literally what he is.
Lanky, autistic string of
piss. [ __ ] hell. But what makes me
laugh is how they try to say that they
they [ __ ] with you
psychologically, but you live in their
head. Like, think about it. They think
of you every day. They've got a channel
dedicated to you. They post about you
every day. So, who's the one that's
being [ __ ] with psychologically? These
people. If you think about it, it's these
people. Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that's why you never meet. That's
why you never Well, no, but to but to be
fair, Tmy's not that bad and Timmy's got
autism. No, Timmy's got autism and he's
his autism isn't as bad as that. That is
proper proper damn bad autism. That is
I've never met somebody in my life with
such autism. You
know, they think that they own you. They
try to ruin any relationship that you
get into. I don't know if it's jealousy
or obsession. Maybe a bit of
both. Really, really bad autism though.
He gets obsessed with people that he
doesn't even know. This [ __ ] met me when
I was a kid, when I was a child. I
wasn't even an adult. And he's still
obsessed. And this virgin is still
obsessed. He is still
obsessed. Yeah. Yeah. He gets obsessed
with people that don't [ __ ] want him,
you know? [ __ ] hell. He's obsessed
with like his mom don't want him.
Britney don't want him. And I don't want
him. And he's still
obsessed. And he's still obsessed, lad. Still
obsessed. Yeah, but that one in
Manchester seemed cool, but she turned
out to be a [ __ ] anyways, so
You should all join me, man. Gets more
pushing. Jimmy has more money than you.
You are way below them.
Ah. Uh, you really really are boring,
bro. Money gets more pushed than me.
Timmy has more money than you.
Yeah. Uh, really? Good for you then.
These people really really are boring, isn't it? Yeah. Oh
boy. They think they know how much money
people have. It's so
funny. I will never show these people money ever
again. I will never ever show these
people money again because the only
people that do that are skin insecure
people. Now, the reason I used to do it
when I used to get money from the casino
is cuz they used to pay me in cash. But
now all my money's in my bank and it's
like, well, why do I need to show any of
these Skindle virgins money when they're
the ones that are insecure? That means
taking labor out of my time to show a
bunch of skimp people money that ain't
got money. I'd rather not. Thanks.
That's not what this channel's about.
And and the thing is, they will say, "Oh, you're
skint." And then you go out into central
London spending hundreds on drinking and
then they just make themsel look like a
tit where they try to reverse the
psycholog where they try to trology you know
like they want you to show them money
because they don't have money so they
want to know what money looks like cuz
these people are skint you
see see what I
mean or should I go God knows
H. Yeah, I would give it a Well,
Yeah. Greasy. Show money or skin. Show
money or skin. Show money or skin.
Show money or skin. Show money or
skin. But that in that uh in that
Twitter thing didn't go
around cuz my friend never saw it and
loads of other people never saw it. So I
wonder who them million people were. It
must have been people in different
countries. Yeah. I never show these
people money ever. ever again, mate.
They can say that I don't have money.
They can say whatever, bro. I don't
care. I'm never showing these people
money ever again. And I think I'm in my
right to do that, uh, Greasy, because
whenever I used to show these people
money, they would never show me nothing.
So, I don't bother no more. I don't show
them nothing. I've actually got some
money right there actually in cash. Not
show them nothing. Like, I'm right now.
I won't show these people nothing.
Well, you see you'll see some cash
sometimes, you know, in the in the gambling
thing, but um Yeah.
See, now Sean will be obsessed with this
person for years now. You see how people
move on? People don't care. Sean will be
obsessed with this person even though
I've never met them and he's never met
them. Never even met them. He will be
obsessed with them now for years. That's
how bad his autism is. He needs incarcerating uh
incarcerating. That's what he needs.
People with that deep that is that
deeply autistic shouldn't even be
allowed in public. It's like you know
pedophiles, right? How they want to not
stream and they go why why do
pedophiles why do pedophiles go to
prison? Because they're notes, right? So
to protect the public but he's autism is
so bad that he needs to be incarcerated.
Like I'm I'm not even joking. I'm
literally I'm literally not even joking.
He's already obsessed with Izzy sloppy
second. He's already obsessed with
Morgan the sloppy seconds. And now he's
obsessed with this person who I've never
even met. [ __ ] hell. So yeah. Yeah,
bro. And that's it, bro. Yeah.
I used to love putting the approaching
videos up. It used to trigger that
virgin. I think that's why he he got my channel
banned. Yeah, I know. I know. People
just forget and move on, but not that little virgin. It's
because what it is is it's it's a form
of autism. He sees that somebody has
gone out and got an American woman,
Morgan, and then you got with Izzy, and
then you're speaking to this person who
was kind of normal and then they turned
into a [ __ ] His autism doesn't accept
doesn't allow him to accept the fact
that other men can go out and pull
normal women and get normal women and
function in normal environments. Whereas
he can't he can't get anything normal,
anything that's not disabled. He can't
even be friends with normal people cuz
his autism is that bad and his autism
doesn't allow him to accept it. So he it
leaves him confused thinking, "No, like
how could that possibly happen? I mean
I've got Sarah here. She got special
needs. I've never been with a normal
woman, so there's no there's no possible
way Peter Belly could
have. And that's what happens, bro. So, yeah.
Normal people would have just moved on.
Yeah. Not that
virgin [ __ ] is is batting. There's
there's there there's two things,
Charlie. You either ignore them or you
batter them. That's that's the only
thing. There's no restraining orders.
There's there's not even police with
somebody with that amount of autism. Cuz
I used to think the restraining order
would have worked, you see. But a
restraining order won't work because
they'll just make other accounts and
then police would get fed up. Like I
actually think that the only thing for
these people is a good oldfashioned
hiden. And that's why they call it
oldfashioned. You see, you know, that's
that's the only thing is
probably Yeah, probably just whoop their
ass. If you can get if you can you can
get your hand on them. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I don't think so either,
mate. He's so
jealous. He's so jealous, man. Like, all
he does is bring up Morgan and Izzy.
He's so jealous, man. I don't understand
why he's so jealous that I had a one
night stand with these
people. Yeah, I think that is your only
way. All right, listen. Um All right,
bro. You know this woman? Sorry about
the message yesterday, bro. I was
talking to this [ __ ] woman uh yesterday,
bro. From um Manchester. We twe we
speaking for 4 days. Sorry about the
messages, man. And we arranged to meet
and everything. All of a sudden, she
blocked me on Instagram. Tried [ __ ]
lying about that. She blocked me on
Instagram. And then when I told her
like, "I know you're lying." She blocked
me on [ __ ] uh WhatsApp. So, I'm going
to Manchester next Friday. I'm putting
up post of her cuz I booked a hotel. I
thought, "Fuck this, mate. One too many
[ __ ] times, you cunt." And now these
people are [ __ ] messaging her. So,
he's she's getting posters of her, bro.
I'm going to put up posters of her. He's
[ __ ] now, bro. And trust me,
Manchester is not as big as London. I've
had enough of these people. You know,
I've I You know what, LT? I was actually
in a good mood. You know, when I like I
told you about that horror film and
that. Yeah. I was actually in a good
mood the past couple of days and this
[ __ ] was starting to w me up, bro. Like
I was getting them sicks that like you got yesterday.
So yeah, I'm going Manchester next
Friday, bro. It's all booked. So yeah,
man. It's going to be a banger.
All I wanted was a [ __ ] quiet life.
All I wanted was a [ __ ] quiet life,
bro. But I was like, "Bro, now get
another phone saying, "Listen, you think
you can take the piss out of me with
your little [ __ ] friends? Don't think
Manchester is is is very far to travel
to cuz it ain't Yeah, we've done
Middlesburgh for people there, mate. So
there's no distance for Peter Belly, man.
Even though it makes no sense
retaliating, you have no choice but to.
Even though all logic says, "Oh, don't
retaliate. It's not going to do
anything." But you feel like you need
your own back on them, bro. That's what
you fully fully need. You feel like you
fully need your own back on him, bro.
It's hard to explain unless you've been
in that unless you've been in that position.
Yeah. Like you will never understand. It
just sounds like waffle in it.
But believe you
me, bro. All that, bro. I don't even
Hey, I don't even message you that that
much now, LT. Unless it's for a sing
along, you know, unless it's to see how
you're doing or for a sing along.
Sometimes I message you for for a sing
along, you know, but that's about it.
But no, I am actually going Manchester
next Friday. I've had enough of these [ __ ]
mate. No, I've had enough of these
[ __ ] Like, don't worry, bro. I'm not
going to go on no massacre or start
hurting people. I'm just going to put up
posters of this
[ __ ] and I'm going to say that they were
dirty little nons that nunched up my
kids. Yeah, I don't [ __ ] about, bro.
Stop [ __ ] around with people. Yeah,
you're going to learn one day. a sing
along like I I I'll write you like
lyrics. I'll write you like lyrics. And
I wanted to know that if you've got um
if you know the the
song. I said I hate women to the to this
woman. She said you should be a guy. I
said you should suck my
dick. You should suck my [Laughter]
dick. Suck my dick. You little [ __ ]
That's what I just said to them. But
yeah, this C in Manchester is getting
it, mate. I might I might end a [ __ ]
trip. Yeah, with a lovely fish and chips
and Frankie by the seaside in Blackpool.
Ah, what a lovely
site. Message Antman. Antman started
messaging the woman. I gave I gave her
number to him and that I said, "Tell the
[ __ ] I'm coming in it." Like, give her
the heads up in it.
I'm going to put it by the train station
as well. Her workplace, Trafford Center.
See, London, you see, you can get
exposed in London and London's very big.
Manchester, it's not as big as London, mate.
So, yeah, Manchester is actually quite
small around the city center and that,
but I don't know where they work as
well. I've had it up to here with it,
mate. I've had it up to [ __ ] here
with these [ __ ]
LT, you know.
A sing along. A sing
along. Oh yeah, that Mark came on here
the other day pretending to call people
out again. You know, you know what I'm
saying? Like this guy was pissing me off
as well. Like this is what I mean that
there's there's no point wasting your
time with people on this community, bro.
Because no matter how many times you
meet these people, they will just come
back on like nothing's ever happened
again. Mark been to his area two times.
Sean been to the Virgin's area three
times. And no matter what you do, they
can come back on here and start their
[ __ ] again like nothing ever happened.
This is why I don't bother with these
people. He's coming on here like he's
some kind of hard man. Why does this
Mark Samson do this? Why does he
actually actually do
this? Why does he do this? Why does this
Mark Samson do this? It's been like, why
does he come on here and do this? They all Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I just got I've just got
this little virgin obsessed with me,
man. But yeah, don't defend this [ __ ]
woman in Manchester, L2. She deserves
it, bro. I'm only doing posters. I'm
only doing posters. I'll take the piss
out of you. Yeah. You want to take the
piss out of me, I'll take the piss out
of you, you silly [ __ ]
Yeah, I know people in Manchester as
well, bro. I I met my friend. He come
down from Manchester um last
week. You know what I mean? Yeah. [Laughter] So yeah,
bro. Yeah. So I I uh I'm actually known
around Manchester, Charlie. I know all
the Barbers. I'm actually quite
popular. I'm actually quite
popular. I'm actually I'm actually quite popular actually,
bro. I'm actually quite popular, bro.
I'm actually quite popular, bro. You know that?
Yeah. See, see with me. Yeah. I'm not
Ant-Man. I'm I'm I'm not going to go out
with a load of posters like sorry with
an axe and and do time for these [ __ ]
I'll just put up posters of them. I
would just put up posters of them. I
don't need to [ __ ] [ __ ] around and do
all that, you know, go prison and I'll
just put up posters of
them. That's how you know you're driven
to the edge, bro. When you're going all
that way to put up posters, you're
[ __ ] bad, bro. I mean, I'm not I swear. Yeah.
Yeah. I remember a boy I went to
Manchester see if my friend would come
out. You remember that when I went to I
wanted to see if my friend would come
out. I [ __ ] shouted the place
down. I shouted the [ __ ] place down, mate. Yeah.
I'm getting sick of these white knights.
So, I'm getting sick of these white
knights. These little white knights
ain't got a bad word to say about living with
it. It was [ __ ] driving me mad
yesterday, mate. Driving me [ __ ] mad. It
was mad, mate. Mad.
when they're [ __ ]
dead. You know what I
mean? Just pretending to call people out
again. Just pretending to call these
people out again. But I love it when
these women meet me. These women need to
meet me so they realize they should they
can't do it to anyone ever again. Like I
want them to have that opinion on men.
Any woman that [ __ ] somebody over and
waste their time. I want their opinion
to be all men are bad. All men are bad.
I want I want that to be the case. So
they stay away from people and they
don't hurt them. That's what I want them
to be like. That's that's exactly what
it is. You know, if they if they are
scared of men after I go Manchester and
I put these posters up, that's what I
want. I want you to learn that you could
there's consequences for your actions.
It doesn't matter whether you're a
[ __ ] man or you're a [ __ ]
woman, you know? That's that's my whole
thing. She's saying that she's got
mental health. Oh, I've got mental
health. Who doesn't have mental health?
See, it's the same as that. what what
that Morgan was was saying to you trying
to play the victim. You know, they like
to play the game. No, no. This is what
these [ __ ] like to do, bro. Yeah.
They like to play this mad game with
people and then they think they can get
off scotfree and then as soon as they
meet their match, they always play
victim, don't they? Whenever they meet
their match, mate, Uncle Badass. Yeah.
They always [ __ ] play the victim.
What is that all about, bro?
You know, cuz I went on my Instagram uh
D gains. Yeah. And you know how you can
see who you're following and your
followers? I was like, "This ain't
looking right, bro." Like, cuz I'm very
I'm very clued up with that kind of
stuff. I was like, "Oh, what? There's 80
followers instead of 82 followers, bro.
This ain't looking right." You know what
I'm saying? This ain't looking right,
bro. I don't have his channel, bro. It
was just It was just It was just Arsenal Mark.
The channel was just Arsenal Mark, lad.
Yeah, it was just Arsenal
Mark. But I don't know which which one it is,
bro. But what are you saying now? Are
you Are you Are you Are you
free? Because this ain't looking right,
L. It's not looking right.
I'm telling you it ain't. Look, that
Instagram account is not looking right.
Yeah, 100% it
ain't. I'm actually building my
followers up as well. You
know, I'm quite new to Instagram LT. You
know these people. Well, do you know
what? Yeah, I was actually, like I was
saying to you earlier, I was actually
all right for a couple of days until
this [ __ ] started pissing me off. You
know, I was actually good for a couple
of days. I went to the pictures, you
know. I I went to the pictures. I
watched that Heart Eyes. I told you
about that horror film. I was actually
in a good mood until this [ __ ] from
Manchester wanted to start playing
games. I was actually in a good
mood. You know, went about my business,
not causing any problems. You
know, do you know what I'm saying, bro?
Like, they just ruin my
mood. woman abuse, but I don't want to
do on Instagram because what they do is
they report you. That's what they do.
They [ __ ] report
you. So, I can send it on WhatsApp.
Yeah. You know,
Yeah, bro. in this country out here.
Unless you're black or you're a woman
abuser or you're some white guy with
[ __ ] tattoos or you're a crackhead,
you're not getting women in this
country, bro. You're not getting women in this
country. Unless you're one of them like
three or four things, bro, it's it's
done. I hate westernized women. I'm
going to prove my point next week, bro.
I'm going to prove my [ __ ] point next
week. You [ __ ] watch,
bro. I'll prove my point next week, bro.
Watch. I made it up to here with it, lad.
See, I'm not a hater, bro. I don't care
who gets for food, but I'm just saying
that's what they go for. It's either
white guy who abuses women with a tattoo
on his head. It's either a crackhead, a
drug dealer, or it's just a black guy.
That's the only kind of people that they
want. And if they're interested in a
white guy, it's somebody who's a
scumbag. So, I know my place. Like, I'm
not going to sit here. I'm not going to
mope around. I'm going to get my
passport. renewed next week cuz it runs
out in March and I'm out of here. It's
not my problem anymore. It's not my
problem anymore. I'm I'm sick of these
[ __ ] in this country. I don't want
to hear about it. I don't even like
hearing about it. It annoys me this country, you
know? It annoys me, bro. We all see what
these people go for. Come on now, bro.
I'm lying. We see it all the time. Do we
not see it? Yeah.
So [ __ ] it in it. Hate him, bro. I
[ __ ] hate him. I didn't go out
yesterday. I went out on
Friday, you know. No, I didn't get a
hangover. I just went out with my
friend. We had a few drinks. I just a
bit hammered, but that's
it. They're only like [ __ ] it seems.
So yeah, they're the same kind of
people. Is what it is,
bro. I can't believe I'm actually going
to Manchester next week just to put up a
load of posters. What? What has this
country come to, bro? You think I really
have time to be [ __ ] doing that? But
I'm not going to let this kind of get
the last laugh out of me, bro. I'm not
going to let this kind of get the last
laugh. You know, it's about time, bro.
We're not And this is what I was saying
earlier, bro. It's not one thing. It's
not two things. It's amalgamation of
things and they all add up and you
think, "Fuck this, mate. It's time to
give these [ __ ] some back." So that
[ __ ] in America made the [ __ ] change her
number, made her boyfriend split up with
her, made her run to law. [ __ ] her. This
person I'm even more closer to now.
You know, enough is enough, mate. You know, [ __ ]
hell. Enough is enough,
man. Oh, he's stalking my sloppy
seconds, by the way. He's stalking my sloppy seconds.
Um, oh, you told your mom. Oh, I'm
coming to M Man Manchester to put up
posters of you. She's told her mom now.
LT, she's told her
mom. What the [ __ ] bro? What's your mom
going to do, bro? Respectfully, what's
your LT? What is their mom going to do?
Come on. Huh?
Whoa. You were talking to my sloppy
seconds for 1 hour and 12 minutes. Oh,
you are obsessed,
Sean. Oh, and you want to tell me that
people sound like a crackhead? Have you
[ __ ] Have you Have you heard your
ugly fat girlfriend? You want to say
that these people, you know what I
mean? Yeah, I'm putting up posters of
them anyways. So anyways, there's no
there's no this person can lie about me
because I've never actually met them. But yeah, but
yeah, playing the victim again. You love
playing the victim, don't you? When you
caught out, don't you? You love playing the
victim. You love playing the victim,
don't you? These
people, you know, and look at this
personality. I've not even met them, so
they can't say that I've grabbed them or
I've done this, I've done that. [ __ ]
this [ __ ] They're getting it this week,
bro. I swear to God, they're getting it.
Yeah. They are getting it,
bro. No, I'm not taking No, cuz I'm sick
of it, bro. I'm sick of it. Yeah. Do you
not understand? I am sick of these
people. Yeah. Time and time and time and
time and time again, bro. I'm sick of
these [ __ ] You don't understand how
they're allowed to be [ __ ] for no
reason and they get away with it every
single time. I've had enough of it. I'm
not leaving it, brother. I'm not leaving
it. Yeah. I'm not leaving it at all,
bro. Yeah. I'm sick of these people.
Yeah. It's not one person or two people
or No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. This
has been going on for too long now,
mate. No, no,
no. Yeah. Yeah. Don't like, do you know
what I'm saying? And I'm not taking no
[ __ ] L. I don't even care about the
[ __ ] person, but it's principle, bro.
You know what I'm saying? It's
principle. I'm not taking no [ __ ] L.
These these westernized [ __ ] need to
learn, bro. Yeah. And let me tell you
something right now. If there was no
laws in this country, you know what I
would do? I would go outside and bag one
of them up, bro. I'm not even joking. I
would smash their [ __ ] face. And but
there's certain laws in this country
that you can't do that. Yeah, I would,
bro. I'm not even trying to. You think
I'm trying to say this stuff to annoy
you and wind you up, but I'm not. Like,
think about how I feel. Yeah, you have
to listen to it. Think about how I feel
with these little
[ __ ] If I had it my way, bro. No sick
[ __ ] bro. I I would kidnap them and I
would torture them. Like, I'm not even
jo I'm not even joking. Not sexually.
Not sexually. I wouldn't rape anyone,
but I would I would make him pay,
bro. No, you don't understand, bro.
Yeah. You have your little life with
your woman LT where you live. You don't
understand how this works. Yeah. It's
not funny, bro. It's annoying. You know,
and when you have to keep dealing with
these people [ __ ] bro. [ __ ]
off. I'm doing my thing next week. I'm
doing my thing next week, bro. Yeah.
You're fed up with hearing it because it
doesn't affect you. Yeah. Cuz it doesn't
affect you, bro. You understand? Yeah.
You're very selfish in that way. It
doesn't affect you. So why would you
care? Just like when you used to you
used to laugh at these people. Yeah.
Like semi laugh. Yeah. And I told you
it's not funny what these people here
were doing. And then they target you and
all of a sudden it's not funny. See?
See? You know what I mean?
Yeah, I'm just venting. No, I won't,
bro. No, I
won't. You got these weirdos messaging
now as well.
I'm saying, bro, no one's venting. No
one's venting at all. I've got the hotel
booked. Well, I've got it reserved. I've
got the I've got the the the hotel
reserved, bro. I stay in the same hotel
every time I go to Manchester.
Like, do you want something to be scared
of? Like, here's the thing. Have you
ever heard Have you ever heard the boy
who cried wolf? Have you ever heard the
boy who cried wolf? I've heard about the
boy who cried wolf. But the thing is, I
will actually make you scared. It's the
same thing to this silly little [ __ ] in
America. I will actually make you scared
with these posters. And when I come when
I come to your workplace and I pull up
posters of you. Yeah. And it will be
like the boy who cried wolf, you know?
That's what it will be like. Yeah.
Yeah. And that's
it about as always. As always, I've
pulled up on more than anyone on this
[ __ ] community. Yeah. It's just
people on here seem to have selective
memory. seems to have selective memory.
You know, that's what it
is. And that's how I know I was wasting
my time in this community. Like I told
you earlier, Mark Samson, been to his
area two times. The [ __ ] don't show up,
but everyone forgets about it. Everyone
forgets about it. They don't forget
about him being a no-show little [ __ ]
but they they forget about me going to
his area two times. That's why I give up
with you people. Cuz even if you go even
if you go for one person even if you go
for one person right on here. Yeah. Even
if you go for one person on here lad
someone else is going to come and it
will be the same thing as well.
You're sad though, Shaw, man. Being on a
being on a phone call with my sloppy
seconds for 1 hour and 12 minutes. Wow,
you really really are obsessed. You need
incarcerating. I was just saying this as
well until uh before this LT joined as
well. You know, this um this Sha um LT, he needs
incarcerating, you know, like pedophiles, right?
um that uh you know you know you know how
um pedophiles are caught and they're put
in prison. Yeah. He needs to be
incarcerated because of how bad his
obsession and his autism is and it
becomes very very dangerous. You have
not pulled up more than anyone. You go
to locations and bounce. That's why
Prime had to catch me off guard. Okay.
Manchester try to meet Bomb. Mark. Uh,
tried to meet Bomb, tried to meet Mark,
tried to meet Trevor Dawson, tried to
meet Triple H three
times. Um, went to Sha's area three
times, begged and pleaded begged and um pleaded
um for these people to show me where
they are and they wouldn't. And then I
did go to some cities asking people if
you're from this area come out. What do
you want me to do? Bro, I don't
understand what you actually expect me
to do. Okay. Okay. Let me give you an
example, right? Okay. Say I wanted to
meet somebody right now on this
community and I'm pissed off. These
people annoy me. I want to [ __ ] [ __ ]
up that red star. I want to [ __ ] up that
Sha. What do you expect me to do other
than go to their area and try meeting them?
What else do you want me to do, bro? Get
a magical wand. You know what I
mean? She didn't reject me. She wasted my
time. So, like, say example, I wanted to
meet someone now. Okay. Okay. What?
What, bro? What? What is it? What is it? You
know, what would I have to do in order
to meet one of them two as an example? It's ridiculous, bro. You
know, I have tried meeting people on
here. I have gone to different cities
telling people where I
was. And we're green. Well, did Terry
show up? Okay. Okay. Did Terry show up?
Did Mark show up? Did Terry show up? Did
Mark show up? No, they [ __ ] didn't.
So what, bro? So I called you Terry and
Mark. Yeah. Okay. Did they show up? Did
they show up? No, they
never know what I'm
saying. But this country in Manchester
is [ __ ] getting it, bro. They [ __ ] piss me
off. [ __ ] piss me off, bro.
The thing is, you didn't show up, but
they didn't show up. I didn't show up
because they didn't show up. They didn't
show up. That's the thing. They didn't
Yeah. You know what I'm saying? So, that's it. Yeah.
I can't believe I need to go to
Manchester next week and pull up some
posters. I really can't believe I'm
having to do that,
bro. I actually can't believe I have to
do that, bro.
No, he never. No, he never. He never
ever spoke about
LT and I don't speak to B anymore. I
blocked him cuz you're all sick and
twisted. I blocked him cuz you're all
sick and [ __ ] twisted. No, he never
ever said anything about how you bro.
Stop talking [ __ ] bro.
What's popping today? Um, don't know,
but I just going to make a cup of [ __ ]
in a bit. I need to go to Manchester next
week. Um, to put up post of this woman,
ruin her life, and then come back to
good old London hopefully in one
piece. Is that okay with you,
boss? Is that okay with you, boss?
You know what I So, you know what I find
so bad about Harry is how he lets people
come to his city and he doesn't pull up.
That's what I love. You let somebody
come to your city and you kept
quiet. Oh, basically I was speaking to
this person in Manchester for 3 days. I
met them on Instagram. We was voice
noting voice noting
talking and um we're supposed to meet up
next week. So, I booked a hotel and then
I went on my Instagram like was talking
for 3 days and notic they blocked me. I
was like, "Why have you blocked me on
Instagram?" No, no, she's real. She sent
me voice notes. And I said, "Oh, why
have you blocked me on Instagram? Is
there a problem?" She's like, "Oh, I
deleted my Instagram because it was
doing my head in." No, no. I was like,
"I literally know that you have blocked
me." And then um then she blocked me on
WhatsApp, so I'm just going to go and
put up post of her. I'm sick of these
women, bro. I'm sick of these women
wasting my time. I've had enough of it.
And I've already booked the hotel for
Friday cuz that's when I was going to go
up there. So, I'm going to go up there,
put up posters of her, calling her a
nons, slagging her off, and then come
back cuz I've had enough of it,
bro. It's about time somebody fighting
back to these little
[ __ ] I generally hate them.
Like I generally generally generally hate these
[ __ ] I don't know, bro. That's what I
don't understand. I don't understand.
Like, if it was for one day and then
they [ __ ] off then. Yeah. Did I say
any weird stuff to her or
something? Um, she didn't reject me, she
wasted my time. And did I say any weird
stuff to her or something? Stop asking stupid
questions. Stop asking stupid questions.
If I said anything weird to somebody to
make them block me, I wouldn't be going
to Manchester pulling up posters of
them. Stop trying to do anything but
blame the women. This is exactly what
I'm talking about. I know you're only
asking. I know you're only asking, but
it comes across as a white knight. Yeah.
Stop trying to find excuses to defend
women. Yeah. I'm not taking no, bro. I'm
going to Manchester next
week. No, no, no. It wasn't. It wasn't.
It wasn't. I'm nowhere near 30, mate.
Listen, why do you keep calling me
nearly 30? I'm 27 and I've had a better
life than you. You're in your 30s. Still
a [ __ ] virgin on YouTube every day.
Look closer to home, bro. Yeah. Anyways,
I'm going Manchester anyways next week. Anyways, it's all
done. Do you want me to show you the
screenshots? I'll show the screenshots
if you want. To be honest with you, bro,
it's not it's not weird. They do it all the
time. No, it's not weird. They do it all
the time. I had where they say they're
going to meet you and then they just
disappear. Normally they just disappear.
No, 27 is nearly 30. No, 27 is 27. 30 is
30. 3 years. Stop repeating yourself.
It's boring now. Oh, you're close to 30.
No, it isn't. 27 is 27.
Anyways, I mean, I can show you these
screenshots if you want.
Nar, do you not understand that they are
weird? There's nothing. You'll go insane
trying to figure these people out. They
are weird. And some of you might not
want to hear it, but they're not all
innocent. I know people like to say,
"Oh, they're innocent. Innocent women,
you know, they don't have a bad word to
say about women." But in reality, that's
not the way it is. As much as people
like to think that's the way it is, cuz
they ain't got no bad words to say about
women. As you know, they don't have no
bad words to say about women for some reason.
That's what I didn't understand. That's
what I don't understand. They wasted
their time and your
time. But yeah, when I noticed that the
Instagram was gone, I was like, "This is
dodge, bro. This I'm getting some I'm
getting weird vibes. I'm getting weird
vibes off this person." So yeah, voice
noting, messaging, voiceing,
messaging sent you. Bye-bye now. You're
boring, mate. You're boring now. Bye.
You're [ __ ] But yeah, um she wasted
three, four days of her own time and her
own life and gave her a number just to
do that. But guess what, Nero? They'll
be wondering where all the nice guys
have gone. Where are all the nice
guys? Uh well, you what's the word
again? You you run them through. That's
what you done.
Yeah. You wasted their own time. Yeah.
But I mean, how many times have they
done that? Wasted their own time.
You know, a lot of them have done that
before. I had a friend I was speaking to
for about four or five days and then all
of a sudden she went quiet. That's what
they do. They're not normal. You trying
to figure out these people that are not
normal, you will drive yourself insane.
You will drive yourself [ __ ] mad,
lad. Cuz they're not normal. There's
nothing normal about
them. They're [ __ ] in this country.
They're absolute [ __ ] in this
country. That's what I didn't
understand. Why would you waste three
days of your life and three days of my
life? Cuz I was actually thinking
exactly the same thing as what you just
said. One sec. What's up? Yeah,
bro. [ __ ] It's a madness, isn't it,
Nero? I didn't go out yesterday. I went
out Friday to have a
drink. No, I said to them like, "No, no,
no. What I said is when they said that
they um they deleted their
Instagram, like I knew straight away
that they were lying. I said um like I'm
sat here with my friend and he's typed
your name up on Instagram and you come
up and she just blocked me straight
away. Block my number, block my WhatsApp,
everything. They never said why, bro.
And none of these people on YouTube was
involved. None of these people on
YouTube was involved because if they
were involved, they would have blocked
you before that and they wouldn't have
even messaged you back. So
yeah, there's no way it's anything to do
with YouTube because look at all of the
times YouTube weren't involved. Look at
all of the times that YouTube wasn't
involved. USA Izzy, this French one from
last week, somebody else from last week.
Think of all of the times YouTube was
not involved and these same things
happened. It's not YouTube, bro. It's
their weird. Yeah. People might have
messaged them after
um you know after like they had already
done it. Yeah. But before that they
never they never bro they [ __ ] well
never they're weird. They're weirdos.
They're weirdos but they're piss takers.
But even though Right. This is what I'm
saying. I put this I was telling some
people about this on my Instagram. They
won't have no bad words to say about
women. They'll be like, "Oh, well yeah,
maybe she's changed her mind, or maybe
it was you sending two exes, even though
she was sending me two exes." They will
literally do anything but blame the
woman. Even though in that case, they
were taking a piss out of you, right?
They were wasting your time. They were
probably taking a piss out of you with
their friends. These people don't have a
bad word to say about
women. It's [ __ ] mad, bro. Like,
they're allowed in their head. Women
can't do no wrong.
They can't do no wrong. It doesn't It
doesn't matter what circumstance it is,
they can't do no wrong. It is weird. I
was shocked to be fair cuz I I booked a
hotel for next uh
Friday. So, I can show you the messages
so you get more of a gist of it if you
want. I don't I drive
up. I think they're mentally ill,
bro. What do you
think? I'll show you if you want. If you
got Instagram or Snapchat, I don't really care,
bro. There's got to be somebody on my
Instagram that is following me from
here. There's got to
be. Uh, no. She was the same age as me.
Nope. 27. She was a month older than me.
Nope. Nope. She was 27. Same hobbies,
same age. I thought, "Oh my god, this
person's the same age as me." I've
always wanted to get with somebody
that's exactly the same age as me. Maybe
it's like an OCD thing. Nah, 27, the
same age as
me. Same age,
job, but nah. See, the thing is is that
this is a misconception. You think that
them being older means anything? No,
they still play games. It doesn't matter
how old they are. You can ask LT. The
games never stop with these weirdo
women. If they've got a [ __ ] between
their legs, they're [ __ ] Simple. It
doesn't matter how how old they are.
They can be 18, they could be [ __ ]
48, and they would still play the same
games. They all do it. I had one before
in Australia. Um, I approached one in
Liverpool Street in Australia.
There's like, oh, they I think they must
have been about 37, I think they were.
And they lied to me saying that they
were going back to Australia even though
they lived here the whole time. Age
doesn't mean anything. They're all the
same. They are all the same in the in
these westernized countries anyways. So,
doesn't matter how old they are. But
yeah, it's um Nah, nah, they still play
silly little games, bro. I used to think
that as well.
Nah, age doesn't mean nothing. This
person was the same age as me. A month
older than me, they were. And they still done it.
So, I think the reason they blocked me
on Instagram is cuz they were lying
about going to this wedding on Saturday
and they knew by keeping you on
Instagram, you would know that they're a
liar. It would been proven that they're
a liar and that's why they blocked
you. Um because they know that, you
know, you would have found out that
they're not at a wedding. So that's it.
That's why they do
it. That's why they probably done it.
But I feel like a little bit of a
[ __ ] cuz you're not going to sit
there and lie to me. Oh, I deleted my
Instagram like I'm some sort of [ __ ]
Yeah. And then when someone tells you,
you block them. Like, bro, I'm I'm sending them
posters. Yeah. It doesn't matter anyways.
It doesn't matter. And when I told her
like, "You're lying. I know that you're
lying in a roundabout way." They blocked
me. That's like my friend with that
Morgan when he wasn't buying her [ __ ]
when she was trying to make up stuff
about me. Um, they block. They all
block. When they can't when they can't manipulate
people, they block you. It's a common
thing that they do. So then what would
have happened if I never said, "Oh, uh,
yeah, I didn't know that. Um, I I know
that you blocked me and
retro would have just spoke to you for
the week and then probably not met you
because why have they why would they
block you on
Instagram?" It's so mad. I should be
used to all their games now. I should be
used to all their games. But I think
what it is is that Antman's like, "Oh,
like it's the same old England." But I
think what it is is that you you you
hope that with one person it will be
different, but it will never be
different. It will never be different.
But you hope it will be different, but it never
will. Oh, stop making excuses about she
wasn't interested. Stop making excuses,
mate. She was speaking to me for 3 days
non-stop. Yeah. Stop making excuses.
That right there is making an excuse.
This is exactly what I'm talking about.
They will always make excuses for women.
Yeah. About she couldn't say it. Stop
making excuses. Oh my god. About how
they wasn't interested but because she
couldn't say it. Okay. So you give your
number, you speak to someone, you speak
for 3 days straight you arranged to meet
them, then you're not interested, bro.
Make it make sense. Yeah. If by the f
third or fourth message, right, you said
that, then fair enough. Yeah. Simple.
Stop making excuses for them, you know?
Like it was their plan the whole time to
talk to you and waste your time and get
attention. Stop making excuses. Stop
making it out like they were talking to
you. Yeah. They were going to meet you
and they weren't. Don't worry. I'm
interested next week when I'm putting up
posters. I'm more than interested. Yeah.
Trust me. I'm going to take the hint
when I'm more than interested next week
and I'm going to ruin their life and
[ __ ] their life up cuz I've had enough
of it. I've had enough of it, mate.
Yeah. You're lucky today the [ __ ]
train tracks on Sunday. Don't Don't come
at me about, oh, um, you need to take
the hint she wasn't interested. Is that
all it is? Not that they were taking a
piss out of you. Not that they were
wasting your time. You see what I'm
saying, bro? Allow it. Allow it, bro.
Allow it. Yeah. Stop making excuses for
them. It's pathetic. Yeah. They had no
intentions of meeting you to begin with.
Yeah. If they're not interested, why are
they giving their number and telling you
they're going to meet you then? You
know, that's And here's the thing. if
they if they um
yeah about the easy thing. The easy
thing wouldn't be would would be not
leading someone on. How about my
response? The easy thing would not be
would be to not lead somebody on for 3
days. That would be the easy thing. But
you won't admit that because you ain't
got a bad word to say about women. So
there's no point. And and and here's the
thing. There's no point even me and you
going back and forth. You've got this
thing in your head. Women can't be
wrong. They're perfect. No. No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. Bro, I'm not going
to sit here and argue. You want to talk
about an easy thing? An easy thing is
not leading somebody on for 3 days.
Would you lead somebody on for 3 days if
you weren't interested? I [ __ ] well
wouldn't. I [ __ ] well
wouldn't. And I wouldn't keep talking to
them if I was not interested. You just
make excuses in your head. Women can't be
wrong. Yeah, that's pathetic, bro. That is
pathetic. You have no bad words to say
about women. You've got no bad You're
just like these white knights. I'm not
going to call you a s. Yeah, cuz that's
not the correct term for it. But you are
a white knight. You definitely are a
white knight. Cuz this person had it in
their head that they were going to take
the piss out of you. They were going to
speak to you for 3 days, right, and
waste your time. It's just like that
[ __ ] in America. I'm not accepting it.
I'm not accepting you thinking that you
can be a [ __ ] and get away with it. I'm
not made like that, bro. I'm not made to
let these little rape victim scummy
women get away with it. I'm not a [ __ ]
you know? I've been a [ __ ] for too long.
Yeah. And I'm not a [ __ ] I'm not
letting these little rape victims get
the last laugh out of me. These little
[ __ ] I'm not letting them, bro. I'm
not letting these little rape victim
vindictive little [ __ ] keep getting the
last laugh. You know what I'm saying? No
way, bro. You can carry on white
nighting all you like. I don't care. Simple. You
know, you know what I'm saying, bro? That's
it. You see how white night you You see
where white knighting gets you. But you
always make excuses for these women. Oh,
they change their mind. You always make
excuses. Why can they never be the one
in the wrong? Let me ask you this
question. Why can they never be the one
in the wrong? Answer me this question.
Why can these little [ __ ] never be the
one in the wrong? Why just not one time
you can say they were leading you on
taking the piss out of you? They're
evil. Why is it you can never say that
about a woman? Can you Can you answer me this question,
please? Can you please answer me this
question? I want to know. Simple. I want
to know, bro. Like, you say people are
whining, but they're
not. You always make excuses. Why is it that no
one, you know, you know what I'm saying,
bro? Like, you Why is it that you can
never ever say one of them is wrong? Why
is it why is it why is it always
excuses you know why is it and it is you
saying that you need to take a risk he
wasn't interested because that is making
an excuse like as you might not think
that's making an excuse but it is making
an excuse because you're trying to
sugarcoat what they've actually done you
know and I think that's the perfect word
for it as well you're trying to
sugarcoat it you know you are trying to
sugarcoat it okay or maybe LT maybe
maybe Maybe, maybe, bro. Maybe that they
were just taking a piss out of you for 3
days and this was born. Maybe. How? That
can't be a possibility, can it, LT? It
can't be a possibility, can it? Because
it's a woman. No, that can't be. Why?
That can't be a possibility, can it?
That can't be a possibility. No, bro.
People don't go along with what you're
saying. Me? A lot of people tell me I'm
wrong. Some people say they were taking piss, you
know. Nah. Yeah. They definitely just
weren't interested or lost interest.
They weren't taking the piss out of you
or nothing. Nah, nah, nah. They can
never do that cuz they're women, aren't
they? So, because they've got a [ __ ] in
between their legs, they can't possibly
do the same [ __ ] as men do. You're
pathetic, bro. It's
pathetic. It's pathetic. And the only
reason it's normally it doesn't piss me
off, right? Because like Simpsons and
Simpsons and white knights are white
knights. I don't really care. It's never
going to stop. But I when I'm say when
I'm explaining this to people and people
are still trying to defend this [ __ ] it
drives me mad. It drives me [ __ ] mad
when they're trying to make they're
trying to sugarcom it. You know what I'm
trying to say? No, bro. They were
texting you to waste your time and take
the piss. End of story, bro. There's no,
"Oh, they changed their mind. Oh, you
said this." No, bro. Nei, bro. Not in
this case. Neither. Yeah. How about that one? So that's
it. And here's the thing. That Red Star
account is Sean. By the way, you're
trying to say that this woman shouts
sounds disabled. So, she's trying to say
that. Yeah, this woman sounds disabled
apparently. Bro, listen. No offense. I
hate this little [ __ ] They're going to
get it in Manchester next week. I swear
to God they're getting it. Yeah, but you
want to talk about people being disabled
cuz we know you're that Red Star
account, Sean, because you're saying by
shock. It's nice that we know that
you're under this account now, bro. Have
you Bro, listen. Let me put your girl
back on the screen so everybody can see
what she looks like. Yeah. You want to
go around with somebody with a face like
that and try to tell me how other people
sound disabled, please, mate. Yeah, them
[ __ ] teeth need [ __ ] coloring in
with a [ __ ] white [ __ ] pen. That's
what they [ __ ] need. Like, look, bro.
Listen, you would know all about
disabled people. Yeah. Look at that.
Look at that face, bro. Allow it. I
[ __ ] allow it, bro. Yeah.
This cunt's getting it,
bro. [ __ ] an hour phone call. God,
that's obsessed, bro. You can just tell
that this [ __ ] is just so obsessed. Like
talking about me and No, no, no, no, no.
Oh my god, he's so weird being on a
phone call with somebody that you don't
know having a conversation about me. You
need to get some [ __ ] help. Like you
you you people want to sit there and
tell me that I need to get some help,
bro. There's enough of you on here that
need help, bro. Nons people that defend
women, they need help. They need some
[ __ ] help, bro. Oh my god, bro.
Before they tell anyone about how they
need help, you know, what I'm
saying? [ __ ] mad, bro.
So, who's stalking this Instagram anyways?
LT. But yeah, don't just stop using
these excuses as, oh, they're not
interested. If you're not interested,
why are you talking to someone for 3
days? And then and then people normally
say, oh, well, they're too nice. But
they're not nice though. But the thing
is they're not nice because if they were
nice they wouldn't do the things that
they do. I.e. ghost, i.e. block, i.e.
make people depressed. So don't use that
as an excuse. It's all
excuses. I find with women they have a
million and one different excuses made for
them. Like does it not ever think does
it not ever occur to your mind sometimes
that maybe they're just taking a piss? No. No. you
know, but it doesn't matter because
Yeah. And this is the thing, LT, this is
why I don't add women on in like the
thing is I weren't going out and I
stumbled across this person. I was like,
"Okay, let me add them and message them
and that. Let me add them and message
them, right?" And then [ __ ] that's
the only reason I don't add anyone on
Instagram. I don't speak to women online
cuz of these stalkers and I just don't
like doing it online. But
yeah, but you do you do realize you are
making excuses for
women, you know,
like you you you try to justify their
actions and you don't even realize that
you're doing it, you
know? You know, I don't agree with you.
I don't agree with you, bro. I don't
Honestly, no. I don't speak to anyone on
Instagram. I just don't speak to women
on Instagram because of simps, because of white
knights, you know, because of white
knights. Probably not going to reply to
your message. I just online's not the
one. But you are making excuses. as well
that can't Manchester, you are making
excuses because if you're truly not
interested, right, then you shouldn't be
speaking to someone. And do you know
what? I'd actually get it if somebody
met you once and then they weren't
interested, then I'd be like, "Okay,
what if they met you and then they
decided I mean, okay, you know, they
haven't met you before, but bro, you
can't justify their actions. They spoke
to you for 3 days. They said they were
going to meet you. They said that they
were going to meet you and now they're
not going to meet you because they were
wasting your time. Do you know how
attraction works? You
know, your best thing would just be not
to waste someone's time to begin with
and we wouldn't be
here. You know, [Music]
These people push you to
it. These people push you to this [ __ ]
and you don't even know it,
bro. They push you to it, bro. You don't
get it. Here you are.
You even made excuses for that slag in
America. That was more
excuses. What's this person's excuse
then? I grabbed them. Well, that can't
be true because I haven't met
them. So, what's their excuses? Lovely,
bro. So, then let me ask you this
question then. Why do you moan and why
do you winge?
We have to hear you people winge about
you people being anti-men. Oh, men are
all the same. And then when somebody
says they're going to meet you, you're apparently not
interested. So, I mean, what is it?
Like, they the thing is they say that
you're these people, but they're the
only people that they go for. Drug
dealers, crackheads, [ __ ] a a woman
beating [ __ ] guy with a tattoo or a
black guy. They're the only kind of
people that they're interested in. So
surely if you're a scumbag you'd be in
the category of one of these white guys.
So therefore you would be getting women.
If they were really what you were saying
like a negative waster when you're this
and you're that you would be with a
woman cuz those are what women go for.
Look around the country lad.
They don't want a real real man. They
want a They want a woman abuser or a
drug dealer or a crackhead. That's what
they want. Look around the country. Look
around the countries. Nice guys finish
last. Have you ever heard that saying,
nice guys finish last? You
know, I'm going Manchester next Friday anyway.
pull up posters of the
[ __ ] I might even bump into the [ __ ]
I'm going to go to where they work as
well. I know where they work. So,
yeah. Yeah, you keep telling yourself
that, mate. Yeah. Yeah. You keep telling
yourself that, do they? Yeah, you keep
telling yourself that. Well, I know what
my experiences are, so I'm not going to
intervene in this argument. Nah, they
[ __ ] well don't, mate. They [ __ ]
don't. They [ __ ] well don't,
mate. This is the one time you would
gamble. I'm going, bro. I'm going. I'm
teaching this little kind of lesson. I'm
going to a workplace as well. I'm going
to a workplace as well. So, and I'm
going to put a number. She's going to
get the same treatment as USA. Is he?
They're going to get the same
treatment cuz this pissed me off, bro. I
was I was I was actually in a good mood
before this. Go cinema, talk to this
person, was going to meet them. I was
fine before I started getting [ __ ]
around with by this person, you know.
Honest to God, I was. You believe it,
you don't believe it. That's up to you,
bro. So, they put me in a bad [ __ ]
mood again, you know? I've had to wake
up [ __ ] thinking about it as
well. But what the [ __ ] could you have
been speaking about for one hour?
Yeah. For one hour. What could have you
been speaking about for 1 hour? Like you
don't even [ __ ] know me. So how could
he been speaking about me for 1 hour? You
know, you're diagnosed autistic, but
you're calling another woman
disabled. How's that work then? So,
you're actually diagnosed with
autism? Well, I'm I'm not going to
[ __ ] Liverpool. Yeah. I'm not doing
this stupid [ __ ] again. I'm going to
Manchester to [ __ ] this person up and
I'm coming back. End of. That's it. I'm
going to stay in a hotel for a couple of
hours and I'm coming back. I'm not even
drinking there. Yeah. And that's
it. I'm not playing these silly little games again,
bro. Yeah, she can contact the police
all she wants, you
know. Bro, listen. She can contact the
police all she wants. I don't care. I've
had enough of it. We're beyond that point
now. I don't care, bro. No, no, no. I'm
sick of these people. No, no, no. I'm
sick of these people wasting my time. If
only you knew. Yeah. If only you [ __ ]
knew how annoying these [ __ ] are, you
know? That's why I stopped going out to
get away from it. You know, I went out
Friday to meet my friend, okay, up the
road. Whoopy whoopy woo, bro. To catch
up. And then Saturday, which was
yesterday, I didn't go out. I I wanted
to get away from these people, these
[ __ ] stupid scumbag [ __ ] women.
But you still have these problems even
when you don't even leave your [ __ ]
house. [ __ ] them, bro. [ __ ] them.
They're getting it. I don't care. Let
them call the police. I don't give a
[ __ ] you know. That's
it. I'll upload it when I get back
anyways. So, good luck. Yeah. Call the
police. I don't care. I don't give a
[ __ ] Call the [ __ ] police. I've had
enough of it, mate. Trust me. If you was
in my shoes, you would understand. Yeah.
Why do women get a free pass on
everything? Look, even this LT was
trying to defend her. Oh, she was it was
just easier to block you to say she
weren't interested. Yeah, that's why she
was talking to you for 3 days. Yeah. So,
if an if a disinterested person is doing
that, then they're wasting your time
then, is it? If someone's not interested
and they're using you for attention for 3
days. Yeah. Well, have you had have you
been [ __ ] around with women all your life?
No, I'm not messaging them. They blocked
me on everything. No, no, no, no, no.
I'm I'm doing the posters. Nah, she's
another Borggan. She's going to block
people everywhere. He blocks people
everywhere, bro. Don't worry. No, no,
no. The posters will get their
attention. Don't you worry, mate. You
can run, but you can't hide,
[ __ ] That's it. Nah, there's no
point messaging them, bro. They don't
care about your messages. They're behind
a block button, bro. When I'll be
messaging them again is when I've done
posters. I don't care. Yeah, you've not
had you've not had your time wasted by these
[ __ ] So that's it. You've not had
these scumbag women waste your [ __ ]
time. You know what I'm
saying? Yeah. Well, they've messed me
around, mate. And I'm getting my own
back. I'm sick of it. I'm actually sick
of it, bro.
I'm actually sick of these
people. Yeah, you're not about it, bro.
You're not about it. I'm going to block
this Har. He's so boring. It's the same
repeating with him. I'm blocking him,
bro. I'm blocking this [ __ ] I don't
even know why he's on my channel. It's
just the same [ __ ] Oh, you're by You're
not about it, bro. Get yourself gone,
bro. [ __ ] off. [ __ ] off, you stupid
Yeah. Oh, you're by your skin. [ __ ] off.
Same repeating with him every day as well.
So yeah, I'm sick of these people
now. I'm sick of these people. I'm
actually sick of these people, bro. And
it's not just one person. It's
amalgamation of all of them.
You know what I mean?
I see. I need to get some food in a bit. Man's hungry,
bro. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, bro.
Listen, did I go out Saturday? No, I
went out Friday to meet my friend. I
don't what I don't I hate women in this
country. It does make sense. I hate
women in this country cuz I know exactly
what's going to happen when you go out
and you approach a woman and you get
their number. They're just going to
leave you and waste your time. Like they
all do. Like they all do. You're telling
me to take a break, bro. Ban's been
taking a break. I stumbled across this
person on Instagram. I was messaging
them. I thought they were cool. And
they're all the same. Just like all
these other women, man's been taking a
break, bro. I only went to the local
pubs. I only went to the local pubs
Friday to meet my [ __ ]
friend. Why don't I? Because I stumbled
across them on [ __ ] Instagram and I
messaged them days before they replied.
I was like, "Okay, well, maybe this will
be somebody that will prove me wrong."
But I will never be proven wrong. As far
as women go in this country, I will
never be proven wrong.
I know that I will never ever be proven
wrong. The day I'm proven wrong is a day
I never win ever again. When somebody
actually proves me wrong, bro, I will
never win ever
again, you know? But I know that day
will never ever happen cuz they're all the same.
So, somebody was messaging me back from
days ago. Bro, what the [ __ ] did you
want me to do?
So, she's one of my victims
now. Do you know what? I didn't
think I didn't think I was going to have
any victims. Like, you know what I
mean? That's what I'm doing, bro. I'm
renewing my passport in a week or two
and I'm out of it, bro. It's not going
to be my problem, mama. That is
generally generally how I feel. I feel
like they're all [ __ ] in this
country. These women, I feel like they
go for the same kind of
guys. Um, and they're just horrible,
evil [ __ ] in these westernized
countries. That's generally how I feel,
you know. That's generally generally how
I feel. I feel they're all the same. It
doesn't matter where I'm off
to, they're all the same.
That's generally how I feel. Eh, but I
thought this person's the same age as
me. They seemed, you know, give them a
chance. But nah, these women will never change.
Uh-uh. Uh uh uh. These women in this
country will never change. And that's
it. This country annoys me. The weather, the women.
Yeah. I hate him. I I don't want to deal
with him. I hate him. Who the [ __ ] do
they think they are, bro? Like, who the
[ __ ] do they think they
are? Now, who do they actually think
they are, bro? Like, come on now. You
know, and you know, when you're saying
great work with that woman that blocked
me before you even contacted her, Sean,
you do realize that I could actually go
and speak to another woman and get
another woman's number today if I wanted
to and keep talking to them. It's
nothing to me. It's it's it's something
to you autistic people on here because
you don't leave your house and you can't
function in normal rel um environments
but nothing to do with me you
know I am going to have to go to
Thailand but I still want to make my
point I still want to get my point
across. I still want to get my point across. You
know I [ __ ] hate them bro. But for
some reason, people ain't got a bad word
to say about
him. No, she didn't block me due to
nonsense. And I'm not going to keep
going on and on and on and on and on
about it. She blocked me because she's a
[ __ ] That's why. And she didn't want me
to find out that she's lying and she's
not going to a wedding. It was all to
cover up the fact that I knew she was
lying. She ain't going to no [ __ ]
wedding. They're just the same [ __ ]
Wales, America, [ __ ] Manchester,
[ __ ] England. They're all the [ __ ]
same. They're all the [ __ ] same
[ __ ] [ __ ] in this country.
Yeah. They will never change. This
country will never change. You
know, that's it. So
yeah. Well, I'll be seeing her next week
anyways. Well, I won't be seeing her.
I'll be put up
posters. She like she's warned her mom
about me. She's warned warned her
[ __ ] mom and dad about me. I love it, bro.
Yeah. M. No, it won't. A flight is like
£900. Shows how much you know. A flight
to Thailand you can get for4 to
£800. No, it won't cost a few G's to get
there. No, it won't. And if you're there
for a month, it's like three grand
spending money. I know cuz my friend's
been there three times. It doesn't cost
a few G's to get there. The most
expensive flight to Thailand is about
grand. And you can get cheaper ones if
you want to do it, not directly. So,
shows how much you
know. shows how much you know he
led and man's flight was £400 but he has
to stop at China and that and do a
layover. It's not a couple of G to get
Thailand. It's like a grand maximum and
then once you're there it's dirt cheap.
No, you said Thailand will cost you a
few G's to get there and spend the money
you would need 3 to
4K. So, no, you said a few G's to get
there, which is implied a few
grand. So, no, it's not exactly what you
said. You said a few
G's. Yeah, which is a few grand. Doesn't
cost a few grand to fly to Thailand.
But I never thought it would ever come
to this side. I never thought it would
actually come to you leaving your own
country. [ __ ] hell.
I want to comment. You don't think I'll
go? Good for you. No one cares what you
think. You're irrelevant. No one cares
what you think. You don't think a lot of
things. Just like you didn't think I was
going to go and see bomb. Just like you
didn't think I was going to go and see
Arsenal. Mark, you don't think a lot of
things, but your your opinion is irrelevant.
Oh yeah. Yeah. Well, your opinion
doesn't mean nothing. Your opinion is
irrelevant. Your opinion has more
meaning than than your my [ __ ] that
comes out my ass is more than your
opinion. How's about that one? Oh yeah.
I've got this I've got her calling me.
I've got this [ __ ] calling me
now. I've got this [ __ ] calling me now, [Laughter]
mate. LT, this is another chapter, isn't it,
boss? Isn't it,
boss? You were in no relationship.
No, I'm not letting you hear nothing,
mate. You little mongos can get your own
entertainment. I told her to stop
[ __ ] calling me,
bro. Stop calling me, mate. [Laughter]
I said you can say whatever you want to
my face next week.
Yeah, it's true, mate. It's
true. Why do I call LT Boss? Could I want
to cuz I want to, mate. It's [Laughter]
funny. It's so mad that any woman that
speaks to me, they don't think that if
they [ __ ] me over like they're going to
get anything and then their whole family
gets messaged and everything. It's a
madness, ain't it? I [ __ ] love it,
mate. I [ __ ] love it, mate.
Sean, just like Britney's not interested
in you and she rejected you. Just like Natalie
G. Just like Natalie G rejected you and
Britney rejected you in it. You'd know
all about people not being interested um
with you in you, don't you,
mate? Don't you? You'd know all about
people not being interested in you,
would you? Britney, Natalie G rejected
you. Now, in Natalie G's exact words,
Sean, now obviously you were you were
single at the time and obviously I used
to have this thing called fat women. So
I was like, "No, Eddie G, would you ever get
Mich He's not my
cuppper. He's literally not my cup of
tea." And all of a sudden, as soon as
she said that, you started being nasty
about her, you know, big nap. When as
soon as she rejected your advances and
it was established that you weren't her
cup of tea, Shan, you you got really
mad, didn't you? But there's nothing
wrong with that though, Shield. There's
nothing there's nothing wrong with
that. Oh, he's f away all night. Well,
good for him because he doesn't know
where I live. Oh, will he? Well, good
for him because he doesn't know where I
live. And I'm going KFC soon anyway. So,
if he knows where I live, he'll see me
outside, won't he?
Um, yeah. Oh, really? Oh, did she? Oh, that's nice.
All right. Is he Oh, that's nice for him.
Yeah. Huh? Is that supposed to make me
scared and not leave my
house? Like, I don't understand.
Anyways, bye-bye. Rat
face. Rat face. Rat
boy. Uh, yeah. He's waiting all night
until I get KFC, is he? I think it's
about that time to get KFC,
mate. Yeah, I think it's about that time to get
KFC. Right, let me have a piss and I'm
going to go
KFC. Am I scared to leave the
house? Am I scared to leave the house? [Music]
HFC. Someone waiting for
me. Am I scared to leave my house? H um [Music]
um Am I scared to leave my house?
Um Um I actually just forget something.
Um, this could be some early stages of
uh panic attack here, lads.
Um, scared to
leave. Not scared at
all. Come out. Come out, wherever you
are. KFC time, baby. Here we go. I might
do a video about KFC for you, mate. Just
got out the front. Right. I'll do a
video about KFC for you and uh I'll put
the camera on if anyone tries jumping
me. All right. Catch you later, C. See
you in a bit.