There you go. [Laughter]
That is funny, bro.
It will never end, mate. This [ __ ]
[ __ ] in Manchester keeps trying to call
me, bro. I keep airing it. Yeah. And
then messaging them and then they don't
reply back. They keep calling
me. [ __ ] slang. Now piss off. Is that
right, Charlie? Just piss
off, you know.
Don't know. She must be scared. She must
be, bro. I hope you are [ __ ]
scared. [ __ ] [ __ ] Oh, Sean deleted
Chase's comment, by the way. Sean
deletes any comment that uh he doesn't
agree with. Sean uh Chase was like,
"You're obsessed with PJ." It got four
uh likes and he deleted it. The little
scaredy [ __ ] He says he owns people
online, but he [ __ ] deletes their comments. Little
virgin. What do you mean not? Well, like
what in the head? [ __ ]
knows. What do you mean? Not well. 27. She's
27. She probably has disabilities like [ __ ] Morgan. Eh. Yeah. Yeah.
No. Um, Chase commented on Sean's thing
saying, "You're obsessed with PJ and he got four
likes." And, uh, Sean deleted a
comment. Yeah. Sean deletes comments
that he doesn't agree with. [ __ ]
virgin. Me and Chase was talking about
how weird it is that he was on the phone
for 1 hour and 12 minutes talking about me. He's
obsessed. This virgin is so obsessed
with me. Oh my god. Me and Chase was
talking about it. What the [ __ ] could
they been possibly talking about for over an
hour? God, he is obsessed. This little
virgin. Never meet a person with
autism. Yeah, Chase doesn't like him anymore. He's
weird. Yeah, Chase don't like him anymore. He's
found out that he's weird.
Never meet somebody with autism,
Charlie. Never meet somebody with [ __ ]
autism. And that's the lesson,
lad. And that's the
lesson. He is definitely definitely
definitely obsessed. And this [ __ ]
doesn't even know me. He is so obsessed.
I actually live in his head. Like, I
actually live in this virgin's head.
Yeah, I live in this virgin's
head. Free of charge. At least I know
I'll never be
homeless, you know? Just some [ __ ]
random woman that he doesn't even
[ __ ] know. He is
obsessed. Obsessed little virgin,
mate. He's obsessed. He is obsessed. Do
you not understand? Obsessed. Deeply autistic.
Yeah. A little keyboard
warrior. Apparently I have a deformed
really. Oh, who told you
that? A deformed really? Don't think so.
Who told you that? No, definitely not. You're weirdo. [ __ ]
weirdo. So many weirdos on this community,
Dad. Someone put it on his
wall. Good for
him. You know, these people will never
leave you alone until you leave YouTube.
You do realize that, Charlie? Well, I'm
saying that they won't they probably
won't even leave you alone when you
YouTube. It's mad, isn't it?
Nah. These people are obsessed, bro.
Proper proper proper
obsessed. And you haven't been told
anything because that woman's not seen
my dick. So, try again, [ __ ]
Try again. You're the only one with a
disabled dick erectile dysfunction
virgin. Still having trouble getting it
up. Never had trouble getting it up. My name's not
Nlegs. Never ever had trouble getting it
up, mate. That's you and Ngle. That's
not me. Speak for yourself on
Nlegs. Never ever had trouble getting it
up. That's the Kent Virgin, not me.
go self project somewhere else. But
that's definitely definitely definitely never been
me. Yeah, they would. Yeah. Uh Uh-huh.
Yeah. Mhm. I live in the head free. Free of
charge. Yeah. Anyways, bye-bye
now. Yeah. He's such an obsessed little
virgin. But I'm sure going to Manchester
next Friday to give
to to [ __ ] this woman
up with these
posters. My army friends, "Oh, don't do
it. You're better than that." I was
like, "Nah, mate. I've had enough of
these [ __ ] one too many times. One too
many times, bro.
You know what I'm
saying? Silo virgin.
Nope, it's someone different. I know a
lot of people in
Manchester. No, it isn't.
tried calling me a few
times. All right. Isn't this woman who
blocked you the one that day that wanted
to give you a [ __ ] Uh, no it
isn't. Yeah, she isn't calling me
anymore. She isn't calling me anymore,
but she was calling
me. Yeah, I will go there, bro. I don't
care. I've got it
booked. You know, I've got it all booked
anyways. I've got it all booked. Yeah,
I've got the messages. I've got all the
So you either say sorry brother or I'm
actually going to come up there next
week cuz I've got a hotel booked. I
don't care. I've had enough of these
[ __ ] These people don't understand,
bro. If these people really don't under
[ __ ] stand until it happens to them.
I've had enough of these little
[ __ ] mate. I don't care where they
live. I'm coming, bro.
Simple. Yeah. And she and she knows that
I've done posters as well. And she's
probably gone on my YouTube channel as
well. [ __ ] her, bro. It
Yeah. I'll give you the same opportunity
as I gave that mortgage. You say sorry
or I'm coming up there.
Simple. It's all
booked. And if you do say sorry, then
I'll just just cancel the hotel. I
reserved it. So I pay at the property
booking.com for the win. You know what I'm [Laughter]
saying? I'm not a [ __ ] mate.
Yeah, I've had enough of these
bastards. These [ __ ] women. I swear to
God. They called me a few times, but I
didn't pick up. And then when I tried to
call them back, it's like they blocked
you, but they they they were trying to call
me. They know who I am, mate. Trust
me. You know you want to troll people.
Yeah, I'll troll you in real
life. That's my thing, Charlie. I'll
troll you in real life. You
can. Oh no. Literally, bro.
Literally. Literally, mate.
Literally. I hate him, mate. I [ __ ]
hate him. I don't know about
you. They're [ __ ] little rats. That's what they
are. Little rats.
Um, I can't cuz she wrote
another I can only receive calls from her. But yeah. Yeah. Police
record, Charlie. Please record. I'm
going all the way there to put up
posters. The same website you can watch
[ __ ] Stewart little on. That's a [ __ ] madness,
bro. I will be going though. I've had enough of
them. I've had enough of them, mate. I
really have had enough of these rat
women in this
country. They're rats. They
are absolute [ __ ] rats.
Yeah. What do you think?
See if the [ __ ] calls
back. Yeah. Yeah, you can.
But people don't have a bad word to say
about women. Charlie, oh, she might have
changed her mind. No, no, no, no, no.
See, they never they never
um they never see the women as wrong.
They never they never have a bad word to
say about women. They do nothing but
defend them. It's like even LT earlier.
Oh, uh, she was not interested. She just
didn't want to say. Ah, yeah. So, you
speak to somebody for two days and you
give them your number. You speak to them
every day for 3 days cuz you're not
interested. Stop sugar coating [ __ ]
bro. They knew what they were [ __ ]
doing. But that's what I'm saying. They
always have excuses for women. They
always sugarcoat [ __ ] to make it them
look innocent. This is what I'm saying.
That's the [ __ ] that annoys
me. Nah, bro. They're evil. Simple.
They're evil scum. That's
it. Evil scum and rats. That's what they
are. I messaged Morgan's friend just now
saying, "Um, do you know somebody called
Morgan?" They've got them on their uh
Instagram and uh she didn't reply back
and she blocked me. She must have made a
post about me. That horrible
[ __ ] That horrible Morgan [ __ ] must
have made everyone aware about me, bro.
you know, I still pop up time to time.
Yeah. And you know why I want to put up
posters of this [ __ ] as well next week?
Because how many of these [ __ ] women go
around making group chats to people,
their little cowardly little group chats
where they send people's messages and me
and they send their little [ __ ] me um
their little group
chats. You've seen it. Them group chats
they [ __ ] make a people. Yeah, I'll
make a real life group out of the
poster. How about that one? I'll troll
you in real life. Not just online. I'll
just do I'll do it in real life, mate.
I'll do it in [ __ ] real life.
I'll do it in [ __ ] real life, mate.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. Know what I'm saying?
Yeah. Don't little group chats. Little
cowards. No, I'm good. Thanks. I'm done
in this country.
I'm all right, mate. I don't want to
deal with any [ __ ] in this country
anymore. I'm all right, mate. You can do
it, though, if you want, but I won't be
there. No, I'm all right, mate. [Music]
Just follow the whole sugar, I think.
No, I'm good, bro. I didn't get hangover
this week either. No, I'm I'm I'm good.
I'm out this country, mate. As soon as I
get this passport sorted
out, I'm done in this country. [ __ ]
you. That was like my final
straw. Legit, that was my final
Yeah, that was it. Mhm.
Nope. There's nothing on now until Well,
you got that Danny D film next month and
then not until the 27th of March. So,
yeah, not for a
while. Not for a while now. Nothing's on
It's good to see them on
it. Yeah, but you got to pay
£200 and I'd rather just pay £88 and
wait a week. So, yeah, it's not running
out now. It's not running out until
March anyway. So, I just paid the £88.
I'm in no rush.
So yeah, you can do it, but it means
paying £200. £27 it is. I'd rather just
pay £88 and wait a week. No rush. So yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Call me back, you little [ __ ] I dare
you. Call me back, you little [ __ ] Come
on. I'm ready for you now, mate. I'm
now. I know. It's a madness, isn't it?
Unless you get
escorts. Haven't decided yet, but out of
here. Definitely out of here,
mate. [ __ ] definitely out of
here. That's where I'll be going. Out of
Yeah. Yeah. You can only use it on
escorts. You can only use it on escorts, lad.
Yeah. Mhm. Mhm. Mhm. Bummer.
Now, why don't this little [ __ ] message
me now? Come on. Yeah.
Imagine that Charlie not even money works ei
been born without a
fus. I might as well been born looking like Tim
Eldridge. I might as well be like
looking like Tim
Eldridge. It's pointless, isn't
it? Being born looking
normal. Yeah. will work.
Yeah, last time it never
worked. Yeah, you said that last time it never
worked. Said that last time didn't never
work. I'm done in this country, mate.
sorry. I'm done in this country,
brother. Can't be of it
anymore. I didn't go out yesterday
because of that that reason. I wasn't
even hung over yesterday either. Mich
um do you remember Charlie? Do you
remember the um do you remember Sean? If
you don't find Cheryl Cole gay, if you
don't find Cheryl Cole good-looking,
you're gay. You can't deny she's attractive.
I don't know why that made me laugh,
lad. That made me laugh,
lad. Yeah, she blocked me on Instagram,
but she told me that she deleted Instagram,
Charlie. She told me that she deleted
it, but she I I knew she had blocked me.
She said she delete uh deleted uh
Instagram for a bit to have a break, but
I knew she had blocked
me saying she deleted Instagram.
Charlie and I went on like another uh
Instagram it come up. Charlie. Oh
no. What was that all
about? Yeah. And I texted as
well and it come
up and she started saying that she deleted
it. Does she think I was born yesterday? I deleted
Instagram. Why do you think she delete
she blocked you on
Instagram? She's like, "No, h I didn't."
And then when I was like, "I know you
have." She blocked me on WhatsApp as
well. We don't have a bad word to say about women.
Oh, we use a magn say no bad
words. No bad
words. Yeah. So then what would what
would have happened then? would have she
just eventually blocked me on Instagram,
sorry, on um on
WhatsApp. So then what would have
happened? They they surely to god
weren't going to meet you. If they had
blocked you on Instagram, surely to god
they wouldn't have still met
you. I know he's a
desperado, but he already said that if
you don't find Cheryl Co attractive,
you're gay. He just said that to fit in.
Yeah, he was just trying to fit in with
the crowd being a little
copycat. He was just He just found a
trend. Yeah, he just found a trend. He's a little copycat. No
originality because he's
copying. How can you have any
originality when you're copying, you know?
So, why was she going to keep me on in
uh on WhatsApp but not Instagram,
Charlie? What was that all
about? That doesn't mean
right. That's what I didn't
understand. I can read you out the
messages if you want.
I can read you out the messages if you want. I
said, "My favorite drink is Guinness
Captain Morgan's You." And I said to
her, "Why did you delete me off Insta?"
She said, "I haven't, babe. I've just
deleted Insta for a bit because it was
doing my heading."
After after I comment on that video, I
got loads of requests and it's not
stopping. Yeah, I like Guinness and
Captain Morgans's too. More of a vodka
drinker though. Haha. Vodka. Typical for
you. Haha. Really? Lucky I just got you
in time then, eh? She's like, "Haha, I
know. It's so easy to drink. I don't
mind brandy either. Depends what mood
I'm in. Honestly, I was I was just going
to eat it. I was going to leave ages ago
because it's been non-stop." I said,
"Haha. Uh, it's good you picked me. I
feel special now." I was like, "You I
was like, you out the bath?" I was like,
"You out the bath now? I can see. Uh,
can I see the selfie?" Then I said, "I'm
with my friend." And he typed you on
Instagram and it came up. So you have
blocked me. Like Yeah. So I don't know.
Yeah. So I said, "So you have blocked
me." And then she just blocked me on WhatsApp as
well. Nah, it's not that mate. That's
not an excuse.
No, that's not an excuse to be honest,
mate. Sad to
say that's not an excuse. You already
had me on Instagram. No.
No. Normally when they block you this,
it's not a good sign, bro.
No. What? So, what have they done? What
have they done? Just met
you. What have they done? Just What
would have they done? Just met
you. Whilst they blocked you on
Instagram? Nah, bro. I don't think
so. No. She said she had a wedding on
Saturday. She said she had a friend's wedding.
friend's wedding. I don't think
so. A friend's wedding, she
said. Do you believe
that? I think I believe that, man.
Yeah. Yeah. She said she had a friend's wedding on
Saturday. No, not
exactly. I know where she
works, but apparently she had a friend's wedding on
Saturday. Yeah, her workplace.
Yeah, I know her workplace.
Yeah, I think these women are all the
same. Don't know about you, I think
they're all the same.
Me? Oh, yeah. I forgot about that. Do
you think these women are all the same,
Charlie? I do.
I think they're all the same
me about you, bro.
She might unblock me. Why would she
unblock me? It doesn't make sense. One
sec. Yeah. Blocked.
Yeah, I'm blocked, bro.
It's mad how you just can't meet someone
that's normal in it.
You just can't meet somebody that doesn't play
games. I reckon I reckon Do you Do you
think there's anyone um out
there that don't play games?
No. No, I don't think so.
this someone that don't play
games. Don't think so,
bro. Wish I could just find someone that don't play
games. That's not devious. That's not a
liar. But they don't seem to exist
nowadays. Not in the country, mate. Not in this
country. You got people like LT making excuses for her. Making excuses.
Yeah. I had people even try and say it
was because I was sending two exes even
though she was sending two exes.
a bad word to say about
women, do they,
Charlie? They don't have a bad word to say about
women. She was saying that me and me and
her can have KFC together.
Yeah, that's what these people do. They
sell people a
dream. That's all they do is sell
people a dream.
They used to blame my beard, my
haircut. Um, they blamed
everything. Yeah, they blame my beard
before. I had a gay guy say blame my
beard. They blame everything but the
woman. That's what they do. They blame
everything and everyone but the w but
the woman. But they say that they're not
sexist and they say that they're not
white knights. But I don't know,
man. They seem to blame everything but
women. They blame your beard. They blame
everything. You'll find anything to
blame you. That's what I'm
saying. They don't care who's right or
who wrong or who's wrong. They only
they're only interested in blaming a man that's tried
everything. Funny. Funny, but
true. They have no bad words to say
about women in it,
Charlie. It's crazy, isn't
it? I wonder why that [ __ ] done what she
done. And this wasn't even from a cold
approach. This was [ __ ] this was
Instagram. I thought, "Oh, okay. We're getting somewhere
here." But nah, they're all the same,
mate. All the [ __ ] same. I used to
think like traveling to different cities they'd be
different. I was delusional, bro. Like,
I used to travel to different cities
thinking they'd be different, but nah. No, [Music]
no. Don't you always? Don't you always?
It's a gambling, isn't it? That's what they do.
But they'll always have people like LT to defend
them, making excuses for them as they
always do. Oh, well, they always say
like they always make them like look
like a victim. Like maybe they changed
their mind and they wanted to be nice
about it. Like they always make excuses
for them. They can never be, oh well,
maybe she was a [ __ ] and she was
just wasting your time or she's a [ __ ]
Like never, never will they ever say
that about a woman.