Yeah. Oh, [ __ ] woke up with [ __ ]
mood swings again,
man. Had trouble sleeping yesterday.
Woke up with [ __ ] mood
swings. I was [ __ ] texting that
[ __ ] Somalian woman saying how I hate
all you women. You're all [ __ ]
scum. Literally, I was messaging her.
It's funny, bro.
They really truly are evil. I know
people make jokes of it, but they
really, really, really are evil. Scum
the earth. They really, really, really
are horrible. Horrible people in
general. They really
are. They really, really are horrible
people. I hate him. Literally, I hate
him. I told Ant-Man this morning as
well. I told Ant-Man this
morning. We are evil. Sad,
bro. I'm going to talk about it. It's my
channel. I'll do what I want, bro. I'll
do what I want when I [ __ ] want.
I do what I want when I [ __ ] want,
mate. It's my turn. I'll do what I want. [Laughter]
Yeah, I'll do what I want, mate. Quit
gambling my pip. I get more money than
you a month and I don't gamble my pip. I
don't gamble anymore. Try again. Stop
talking about people that you don't
know. I think that's the main
point. Um I don't gamble my pip and I
get more money than you a month. So try again.
And I don't gamble my pip because uh I
don't gamble really much anymore. So try
again. Try again. I get more money than
you would ever
have. So yeah, keep guessing about other
people's lives, bro. It's what you
people are good at on here. It's talk
like you know other people's lives. But
the most entertaining is is you don't
know about anyone's life, only your own
lives. So that's that's what's
entertaining about it to be fair.
You really don't know about anyone's
life, but you think you do in terms of
like finances and what they get and
[ __ ] Like, you really really don't know
nothing. Like, you
know, you know about the women vendetta,
cuz I tell you, but that's about it. You
don't really know anything else. You act
like you do know everyone's life, but
don't. You really, really, really don't.
You really, really, really, really don't.
That's the funny thing. You don't know
about other people's
lives. I felt like going out yesterday
and just smacking up a woman. I woke up
today thinking about smacking up a
woman. I'm saving myself. I'm saving
myself for Manchester. I told Q as well,
the Q's a real one as well. Like he
still talks to me. That guy's a real
one. That guy is actually a real one.
No, no lie,
bro. He said, "Oh, don't do it. It's not
worth it." And that like I said, these
little [ __ ] are [ __ ] pissing me off,
bro. I [ __ ] hate him. Do you not
understand? Yeah. Do you really really
really not understand? I hate him with a
passion. Get it through your [ __ ]
head. Really really do hate them.
Genuinely genuinely do. Like I [ __ ]
hate him, man. I swear down. I hate all
of them. I hate all
women and I hate people that defend them as
well. I really want to hurt one. Like,
you don't understand, bro. So
bad. Oh man. and that's
it. They're evil,
mate. What hobbies do you actually
expect somebody to get? You can't always
go to the cinema. The gym's boring.
already been to new places. There's no
hobbies. I hate women. I hate women. I
them. I hate women,
lad. People that defend him as well. You
know what I'm saying?
defend them just for being a woman.
That's [ __ ] embarrassing.
Nah, I'm all right, mate. I don't I
don't meet spastics. Nah, I'm all right,
mate. I don't meet
spastics. My mom should reply back at
like 5:00 in the morning. I said, I'm
getting these nasty, dirty mood swings
again. Dirty, stinky, off smelling
[ __ ] mood swings again cuz of these
women. every [ __ ] time, bro. I hate
them. People that defend them and keep
defending them like they're innocent. I
[ __ ] hate them, bro. I swear now,
bro. I feel like getting this cup and
smashing it against the [ __ ] wall. It's [ __ ]
annoying. Roll on [ __ ] Friday, bro.
Roll on [ __ ] Friday, bro. I swear to
God. Roll on [ __ ] Friday. Got me going, bro.
Swear to God, I don't care. You
know, I'm sick of these scumbag
women keep getting away with everything
and people keep defending them. People
keep blaming the [ __ ] man, defending
them, defending them, defending them.
Nah, women are bad for your mental
health. Nah, I don't play properties. I
I don't even gamble. So, I don't know
why you keep going on like I [ __ ]
gamble and I don't even gamble. It's
women that are the problem. They're the
ones that are bad for your mental
health. Nothing else. It's
women. It's these [ __ ] women. That's what it
is. Yeah. It's these [ __ ] women. I
hate them. I [ __ ] hate him. Every
single one of them. I swear to God. I
[ __ ] do, bro. I hate
them. They're evil. Evil. evil
scum. And like I said, I hate the people
that defend them as well. You
know, I'm not [ __ ] dealing with these
again. I'm not dealing with these hunt
women again. These evil [ __ ] Nah, I'm good,
bro. So, yeah.
not many people reply on Instagram anymore. You
know, I just wish we lived in a world
where there was no women. We could just
remove all women and just [ __ ] sex
dolls or use like flesh lights or
something and just remove all women
because they're no good. They're evil.
Why do you want evil in the world? They
say they're not. People say they're not.
Someone's like, "Oh, you know they're
not. You just need to heal from You just
need to heal. You just need to heal." I
said, "Well, no. I know they are. That's
why I'm saying they are. Obviously, you
know, 8 hours
ago. Yeah, I'll be on Reddit. Sucks, isn't it?
Way of life though, is it? It's the way life.
Sadly. Sadly, I woke up. That sucks. I
didn't want to wake up today. I wanted
to [ __ ] die my sleep every day. But
here we are. Awake again, dealing with
the same problems again. Same old
England again, eh? So
yeah, women, they're evil
scum. Women are evil, evil, evil scum
that people defend. And I don't know why
they keep defending them. I don't know
why they sit there and defend women just
for being women. They're also known as
white knights. Women are
worse cuz they're [ __ ]
They're absolute [ __ ] in this
country. That's what they are. [ __ ]
scums, scumbags. So definitely
definitely definitely women
100%. I mean, you can go to the pub and
then you can you can play fishing frenzy
and um you know, get a bonus in the pub,
you know, win some money. Women are just
evil. They're [ __ ] evil. I dealt with
a few evil people the past two weeks
actually and that was like nah mate,
enough is enough. That's why I didn't go
out on Saturday. Enough is enough, mate.
You get to a point where you you say to
yourself, "Nah, enough is enough, mate.
I'm not dealing with these little rape
victims anymore. [ __ ] that, bro." You
say to yourself, "Enough is enough." And
that's the point I got to in the end, you know?
So, yeah. And people just love blaming
men as well. So, I thought I just
wouldn't partake in it anymore. There's
no point me partaking in it. No. Yeah,
bro. No, you won't. That doesn't work.
They've also got high standards. Stop
giving me suggestions. I've tried
everything, mate. I'm 27 and I've tried
everything. No, thank you. Stop trying
to give me suggestions. I've tried
everything, mate. I'm 27. I'm not here
to get suggestions. I'm here to moan
about women and how evil they are. I'm
not here for
suggestions. There's no hope. Suicide is
the only way out. I was saying to this
person yesterday as well, suicide's the
only way out of this problem so long as
you stay in this country. And they were
just like defending women like they
always do cuz they always defend women. But
yeah, suicide is literally the only way
out. I think I I generally generally
generally generally think that it
generally is. It generally is, bro. Is killing
yourself. Like generally is. I think
suicide is the only way out. Like I've
been trying I've been trying to find the
the solution for years and years and
years, right? And I think generally
killing yourself is the only way this
will end or dying in your sleep or such
thing as leaving the country. There's a
few things, but this is no good in this
country, bro. I will never ever ever
[ __ ] with these people in this country
ever again. I hate him. I hate every
single one of them. Seriously, that
Manchester cunt's getting it on [ __ ]
Friday. I woke up today and felt like
going today, bro. But obviously, it's
all booked for Friday cuz I booked it. I
was like, I really want to go today,
bro. I have this [ __ ] blood rushing
down to my feet, bro. It's annoying me,
you know? I want to take the [ __ ]
piss out of them now. You know them
little group chats they have them little taking the
piss. You know what I'm saying? Like I
want to actually take the piss out of
them. There's no decent ones. Decent
women don't exist. They're all the same.
They don't exist, mate. They're all the
same. I've never been proven wrong. I
have never ever ever been proven wrong.
They are all the same. And no one's
going to change my mind but them. But
they can't change my mind because all of
them, all of the ones that I have
met. Um, all the women I've met, they're
all scum. Like, every single one I've
met are all [ __ ] Scum, liars,
devious. They're all the same. They're
literally all the [ __ ]
same. They're all the [ __ ] same, bro.
Every single one of them are all the
same. That's why I don't bother. But
what's the point of talking to people
that are all the same? You know, it
doesn't make any sense. Why would you
want to interact with somebody that's
the same as someone
else? Yeah. Well, it's not easy in
London. In Pakistan, it's not easy in
London, mate. I tell you that. They're
all [ __ ] Come visit sometime. You
should come and visit
sometime. They are horrible.
New York, Boston, London, all of them
places. They're [ __ ] horrible, mate.
[ __ ] horrible scum. Scummy little
[ __ ] That's what they are, mate. Scum
of the earth.
Scumbags. Lally what they are, mate. Literally. Yeah.
But that Manchester one's getting it,
bro. She's getting it, bro. She's
definitely definitely getting
it. On uh Friday, I've had enough of
these [ __ ] I was even telling Q about
this. He messages me as well. Well, he messages back.
So they're good, bro. They're good. He's
actually good. Q is actually a real one,
bro. Despite all the [ __ ] he's seen me
say and that, he still messes
back. Yeah, cuz he's probably met me two
times and he knows what I'm about, bro. You know. So,
uh, it's just someone I met two times,
some black guy. He found me on the
Instagram thing, the post. He says, "Oh,
I know this guy." But yeah, he still
talks to me. It's
mad. But he still talks to me. So
yeah. So yeah, bro. I wish women weren't
evil, mate. Just go gay. Stop. Stop
saying stupid stuff. Nah, I'm all right. Thanks.
Another day in bed, eh? I don't think
I'm going to get out of bed
today. No, I don't think I'm going to
get out of bed today, bro.
Nah. Where's good old
Greasy? And stop calling me Pete. It's
[ __ ] creepy and weird. Stop calling
me that, you
creep. Yeah, stop stop calling me Pete
as well. It's [ __ ]
weird. God, that's so weird. You calling me
that? Yeah. I'm staying in bed all day,
bro. Call me Pete one more time and I'll block
you. Call me Pete one more time and I'll [ __ ] block
you. I will block you, bro. If you call
me Pete one more time, I'm not even
joking. It's [ __ ] weird.
Bye-bye. Easy. Easy. Stop calling me that, you
creep. No, he doesn't let me in. He
No, he's blocked me. He doesn't let me
in. Yeah, I'm going to stay in bed today
depressed, thinking of my bad
experiences, wanting to die. You know, I
thought I would have actually died in my
sleep. I've been praying to die in my
sleep, but it never happens. It never
happens. You just wake
up. He said he will turn up. Bye-bye.
You can get a timeout. Don't start weird
[ __ ] on my [ __ ] channel, you [ __ ]
brain dead [ __ ] forey
[ __ ] [ __ ] start [ __ ] on my
channel. Meet me. Oh, what? What? Kevin
Murphy will meet me when I'm in
Manchester. Yeah, nice one, mate. I've
been to Manchester 10 times and he
didn't show up then. And he also didn't
show up when I was in Liverpool. End of
conversation. Go take your brain dead
[ __ ] drama somewhere else, you little
[ __ ] All right. He's going to meet me.
He's not going to [ __ ] meet me
[ __ ] nowhere, mate. The little
[ __ ] scouse prick. He didn't meet me
the last time I was in [ __ ]
Liverpool. He didn't meet me the last 10
times I was in Manchester. So what?
What, bro? What? What?
So what, bro? Come on. What? You
know, I was messaging this person's
family last night. You know that one
from Manchester? I was messaging her
family. I was messaging all her family and
that. Yeah, I was messaging her family,
bro. Yeah. Uncle, grandma, [ __ ]
sister, brother, everything. You name
it. I've had enough of these
[ __ ] I've had enough of these [ __ ] I
really have had enough of it, mate. Like
you really don't understand enough. I've
had enough of him,
lad. I'm just messaging all her [ __ ]
family and everything. She's getting a [ __ ] Morgan
treatment. Yep, we know that,
mate. Let me message more of a family. One second.
going to say she's talking about my kids
as well. One [Laughter]
second. The mad thing is I don't even
like them and I don't even want to get
with them. It's just I don't I just
don't like [ __ ] I just don't like
[ __ ] I think they're better than
you. That's what it is.
Yeah. That's it. I hate it,
bro. I I'm a [ __ ] No
one. I [ __ ] hate him, mate. Look what
I done to that [ __ ] USA. Is he? Look
what I on to that [ __ ] Look what I
done onto that [ __ ] [ __ ] I'm
saying I hate him, bro. And imagine you
happen to do that. When you approach
people, you have to deal with that as
well. Do you know when you approach
people, you have to deal with that? Like
imagine imagine like you approach
someone and it happened. It'd be even
worse. All that time, all that
effort. They're [ __ ] absolute
[ __ ] I had some guy on Reddit tell
me to be a
millionaire. He said, "Oh, you should
try to be a millionaire. You should try
millionaire." That's what he says. Oh my
god. Yeah. I'll just go and be a
millionaire. One second. You
know, they just never blame women. They
just don't want to ever blame women. No
matter what the who it is or what the
circumstances, they just never will put
the blame on women for some reason. It
might it must they must think it's going
to get them laid by defending women or
something, but it doesn't because women
don't even like them, but they still
defend them. It's mad. So yeah.
What the [ __ ] Luminal
evil. True evil.
Yeah, he never I have and I hate him.
Yeah, I have and I still [ __ ] hate
him. I [ __ ] hate him. That's what I'm
saying. They'll defend women, but women
don't like them, and women won't [ __ ]
them. But they will still defend them,
saying, "Oh, women don't know you
nothing. Oh, they're not all the
same." Because they think by saying this
stuff, it will get them laid. They think
by defending women, it will get them
laid. But it won't get them laid. They
simp. That's all their lives are about.
You know what I'm saying?
They're [ __ ] evil, mate. They are
evil. Generally generally [ __ ] evil,
man. I wonder how they become so evil, you
know. Yeah, I'm just messaging a [ __ ] family, bro.
I say that she's touched up my kids and
everything. Yeah, I'm just going to say
she's touched up my
kids. I just create some bad rumors in it. Yeah. Isn't it [Music] It's
One second. Let me try. [Laughter]