What is this? What's wrong?
No, because you're not going to know
when I'm going to be
there. No, you won't. Mm-
Oh, so he's going to man he's going to
Manchester this time,
right? Oh, okay. Interesting. H.
So, why didn't he meet me the other 10
times when I was in Manchester the other
10 times? Why didn't he meet me
then? He's not meeting anyone.
anybody. I've been to Man uh Liverpool
once and on YouTube I've been to
Manchester about three or four times and
he's never met me. So, what makes this
time different? Huh? Where is
it? Well, I'll see him there then, mate.
I will [ __ ] see him there.
Yeah, I'll see him there, buddy.
M not even popping
up. Yeah, I'm putting up posters of this [ __ ] mate.
I'm putting a post of the Trump in
Manchester. Let's go.
Yeah, I [ __ ] hate women in this country,
mate. I hate them, bro. I was talking to
one. Oh, you can't give up at 27. I
[ __ ] mate. What do you want me to do?
Go out and get more bad experiences? How
about you [ __ ] off and suck my dick? How about that?
I'm having a conversation with this
woman about suck and
dip. She says,
"Oh, it's disrespectful that I kiss my
baby baby father after I suck his dick
and out." It's not disrespectful at all,
mate. You know where your [ __ ] dick's
been. You know what I'm saying?
Especially if you're with the [ __ ]
person. Especially if you're with the
[ __ ] person, mate.
I don't even want to talk about these dating
[ __ ] I don't want to talk about it. It's so
depressing. I'm talking to this woman. She's
right. And she said, "Oh, you're good
looking. You should find someone." And I
show her some of my approaches and stuff
and she's married and we voice noting
and she doesn't believe that I can't
find no one. And I was like respectfully
like I've given up with this [ __ ] I
don't want to talk about it anymore cuz
when I'm talking about it I'm reliving it. You
know, they don't
understand. These women don't
understand. They have life on easy mode.
They have everything given to them on a
silver spoon. They don't understand
anything about life.
And it's not even about like [ __ ] the
pass, boy. I don't want to go out. I
don't want to go out and do it anymore
because I know exactly what I'm going to
get. So that's what it is. Like looking
moving forward, I know what I'm going to
get. I don't want to entertain it anymore
here. No, we're not I'm not going I'm
not going after her. I'm just talking to
and she doesn't understand. She thinks it's
easy and we was having an argument and
she thinks stating is easier nowadays
than than it was in the
70s. But I think it's it was easier in the
70s. I think it was easier in the 70s
than it was in the than it was now. '7s
' 80s, you know.
I don't know why she fake. She's a
[ __ ] [ __ ] But yeah, she's trying to
say that it's easier to date nowadays
than it was back in the 80s when it
isn't. It's harder
nowadays. I don't want to talk about
depression. For [ __ ]
sake, it's not more accessible for now.
Not for men. It's not because women have
too many options.
I'm not going to get into it, bro. I'm
not going to sit here and argue with
you. Like, you have your opinion.
Um, like I'm not going to sit here and
argue with you. Like, this is exactly
what I said to this woman as well.
Um, I'm not going to sit here and argue
with you, bro. It's a waste of my time.
disagree to disagree and [ __ ] um that's
it. It's not accessible. It's it No, I'm
not going to explain it. I'm not
explaining it anymore. You have your
opinion. I have my opinion. I know my
experiences end up. I'm not going to sit
here and argue, bro. Telling you I'm
right, telling you I'm wrong. You
know, I'm not going to sit here
Hold me. You just slow down, woman.
You're [ __ ] married and you're
talking like that to me. [ __ ]
me. But she said, "Oh, you can't give up
at 27. I can give up. Watch me give up.
I had already given
up." Yeah. And and there was no online.
So what did that mean? Women didn't have
as many options, so it was easier
getting people. I'm not going to sit
here and and argue with you, bro,
whether I'm right or wrong. It's
pointless. I know what I'm talking
about. I live in this day and age. I've
gone out several times a week. I know
how it is
here. I'm giving up. And when you have a
woman try to tell you don't give up, I
feel like you're you're being funny with
me. I feel like you're taking a piss.
Just let somebody give up and live their
life in peace. I don't know why you want
them to get any more bad any more bad
experiences. I call that a narcissist. Yeah.
I called her a narcissist cuz I've just
told you what I've been through. I've
just showed you all the screenshots and
you're telling me to not give up. It
makes perfect sense to give up [ __ ]
trying in this
country. I didn't go out last
week. Giving up is the only way, bro.
Like, trust me.
Yeah. Nothing's going to change in this country.
Trust me. So just give up, leave, head
off. Cuz I know exactly what's going to
happen when you go out again. Here's the
thing, Joe. I know exact if I
had if there was a if there was a woman
market on in the bookies, I'd be a
millionaire. I'd predict everything that
would happen. I can predict everything
that they will do, right? And that's
it, you know, and and that's and that's
the end, bro. Like, I would be I know
exactly what will happen. [ __ ] the past.
Let's move on from the past. Let's look
forward. I know if I went out on Friday
and I went out on Saturday, exactly what
would happen. And that's not a mindset. That's
reality. It's like less It's like West
Ham losing 20 games in a row. Yeah. West
Ham losing 20 games in a row. They're
not lo They're not winning the [ __ ]
next time they [ __ ] play. Yeah,
you've got a history of it, you
know? So, that's the way I see. Might as
well give up. Give up and not even try.
And it takes me a lot to say that after
that Manchester one as well, bro, that
was the icing on the
cake. [ __ ] that. That was the last
person I was trying with as well.
Um, I thought, let me give this person a
shot. They reply back and look, they're
snakes as well. So, yeah, she was the
last option. She was my last attempt to
try and that's
it. I was like, she might be different.
She's from the north, but nah, all the same. End
of. So, today I'm proving
wrong. We're going around and around in
circles. Exactly. But bro, I didn't go
out this week cuz of giving up. I I
didn't go out this week though. I went
to meet my friend cuz he was up the road
and I thought I'd have a few beers with
him and then I got an escort. I have given
up. I have given up
though. And two weeks ago was the last
time I went in two month. I went out in
months. Yeah. Now get on the knees.
I hate him though. I actually hate him.
And when I have a woman trying to tell
me to not give up, I feel like they're taking a piss.
Yeah. Yeah. Of course you would.
Yeah. Born a virgin and die a virgin, I
guess. Story of your life, buddy. Story
of your life. You're the only one on
here that's not been seen with women. I
have. You haven't.
Story of your life, buddy. Story of your
life. Takes one to no
one. Good. Do you feel better for giving
up? Um, when I gave up, uh, I felt
better. Yeah. Cuz if I wanted anything,
I knew I could just pay for it. Like I
was into horror films and stuff. I felt better. Yeah.
Um, but obviously there is going to be a
time where I go out and drink and then
when I do drink, I do approach. But
that's like every month or every two
months. That's not really considered
trying. So yeah, you basically have
given up if you're not actively looking.
And yeah, I just feel
better. I felt a lot
better cuz I I
know that if there was somebody in this world for
you, you would have met
them. You would be with them. If they
were different, if any if they if the
women were truly
different, you would be with someone
now. So that's my whole take on it. So
you're not with
someone on the fire, you
know. Am I still? No, not
really. Not really, though.
Oh, what you doing,
mate? I'm so
bad. Sorry about
that. Yeah, she's so openly talking
about sex [ __ ] She's married. It's
crazy, bro. How is she so openly talking
about sex when she's [ __ ] a married
woman? That's a [ __ ] madness.
That is [ __ ]
crazy. Maybe when you're in your 30s,
you'll have more
uh you'll have more success. Doubt it
though. Women are all the same. It
doesn't matter what age they
are. Like I don't know why people think
when they get older they're different.
They're not. They're all [ __ ] That's
it. And they'll always be [ __ ]
But yeah, I was trying to explain to
this woman is that there's no point
trying because if you go out, all you're
going to get is I've got a boyfriend.
Um, you're too old for me. You're too
young for me. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Get a few numbers and then eventually
get ghosted and you're just stuck there
with a hangover for a few days. And I
said to her like, so what is it?
Are people supposed to Are people Are
to So, are people supposed to
um Are people supposed to go out every
week drinking until they find a woman?
So, how long do they have to keep doing
that for? How long does somebody have to
keep doing this for? Last one
before I go, you know, you know, saying
all the time about it. You see how Yuki
has done it twice. You went viral when
nothing happened. Explain. Um, well Joe,
I can explain because I've been live in
Manchester running up my mouth about
kids and no one does nothing. Explain
that one. I was at Manchester Picadilli
running up my mouth about kids and
everybody heard me. They all looked
back. They never done nothing and no one
on this community done anything. Explain
that. Yeah. As soon as I was in London,
my windows went in by [ __ ] London
Taylor. My windows went in by London
Taylor when I came to London. When I was
back in London. Yeah, when I go up
north, I ran my mouth, screamed,
shouted, and no one know that had the
balls to do anything to me. I didn't
even look back. So, I mean, explain that
one to me. Yeah. Works both
ways. Uh uh
uh. Trust me, bro. Northerners are not
about it. They're not about that life.
You know, I've I've been to Manchester.
I've run up my [ __ ] mouth. Why I talk
to him? cuz I forgive and
forget to be honest. And he seems to be
the only one on here that sort of talks
a bit of sense. [Music]
Yeah. So, yeah. So, basically what I'm
saying is like how long does somebody
have to keep trying
for? We've got some good films coming out
soon. So, yeah, I'm not I'm not drinking
anyways for don't know when when again,
but yeah, I just can't be bothered with
it cuz I I just know it's the same [ __ ]
This is the same old [ __ ] in this
country. I said I will give this person
a chance. They live in Manchester. If I
need to go Manchester, so be it. But
look, they even turned out to be the same. So
yeah, I'll believe it when I see it. I
think that's fair enough though, is it?
I believe it when I see it because we've
been hearing for years that God exists,
but we've never seen God. We have no
evidence that God actually exists. It's
the same when somebody says, "Oh, women
are different." Or, "There's someone out
there for you." I believe it when I see
it. I think that's fair
enough. I don't care about that
irrelevant little virgin, Joe. He's
obsessed. I don't care about that
obsessed little virgin. It's funny you
called him nons legs, though. At least
you know he's a nons. He's obsessed with
me, Joe. He was on the phone to that woman.
Ah, bro. He was on the phone to that
woman for 1 hour. What the [ __ ] could he be be
talking? Uh uh uh. What the [ __ ] could
he be talking about to that woman for
[ __ ] 1 hour and [ __ ] 12 minutes?
He doesn't even know me. She doesn't
Ah, that is obsessed,
bro. I'm trying to pull this thing on my
tooth. He's obsessed, lad.
Yeah, of course he was, a little virgin.
Of course he
was. Do you think it was weird what she
done, Joe? I thought it was very weird
to me. I thought it was very, very, very
weird what she
done. Spoke for [ __ ] 3, four days,
arranged to meet you, then disappeared.
Why waste your time and waste someone else's
time? Oh, lost though.
Los still wanks over Morgan. The [ __ ] sad
bastard. Well, obviously she can't say
that. No, it wasn't because of Twitter.
She didn't know about Twitter. Stop
making excuses. Nothing happened. No,
Joe. Something else must have happened.
How many times has a woman spoke to you
and arranged to meet you and then never
met you? Nah, nothing's happened because
there's there's a woman that I've
approached and there was a French one
that I arranged to meet with her and she
didn't know my name. She didn't know
about [ __ ] Instagram or YouTube. So
that's not an excuse because other
people have done that that don't even
know my [ __ ] name or knew me on
Instagram. So there was no way that
anyone could have found her. So no no
they're just [ __ ] Joe, you don't need
to underestimate or try to brainstorm or
try to find things. They're just [ __ ]
in this country, which is why I don't
entertain them. I gave this person the
benefit of the doubt because they were
texting back and I thought they were
decent, but they're not. So
uh uh uh there was a French one um from
last Thursday, not last Thursday, the
the the Thursday before that. And we was
talking. She didn't know about
Instagram, didn't know my [ __ ] name,
nothing. And then we arranged to meet
and all of a sudden she went quiet. So, uh
uh-uh. They're just [ __ ] in this
country. Uhhuh. Uh uh uh. The women in
this country are just
[ __ ] They're just [ __ ] in this country,
lad. So that's how it is. Hey.
Uh, and why do most of these women seem
to have problems as well? I've noticed
that most of these women seem to have
problems, like mental problems and all,
but no, there wasn't a reason. She's
just a [ __ ] It didn't scare her about
the hotel. I said, "I'll meet you
outside the hotel reception." That's a
normal place to [ __ ] meet. But it's always
excuses. I haven't been gambling. I
don't really gamble much
anymore. Ah. Oh, yeah. South America's a
good one as well. Brazil. Brazil's good.
Oh, yeah. Brazil's good. It's easy to
get women in Brazil. Most of the escorts
of Brazil. I've been with some Brazilian
people that were escorts as well. Yeah,
Brazil is good. It's not west. Anywhere
that's westernized is just
impossible because they all watch the
same [ __ ] But yeah.
Brazilian people are cool, man. It's
like it's self
America. Ah, this is what I'm trying to
explain to this guy as well. I haven't
typed those. Oh, this [ __ ] Good for it. Uh
uh what I was saying is, yeah, is
uh I was talking to this guy on
Instagram and he says, "Oh, what about
Australia? What about America?" No,
they're all the same. America,
Australia, Canada, it doesn't matter.
They're all the same. All the women
there are the same. The only difference
with Australia is, yeah, they might be
more nicer and down to earth, but
they're still not going to [ __ ] you.
They're still not going to date you.
They're westernized [ __ ] It's it
doesn't matter where you are if it's if
it's west if they're in the
West, you know. But I explained to them
they're different in in they're all
[ __ ] in different ways. So I went over
it. So I said, "So with the British
ones, they'll pretend they've got
boyfriends, give you mad attitude. With
the Americans, they'll give you they'll
they'll be fake nice. They'll be fake
nice with you and then uh do mad devious
[ __ ] or lie to you. And then Australian
ones will be more nicer and down to
earth and then just pretend they got
boyfriends." So they're all bad and in different ways.
Yeah. Yeah, bro.
One second. Someone sent me a voice
note. God, she sended me 5 minute
[ __ ] voice notes and all all this
madness. [ __ ] hell, woman. Bro,
you're a [ __ ] married [ __ ] woman,
man. Your [ __ ] voice know me about
[ __ ] sex. What the [ __ ]
Oh, that is straight [ __ ] autism
right there, man. That [ __ ] virgin is
so obsessing with
me. Why is this virgin so obsessed with
me, though? This is why you don't meet
somebody with autism, people.
This is why you do not meet people with [ __ ]
autism. They don't leave you alone.
You're stuck with them until until they
they're dead or in prison.
Basically, you're stuck with him, mate.
You're [ __ ] stuck with a
cat. You're stuck with him, man. [ __ ]
autism. Now he's obsessed with someone
in Manchester who I've never even met
now. [ __ ] hell. His autism gets worse
and worse and worse. [ __ ] hell.
Oh, heat this [ __ ] thing up, bro.
What you want to put up? But God, he's a
[ __ ] He is
obsessed. Would you agree to me that he's obsessed?
I don't stop going on about him. Terry,
have have you seen his
channel? He's got a channel dedicated to
stalking me every day, bro. He's the one
that don't stop going on about me. He's
literally obsessed. Do you want to see
his channel? He literally does about 100
community posts on me every day. He's
obsessed. He's He's obsessed with me and
anything to do with me. I don't stop
going on about him. Do you want me to
link you his channel? He's literally got
a channel dedicated to Peter Belly and
stalking Peter Belly every single day.
I'm literally living in his head free
regardless of uh Yeah, bro. That he
finds women you have met. He hasn't
found women that I have met. He's only
found one that I've met and the other
one [ __ ] LT gave the number. He's a
little virgin. Because he's a little
virgin that's never had sex. He thinks
that these women that I've met, he's
going to get with because he's a little
virgin. He's never had it in his life.
He's a little virgin. So, he thinks by
creeping around these women, they're
going to sleep with him. And then he
finally loses his
virginity. I keep going on about him.
Get the [ __ ] out of here, Terry. [ __ ]
terrible trainers. He's got a whole
channel dedicated to stalking me. You
might have not seen
it. He's only ever found two women that
I met. Well, no. I gave him their I gave
their details out.
But he doesn't ruin anyone's life. It it
it No, no, no, no, no. But what I'm
trying to say to you is it doesn't ruin
anyone's life cuz I've got more money
than him. I get more money than him. I'm
better looking than him. He doesn't ruin
no one's life. I've sat here and I've
explained this to you many, many times.
You're sat there being obsessed with me
every day. I'm ruining your life when
you have to come on YouTube every single
day being obsessed with me. I'm I'm
living in your head. I'm affecting your
life. Especially if somebody somebody is
in a relationship as well. You're not
ruining no one's life but your own.
Being obsessed on YouTube 24 hours a
day. The only one the only person's life
who is being ruined is
yourself. Is yourself. Bye-bye, Virgin.
You being on YouTube every day obsessed
with me, I'm ruining your life. I'm
living in your head. Think about it.
Despite what Despite what reaction you
may get, I'm literally living in your
head every day when you come on YouTube.
You people don't ruin no one's life. You
people don't ruin no one's life at all.
Not one little bit do you ruin anyone's
life. You ruin your own lives. You don't
ruin my life. You've never ruined my
[ __ ] life. Never ever. I still get
over £3,000 a month. Thousands. I'm
better looking than all of you. Got
better clothes than you. Yeah, you don't
ruin my [ __ ] life. You've even tried
people getting people's [ __ ] money
stopped. It ain't [ __ ] worked. He's
the one laughing at you, but I'm the one
laughing at him being obsessed with me.
I'm Yeah. And I'm laughing at his
obsession with me every day on YouTube.
He's obsessed with me every day on
YouTube. Does that Does that not Does
that Terry, have you got autism or
something? You're saying that he's doing
stuff to ruin my life, but he's on
YouTube obsessing over me every day.
You're winning. You are winning. When
you have got somebody obsessed with you
every day on YouTube, you're owning
them. You're doing something right
because they're doing it cuz they're
jealous of you. That's the facts, bro.
Okay. I I will I will give you this
channel right now. Okay. I Okay. Okay. I
will give you this
channel. You know he's winning. What? By
being obsessed with me every day. What?
Me living in his head? He's
winning. You keep telling yourself that.
So, somebody that is obsessed with me
every day is winning. You keep telling
yourself that. So, somebody that comes
on YouTube every day obsessed with me
being jealous is winning. That's me
living in their head. I'm winning. I've
hit the jackpot. If I'm living in
somebody's head that I've only met a
dozen times years ago, I've hit the
jackpot. I'm doing something right. For
them to have that sort of jealousy
towards me, I am doing something right.
I am doing something right. He doesn't
have me raging. He doesn't have me
raging. He doesn't have me raging, mate.
I went around these area pulling up
posters. I made him run to the police. I
made him run to the police about me. I
literally made him [ __ ] scared. He ran
to the police screaming how he was not a
fighter. I'm not a fighter. I'm running
to the police. Terry, I know we've got
selective memory on here. I had him
running to the police over
posters. He doesn't take no W. Just like
you don't take no W, you silly little
[ __ ] Just like I can sit him all day
talking about your kids and come to your
area and you won't do nothing. I can go
tell you that Terry terrible trainers
fiddles with his kids but he won't do
nothing about it. Terry terrible traders
[ __ ] fiddles with his kids everyone.
And he won't do nothing about
it. It doesn't matter. It doesn't
matter. It's because he's an obsessed
little virgin. I don't care who he finds
that I don't meet. He's an obsessed
autistic little virgin. He's been doing
it for years now.
It's nothing new about him being jealous
of women that I've met. It's nothing
new. It's the same old. No one cares.
You say it like it's You say it like
it's a new thing with this version. I've
not even met this person. I haven't even
met them. You're obsessed. Terry, you
fiddle with your kids. If you're really
about anything, you would do something
about it, bro.
And that's it, bro. Like, it it's the
same [ __ ] you do anyways, bro. All of
the [ __ ] you do is exactly the same.
It's the same [ __ ] that you do, bro.
Stalking women that I've met or not met.
It's the same old. You're obsessed. You
make yourself look obsessed every day on
YouTube, you know? And I was [ __ ]
raging at you. I wasn't raging at that
little [ __ ] virgin.