Just a quick one. Just wanted to see if
it's the same people on your
job. Same people on YouTube,
man. Listen, bro.
I'm going to make this [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] keep hearing about this Mark
Samson guy and I'm not liking it. You
know, that's why I [ __ ] made a new
[ __ ] channel to get away from these
[ __ ] M on here. [ __ ] me, bro. You're
still hearing about it.
Yeah. Wait, summer. Oh, Mark Samson
always does this during the summer.
potentials to call people out. Yeah,
he's on YouTube. Like, how many years is
this going to go on for with these
[ __ ] mongos on this community? Like,
seriously, man. Like, it's it's at this
point it's embarrassing. And you know
what? Like, I'm actually half these
people's aids as well. And even I can
[ __ ] see it. It's embarrassing,
man. And to be honest with you, man,
this Mark Samson wasn't calling anybody
out in the first place. He's just a
keyboard warrior. Why? because he's on
YouTube making videos and people that
are about that life. People about it
don't sit on YouTube making
videos, you know? It's the [ __ ] man.
Why are you even still on it, bro? This
community has nothing to offer. It's
just people in their 40s that self
project. People pretending to call
people out even though they know where
they live. Like, [ __ ] hell. Like,
when does when does somebody say to
himself, "Okay, this is it. I'm I'm off
of here now. I'm on another community.
And the fact that all grasses on here as
well, that's another thing. Like the
[ __ ] man. I don't know if you call it a day.
Crazy. People really need to learn to
call it a day on here, man. Seriously, man. You
know, and he never called anyone out to
begin with this Mark Samson because he's
on YouTube making videos. People that
are a gangster don't come on YouTube making
videos. Doesn't take [ __ ] Einstein to
figure out. He does this every summer.
Let me guess. Yeah. He had his legs out
with his shorts mentioning me. Mention
[ __ ] someone else saying he's trying
to fight everyone. Oh my god. These
people these these old these old age
pensioners really are embarrassing, man.
I feel bad for them,
honestly. [ __ ] bad, bro.
nothing better to do at that age. Like [Music] seriously, but
yeah, just to let you know, bro, like he
didn't call me out to begin with. He's
pretending to call people out because he
has people's address. Why is he making
YouTube videos? All of this stuff, yeah,
is for attention. Oh, I'm coming. This
Mark Simpson says, "I'm I'm coming. I'm
coming. I'm coming. Bro, this is all
attention seeking. We've been hearing
this now for about 3 years, 4 years, 5
years. No, I'm not back, man. I was just
like, just wanted to respond to your
email, LT, man, that I don't know why
you're still doing it with this guy,
bro. Like, I'm checking my emails
wanting important things and you're
still entertaining these
muppets. Oh, is he coming to Stratford?
Is he? Oh, that's good for him, mate.
I'm a I'm a See, this is what I'm
saying. This is exactly why I come off
this community, bro. Because of this
whole [ __ ] [ __ ] because this is one
of the reasons I come off of it. I've
been I've been building my um Well,
there's a few reasons. The grassing, the
make believe call outs, the projecting,
like loads of reasons, bro. No, I'm not
I'm not back on here, man. Just thought
Just see if it's the same people on here
as it always is.
Yeah, I don't love it here, mate. I
think you all weirdos. I really don't
love it here. I really, really don't,
mate. I've got a new channel. I done an
approach um two days ago and I put on my
new channel video the whole infield as
well. No, I really don't love it here. I
really don't. I think you all weirdos
grasses projectors. I really don't love
it here, mate. As soon as that Jamie
Thompson Yeah. As soon as that Jamie
Thompson found out my new channel, I deleted it,
bro. I deleted it, bro. I made a new
one. I swear to God, he never found me
again. Nah, it's too weird for me, bro.
It's too weird for
me. Yeah, I done an approach two days
ago. Recorded the whole
infield. I can show you. Well, I'm not
showing you the approach, but I can show
you the picture if you want. But yeah,
uh, this place is weird,
bro. I really don't love it
here. Where is it? One sec. Put it here somewhere.
This is the stuff you people need to be
doing, bro. Let me let me show you it
right now. What you need to do, you get
over your job. Get a life. The weather's
nice, man. Come on. It was even better
yesterday. You know what I'm saying,
lad? You ready to get a life?
That was me during the
infield. I was out there smashing
it. Stone cold sober as well. I got my
friend to record
it. So, um, yeah. But I mean, you ain't
really got no excuse now to be honest. I
mean, the weather's nice. It's summer.
Why are you on YouTube every
day? Why are you on YouTube every day?
YouTube, you know, you come on here, you
say that everyone's skint, I'm skint,
I'm this, I'm that. Okay. Yes, I'm all
of these things. Yes. Yes. Yes, I am.
So, why are you on YouTube every day
then? Answer me that question. I'm I'm
all ears, bro. I'm all ears. You come on
here every day. You say that people are
skin this that this that that. But you
are the ones sat on YouTube every day on
a summer's day. On a hot summer's day. I
don't know, man. Looks like projection to me.
So yeah. No, I said I come on here
occasionally to see if it's the same
people. And it is the same people. It
literally is the same people every day.
Ain't got a
life. It's so mad how none of you can
take one day off of
YouTube. Like you think it's good
entertainment. I don't think it's good
entertainment. Not this. Not Not this
community. This community is [ __ ]
[ __ ] No, no, no. Yeah, YouTube. Not
this community. Yeah. No, no, no, no.
This community bors me. This community
makes me lose [ __ ] brain cells. Okay.
Okay. What's entertaining about it?
Right. You all call other people what
you are yourselves, excluding Greasy,
right? You all pretend to call people
out, but then you get the police
involved. So, like, how is any of that
entertainment? How do you know who's on
every day if you aren't on YouTube?
Because I know you people are on YouTube
every single day. It doesn't take
Einstein. You ain't got a life but
YouTube. What do you mean? How do I
[ __ ] know? It's obvious. As soon as I
go [ __ ] live, you come in seconds on
a hot summer's day. It's not even a
community. It's too small to be a [ __ ] community.
I don't know how people can be on here
every day to be honest with you. I don't
even find it entertaining and it's
[ __ ] boring. It's full of just
self-projecting naristic glasses that
have zero and like that's that's
literally what it
is. Hey Grey, this was me approaching a
woman two days ago. Got my mate to record
it. I was slick with it, Greavves. I was
slick with it, lad. [ __ ] slick with
it. Oh, I didn't show you the new um I
come on here every day because I'm
lonely. No, that you're self projecting
again, bro. I got friends. I see my
friends every day. I go out every week.
You're talking about yourself. Lonely,
bro. I just cook some food. I don't come
on here every day. You people are on
here every day. You're literally talking
about yourself. This is exactly what I
was telling you about. You're talking
about yourself. If I come on here
because I'm lonely. Okay. If I come on
here once a week because I'm lonely, why
do you come on here every day then, bro?
You're talking about yourself. You're
self projecting, which is one of the
things we said earlier. Anyways, Greasy,
uh, I need to show you the new merch.
Oh, I forgot to show you the new merch,
bro. The new merch, bro. Look. Oh, look
at that, bro. Look at that,
bro. Look at that. Tell me that's not
sexy, bro. Tell me that's not sexy.
Tell me, bro. Look at that. Banger. Bam,
bro. Yeah, it was these people's month's
[ __ ] money, bro. Oh, and you know
what, Greasy? Yeah. When I put the first
wash on, it smelt like the washing
stuff, the comfort, the washing stuff.
The washing stuff, the comfort,
um, and the new machine all at once.
Squeezy. Imagine that. All at once. You
come on here because you're lonely and
depressed. Oh, you're talking about
yourself again. Self
projection. Talking about yourself
again. We don't have projection on this
channel. Yeah. That's why you're on
YouTube on a hot summer's day. Huh?
Yo, and YouTube on a hot summer's day,
bro. I was out for the past two days.
I'm taking a break today. I'm literally
going out tomorrow. I'm going to be out
all day tomorrow. Yeah. On the bank
holiday. Yeah. I went out two days in a
row. I'm taking a break. So, and
anyways, you coming here because you're
lonely and depressed. That's literally
your own life. Self-reflection, looking
in the mirror again, just like when you
tell people they've got no money,
they're this, they're that. It's you.
You, you, you, you. Because if it wasn't
you, you wouldn't be on here every day.
You would not be on here every day if
you had this fantastic life. Literally,
bro, I was live for literally less than
four minutes. And guess what? It's the
same people every [ __ ] day. It's the
same people. It suggests that they've
got no life, no money, and it's every
like you, this is how you build a
picture of these people on YouTube.
Yeah. They come here every year saying
that people have got no money, they've
got none this, they've got no that, but
in the end, it's themselves that they're
referring to their own lives and that's
why they're on here. Think about it.
Yeah, there's so many communities on
YouTube, so many different communities.
Why would they be on this one? It's
because they don't even fit into another
community. They're that [ __ ] hated.
That's why they come on here and trying
to troll because it's the only
entertainment they get because they're
they're loners. That's that's not me
being nasty. It's it's it's it's
spooning and spilling facts. You know,
I've just had some food. I've just got
out the bath. I put my fresh combs on.
I'm chilling today. I'm going to be out
tomorrow. I've been out the past two
days whilst these people have been stuck on [ __ ]
YouTube. Stuck on YouTube. Why you on
YouTube now? Forget it, bro. I I get it
in the winter. The winter makes sense. I
get it. I get it in the winter. You
know, it's cold. People trying to save
money. But I, you know, I've already
been out today. Well, tech I've actually
already been out today, actually. I was
out today. I was out yesterday. Done
some approaches the day before
yesterday. I'm going to go out tomorrow
sending it just drinking. I'm going to
send it whilst drinking, but I'm just
going out to drink. But these people are one
day, you know, grievy. One day I will
go. Okay. One day I will go live and
these people won't be on here. Then I'll
be like, "Okay, I'm the low life. I'm
the low life." Well, the day I go live
here and I don't see any of these people
on here, I'll be like, "Yep, I'm the low
life. I've got no life." But it would
never happen. You know what? I might go
live again tomorrow, you know, when I'm
drinking and I want to see what these
people are doing, lad. I want to see
what these people are doing. [ __ ] off.
Why does he keep doing
that? Yeah. Flexing going outside, bro.
It's a flex to you people. You people
are housebound, bro. It's a flex to you
people. You people are [ __ ]
housebound. You can't even leave your
house. So, it is a flex to you. To
normal people, no. But to you
self-reflectors, it is. Have I been
gambling? Nope. Not since the other day.
Nope. Ain't been gambling. Got plenty of
money. Going to go out tomorrow and send
it. No, I'm just talking about what you
people do, man. Why do I need to be
gambling? You know, it's just annoying
when you wake up, you look on your
emails, and you're hearing about the
same Mark Samson guy. Believe me, LT, he
never called anybody out. He never
called anybody out ever. It's all
pretend. It's literally all pretend.
This whole, oh, I'm coming to Stratford
or I'm coming to Rumford, it's literally
pretend. Literally, it's just make
believe for attention. And he seems to
do this in the summer as well. He loves
doing this in the summer as well. No, I
was just talking about you people. How you just weird? Really? But
yeah. No. Self projection
matey. Self projection
matey. Self projection. Matey.
Matey. Yeah. want to be on
it otherwise. Oh, it's hot today, ain't
it? It's [ __ ]
hot. Um, I got a new mug coming.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm normal compared to you
people. Yeah. Compared to you
people, you're haters. You come on, you
come on the internet every day hating.
You come online hating, grassing,
[ __ ] You're just all
weirdos. Just weirdos, lad. Just
absolute weirdos. Ain't got a life.
Like, and bro, I haven't been gambling.
I'm good, bro. I'm just saying. Just
weirdos, you know? People that are
double my age sat on YouTube every
day. You know, I'm not in no disabled
boat, mate. Count me out. I can take a
day off of YouTube. You people can't.
That's the difference. I can take a day
off of YouTube, but guess what? You
people can't, you know, and that speaks
to volume, I think, when somebody can't
even take one day off of
YouTube. Now, count me out,
mate. Count me out,
matey. What? What I think this community
is? Yeah, let me I'm trying to think
here. I think this people in
their late No, no, no. I think they're
past their 30s. They're in their full
E50s and they never made it in life.
Ain't got a pot of piss in sad with
their life, no confidence. So they come
on here and self-reflect because that's
the only bit of attention that they get
and they know that it's too late for
them to change. So they just come online
to try and bring other people down to
their level. And that's what people do
on here. And the grassing I can't stand
as well. That's why you don't see me on
here. It's the grassing.
So, it's it's the grassing, it's the
self-p projection, it's the weirdness,
stalkingness, you know, you name it,
bro. That's why I can't be [ __ ] with
it anymore, bro. I still live with my
mom. You don't know where I live and you
will never know where I live. Anyways, I'm banning
you. Yeah, man. See you
later. You don't know where I live and
you'll never know where I live or who I
live with. Yeah, just weirdos. That's
what they are.
weirdos. So all the hell is [ __ ] weirdos. Huh?
These clothes smell lush. I wanted to go
out today, but I said I'm going to go
out a day a week. I said I'm going to go
out one day a
week. I've got these fresh clothes on,
man. Just got out the [ __ ] shower.
Oh, these clothes are so sexy, man. They
smell so good. Oh my god. New machine
smell, new comfort, new gel. Oh my
god. [ __ ] smelling the dog's
bollocks, mate. Smelling the [ __ ] dogs
bollocks. The new final
destination. I ain't played that, man. I
know it's a
game, but yeah. Hope you're not a little cold approaching.
Anyways, I'm off to Thailand in a couple
of months anyways. I've booked a holiday. So,
yeah. Yeah. That's why it's important to
take breaks. You
see, you know, it's important to take
approaching breaks and drinking
breaks. I'm only going out tomorrow cuz
it's uh it's bank holiday, is it?
Yeah, about to catch you a little bit, eh?
Yeah, lady boys. Nah, man. That's the
plan. You just go out once a week in
this country. I could do Saturday,
Sunday, but I'm going to end up spending
like 300 quid. You might as well just
try once a week. It's the same really. I
just want to go out and drink anyways to
be honest. Need to get a haircut though. So,
Going to wear my nice um the t-shirt.
Oh, that's going to be last year. A
t-shirt. Can't beat it, man.
Sorry, there was a knock on the door.
Scared the [ __ ] out of me, mate.
Yeah, I done a cold approach uh two days
ago. Sober on the street. Sorry, man.
There was someone on the [ __ ] uh
door. Yeah. So, yeah. Oh, that's nice.
Yeah, man. Just done a cold approach. I
was [ __ ] just see I done two actually that
day. He's just around my area.
Sober doxed. Yeah. You keep telling
yourself that you
weirdo. But yeah, man. My friend recorded it.
Yeah, my friend recorded
it. Yeah, I made a new channel. I've got
like all the approaches on there, bro.
Stick. I ain't got 3,000 subs, but n
you're not watching it, mate. Sorry,
mate. None of you little weirdos see
anything that I do.
Nah, mate. Nah, I'm not showing you.
Nada. Nada, mate. You can see a picture and that's
it. You can see a picture and that's it,
mate. That was actually sober as well.
I'm going out
tomorrow cuz Saturday is in it. So, send it tomorrow
again. Yeah, it was [Music]
sick. I I'm not going to prove it to
randoms. No, no, no. Do not No. The
whole point of making another channel is
so these people can't find you and hate
on your videos and spam like and it's
just I don't want these people following
me. I don't mind going live and saying
[ __ ] I got an email about this [ __ ]
Mark Samson guy. But I'm not putting
content on this channel, man. Too many
weirdos grasses. All that [ __ ] we don't
need. That's why I don't I don't really
come on here
anymore. Once a week maximum.
That's me dumb, bro. Yeah, I got a new
channel, man. I don't know to get away from these
weirdos. These little
self-reflectors. These little
self-reflectors. I like that. It's cute, isn't
it? They won't find it, mate. They won't
find it because I've had it for a couple
of days. They won't find it. You know
how they found my other one through
Instagram? They somehow can like get
into my Instagram. I don't know how they
can do it, but since I stopped giving it
to my friends on Instagram, they've not
found it. They won't find it. They won't
find it. Trust me, they won't find it.
They found the last one because of um
Yeah, they found the last one because of
um because of the um Instagram thing.
They won't find
it. They won't find it, bro. Trust. I've
had it a few days.
I'm already getting some like thumbs up
and that from like genuine people, you
know what I'm saying, which is good. So,
got some approaching videos there, some
holiday videos there, cooking. I got
some cooking ones there, some lush
videos. So, yeah.
So do not want these
people got no subs though and he's pro
promote my channel a little bit
more a little bit. A little bit
more. You don't have
it. So what happened to the main
channel? Uh, just got banned
obviously. You don't have
it. You don't have it, mate. Cuz you
would have made it known. You don't have
it and you'll never find it. Had T-Bone,
had Chicken Phillips, chips, the lot,
mate. The lot. So hopefully genuine
people are going to find this channel
and like it basically.
But yeah, they are going to do that. But
yeah, just to get away from these
weirdos grasses, the
projectors. That's the whole point of
making a new channel. You
see, but they haven't found it. Trust
me, I know about
it. Yeah, that Jamie Thompson, he's a
he's a proper stalker. He
is just some jealous stalker that wants
to be me. Some jealous stalker that
wants to be me. He takes stalking to the next level, man. Jamie
Thompson. Yeah, it's not really found,
mate. Because it was already found,
people just started commenting and yeah,
you can't help yourself. So,
yeah. So, yeah,
man. Yeah, it's a glassing. What I can't
stand on here, it's the grassing. So
them doing this stuff, it actually tears
people away. It makes people just not
want to come on here. Like the whole
self-rejecting. See what what it is is that
they they want drama. They want to
torment people, but they will do things
that would just make people leave and
not come back. Like grassing,
projecting, repeating, all of that stuff
would just make people just not want to
come back, you know?
And I thought to myself, I was like,
"Shit, I've actually been nicked about
15 times over this website. I am done."
Literally, I'm done,
bro. Like, I was just thinking of it and
I was like, "No, that is me done, bro.
[ __ ] that." And it just repeating and
it's just toxic as well. So, there's no
point. They're just little glasses as
well. Grassing, little jealous glasses.
There's no point being on a jealous
community full of
grasses. So, how do you remember the
hotel? Yeah, of course I remember the
hotel. Of course, I remember the [ __ ]
hotel, bro. Who Who wouldn't remember
the hotel? Everybody remembers the
[ __ ] hotel, bro. So, that's why this
there's no point, lad.
Yeah, the police seem to want to get
involved when it shoots themselves.
But the maddest thing about this is
what's so [ __ ] up with this country is
that you could literally have your bike
stolen and the police won't do nothing
about it. Yet you say a few mad things
on YouTube, they're on your door before
you they can say [ __ ] before you can say
Jack [ __ ] Robinson. It's a madness, isn't
it? [ __ ] up. [ __ ] up,
man. Everyone knows. I know. It's
[ __ ] isn't it, mate? They also have
their favorites as well because it's a
very corrupt country.
Yeah, they also have their favorites in
this country as well. I've noticed that.
We're not going to get into it, but
yeah. But yeah, they they literally,
mate, they you wouldn't believe the
amount of times they have come on on
this [ __ ] dot. Literally, bro, like
you you don't even want to
know. And that's why that's another
thing as well, bro. Because like that's
why I'm like not on there trying to stay
good and stuff because if they ever come
again, I'm going to knock one of them out,
bro. And I'm going to end up going
prison. So like there's there's there's
literally no point, bro. Like there's
literally zero point of getting into
this this madness
again. Yeah, they've done it, bro.
Listen. Oh gosh. They it's like they
when it comes to online anyways like
with this online stuff they will find
any excuse to come here or there
wherever I am like any little excuse
they will find any little excuse as I'm
not giving these people excuses anymore.
Simple and that's it.
So yeah they done it a couple of weeks
ago as well they tried to take my phone.
I was a bit too fast for them. Yeah, I
was a bit too far from them and I was
like, "No, that is it, man. I can't deal
with the grassing. I can't deal with the
projection." Like, [ __ ] that, bro. But
yeah. Yeah. They tried taking my phone.
I was too fast for
him. Yeah. And then and then it's like
obviously you're not being on this toxic
community, you're not going to have have
these issues anymore. You know what I'm saying?
So, yeah. It's mad.
They literally find any excuse, literally any
excuse. That's what taxpayers need to
worry about, bro. They They need to
worry about these police. Like me, for
example, I could go right now rob a bank
and I'd probably get away with it.
What's so matter of like as an as a like
saying this as an example, you could
literally go out with a knife right now
and you'd probably you'd probably get
away with it. You'd probably get away
with it. Oh, you say something on
YouTube, they're on your door and you're
in a cell for 24 hours. [ __ ] this. You
know what I'm saying? Yeah. Or 12 hours
or whatever. You know, like that's
that's how it is. And you probably would
get away with it. That's the maddest thing about
it. They ain't got a life, man. They're
scared to go after like [ __ ] real
criminals. The system's [ __ ] bro.
Over, man. Yeah. It can stay amazing,
bro. I'm going out tomorrow.
I'm going out tomorrow. Yeah, I've
already been out the past couple of
days. I went out today as well. I'm going out
tomorrow. Put my stuff in the washing
machine and Yeah. Yeah. Nothing. I'm going out
tomorrow. No, I don't meet people on
YouTube. I'm all right.
Thanks. I don't meet people on YouTube,
especially men. Them days are done, man.
Yeah, they they locked me up over false stuff,
bro. And then I had to go back up there.
Yeah. Yeah. [ __ ] It's
mad. Yeah, I'm good, bro. Thank you very
much. Well, I'm going to meet you and
then you're going to end up being prime
and I'm going to have to head butt you
in your nose and then get myself into
more trouble. Nah, mate. Nah, mate.
And then you're going to end up being a
prime two years down the line and I'm
going to headbutt you in your chin and
I'm the one that's probably going to end
up getting nicked. Nah, I'm good,
bro. I'm good,
bro. But you can go out, man, and send it. So,
yeah. To the Andy. What? Andy guy. Who's
that? Don't know who that is. Andy guy.
Yeah. But the only mad thing about it,
when you report these people to YouTube,
at Bobo, do you know what the police
will say? Do you know Do you know what
the police will say? Oh, report it to
YouTube. Report it to YouTube. The
hypocrites seeing that, right? They'll
tell you to report stuff to YouTube or
Facebook, but as soon as someone reports
you, they're on your [ __ ] door again.
Like you don't know how many complaints
I've had to [ __ ] file, bro. It's it's
madness. It's it's it's actually
madness. But yeah, that's how you know
they're starting proper
dodge like about about the system. It's
proper dodgy. It's proper
corrupt. But they're just scared to to
go after real criminals. It's got to be
what it is, bro. It's got to be what it
is. No, we're just talking about like
the history of police on this community.
and how many times they've come in the door.
And I remember one time they arrested me for
um for um smashing up my own
door. [ __ ] hell, bro. Literally, he
for like smashing up my own door and
they tried to caution me for it as well
and I said, "Nah, mate. Take me to
court." And then they dropped
it. So, it's actually mad. Like they
actually they actually have their
favorites in this country.
Yeah. You don't know the [ __ ] I said to
them last time as well when they come
here. I said like what the [ __ ] are you
doing coming on this [ __ ] door? Like
I shouted in his face and everything.
He's lucky I didn't knock him out. And
that's why I don't want to get get into
involved with this anymore with this whole YouTube
thing. Like you know what I'm saying,
bro? like this. That's why I don't want
to get involved with this stuff no
more. Just stuff related to social media. Yeah. So,
yeah. And then when I I went to and I
went to the police station as well cuz I
have to like report this thing as well.
And I told them about themselves so many
[ __ ] times. Stop telling me to report
stuff to YouTube. I'm reporting it to
you. And if I have to come back every
week, I'm going to come back every week.
And I'm going to come back every single
week on the exactly the same day. And
I'm going to be a pest. That's what I
said. I'm going to be a pest. Stop
telling me to report it to YouTube. Go
practice what you preach. Go look up my
name. Look up my name on the system and
tell me that I need to report stuff to
YouTube. Yeah. Practice what you preach.
And if you don't know what that means,
then yeah, that's
it. You know what I'm saying? Practice
what you [ __ ] preach.
Yeah. Like literally practice what you
[ __ ] preach, bro. It's [ __ ] madness.
Yeah. So, yeah. That's what's that's
everything that's wrong with this
community. To be honest with you, I'll
give you my new channel, but you can't
give it to anybody on here. Like, not one
person, you know? Like cuz they're
actual like they're quality videos I'm
putting up, bro. You know what I'm
saying? And I don't want anything to do
with people in this community. That's
what I'm saying, bro. You
know? Okay. Well, that's up to you, bro.
But anyways, the weights, the hotel, the
5:00 p.m. wakes up. I've actually lost
count, bro. I've actually lost count.
They've actually they've actually like
made up charges as well a few times.
They've actually made things
up. Yeah, they've actually made stuff up,
too. Um, yeah, there's been a few times.
There's been a few
times. There's been a good few times
they found any excuse to come on this
[ __ ] door. And I'll say that as well
to them as well.
Yeah. Madness, bro. It's got to be about
10 15 times, isn't it?
Yeah, to be fair, I should have come off
YouTube a long time
ago, mate. They're never going to find
it. They're never going to find it,
mate. They're never going to find it.
Different handles and all that, bro.
They're never going to find it. They're
never ever ever going to find it. The
only reason they found it last time is
because they're a they're somehow able
to get into my Instagram. And then once
I stopped sending it to people on
Instagram, they didn't find it anymore.
They're not going to find it, bro.
There's different handles, different
names. They're not going to find it,
bro. They're not going to find it. Trust
me. Believe me, they're not going to
find it, bro. All the titles are different. Yeah. So, yeah,
bro. The system is definitely corrupt.
Let's put it that way. Huh? Yeah.
But what's so mad is that like you'll
say stuff to a woman, right? You'll
actually do stuff that you deserve to
get nicked for and then they don't actually lick
you. Like when no one's even said
anything back to you, but then as soon
as you do this shitty community, they
seem to want to keep coming on the door.
It's mad. This is what I'm saying. This
is what I'm actually saying, bro. You
know, this is what I'm saying.
It's [ __ ] It's It's It's [ __ ] bro. It's actually
[ __ ] Yeah. I hate this
country. You know, it's all backwards. So, yeah.
Yeah. And then they tried leaving me
without a phone
again. And then they tried leaving me
without a phone again. And I said to the
[ __ ] pig as well like don't you think
you've got enough devices that you ain't
gave back. You're not getting the phone.
You can keep looking all you want.
You're not getting it. And you should
see the the dirt. They gave me the
dirtiest look, mate. I said you're not
[ __ ] getting it. You don't start
coming into people's [ __ ] homes
thinking you could take what you want
cuz you got a silly little uniform on.
You know, trans will be the [ __ ] a
fine thing if you actually gave half the
ones you took back, which we're still
waiting for. That's another thing they
do. Sometimes they don't give your devices
back sometimes, right? They don't um
give your devices back. When they take
your devices, they don't give it back
all the time. That's another thing.
Would I survive in jail? I don't need to
answer that question because I'm never
going to jail. But anyways,
um yeah, like yeah, and and and this is
how you know how corrupt it is because
they knew by taking that phone, if they
were going to get a phone, I I've got
all my like evidence like on my phone,
literally like I've got all the evidence
of like this whole YouTube [ __ ] on my
phone and they knew by taking that
device I'd have no evidence. It's all
corrupt, you know?
It's all [ __ ] It's [ __ ] up. You
know, they knew if they took the phone,
I'd have everything's on the I've had to
literally have a whole album with like
110 different things about what these people have
done, you know? Like I've got a big like
defense in that. So, and they knew by
taking the phone, they're not going to
give the phone back, right? And then I
have no evidence. It's [ __ ] It's
[ __ ] bro. That's what I'm saying.
It's corrupt. That's what I'm trying to say. It's
corrupt, but that's the way it is in
this country. I don't think it's like
that in any other
country, but it is in this country. Death, man.
Yeah. But anyways, moving
on. Moving on, mate.
Anyways, we're not talking about this
anymore. Not talking about this
anymore. Washing some clothes for
tomorrow. Going to go out send it.
Hopefully the weather's lush as it is today.
want to go out and send the [ __ ] Yeah. [Music]
Yeah. Gary, buddy, I'm not Monty Man or
Timmy. I can see what you're doing to
mine off. If you want to be a blatant piss
taker, Mark, listen. You're taking a
piss out of me making noises, bro.
You're one YouTuber. You can't even
leave your house. Shut up. I'm not Monty
Man or Timmy.
Yeah, I was sneezing. Bro, stop it. I'm
not money man or Timmy. You can't troll
to save your life. Literally leave your
house. Leave your front door, bro, and
get a [ __ ] tan, bro. You understand?
Literally, just literally get up right
now. Leave your house for about 1 hour.
Get yourself a nice tan and come back
because this trolling thing really does
not suit you. It really don't suit you,
bro. I ain't going to lie to you, bro.
It's suiting you less and less and less
and less and less.
And you're giving me Lewis Bill Slugger
vibes, bro. Like, please stop it. It
don't suit you. You're boring. You don't
have the IQ to come on here and try to
troll a man like
me. You know, you're boring. You're
very, very boring. Literally, leave your
house 1 hour, go for a little stroll,
and come back. You're boring, bro. Stop
it, bro. Stop
it, bro. Stop it. I'm not a money man or
Timmy. Stop it. Please.
Please, bro. I'm feeling bad for you now. Stop
it. Anyways, what's your plans for tomorrow? Anyways,
people. Yeah, I might do a cheeky live
stream tomorrow for about 10
minutes. Yeah, for cheeky 10 minutes or so.
Yeah. Yeah, man.
Yeah. Why bo for 10 minutes? Because I
want to show you people what life is
about, Mark. Not being sat on [ __ ]
YouTube on a hot summer's day like you
waiting for people to go
live. You know what I'm
saying? Not [ __ ] sat on YouTube
waiting for people to go live. and
you're gonna be on YouTube. I want to
check tomorrow that when I'm live, no
one's on YouTube because your lives are
so good. I've got no life, right? I'm
this. I'm that. I admit. I'm this. I'm
that, bro. I just don't want to see any
of you on your ch tomorrow because your
lives are so much better than mine. I'm
skin. I'm this. I'm that, bro. I'm all
of these things. Yeah, I know, bro. I'm
all of these things, bro. I don't want
to see you. I don't want to see any of
you people on my live stream
tomorrow. You like coming on YouTube on
a hot summer's day? Well, that means you ain't got
life. Yeah, I do hate approaching, but
I'm going for a drink. I'm going out for
drink. Yeah, I want to go out for a
tomorrow. The joys of not being skint.
enjoys not being
skinned because I'm going out for a drink tomorrow anyways. Yeah. So,
yeah. Not at all, man. None of you are involved in
anything. Not at all. None of you are
involved in anything. Any legal things?
No, bro. Why would I do that? I've
already got enough evidence of what
people here have done. Why would I do
that, bro? Do you know how many pages of
harassment I have got on my phone? I
don't need to come on here and and get
any [ __ ] more from [ __ ] fake
accounts. Are you crazy? Like that I've
got like I've already got over 100 things. That's
enough room. Little smoke. I'm on my
break, but nowhere near 30. Got more
money than you. Try again. Yeah, I'm
nearly 30. Yeah, not 30. Got more money
than you. I've had more jobs than you.
Try again. Don't force it. Want to play
the money game? Oh, bro. Want to play
game? Please stop embarrassing yourself
because you'll lose again. Anyways, go
self-reflect on another channel. Not this one.
Anyways, well, is that what you're
doing, Slim? Yeah, I'm out tomorrow,
buddy. I'm out tomorrow for some
beers. Out tomorrow for some beer beer
calls. Beer calls, mate. Beery [ __ ]
calls. Yeah, man. I got two dates last
week, so hopefully get another two next week.
So yeah, but guess what, mate? Guess
what? Guess what? I've got friends. I
can go out with somebody as much as I
want. But at least at least I'll be out
drinking alone rather than being sat
alone on YouTube like you. At least at
least at least I'll be out alone
enjoying life alone, not stuck on
YouTube alone waiting for people to go
live like you. So yeah, man. At least I
won't be stuck on YouTube like you by
myself with no one in a in a [ __ ]
house like you. At least I'll be
enjoying the weather alone, not sat on
YouTube alone like you. So I mean I've
got that going for myself. You know what
I'm saying? It's the same as like think
about it, bro. You remember when Pat
Mustard Yeah. used to He started like
the whole thing, bro. Bro, you know how
that all started? table for one. That
all started from like hat mustard. Bro,
I'd rather be sat eating good food alone
than be sat on YouTube alone with no
money like these people. I admit it,
bro. Yeah, that's what I mean. I I I
admit it. I literally admit it. Oh,
you're out with a misses. Of course you
are. Yeah, because everyone on here has
got a miss, isn't it? Yeah, it's
[ __ ] You all claim that you've got
a misses. You all claim that you're
married. Your YouTube activity says otherwise,
buddy. Your your YouTube activity actually says
otherwise. Nah, you've got misses, but
you want every day. Well, mate, I feel
bad for you. I'd rather be out by myself
than to be on YouTube by myself like
you. Hey, at least I
admit you, bro. You people are just
little self-reflectors. If you had any
friends, you had a misses. You wouldn't
be on here. You would not be on here.
This is what I've This is what I was
saying time and time again. If you
weren't loners, if you had money, you
wouldn't be on here. There's no if, but
you wouldn't be on here every day. Okay,
let me rephrase that. You would not be
on here every
day. You would not be on here every day,
Mark. If you had money and you you had
this great, you wouldn't be on here
every day. You can say, "Oh, you like
YouTube." No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. But
you're on YouTube every day. It doesn't
look right. It's not looking right from
where I'm sitting. From where I'm
sitting, it ain't looking
right. It's not looking right, man. You
You You got to understand where I'm coming from. So,
yeah, bro. Well, at least I'll be out
there getting numbers and enjoying the
weather, unlike you. What are you going
to be doing? [ __ ] sat on YouTube
waiting for people to go live. Sat on
YouTube, low life on a hot summer's day.
Okay. Okay. Okay, bro. Bro, listen. Put
your camera on right now. Right. Listen,
let me let me let me put the link up and
put your camera on right
now. Put your camera on right this
second. Come on. Please, bro.
Please. Yeah. Put your camera on right now.
One second. You coming people, Bro,
you're laughing at yourself. Bro, I've
got You're coming to laugh at people
like you. What? Someone that's got more
money than you. Somebody that doesn't
have to work, that's got more in life
than you, bro. You're laughing at
yourself. Listen, bro. I'm better
looking than you. I've got more money
than you. You want to play the money
game again? You're laughing at yourself.
Listen. Right. One second. I think the
thing got jammed. One sec, bro. Listen.
You're laughing at yourself. One sec.
Okay, let's play this money game,
right? Come on. Come in. Come in the
hangouts right now. Why is the thing
jammed? Okay, I got to do it from here.
What's it? Bro, you're laughing at
yourself, bro. That's all you're laughing at.
My life is a ton better than yours. Oh
my god. Like, bro, if only you knew. Yeah.
Listen, bro. Yeah. I've got more money
than you. I'm better looking than you.
How can you sit there and laugh at
someone like me who's got a better life
than you? I live in a better city than
you. I'm better looking than you. I'm
younger than you. I've got more money
than you. And you could laugh at me,
bro. Stop embarrassing yourself. It's
not looking right. Everyone has seen
my£500 bed. Yeah, I was staying at a
friend's mate. I was staying at a
[ __ ] friends. And mate, even if it
was a mattress I'm sleeping on, guess
what? My life is still better than
yours. Think about it, bro. Okay. Okay.
Let's just say for argument sake, I
don't have a bed, bro. I got more money
than you. I'm better looking than you.
I'm not on YouTube every day like you.
I'm not past my sale my [ __ ] uh my my
sale by date like you show us your
money. Come here and show us where you
are right now. You're on YouTube alone
in your house. You're alone. You're a
loner. You're laughing at yourself,
bro. Show us. Show us you right here,
right now. Come on. Come on, bro. Come
on. Come on. Please. Come on. Right
here, right now. Right here, right now.
Come on. It's not hard.
Show us where you are. You're on YouTube
on your ones on your on your Jack Jones.
You're a loner, mate. I literally come
off of YouTube for one week. I come back
and you're the first one on there
because you ain't got a life, mate. And
you can't use Yeah. that it's it's
winter now. You ain't got a life. You
ain't got no money. You got nothing. But
you're talking about a [ __ ] bed.
Everyone has seen my [ __ ] bed. Let's
see your money. Let's see your misses.
Exactly. Stop it, bro. It's
embarrassing. I've got everything but a
women woman. I've had more women than
you, mate. I've had more women than you
will ever have. Stop. Another one that's
been on YouTube for four or five years.
Yep. Four or five years I've seen you,
mate. I've had more women than you have
ever had. That's again, that's why
you're on here on YouTube every day cuz
you got nothing. But guess what,
bro? I've got everything but a woman.
You've got nothing. You got no money.
You're [ __ ] stinking. You're on
YouTube every day because you can't
leave your house. I'm winning by a
[ __ ] by a by a nuke, mate. By a
[ __ ] nuke. No TV, no bed, no fame, no
money. Talking about yourself again.
Self projection. Talking about yourself
again. You're talking, bro. Do you want
to play the money? Okay. Okay. Do you
want to play the money game
again? Okay. Do you want to play the
money game again? Do you want to play
the money game again and get beat again?
No woman, no friends, no job. Are you talking about
yourself? That's self projection. You're
You just described your own life. Stop
talking about yourself, old man. Stop
talking about yourself, mate. You're
talking about yourself. I've got more
money than you will ever have. Stop
talking about yourself. No, bro. You're
literally talking about your [ __ ]
self. Stop talking about yourself time
and time and time and time and time and
time and time and time again. You want
to get embarrassed again?
Do you literally want to get embarrassed
again? Do you want me to show you money
and embarrass you again, you little
keyboard warrior? Okay, I'm going to
embarrass you again. One second. I'm
going to go to the ATM and I'm going to
embarrass you again.
One second. Where's my uh There you go.
Second. Let me move my mic and I'm going
to have a big [ __ ] laugh at you as
well. One second.
two seconds. I'm going to the bank now
anyways. Oh, you know what I can
actually do with a beer today actually.
Let me own these little clowns
again. Oh, do you know what? I thought
[ __ ] it cuz it's Friday. Let's just [ __ ]
with them, bro. It's a is it? It's
[ __ ] aces, mate.
Literally. Yeah. Stop talking about
yourself. Stop talking about yourself
every day, mate. Stop it. You're
bouncing. Sort out,
man. Good boy, bro. Good
boy. Anyways, I'll be right back. Two
sex. Bye-bye. One second. Two