All right.
Okay. Go, son. Just want a
beer. Oh, [ __ ] it. Let me have one beer.
[ __ ] hot out there,
mate. It's [ __ ] hot,
man. Yep. Don't want anyone seeing me
this end up getting [ __ ] robbed.
You literally will end up getting robbed,
mate. Ped and mate.
Yeah. Yeah, man. On a Guinness. I'm not 10 minutes
later. Right. So, I'm going to show you
how these people in
here are nothing but old age pensioner self-reflectors. Five. Seven.
Yep. And I
want There you
go. Look how it rubbed
me. But I swear I get I swear I'll get robbed tonight.
[ __ ] You could have probably put 20
pound on the [ __ ] fishing frenzy. So
anyways, back to you little self
projectors, right? Before I get into
this, you always want to keep coming
online talking about people that you
don't know. Oh this, oh that.
And I tell you respectfully, yeah, don't
come on my [ __ ] and start [ __ ] trying
to troll me because you're not [ __ ]
good at it. Yeah. You're not good at it.
You can't troll to save your life. Yeah.
You don't know people's life. You don't
know what people have. You don't know
what people don't have. You understand?
Like you're strangers on the internet.
Yeah. That's literally all you are. So,
hold on. Let me just let me just start
with the old legs. Yeah. Look at these
sexy legs, bro. Actually sexy though.
Why is it all this way
then? That's the right way, isn't
it? It's like here. Hold
on. Seems to be like opposites. Anyways,
on a Guinness, what is wrong with this
camera? On a Guinness, that's the money,
right? I want to play the money game.
There you go. You got a stack there,
right? Took straight out from the ATM. I
want to see your people's money now
since you want to come online every day.
Call the people's skin. Oh, this
person's skin. That person's
skin. Talking about people that you
don't know. Come on, let's see your
money. Let's see all your money. Come
on, let's see your money. You got me out
like a [ __ ] drinking [ __ ] beer. Come
on, let's see your money. Come on. I'm
the skint one. I'm the skint one. I have
nothing. I'm the skin one. I've
literally had to like max out my [ __ ]
ATM [ __ ] withraw. Let's see your
money. Come on. Let's see all of your
money. Come on. Come on. You come on
here and you call people skin. Yeah.
It's £200. Yeah. Anyways, come in and
show us your money. Let's see all your money. Come
on. Show us your money, boss. Come
on. Come on. Come on. Yeah. 200 pound.
Yeah. Yeah, it's 200 pound, bro. Yeah,
it's 200 pound. Yeah, bro. You people
have got nothing in your lives. That's
why you sit on YouTube every day trying
to troll people. But here's the thing.
You're not even good trolls. You're just
skin little low lives. Skint little
nobodyies that come on here every day
cuz you ain't got nothing. Yeah, it's
£200, bro. Count it. It's
£200. It's £800 quid. Yeah. Simple. You
just come on here and you just said,
"No, it's not £400. It's £800.
Yeah. No, it's £800. Yeah. Pip is lush.
Yeah. That's pip, isn't it, Grezy? Yeah.
Even though I spent £300 on a washing
machine. Huh. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's
pip, isn't it? Yeah. Okay. Yeah. That's Pip, though.
Yeah. It's £800. Actually, they didn't
let me withdraw no more. You just come
on here. You called me skin. I've had to
withdraw this money again, and you can't
show me nothing. Bad, bad, bad, bad, bad.
When will you people just stop
embarrassing yourself? Sad, sad, sad.
Honestly, sad, sad,
sad. Bad news, bro. Thailand's been
cancelled. No, it ain't been cancelled,
mate. It's already
booked. And that's the thing, Grezy,
buddy. It's not Gy. It's
£800. Yeah, it's
£800. Obviously, I got more, but it
didn't let me withdraw anymore. That's
my limit. What did I
[ __ ] Going to play some fishing frenzy
with 20 pound. I'm only doing 20 pound and that's
it. I go for a beer and yeah, man. I'm
only putting 20 in, but I put more than 20 pound
in. I'm not putting more than 20 pound in. [ __ ]
that. If we win, we'll stay out. But I'm
going out tomorrow. Yeah, that's £800.
Done. It didn't let me withdraw no more.
You come on here. You call me skin. Why
can't you show me nothing? Because you're
self-reflectors. You're self
projectors. You ain't got a life. You
talk about yourselves every [ __ ] day.
You come on here and you talk about
yourselves every day. Look, you've just
been shown money again. It doesn't
matter about the [ __ ] amount. You've
been shown money yet again and you can't
show me nothing. It's typical with you little
self-reflectors. You've been doing it
for years now on YouTube talking about
yourselves. Self-reflecting [ __ ] trolls.
Low lives. You can't even troll either.
You You suck at it as
well. So, yeah.
Right. I'm putting 20 pound in fishing
frenzy and that's it. If I win, I'm
going to stay out. If I don't, then I'm going out
tomorrow. Anyways, let's see your money, bro.
Anyways, brother, let's see your money.
You come on here and you said that I'm
skint. Yeah. Let's see your money. Come
on. Yeah. No. Oh, is that your excuse?
Yeah. No one carries cash. But you
people are all the same. [ __ ] little
trolls. Skin ain't got nothing. You You
are all the same on here. All the same
skinn little lives. I've noticed that
with this community. Yeah. You've all
got the same excuses. You've got nothing
in your lives but skintess and YouTube.
I'm telling you, bro. That's all you people
have. No one carries cash. Well, go get
some [ __ ] cash. I've just withdrew
cash from the ATM, mate. Some people
have got a limit of a [ __ ] thousand.
Exactly. Yeah. You're just skint little
old age pensioners. You self-reflect
your lives onto other people. Sat on
YouTube on a summer's day. You got no
money, not a pot to piss in. So, you
[ __ ] come on here trying to [ __ ]
troll other people. You ain't got a life
though. That's the thing. You ain't got
a [ __ ] life.
ain't got a [ __ ] life, mate. Well,
these people's calling me well. To show
that you're not skin. To show that
you're not skin. Come on. Exactly. Cuz
you people are skinn, man. Skint than a skin flin.
Anyways, odd frenzy. Now, you know what?
When I'm playing it, I'm not even going
to put the camera on to entertain you little
weirdos. You know what? I might go out
today, actually. [ __ ] it. What's day
today? Friday is it? Maybe.
Maybe I might go out today, you know.
Still Was it Friday? What's What's the time though?
What? I might go out today, you know. [ __ ]
Yeah. You know what? I feel might do it
today, you know,
still. I might go out today. [ __ ] it.
mate. Listen, stop trying to [ __ ]
troll people. You're bad at it. Shut up.
Yeah, I'm going to send it today. I'm
going to go to the barbers after this
fishing frenzy. I'm going to go to the barbers. Yeah.
Right. Sorry Barbers. Going to [ __ ] a
bit and then just get on the piss. Yeah. [ __ ] it.
What's Friday? Is it? Yeah. [ __ ] it.
Right. Let's win on Let's get a bonus on
you, Frankie. Come
on. I don't think
so. Oh, you
can't. Yeah. Get a big win. Ain't going to happen. Come on.
Nah, bonus. Come on.
Don't you just seem so
valuable when you have some drinks? E. Hey,
Zippy. Any got man? No. No.
I even got one [ __ ]
cheese. No, I'm offering£60 and go suck your
mom. I'm going to get my hair done and
send it to her.
Right. I'm going to try one more. [ __ ]
it. Come on. Oh,
I'll try one more 20 and I'm done. No. That'll be
40. We'll put more in. Come
on. It's not having none of it, is
it? Put more than 40 pound in. Need to
get my head on and
[ __ ] Not even a sniff of a bonus. I
think I've had one tease, I
think. What the
[ __ ] I don't know.
Yeah, bro. Again, I'm not money, man. Or
two. Stop it. Come on.
No bonus. Might even get a [ __ ] bonus
on it. £40 and no [ __ ] bonus, eh? [ __ ] joke,
mate. Not even one bonus. Nah.
Mood swings are coming in
again. Nope. Not even a
bonus. Three more spins. Not even a
bonus. One more spin. Not even a bonus.
£40 and I didn't even get a bonus.
Nothing. Not a
sausage. But one more pocket. That'll be £60. Oh
god. This is bad news, bro.
This is the last one I'm doing. 60 [ __ ] grid.
Yeah, I need to go get my hair done and
I'm going out sending
it while the weather's still
good. No, I'm done, bro. 60 pound in 400
pound. At least I can try and like 40 more in
it. This is a joke,
lad. Nope. Down
to10. Well, I'm going out today. Sending it
anyways. Come on. Not even a bonus.
Ain't even got a bonus out of 60
pound. But you win some, you lose some.
So they say,
I think we'll keep happening in to
ourself cuz uh we kind of has to stay
out in it. It's not having none of it,
mate. Look, it ain't having none of it.
Look, 60 in nothing. It's ruining the
whole day. It makes you not want to do nothing now.
Like, bro, stop trying to troll me. I'm
not Monty, man, or Timmy. I've told you
this about a million
times. Just ruins the whole day, in it.
And you can see the amount of money I
have like that I showed with me. It
ruins the whole
day. It ruins the whole
day. You know what I'm saying, bro? It
actually ruins the whole day. It just
makes you just not want to do nothing.
It just ruins the whole [ __ ] day.
Am I the only one that feels like that,
bro? Like, it literally ruins like the whole
day. I swear down, it ruins the whole
vibe the whole day. It doesn't matter
how much money you have. Secular slot, if you're
listening, it ruins the whole vibe the whole [ __ ]
day. Yeah, I don't care. Good for
them. ruins the whole day in it. It
ruins the whole day. I feel like I'm not
the only one that thinks that. It
literally ruins the whole vibe and the
whole day. Whatever you got going on, it
ruins it. It does. It literally
does. It ruins the whole vibe, the whole
day. It literally
does. It literally ruins the whole vibe.
the whole day. £60 and not a single
bonus. But you can win sometimes. You
can win sometimes. So they say, but 6
months and no winner here. Don't know
about any of you people, but I'm 6
months and not a single win. But you can
win. You can win on it sometimes. Think
of the garments. Think of the garments.
All the times you won garments. So they
say, but six months and not a single winner.
winner. But I guess it's just unlucky
the eighth month now. So they say. I say
that sarcastically. So they
say. And here's the thing, Mr. B, right?
They seem to think just because you've
got money, this is literally like 1% of
my money, bro.
Yeah. 1% of my money. They seem to think
just because you've got money, you got
your bills paid, whatever. it's okay.
Everything's fine. They seem to think
that makes it okay because you haven't
lost a lot of money or or because
um you haven't lost all your money.
People seem to think that it's fine. Oh,
it's okay. You know, you into him, you
that's their whole outlook on it, bro.
It's it's not true cuz look, you just
see it right now, bro. You just see it
now. Am I lying, bro? Am I lying? You
just seen it right now. Am I lying, bro? No. See
They seem to think just because you have
money or because you've lost 20 pound 40
or it's not a big amount of money. Oh,
it's okay. At least you're not skin.
That's what people seem to think when
it's no, bro. Like, you don't know what
I feel like doing with this class. Like,
that's what they don't
understand. That's what they don't
understand. They seem to they they don't
seem to comprehend these things. They're [ __ ]
idiots. Anyways, I'm going to go put
this back and [ __ ] Don't have a
haircut. So yeah, we're going to do today instead,
bro. [ __ ] me, man.
Yeah. What is it, Monty? I'm just
drinking some beer, man. I went on two
dates last week. I'm just going to go
get my haircut and [ __ ] send it again
today. [ __ ] hell, mate. [ __ ] hell.
I'm going to have to sit on that [ __ ]
Bob Barber chair for [ __ ] an hour.
Wish me luck, mate. A whole [ __ ] hour
just to hear the same [ __ ] about
boyfriends. [ __ ] this. Bad enough, mate.
Yeah. Might as well down this off. Might
as well down the pint in it.
Yeah. One sec. I can't do the I can't do
the box. It doesn't let me.
It doesn't let me do it,
bro. How do I do it? I need something
back in it or
something. One second, Monty. Hold
on. Not one
feature, but it's just gambling, so they say.
What do they say?
Yeah, it doesn't matter, mate. I've
still got more money than you and I have
more money than you and I'm better
looking than you. That's fine, bro. And
I'm going to be getting some women
today, unlike you. And I've got more and
I've got more money than you as well.
£60. I know, bro. But guess what? I got
more money than you. And that's my life
made up, mate. That's fine, bro. I don't
care if that's if that's your Friday
made up cuz I'm going out cuz I've got
money and I'm not housebound and skin
like you. That's lovely, mate. And my
Friday is going to be made up. Hey,
later. 60 sheets gone. That's fine, bro.
60 nothing to me. Not like you skin. You
skin bastard. You can't even show me any
money. You You skinned little [ __ ]
So, I don't care bro. It's fine. It's
still good in the hood, bro. But guess
what? I still got more money than
you. Yeah, my day is not ruined. I'm
going to get my haircut. Going to get my
haircut, pull some women. Something you
can't do cuz you're ugly and you got no
money. Yeah. Something that you can't do
cuz you got no money. You're going to be
sat on YouTube with no money. With no
money, no woman, no friends. I'm going
to be s I'm going to be out there
drinking, pissing up with the money that
you don't have. With money that you
don't have. Lovely. Gly with money that
you don't have. I've got a funny laugh
in it. Yeah. I love it, mate.
could have got it done with that, mate.
It doesn't matter, bro. I've got more
money than you. My my You know what? You
know what's made my day? That I've got
more money than you and I'm not YouTube
dependent like you. That's what I love,
mate. That's what I [ __ ] love.
Yeah. Anyway, see you low life later.
I'm going to be live later. Anyways,
you're still going to be on YouTube cuz
you ain't got a life. You ain't got a
pot to piss in. You ain't got nothing
but YouTube. Anyways, I'll be right
back. See you
later. Skin all whipped.