No [ __ ]
[ __ ] Where is your boyfriend there? he again? [Music]
Thank you forever [Music] Man, man [ __ ]
What a [ __ ] [ __ ]
What a [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah, mate.
That's what it [Music] is. Bro.
Yeah. London's the hardest city. Telling you. [Music] the whole
city. I'm going to start sending it again, brother. [Music]
Where's the terri clever
guy? Victoria, mate. It's been all
[ __ ] day, buddy. It's been all
[ __ ] day, buddy. I got a boyfriend,
bro. And I'm far approaching. I
got I got
one. You're speaking to this [ __ ]
stunt over there. She was saying she's
from [ __ ] Germany. Okay, I'm from
Germany. And then she's, "Oh, I got a boyfriend."
[ __ ] the West, buddy. I'm from Thailand.
I'm coming to
Thailand. I'm going Thailand. I'm going
Thailand. I can't deal with this no
more, bro. My [ __ ] enemy, all night,
bro. All night.
You're my boy, bro. It's been all
day. Yeah. Listen, I love you much.
Yeah. I had one woman say to me, "She's
married and she's 16."
I was laughing at it. She said she's
married, but she's [ __ ] 16. How does
that make sense? You ain't 16. You're
wear Come on.
Yeah, bro. Victorious being
you. I victorious.
Victorious. Victorious. Listen.
Victorious. 700 lb t-shirt. Bro,
listen. 700 lb
t-shirt. 150 g. Talking about trainers,
bro. Man's got over bag on his body,
bro. Imagine that. Over bag on his body.
I'm still getting these women feel
better than me. And bro, I London's the
worst [ __ ] place for it. Victoria,
I'm telling you.
Yeah. I got one
number. Yeah. One [ __ ] number. One
number. One [ __ ] number,
bro. Six approaches, bro. Yes,
buddy. I'll be on it all night. Will I dance and
[ __ ] Come on, [ __ ] Come on. Yeah, I've already [ __ ]
bro. You want me to do this one here,
bro? I'll be sending it all [ __ ]
night. All [ __ ] night, bro. All night
long. These two guys laugh at me, mate.
I talking about
Westhead. Oh, okay. You beat me to it then,
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
I think they're with them.
Let me get this drink. Let me get this [ __ ] drink. [Laughter] [Music] Sorry about
her. I'm going to be sick on the table. [Music]
Let me I'm going to be thick on the table.
What's your name?
Filipina. What's your name?
Thank you so much. Yeah. Hello. Where from? London.
Unfortunately, I get
Oh, come on,
buddy. You give me a glass then. Go. Can
I get a glass of
beer? Any beer? Any beer? Any
beer? Any any beer. Anywhere. Any
open it as well. Okay. Excuse me.
What's her name? Huh? What's that? Finger
asking how old you
think. How old is you? No, you're
not. Hold it.
And how old?
I'm older than you. Yeah.
23. I'm 23.
I take that as a confidence.
Bro, I'm 27.
That's obvious. Normally people get
started, right? So say
Yeah. Like I'm definitely not 23 100%.
So you got a boyfriend?
She does. Everyone's got a boyfriend. I
need to get myself a boyfriend. Do you know anyone?
No. No. If you have like a guy number
the men you go for [ __ ] Not every man.
The men that you go for [ __ ]
Give Give me a guy's number and I and I
want a boyfriend.
No. No. No. Give me some guy's number. I
want a boyfriend. Yeah.
No. No. No. No. No. No. Any any guy. Any
any guy. Any guy.
No. No. Obviously not. Give me know your
make believe boyfriend and natural guys.
Yeah. Give me give me a guy's number and
I can't. No, I just want any I want a boyfriend.
Why you have to know so many people?
But you said I was 23. I take out,
mate. They're [ __ ]
thick, mate. Oh my god,
man. They're [ __ ] [ __ ] I've got
no game. I've got more game than you,
bro. I've got more game than you would
ever have. You little keyboard warrior.
Stop talking about
yourself, bro. Hey, notorious. They said
they thought I was 23. All right, big
up. They said I was They thought
23, bro. I got no game. I got more game than you,
[ __ ] They It ain't about how
games are. It's the fact that there's
too many stuck up [ __ ] in this
country, bro. There's too many stuck up
[ __ ] in this country. That's what it
is. It ain't about your game, but I'll
shine them up. You see me now [ __ ] all
[ __ ] Wait, wait, wait,
wait. Victoria, listen.
yourself. Talking about yourself
again, this is [ __ ] up. Adrias, bro,
this is [ __ ] up, mate. They've all got
make believe [ __ ] boyfriends, bro.
[ __ ] Bro, did you just see me?
I'm socially awkward. Never been
socially awkward in my life. Talking about yourself. So, so
good. They've all got Makebelie
boyfriends. Little [ __ ] Bro, notorious mama.
You see me go over and sp and speak, bro. Yeah,
bro. There's a lot of Makeel boyfriends going up.
They be going a bit deeper still, [Music]
won't I? I need to go in P. What's that?
[ __ ] gave me a fear of [Music]
blood. How you doing,
boy? How are you, man? You're good. Nice, man. [ __ ] me,
bro. I I've got like,200 lb on my body,
bro. And I still got people think
they're better than me. Imagine that. It seems it one
sec. I got one, but it's not enough. But
man's been out. Yes. [Music] Forward. [Laughter]
woman say hi. I said I knew this woman
say hi to her. What's your name? Huh?
Where you from? [Music]
You live in London. How you finding
it? She live in East
London. Where in London do you live?
T that's actually [Music]
so what's your plans for what's What's up,
I knew you was in guest west. You got to be
west. I got two numbers so far. I'm I'm
going to I'm going to send
it all night. All night all [ __ ]
night. Yeah, I got two. The more you go
deeper, the more you try [Laughter]
up easy on the Yeah, I would have Done. Thank you. No server.
All right, buddy. [Music] Yeah.
Where's it going? Left
B. Left B. Beautiful. [Music] Oh, all done.
Sounds like a
spaceship. Of course,
how are you going to come to a club and
have No, no, no. It's my friend.
You're getting drunk in it.
Not bad. Yeah.
where you are with. Yeah.
Where you from, man? Where you from?
Southeast. What about Richmond? Southland. Yeah. I
went I went I went to [ __ ] Brixton last
year. 10 years ago. You speak dodgy
about that. 10 years ago have been stabbed. Yeah.
Yeah. 10 years ago you'd walk and it was
dodging. It was dodging.
Nowadays I get I get the tube into
station every day. Yeah. And what I'm
full of like I'm in a sink like I've got my
bags. How do you say you're
crazy? You're crazy. It's safe. You said
that you're a crazy [ __ ]
That's a goddamn You're a
crazy I'm going
to just get a glass of tap water.
That's all right. I tend
to love it. Can I get a double while I'm cutting double? picture.
Yeah. Hey, honey. [Music]
£30 for [ __ ] drink.
30 [ __ ] back for two numbers. Two
numbers. [ __ ] 30 for one. 135. [Music] two
numbers. What's it
That's a good part. What's that?
Screw it. Screw it. [Music] Goodbye. [Applause]
phone. He don't know where I
am. He don't know where I am. Good
luck. Yeah, good
luck. Anyways, I'm good.
I got some more in a bit.