I
up. Big up. Big
I've got four numbers. I got four
numbers. Big up.
Yeah. Big up the boss, mate. I'm the
man. I am the [ __ ] boss. Phone numbers. [Music] What number? Hello. Four numbers. Four
numbers. Four numbers. Four [ __ ] numbers. Big number.
Big by myself. Got four
numbers. It's a [ __ ] front.
on your next ball, buddy.
Hey, I'm going to stay here for like
five more minutes. I'm [ __ ] doing
it. Get in there, [Music]
you big it. Hang it.
I got four. [Music]
Hey, all four [Music]
Okay. Just tell us some [Music] for a Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I got four numbers. I got four numbers. Four numbers.
I got four numbers. I'm going to do some
more. I'm going to leave
here. I'm going to do a couple more when
leave. 41. 41.
I got four, bro. Four [ __ ] numbers. I
really got somewhere else. I'm going to [ __ ]
off. Do one more. Just [ __ ]
off. [ __ ] mate. Oh.
out of three months. Three
months. Three months. Three
months. You got these
self-reflectives saying that I'm [ __ ]
socially awkward. I've never been
socially awkward in my [ __ ] life.
Self projected these people self their
own lives. You got life for
you. It's vod. It's w
Hey, I'm out here. I want to keep it
moving for 4%.