[ __ ] hell,
bro. Not even a sore loser. I'm just I'm
just saying that it's it's [ __ ]
rigged. Why the [ __ ] would I be a sore
loser over losing a 20 pound football?
I'm telling you that they know where the
money is. That's not being a sore loser.
That's telling you how the [ __ ] it is.
Why the [ __ ] would somebody be a sore
loser over 20 pound? But because I'm
telling you my opinion. So my opinion
makes me a sore loser. There is no way
in [ __ ] hell Not count was it not
county scored on the 91st minute. It's
not possible. It's rigged. You can call
people that saw a loser all you want
over 20 pound. I'm not
bothered. I'm not [ __ ] bothered.
[ __ ] 20 pound,
bro. Yep. It's rigged as [ __ ] They know
where the money is. It's just like that
[ __ ] fishing frenzy. It's the same as
that [ __ ] roulette. It knows where
the money is. And this was only a 20
pound bet, a double both team to score
no draw. And it still affects your whole
entire body and your whole mind.
Literally, it [ __ ] well does. It's
no, it's no different to playing
roulette or any any other thing. It's
[ __ ] annoying as [ __ ] And it's not
being a sore loser either. No one needs
to be a sore loser over 20. We have
enough money, you know. Stop blaming
everything but gambling and keep saying
that it's gambling because it's not just
gambling. And look, there you go. It's a
20 pound [ __ ] football bet, you know?
It's something more than just gambling.
You know, we've been hearing this excuse
now for months upon months upon months
upon months upon months. It's something
more than that, you know, and I've been
saying this for months and months. It's
something more than just
gambling, you know. There you go. That
was a 20 pound [ __ ] football
bet. That was a 20 [ __ ] football bet.
say the amount is
irrelevant. The amount is irrelevant.
This is a good example.
can fix the [ __ ] It's like they
purposely know what you're betting on.
There you go, bro. I only put 20 pound
on it and guess what? I got um [ __ ]
they scored on the 90th minute. [ __ ]
the whole bet up. It was looking so good
as well. But yeah, it's rigged. So, they
know where the money is. Of course,
there's no way, bro, cuz look when you
don't bet on these things. Yeah, it
never ever happens. I'm getting them
[ __ ] dirty, suicidal, nasty thoughts
again. And it was only 20 quid. It was
only 20 pound as well. Guess it wasn't
the um the quantity of money all along
then, was it? Cuz people used to say,
"Oh, like you gamble um you know more
than you can afford to lose." I just
gambled 20 pound. I can afford to lose
20 pound. I feel like killing myself
literally. And there's no underlying
issues either. It affects your whole
body and your whole mind. If anyone
would would be able to understand this,
but it seems like no one understands it.
All they tell you is it's just gambling.
You win some, you lose some. That's all
they say. They That's literally all they
say, which is why we bend off the
machines. So, we thought today we'll put
a 20 football bet on and we'll be safe.
I feel like literally killing myself,
you know? I feel like [ __ ] hanging
myself. It's not just gambling. I'm not
buying it anymore. We've heard this time
and time again. These excuses. It's
gambling, mate. Win some, lose some.
We've heard this before. It's boring
now. And this was only a 20 pound
football bet. It's ruined my whole body,
my whole [ __ ] mind. I I I can't I
want to go and eat now, but I can't keep
still cuz it's [ __ ] winding me up as
usual. [ __ ] winding me up as usual.
This [ __ ] gambling always winds you
up. It This is what I tried to say to
people. It controls your whole body and
your whole mind. It literally does. It's
so [ __ ] annoying. It doesn't matter
that it's 20 pound, bro. Who gives a
[ __ ] It doesn't matter that it's only
20. It's not the amount, it's how it
makes you feel afterwards. God, I'm sick
of explaining this over and over and
over again. It could be 5 p. It's not
the amount, it's how it makes you feel.
It literally does. It controls my whole
mind. Literally, bro, it's so [ __ ]
annoying. Like, if I could explain it to
you. Yeah. It's so bastard annoying. It
doesn't matter whether you can afford to
lose it or not, you know?
It's not a loss. It's a loss because you can
literally you can um cuz you could I
could literally give £300 to someone and
it wouldn't bother me, you know? It's
[ __ ] rigged as [ __ ] mate. Yeah, I
had um both teams to score, either team
to win. Yeah, Harriate, Harington,
Fleetwood, and Knox County. And I think
Knox County scored and [ __ ] it all up
on the 90th minute. Yeah. But it's just
gambling, mate. Win some, lose some.
I've been hitting that now for months
over and over and over and over and over
again, you know.
You know what I'm
saying? Do you not understand that I
have to keep saying this over and over
and over and over and over again? It's
not the amount of money. It's not the
amount of money. It's not the amount of
money. I don't know how many times you
have to explain this to someone. It's
not the amount of money. It could be £10 or
£10,000. It's irrelevant, mate. And at
the end of the day, yeah, even if it is
you being a sore loser, you can't
control how it makes you feel. It
controls your whole body and your whole
mind. This is what I was saying to this
this guy. You can't control how it makes
you feel. You literally can't control
how it makes you feel. And this is what
I'm trying to say.
It doesn't matter if someone's got more
money than someone. It doesn't matter.
Well, let me let me explain it. Let me
explain this. Listen.
I was just about to go for a [ __ ]
curry as well. It doesn't matter if it's
only £20. It's not the amount of money.
I'm sick of saying this over and over
and over and over again. It's not the
amount of money. It's not the amount of
money. Numbn nuts. Dummy. It could be
£10. I'd still want to kill myself. It
doesn't matter the amount of money. It
doesn't matter that it's only £20. The
amount is irrelevant. It could be
£10,000. It could be 10 p. Simple. It
affects your whole mind and your whole
body. The amount is
irrelevant. [ __ ] hell,
lad. But how many times you have to
explain stuff to these [ __ ] retards
over and over and over and over and over
and over and over again. It controls
your whole body and your whole mind. It
literally does me. Like I can't even go
up I literally can't even go up the road
now and get what I need to get because
it's [ __ ] winding me up. I'd probably
end up [ __ ] beating someone up on the
[ __ ] street or something, you know?
It was literally a 20 football bet. Uh,
not really. Got a few numbers. Didn't
really go anywhere. I don't really care
about that anyways. My passport's
renewed now or getting renewed.
Yeah, I probably just will stay in bed
and be depressed all day probably when I
do finally go out and eat because that's
how gambling gets me. You laugh at it
and this is why I I put the losses on on
the channel because you laugh at it
because you don't think someone's
serious. It literally affects my whole
life. If I lose 10, 20 pound, I'll do a
U-turn and go to bed no matter it. It
gets you that way. That's what I'm
saying. It literally gets you that way,
you know. And the only reason I did not
go back into that shop yesterday, I'll
tell you the truth, I didn't go back in
that shop yesterday and [ __ ] smash
that guy in the head with a [ __ ]
hammer because my mom said that if I do
it, she's going to find out and she's
never going to talk to me again. And my
friends were like, "Leave it. Leave it.
Leave it." So I was like, "For their
sake." Again, over gambling again. It
doesn't matter the amount. It's
irrelevant. Losing it doesn't matter
what amount. It's irrelevant.
[ __ ] Indian as
well. Yeah, trolls watch me lose. But
guess what? I've got more money than
them and I'll always have more money
than them. And I'm better looking than
them as well. I'm better looking than
them and I've got more money than them.
So, who's the one that's really losing?
them in life. So, put it that
way. Me, bro, lose, mate. I've got more
money than it will ever have. Do you
understand? So, does it really
matter? It does. It affects your whole
body and your whole mind. This is what I
was saying to this guy in the shop um
the other day before he started being
dodgy and that I said it affects your
whole body and your whole entire mind.
It literally [ __ ] well does. It
literally [ __ ] does. When you're
watch it doesn't matter about again I'll
repeat myself. It's not about the amount
of money. It could be £10. I'll repeat
myself again. It doesn't matter the
amount of money. losing on it is
degrading. It's horrible. It controls
your whole body and your whole
mind. Yeah, you always lose. But guess
what, mate? Guess what? I've got more
money than you will ever have benefit,
boy. How about that one? I've got more
money and I've had more women than you,
bully victim. How about that one? You
little bully victim. And I've got more
money than you and I'm better looking
than you. And it kills you and I love
it. Go [ __ ] your mom. I love seeing you
people skint on benefits on YouTube.
Ugly as [ __ ] Ugly as [ __ ] on benefits
every day on YouTube. I love it, mate. I
love the fact that you're all on benefits
skin. Yeah, not today, mate. I lost 20
pound on a football bet. I feel like
killing myself, getting them mood swings
again. Yeah, I got let down on the 90th
minute and I'm getting them suicidal
thoughts again. I was actually okay
today actually as well before I gambled.
Um 20 pound actually. I gambled 23 pound
today. I had three pound change and I
put uh I I done some draws and these
people keep saying oh it's only 20 pound
it's only 20 pound the amount of money
is irrelevant it's how it makes you feel
I don't know how I have to explain this
many many many times many many you
literally can't control it's like it's
something in your body degrading you
laughing at you it's horrible it's
horrible and you can't and you can't
switch it off either it controls
controls your whole body and your whole
mind. Surely that's not entertainment.
Doesn't matter what your [ __ ] mouth is, you
know? Yeah. I feel like killing myself,
bro. I feel like getting that knife and
slit my wrists. I'm not going to lie to
you, bro. I feel like getting a rope
out. And I was fine before I gambled
today. And it was only £20. It was only
20. I didn't touch the machines. I'm
done with them. It literally makes me
want to take my own life when I lose. It
literally does. It literally does. Like
I will be fine, completely fine. As soon
as I put my money on that table again
and I lose, I get suicidal again. This
is why I don't This is why I don't do
this [ __ ] anymore, bro. I lost 20 on the
football. I feel like killing myself.
Yeah, I done two football bets today.
Accumulated to 23 pound. Lost. Feel like
killing myself. I literally got let down
on the 90th minute as usual. As usual.
Does this Antman not understand that you
can't help how it makes you feel? Do you
not understand? This is what I was
trying to explain to this guy in the
shop. 200 is nothing to me. It's how it
It's like you're being degraded. It's
horrible. It literally literally is. I
thought I would have been safe with a
football bet today. £23. It literally
controls your whole [ __ ] mind. It's
like you've got a twin. It's like you've
got a twin living inside you and you
can't switch off. It doesn't not it's
not about the amount of money. It's it
the amount of money is irrelevant. I
keep saying this over and over and over
and over and over and over again. I keep
saying this over and over. It's not the
amount. It's how it's getting you and
how it's making you feel. You know, it's
get it gets you like that,
bro. Yes, bro. I've already explained to
you and you are the manta. Yeah, we all
saw we all saw yesterday when I put my
camera on, you little manta, that I'm
better looking than all of you. So why
don't you stop calling yourself a manta,
you little bully victim. Why don't you
[ __ ] off your little YouTube bully
victim on benefits? I get more money
than you and I'm better looking than you
will ever be. You little benefit boy.
Bully victim. You are the m off YouTube.
That's what you need need to change your name to,
bro. You know these people don't
understand that it's not about the
amount of money. I've explained this
about a million times and they still
don't understand it. I've repeated
myself over and over and over again. I
will I will literally explain this,
right? And they'll be like, "Oh, it's
only 20 quid." They don't understand.
They don't understand. You know, no, I
do learn. No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. I do learn. I do learn. I do
learn. That's why I don't play the
machines anymore. No, no, no, no, no,
mate. I do learn. Why do you think I
only learn the football bets today? Oh,
I done two football bets. You know, I do
learn because I've not touched the
machines since that day. I said that was
that that that's going to be me gun for
a month and I meant it, you
know. So, I am actually done with the
machines and I said that for that month
as well. We're not talking about the
machines. We're talking about these
football bets, you
know. Yeah. You're never going to get
Fanny in London. I got my passport
sorted anyway, so I sent that off. Yeah,
it's London. It's full of [ __ ]
You don't understand that it's not
about£20. I will give £500 to a homeless
person and I wouldn't give a [ __ ] You
don't understand. It's not the quantity
of money. Do you not
understand? You know what I'm
saying? Yeah, I do it because what else
is there to do on a [ __ ] Saturday? I
went out drinking yesterday. I'm [ __ ]
bored. Yeah, I know what you mean.
Whatever, bro. You can't win every time.
I've not won for months. How about that
one? Yeah, we've heard that one before.
You can't win every time. It's just
gambling. You win some, you lose some.
Mate, it's not just gambling. It's
something more than that. By the time it
hit December, it's something more than
that. Get the [ __ ] out of here with it's
just gambling and you can't win every
time. Suck my dick. My dick goes hard
every [ __ ] time. How about that one?
Stop [ __ ] using that as a [ __ ]
excuse, mate. We've been dealing with
the same [ __ ] since November now. Just
bun it off. Allow it. It's annoying.
Yeah, we know. You know, it's just
gambling. You win some, you lose some.
We've heard all of this before. It's
boring out. Um, I done a double both
teams to score. I done a double both
score. Again, it's not about the amount.
It's not about the money. I've just
explained to you about a million times
how it's not about the money. And you
keep talking about 20 quid. You know,
you're talking about the quantity of
money. Again, when we've been over, it's
not about the quantity of money.
Yeah, bro. But guess what, L J? At least
I'm not in my 40s. Four I no driving
license, no misses like you. Yeah, she did
reply. I'll just 20
pound. I'll tell you teams. I don't
double both teams to
score, you know. And the women's [ __ ]
doesn't make it easier either.
Yeah. More like it fuels negativity. Eh,
that's what gambling does. It fuels
negativity. That's what it does. You
know what someone told me before years
ago? No, they did score. I done a double
both teams to score. Aon and I can't
even remember the teams, bro. I think I
put it here. But
yeah. Yeah, of course you are. Anyways,
I'm blocking you, Spacker.
Yep. Uh, what was it? Oh, here. No.
Where is it? Where is that football? Ch or
something. Yeah. Well, basically Knots
County scored and we didn't need them to
score and they scored.
So, yeah. No, I'm not turning out like
that, Slug. I'm telling you how it is.
But then you go back again and say, "Oh,
it's only 20." Doesn't matter that it's
only 20 pound. Losing on it is
annoying. Losing on it is [ __ ]
annoying. You should have to accept it.
It's [ __ ] annoying. It fuels
negativity as well. There's a guy on
YouTube years ago. His name was um it
was just both teams to score no draw and
one drew on the 90th
minute. It was Aquentin and who's the other
one? Oh, [ __ ] sake. What was the other
one? I can't remember, bro. Yep. Oh
yeah. Can't even remember,
bro. You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. So, yeah. His name was uh Big
Cheese. And he said to me that gambling
fuels negativity. That's so right. Oh my
god, that's so true. Doesn't it fuel
negativity? Even with football, it
literally does. Doesn't it fuel negativity?
Doesn't it? Doesn't
it? I'll show you what it was. I'll show
you what it was. I think the football
bets are downstairs. One sec.
Okay, I'll show you what it was cuz I
can't find a
best. Probably dash somewhere to be
honest. You know why I still do it? Cuz
I was born on Saturday and I wanted to gamble
20. I thought it was only 20 but obviously not. So it
says I'll tell you anyways. I tell you
uh where is it? Okay.
So Harriet and Aquinton and Fleetwood
and Fleetwood and Knots County are done
on both teams to score on no draw and
they were both 2-1 and the 90th minute
Knots County made it 2-2 and it [ __ ]
the whole bet up. It was actually
looking good as well. Ah
[ __ ] No, I'm not going to tell him
nothing. And the women shit's been
pissing me off as well, you
know. No, they're not good, mate.
Yeah, it's gambling, so they say. Yeah,
I got a few numbers. Yeah, but only two
replied, but I even messaged one back. But
yeah, I spent like £500
yesterday and I got my passport done
this morning. So I couldn't even go out
today even though I wanted to cuz I
ain't got a passport. I was like, "Oh,
if I win this football bet, should I go
out?" And I've remembered I can't go
out. Do I think it's rigged though? 100%
I think it's rigged. One million
million% I think it was rigged because
isn't it mad how whenever you do double
both teams to score no draw, they both
score? Nope. Not at all. I gambled today
cuz I was bored. No, it wasn't because
of women. I don't care about women. I
women, mate. Well, it [ __ ] is rigged.
It It is rigged. But this is this is
what I'm saying. Gambling fuels
negativity. It makes up negative things
in your mind. That's what gambling does.
It's not win some, you lose some. That's
a load of old
[ __ ] No, the issue is gambling.
Because if you didn't gamble, you
wouldn't have these problems.
Well, how is it rigged? Because it is
rigged. Yeah. I What do you mean nobody
would gamble if they had a date? Of
course they would. I gambled on a date.
You [ __ ] spacker. What are you [ __ ] talking
about? Okay. I'm a sore loser. Antman
says, "I'm a sore loser because I'm
telling you that it's rigged." Okay. I'm
a sore loser. I lost 20. Oh, wo is me.
I'm a sore loser, bro. I lost 20 pound. Okay, bro. Yeah.
It's not about it being a form of
entertainment. But what these people
don't understand is they think because
it's a low amount of money, it shouldn't affect
you. Nah, I'm all right. Thank you,
mate. I'm good. I'm going to be
depressed today. I'm probably going to
have a curry then just go to bed and
stay in bed. It's mad how gambling can
affect your whole mind, even when you've
got money. It's mad, isn't it? It
affects your whole mind, your whole
mood. Did I pull? Um, no. I got four
numbers. Two of them replied, but dead
basically. Don't really care. Doesn't
matter if it's only 20 quid. Again, I'll
explain it to you again. Listen, it's
not about the money. Okay, let me let me
explain this to you again. Has anyone
used to play
FIFA? Yes, no one forced you to gamble,
but it shouldn't make you feel like
that. Why is it making you feel like
that? Anyways, it's not about the amount
of money because has anyone ever played
FIFA? Yes, I used to play FIFA and I
used to smash up controllers and
everything. Yeah, I I went through about
five controllers like and we didn't bet
money. So, it's not to do with with with
money. You don't like losing, you know.
If you're somebody like me that don't
like losing, you shouldn't gamble, you
know. Simple. I don't like I just hate
losing. It fuels
negativity. You know, that's what it
does to me. Maybe most people not like
this. You can't compare the two. Um,
actually, you can. Oh, [ __ ] off rat
face. You ratface bastard with a fat
ugly girlfriend. You're a rodent face
bastard. Where was your money yesterday?
Get your money out, rodent face. Get
your money out, grand a month boy.
Listen, I spent £500 yesterday, Sean. I
spent half of your monthly benefits. Get
your money out, rodent face. Show the
lads your money that you don't have.
Woo! You [ __ ] little rat. Get the
money out for the lad's rodent face.
Bring your fat ugly girlfriend. That's
my That's my meme for Sean. Sean calls
me uh calls me a big nose and I call him
a ratfaced ugly [ __ ] with a fat ugly
girlfriend. The fat ugly skint
girlfriend. I'm skinn mate. I showed you
over a grand yesterday. Virgin boy.
Virgin boy non spy on a grand a month. I
showed you over a grand yesterday,
buddy. I showed you well over a grand
yesterday in the pub. Where's your money
rat face on a grand a month? You are
skinned and you are balding and you look
like a rat. You're a bold, ugly,
disabled, autistic rat. You're a
diagnosed, bold, ugly, [ __ ] rat face
little virgin. That's what you are.
How's about that one? You're an ugly
diagnosed disabled little rat. Like
you're [ __ ] nons dad. You rat face
[ __ ] I'd rather have the nose of
[ __ ] Pikachu than look like a [ __ ]
rat, bro. Don't you think it it um you
don't understand why you've not had a
woman? That's normal. It's your ugly
face. Your ugly face scares them away.
Do you remember that time in Eminem shop
when you got rejected by that Spanish
woman? Mate, I told you it's the ugly
face. When When you Bro, when you first
come on it, Yeah. you thought I was
trolling you. I said it's the ugly face.
You scared them away like the [ __ ]
[ __ ] shovel, mate. Yeah. Three years and
you still ain't [ __ ] her and you're
still a virgin and she's still disabled.
You've been with your disabled woman for
three years who has never gave you any
sex. Congratulations, buddy. Bye-bye.
You're banned. Anyways, come back when
you can show money, rat face. You little
rodent. You little rodent face with no
teeth. You ugly rat. Ugly rat
boy. Ugly rat
bastard. You know, see, see, the thing
is, I can say loads of things about you.
You look like a rat. Your face looks
like it's melting. You're balding. You
got [ __ ] big [ __ ] ears. You look
inbred. You know what I'm saying? Nose
of Pinocchio. Why does it say Why does
Pikachu? Pinocchio. That's the
one. But, um, back to Gamblin. So, it
doesn't matter if it's 20 pound. I don't
know why you seem to think, "Oh, because
it's only£20. Oh, it's
fine. It's not, bro. That let me down for
£150. And I could have done with that
£150. I have enough money, but I could
have done with it. You know, I went out
yesterday. I tried. I didn't come back
until like 3:00 in the [ __ ] morning.
I had to pay out for a [ __ ] passport.
I could have done with it, you know? I
could have done with that 150 [ __ ]
quid. It's a It's a £350, bro. Who's
turning that away? You
know, come on, bro. It's
£350. I could have done with that, mate.
It's free money. No, I don't want another
go. Yeah, I don't still do it though. I
don't still do it though because I don't
do the machines anymore. I don't do the
machines anymore. What else do you want
me to do on a Saturday? I'm [ __ ]
bored. I'm [ __ ] bored. It's Saturday.
I'm bored. I don't play the machines
anymore. I done it the other day. Yeah,
cuz it was the first time in a month. I
thought, "Fuck it. Let me just have a go
on it." Yeah. You can't class that as
[ __ ] gambling, bro. Come
on. Doesn't matter about the money.
Listen, let me explain. I I I'll tell
you how you know this is not about the
money. I'll tell you how you know this
is not about the money. Right? And I'll
explain this again. Yeah. You can give your mom
£300,400. I don't need a job. I get enough money.
Yeah.£300,400. It won't affect you. You
can lose £10. It makes you want to kill yourself.
So, it's not really about giving someone
money, is it, mate? You know, we bought
a homeless person, five guys before.
It's not to do within money. It's not to
do with the amount of money. Yeah. I
don't know why you keep saying that it's only
20. Your problem is you don't like
losing. End of. It doesn't matter what
the amount is, you do not like losing.
Yeah. So, you should not be gambling.
End of story. You can't control how it
makes you feel. Don't do it. Simple.
Simple. Yeah. Well, mate. Yeah. And do
you know what? It's not No, no, no. Do
you know what? It's not even necessarily
that you've lost. It's because you keep
It's because you keep losing. If you had
won and then lose, I'd be, okay, well, I
lost. But you don't ever win. It's lose,
lose, lose, lose, lose, you know.
Bye-bye, rat face.
you little rodent. Ugly rodent. Anyways,
yeah. So, yeah, I forgot what I say now. But
yeah, you you shouldn't gamble basically.
Simple. Yeah, but I won't be going out
drinking for a month now anyways. So, I
did study it, you [ __ ] idiot. I was
studying it for a few weeks. Why do you
think I came so close to
winning? Look how close I was. 90th
[ __ ] minute. You know, I was studying
the [ __ ] teams and that doesn't mean
anything anyways cuz football's so
unpredictable that you can't study
football. Yeah. Okay, you can study it
obviously, but you do realize that
football is very
unpredictable because I've been watching
their past few games. I've been studying
them and their defense. But yeah,
ugly rodent. Yeah, I remember Sean. I'm
not going to block you. Do you remember?
No, no, no. I actually find you cute. If
you don't find Cheryl Cole, you're
attractive. You're you're um you're gay.
You're a little copycat. You little
copycat. I said that to you as well. I
said that to you when I met you. I was
like, you're just copying people. You're
copying people. You literally would not
say that if her name wasn't Cheryl Cole.
You was literally Do you know what it
was? You started that trending Sean
because people thought you was gay and
you are gay. So you thought by saying oh
sh people wouldn't think that you're gay
anymore that it was to cover up the fact
that you're homosexual and to cover up
the fact you thought by saying that oh
she's hot she's your gay no um then then
people wouldn't think that you are [ __ ]
homosexual you can't even say rodent
correctly mate listen you're diagnosed
with autism get the [ __ ] out of
Yeah. Yeah. I lost about 15 times in a
row in them machines. Yeah. But we're
done with them machines anyways. We know
what them machines are about, man. We
don't play them anymore. [ __ ] the
machines. We're not talking about the
machines. We're talking
about We're talking about
[ __ ] Yeah. His college friends
thought he was gay. That's why he
started the Cheryl Cole thing. If you
don't like Cheryl Cole, you're gay.
Because he wanted to fit in. [ __ ]
loser. He only liked [ __ ] Elvis
Presley because he was a [ __ ] non.
He's got no originality whatsoever. He's
just copying. That's just copying. Think
about it, bro. I've had more women than
him and that Sher Cole is ugly. She's
[ __ ] ugly. And it's nice to have my
sexuality confirmed to me by a ratfaced
[ __ ] virgin that's never stuck his
dick in nothing. Yes, I'm gay, bro. Okay. Yeah. Yep.
Yeah. Got starved by his mom. He said
that Shevel Cole thing to fit in. She's
not [ __ ] attractive at
all. She's not fit. She's [ __ ]
stinking. She's [ __ ] stinking,
mate. People used to say she was fit to
in. I lost £300. And guess what, mate?
I'm on three times more than what you
get a month. And that's what's lush. I
spent half of your monthly benefits
yesterday. That's [ __ ] lost. That's
[ __ ] beautiful. That's absolutely
lovely. And I didn't lose 300 pound
yesterday. I actually lost 280. So, uh,
yeah. Um, and that was actually the
other day. But guess what? I still get
more money than you. And I have more
money than you would ever get. More
women, better looking. So, try again,
buddy. Bye-bye now. You're on a grand a
month, mate. I swear to God, I spent
about £500 yesterday. I'm not even
joking. [ __ ] grand a month. a [ __ ]
thousand pound a month. Nah, that's not
enough for Peter Belly's um lifestyle.
Who's going to pay for the Stone Island
baby goes, the Stone Island
jumpers? She's not She's nowhere near
attractive as people make out she is,
Joe. She's nowhere near as good-looking
as people make her [ __ ] out to
be. No [ __ ] way.
I was thinking of that guy from Scotland
again, that Tam from Glasgow. I really
need to find him,
bro. It's going to be very hard to find
this guy, but I reckon I could do it.
I'm going to search for him on Facebook,
even if it takes me like 3 hours to be reunited with
Tam. But she's nowhere near as as
good-looking as what people say she is.
She's about a six. She's about a six out
of 10. She's nowhere near as as good as
what people make her out to be, mate. Trust
me. Nowhere [ __ ] nowhere
near. Um, just to have a pint in
Glasgow, you know, just to have a little
pint in in in Scotland with him whilst
we were a little
kill. He's the one that got away, mate.
I hate the one that got
away. Are you the same? I hate the one
that got away. What did you think of
that burger, Joe? Did you watch the
burger video of me eating that
burger? It almost [ __ ] killed
me. It almost [ __ ] killed me. Did you
watch that video,
Grezy? Oh, imagine baby Peter from
Scotland wearing a little
kilt. A what a lovely
sight. Yeah, they wear skirts in
Scotland. What's What's wrong with that?
Yeah, I will never find him,
mate, because my his number was on my
other phone and it got
stolen, mate. It almost [ __ ] killed me,
Grezy. People thought it was funny. It
almost killed me. I got four numbers.
Yeah, but the guy that I was with, he
didn't get any. But we was doing
approaches together. I said, "Hold my
hand." Once he once he holds the hand,
we go over there and we send it. I said,
"Hold the hand of Peter Belly. We're
going. Let's go, son."
Yeah, we're [ __ ] going, mate. We're
[ __ ] going, bro. One second. Oh, the
link. Yeah, I'm not letting Virgin on
Virgin Sea on. But yeah, anyone else
like Timmy and that Baz, they can come
on if they want.
Yeah. No, not held my hand like that,
but I pulled him over to come and
approach, you know.
Yeah, you are the na, Sean. You are the na. Bye-bye
now. Am I sure? I'm not bent. Uh, yeah,
sure. No, that that almost killed me,
bro. When I had to sign that thing, I
was like, okay. Um, I'm going to go for
Vindaloo in a bit as well. So, but
Vindeloo is nowhere like that. Nothing
like that, bro. That was mad. But it was
the world's hottest thing. the world's
um thing. So they say
hello. Hello. Yeah, you
just [ __ ] not count let me down for 150, bro.
What? Did you not score? No. No, they
did. It was a double. It was a double
both teams to score. Either team to win.
Yeah. Both the teams was 2-1 and Knox
County scored on the 90th minute, making
it 2-2. The [ __ ]
[ __ ] hell, lad. And that's what's so
annoying about I think if I just lost it
outright, I would have cared. But like,
bro, I didn't need £150, but I could
have done with it. You know what I'm
saying? Like it's it's money. You know
what I'm saying? You know what I mean? I
know. I'm just [ __ ] just saying, bro,
just don't turn out like slug, bro. Don't be
living and everything, bro. Why? I would
never turn out like him, bro. Come on
now. He's only 20 quid, but still like
he he would gamble the shirt off his
back, bro. I know. Was I Was I in here
yesterday [ __ ] with with Slug? Yeah.
I showed him over a grand and he didn't
come. He didn't He didn't um Oh, yeah.
He showed [ __ ] £400, didn't he? Yeah.
And I showed over a grand. Did you see
it? Yeah. I know. He's a Mong, man.
Yeah. I just don't I just don't turn out
like [ __ ] Sim, bro. Guys, could you
could you live off a grand a month? Nah.
No. [ __ ] a grand a week, lad. Yeah.
You can't I spent £500 yesterday. You
know what I'm saying? No. Do you play
them [ __ ] fruit machines that Tim
plays in the [ __ ] like bongs and
that? N bro.
He's a dick.
There's no money in the industry
anymore. He plays 25p a play, you know.
Yeah, bro. Did you Did you Did you watch
that burger video, bro? It was [ __ ] hot.
Oh, no. Oh, it was mad, bro. Yeah, it
was mad, bro. That's why I thought I was
going to die.
I'm not I'm quite new to this [ __ ]
like community, bro. But [ __ ] Did you
meet Timmy and some other geyzer?
Yeah, years ago. What? For a fight? No,
I went to meet him normally and then
Timmy just showed up. I didn't plan to
meet Timmy, but he just came along
anyways. Well, did he start throwing
gigs and that? Um, no. They just they
didn't do nothing. When I met them, they
were just we just went on a we just got
on the sniff in it. Oh no. [ __ ] Timmy
was saying he battered you and put you
in a [ __ ] No, he No, he come he come
he come here with Tiger, bro. I took
Yeah, that was another time. I beat them
both up, bro. The video's there. He
couldn't even He tried to kick me. I
Bro, I held his [ __ ] leg.
What? Did he throwing kicks again? Was
he? That's all he does, mate. That's all
he does, he just throws [ __ ] karate
kicks. Yeah. And then I catch him. I I
remember I was walking I was walking up
the car, bro. He tried to kick me. I
walked up the car and held his leg.
Have you not got the video? No. So I can
put on channel full video. No, there's
clips of it on channels. You can
probably find it, but not like the full
video. No. [ __ ] he's actually
throwing kicks again. My god.
I'll link it to you. The burger video.
I'll link it to you. One sec, bro. Uh
slug whack. Is he mate? The [ __ ] embarrassments.
See, he just follows me everywhere I go.
How How often do you go drinking in
Liverpool city center?
Um, don't know.
[ __ ] a few times a month. Like I got
a beard and I so I can't really [ __ ]
go. Do you actually do you actually go
to the city center though? Like Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. The women are stuck up there
like London, huh?
Sound here, man. London. Night City,
lad. Have you been to I've been to
Liverpool once but Yeah.
Yeah. No, I haven't. I not been London
like never. No, it's part How old are
you? 30. Okay. I'm 27. Yeah, I've been
to I've only been to Liverpool once. It
was like on a Monday, but yeah, I went
drinking and that bro I went to I went
to the the lobster pot, bro. It was
[ __ ] disgusting. that stinking there,
lad. Oh my god, bro. It gave me the
shits and everything. I remember it. I
was staying by the Travel Lodge. Yeah.
So, there's a Travel Lodge and then
there's a sea and then once you go
across the sea, you're like the the
wheel. I think you know that by the sea.
Yeah, that's what I was saying. [ __ ]
that lobster stinking, bro. It was £25
for a night. I thought, [ __ ] it. Ain't it? Yeah.
Get any beers like? Nah, bro. Nah, not
not like [ __ ] that. No, Newcastle's
the best bit. I live in Newcastle. That
That's good. Glad that's own you. Slug
stuff going on,
mate. [ __ ] slugs in the chat making a
P of himself.
Yeah. Yeah, he always does, man.
I can't believe you. You gamble in it. Yeah, man.
Yeah. It's bad, don't it? Horrible, lad.
It's bad, man. But anyways, I need to
go. I'm going to go I'm going to go for
I'm going to go for a curry. I'll be
back later, but I'll be back live around
9 or something. I'm sorry, lad. Wait,