Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Yay. Oh, last night I stream today and
I'm off this [ __ ]
again cuz uh if you stay on here Yeah.
literally longer than two
days. I swear you actually become like
one of these bongos. Like I'm not even
joking, bro. You actually become like
one of these bongos. No [ __ ]
bro. Yeah, you actually become like one of these
people. I'm trying to find out where I was drinking
yesterday. These people really do I
really feel bad for these little sados
on YouTube. These little low lives. You
got to feel bad for
them. You have to feel bad for them, bro.
Oh [ __ ] They ain't got a life to stand
on, do they? Bless them. That's why they
come on there every day. Got to bother
people cuz they got a life. Yeah, they
ain't got a life, but you do. And then I
got like people just [ __ ] writing
[ __ ] about me. So I said, all I said
was, "Bro, respectfully, don't try and
troll me like I don't know what you're
trying to do. I'm not Monty Man or
Timmy. like they're proper like just
they're proper just bongos on here in it
really except for Notorious but actual
bongs but and I swear now you see the
same people on here that you've been
seeing for years as well like that
terror terror be that's the guy that
tried saying oh if you go to uh
Southeast London oh I'm going to see you
and you see the same people you see the
people. Why do they even say that
they're going to come to me yesterday?
Bro, I told them you don't know where I
am, but if you do, come. I'm waiting for
you. [ __ ] proper mongos on this
community. Proper proper proper life losers, you know.
Yeah. And again, they got shown money,
couldn't show me anything. Uh, isn't
that isn't that always the case with these people?
Is that not always the case with these veteran
people? Anyways, that's my effort
done for the week. So,
yeah, about six numbers. [ __ ] those.
But yeah, I'll be out
on Thursday, baby. Next
Thursday. Sat on a [ __ ] I [ __ ] sat
on a [ __ ] chair for an hour. [ __ ]
that. Crazy, bro. I hate getting my
haircut. It's boring. Been sat on a
chair for 1 hour. Boring.
But if you don't do something once a
week, if you don't have anything to look
forward to once a week,
then you know what do you
do? You know, I'm off in a couple of
months anyway. So I I I just look
forward to going out once a
week. Yeah. So that's how it is.
But you definitely hear a lot on Fridays.
imaginary boyfriends. Always Fridays you
hear it you hear it more on Fridays than
you do on
Saturdays. It's crazy, but it's just
something you have to put up with when
uh you go out,
unfortunately. Yeah. When you go out,
unfortunately, that's just something
that you're going to have to deal with
in this country.
So, like that's just the way it
is. It is what it is really. back. But two
uh but two weeks ago definitely w me up.
Definitely definitely w me
up. It was two weeks ago cuz it wasn't
last week, was it? No.
Hey, see Mark, how you doing, bro? I
went out yesterday with a
piss. Got five numbers. Hopefully some
of them reply, but I I ain't text them
yet. Bro, seaside Mark, bro. Wish I was
your age, man. [ __ ] hard to pull nowadays,
buddy. Oh, bro, I was out on the piss
yesterday. I was sick. [ __ ] I had to
get off the train and be sick. I didn't eat
enough. Yeah, I didn't eat enough,
bro. Yeah, I should have ate more. I
didn't eat enough. That's why you always
are supposed to eat a lot the right food
before you drink. Otherwise, I never
drink when I sick. I've never I'm never
sick when I drink. [ __ ] So
yeah, I should have ate more, bro. No, I
ate before, but I just didn't eat enough
or the right food
rather. Yeah. What I'm going to do today
is probably have um uh I'm probably just
going to have a Vindaloo and just
[ __ ] I'm just going to have a V. My
stomach weren't empty. I just didn't
drink. I just didn't eat
enough. My stomach wasn't empty, but I
just didn't eat eat enough. But
yeah, I might do a football. I don't
know. I don't know. Should just put that
60 on the football. I know. I lost
[ __ ] loads of money yesterday. Didn't
like hearing about that when I went to
bed, bro. That's [ __ ] up.
a football match. No, I
bet. No, I'm not doing a
football. You could do it. Could
do cuz I like
£40 like cash cuz of
um where you [ __ ] do it. I
mean if I win a football bet I'll go back out
today. If I won't
simple go back out. I don't think I can
go back out today, man. I didn't line my
stomach up properly. You don't line your
Happens later. Let me see the football
light up. Hold up.
Yeah, I had to [ __ ] fork out for a
[ __ ] washing machine. This [ __ ]
There you go. I bought a washing
machine. I'm showing money. These people
still say you're scared. They
self-reflect, lad. These people see
Mark. They're self-reflectives. They say
that you're scared. You're socially
awkward, bro. These people just live to
hate. These people actually live to
hate, bro. the these people in this
community, Mark, bro, they used to do it
with you as well, buddy. They used to do
it with [ __ ] you as well,
man. Yeah, I got an escort yesterday,
got on the pierce, got
takeaway, spent near enough probably
with a whole football, I probably would
have spent about £200 to be fair.
They're just repeaters. They just self-reflect.
That's all they do to see Mark. They
used to do it with you as well, bro.
They envy anyone that's got a better
life than them. Like, I showed these
people money again yesterday for the
millionth time and they still can't
show. They just they're just self
They're just self projectors. That's
literally that's all they are, bro. Self
projecting repeaters. Ain't got a life.
Can't get off of
YouTube. That's that's all they are,
bro. You see the same people, Mark,
that's been on here for years. the same
people you you see on
here. I might do a football bet. I don't
know. Is Swindon playing? I always bet
on Swindon, but I don't know if they're
playing or not. Yes, they are.
Yeah, I think I'm going to do a football
bet. Let me
see. Yeah, I think I am, bro. [ __ ]
it. B both seems to
score. So I got I like better than
William Hill, but there's no William
Hill [ __ ] around me on
42. Not worth it, is it? It's not
worth it. 90
quid. What is it? 90 [ __ ] quid. Yeah.
Um, what is it? 90. Yeah. 92.
Um, no. I can't be bothered,
man. I I meant to be saving, bro. That's
the thing. I meant to be saving. I
already went I already went a bit. I
already went a bit, but like I'm just
going to get text numbers, get a nice
takeaway, and then just chill out till
the next one.
you know, I kind of went sort of over
and I got my hair done as
well. Like it's [ __ ] up. No, I'm not
I'm not going to do it for like that.
It's a point. And there's no point put
20 pound on because they're not even
going to come in.
So, absolutely [ __ ] pointless. Unless
you stick 70 quid on it.
Um, I don't
know. I don't know, bro. [ __ ] What?
What is it? What is
life? want to do a big football
bet. Not a big big one,
but supposed to be some kind of [ __ ] down.
[ __ ] Yeah, bro. I'm going to do a
football bet, I think. [ __ ] it. I have
not done one for ages. It is bank
holiday, so and I'll be in it.