[Music]
Yo, be sleeping. My people be sleeping.
Oh, I'm [ __ ] tired, mate.
Wait, where's my
color? You [ __ ] drunk, you
idiot. Got [ __ ] banging headache. Oh,
I got some power. I got
power. I do. Yeah, that's what I need
for this [ __ ] headache.
Going to take three of
them. Yeah, I do have power
suitable. Need to take him, mate.
[ __ ] That was a bad
one. One sec. Oh, [ __ ] hell. One
second. Let me take these
pills. Oh, one second, bro.
One second. Let me take these
doors, bro. It's the devil, man. One
second. I'm badly hung over. I put a
football belt on. And I was like, if I
win, I go out today. But I don't think
I'd actually even be able to go out,
bro. I am actually [ __ ] No, I'm not
even joking, bro. I'm [ __ ] I think I
could even go out.
Well, I hope
uh you got a sort of understanding about
how hard it is to um all in this
country. Well, especially
London, I got five numbers. I don't know
if I can be bothered to text them though to be
fair. If I
win, if I win, I could go out tomorrow,
but I think I go out today.
I deserve to win a football. I know six
weeks. What a
joker. Six weeks. Yeah. Yeah, boss.
be out today, shouldn't he?
Bro, how many I've got a
boyfriends? Too many. I lost count. Yeah, too
many. Far too many, mate. Far too
many. It's the way it is. I got this
football bet on. Anyways, even if I win,
I don't think I can even go out. I'm just so [ __ ]
Yeah. Anyways, you're banned, you little
keyboard warrior. I with you enough
[ __ ] yesterday, you little self-reflect up.
So, let's let's let's let's
uh look at what you people do on here.
Yeah. You sit on YouTube,
right? You haters. Yeah. What do you
people do this? Yeah. You sit on YouTube
calling people skin. People show you
money, you run away. People go out club
and you call them socially awkward that
you people can't even leave your own house.
Bro, this is the most saddest,
pathetic community I've ever stumbled
across in my whole [ __ ] life. It's
actually full of like
life projecting losers. Like there's
there's there's nothing more [ __ ] to
it, bro. Like, you know, look at me
yesterday. I was out [ __ ] drinking,
bro. I was having a boogie. I went up on
the table. These these people they ain't
got a life, man. And
now But yeah, you hear you
hear it up. Oh, it isn't it?
the way it
is with the same mindset right there.
Stuck up right
there. I had about over £1,000 as
well. It sums up the country really if
you think about it.
£900 and you're gone as well. I dealt
with you enough yesterday, you little keyboard warrior.
Bye-bye. You're out. I dealt with you enough
yesterday. You little self
projectors. I said, "Yeah, if you want
to blatantly try to mock someone, you
know, and you're blatant about it, it's
funny, man. To me, it's funny. So don't
don't come on here. Yeah. You know what
I hate is when you get these little
retards on here that think they're
smart. They actually think they're
intelligent and they think they can
troll you. They actually think they
could sit there and actually troll you
like you don't know what they're doing
and they're thick as pig [ __ ] as well.
That's that's the [ __ ] I find like
insulting when these weasels come on
here thinking they control. Like, bro,
they failed at everything in their life.
And even they even failed at trolling like [ __ ]
lads. I got like 1:00 a.m. I got five
numbers. I've not text them yet, but
uh so I had a nice haircut, nice
beard, nice t-shirt, nice jeans, nice
trainers. Still heard I got a boyfriend
[ __ ] Oh my god. I think you could wear
like a 2 million pound suit and you'll
still get I've got a boyfriend. But I I
generally think like honestly you
will. I had to deal with a lot of
[ __ ] yesterday. a lot of [ __ ]
Like it's it's not even a
joke. Yeah. But obviously it gives you a
bit better understanding, you know, what
this country is really
like. Goes in stages. You see, they're
all they're all [ __ ] with unrealistic
expectations. I don't know what else
there is to
to to say. It's how you carry yourself
through. Not at all. I carry myself
fine. I've got loads of friends. It's
not about it's it's them and Instagram.
That's what it is. Like people spend
years trying to figure out why. And it
is literally them. Like bro, mo most
time, a lot of the time you can't even
say two, three words about them saying
they got a boyfriend. It It is literally
them and their expectations. Like I
don't even like saying standards cuz I
like expectations. It literally is them.
Anyone that's got like life experience
well actually know
that they should go on loads of dates.
No, I'm not out today. I'm hanging. I'm
on a football bet.
No. Yeah. It's not how you carry
yourself. It's them. They They watch too
much Tik Tok. They watch too much. It's
It's what somebody told me before.
There's they they said to me that
there's too many sucker [ __ ] in your
country. And I and I actually think they
were right. Like this woman said, "Well,
no, I know they were right, you know."
No, she said she said she's watching my
approaches. She's like, "Okay, well,
there's nothing wrong with how you look.
There's nothing wrong with
um how you look. There's nothing wrong
with your approaches. Maybe there's too
many stuckup [ __ ] in your weird
country." And I generally think that's
what it is because when you walk around
Yeah. see people walking around like
their [ __ ] don't stink. That's literally
that's literally what it
is. Because would you have this problem
if you went to Asia? Would you would you
would you have this problem if you went
to Asia? No. Would you have this problem
if you went to Newcastle as much? So
obviously it's the [ __ ] in London. Of
course it is. That's all it points to,
you know? It's them literally. Like I
was telling this um there was these two
Irish people and I said, "Oh, like how
women waste your time and waste your
time on dates." I was going for like two
weeks ago and they're like, it's like this
minionist. I can't even pronounce it. I
said, "Well, no, it's not because I
don't care enough. I'm just saying that
to like last week wow me up. How is that
a misogynist? Misogynist. That
misogynist. He said it sounds
misogynistic. No, it does not. It's
literally talking and stating facts.
Idiot. The guy's from Ireland as well.
No, you can send it, mate, but I won't
be. I'm in my little
nesticles. I'm in my little
nesticles. I won't be sending nothing,
mate. I remember my little nest was
waiting for the football.
Yeah, but no, you'll get loads and loads
and loads of nos and you won't get
Yes. Bro, stop trying to troll me again.
I'm not Monty Man nor Timmy. Please stop
it. Stop it. Please. I'm not Monty Man nor Timmy Eldridge.
So, why don't you go out and send it?
Why don't you go out and send
it? You go out and send it,
bro. Why don't you go out and send it?
I'll meet you and we'll send it
together. Come on. Okay. If you meet me,
I'll send it with you. I I'm hanging, but I'll
still I'll just be able to make it.
Yeah. Yeah. If you meet me, I'll send it
with you. Come on. We'll do it together. Yeah. Yeah.
I have all this money. I don't have
loads of money. I'm skinn. What are you
talking about, bro? I'm completely
skinn. I have all this money. I don't
have all this money. I'm skinn, mate.
What are you on about? I'm eating
[ __ ] cold bean, man. I don't know
what you're on about. Uh, meet me in Tottenham Court
Road. Okay, listen, bro.
I'm I was drinking white rum yesterday,
bro, and it almost killed me. Yeah, I am
[ __ ] hanging. Like, I don't even
think I could do today even if I wanted
to. Like, if you stick to Guinness,
you're okay. Spice rum, you're okay. You
go over that, bro, and you start getting
them doubles, you're [ __ ] You're
[ __ ] Like, I done two days on a bank
holiday, but I can't [ __ ] Yeah.
Nah, bro. Don't encourage me to play
that um [ __ ] Slim. But like, I probably
won't even get any replies back or they
won't meet me. But that's what you're
dealing with in this country. At least
you get a better at least you get an
understanding. You finish 12:30. Okay,
man. See you
there. I hear
that. No, I got a 60 football bet, man.
I'm not paying no Frankie. [ __ ] you.
I got an escort yesterday. Got some
food. I really need to
[ __ ] I don't know, bro. I need to
[ __ ] slow down, bro. Then I have to
buy that [ __ ] washing machine as well.
[ __ ] I need to really chill, man.
Yeah. Is he paying well? That's nice of
him. I'm not I'm not playing it. I'm not
it. I bailed it yesterday.£60. I'm Yeah,
I'm not playing
it. None. None of your business. Baked
crisp. It's none of your
business. Worry about your own income.
money. You don't need to know that. Nice,
bro. It wasn't months without a bonus.
It was months without a
win. You need to worry about your own
lives, bro. You know, you come on here
stay calling me skin. I got out of
money. You couldn't show me nothing. You
say people are soci socially awkward,
projecting. These haters don't even
leave the house. Please stop it. They're
just Do you know what it is? This
community slim. Yeah, they're people in
their 40s that's achieved nothing in
life and they take it out on the world.
That's literally what they do. They come
on here, self-reflect, and try to bring
other people down with them. Think about
it, bro. Imagine not being able to go
one day without YouTube. That's a
problem, bro. That's a [ __ ] problem.
Not even one [ __ ] day. Imagine that.
So, it's like they they're just miserable.
Like they're just old age pensioners
that's got [ __ ] all and they just come
on here and project
lad. I don't know what else to
say. What's my opinion on
them? What's my happiness [Music]
cooking? And well, I'm going to Thailand
in two months. So
that in sleep bubble bar six
sex. Yeah. I don't even have a bed.
Okay. Have a bed again. I've got a £500
bed. I don't even have a bed. Okay. I
don't have a bed. Yeah. I've got more
money than you. Okay. I've got no bed.
That £500 bed is not mine. Okay. Yeah. I
don't have a bed.
Hey, even if I was sleeping on a
concrete [ __ ] floor, my life would
still be better than yours. My life
would still be better than yours. Even
if I was sleeping on a concrete
[ __ ] ground floor, my life would
still be better than yours. And bye-bye.
Now you're gone, little [ __ ]
spacker. Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
Yeah, you saw a mattress on the floor
because I was staying at my friends.
Yeah. And what's your point, bro?
Listen, stop telling people to show
things as well. Yeah, Greavves will be
my witness. You have been shown money.
You have been shown women. You have been
shown [ __ ] all sorts of [ __ ] I've
never seen any of you show me nothing.
So, stop self-reflecting your little sad
lives onto other people every day.
telling people that they need to show
this and they need they need to show
that. Bro, go [ __ ]
yourself, you know, like that's it. Show
this, show that. Let's see some of your
money. Let's see your bed. Let's see
your face. Let's see your friends. Let's
see your woman. You don't like to hear
that, do you? Cuz it's the truth. Self reflectors. Self-reflectors.
Hey fruit king, I showed money
yesterday. You couldn't show me anything, you
know. So, mate,
listen. You're trying to hate on me for
not having a bed when I have a bed. Bro,
focus on your own lives. You people on
YouTube all day, every day. Yeah.
Bye-bye. Uh, slug. What's his name?
Slug. Lewisville. Slugger. Bye-bye. I
can smell you a mile off. I can smell
you from a mile off. You know when
someone's cooking chips? Yeah, it's the
same spastics every day, bro. You know,
you know when you could smell chips,
Grezy. A bag of chips cooking. I can
smell these [ __ ] trolls from a mile off.
They're that bad at it. I can actually
smell them through the screen. They
doing it. These bad these little sad act
weasels. I've been doing it for years, you know. These little
self-reflectors. They're sad bastards.
Slim. They got nothing in their life.
It's why they do this. Because they got
nothing in their life. They're
nobodyies. They're nobodyies, bro.
That's why these people are older than
me. These people are older than me and
they and they're doing this stuff. Like,
it says everything about their lives,
lads. It's [ __ ] Am I out again? I'm
hanging. No, I'm not out. I'm not out
again today. Even if the football bet
wins, I'm still not out. I'm hanging,
bro. I'll [ __ ] drop dead. I think if
I tried to I had to get off the train,
Greavves, and be sick. I said, I'm going
to I'm going to be sick. I was I was I
climbed on the table, Greavvesy, and I was
dancing. Yeah, the V is like, "Oh, you
got to get off the table." I was on I
was on the table having a little boogie,
Greavvesy. A little
bug. A little
boogie. Can show the video if you want.
Yeah. Everybody knows that you're a crazy
[ __ ] I feel like I've got [ __ ]
alcohol poisoning, bro. I feel like I've got alcohol
poisoning. Actually feel like I've got
alcohol poisoning, lad. Not
even I feel like I'm dying, bro.
But yeah, you got a bit of what it's
like greasy, right? That you can look
good, you can have money, you can wear
expensive stuff and triate in this
country is a nightmare. And it's only getting
worse. It's only getting worse, especially in
London. Did I have success with women?
What do you think? I was live for about
two hours yesterday. You heard the the
[ __ ] I was getting. Oh, I got five
numbers. I ain't text them yet. So,
no, cuz that's how it's always going to
be in this
country. Like, get used to
it. So, no, man. This is what I'm
saying, brother. You people need to go
out, bro. You need to leave your house
sometime. Yeah. And you should actually
try and pull. Well, to be fair, you
probably even live in London. Could be
anywhere in England. Nah, bro. Um, it
was just the same I've got a boyfriend
[ __ ] I managed to get five numbers, but
I ain't even bother texting them to be
honest. Nah, bro. It was
um Yeah, imaginary boyfriends, all that old bollocks
and just [ __ ]
basically. And I said it hard, bro. Like
I even done in the Weather Spoons. Done
it in the
pub pub. I done in a Weather Spoons and
Yeah, I heard it a lot
yesterday. Yeah, I have to deal with a lot of
[ __ ] That's why I don't like doing
it more than once a week,
lad. Yeah, it does drop off in China.
Yeah, that's it, bro. It does do that.
Yeah, that's what happened to No, I
didn't. But I played Frankie yesterday
with£60 in the pub. But after that
though, so I won't be out until next
week. I won't be out until next week.
Eh, I actually think it's actually
possible dating in this country though.
if you didn't meet somebody when you was
like young or you didn't meet somebody
through work or something like I dealt
with a lot of [ __ ] yesterday like even
before I started recording and it's yeah
I think unless you you met somebody like
that I think you're basically screwed
now cuz of Tik Tok and Instagram cuz people
don't they're just all they're just all
stuck up cuz like any anyone can write
anything on the internet. Yeah, women go
for this or women go for that or
whatever whatever is people write on the
internet. But when you actually go
outside, it contradicts everything that
they say. Your experiences will their
advice will contradict everything that
you experience. It's nothing like what
you read online. You
understand? No, it does stop in China.
It does. It does. Look at that bin and
he told me, "No, no, it does stop in China.
Yeah, it's a cheaper flight. It does.
No, no, no, no, no. It does, bro. Trust
me. Trust me, it
does. I was trying to speak to some
people yesterday sober and then they
like, "Oh, I'm all right." And then they
just go back to their phone and they
just stuck up. It's like unless you met
somebody years ago, it's pretty unlikely
like cuz you need to get a number and
then the number needs to message you and
then they need to meet you and then they
need to meet you again. It's it is it is
like you've seen it from my own
experiences. Yeah, I spent a lot of money
yesterday. Like the grooming weren't
cheap. So that's the reality of it that
you can learn from it.
Like yeah, I booked Thailand. Yeah, I
only booked the
flights. But it is it is impossible in
this country. Like all jokes don't
aside. I went to Weather Spoon yesterday
and I done this approach right. And you
know what she said to me? She said she's
married. I said, "You're married?" I
said, "How old are you?" She was about
19, 20, I swear to God. And she's like,
"I'm 16." I was like, "What? You're 16
and you're married?" I was like, "I'm so
done." Like, I literally just walked
back and got myself a Guinness. So,
you're in Weather Spoons drinking, yet
you're married, yet you're 16. Okay,
whatever. And then the other pub that I went to,
um, what was it? Yeah, it was another
pub that was not Weather Spoons. I was
like, "Okay, let me do this one." Then
they was like, "Guess my name." I said,
"Oh, what's your name? And [Music]
um I said to her like, "What's her
name?" And uh she said um it's beginning
with St. I've got to guess it. I said
St. Stephanie Stav. I don't [ __ ] know
what your [ __ ] name is. I didn't say
that. I was like, "Okay, give me your
number and then I'll message you. I'll
have a think and then I'll message you
some things I come up with." Um, I have
a boyfriend. [ __ ] this. Then I went
outside and then done some more. Then I
went to a club. But yeah, it's they're just
like NPCs, bro. And you know the worst
part about it? Yeah, obviously it's the
money as well. Like it is expensive to
get your haircut. You have to sit on
that chair for an hour. Imagine you have
to sit still for a [ __ ] hour to get
your hair done and like you're still
going to hear the I got a boyfriend
[ __ ] Just just imagine that, bro. You
know, it's crazy. This country's
finished. So different to what you
experience to what people say, you know.
Um Yeah. And it it seems it's got harder
for the past 2 3 years.
If you got a date every week, it
wouldn't be too bad. But I don't think
I'm going to have any dates from
yesterday. I don't even think any of
them will reply
back. Goes like that sometimes.
Sometimes you can get five numbers, they don't reply
back. You can get three numbers, they
all reply back. One meets you. Just just depends. But
um yeah, it's shitty, man. it.
Get my haircut next week. Should last a bit
longer. But the reason I say they've got
unrealistic expectations is because I'm
above average looking. You groom, you
dress good, you're confident. you know,
obviously the amount of people that
you've met and stuff. So, if that's not
good enough for them, then bro, it's
unre it's unrealistic expectations that
they've got. It's got to be, you
know, I've been Oh,
he Yeah, it is bad. It is bad. Yeah.
Better luck next
weekend. We got tie bride
back. That's nice though. You can get direct. Yeah.
No, it's bad, bro.
Bad. Hopey this football bet [ __ ]
wins. Well, even if it does win, we
can't even go out anyways cuz we're
[ __ ] Yeah, Gre, they're just not
interested in this country. That's what
Antman said about 3 months
ago. I was looking clean
ass. Fresh clothes cleaned in the
[ __ ] in the in the in the washing
machine. So, it's a bit like people on
here like when people say stuff on
Reddit, they don't have any life
experience. Like because again, what
they say and what you see is two different things.
And they can go on about other people in
relationships, but bro, think about it
realistically. How did these people
actually meet? You
know, but it is
um it is what it is. So yeah.
Yeah, that's the fan greavesy you can hear.
Yeah, pigs might fly. Pigs might
fly. One second. Someone sent me a voice like that.
Sorry about that,
bro. Sorry about that [Music] delay. So,
yeah, Gregy, it doesn't sound like
you've got any goals in your life, to be
honest. Doesn't seem like you got uh
You got any goals in your life,
man? Cuz you say that like my only
happiness is women. A, it's not. And B,
you don't seem to have any goals. Do you
actually know what a goal
is? Mine is leaving this country again. So, you
know, I want to go to that Simpsons
thing in Florida. Have you seen it? Universal
Studios. [ __ ] It's expensive, though.
It uh greasy.
Yeah. Have you seen it? The Simpsons uh thing.
That's me in Tottenham Court Road. What stage? Stage.
Oh, [ __ ] hell,
bro. Yeah, I want to go c I want to
watch a horror film in the cinema, bro.
That's what I love. Horror films in the cinema.
Yeah, I want to watch horror films in
the cinema, but there's none out
such. Yeah, I put this football bet on
£60. It returns
188. And man's like, it's not even worth
putting it on. And I think it is. It's
more than three times the amount
back. So why not? But it's more than
three times the amount back, is it not?
So if it
wins, I'll try to go
out, but I don't think I'll be able to,
bro. I generally don't think I'll be
able to. I'm not telling you my bet,
bro. I'm not telling you it. It's a
secret. But I both score, but I'm not
sending you the teams. Yeah. Yeah. Simple.
Yeah. Why don't you go Scotland, Grebsy?
You've always wanted to go Scotland. Why
don't you make that a goal?
just go to Scotland since you love
Scottish women so much and you love Scotland so
much. Why not,
bro? You always say you want to go
there. It's summer,
right? Give it a while. I would give it
Oh. Oh, B. I am
[ __ ] I am
[ __ ] Uh, and you
got so didn't mean that. Yeah, agrees.
Why don't you go Scotland, bro? You
know, if I was you, if you was going to
go Scotland, I'd say go there for 3
days, go to Edinburgh, then go to Glasgow.
Like I even say Edinburgh is my second favorite
city. That's lally my second favorite
city. I love Edinburgh. Like the
scenery, the weather spoons outside. I I
don't know. I just like it. I think it'd
be a good place to move if I was to move
out of London.
And I didn't have a moment that I think
I'd probably go. I think that's my
second favorite in terms of like I don't
know. It's It's nice. I don't know. I I like it though. Yeah.
Like what's happening? Not much. Same old
[ __ ] Same old. Same old. Hug over the
[ __ ] Can you hear me,
Grezy? Can you hear me, Grezy? Yeah.
Yeah. You can't even Yeah.
So, but yeah. And Yeah. And then if you
And it takes more than one meeting to
see if you feel a vibe or not,
bro. Um, these women are mad. Where have
I been? Just not on this side community
anymore. It's just full of sados. I'll
be gone again tomorrow for probably a
month or 3 weeks or something. I don't
really come here anymore. It's just the
same [ __ ] I got an email from LT like
two days ago saying that he's went to
like box area and stuff. I was like,
"Bro, you do you know what I called him,
bro?" I said, "You're a pair of
[ __ ] You're you're you two are a pair
of cunts." And I actually said that as
well. I was like, "Bro, how long are you
two going to keep doing this, bro? This
has been going on for [ __ ] years now,
mate. It's the same pattern. It's been
going on for years. This Arsenal Mark.
Yeah, he does this whole calling people out for
attention. They're not about that life.
I said this yesterday when I was drunk.
They're not about that life. I don't
know why anyone takes this Mark Samson serious.
Like, if the guy was serious, he'd be
coming on someone's door. If the guy was
serious, he'd be live on someone's road.
Like if if that Arsenal Mark guy was
serious. Yeah. He'd be like, "Right, PJ,
I'm coming to your area." And then he
would just go live on your road for like
20 minutes, 30 minutes. But it's not. It's
attention, you know? Like it's You
wouldn't be on YouTube if you was about
it, you know? It's funny. It's embarrassing, bro.
Please. Where where is Tim? Has he been
posting as Timmy?
Yeah. He's not posted is he to me for a
while. I've just gone to the channel.
Yeah. He always makes the te of
himself. It's like Lord J. Yeah. He made
a te of himself like constantly going to
Birmingham. I said, "Why don't you come
on my door again and see what happens?"
I said that to him. I said that to him
literally yesterday. So, why don't you
come on my door again and see what
happens? Yeah. This is the third time
you've gone for Timmy. You've come on my
door once years ago. I stood in front of
my mom. You want to give me an L? I'll
take the L, bro. Come again. Simple.
Like, [ __ ] You've been to Birmingham
like two times. Who goes to Birmingham
of all places? When somebody comes to
[ __ ] England, bro, they come to
London, you know? Like that L J is a
proper anxietyridden [ __ ] like he is not about
anything. He really ain't about
nothing, you know? He just goes for
these [ __ ] disabled people, you
know? That's what it
is. PJ, what? Lord
J, I don't know. Yeah, he can get just
tell him whenever he's back in England
to come on my door. Yeah, we know that
he's scared of LT and all of this. You
can even come unannounced if you
like. You know, he's a [ __ ] idiot,
bro. Hable [ __ ] He's a knowable [ __ ]
He is. But that's what I just said to
LT, man. You and this Arsenal Mark,
you're a pair of [ __ ] Is that a funny
word? Creepy. Pair of
[ __ ] [ __ ] They're [ __ ] They're
mate. No, I'm not meeting anyone on this
community. I'm not meeting anyone on
this [ __ ] backwards community. Why
would I, bro?
No [ __ ] way. Never. Ever. Ever. Ever.
Ever. I don't need to meet men on the
internet, mate. I've got enough friends.
I'm good. You know what I'm saying?
Greavvesy. Greavvesy. Do you remember
taking a baby away from its mama? You
know, I was going Greavves, you still
there? I was going through some of my
approaching videos two days ago and the
one come up where I met my mama.
didn't even look for it on purpose, but
it was there, bro. Like, where I met my mother.
Grezy, your your daddy and mommy left
you. You said that my parents left me in
it, Grezy. A
bless. Ah, bless. But no, I would never
leave. I would never. Um,
no. So, yeah,
man. Yesterday was a proper madness. What's
this? Them army [ __ ] I keep saying to
this guy who's in the armor like, "Do
you want to meet up or not?" Yeah, stop
wasting my time. You want to meet up
again or you don't want to meet up? [ __ ] sake.
Yeah, he was laughing at
me. No, I went out yesterday, man. I'm
all good. I'm all good, mate. I'm about
to have a little snooze. I feel sick. I
do. I feel sick, mate. I should have
lined my stomach up more.
I actually feel so
sick. I feel prop sick, mate. Oh,
man. Anyways, I'm out of here. Yeah. So,
I'll see you in about two weeks or 3
weeks or whenever I'm gone in a bit. There.