He's still [ __ ] hanging from [ __ ]
Friday. He's still hanging from [ __ ]
So, I'd give that one a whirl over
there, but it's not really my time. I've
already done two approaches so I've sober.
Yeah, but I'm still hung over from
Friday. Definitely. This will be my last
day now for like three weeks,
but going to make it really count. I'm Oh
yes. Oh yes.
Dian told you them hangovers can last
three days if the
[ __ ] right [ __ ] spirits mate. Tell
you all stay holiday in it.
I am [ __ ]
so I would do her, but I don't really like her.
Ah, don't really like her, mate.
So we won't give it a
one. Open it up like a
[ __ ] could actually last two days.
Yeah, I'm two sober. I haven't done any
drunk yet. I'm not drunk. I'm tipsy.
Tipsy s [ __ ] from Friday. So psychic.
Yeah. Don't like her enough to do
it. Don't like her enough to do it, man. Yeah.
I'm off Thailand in two months anyway,
so I as [ __ ] mate. Might as well make
you count, you know.
[ __ ] kind of just want to go home. I feel but stay. Yeah. Oh
man. I don't know if I'm going to be
able to do an all night or not. That's
the real question.
Can I do an all
nighter? I don't [ __ ] think
so. Oh, [ __ ]
it. Had some man anxiety yesterday cuz
of [ __ ] drinking the night before.
Jeez. It's no good for the membrane.
It's no good for your mental health. Come
on. So, I don't really like her. I'm
looking at that one over
there trying to think, should I give it
a whirl or not? But I don't really like her
face. Otherwise, I would give it a
whirl. A well
word. However some people [ __ ] say it. Huh.
Oh, [ __ ] hell,
man. Today I'm going to be literally
[ __ ] for about 3 days. Three days. I'm
going to be [ __ ] for
minimum. I'm pushing myself here, man.
Really, really am. It's why you don't
[ __ ] with white spirits.
Don't [ __ ] with white spirits. [ __ ]
kill you. That
will just stick to beer today. Hopefully
I'll be all right.
Ah. Stick them to be.
Oh yeah, man. I'm just out here. I'm
still [ __ ] from [ __ ]
Friday. That white rum almost finished
me, man. It almost finished
me. I'm out here. I don't to approach
the sober. I'm just drinking. I'm going
to send it again today. That's me done
for 3 weeks until the next bank until
holiday. Yeah, I'm just sticking to beer
today, though. So, should be all right.
Should be all right,
mate. Yeah, I'm on the It's bank
holiday, is it? So, [ __ ] Yeah. But
I'm just going to stick to beer this time.
Uh, need to watch my phone here, mate.
in case some [ __ ] that [ __ ] snatches it, runs
off, drink it again cuz it's bank
holiday, bro. And I'm done for 3 weeks after
today. I spent about 600
pound to bank holiday. I spent about 600
quid. [ __ ] you,
mate. Yeah, I got five numbers. [ __ ]
all. So, I'm making today the last day
for three weeks because it's pointless
going out, man.
I got the numbers. They just didn't just didn't lead
anywhere. That's England for you though,
is it? That's England for you, man. Especially
London. Too many suck up [ __ ] Oh,
Drinking. Just drinking, gambling,
food. Just drinking basically. Haircut,
drinking, food. Put someone on a football. bank holiday. But
yeah, nothing really come off the
numbers, so I'm having to go out and do it again.
Yeah, I done an approach here in Crispy
Creams. There was three of them. I done
it completely sober. Yeah, she's about
to give her number and I think her
friend semi coproed me, mate. Her friend
defo cop rocked that.
Yeah. Did he? No one cares. Good for him. Um,
yeah. So, that's that. He looks all
right. Mate, he was
drinking. It's about 100 pints.
How do you word that one out when it's
like£10 a drink in
London? How do you word that one out?
It's about 100 pints. How do you work
that one out when a when a drink is
about 104 pound in
London? How do you word that one out?
That don't make sense. Drinking, gambling,
haircuts, [ __ ] [ __ ] How do you make
out that it's
£100 when it's about£10 a drink? And I
was drinking spirits as well. That don't make
sense. Anyways, yeah, I don't eat crispy
creams and she was about to give her a
number and then then she
never and then it's getting busy, mate.
It's getting busy. Then um then I
another one and sort of walked away.
So if she comes back and she sits
through that other person, I'm going to do
her. I mean approach her, not not do. Yeah, man.
Oh, bro. Okay, whatever. Yeah, I'm not
going to argue with you, bro. I know
where I live and I know how much things
cost. Okay, bro. I'm not going to sit
here and argue with you. [ __ ] sake.
Please stop it.
There's some sexy people here today.
Everybody knows that you're a crazy
[ __ ] ain't it, Grezy? Everybody knows
that you're a crazy [ __ ] Do you
remember that, Grezy? That's what I say
to myself. But before I go out
approaching, I just say, "Everybody
knows that you're a crazy [ __ ] I just
done too [ __ ] sober, bro. Just before
hitting this uh
Bad, right? And you're banned. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye, Louis Slugger. I can smell you
like a I can smell your mile off.
Bye, Graves. You I am a crazy
it. You have to admit I'm a crazy [ __ ] It
crazy. She comes back up there. I want
to [ __ ] go over, mate. 100%.
Don't mind if I do,
Grezy. Don't mind if I do,
buddy. Don't mind if I do, bud. Don't
mind if I do. She just gone to the
toilet. I think she went with her
friends. But if she comes back and she
stays, I'm sending
it. I didn't go out last night, you
idiot. I went out
Friday. I was sick, Greavvesy. I had mad
anxiety and paranoia for like two days
cuz the drinking. That's why today I'm
sticking to beer. I'm sticking to the beers
today. Sticking to the beers, mate. De
spirits is not a joke, mate. [ __ ]
kill you. That
will so many suck up [ __ ] in this country.
Yeah, bro. I hardly go live. LT, what is
it with you and this Mark Samson, mate?
If you want my honest opinion, bro.
Yeah. You two are just a pair of
[ __ ] Like, bro, he never called me out
to begin with. He does this whole
YouTube thing for attention. Do you not
understand? It's attention
seeking. You understand, lad? And your band. Bye-bye,
Louis. LT, I'm hardly ever on here, bro.
Hardly hardly ever on here. It's a bit
early and I'm not drunk enough yet. So,
bro, the guy, how long has this guy been
doing this on YouTube now? How long,
bro? And I woke up. Yeah, it was like
8:00 in the morning. I got an email from
you about this [ __ ] from this [ __ ]
bro. Like, what the
[ __ ] Real bad people do not come online
making videos. You understand? Real bad
people don't come on YouTube making videos.
It's common sense.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm sending it again today,
mate. I'm sending it again today.
Yeah. No run, though. I'm not getting on
the run. [ __ ] that. The rum almost killed me.
Bye-bye. Now I'm back on it,
mate. Spending the dough, bro. spending
the but bro what I don't listen listen
anyone that makes videos on me like
Timmy Mark Samson anyone I ignore it
like I'm not here for drama because I
know that if anyone was about anything
they wouldn't be coming on YouTube
making videos like I'm not even drunk
saying this but like okay I might be a
bit tipsy yeah but I know if someone's
about something they don't come on
YouTube making videos it's common sense
know, that's why I don't bother with it,
bro. Like, people come here and try
hate. I don't I'm not interested, bro.
Like, people claim they know where I
live. Well, come up. Pull up, bro. If
you got a problem, I'm not going to sit
here and argue with people, bro. It's
just like that Terry guy. LT, I told you
for ages. This guy's got about nothing.
Yeah. He's laughing about people getting
nipped. He's emailing people. He didn't
show up when I when I last went to his
area. He's not about that life. You
understand, bro? Come on. And you're
bad. And you're bad. See
you. Yep. And you're bad. Oh, I got no
friends. Just like you said, I was skinn
yesterday, didn't you? And I showed you
money again and you all run away. Yep.
I've got no friends. I'm skin. Yep. Yep.
Yep. Yep. Yep. I maybe think that you
people are yourselves.
I maybe think that you people are
yourselves. Yeah. Okay, buddy. That's
why you got shown money yesterday. Uh on
Friday, sorry. And you couldn't show
nothing. Okay, bro. I'm very skinn. I've
got no friends. Nope. I've got no one.
I'm just like you then, aren't
I? I'd rather be sat here in a pub
drinking by myself. That means sat on
YouTube by myself. Yeah. Like you people
sat on YouTube. No life, no nothing. by
yourself. I'd rather be spending money
alone than being on YouTube alone,
self-reflecting for seven years. Hey, I
admit it. You know, I told Grezy the same thing.
Oh, where's that [ __ ] gone? I'm going
to [ __ ] do her in a minute. Squeeze
back. If she comes back to I'm going over there. So yeah, bro.
Yeah. [ __ ] hell, man. Give us a think.
Yeah, man. And you know what it is as
well, Ali? It's the same people doing
this whole undercover hating um Harry
[ __ ] Lewisville Slugger. They're just
sad acts in their 40s. Like, you think I
don't know it's the same people. Now,
how many times did I have to say on
Friday, I'm not Monty Man or
Timmy. I am not Monty Man or Timmy. You
can't troll somebody like me. So stop
trying to. You
understand? They're just self-reflecting
little losers. Like low lives. That's
what they are. Like they talk about
themselves every day. Like bro, you know
how many friends I've got? I can go out
with a friend today if I wanted to.
Yeah, I've got loads of friends. I'd
rather go out alone cuz I'm sending it.
And what? Bro, just like a travel loan.
These people on YouTube alone every
day. That's it. I made a new channel.
Oh, listen LT, I emailed you about this
as well. You know how they discovered
me? Because when I would send my friends
on Instagram my new YouTube channel,
they found it like that. That's how they
discovered me. But then when I stopped
sending it to people on Instagram, they
never found it. They found my new
channel. I had to make another one.
Yeah. I Bro, I post content videos on my
new channel. Like, I'm not going to tell
you exactly what it is, but there's
content on that channel. Yeah, there's
content on that [ __ ] channel, bro.
And that's how they discovered me
through that Instagram. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Be careful where you um be careful
where you comment,
bro. Be careful where you comment,
man. On it. Having a Guinness
boo got the builders in so to speak.
E I'm a bit drunk now. But hey, I'm not
an alcoholic. But don't mind me. It's following. Eh.
Yeah. That's how they That's how they
But that's what I'm saying. That's how they discovered
me. Okay. That's what I don't know how
they found you, bro. But I know how they
found me. I know how they found me cuz
when I stopped sending it to people on Instagram, it
stopped and that's how they discovered
me. Yeah. It's like JB Thompson. He's He's Yeah.
Yeah. It's all right to go live and have
banks, but any kind of drama I'm not involved
in. It's just like that Kevin Murphy. I
said, "Yep, yep, yep. I'm the biggest
[ __ ] Kevin Murphy. Yeah. I'm the
biggest [ __ ] Yeah. Yep. Yep. Whatever.
I'm saying whatever you say. I'm the
biggest [ __ ] Yet yet. I don't get into
it with these little keyboard warriors
cuz I know that if any of these people
was about anything, they wouldn't be
coming on YouTube making videos. It's common
sense. It is [ __ ] common sense.
Yeah. That's it.
Where did that [ __ ] go? I'm going to go send
her. I'm going to go send I'm going to
go send it.
Yeah. Uh, not much, man. Just the same old
[ __ ] I booked Thailand as well. I
actually did book
Thailand. Yep, I actually booked
Thailand. Feel like my foot is [ __ ]
you know. Where did that [ __ ] go in the
white? I'm not chilling. I'm not chasing
after no one, but I'm just going to sit
here and wait. LT, I'm picking my
moment. I'm picking my moment. LT, I'm a little
watchdog. LT, do you know who I am, bro?
I'm a little
watchdog. Yep. I'm a little
watchdog. You know when they just like
look at the beef and that just staring
at the beef. That's me, bro. I'm a
little watchdog. I'm thinking about a
moment. I'm not chasing after no [ __ ]
up the [ __ ] road. [ __ ]
that. Sat here picking my
moment over [ __ ]
this, bro. I'm telling you. Listen, LG,
that's how they discovered me. I'm
telling you, bro. That's how I was
discovered. I done two approaches on the
street sober. Yeah. Nothing. But it's
still early days, man. We'll send it all
night. We will send it all night. Trust
me. And I'm going by
myself. But he's going to be there as
well. Yeah. I done two um sober before I
started drinking. Dead. Dead. I done one
in the shop. I done one in the crispy
cream shop. There was three of them. I
thought, "Fuck it." Where the [ __ ] did
that [ __ ] go? She must have went
upstairs. Never walk back down. There's an
upstairs. Anyways, I'm not chasing no
[ __ ] If I see them, I see them. I don't
[ __ ] Nah, there's no being positive in
this country. It's [ __ ] It's full of
stuck up people. I hate England. I don't
like England. It's full of stuck up
people. Nah, you can't be positive in
somewhere like London. It's full of
[ __ ] But yeah, we're drinking
anyways. We're going to send it anyways.
But what's really going to happen today,
bro? Nothing. Spend another 200 pound get nowhere. Oh
well, that is what will happen.
But I don't really like that look of
anyone. I mean, she's What was that? I
don't [ __ ] realize she was dead.
I was going to.
Nah, I don't like her. She seems a bit young,
man. No, not really been gambling. I put
a football bet on yesterday. It didn't win.
So, I lost £60 on a
football. Yeah, man. 60 on the football.
I didn't style the hair today, but
um what is it
for? Why is there Why is there like two
women women and there's like a kid opposite
them? Why is there like a kid opposite
them? No, that's definitely stuff. They
got to be like
[ __ ] That's a dodge. They've got like
a child like right sack opposite them. I
ain't getting involved with
that. I'm not getting involved with that,
buddy. Where the [ __ ] is this coming? I
think when I go toilet and I see them,
I'm going to do it. If I If I see them,
I'm going to do it. If I don't see them, I won't.
There's no opportunities there really, is there? Not really.
Oh, I got one reply back from [ __ ]
Friday. [ __ ] off, man. What? All the way
from Friday. It took you [ __ ] two
days to reply. [ __ ] pair of [ __ ]
That's what they are. [ __ ] pair of
[ __ ] man. Yeah.
Oh, well, at least we got one reply out
of five numbers. Don't beat yourself up. [ __ ] hell,
mate. Yeah, I made myself some
burgers. Yeah, I made myself some burgers,
man. You are a bit of a [ __ ] Oh, so I
had to send a voice for you to reply. [ __ ]
off. Taking a piss. Obviously taking a
piss. It's all about the voice. I'm telling you,
man. Look at me. I'm like a little watchdog.
Rezy. I'm like a little watchdog. Pick in my
moment. There we go. There we go. There
go. Look at me, G. I'm picking my moment.
How cute is
that? I'm in no rush. Plenty of people
around. I'm in no rush, bro. Plenty of
people around. Plenty of time in a day.
Just picture my
moment, you know.
Yeah. Yeah, I don't really come on here
anymore, man. Too many glasses, too many
repeaters, too many self protectors.
Did you have if you have
anything? Oh, yeah. Did Did you just
realize that, bro? Like, listen, listen.
Yeah. They tried to say that I've got no
friends, bro. I have got friends. I just
like to go out by myself sometimes. I've
got more friends than them. I've got
more money than them. Listen, bro. These
people don't even leave their house. Why
do you think they hate on me all the
time? Yeah, these people do not even
leave their [ __ ] house. They've got
no money. They got no friends. They got
no life. And that's why they latch on to
me, bro. Why do you think they latch on
to me? They do that. Why do you think I
made a new channel, bro? Because of that same reason.
to the right. No, I might actually go
when she comes back.
When she comes back, I'm going to actually do
her. [ __ ] it.
music. I'm a little
watchdog now. I'm a little
watch. Yeah. Call me the watch dog. Yeah. Watching.
Yeah, they do do it to specific people.
Why do you think they don't do it to Monty Man?
to Why do you think they don't do it to
M man? Why do you think they don't do it
to Timmy? Because they know that these
people have got nothing. They know me.
I've got more of a life than them. You
know, I'm You know, bro, I'm not going
to get Listen, they do do it to specific people.
No, I'm not
watching. I'm a
watchdog. Listen, LT, I told you this.
I'm a little
watchdog. Why am I greasy?
Wait. Why beat up? Yeah, I'm blaming you.
You see the camera gone and mic
muted. Yeah, he sting me as well. He stunks
everyone. He stunks everybody, buddy. He
everyone. Are you nervous?
I'm going to put this and lift it
up. Yeah. Look for my teeth. My teeth ain't bad.
Look. Wait a minute. That one's
actually I don't have to face. That's
what I was just looking at. When she comes out the
lights. Oh, you're getting scared.
No turning back
now. We all know LT that you wanted to
get into Morgan's
knickknacks. Like we all know that you
wanted to get into Morgan's nickn. And I
don't blame you, bro. Like, you picked
your moment, you know, trying to be the
alpha male. Now, I get it. Get it, bro.
Honestly, I do. But you was picking your
moment trying to get her little
nickn. Anyways, I need to keep it
moving. Yeah, cuz I'm going to send this
approach when she comes back down. I
need to send it. I'm getting distracted.
I've already been live half an hour. So,
yeah, I'm out. I'll be back later
anyways. I'll keep you updated
with what I got basically. So, yeah,
I'll be live a bit later in a
B. In a Bizzle. Yeah, we should have had
about two three numbers by now. But end.