What were you saying, mate? It's been [ __ ]
shot. Hey, get up there. They're all
[ __ ] MP [ __ ] sees
that. They're all [ __ ] NP [ __ ]
C's, mate. Telling
you. I'm gonna have to go out on the
street and do these
approaches. Have to go out on the [ __ ] street.
Me? Cuz uh I got one number today. One
number. I don't even know if the
number's [ __ ] real. Today was
me. [ __ ] bors me, bro.
Imagine being in the
same soldier with that [ __ ]
Hey, I just [ __ ] spoke to one and she
walked in. She said she [ __ ] boyfriends,
bro. You left. One walked in. I thought
I said it. What did it say to you?
Nothing. [ __ ] you would. They just
say nothing. I mean, they're [ __ ]
[ __ ] bro. I just went to one. When you
walked out, one can't. They're
[ __ ] We can try this with [ __ ]
six girls. There's no man in there. Oh,
one minute, bro. Give me a rain, bro.
Give me a break. Give it. What you
looking for? Oh, we'll do it. What?
Sick. You want to do six? Six.
I'm going to
He wants to sick. This guy is a crazy
[ __ ] He's a crazy,
bro. What's the point?
They've all got [ __ ] boyfriends. Why
do you want to speak to someone? Six.
What? Six people. What's the
point? They all got [ __ ] boyfriends,
mate. On your mate. It's been [ __ ] [ __ ] today.
I'm on a corona and it's [ __ ]
[ __ ] It's [ __ ] [ __ ]
bro. Mate, it's [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] mate.
Oh my god.
I'm going [ __ ] Thailand in two
months. You betcha. This is B time. Tin mate,
listen. They've all got imaginary
boyfriends, mate. They've all got
[ __ ] imaginary [ __ ] boyfriends.
Where the [ __ ] are these bikes?
these five minutes?
M they've all got
boyfriends. Australian Dave's been
sending it all day now. I've got one
number if it's even
real. So many make believe
boyfriends. Bro, the west is finished.
I'm going Thailand. [ __ ] this. I'm going
to Thailand in two months. I've already
booked it. I'm [ __ ] out of it. [ __ ]
this, bro. It's
impossible. I don't sober
drunk, mate. They're not interested in
this country. I'm off to Thailand. [ __ ]
this. I'm done. I promise you, bro. I'm
the man F. Hey, they all got a
boyfriend. You got a boyfriend, do you?
Hey, they've all got boyfriends, mate.
I've heard it about a million times
today. But we're in a club in a nightclub.
I need to go and be my friend in the big
get some KFC. They've all got they all
too many stuck up. I got two reply from
Friday. They're all stuck up. Anyone
that wants to come to London, you'll see
it. Mate, this country is impossible
though, mate. It's too these specialized
countries. I'm off to Asia. I'm off to
Thailand. It's boring. [ __ ] nice.
They've all got [ __ ]
boyfriend. They all got boyfriends. [Music]
I'm going to do behind us there. Which
one? Behind us. Behind us.
Behind us. Look behind us. Over the
shot. Over there. Look behind us. No.
No. Behind. Behind.
Bro, behind us on the on the end. The
end. The end. The end. Look right. The
end. The two. The two that bow.
I'm going to do the one on the right.
I'm the right [Laughter]
going this push. I'm going this push.
They both got weapons. Bob,
I You're doing it right. I'm No, I'm
doing it. I'm doing a No, I'm doing the
right. You're on the left. Yeah. Yeah. 100%.
No more boyfriends.
Hopefully we don't get the [ __ ]
boyfriend [ __ ] One time, please. Not
one time in a whole night. Let's go, dude.
I got her number. I got her [ __ ]
number, but she didn't seem that very
enthusiastic. [ __ ] hell, man. How you
doing, bro? Good.
Good. Good, man.
I can't wait to go to Thailand. I got
her number. It's her real number. But
[ __ ] me, mate. [ __ ] me. What's a man got
to do in this country to get [ __ ]
Bro, I need to go. I need to go KFC, bro.
Well, you know how much I spent over the
bank holiday? Yeah, I spent about
£600. Just over the bank
holiday. Madness, isn't
it? [ __ ] hell, bro. From [ __ ] all
basically. But seven numbers ain't going to fat,
mate. Yeah, I got her [ __ ] number.
But [ __ ] is she going to apply?
I need to do some street purchase soon again.
Easy on the
old. He's still over there, is he?
Hey. Hey. Got another one. Got it.
Where's the guy? He's over there, bro.
Where's talking to the girl? No. On the
right. Right. Look,
I got a number. [ __ ] it. It's [ __ ]
hard, bro. It's hard, bro. I'm done. I'm
[ __ ] I'm done. I'm done.
Yes. They don't sell
Guinness. They don't sell Guinness. What the
number? [ __ ] hard, mate. Oh, [Music]
UK. Well, at least she didn't say she
had a [ __ ]
boyfriend. I need to go see my friend.
He's waiting for the
KFC. I got two numbers. I got two
numbers, but I think one of them is
fake. I don't know. got a
feeling this time. What is he doing,
man? Go to the colonels, mate. Before
they shut down.
So, how many numbers did you say? How
many numbers? One. I got two. Man, it
was [ __ ] hard, bro. It was hard, but
we tried. We tried. We tried. We tried.
I need to go and do on a [ __ ]
straight, bro. It's [ __ ] hard. It's hard, bro.
All right. All right. You fine, bro.
I've been trying all day, bro. What do
you mean? You see me, bro? What the [ __ ] I just
bro you behind you behind you bro. Come on. Scared.
Yeah. You already done it. You already
done it. It's [ __ ] just [Music]
boyfriend that girls. Go.
You're a crazy [ __ ] man. You need to
chill out, bro. You crazy [ __ ] I don't
know this guy. [Music] Cheers, man.
Cheers. Add me on WhatsApp. Add me on
WhatsApp. We staying full, bro. Yeah,
man. What's your number, buddy? [Music]
Yeah. Yeah. What's that? Buddy,
we need to send it, man. We need to send
bro. I just don't want to
What's your name? PJ. PJ. PJ.
Yeah. I got Yeah, literally my name, brother.
PJ. That's it, man.
But there's more people coming.
Huh? You want the B?
11. There you go. I'm on I'm on a beer
today, bro. No, no spirits. I If I drink
spirits today, I'm [ __ ] for three days.
Your friend's a crazy [ __ ] man. He's
still talking to them. Crazy [ __ ] He's
a crazy [ __ ] He's over there, bro. Did
you see me?
I was there for like 10 minutes.
I got her number. It's been a bit of a crunch. Yeah.
Got her number. All right. [ __ ] it.
We should go to another club. We should
go into another club.
Yes. Yeah. I reckon we really should.
I need to go
super I get two.
I'm try and get another
one. I got two numbers. No. Yeah. Yeah. All
right, let's go somewhere.
Oh, two numbers. I need some more numbers,
bro. I'll be back later. I'll be back
I will be back later on. Hey Monty.
Hey, that's a real Bonnie man as well. Get up
there. I won't try too much. Bonnie,
listen. Bro, what is your problem, bro?
Listen. You can't blame me for all this
YouTube [ __ ] I've had it as well, bro. bro. Yeah.
I've had it with this YouTube [ __ ] as
well, but you can't just blame me, bro.
And I know Natalie tells you about me as
well. Yeah, it's the real money. Yeah,
it's the real money. Hey, listen, Monty.
Listen. I know for a fact Natalie G has
told you about me. Yeah, I know for a
fact told you about me. Am I lying? No.
No. I'm not lying, bro. You see what I'm saying? Yeah, listen.
Listen, Bonnie, man. I got Nick. I got
nicked two weeks ago, bro.
Listen, Bonnie. Listen to me. Yeah. I
got nicked two weeks ago and I got
[ __ ] reminded in [ __ ] court. I had
to go court. Yeah. And I'm not going to
get into the ins and outs of it, but I'm
going to win the case, bro. I got
nicked. They tried to take my [ __ ]
phone. They reminded me in the police
cell, mate. I've had my f Bro, I've been
nicked for about 10 times over [ __ ] YouTube, bro.
Yeah, bro. Listen. Funny, bro. Listen.
They come to my [ __ ] house. They
tried to take my [ __ ] phone and they
reminded me in a [ __ ] police cell.
Bro, I had my fair share of problems
with this website. Believe that, bro.
Believe it. Believe it, bro. Yeah.
Why do you think I don't come here
anymore, buddy? This is why you don't
come on here anymore. Because of this [ __ ]
Yeah. It is Monty. It is money. No. No. Listen, bro. Bro,
listen. Money. I'm telling you,
bro. The police come on my door about
two weeks ago. They tried to take my
phone. They [ __ ] reminded me in a peace cell.
Yeah, I will talk to you about it off
YouTube if you ever want to know. But
I'm not talking about YouTube, bro. Trust me.
Yeah. Trust me, bro. It's a bad thing. I won't join.
Tell you money. [Music]
Here's money. Here's money. Money. Listen, bro.
Yeah. I told you to get off of YouTube a
long time ago. Yeah. I told you to get
off of YouTube a long time ago. Why do I
don't come on here anymore, bro? Monty,
listen. I always stuck up for you on
YouTube. I stuck up for you, bro.
Listen, bro. These people on
YouTube. Yeah. They've tried getting me
in prison. They've tried stopping my
money. Bro, if only knew a quarter of
what these people on YouTube have done
to me as well. Yeah. And I told you to
get off YouTube some time ago.
Yeah. I told you to get off YouTube.
That's why I'm not in here much anymore.
It's got a ticket. [Music]
Where the [ __ ] are these [ __ ]
Oh, look at his [ __ ] He's trying to steal my
bird. He's trying to steal my bird. But
I already got a
number. I'm done. I'm out of here. [Music]