Oh [ __ ] in hell,
bro. 100th one now. I think 100th
session, bro. It's getting boring now. This
is at least when you used to win, you
used to lose a lot as well. Lose a lot
as well. But that's three days done as
So, three days out the way.
Yep. Waiting back for my message from my
old good old thingy.
Yep. Yeah, man. Lad. Yeah. I'm not on
YouTube, man. I just wanted to like, do
you know what it is? Yeah. I feel like
just just because this is a gambling
community, right? Yeah. I feel like when
I'm in the mood for this, yeah, I want
to make it known in case anyone like
Well, people don't put Gabby, but to
make it known before you like even
[ __ ] do it again. It's [ __ ]
madness, bro. This is literally about
the 100th losing session on these
machines, but people say, "Oh, it's
gambling. It's gambling. You can't win.
You can win." Literally, you literally
can't win. I've literally not won in 9
months, bro. And you know what? I just
said to Ant, I was like, "Bro, you and
these people on YouTube are you, you are
delusional, bro. Even if you have money
and your bills paid, it will still
affect your whole mood. You don't need
to be skinned. You don't need to lose
loads and loads of money for it to
affect you." Like, I I don't know where
like I don't know how many times I've
had to say that. Yeah. To to to people
for them to actually understand. They
don't understand it. Like they really
really don't understand that you don't
need to lose all your money, half your
money, loads of money. You could be
comfortable still and it will still affect
you. You know, it will still affect your
whole mood. It's like I said, it's like
a parasite growing inside of your body,
mocking you when you lose. That's what
it is, you know. It's crazy. Yeah. I got
a two pound bonus and they pay me£9.
[ __ ] off. You know, [ __ ] off, mate. You
know what I'm saying? Yeah. It's
[ __ ] It's [ __ ] bollocks. It's
absolute [ __ ] bollocks, mate. You
know, it's absolute bollocks, mate. I
swear to God, bro. One of these days, I
don't really do it much anymore. Yeah, I
don't even do it much anymore. Obvious
obviously, you know, I go out and you
when I went out the past two days, I
didn't do it, bro. One of these days, I
will do it. And and I will go back, bro.
And I will go back. Trust me. This is
why I I stay away from this [ __ ] you
know? It doesn't matter. Grezy, if it's
enough to get one person like this, it's
that that's enough. If it's enough to
get one person like this, that is
enough. Well, let me get let me tell you
something, Grezy. Other people have not
been losing for 9 months. Other people
have not been losing for [ __ ] nine
months, have they? Yeah. Or eight months
or however long it is. Just losing streakers, you
know? Yeah. They've not been losing for
[ __ ] nine months, have they? Yeah.
It's a me problem, though, isn't it?
Grezy, even though I've seen betting
shops smashed up. Oh, it's not all on
the gambling places. Okay. Okay. Okay,
Grezy. So, I I'll give you an example.
So, I went in today with
£150. I was about to put my fist through
that whole machine. Why is that then?
You say it's a you problem. Okay. Got
money, got my bills paid. Okay. Why is
it a you problem? Why is it a you
problem? What did I do wrong, bro? What
did I do wrong? What did I do wrong,
bro? It doesn't need to be a grand. It
doesn't need to be a grand, bro. No, no,
no, no, no, no, no. It's not about the
amount of money you lose. It's just
losing is annoying. It don't need to be
a [ __ ] grand. Why does it need to be
a grand? Yeah, it wasn't a pound. It was
£150. But why does it need to be a
grand? Mate, Grezy, listen. The last
time I done it was I think it was about
10 days ago and it was about £100. I
smashed my whole mug and everything. I
had to buy a new mug. That was £100.
That was literally £100. You don't need
to lose a [ __ ] grand or big amounts
of money for it to affect you. It
doesn't need to affect you financially
to affect your mood. You absolute
imbecile. [ __ ] hell,
man. Jesus Christ.
Uh, what the [ __ ] You're crazy, man.
You don't need to lose big amounts of
money for it to affect you. It's just
losing kills the whole vibe, the whole
atmosphere. And it's the constantly
losing as well. It's the constantly
losing. You know, if you win sometimes,
I'll be like, "Okay, I lost. Fair
enough. Okay, cool." Bro, I Well, how
many people do I see behave like me?
Well, I Well, that's I can't help how it
makes me feel. I can't help how it makes
me feel. You can't help how it makes you
feel. Am I right or wrong? You can't.
No. So, there you go. Simple. Yeah. If
you can't help how it make You literally
can't help it. It's like somebody with
Tourette's. You can't help it. It's
[ __ ] annoying. It is
annoying. You know, it's annoying. It is
[ __ ] annoying. Nothing else gets you
like this. Literally nothing else does.
Nothing else [ __ ] well does. Nothing
does like this. Nothing does like this.
You know, nothing does like this. So,
stop [ __ ] saying, bro. Like, you need
to Yeah, I am leaving YouTube. I'm off
of YouTube, but I just feel like this is
like therapy sessions. Yeah, it's
annoying, bro. It's every time. I've
lost every time for about eight months.
Yep. I haven't been up once. Madness.
Yeah. I thought, you know what, Grezy? I
went to get some steak, some washing
stuff. Let me just nip in the bookies
with £150 knowing I had money left. And
guess what? I lost. So, mate, doesn't
matter if it's a me problem. You can't
help it. You literally can't help it.
You know, I don't have a problem
gambling. I don't have I don't have
problems with gambling. I've got money,
plenty of money. I rarely gamble. And
this is exactly what I'm saying. You
don't understand, mate. If I had a
gambling problem, I'd be s Do you really
want to know what somebody with a
gambling problem does? They sit there
and eat beans. They sit there and eat
cold beans. They're up to their neck in
debt. Bro, I don't have any of these
problems. You know, it's not about the
[ __ ] money. Just you don't, bro.
Listen, I have got money. I have got my
bills paid. I have got a nice juicy
steak today. It's not the money. It's
not the money. It's what I used to say
to Bomb over and over and over and over
and over again. I used to say the same
thing to Bomb. It's not about the
[ __ ] money. It is [ __ ] annoying.
Yeah, I remember before, right? I lost I
lost 20 pound. Yeah, in the Weather
Spoons. I think this was two weeks ago.
It was the last bank holiday, bro. I was
going to do something with that glass.
I'm not even joking. I had to speak to
the security guard and then he calmed me
down a little bit, but I was like, "Bro,
I was an ounce away from doing the
madness." And this is what it's not
about [ __ ] money. You don't need to
be skinn or have no food for it to to to
get you like that, bro. I don't Oh my
god. Yeah, it you you do you need to
stop because of how angry it gets you.
That's it. Not because you can't help
yourself, not because you can't help
yourself. That's the difference. You You
need to stop because of how angry it
gets you. Not because you lose all your
money. And that's it. Oh, it was a
Horus. I was playing I Horus. I got a
bonus two pound and it paid nine quid. Nine [ __ ]
quid. I'm not as angry today. But
Greavves, you know when I lost that£100
two weeks ago, I couldn't let it lie.
That's why I smashed the mug. I couldn't
let it lie, bro. It went on for like
three, four hours. I couldn't let it
lie. I swear to God.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I got n I got a 9 quid
uh bonus on a two on a two pound spin.
Yeah. Yeah. But it's like what Ant-Man
says, you can win. Look at the garments.
You can win. You know you've won. Look
at the garments. So he says, but nine
moms don't lie, bro. Nine moms don't
lie. Do Do I think I could stop? Of
course I could stop. I'm not addicted to
it. I'm not [ __ ] addicted. If I was
addict, if you was addicted, you would
be like Timmy. Yeah. You would have
nothing. Nothing. You'd be porn and
stuff. Yeah. I tell you a story. I
shouldn't even bait his name out. Yeah.
Ant-Man had about two and a half grand.
Yeah. Last week he's got nothing now.
Gambled a lot. He has nothing. He had to
borrow money. Yeah. That's that's bad.
And I said to him like, "Bro, I've
gambled a lot." Yeah. Yeah. And I I I I
think the most I've ever lost was two
grand, but I've never lost all my money,
bro. Not for like four years. Not for at
least four years. Yep. Literally, bro. I
said, "Bro, you lost you lost more than
me." And I And I had more than you.
That's [ __ ] madness. What the [ __ ] I
was like, "Nah, bro. That's that's
fucked." Our seems seems seems to come
in stages. He [ __ ] I think it was
about 2.8K loss. That is a madness.
Well, I think it was the FBI and
football when I lost money. When I lost
that two grand, I still had money. You
know what I'm saying? Any cold approach
is not come. Uh, not for you idiots. No,
I don't not for you little
idiots. No, I don't entertain these
weirdos on here anymore, man.
Bye-bye. Yeah, I don't I don't entertain
these idiots on here anymore. I do cold
approaches on my uh other channel for
new people to see. I don't really come
on this self-p projecting grassing
community anymore only to rant about
gambling just so people are aware.
There's no point really coming on it for any other
reason. It's the most weirdest
community. Do you know what? In a way,
yeah. Well, he's already got Thailand,
but but whether he'll be able to afford
to go now or not is uh is a different story. But
yeah, what's I saying?
Um, yeah, I kind of blame Timmy, you
know, right? I actually, if I didn't
gamble, then I wouldn't come across
Timmy's channel, then I wouldn't come
across this [ __ ] community with these
little weirdos. Grezy, think about it.
It all come from me being introduced to
a machine to me watching videos on it
and then me watching Timmy. How long
until I go to Thailand? None of your business,
man. Couple of months. There you go.
Done. Couple of months.
So, and these people are not trolls,
bro. Don't call them trolls. Don't call
these people trolls. They're just
self-reflectors. They're not [ __ ]
trolls, buddy. Stop calling them trolls.
They're not trolls. They're just
self-reflectors. They're just low lives.
That's what they are. They're just low
lives. That's what they are, bro. I
thought you thought I hated planes. Not
me, bro. I don't hate planes. I'm not
scared of planes. Not me. You got the
wrong person. But bro, they're not even
trolls. They're just low lives. Low life
self projectors. They're not even trolls,
man. Yeah, bro. What? Bro, I spent £50
on Sunday just drinking beer. Yeah, I
still like to go out and have a drink
before before I'm going away in a couple of
months. Yeah, but I'm going in a couple
of months. I'm still going to go out
every week and have some beers. Might as
well. What else is there to [ __ ] do?
But the West is dead. Yeah, it is dead.
But I just go out to drink anyways. It
is dead. It's is the way it is, you
know. Yeah, it is what it is. It is what it is,
man. But now I'm just going to go out
once a week instead of I done two days,
but is bank
holiday. Um, I'm going for the day.
Bye-bye. Lewisville Slugger, I can smell
you again, bro. I can smell you like
them chips in a fryer. You're very bad
at this trolling game. I'm telling you,
bro, you need to listen. It's getting
embarrassing, bro. I'm starting to feel
really bad for
you. Yeah. But yeah, anyways, it's not
about the money anyways. It's not about
the money. It's not about the money,
bro. I got a nice juicy steak today.
Anyways, it's not about the money. It's You
know they're not trolls, Jimmy. [ __ ]
Can you stop calling them
trolls? Can you stop calling these
people trolls? They're just low lives.
Stop calling them trolls. They're not
trolls. They ain't got the IQ to be a
troll. Stop it, bro.
Please. Seriously, man. Stop calling these people
trolls. So, I'm going Thailand and then
from Thailand, I'm going to go to
America from Thailand.
So, going to be there for a month, then
I'm going to [ __ ] off. Yeah. Try hard.
Yeah, there you go. And then I'm going
to go I'm not just going to come
straight back home. I'm going to go
there and then I'm going to come home.
It's going to be a little while, bro.
So, yeah, I've already know I already
know what I'm doing. So, but I'm still
going to go out every week on the beer.
Yeah, I agree with you. So, when I drunk
the beer on the um Sunday, was it on the
Sunday? The next day I was fine. I was a
little bit tired, but I was fine. When I
drunk [ __ ] rum on a Friday, bro, I
was [ __ ] the next day, bro.
Paranoia, [ __ ] headache, being sick.
That's I'm just going to stick to beer
now. I'm just going to stick to beer,
man. It's cheaper and you don't get the
hangovers, man. Anxiety and [ __ ] I
started getting like paranoia and that.
I swear to God, I thought people was
coming to like do me in or something. I
don't know where it come from.
That's why I just stick That's why I'm
just sticking to uh That's why I'm just
sticking to beer from now on because at
least I know I can go and get beer. I
can spend £60 every week. Yeah, I'll
spend £60 every week. I won't get no
hangovers. It's It's fine, you know? But
not that white rum. I was drinking white
We white [ __ ] rum is bad, bro. So
yeah, I'm just doing that now.
So I'll be out every week. I might mix
the days up. I might mix the days up,
but I'll be out every week. Once a week.
It's going to be one day a week though.
Only on only on two days last week cuz
it was bank holiday.
So yeah, it was bank holiday. So
yeah, it was the pink holiday.
Yeah. Nah, bro. I've got it all saved.
I'm saving. I've got it, bro. I've got it.
I've got it. I've got it all figured out.
So, I'm not just going to come back to
[ __ ] England, you know, cuz I want to
do the continent Asia, you know, before
I die. I think it'd be nice to say that you've done
Asia, unlike unlike Bomb and L cuz
they're not well traveled, you see.
They've basically been nowhere. So, it'
be nice to do anywhere in that
continent. So, you can just say, you
know, you've been there, you
know. So, yeah.
Thailand's not expensive. It's America that's
expensive. You go to Thailand for like
two and a half grand for the whole
month. Everything. It's America that's
expensive. Not [ __ ]
Thailand. We're talking like three.
You're talking like five grand for the
week in America. You
know, why not go China or
Japan? Um because I'm going to
Thailand so that's
why. [ __ ] £600 I spent over bank holiday. [ __ ]
hell. Just drinking football. [ __ ] It
weren't even gambling. I swear to God it
weren't even gambling. It weren't even
gambling. Swear to
God. Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Yeah,
that's what I'm saying. Yeah, America's
expensive. Like you even if you go for a
week here, you're talking about five
grand for everything just for you. Just
for you. Nice hotel. Nice hotel. Stop
calling yourself a [ __ ] We don't have
that on my
channel. Yeah. Stop calling yourself a
[ __ ] We don't have that [ __ ] on my
channel, buddy. We don't have self
projector on my
channel. Um but yeah. No. Yeah. So if
you want to like a decent decent hotel
in a week in America with spending money
is about four and a half grand. Yes it
is. Yes, it is. It's like that's like
three trips to [ __ ] Thailand almost.
That's what I'm saying. So, you should,
you know. So, that's that's that's what
do. But what I might do is when I go to
thingy, I might just I might stay there
for a month, maybe rent somewhere for a
month and then just work there for a
month. I think that's your best bet.
Just have two months away. Can make some
serious money over there. Cash in hand,
work, work there for a month, and then come back.
I think that would be your best bet, you
know? I think that would be your best
bet. Like even if they ask for a
deposit, I think just go there for a
month. Yeah. Rent like a condo and just like just
[ __ ] just Yeah. Just rent a condo and
just just just work there. Work there.
Do some approaches, make some money,
come back. Bob's your
uncle. Bob is your [ __ ] uncle.
So yeah, I think that's that's that I
think that's your best
bet. I think that's a good idea, is
it? They are, bro. They are. They are,
man. Oh, yeah. I read something about
this L. Yeah, I don't know why they keep
mentioning me, bro. I'm not even on here
anymore, but they were mentioning me,
bro, saying, "Oh, LJ
um um to be fair, LJ come to me and he
made me [ __ ] myself." LJ did not make
anybody [ __ ] themsel. I was standing in
front of my mom and I'm not going to
keep going over the story over and over
and over and over and over and over
again. Like the the the moral of it is,
yeah, you came here and you done
nothing. End of. You come here and you
done nothing. I don't need to go back
and forth, back and forth, back and
forth. I've told the guy a million times
he's more than welcome to come on my
door like he keeps going on Timmy's door
four times. I'm not going to keep going
back and forth, back and forth, back and
forth because to me, bro, it's keyboard
warrior [ __ ] And I'm not 11 and and I'm
not 10 years old. Like I was saying to
you the other day, when I hear Mark and
Timmy and all of that, I laugh at them
now. I laugh at these people because I
know that most of these people here are
grasses. I know that. And they're not
serious about fighting anyone. So you
just laugh at them. We just laugh at
them. You know, we they're just
something to laugh
at, you know? We can't even do videos
like saying meet me here, meet me there.
Like they're laugh. They're laughing
stocks, but they still come on YouTube
talking like they're bad. So, I just
ignore them, bro. I don't I don't get
into it with these
people. And the thing is, Harry, the
reason I don't get into it with these
people is because they're on YouTube. Do you
understand? People that are about that
life do not come on YouTube arguing and acting
bad. Everyone knows that. So, what's the
point, bro? It's You might as well just
live your life and chill, bro. Like, [ __ ]
[ __ ] arguing with people on YouTube
every day, man. That's life's too short
for all that [ __ ] Life's too short for
all of that that old bollocks, you
know. You never know, bro. Like, [ __ ]
all that. I'm done with all that,
bro. But sometimes Timmy's videos are
entertaining because he's like, "Oh,
meet me here, meet me there." I was
like, "Come on, you're not serious. Come
on, you're not serious, man."
Like, how long have you known where
people have lived and you ain't like why
do they still do this? Why do they just
shut the [ __ ] up? Get off of YouTube and
live their lives or actually put some
gambling content on on their channel,
you know? Like, I hear about this
Arsenal Mark does videos on me. I hear
about it, but I don't go to the channel.
I just laugh at it. I'm like, "Huh? Oh,
is he having is it his time of the month
again?" Where he's coming on YouTube
pretending to call people out. Is it
it's his time of the month again? You
know, it's his time of the
month, you know. He likes to do this in
the summer as well. Like, look, because
think about it. Yeah. With Mark, I know
what he does. Yeah. He's 55. He's an old age
pensioner. You know, he he doesn't have
a life, so he just comes on YouTube
pretending to call people out. So, I
just just whatever. Yeah. Okay. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Whatever.
Okay. Yep. Yep. You're coming Stratford.
You're going rob for. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Yep. Okay, bro. You know, like just
laugh at him. There's something to laugh
at, bro. Really
are. And they're so addicted to YouTube
as well. Imagine this LJ. He got caught
out on a scam and he's still on YouTube
every day. He's still on YouTube every
day and he can't get off YouTube, you
know? Imagine that. Even after being
exposed as a scammer, these people have
got [ __ ] in their life at YouTube. I
came on here to rant about the gambling
to make people aware and I'm gone again,
you know? I'm gone again.
Simple. And even then, they can't get
off of YouTube. Like, even when they
they [ __ ] up, you know what I'm saying?
It's madness, bro. [ __ ]
this. But the mo, like I'm saying, if
people was about that life like fighting
and they would be on people's doors,
they would they wouldn't be on YouTube.
And again, I'm not trying to start [ __ ]
and say, "Oh, like I'm about this and
everyone." No, I'm not, bro. I'm just
saying when it comes to these people, you
know, it's just just backwards.
Backwards. You know, at the end of the
day, yeah, if I if my biggest regret in
my life Yeah. is gambling. A because of
all of the problems it's caused, the
mood swings, and B, if I didn't gamble,
I would have looked up Timmy's name. I
wouldn't have found Timmy and I wouldn't
have found this community, this shitty
community. So, you know, that's that
would probably be my biggest regret, I
think, in my life if there was to be
one. If I could go back in the past and
change it, I wish I never got introduced
to a [ __ ]
property, you know? Would have been
nicked about 100 [ __ ] times as well.
So, why don't
you why do you just do your damning
videos and just stop doing these silly little
videos, you know? Mark, [ __ ] Timmy.
Why don't they just stop this [ __ ] now?
Seriously, it's boring. Like, it's it's
summer now, you know? It's actually [ __ ]
summer. Going to the butchers. Go get
some steak and cook some [ __ ] steak
or something, man. Get off of YouTube, you
know. [ __ ] It's It's crazy,
bro. Yeah, these people they do dally.
They do dally in their head. I'm telling you. Proper
dudally. It's like me. I go out every
week. I know I'm probably not going to
pull. I got some numbers. Some of them
replied back, but I just go out anyways
because what else is there to do? Yeah,
I just go out. I know that I'm out of
this country soon. Something to look
forward to every week. Oh, the football stopped playing
now. Look, bro.
Like I've actually got the football bet
here. I lost I think I lost this
football bet. I lost 60. This was over
the bank holiday. I done 60 on the
football bet. I think it's here
somewhere. Where is it? Yeah. So like,
but I can't look forward to the football
every week now cuz the season's
finished. But I just go out and have some
beers, you know? It's not a problem,
man. So yeah.
I just got a thingy. But anyways, I'm
going in a minute
here. But the point I was trying to make
is that I'm not addicted to gambling. I
don't lose all my money gambling. I don't go
hungryless because I've gambled. It's
just the mood swings that it gives me.
End of. and it doesn't make me want to
keep doing it and doing it and doing it
and doing it and doing it and doing it
it. And I was thinking to myself, like,
are you sure you're just not one of
these people that just don't like
losing? Like, because there's some
people out there that they just don't
like losing. They just don't like
losing. And I was saying to myself, nah,
I don't even think it's that, you know,
because I feel like if you won some of
the time, you wouldn't be asked. You'd
be like, okay, well, I lost. happens,
but it's the continuous losing. And if
you don't like losing as it is, you
shouldn't do it. Simple. This is what
you need to get ingrained in your head
before you think to yourself again, "Oh,
do it. It's only 100. You do not like
losing." Do not do it. Simple. Yeah,
losing is a part of life. But not losing
for eight months in a row. Losing is not
a part a part of life though, really, is
it? Because when I was eating three
times a day, I was keeping myself to
myself, what was I losing, bro? I wasn't
losing anything. So, no, losing isn't a
part of life really. How do you work
that one out? How is losing a part of
life? Not really. Not really. It's not a part of
life. So, and it can be avoided and it
can be minimized. So, that's it.
So, it's not a part of life, mate. It's
life. Cuz one day I will do it, bro. And
I will go back there and I will destroy
the machines and I'll get a big fat
five. That's what I'll get. And it's not
worth it. It's literally not worth
it. You'll be like that guy that went
back with a hammer and activated 15 on the pound.
H. It's not funny what happens to you
though, is it?
No, you are tapped, Greasy. You're [ __ ]
tapped. You're actually tapped. You are.
Oh, do you know what I had for my
breakfast on um Saturday?
Greavvesy Sunday. I had a load of old
bill for breakfast.
I had a load of old Bill for breakfast. It was
delicious. It was delicious. I put it
all in the pan. A load of old
Bill. Load of old Bill for breakfast.
Can't beat it, mate. Can't [ __ ] beat
it. Load of old
Bill. Very crispy as well. Yeah. I've
got steak for lunch today, Grezy. I got
steak for lunch.
Steak and onion rings and
mushrooms. Oh, I had KFC as well earlier, too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah. In a minute.
Take some money out the [Music]
next. What's the date
tomorrow? Yeah. Okay. Oh, that was a 599, wasn't
it? Yeah. So, I'll be out again. I can't
believe it's already Tuesday. Where the
[ __ ] is this week gone? But I was
pissing it up, though, weren't I
grievously? I was out there pissing it
up to be fair. I was out there giving it
a good piss
up having a piss up. I said to this
woman, "You should cook us a roast
dinner, a roast beef and a bit of pork."
She's like, "Oh, why is it the woman the
woman that always has to cook?" I said,
"Because I want some tasty roast dinner, you know."
very bad. It was funny. But
yeah, you win some, you lose some, eh?
Grievy. Greasy. You win some, you lose
some. So they say,
huh. So they [ __ ]
say. You win some, you lose some. [Music]
Not so sure about
that. Not so
sure. Not so sure about
that. You win some, you lose some. I've
not won in seven months, eight months.
I'm not so sure about that. I put a lot
of money in these machines and
nothing. I don't know, man. I I messaged
Adman saying, "I don't believe you
anymore. you're a
bullshitter. You can win some of the
time. You win 10% of the time. I just
said, "I don't believe you." I think
you're a total
bullshitter because if that was the
case, you would win. You would You'd be
winning. Would have won. You know,
load. Ah, you knew what I meant by that, didn't you,
Grezy? Ah, just a plate of bacon, you
know. Nothing wrong with a plate of
bacon. Ah, can't beat that. That gy just
a plate of
bacon. Just a plate of
bacon. You know, you ever had that
grievy? Just a plate of
bacon. You know, 10 slices of bacon in the
morning. Oh, yeah.
Anyways, I'm out of here and I'll be back
uh Saturday. Well, maybe. No, I won't be
back on this Saturday, but I'll be out.
I'll be out boogieing again, Grezy. I'll
be out having a little boogie. Having a
little boo. You like it when I'm in the
club, don't you, Greasy? Having a little
boo. Do you like it? Do you like it,
Greavves? When I'm out
there. when I'm out there having a
little boo the past two
days clown on the [ __ ] table. Oh
man. Could be worse. You could be like
Antman and have6 pound to your name and
he's worse as well cuz he doesn't get he
doesn't get as much money as me. So he's
like once he's lost like two and a half
grand he's [ __ ] He needs to save all
that money back
up. Yeah. Boogie the night
away. Ah, bless
you. Boogie the night away, mate. Just a bit of beer.
Yeah. Yeah. I got a lot of it on Sunday.
Boys, do you remember that? I said to
man, how's it going, man? You still in
the weather spoons? He's like, they all
got a boyfriend. I was dead. I was dead when he
said they all got
boyfriends. Yeah, they've all got
imaginary boyfriends, bro. That's
England for you, man. Get used to it or
[ __ ] leave. You know what I'm saying?
They've all got [Laughter]
boyfriends. Anyways, I'm out of here,
man. I'll be
back for know I'll be back for a very
long time. though in a