Yeah, been a
long stretch the old speed.
There we go. That's the
level. There we go. Lad, let me tell you
something. When a few more people join.
Yeah. Nah, not anymore, mate. Not
anymore. You people really thought I was
going to go prison. And that's one of
the reasons I'm done with this community. the
grassing, the um repeating, the self-p
projecting. Bro, I was literally done
with this [ __ ] even before all of that.
Yeah, but I'll reply in a minute, lad. Yeah.
Listen, let me tell you something. Yeah.
When more people join. Yeah. You want
know numbers? I'm always getting
numbers, mate. What you all about? I
actually felt like doing some approaches
today, but I didn't bother. Listen, man.
I'm going to let more people join and I
shouldn't even be entertaining this
keyboard. Oh, I got a DVS check by the
way. Um, I had to do it for a certain
thing I'm doing. I'll show you if you
want. I've covered all the details.
So, how sure are you,
mate? Where was it? I've got a criminal record.
Yeah, I've never had a criminal record
in my life. Hey, look.
That's me. I had to get this DBS thing.
Cost me money. Don't have a criminal
record. Never had a criminal record.
Ain't ever getting a criminal record.
Even when I'm
31. Yeah. Simple.
I had to get this for some reason. Good
luck, man. Hey,
listen. One second, bro. Let more people join.
Listen. Right. Red
Star, you want to try and say how you
control people while I control you. Cuz
guess what? You will never ever tell
anyone on here where you live, what
location you live, what city you live,
cuz I'm just going to go there and go
live. So stop saying that you control
people. But bro, I've been controlling
you for 3 years. How many times has your
[ __ ] ass been asked to show where he
is? I'm not even asking you to come on
my door. [ __ ] coming on my door. You can
live anywhere and that'll be your
excuse. I don't want you to come on the
door, bro. But how many times have you
been asked to show where you are or say
where you are and you haven't done it,
bro? The only one that's being controlled is yourself. You
know, the only
um person that's being controlled Red Star is
yourself. And you don't even have a call
to her. You're just a natural [ __ ]
Yeah. You're fast enough to um beg
London Taylor. You beg London Taylor.
You beg every Tom and Dick and Harry,
bro. Why are you sat there begging
people to do your dirty work when you
can't even show where you are? Who's the
one that's really being
controlled? Like, do you really think a
man will ever tell will ever make me
scared to say where I am? No. No. No.
And if you notice, right, when these
people go on Timmy's channel, they don't
even say it then because they know. They
just put people like this Red Star,
right, and this Jamie Thompson, bro?
They're just 40 year old virgins that
have got nothing in their life but YouTube.
Yeah. Don't have a criminal record. I I
just showed you my criminal record.
Check. I just showed you my criminal
record. I don't have a criminal record.
I've just shown you my
DBS. Nah. Never getting a little fright,
mate. Nah, I'm not scared of no one. So,
don't We've seen you on Timmy's. Yeah, I
saw you on Timmy's the other day. Sat on
YouTube. Red star. You're 40year-old
virgin. You ain't got a life. Yeah, you
ain't got a [ __ ] life. You
40-year-old sad virgin. Don't sit there.
Yeah, you you mate, listen. You control
me, mate. I I control you. You can't
even say where you are. And you are the
manta. You can't even say where you are,
you little scared [ __ ] Anyways, one
second. I'm going to start blocking
people in a minute as well. Listen,
manta, you are the one that's
controlled. You can't even show. You
can't even say where you are. That's
embarrassing, bro. About how how like
literally literally you can't even say
where you are. Listen listen, bro. I'm
telling you right now, Red Star, tell us
where you are. If you're not controlled,
tell us where you are. But he's not
going to do that, brother. Because she's
he's a 40-year-old virgin. Listen, bro.
Go on that Red Star page. He's some fat
virgin that lives with his mother. I'm
telling you, bro. Look how long this
loser has been on YouTube. Yeah.
Obsessing over me time and time again.
He's a loser. He's a 40 year old virgin.
He's got no money. I'm telling you, bro.
I swear down. I never lied to you, bro.
Just when I told you, bro. I told you for
ages. Don't have a criminal record.
Don't have a criminal record. Don't have
a criminal record. Don't have a criminal
record. Don't have a criminal record.
Don't have a criminal record. Hey, I
just showed you two pages. Yeah.
Look. Where is
it? Look. Can you read? I had to get
this for a certain reason. There's a
reason I had to get something. I had to
get it for some reason. Yeah. Like, allow it.
Yeah. But yeah. Anyways, nature girl,
that's why there's no point being on
this um community. This is why I don't
comment. I can tell you everything that happens, bro.
They're going to sit on YouTube, call
you what they are themselves, run to the
They run, these people run to the police.
Um, they What else they do? You get
Arsenal Mark that pretends he's a hard
man. It's boring now, bro. Stop it. It's
boring now. Uh, I I just showed my
criminal record check, Joe. Yeah, I had
to get a criminal record check for
something and I don't have a criminal
record. So, yeah, I just got out of
Well, I just come back from
court. So, yeah, I've got to go back in
three and a half
years. I've got to go back to court in
three and a half years.
Oh, and listen, Red Star, you don't
control anybody, mate. I've been asking
you to say where you live for years. You
are the one that's controlled. Let's
Let's start talking about that. Yeah.
You come on YouTube every day. You beg
London Taylor to do your dirty work, but
the scared little controlled boy won't
show where and tell where he is. And
you've got no court order. So what's
what's what what's your excuse for being
the [ __ ] You know what I'm
saying? You know, nah. Nah, Joe. I can
leave the I can leave the country. It
probably get dropped before the three
and a half years to be honest. They say
there's a big chance of it getting
dropped, but No, I can leave the country
and everything. No, no, not really, bro.
I can leave the country.
Everything. No, no, no, no. It's not
like that. So, I just basically said
that like these people have been
harassing me. I've got everything these
people have done
and I'm literally willing to take it to
trial. Like, I've got everything. No,
bro. It's not a suspended
sentence. Yeah. I can leave the country.
I can do what I want.
They say I've got to go back in 3 years,
but chances are they're going to drop it by then.
So, yeah. So, no, there's I can do what
I want. But
yeah, like I just said to the solicitor
that like I've got people harassing me,
everything. I've got everything on my
phone. I'm not pleading guilty. And he
said that like, oh, if if you do if you
don't do it, then you just got to come
back in like three and a half years. By
that time, they would have probably
dropped it. So, and it gives me and it
gives me a chance to obviously build up
a case on these people. So, it's
Yeah, I'm not going to get into it, bro.
I'm not going to get into it. So, yeah.
But that's why I don't [ __ ] with this community
anyways because um yeah, I know that I'm
not going to get in trouble. Yeah. But
that's it. So,
anyways. So, yeah. Yeah. Anyways, we're
going to talk about this so much. So, that's
over. Ah, I'll be 30 [ __ ]
one. Yeah, there's so much against me.
Anyways, I'm going to start blocking
people if you keep bringing up now. I'm
done talking about it. I'm not talking
about this anymore, bro. I'm here. I'm
not in jail. Yeah, you failed. So, that's
it. I'm not talking about it no more. No
more approaching girls anymore. Are you a [ __ ]
[ __ ] Are you a [ __ ] [ __ ] I'm
literally out. I can do what I want. You
a [ __ ] or something? Are you Are you
an actual [ __ ] You can just hear
what I've just said, you [ __ ] God,
these people are [ __ ] So, anyways,
Joe. Anyways, you seem like the only
person on here that has somewhat of a
brain. There's no point coming on this
community anymore. This is why I don't
comment anymore because it's like what
you said, bro. It's that Do you know
what? It's kind of like what you said,
lad. Yeah. It's that these people,
right, they come on here. Yeah, I can
approach. I can do what I want when I
want. Unlucky for you. Listen. Anyways,
Joe. Ah, I got a [ __ ] blister on my
foot. Uh, it's like what you said. Yeah.
These people want to torment people.
These people want to do all of this [ __ ]
to people every day, but then at the
same time, they're trying to get them in
prison. So, it doesn't make any sense.
It doesn't make any sense because it's
like what you said. Okay. So, say they
ruin your life, right? And say you ended
up in prison, which is not going to
happen. Then what? And because of all of
the grassing that they do. Yeah.
Yeah. Listen. And because of all of the
grassing these people do, Joe, it's
going to make people not want to come on
YouTube. It's literally like I'm done,
bro. Like, these people can call me what
they want. They can do what they want as
soon as like cuz I thought Yeah. And and
the thing is, Joe, you have to actively
pursue it. Like cuz obviously when like
when these people was calling the police
on me, bro, I had to call I had to call
um like the police to basically so when
it if it goes to trial, I have my
evidence. And you think, oh, you just
report it. No, no, no, no, no. You've
got to actually harass the police every
like you have to keep getting on them,
on them, on them, on them, on them,
which is what I had to do. So it's like,
so hold on a minute. What what side are
these people on? or they the bad man or
are they the the
crybaby? Because they have to actively
pursue it. So hold on. You're acting pe
these people are acting bad on the
internet. They're begging LT to do their
dirty work yet in the
background these people are crying to
the police and somehow they think that's
them winning and they somehow think
that's them winning. Really, bro. And
trust me Joe, it's not that they've
these people call the police once. They
harassed them. They harassed them. Trust me, bro.
So, yeah. Like, trust me. And I said to
them, like, why has it gone to crown
court? Like, why is it crown court? And
they said that I said to go to crown
court. I never said to go crown [ __ ]
court. It should have been dealt with at
a magistrate magistrates. And then they
said, "Oh, there's been a [ __ ] up
somewhere." So, I knew that there's no
way, bro, crown court is where [ __ ]
pen like drug dealers go and [ __ ] drug
dealers, you know, murderers, [ __ ]
drug dealers. That's what But apparently
I said, but you get a fair sentence
there anyways, to be fair. And they said
there's no chance of you going prison.
No chance. I'm not going to lie, I [ __ ]
myself, bro. I was scared. Like, not
like cuz obviously you hear about crown
court, never been caught in your life.
Like I was scared. I'm not going to lie
to you. But, you know, I I knew that
like But yeah, they it was
Yeah. Yeah. It last about 10 minutes,
Joe. It last about 10
minutes. 10 [ __ ]
minutes. But yeah, this is why I don't
[ __ ] with this community anymore,
bro. I got my criminal record check to
start a certain thing. I It come the
other day. I don't [ __ ] with this
community anymore. We we know the story,
Joe. We know the story. We've been
there. We've done it. We've worn the
t-shirt. We know the story now. So, it's
just going to not make one of people
just come online, you know? And like
it's mad. So, and they have no shame.
Like, there's no point calling these
people a loser, Joe, because they've got
no shame. They have no shame. Like, so
there's no point even saying anything to them. So
yeah. No, I didn't wear the Sony, mate.
I wore my [ __ ] Mal t-shirt. So
there's no point, bro. And I don't even
gamble anymore, Joe. So there's no point
me even putting anything out there. I
don't even gamble no more. I just
Yeah, I was trying to recover from this
foot injury. So I'm just done with this
[ __ ] no more, bro. So the very thing
these people have tried to do, they've
done the opposite now because now we're
just not going to come on YouTube. Same
as Monty. So it's that that's that's all
is, you know, and it's not even if you
don't go to prison, it's not it's not
even that. It's a madness, bro.
Like, so that's why there's not even no
point. So they've this defeated it's
like Red Shaw can say what he wants,
bro. At the end of the day,
yeah, he that Red Shaw can say what he
wants. He controls people. But guess
what? How many times have I asked this
guy to show me where he is? And he
won't. So, it is what it is,
man. So, they've defeated the object
because now we're just not going to come
on YouTube. Simple. I've got a new
channel, by the way, Joe, and I'm
building it. Yeah, I've got some sick
content on my uh One second
here. I've got some approaches today,
but this could be [ __ ] I was going here. But
yeah, celebrate, brother. I got other things
doing. Oh, is he? That's nice for him,
man. Oh, really? That's nice for him.
But nah, I can't trust you, Joe. I I
made a new channel to get away from
these people. The grass and the repeat
and the self projector. I literally done
it to get away from these people. I only
come on here like every week and say,
"Timmy, you're still on YouTube. Greasy,
you're still on [ __ ] YouTube." Like,
that's just a thing that I [ __ ] do.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Like,
it's just a thing that I [ __ ] do,
bro. You know what I'm
saying? So, yeah, that's why I don't And
yeah, it's just not worth it, bro.
So, he's coming.
Get me up here. P. Yeah. Turn my camera off.
Wait a second.
Yeah. Yeah. I went to court, man.
Yeah. What happened?
I just said not get I just said I just
said these people have been harassing me
and that and then they said, "Oh, well,
the trial was in three and a half
years." So I said, "Okay, they're fine,
Tim." You know what I mean? Half years.
Three and a half years. Yeah.
Yeah. What you need to do now is just
grab as much of D as you
can. Whole album at Monty. I've got a
whole album of what these people have
done, bro. I've got like [ __ ] 110
pages, brother, of what these people
have done. Yeah. Yeah. But what what is
it about? Why you going caught?
I'll tell you off. I'll tell you off
here, bro. Like I can't say too much on
here it cuz these people like you know
what I'm saying like obviously I would but yeah.
Yeah. What is it for all this
approaching [ __ ] and all? No no no
not at all bro. Not at all. Not at all.
It's not even anything to do with a woman.
And now that's now people now people are
just not going to come on. You know what
they what they're doing when they're
doing all this. People just not going to
come on like you don't come on no more
so there's no point you know no I'm in a
[ __ ] new relationship hang not come
on YouTube like they're just going to
repeat and [ __ ] so [ __ ] them I bro I
don't come much I
don't I just don't bother with it no
more bro like yeah I don't I can't be
bothered with it I'm not [ __ ] up my
relationship for these little clowns or
doxing this address or nothing like so I
don't live much anymore. No, I don't.
But even if they had your address,
they're not going to do nothing because
they apparently know where I am. So
what? It's just weird. It's just weird,
bro. It's weird. It's weird.
Yeah. Do you know who I'm with now?
Obviously, bro. What? Stupid. Okay. So,
you know I'm with now? Yeah, of course,
man. Everyone knew
that. You know what I'm saying?
Does she talk about me?
Do you talk about him? Do you don't know
I might be going Birmingham next week
actually. Uh, I might be going
Birmingham next week. Oh, yeah. Yeah. I
met somebody from Birmingham in London
um two weeks ago. They went back to
Birmingham in it. They live there. So, I
might [ __ ] go. That's not too far. Why not?
I thought I'm not meeting you. No, I'm
not saying you. I'm just saying I'm
going there. I'm not asking you to meet
me. You [ __ ] Yeah. What do you want
me not to meet you, PJ? And all you
around? I'm just saying I'm going there.
It's pointless, isn't it? It is
pointless. It's just [ __ ] weirdos. PJ.
Yeah. I can't believe money. I went to
court over that.
Yeah, you be going have you got to go
back and have they got evidence on you?
Yeah, but it's only a it's only a small
thing. But I've got evidence on these
people, too. And I'm calling the police
on these people, too. I've been I've
been following it up in that, Monty,
because you have to, is it? So, it's not
even that. It's not even that when I did
the riots and that in Plymouth and that
[ __ ] the police don't even go in
touch with me. I don't even know what
was happening with me.
You might go.
Yeah. How long was you going to sell for?
They were keeping me in. They was going
to keep me in longer. They were going to
keep me in for
[ __ ] till I go to court, but they
didn't. Yeah, they they reminded me.
They reminded me.
Yeah, they only allowed to keep you in a
cell for 24 hours unless you got to go.
I had to go to court in the morning.
They Bro, they come, Monty. They tried
taking my phone in it. I put I put it
like I hid it in it cuz they were trying
to take my phone. You know how they try
to take your phone and that? Yeah. I've
got to go back to police station only to
get my other phone cuz the police told
me I need to go and pick my phone up. So
I need to pick that phone up.
Yeah. So basically Yeah. So bro, so then
I had to hide the phone. Then they put
me in a cell. Then they they took me to
court in the morning. The court let me
go and then I had to I came back and I
and I got the phone in it. I was hoping
the phone was still there.
But your phone's still there, right? Yeah.
Yeah. I trust it, but I trust it. I
trust it in the garden.
But yeah, if you didn't have nothing on
that phone and then you would have been
okay. No, Monty, because they would have
gave my phone back for like months.
Yeah, I Yeah, I didn't get my phone on
my phone, Monty. But bro, they've took
my stuff before and they've not gave it
back. Sometimes they don't give it back
or they don't give it back for [ __ ] months.
Yeah. I've got to go to a police station
and get Man, I got a police letter here
telling me I got to pick up my phone.
Yeah. Yeah. Look, I'm not showing the
[ __ ] letter if they would I would
have gave it to them. [ __ ] that. Got a
chance cuz when they take it, they don't
give a sometimes, bro. It clicked on. It
clicked on. Yeah. No, I'm not showing a
letter. But yeah, I've got a letter here
um of the police telling me I need to
pick up my
phone and but I was about to show it but
I'm not showing it cuz the the address on it.
I [ __ ] nearly doxed myself. I didn't I didn't.
What would you do if you went to court
cuz these people you'd go not guilty
obviously isn't it?
It depends if you if you've done it then
yeah I go guilty like with the riots I
you there's proof on you you got to go
guilty what did you did you did you did
you go to court no man I played a
[ __ ] [ __ ] card mate
you did you get charged
no I haven't been I know I've not been
charged with [ __ ] all I'm on my last
chance though yeah bro you need to be careful
I'm on my last chance with the police
anyway. So yeah,
not being careful. I don't know why
these people are saying that they
control me when they can't even show
where they are or tell people where they
are. That doesn't make sense. Well,
these people troll themselves the way
they look. PJ, I know, bro. I know.
Yeah, for real.
The way they look, they troll themselves daily.
Every day. every day.
Yeah. So, you been doing any more dick
fing videos, PJ? Huh? Have you been
doing any more porno videos?
Nah, I've got another channel. I've got
another channel, man, where I put
content out there where none of these
weirdos know about because I don't want
them following me.
Yeah, but you know, they are going to
follow your PJ. They don't know the
channel. No, but money, they don't know
the channel. How? They can't find it.
Yeah, but they will find it. That's the
thing. They will find the channel and
you know they will. Well, in like 10 years maybe.
I don't know PJ. You know what these
people are like? They've already found
[ __ ] Yorkie again.
Really? Yeah. They found Yorky's address
again. Yeah. York is [ __ ] again.
Yeah. I went back to my I went to my I
went to my mom's the other day.
Yeah. And you residing with her, weren't
you? No. And the neighbors never said anything, bro.
So, what fascination do you get out of
Monty? I've also got where like where
they've like sent um letters to labors and [ __ ]
Yeah, they've done that with me sent
letters to my neighbors. So, I've got
I've got all the like I got all evidence
of like what these people have been
doing. And they they deleted Molly, but
they don't think I've got everything.
But I do. I have everything, doesn't it?
Three and a half years. Eh,
three and a half years of what [ __ ]
Yeah, man. That's why I don't bother
with this anymore.
Yeah, I've been offering L J out to meet
me. He won't meet
me. No, won't meet me.
Yeah, you only meet weasels like yourself, PG.
Nah, mate. He meets Timmy.
No, he meets people like Timmy, mate. My
mate. Oh, [ __ ]
That's long to take to trial, is it?
Three and a half years. Yeah. They don't
forget they're trying to get as much
evidence as they can on your PJ. That's
what what they probably trying to do. to
get as much [ __ ] as as possible. Yeah,
but I've got [ __ ] on these people, so
it's not this has the police have the
police got evidence on anything you've done?
Not major. No,
what evidence have they got? Obviously,
when you get interview, they show you
video clips or voice clips or text what you've done.
Just I'll tell you off of here, bro. I'm
not discussing it on here.
Well, add me on Facebook. Add me on
Facebook. If you hear me egg, you know
it. Yeah. Yeah. But you and I, bro,
where are you? You add me. You blocked
me now. I'm I've got a new Facebook.
Mine's a new Facebook. It's a picture of
me and Natalie together. Well, in a tent.
No, there's not, bro. What?
multi- multi-man needs.
Yeah. Yeah. Add me. Add me on Facebook,
Pete. There you go. You done it. Yeah, I
did. I just did. Yeah.
I'm accepting it now. Yeah, I got it.
I'll tell you quickly what it's about
and I'll go back live. Yeah. One one
second. Let me tell you voice you. Yeah.
Yeah. One sec. One sec. Okay. Yeah. Go
on. Go on.
Ben, you're a fake account. You little
weirdo. Sort yourself out.
Ben, I don't want to talk about you and
Kaye. Have fun with her. Yeah,
anyway. Yeah, I know it is.
I've got my angel sat next to me.
Yo, fake Ben, why don't you sort
yourself out and get a job?
Yeah, I'm screenshotting that,
lad. Yeah, thank you for that. Thank
you. I send that that that to my mom. Anyways, here
is here we go. M
I mates with someone who called social
services on your kids.
Oh yeah. No, PJ. Oh, you he's all about Pia.
See what he's doing.
It want to see what he's been up to. Yeah.
Oh, here we go.