Just a quick
check. Um, see if it's the same people every
day. Obviously, they come on here, call
you low life, skin, etc., etc., etc. So,
I don't want to see anyone on my live
stream cuz I'm the skin low life
apparently. I don't want to see none of
these people on my live stream.
Yeah. Oh, same people every day on
YouTube. Same people every
day. Yeah. I had a Lust barbecue two
days ago. It's all on the main channel,
you see. I don't post anything for these
little mongos anymore, the little grass
and repeaters. Shame really, but because
there's some content videos to be had to
be put out there, but nah, I don't [ __ ]
with the grassing
community. Not me, lad. I just come
watch to see if it's the same people
every day. Same people, same argument.
And it always
is. Always is. Same people every
day. You know, I could have a barbecue
today. I've got one or two,
but I had one two days ago. Mother one next week.
Yeah, [ __ ] spent £150 [ __ ] two
days ago just on meat, barbecue, [ __ ]
ice cream, and
[ __ ] It's bad. So, yeah, next week
definitely. I'm not talking about it no
more, bro. I'm done with it. I'm over it
now. Stop bringing it
up. Yeah, I'm not talking about this
[ __ ] no more. It's boring now,
bro. Yeah, I'm out. I'm free. I can
leave the country when I want. I can do
what I want when I want. I'm over it.
I'm not talking about it no more. End the
story. Oh, you must be late, bro. Oh,
well, okay. Let me tell you what
happened then. Basically, um, someone on
YouTube grasped me, then I had to go to
court, then I went not guilty, and yeah,
I got a trial in three and a half years.
Oh, sorry, man. There you go. Basically,
to cut a long story
short, yeah, the police come to the
house, they tried taking my phone. Um, I
hid it from them and yeah, just just and
even though like I basically got away
with it because let let's face it,
right, in three and a half years,
they're not going to do anything. I can
do what I want. Like, but it's not it's
not it's not a point. Like, you could
have lost your phone that day. Yeah. You
could have lost your phone, everything
on your phone and all of the stress.
There's no point being on the grassing
community. That's why I just said let
them have YouTube. That's why when I see
Monty and Timmy argue, I just laugh at
it. I was like, "Yep, yep, yep. We've
heard all of this before." So that's why
like it doesn't matter that you've got
away with it or you can do what you
want. It's it's not the point, bro. It's
not the [ __ ] point. The intent was
still there. The police was going to
they come, they was going to take my
[ __ ] phone and the whole madness of
it all. There's no point being on a
grassing community, bro.
I kind of like quit before that because
the repeating and [ __ ] in the self
projecting, but I was like, "Oh, it's
still fun to come on now and then, but
then when you got grasses, nah, that's
me done, bro." But yeah, I'm having to
[ __ ] report these people now every
[ __ ] week in order to safeguard
myself, which is mad because no one
should be calling the police on anyone,
you know? Nobody should be calling the
police on anyone. Now I have to [ __ ]
do it to self [ __ ] to to protect
myself. You know what I'm saying? So
because obviously if it does go to court
in three and a half years, they're going
to wonder, well, you've reported it.
This person, you know what I'm saying?
So it's I need to actually do it to like
but no one should be calling the police
on no one. That's what I'm saying.
That's why I don't come on here anymore.
I just come on here just to see if it's
the same people
that you know.
And you got people making up rumors. I
can't I can leave the country whenever I
want. Do you not understand what bell
conditions is? Yeah. I've got one bell
condition and that's it. I can do what I
want when I
want basically. Yeah. And the bell
condition is is actually a good thing.
Anyways, it's actually a good thing that
happened. Um anyways, I was just
explaining to this guy. Yeah. I had a
barbecue two days ago,
Joe. I went to buy some meat, a
barbecue. I spent 150 quid. 150 quid. I
spent 150 [ __ ]
pounds. Had a nice T-bone. Yeah, this
scaff is looking nice now. I've done the whole gaff
up. I' got some bruises on my arm though
from lifting it back. But yeah, but
yeah, it is the pitch, bro. It wouldn't
even be so bad if it wasn't for the
grassing. Do you know what I'm saying?
Like, do you really think I can't go to
Birmingham next week and call every
single one of them out and I guarantee
you no one's going to step to me? Yeah,
but there's no point because they're
glasses. So, what's the point? And it's
not just one person. You need to
remember that. It's not just one person.
It's a lot of people on
here. It's a lot of people on here. It's
not just one person. We can't just blame
one person. Been happening for years,
lad. You know the grassing on this
community, you know. Have you tried? Nah.
Yeah, I had a nice barbecue, bro. It's
[ __ ] I don't gamble anymore, do I?
So, lots of um lots of spare money.
Well, I did anyways. But it's the grass
and they come on here every day like
they're bad. Yeah. Coming on here like
they're bad. And then they go crying to
the police. So, hold on. Which one is
it? Are you bad man or are you a grass?
Like, which one is it? And they don't
just report it once. They have to they
have to literally harass the police as
well. That's another thing you need to
grass still grass regardless. But to let
you know, they have to continuously keep
following it up cuz I've had to do it as
well. You know, obviously I've had to do
it because to to protect myself. So
yeah. Yeah. I've got so many enemies,
but guess what? None of them would ever
come on my door. Yeah. Bad man grasses.
That's why I would never like say
anything about LT and that like okay
yeah he tried to come on the door he
tried killing me good for him bro but he
didn't grass so at the end of the day
bro I'd rather someone come in my house
and try and kill me than than a dirty
little grass you know what I mean can't
stand especially somebody that starts it
themsself they come on there like
they're some Billy big bollocks then
they go crying to the police and think
they've won [ __ ] them bro it leave them in
Let them have their [ __ ] and I can
actually leave the country by the way
cuz everyone knows what the bell
condition is. So
yeah, [ __ ] that, bro. Hell
no. Bad man grasses, bro. They all do
it. Timmy, they all do it, bro. People
from Lar's channel, loads of them do it.
Loads of them do
it. Cuz I've got a criminal record
check. Yeah. Uh, I think it was last
week cuz I had to apply for this job
thing. Yeah. And it come back clear. I'm
surprised it came back clear to be
honest. Um, I'm surprised it come back
clear to be fair. Like, no rest shows,
nothing. You know, I've had loads of
dealings over this stupid [ __ ] community.
And like I said, just because it's not
for three and a half years or they've
dropped it, it doesn't matter. The point
is, oh, what happened? It doesn't
matter, bro. You're not going to prison
anyways. But it's N. [ __ ] that. [ __ ] that, bro. You
know, because the thing is, if they took
my phone, I would have physically took
it back off them, you know, and I would
have got myself in serious serious
trouble. And it's not worth it, you
know. We get the point now, you know,
like if if the police took the phone, I
would have personally took it back off
them no matter how I how I'd have to do
it. And trust me, it would have been a
pretty sight. So, we get the point now.
There's no freedom of speech on social
media. There's no freedom of speech on
social media. So, that's why I don't
really go on it
much. I just talk to this person and try
and meet them, but I don't really [ __ ]
with this [ __ ] no
more cuz it's all to do with social
media. They only care about stuff that
happens on social media, bro. They don't
care about stuff that's not, you
know. So then I got a foot injury
because of it as well. [ __ ] all that.
They have their shitty little YouTube, you
know. Is what it is, bro. I've been
doing it for
years. I'm going to have a steak today,
but not on the
barbecue. [ __ ] Took ages trying to
light that [ __ ] cop.
I'll show you a picture of it if you
want, but I'm not putting no videos on here
though. I'll show you the barbecue if want.
Yeah. What I think it is with this
community, they're just a bunch of old
age pences that ain't got a life. That's
what I think personally. the old days
pensioners where their lives are ruined
so they want to try and ruin other people's lives.
Yeah. Just low lives basically. Yeah. Never change. Oh
[ __ ] Almost dropped that there. Look at
that lovely barbecue.
Look at that lovely barbecue.
Adman's going [ __ ] Thailand soon. I
don't think he wants to really go there
and not come back though. I've got this
feeling because he keeps going on about
oh me and you again. I was like brother
listen there's no me and you. I don't
care about these women no more. Like
it's mad like you seem to you seem to
care more than I do. It's crazy. Like
you remember how I used to care. Oh, I
don't give a [ __ ] anymore. You know what
I'm saying? But he still seems to care.
Like, and I said, like, you do
understand like if you go to Thailand,
you got to work. If you stay here, you
don't have to work. But I'd rather I'd
rather stay here and make more money and
have no woman cuz you could you can pay
for [ __ ] sex. You can still like or
or struggle, should I say. You can still
go out and [ __ ] try. But I'd rather
that than [ __ ] be guaranteed one and
have to work and earn [ __ ] money for a
woman or for a woman. I'd rather have [ __ ]
money. I'd rather have money and get
someone two times a year, bro, than [ __ ] [ __ ]
that. This guy can't be serious. And you
know the baddest thing is he's older
than me. Yeah. And he he's mature. He's
not immature. But I was like, bro, do
you realize what you're actually saying?
Like it's mad because it's not like
you'll have a better life. You'll have a
better life over there with the women,
but you you're going to have to work and
[ __ ] So, it's not worth it. It's still
a good place to go. I'm going in two
months as well living there. I don't know about
that. But he seems to care more than me.
I don't give a [ __ ] about these women no
more, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] about any of
them. I'd rather get money, bro. You
know what I'm saying? Like, but
They just ain't worth
it. I've not been out for [ __ ] a
while, you know? I don't really care
about these women,
bro. Got a nice life here. I can have a
barbecue when I want. I can spend money
when I want. Why the [ __ ] do I want I
don't care, bro. I don't even get cravings
anymore. [ __ ] them, bro. Ain't it? I've
had them. They're all the same. They're all devious. you
know, cuz I've just been watching like
some documentaries and stuff. Yeah.
I was watching something in Liverpool.
Yeah. Where this woman got shot in a
house and I was like, "Well, what do you
expect? You're dating a drug dealer."
And what happens when someone's a drug dealer?
You know, you're very much involved in
that life and then you wonder why you
have people in your door if you're
dating a [ __ ] drug dealer. Come on
now. Being a drug dealer, you got rival
gangs after you. You got to watch your
back for [ __ ] police. Come on
now. Like they say they want a nice guy,
then they go with drug dealers or not
even just drug dealers, it's [ __ ]
and then they moan and then some even
get killed. It's a madness, isn't it?
I mean, what the [ __ ] do you
expect a drug
dealer? What the [ __ ] Stupid, isn't
it? It's a mad. It's a madness,
bro. I can never be a drug dealer, man.
Nah, it's too risky. I'd never do
that. Never ever
ever. I like my freedom too much.
So Ice, ice, ice. Come on.
Yeah. Could technically meet this
person, but then it means going all the
way up by a [ __ ] man. So can I be bothered again?
Then I was going to say to her maybe we
should go Blackpool. But why am I going
to spend £3400 going Blackpool and I can
just book a holiday for another holiday
for £3400 when you get back to [ __ ]
Thailand. It doesn't make sense. You can
get a banging
holiday. I'm sure you could probably
even go to [ __ ] IA for [ __ ] £400
for three days as an example. Not that
I'd never go to Spain, but it's an
example. My sister's just come back from
there. It was 300 and something.
The only time, yeah, you could justify
spending money in this country is
[ __ ] is if you [ __ ]
um is if you won the money back when you
were there or something. You'd have to
try and win the money back. And then if
you lose, you've lost double. So when I go out every
Saturday, I've been out for a while. I
spend about 70 80 pound. I just try to
stick to the beer now, but that's 70 80
a week. I can make that back. No point spending
money [ __ ] in this country any more than
that. You know what I'm saying?
So go to Blackpool today if I wanted to. [ __ ]
that. Dumping it.
Unless I want a [ __ ] big football or something.
Yeah. And that's the only way. But other
than that, I wouldn't do it.
Nah, just put a wash on. Waiting for that to
finish. But yeah, bro, you don't need to
be sorry to hear. It's just what it is, isn't it? You
know, look man, we still got that
designer top. Look at that 70 t-shirt. That
is the yellow jello.
Look [ __ ] 70 [ __ ] pound t-shirt. E
Yeah, I take that [ __ ] thing out as
well. Yeah, I'm going to have a steak
today, I think. So tempted to have a
barbecue. The weather's nice, but can't
be spending another [ __ ] 78 [ __ ]
quiz every [ __ ] day. [ __ ] hell.
Um, should give it a whirl, but
nah. I want to make use of the [ __ ]
garden. You know what I'm saying? [ __ ]
beautiful. Meat is so expensive as well.
So [ __ ] expensive.
eaters. So, I want to buy a meal today.
It's going to cost me6 about56 for the for a
meal. Steak, mushrooms, got onion
rims, then pork chops tomorrow, I
think. I can't justify having a barbecue
today, man. Even though I'd love one, but no. Listen, man. Yeah. Oh, steak
there. Still cheap. I'm still saving
money. The steak's like six
quid. Six pound meal. Yeah. Anything less
than £8 a day eating is pretty good. I
think I just skip breakfast anyways most
of the time.
Sometimes I do like a plate of old builder.
Um I have a barbecue last week.
Yeah, and man definitely cares about
women that lie to me. I don't [ __ ] about them,
bro. Don't know if it's because I've had
so many experiences with them. I know
they're all the same,
but don't know,
man. I just don't give a [ __ ] about him.
And then when I said I stopped gambling,
I [ __ ] meant it as well. [ __ ]
meant it, bro. I need to seriously start saving money
now. And the madest thing is I've got
like money in my account where I can
actually deposit. I can actually play
online roulette if I wanted to, but like nah, [ __ ]
that. Absolutely [ __ ] that,
bro. cuz just it's just guilt and it you
know when you gamble money you could
have done other things with it the mood
swings it's just just not worth
doing it's just not worth [ __ ] doing
mate that's why I just packed it
in maybe if you're like in a pub or
something I don't know I don't know what
I think that's definitely me but
definitely me the only thing I do now is
the 20 pound on the [ __ ] machines in
the pub or something.
But as far as I go,
man, don't even get to rush for it
anymore. I think it's been about 12
days. I think 12 days no gamble.
Yay. 12 days.
Yeah. It's good, isn't it?
Need to make some ice for my contrast buff.
to provide a [ __ ]
birthday. Oh, no. I share. How long does
it take? About 3 hours, I think.
I think it takes about 3 hours.
Yeah, man. Was like for four [ __ ]
hours. Four hours,
man. That's a madness.
That's mad. 4 hours,
eh? It must have been live since [ __ ]
like 7 in the
morning. Talking to these [ __ ] spackers.
Yeah, I'll be gone soon.
Anyways, I thought maybe I should go for
a beer today, but then I need to get my
haircut and that. That boot
Maybe I should have put it maybe a bowl or
something. Think it's just as good as a bad
man. Maybe like a bowl or something.
We need more hard. Yeah, definitely. [Music] [Laughter] [ __ ] you.
Oh, got some pushed.
Look what's come through the post. My
provisional. I got it. Get in there. I
don't need to carry that [ __ ] passport around
everywhere. And I used to carry that
[ __ ] passport around with with me
everywhere in my
life. Yeah, that was a quick [ __ ] two
week. Oh, got my provisional now. Lovely.
N use this for ID now. Not [ __ ] carry
that [ __ ] passport around with me everywhere.
Yeah, I got the uh provisional which is
good. I can actually use this for ID, can't I?
I can use that for ID
now. That's good,
man. Don't have to be [ __ ] that big ass
passport. I need it as well.
This nice, man. Good
old Good old provisional
way. Come through the post.
No, could actually get my uh could
actually do my theory
now. But for
that it's cute though, is
it? I actually thought it was going to come next
week. Didn't think it was going to come today. [Music] [ __ ] headache.
I've been meaning to get this provisional for
years, but it just
never doing it. What's today? Yeah. Yes. [Laughter] [Music]
Yeah. Well, anyways, peace.