Some people in here really need to get a
life. Some people on here really [ __ ]
Oh my god. I can't believe it, man. It's
[ __ ] nice day outside and these
people are still on YouTube. Stat on
YouTube with fat
asses. I really I really feel bad for these
people, you know.
It's so It's so sad. Really, really is
sad. On YouTube all day, every day, even
in the summer. I think we all know who
the skimp ones really are. It's these
people. These people get the [ __ ]
arrow up, bro, and point it at them.
It's these [ __ ] people ain't got a
life. You see, like, I can understand it
in the winter, you know, it's cold. Some
people are trying to save money, but
it's a nice [ __ ] day. have just come
back and they're sat on YouTube. Sat on
[ __ ] YouTube. Ain't got to lie. The
madness year in year out, year in, year
out, year in, year out. I had a [ __ ]
foot injury and I still [ __ ] went out
them couple of [ __ ] weeks. You know what I'm
saying? I feel bad for these old age
pensioners on YouTube self projecting every
day. Oh, madness, isn't it? Madness.
madness. Oh, and all of this stuff
trying to bait people to get mad so you
know you people can run to the piece
again. It's not going to work. I don't
associate myself with
glasses. Yeah. So all of this like um
people trying to get people to react and
you know trying to get people mad. I
don't associate myself with grasses. So
having you know these people can carry
on wasting their time being obsessed
with me. I don't give a [ __ ] I done
associate myself with grasses. Um, at
the end of the day, you shouldn't even
have been really reacting to these
people to begin with, but a grass as
well. That's me down. That's when I draw
the line there. Don't [ __ ] with grasses.
Yeah, I'm good,
man. Just went to the supermarket, got
some food for today. Having another
barbecue next week. That's my bar that
was my barbecued um a couple of days
ago. So, yeah.
Yeah, bro. I don't waste my time with
these low lives anymore.
Yeah. Could have went out for a drink
today if I wanted. I want my 100% healed
before I stop walking the mileage
out. Yeah, it is, man. It is.
Yeah. It's nice, bro. It is nice.
Yeah, I'm wearing my [ __ ] DR t-shirt,
bro. My [ __ ] DR t-shirt.
Yeah. No, I'm still resting my foot.
It's not 100%
healed. Nah, I don't I don't want to
meet people on YouTube, bro. No thank
you. I'm not having anything to do with
anyone in this community. No thank you.
I don't meet [ __ ] men. I don't even
meet [ __ ] women on [ __ ] YouTube,
let alone meet a [ __ ] man. You
[ __ ] mad. [ __ ] that [ __ ] I ain't
meeting no one. And you're you're the
one that goes on JS, aren't you? [ __ ]
that. No way am I meeting the [ __ ]
man. No, I'm good,
bro. Nah, you can meet yourself. I'm
good. Nah, even meet a woman on this
community. So why the [ __ ] would I be?
You know, doesn't make sense.
Yeah, bro. How we doing? Notorious. Man,
I don't associate myself with these
people anymore cuz they're grasses. So,
I only have time for like the normal
people. I don't [ __ ] with grasses. They
can try and bait me all they want. They
can do what they want. They can be
obsessed with me all they want. I don't
give a [ __ ] I've only got time for like
the normal people. Yeah, I had a
barbecue the other day in Tourist. I'm
having another barbecue next week. I
haven't been out drinking, bro. Really,
I haven't been approaching or drinking.
I just can't f with it anymore, man. I'm
still kind of healing from the foot
injury. But yeah, I'll get it. So anyways,
yeah. Yeah. Oh, just a few people
here. A few people on here, bro. So,
what are you saying anyways to you still
on a um you still on a um approaching detox?
So, you feel a
um me and you are tight? Nah, I'm not
tight with anyone on this
community. I think this community is so backwards
that not if she's from this community.
No, I wouldn't. I can find a 10 out of 10 in
London. And there's no such thing as a
woman need a 10 out of 10 either. No, I
wouldn't. Not of this community. No, I
not. You approached when? Today? Um,
what did she say? She had a
boyfriend. I've been approached for a while,
bro. I've been busy, you know, with real life stuff. So,
yeah, I'm not learning that. I think the
last time I approached was like two
weeks ago. He was sober. Yeah. I don't I
don't bother with it anymore, bro.
Nope. I wouldn't meet Natalie G. Natalie G's a
snake. Nah, I wouldn't meet Ni G. A, cuz
she's from this community and B, she's a
snake. I wouldn't meet any woman from
this community. It doesn't matter how she
looks. No, I wouldn't meet a woman of this
community. But G's a snake as well cuz
I've caught her a few times. So, you
know, yeah, bro. We go out tomorrow. The
foot's kind of a lot better, but
nah. So, yeah.
But yeah, I wouldn't meet that, man. She's a
snake. Because she was trying to say
about, "Oh, PJ can dress what he want,
what um how he wants and he still won't
get women." I was like, "Bitch, I've had
more women than anyone on this [ __ ]
community, bro." Like, I was listening
battle. I think it was about two weeks
ago. I'm thinking, "Bitch, have you seen
how many women I have pulled on my main
YouTube channel, you [ __ ] I've been
with more women." Yeah. Than anybody
that you've ever been
with. So, stop talking [ __ ] Cuz I've
caught her. I've caught her um a few
times. So, that's what these people do
in this community, like snake
people. You've not had more than me.
Yes, I have had more than you. And I'm
not going to argue with you, even though
I'm not coming on here to argue. You
know, I'm 27 years of age. I'm not
[ __ ] 7 years old. So, trust me, I
have had more than you. I live in
London. So, I'm not going to argue with
you anyways, bro. Boring argument,
boring conversation that doesn't even
make any sense. But the point is Natalie
G's a snake. So,
yeah. So, like Yeah.
Um, they're all snakes.
So, so yeah, I wouldn't see, you know,
when you say she got big old melons,
that just goes to show um that you don't
have a life, Chicago, because Natalie G
wouldn't matter to you. Okay, let me let
me explain it to
you. Someone that's got a life wouldn't
care about a woman on YouTube because
you're out and about, you meet women.
That's an indication of somebody that
ain't got a life. When they're going
crazy over a woman on YouTube, you got
big melons and that just goes to show
that you ain't got no life because
there's loads of women out there and if
you went out frequently, you would see
better women and you wouldn't understand
and then you wouldn't care. So yeah,
that just goes to show that you don't get
women. Like you [ __ ] yourself up there
when you say that. Trust me, bro. Yeah.
It goes to show you don't get women
because somebody that gets women would
not care about a woman on YouTube no
matter what she looks like. No matter
what she looks like. You understand what I'm saying? So yeah.
Yeah. You're locked. Bye-bye,
[ __ ] And stop telling me to come to
porn church. Stop telling me, brother.
I'll give you my address right now. You
can come on my [ __ ] door and I'll
knock you out. I'll knock you out where
you stand and I'll put it all over
YouTube. Stop telling people to go to
porn church. You I'll give you my
address right now and I'll wait for you.
I will literally wait for you. So
yeah. Yeah. And I'll smash your teeth
down your [ __ ] throat, you
[ __ ] And if you're not if you're
not willing to do that, bro, then shut up. popping in.
Yeah. And you're done. Byebye. You
got a lot of big nose and look like some
of you people, mate. You look like
[ __ ] aliens. Have you seen the state
of you [ __ ] people on YouTube every
[ __ ] day? Every time you get [ __ ]
docked. Have you seen the [ __ ] state
of you? That's why you're on YouTube
every [ __ ] day. Cuz you ain't got no
life. You ain't got no looks. You ain't
got no [ __ ] money. Have you seen the
state of you people? Every time you get
[ __ ] doxed, mate. You wish your only
problem was having a [ __ ] big nose,
mate. You know what I'm saying? Have you
actually seen the state of you people?
Please, please stop it. You're
embarrassing yourself now. Yeah. But anyways,
yeah, I can't believe. Do you know what?
I kind of feel like Eminem, you know, in
a way. I kind of feel like Eminem cuz
I've got so many people obsessed with
me, so many people jealous of me. I kind
of feel like I made it. You
know what I'm saying, bro? Like I kind
of feel like I made it. Like I feel like
I'm kind of famous. I have so many
people like jealous of me and want to
ruin me. I kind of feel famous, you
know? In a way. I kind of feel like
Eminem when you had all them
haters. Like so many people jealous of
me, obsessed with me all day, every day.
It's creepy. But in a way, you kind of
know you made it in it cuz you have
something they don't have. I don't know
what it is, but it's for damn sure for
somebody to spend all day doing this.
They're jealous of
something. They're jealous of something.
[ __ ] damn right they are. They're
[ __ ] jealous of [ __ ]
something. I feel famous. Like, I kind of feel
famous. I have so many haters, bro. I
think it's cuz I'm better looking than
them and I got more money than them. But
I didn't say that. But I think that's
what it is. I think it's because I'm
better looking than them and I've got
more money than them. And that's why I
draw so many
haters. I trap them. I draw them in.
That's what I think it is. You know,
definitely better looking than them,
more money than them, more of a life
than them, better clothes than them,
etc. It's got to be something, bro. It's
something. Yeah. Got to be something,
bro. It's got to definitely be something.
But I don't waste my time on these
people. I don't waste my breath on these
people. Like cuz I know I'm better than
them. So I don't need to sit there and
argue with these people all day every
day. You know, you need to put two and
two together. No, I'm not sending it.
I'm not I'm not ask about that
anymore. [ __ ] that. My foot's a lot
better. It took a [ __ ] month. Jesus
Christ. I must have
really injured it.
getting better though. It's getting
better. No, I'm not sending it. Maybe next week.
Yeah. I just don't understand how these
people can come on here every day being
obsessed all day, every day. It's so
weird. And they don't even know how weird it
is. They're definitely jealous,
bro. Yeah. Yeah, I've not pulled any
women for a while, but I've not really
been out doing
it. Yeah, but it is weird. Yeah. Like
I've been seen with the best looking
women, more money than them. I'm better
looking than people and they still hate
on me. They still they still say, "Oh,
you're a virgin or you're skin." Cuz they're self
projecting. That's what it is. It's
called self projecting. I'm not going to
keep going over it. And you know what
I'm saying, bro? Like, but
yeah. Yeah. That's why they're jealous,
bro. Think of it, bro. I get money. Can
do what I want when I want. I've got a
nice gaff me [ __ ] in it. It's jealousy,
bro. Look at Look at what what Jamie Tom
Okay, let me give you an example. Have
you seen that Jamie
Thompson? You know, no. Have you seen
that Jamie Thompson? Fat,
ugly. No. Is he Is he not fat and ugly?
Fat and ugly. He spends all his life
stalking people on YouTube. He's done it
to London Taylor as well.
put two and two together, you
know, and it's jealousy as well because
they want you to go mad at them as well
so they can get the police involved.
That's another thing these little
jealous people like to do. They like to
like get you mad and saying stuff and no
just to get the police
involved. Like their whole life is
trying to get people nicked. If my life
if I was that much of a loser, bro, I
know and I know these people don't care
again because they've got no shame, but
if I was that much of a
loser, I I I think I'd go in the bath
and bleach myself, bro. I'm not even
joking. I could never be that much of a
loser. But obviously, everyone's brought
up differently. So, yeah. All over all
over, all skin. Um, yeah, just
overweight and skin. That's what they
are. That's why they're on YouTube every
day. Cuz think about it, my exit. Why
are they on YouTube all day every day in
the summer? Okay, the winter, let's just
say the Okay, okay, listen. Listen. Co,
everything was shut. You know, winter is
cold. People are saving money. Okay,
we'll give them two seasons. Why are
they on here all day, every day in the
summer? Hold on a minute. They're coming
on here calling people's skin. They come
on here telling people that they don't
have anything, but they're the ones that
are sat on YouTube all day every day.
Doesn't look right to me. Does it look
right to you? Cuz it doesn't look right me. You know?
Yeah. Sitting online every day harassing
people say a lot about their life,
doesn't it? You
know, I showed them money two weeks ago.
I think it was two weeks ago I showed
them money. Guess what? They couldn't show me
anything. They couldn't show me Shocker. [ __ ]
shocker. Oh no, my [ __ ] charge is
downstairs. Well, when this dies, it
dies, I guess. I can't Oh, I done my
washing today. Yeah, they call me skint
as well. um left it. Even though I got a
new washing machine, new fridge, money,
designer clothes, they still they call
me Skint as
well. They call me Skint,
mate. Yeah, man. I'm all right. Just
chilling. But yeah, I'm not associating
with these little grasses anymore. I'm
not I'm not into weird
drama. Nah, I'm not into weird drama, mate. Sorry.
Yeah, I I was going to go to Birmingham
next week to meet this woman and call
out Prime and Timmy, but there's no
point, bro. There's literally no
point. I was going to say, "Listen,
Prime, I'm in I'm in your actual city
now and try and move me out of it." But
there's no point all of that [ __ ]
because they're all grasses. Why would
you even argue on a grassing community?
It doesn't make sense. Too many grasses.
Too many grasses. They [ __ ] it for
themselves cuz I would have I would have
provided some good content. No, I don't
I don't [ __ ] with these little grasses
here. I just come on and do my own thing,
bro. As a cuck. Did
he? I do need to go out again, but I
don't know when. I just want my foot to be 100%
better. That lasted like a month. You
know that [ __ ] foot
injury. Nah, Rick Mace is a [ __ ] bro.
That fact that I completely destroyed
him. You know, the neighbor that I
confronted before back at the old house,
that neighbor was bigger than him. And I
told him, "Who the [ __ ] do you think
you're [ __ ] confronting?" Cuz he
confronted one of the um tenants before.
And I said, cuz he thought it was me. I
said, "That's me you was trying to
confront. I'm here now. What have you
got to say?" And I said, "If you record
me, I'm going to slap the camera out
your [ __ ] face. I'm going to slap it
out in your [ __ ] hand." And he was
bigger than that guy as well. He was
bigger than that guy. No, bro. That Rick
Maze, he got boyed
off. He got boyed off. He's cool, but
he's a proper [ __ ] Like, bro, he actually
is. Yeah. No, it's not what he's done.
He's just a wannabe gangster. He He is
cool, but he is an embarrassment at the
same time. You know how he he's he's
took more L's on here than me. Even
though I've took L's, I've also took
W's. He's took L after L after L after L
after L that Rick
has. You know what I
mean? L after L after [ __ ] L, mate.
My [ __ ] was bad. Yeah,
man. Money man said that he's got 300 quid left. 300
quid. He said he's got 300 quid [Laughter]
left. Oh my god, bro.
Imagine. Yeah, that foot injury was
[ __ ] stinking, mate. It used to it
was waking me up at like 4 in the
morning. Like 4 in the [ __ ] I wonder
how it must have been from running back
home that time I come out the court. I'm
trying to think how I got it. It must
have been running back home from the court, isn't
it? And if you walked on the [ __ ]
Yeah. It would wake you up at like 4 in
the [ __ ] morning throbbing, mate. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, you can't speed up the recovery
process here. But that was the annoying
thing. But he lives off to 300 a month,
mate. I [ __ ] struggle on [ __ ]
three grand a
month. I struggle on [ __ ] three grand
a month, lad. Nah, not struggle. you know. Yeah.
Yeah. I get 3k a month. It's
okay. But you
know, you can't live off [ __ ] £300 a
month. You can live off a you can live
off a grand a
month. Maybe 800. Not 300
though. Three and a half years. What do you
mean? What do you mean I had a great
result? What are you talking about,
bro? What are you talking about?
Nope. Probably not, bro. That's why
they're so skinny. I'm having a barbecue
next week. Next Thursday, I'm having another one.
I spent [ __ ] live off 300 pound. I
spent [ __ ] When did I have that
barbecue? I think I had it on um Wednesday. That
Wednesday? What do you mean? I've got nothing to
answer. What do you
mean in terms of working or
what? Um anyways, yeah, that Wednesday I
went to get like the meat and the and
the barbecue. I I spent 150 quid.
Barbecue was 50. Got some meat. 150
pound, bro. I spent 150
quid. So, no, I couldn't live off 300
pound a month. [ __ ]
that. I'm going to go back to going out
drinking once a week soon. I just stick
to the beer. So, I spend like 70
80. So, that's what I just do. Need to
get my hair done as well. It's all money,
eh? Yeah, that's my barbecue. Yeah. on
Wednesday. Yep. That's my barbecue. 150 quid. Yeah,
man. Yeah. I had to go [ __ ]
caught. Yeah. Oh, you mean Oh, you're
talking about the court thing. Yeah.
Three and a half years. Yeah. And by
that time, it will get [ __ ] dropped.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, is that what
you're talking about? The the the court
thing? Yeah. It's not the point, though.
No, it's not the [ __ ] point though,
is it, bro? It's not the point if you
got away with it, if you didn't get away
with it. It's not the point. It's why
associate yourself with
grasses, you know? And the only bell
condition that I've got is a good bell
condition that's going to help me. I can
leave the country whenever I want. I can
do what I want when I want. The only
bell condition that I've got is one
thing that will help me. So, that's
that's good, bro. Like, that's that's a
good bell condition. I'm
happy. But these people will be getting
nicked soon anyways. My left hip. Trust
me, they will. Yeah, they people will be
getting nicked soon. Trust me. Like I've
already reported it. Like I'm following
up with it. The woman called me the
other day. Trust me, lad. They are going
to get [ __ ] Like it's only a matter
of time. They are going to get [ __ ]
and they won't be laughing then, you
know? So all of this baiting to try to
get people nicked again, it's not going
to work. It's not going to work cuz I'm
saving everything on top of already what
I have. So, it's all good. It's all
good, bro. I've got
everything. You know, the police are
dealing with it. So, it's all good
anyways, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. Exactly, bro. They said, "Oh, they
said that basically um I mean, they just
tell people to plead guilty cuz it's
easier for them." I said, "No, I'm not
pleading guilty. No [ __ ] way. These
people have been harassing me. I've got
everything that they've done and I'll
take her to trial with me. I'm not
[ __ ] pleading no guilty. [ __ ]
that. Yeah, exactly. And these pe and
and it's not one person left it. These
people have been grassing on it for
[ __ ] years. It's not even just one
person. All they've done is grass grass
grass grass grass. It's not even you
grassing back. You're just protecting
yourself now. All these people know,
bro. It's been happening for years.
It's been happening for years, man. It's
not one, two, it's loads of people under
that grass, you know? Like, I got a
criminal record um thing come back the
other day and it's clear. I'm I'm
surprised it's clear to be honest. I've
been nicked so many [ __ ] times. Like,
you don't understand. Like 10 times over
this website. So, yeah, bro. It's I'm
I'm just doing it to protect myself
now. So, these people will get in
trouble in the end, bro. Trust me, they
will. Trust me. Like, it took them 6
months to [ __ ] come for me. So, you
know, trust me, bro. Trust
me. So, yeah. I just said basically
that's why I'm not pleading guilty. So,
yeah. Yeah, I have. Yeah, I am. I am.
Yeah. Do you know Do you know the first
time? Yeah. Do you know the No. No. So,
it was the second time. You know the
second time I went to the police
station? Yeah. Um, you know the second
time that I went to the [ __ ] police
station? Yeah. This woman was like, "Oh,
uh, yeah, report it to YouTube." I said,
"I'm not reporting it to YouTube. I'm
[ __ ] reporting it to [ __ ] you. How
many times have you been on my [ __ ]
door over [ __ ] [ __ ] social media?
Do not tell me to report it to no
[ __ ] YouTube." Like, and it went on
for about like 5 minutes. Then he then
she finally listened and then a few days
after that, yeah, the [ __ ] police
officer [ __ ] called me and she's
going to be calling me again as well,
bro. Like, um, trust me, it's going to
happen. I follow up every single [ __ ]
week because at the end of the day,
practice what you [ __ ] preach. Report
it to [ __ ] YouTube. Report it to
[ __ ] Facebook. Why are you on my door
then? So you're surely to God you're contradicting
yourself, you know, like I've had it up
to here with it with these police. Like
I' I've been dealing with it for years
years and years and years and years and
years, you know, and it's not worth it,
bro. You know, it's not [ __ ] worth
it. So like it's it's literally just not
worth it. You know what I mean, bro?
So yeah, bro.
So yeah, and that's and that's the thing
cuz you know the thing is left tick.
Yeah. You know when they come on the um
you know when they come on the door that
day, it was a Friday, I think it was. It
was actually a Friday. I can't remember
what I was doing. It was a Friday. Yeah. Um
Um Yeah. They tried taking my phone and
I hid it in the
garden. And then when I got released
like 3 days later, I was like I ran
back. I was running back to the house
share thinking the phone better still be
there. The phone better still be there.
The phone better still be there. And it
was. And I think that's how I [ __ ] my
foot up. That's how I [ __ ] my foot up
for a month as well because obviously I
was running back to the house making
sure that the [ __ ] phone was still
there because all my shit's on it. And I
wouldn't have got that phone back as
well for I probably would have never got
a phone back if they had took it because
obviously there was no way I was going
guilty. No way. And if they wanted to
like keep the like case open then I
wouldn't have got the phone back for a [ __ ] long
time. So because if they took the phone
I would have physically took it off them
no matter what I had to use. So, and
that's the thing is like say I come on
here now and I start going back and
forth and back and forth and they call
the police. Anyhow, police come on this
door again, it's got to be another
story, bro. You know, first time they
done it was at my mom's. My mom was
like, "Oh, leave it. Leave it. Leave it.
Leave it. Leave it." Like, you don't
know the [ __ ] I was saying, bro. When
they come that Friday, I was saying,
"What the [ __ ] are you [ __ ] eating [ __ ]
doing on my [ __ ] door?" Yeah. I was
going [ __ ] mad at them, bro. I was
saying madnesses to them.
You know what I'm saying,
bro? So that's it. And then and I was
saying as well like I beg one of you
little [ __ ] eating [ __ ] in a silly
little uniform to try and tell me to
ride my [ __ ] neck in today. You
[ __ ] pigs. Like I was saying madness,
bro. And then after all of that, yeah,
it's not even worth it, you know? But
yeah, if they ever come on my door
again, I'm just not answering it. So
they're going to have to put a warrant
out for my [ __ ] But they're never
going to come on the door anyways cuz I
don't do anything. But let's just say in
the future in 2 years, 3 years, 4 years,
anyhow they come on this door again over
social media, I'm not opening it. So,
they're going to have to break the
[ __ ] they're going to have to break
the door down. No rest me, you know, cuz
you know, it's also a problem with them
as well because what it is with these
police is they like to get themselves
involved when it suits themselves and
that doesn't work like that. Like you
want to you wanted to get yourself
involved again and again and again and
again and again. Now we'll see it right
through now. And that's why I've had to
[ __ ] make [ __ ] reports, you know?
So they like
to they like to get themsel involved
when it suits themselves.
So yeah, I need to go back there again.
I need to I follow up every week. I've
got two people following up. So it's all
good anyways, bro.
Yeah. Think of how many times like
traumador has called the police. Like so
many of these people and they all they
do is call the [ __ ] police and they
think it's [ __ ]
normal. They think it's [ __ ] normal,
bro. Yeah, they weren't getting that phone, mate.
They weren't getting that [ __ ]
phone. So, yeah, it was
madness. Then they tripped me in a
[ __ ] sweat box and took me to [ __ ] call. So
yeah, I was in there for pretty much 24
hours, you know. I can't stand grasses.
Literally can't stand
him. So I don't associate with him, you
know. It's low life [ __ ] It's just low
life [ __ ] bro.
And I've got too much to lose as well.
I've got [ __ ] to lose. I've got a house
to lose. I've got money to lose. It's
not it's not there's no point we're
throwing stuff away for some YouTube
virgins that ain't got a life. You know,
think about it, bro. It doesn't matter
how tempting it is. You risk everything
for a bunch of losers on YouTube that
ain't got a life. Nah.
Nah. A bunch of [ __ ]
losers. Nah, bro. double man. Think about it
realistically. You know what I'm saying?
But I was told, "Yeah, I don't mind
toxicity, bro. I don't mind
toxicity, but um I don't like
grassing. That's when I sign off,
bro." Ah, boyfriend. Yeah, but it's not
funny when people start
grassing because now you see the thing
is because of these people doing this
now it will make people not reply to
them and go mad and do all the things.
So they're very low IQ because they want
to come on YouTube.
Yeah, exactly, bro. And I'm living my
life, bro. Look, I'll show you what I got, man.
Look, look at this top, bro. 700 top.
need to cut the hair on that. But yeah,
look at that 700 pound top,
bro. They wish they could have a 700
pound top. But yeah, bro, that's exactly
how you get back at them. Yeah, man. Exactly.
Having a nice steak
today. Not a t-bone steak, but a steak.
I'm not that [ __ ] rich.
[ __ ] I'm not that [ __ ] rich,
mate. I fancied a few drinks there, but
like I said, my foot's not 100%, so I
don't want to like irritate it, you know?
Yeah. That's the washing machine. Can you
hear? I have to have a contrast bath every day.
Greasy for my little football
greasy. They've all got
boyfriends. They've all got boyfriends. Ah,
boyfriend. Yeah, bro.
The contrast bath every
day. The contrast bath every
day. My life is [ __ ] good, bro. Get
3k a month. Don't do anything. Got a
yard. Got a big ass kitchen. I can do
what I want when I want. I'm living the
life compared to these
people. [ __ ] Red Star and all of them [ __ ] weirdos.
Yeah, my life is [ __ ] sick, bro. I
could even go to Blackpool today if I wanted
to. I could even go to Blackpool today
if I wanted
to spontaneously. I can do what I want
when I [ __ ]
want. It's good, is it, bro? It's
good. I don't gamble anymore.
So, or you could be on like Benny on £300 a
month. Benny's on £300 a month. Imagine that.
Yeah, I'm not drunk for a while. When I
drink now, I just [ __ ] stick to beer.
I just stick to beer now cuz I can't
deal with anxiety the next day from the
spirits. Like the spirits give me mad
anxiety and paranoia and [ __ ] That's
why I just stick to the beer. It's cheaper as
well. It's cheaper too.
Yeah. I get mad [ __ ] bad hangovers
when I when I go into
spirits. Bad. Bad. When I stick to the
beer, I'm all right. But not the
spirits, bro. I was drinking white rum. Oh,
mate. [ __ ] bad. It was Yeah,
bro. Yeah, but I wouldn't go to Blackpool cuz
um I don't want to spend £300 in this
country. You know what I'm saying? It's
all right going out every Saturday in
London spending50 60 pound on [ __ ]
beer, okay? But not £300. Unless I go to
Cole Island and try and win the money
for the trip, but nah. Then if you lose,
you've lost double, you see?
So, I've not played live roulette in
ages. Nah, [ __ ] that. [ __ ] that,
bro. Nah, I just stay in London. go out
every Saturday, spend 50, 60
quid. Yeah, I wanted to see how easy it
would be to pull there and there's
probably a casino I can get into. Well,
there's a woman that lives like in
Preston, so I said to her like, "If you
want to meet in Blackpool, you can go to Blackpool it."
Um, but yeah, I don't
really I don't really fancy that,
bro. I don't know.
don't want to wait like the thing is you
spend three£3400 there you could spend
that on a holiday
abroad. So why the [ __ ] would you like
waste three400 pound in this country? It
don't make sense. 60 70 80 pound you can
kind of justify but not [ __ ] 300
quid you know. Yeah they'll take one
look at me and be like oh you're from
London. Just like when I went to
Newcastle all them times. Hey
Zippy. Just when I went to Newcast like
when I used to go to
Newcastle be the same in
Blackpool. Oh, you're from
London. Just go overnight. Yeah, but
it's still going to cost money, bro.
It's still going to cost like 200
quid. It's still going to cost a little
bit, bro. And there's not really a point
going overnight cuz it's so far. It's
not like Brighton or [ __ ] South. It's
quite far. I mean, yeah, you could go
overnight. Yeah. Like I used to do in
Newcastle, but you're still going to be
spending what 250300.
So, I just can't really justify it, you
know, trust me. And I've got the money.
I have the money, but I just can't justify
it. And the reason I was thinking of
going there is cuz I've never been there
before. So, I've been everywhere else but
there. Yeah, that's it, bro. That's the thing.
Glasgow and Blackpool. They're the only
places I've never been like major
cities. Been to all the others.
Yeah. [ __ ] four as well,
bro. I don't really bother with women
anymore, but I'm starting to woman at
from like 10 years ago. She lives in
like Preston. She seems all right, you
know? She actually seems all right for a
[ __ ] westernized [ __ ] woman cuz I
just basically just give up with them
now. They're all the same. But like she
seems all right in it. So she doesn't
ignore or whatever. I like who can I
think of that's not a complete
[ __ ] I just hit her up and that. So
yeah, she's all right now.
Yeah. But I don't really asked about
women anymore. My left tier, I don't
really give a [ __ ] about
them. I've got other things to think
about. Bad man cares about women more
than me and he's more mature than me.
Like know what I'm saying?
He'd rather like move to another country
and work just to get a woman than stay
in a country, get free money, and
basically kind of struggle until you
meet someone. That's crazy, bro. I would
never pick [ __ ] over money. That's [ __ ] mad, man. You
know, man, there won't be loads of
opportunities, bro. They're still going
to say they've got boyfriends and [ __ ]
Doesn't matter if it's [ __ ] it's
summer, bro. I'm just going to go out
every week cuz I want to go
out. Not tomorrow though. Still not
tomorrow. I still think I need another
week's recovery. Maybe next week. But
nah, it's not even about that, bro. I
know what I'm going to get when I go
out. Same old [ __ ] I've got a
boyfriend. It doesn't matter that it's
summer, bro. You're always going to get
that. Nah, you're always going to get
that boyfriend [ __ ] bro. Doesn't matter that it's
summer. What's that mean? Well, they're
suddenly going to stop [ __ ] saying
they got boyfriends. Come on, man. And
they all they're always going to say they've got
boyfriends. Well, you just go out and
drink anyways. You know, it's fun,
huh? But no
way would I ever choose to work and get
less money just to be with a woman. That is crazy,
man. That is crazy. [ __ ] that. I'd
rather have the
money. It just takes one to say yes.
Okay, let's go by your logic then. I've
been to most cities in England and I've
never had one that said yes, that stays
with me. So, I mean, if it was going to
happen, it would have happened by now.
That's that's it. I mean, I go out every
week because it's something to look
forward to. I'm leaving the country in 2
months. So, because if something was
going to happen, it would have happened
by now. That's that that's the way it
is, bro. We We don't go out because
that's all we're trying. We go out
because it's something to look forward
to every Saturday or every
um Thursday. Yeah, I know what you're
trying to do, bro. But unfortunately,
there's no positives because if
something was going to happen, it would
have happened by now. You would be with
someone, you know, but you're not. So,
and it doesn't matter anyways. But if
you were going to meet someone, you
would have met someone by now. Bear in
mind, you've tried more than anyone in
the world. You would be with someone,
you know. But you would be with somebody
right now if if if if it only took one.
Yes. So there's no positives in this
situation. There is a positive leaving
the country and that's what I'm doing.
So I'm leaving in 2 months. I'm going to
go out every week and I want to go out
and that's it. I don't care, bro.
It's there's no positives in this
country. There's no positives, bro. You
you go out every Saturday or every maybe
change the days up like Thursday. You'll
go out just drink, send it, and that's
it. All you got to do is count down the
days. 8 weeks until I go. Seven weeks
until I go. 6 weeks until I go. You'll
be looking forward to it. Like when
people count down their days in prison,
weeks in prison, you'll be counting down
your days until you leave the country. So
yeah, that's what I'm doing, bro. So yeah,
man. I want to do America again, but
it's [ __ ] expensive. Like it was
either like Florida or
Thailand, but America's westernized, so it's
[ __ ] But I was thinking in it, but I'd have
to I could do it. I could afford it. I
could afford it. But yeah, it be
u I'd be kind I can afford it but it
would be a lot of money took off.
But I don't know. I had to book a
holiday and it was between them two.
So I just chose Thailand.
But America is expensive, bro. It is.
It's like4 or £5,000 for one person for
a week. I don't know how people afford
it. Obviously, I've saved that, but I
don't know how people can [ __ ] afford
that. Don't know how they afford it,
man. I was looking up to go like on my
birthday. Do you know how much it come
up with a flight chair and a hotel? It
was a £4,000. It was £4,000. So, you're
talking £6,000 a week for one person.
[ __ ] hell, bro. That's
mad. That's crazy, man. I think it's the
most expensive place to go,
though. America is
expensive. But, um, I'm still saving.
Even though I do barbecues and stuff, I
am still saving, but it's just harder to
save in the
summer. I just booked the flights. It
was £700. And I just booked the flights
cuz in Thailand what most people do is
they book you book the flights and then
you just pay for the accommodation when
you're there because it's like 15 to 20
pound 15 to 20 a night cuz a woman will
become obsessed with you. So you need to
move you need to change like
accommodation which is why man does you
just book the flights but obviously with
America you have to book all of it
because the hotels are like £300 a [ __ ]
a night. So
yeah. Yeah. So you just put the flights,
but they're going up and up and up and
up. Not in America it's not. Yeah, it
is. But not in America. Not in America
it's not. Trust me. Cuz even if you get
a flight Yeah. that's £350 400. The
hotels are 250 to300 a night. No matter
where you look. Trust me, right? Nah,
it's not not in America. It's
not. Not in America. But Thailand. Yeah.
Other country. But I know America.
Definitely not. Definitely definitely
definitely not. But in Thailand, yeah,
you're talking £300 a night in America,
man. Or hotel. 250 300 easy for a decent one.