Right. So, this is um to Arsenal. Mark,
let some people
join. This guy's trying to wind me up again.
Right. Yeah. So, I'm going to do a video
to this [ __ ] keyboard warrior
again. And it's basically, yeah, you
either put up or shut up because I know
that you watch me. You keep watching me
because you're [ __ ] obsessed. Like,
the same goes to you, bro. You either
put up or shut up. Yeah. Stop writing
your stupid little comments. If you've
got something to say to my face, you can
go live on Albert [ __ ] square.
Simple. If you got something to say to
my face, right? Just just come. Like, I
don't know what you're waiting for. Just
just come. Stop making your stupid
little YouTube videos. This isn't a
[ __ ] Timmy and [ __ ] Monty
situation. You know what I'm trying to
say? Like, I'm not doing this back and
forth. You're an old man, mate. You've
got nothing better to do with your life.
That's why you come on YouTube seeking
attention. You know what I'm saying,
bro? Like, it's not my fault Jane wanted
Peter Belly. It's not my fault that you
have to [ __ ] s over my [ __ ] sloppy
seconds, you sad old man. Like, put up
or shut up, man. You've been doing this
for 3 years. Yeah. Let's talk about 3
years. 3 years ago, I went to your air
and you didn't come out two times.
You're embarrassing yourself now. Stop
it. Yeah. Why don't you tell everybody the real
you? Yeah. You suffer with
anxiety. You call the police on
people. So just stop this want to be
hard, man. You're not about nothing.
Never have been and you never will be.
You're a You're a granddad, mate. You're
a [ __ ] granddad. If you got something
to say, come tonight. Come tonight and
go live. You know, just go up by Albert
Square and go live. There there's
nothing more. Like you've never been on
my door. You will never say anything to
my face. Yeah. You're not about that
life. You're a keyboard warrior. You're
an old man on YouTube. Get off of
YouTube. Yeah. If you're really bad,
right, you will come tonight. It's a
Friday. Yeah. See, I won't do this back
and forth [ __ ] like Monty and Timmy.
Back and forth, back and forth, back and
forth, back and forth, back and forth
[ __ ] It's [ __ ] boring, bro. Like, if
you're really bad, you will come
tonight. Yeah, that's it. That's it. And
I know you watch me because you've been
commenting about me, bro. I'm almost 30,
brother. I'm 27. I'm not 30 for 3 years.
And yes, I have had more women than you.
Who was the one sniffing around Morgan?
My sloppy seconds. Who was the one
sniffing around Izzy? My sloppy seconds.
Bro, it's not my fault that I'm not 55
and I've got hair and I'm better looking
than you. And your [ __ ] misses kept
[ __ ] begging to suck my dick. It's
not my problem, you know? Like, you
don't need to be jealous, bro. It's not my problem.
Like, just stop it, man. You're really,
really not about that life. Like, I'll
wait for you if I have to. I'll wait,
you know, and that's it. And you can
come and say whatever you want to my
face. Let's see this big old Arsenal
mark. Let's see what the big excuse is
going to be. Cuz there's always a
[ __ ] excuse with him, you know? Simple. Yeah.
You don't scare anybody. Nobody is
scared of you. No one ever has been and
no one ever will be.
Yeah. Went to your area twice 3 years
ago. You didn't [ __ ] come out. People
don't seem to like to want to [ __ ]
talk about that, do they? No. Cuz
they've got selective memory. Just put
up or shut up, man. It's boring
now. Like, why are you doing all of this
[ __ ] Like, are you a grass or something?
Like are you are are you a grass or
something? Arsenal Mark. Like tell us,
bro. Are you a grass or why are you
doing this [ __ ] I'm giving you an offer
right now. Yeah, you're 20 minutes away.
Come on the road and I will come and see
what you've got to say to my face.
That's as clear as it can
be. Yeah. Not this. Oh, we're meeting at
Stratford station or No, no, no, no, no.
I have gone to your area twice. Put up
or shut up. Yeah. You waste all of this
time making [ __ ] YouTube [ __ ]
videos time and time and time again. You
know what I'm
saying? Also, when you go to this guy's
door, he calls the police. Um, I know
this. Like, just stop it, Assel Mark.
Stop it. Yeah, I've not had all these
women, bro. You've tried to simp over my
You've tried to literally simp over my
sloppy seconds. You sad old man. Bro,
please just come
today. End of cuz if you don't right,
I'm not entertaining you.
Simple. I'm not entertaining you.
Yeah. If you're really bad, you'd go 5
minute walking distance away from that house. That's
it. Big hard man but makes you YouTube
videos. Yeah. You know, this community
is is a parody about uh for people that
are actually about that life because
people that are about that life don't
come on YouTube making videos. It's a known
fact. People that are about that life.
Yeah. At the end of the day, don't come
on YouTube doing this. You I'm not going
back and forth with you like Timmy and
Monty. You either come on that road
today and you go live or shut up.
Simple. I've already gone to your area two times.
It's not my fault that Jane wanted me
and not you. It's not my fault you have
to simp over my sloppy seconds. It's not my fault,
man. He's a [ __ ] idiot, bro. He was
even starting on [ __ ] Timmy the other
day. Same as Terry. Like, even bring
Terry if you want. Listen, listen. Hey,
Mark. Another thing is, yeah, even bring
Terry. Both of you, please. Both of you
come. I'm literally asking for you to
come. And I'm asking for Terry to come
as well. He's another one that likes to
run his mouth behind the keyboard. But
you're not going to do it, are you? You
know, so just shut up, bro. Stop
mentioning my name. If you've got
nothing to say to my face, then just [ __ ] off.
Simple. Idiot, man. Guy is a [ __ ] clown.
I don't even want to get into this [ __ ]
because of the grasses on this
community. But like, you know, you come
on this [ __ ] street and I'll come out
and ask you what your [ __ ] problem is. End
off. He's a [ __ ] absolute clown,
isn't it? An absolute clown. Why does he
still do this after 3 years? Some people
really ain't got no shame, man. You know
what I'm saying?
Like, [ __ ] me being almost 30. You're
almost 60 years of age. You're a
grandpa, bro. Imagine your dad or your
granddad coming on YouTube like Arsenal
Mark does. It's embarrassing, mate. [ __ ]
embarrassing. And there's no point even
going on [ __ ] door cuz you're just
going to call the police. So, there's no
[ __ ] point. I gave him a fair offer
today. I said, "If you come 5 minute
walk distance, I will meet you. It's not
a problem. And if you're not going to do
that, then we all know why you won't do that.
You know, I'm not going back and forth.
Oh, meet me here. Don't meet me there.
And just go around in circles. [ __ ] all
that. I'll lose [ __ ] brain
cells. Guy's a [ __ ] idiot,
man. Listen. Yeah. You want to join?
Okay. Okay. Yeah. You want to join? One sec. second.
Yeah. Told you he watches me. He's a
[ __ ] low life.
She's a [ __ ] low life, mate. Of
course he [ __ ] watches me. Listen,
let's arrange this properly. Yeah, come
tonight. Yeah. What excuse do you have?
Come tonight, right? And go outside that
door. I'll go 5 minutes away from that
door and I'll give you every chance to
say it to my face. Yeah. Listen, I've
already gone to your area two times and
you didn't come out. Yeah. The last time
when I was in Patty Power. So, stop this
whole YouTube [ __ ] You're not about
nothing. Because after today, right,
when everybody will even more so know
what you're about, everyone should just
stop entertaining this keyboard warrior
now, bro. You know what I'm saying?
Everyone should stop entertaining this
keyboard warrior. You're trying to say
that you've come on my door, brother.
You've never come on my door. Why don't
you try coming on my door today, big
man? Yeah. It's a Friday. Yeah. What's
your excuse? I ain't got no excuse,
bro. But you've come on my door, bro.
You would never come on my door. The
last person that came on your door, you
called the police. Yeah. You had a panic
attack and you called the police.
Everybody knows that. So, stop this
whole YouTube [ __ ] You're not about
nothing. Yeah. You've got a fair offer.
I'm live. I gave you the link. Put up or
shut up. Simple. No one cares about
these. And then you're going to do a
little video. Oh, I'm going to come to the train
station, bro. Shut up. Yeah.
Come tonight and I will come outside and
ask you what have you got to say face to
face. That's what I'm gonna do, bro. Yeah. End
of. Brother, you're the one who's had to
simp over Morgan. You're the one that's
had to simp over Izzy. Like, please stop
it. It's embarrassing now. You need to
stop this hard man talk, Mark. It's getting really
boring. Yeah. There you go. You're
in, Mark. You got to stop this [ __ ]
bro. It's getting really boring now,
man. You don't scare anyone. No one's
afraid of you. So, I don't know why you
keep coming on YouTube running up your
[ __ ] mouth every [ __ ] day, bro. We
get it. You're bored. We get it. Jane's
probably cheating on you. Jane wanted me
a few times. That's not our problem,
bro. Go get a
life. You know, I don't know what you
keep doing on this [ __ ] YouTube.
Like, you're bad. Yeah. Come today. I'll
stay live. I'll stay live from now if I have
to. Look, you've had to mute your mic.
Come on. You've got a lot to say behind
the text. Come on. What is it, man? [ __ ]
idiot. Yeah, you're the one that has to
simp over women that I've been with
because, bro, we we Nobody wants a bald
grandpa. Come on, man. Come on, Mark.
Nobody wants a bald grandpa. It's It's
getting silly now, you know? really silly.
Yeah. Come on then. What are you waiting
for? You've got you wanted to join. Your
mic is muted. Come
on. A guy like you could never scare me.
I'm literally telling you to come. I
don't know what you're waiting for, bro.
You're a [ __ ] coward. Every time you do
this, why don't you tell people when
someone goes on your door how you call
the police? H Why don't you tell people
how when people go on your door, you
call the police? You s bastard.
Yeah. [ __ ] idiot. [ __ ] gim. Look,
he's a gim, mate. Look, he can't even
say nothing. He's a [ __ ] house. This is
what I'm saying. He's a [ __ ] house.
That's what he is. He's a [ __ ]
absolute [ __ ] house, mate. Yeah. Look,
you can't even say anything over the
hangout. He's a
[ __ ] Oh my god. Hello.
Yeah. Oh, thank God. Are you going to
let me speak or what? I've been talking
for 2 minutes. I didn't even realize I
muted myself, mate. So, what's going on?
Yeah. Okay. Right. You going to let me
speak? Are you going to speak?
Are you going to speak over me or you
going to let me talk? Listen. Yeah.
Okay. Talk. Go on. Okay. Talk. Tonight.
I'm going out for the night. Oh, you're
going out. Okay. Tomorrow.
Yeah. What time? took any time you want
tomorrow. Do a video. No, no, no, no.
I'm not doing this no more with you. You
are a swerver. Your area two times. You
didn't come out. Shut up.
Games, mate. Listen. When you're ready,
when you're ready to let me, folks, when
you're ready, when you're ready to let
me talk, you let me talk. When you're
ready, let me talk this no more. Okay.
Okay. Okay. I'll let you talk. But let
me When you're ready, let me talk. Let
me talk. Come out when I went to your
area two times.
I didn't even know you were [ __ ]
here, mate. You're a joke. You're a
joke. Well, even though I was live for 3
hours. Okay. Yeah, but why are you
talking about the park? Why? You wanted
a time. Yeah. PJ, one thing. One thing.
PJ PJ PJ PJ PJ PJ PJ. Shut the [ __ ] up.
Let me talk. If you can be silent for 30
seconds and let me
talk. Cuz all you do is excusing of your
past and all the [ __ ] you've done. I'm
talking now. Yeah. Okay. Now come. So
when when you're ready when you're ready
when you're ready to let me talk. Let me
talk. When you're ready to let me talk.
Let me talk.
When are you ready to let me talk with
no interruptions? Talk. Talk. Go on. Are
you going to show up now then? Yeah.
Yeah. Go on. Perfect. tomorrow. Your
problem is you are so
insecure. You're such a [ __ ] You're
not going to laugh, right? So you
interrupted me. Yeah, you're going to
interrupt me. You said you're going to
let me talk. If you don't let me If you
interrupt me one more time, I'm going to cut this
off. This is your chance to meet me and
alone. If you interrupt me one more
time, I'm cutting it.
Go talk then. What are you waiting for?
I'm waiting for you to shut the [ __ ] up,
you [ __ ] Listen, you're the [ __ ] Come
and meet me today and I'll smash your
head in you, you silly [ __ ] Stop making
[ __ ] excuses, mate. Listen, it's not
my PJ. My
my are you going to let me talk? Can you
give me one minute without any
interruptions? Stop talking on YouTube.
You're not Can you give me Stop yapping
on YouTube. I'm so boring. This is
boring. You are boring. You are boring,
mate. I've gone to your times are boring
and you've never come. You will never
come on my door. You're already [ __ ]
it. You're already [ __ ] in it again.
You've never come on my door. You're a
grandad. Do you know how sad, mate? Do
you know how sad you are? Shut up.
You're not about that life. Shut your mouth. Last
time the police granddad, can I ask you
a question? Yes or no? Can I ask you a
question? Shut the [ __ ] up. You want to
ask me a question? Come and meet me
today. Say it to my face. Anything you I
want to I want to I want to arrange a
meet tomorrow. I want to arrange a meet
tomorrow. But you want to let me speak,
mate. Yeah. Tomorrow 5:00 p.m. Yeah. No,
he's not on your terms. Okay. Bye-bye.
Now, this guy does this. He's a [ __ ] bro.