So Mark the [ __ ] has bottled it again. This
is what is it the 10th time now.
Arsenal marks a [ __ ] cloud, man. He's
doing the same thing again that he
always does. A range is a time and a
place with someone and then he and then
he makes up another location that nobody
agreed to. They're all the same on here,
man. All night spaz that can't afford an
iPad that has to holiday to Turkey
because he's that skint. This [ __ ]
cokehead Mark. It's just all attention,
isn't it? That's what all of these
people are looking for is attention is
it? It's got to be attention. What these
cowards are looking for on [ __ ]
YouTube, bro? I'm done with them now.
Anyways, [ __ ] my end. Not once did
anybody agree to my end. He's a coward.
Calling somebody out, bro. Yeah, you're
calling somebody out when you know where
they live. Big hard man on YouTube. [ __ ]
off, man. I'm done with this place
again. You know, it's the same [ __ ]
spastics every [ __ ] day. I swear to
God. Bottling it out again. We agreed.
1:00 p.m. Albert Square. Now we saying
by end. I'm done with this place. I am
done. Simple. I'm gone. I'm gone today.
After today, I'm gone, bro. I'm gone again. Done.