This is 100% the last Five.
Oh, sorry about
that. I was doing something,
mate. It's not even charging.
Yeah, sorry about that,
man. Don't even get those [ __ ]
enthusiasm from these [ __ ]
Oh, put the old on that ice pack.
Yeah, we'll be ready for next
week. Don't even know what I'll be doing next week,
but yeah. Anyways, I'm done anyways in
my last live stream for a while.
100%. I just wanted a few people to be
honest, so I had some things to tell
them. That's why I was live a few times.
Oh. I was waiting for two people to come
on today. They ain't been on. That's why
I keep going
alive. Good old lick. Oh
[ __ ] probably some people here,
bro. Come on, man. [Music] No, no. Resty,
resty. [ __ ] hell,
bro. Resting my foot on this ice pack.
Should be good as new by next week. Hopefully.
Yeah. Should be
definitely Yeah. What we say, man? that ch
Yeah, I'll do my weekly um welfare check every
Saturday and that's You done? [Music]
Yeah, my channel is looking
sick. Is actually looking sick to be
fair. It's looking sick. Well, I was
looking what you saying, bro. You
good? I'm just [ __ ] in bed.
Oh, [ __ ] knock
it. Yeah, I'm knocking, bro.
best kind of effect. Yeah, I'm just here,
man. Have a little chill. [ __ ]
out. Yeah, told you I didn't go out
today. Big up me,
eh? Didn't go out drinking.
Yeah, big up me. But
uh Peter Mill said something. He [ __ ] means
it. Yeah, they were good. But I kind of
feel sick, man. Oh, I feel a bit dizzy and sick.
Oh, I don't know man. They didn't Maybe
they're a bit off or something. I don't
know. Can't have been there. [ __ ] knows.
I feel a bit nausea.
Nauseous. Yeah, they tasted good though. [ __ ] knows, bro. Yeah. [Music]
Women are evil, aren't they? Brick bong.
Yes. [ __ ] evil. E. Yeah,
man. Feel a bit sick. [ __ ] hell. I
feel sick. Dizzy. [Music]
No, they can't. It's not they can be,
they are. That's why I don't bother no more,
bro. That's why I don't bother with him,
lad. Like this morning when I woke up, I
was thinking about America again, bro.
Even yesterday, I was actually really
thinking it. But there's no point
because the whole idea is to not be
getting in trouble. And we know for a
fact if we go there, they're just going
to call the
police. Tell me this doesn't make any
sense. That's the thing,
bro. Yeah, it's annoying, bro. It's why
I get myself into these situations no
more, bro. It's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
Proper proper annoying.
Yeah. Can't stand him,
mate. Honestly, can't stand him,
man. You know what I mean,
bro? At least I got my holiday to look
forward to it. At least I got
skin. Life could be worse. But yeah.
Yeah. See, even when I ditch people,
Brick Bong, see the thing is even when I
ditch people. Yeah. Even when I ditch
people, I still like gave them an
explanation. Like this one from
Birmingham. But I ditched them for a
reason cuz I actually done something. I
still didn't ghost them. You understand? So this
Yeah, [ __ ] idiots,
mate. [ __ ] pair of [ __ ] if you ask
me. Rick Bong. [ __ ] pair of [ __ ]
Oh, at least my foot's getting better. I
was going to go Blackpool today, Brit
Bong. Yeah, I was telling you I just
like spontaneously just book a ticket.
But where my foot is not
100, it's like
80% I want to [ __ ] it
up. I don't know. I was bored. Have the
money. Nothing to
do. I don't want to risk
[ __ ] dead. I [ __ ] with my foot iron again.
So So I just just sort of scrap that
idea. I don't know, man. Yeah, the
madness. You know what? It's just nice.
I can't explain it. Like just to have a
roof over your head, clean
clothes, money, you know, it's like you
might think, "Oh, you must have been
bored today. It's a Saturday. You're not
drinking. You're not going out spending
it." But you have to be sat in a
yard with new stuff.
Yeah. Clean clothes, money, food. Yeah.
All your bills paid, gas, electric, like
actually fix yourself, bro. Like,
[ __ ] Life ain't actually
that life ain't actually that bad, you
know? Yeah. You have people out there [ __ ]
struggling. Can't even pay their bills.
You have to worry about
money, you know. I think about it, you
know, just having that like overhead and
food and [ __ ] It's good, man.
And I'm g free as well. G free. 12 days
and counting, mate. 12 days and count. I
think it's 12
days. When did I
last? I can play roulette right now if I want
to. Easily play roulette now.
Okay, now I'm kind of tempted, but not
Like I said, I don't even really miss it
either. The gambling, it's mad because
normally pe people, right, when they
stop, they they sort of miss it. But I
don't even miss it,
man. I just, like I said, I was saying
this earlier, I just wish I never started.
Sorry, but we are going off man.
Yeah, I feel nauseous, bro.
I don't know why. It's kind of
weird. It's that pork I ate,
bro. You don't tell me you're dodgy,
man. Cuz I have to stop eating [ __ ] pork,
man. Yeah, bro. [Music]
And I have to try and learn to walk now
without a limp when this foot thing does get better. Yeah.
I had about [ __ ] four cups of teas
today. I did.
Oh, four cups of teas, man. Yeah. [Music]
Well, at least I save money. We just put in a man
I wonder what happened to that
Charles. Yeah, he got rid, didn't
he? He got rid that Charles.
comment as well. Nah man about sorry
about women having boyfriends. Bro, it's
a bor. Listen, bro. It's a boring
conversation. Most women that say they
have boyfriends, they don't have
boyfriends. Literally 80% of them are
lying. Think about it, bro. What's the chances
that women that's got boyfriends,
they're letting their girlfriends go out
and slag it out?
Like [ __ ] it out, slag it out in a club
every week. Of course, they don't have
boyfriends. 80 literally 80 75 80% of
women that claim they have boyfriends,
they don't have boyfriends.
Like they might be talking to someone,
but there's no way because like I said,
the maths don't add up. If 80 to 85% of
men struggle or single, how can that
many people be in relationships in
nightclubs? The maths don't add up. It
literally does does not add up. Literally like
80% are talking
[ __ ] cuz it's
obvious. It's bollocks,
man. You know,
stupid. More women are single than not.
More men are single than not. So, how
does the ad the maths does not add up?
Literally, the maths literally does not
add up. They don't have boyfriends.
They're full of [ __ ]
like and that's it. You know where
people say it how do you know and that I
was like I'm not going to have this
conversation. This conversation doesn't
make sense. Obviously 80% of them are
[ __ ] lying bro. Why does it matter
anyways? Obviously 80% don't have
boyfriends cuz you go on Facebook right?
You scroll on Facebook, right, and you
go on, for example, women's. Look how
many single women there are, right? More
single than not single. So what? All
these people in clubs
have have boyfriends. It's [ __ ] bro. It's
[ __ ] Come on, man. It's bollocks. Uh-huh.
Yeah. Morgan wouldn't even say she had a
boyfriend. If somebody approached her
now, she wouldn't even say she had a
boyfriend. She would sleep with
him. She wouldn't even say she had a
boyfriend cuz she's a [ __ ]
slug. Yeah. She's a [ __ ] slag. So,
she wouldn't even say she had a [ __ ]
boyfriend. Oh, yeah.
What do you think he'll rock? You know,
when you approach women, how many do you
think are lying about having boyfriends? I think
80% 75 to
80%. Because the maths only because the
maths don't add up because there's loads
of single women out there. There's loads
of single men out there and most men
nowadays are are
struggling. So the maths don't sort of
add up when you're in a club and people
are slagging it about yet. They claim
they got boyfriends. That doesn't even
make any sense because the maths don't
add up. You see, the statistics don't
add up. I'd say 80% online, easy. 75 to 80%, 100%, bro.
Cuz it's obvious, isn't
it? I don't know what you think, but I think about
80%. There's no
way. There's no way. No way. No way. What's
that? What's up?
No, sorry, bro. I'm just about to have a um contrast
bath. I'm about to have a contrast bath for my foot.
Yeah, I'm about to have a contrast
bath. You know, I'm trying to get the
foot better for next
week. I don't even mind the foot taking
long to heal to be fair because I don't
really I don't want to go out drinking and [ __ ]
So, yeah, I had a foot
injury. It's 85% better
now. So, yeah, it only took about
[ __ ] four to five [ __ ] weeks for
sake. Such an annoying injury.
I definitely got that from running, man.
Do I look like a [ __ ] runner? No. Yeah. If
that can have a contrast bath in a
minute. You should have one every night.
I have one every night.
I'm going to send my mom a video of what it
uh what it uh consists of.
Yeah, I felt dizzy for a little bit. I
feel a bit better
now. Use some ice.
Yeah, right. All right, let me do this
contrast bath and I'll be back. Give me
about 10 to 15 minutes. I'll be
back. Yep. In a bit. Be back in a minute.