Hello.
Yep. Just having this
contrast back in the cold water.
a bit as well. Lovely,
man. A lovely contrast bar for the old
foot. Oh, for the old
It should be about long window
time. 3 minutes. 4 minutes. 3 minutes. 1 minute. Oh, madness. [Music]
Madness. One sec.
Sorry about that, mate. Yeah, this is my
last live. Sorry, I was having a contrast
bath. I was having a contrast bath for
the old foot.
I'll be back in a month to do a little
welfare check. They don't have to be every week.
Yeah. A little BS me well for to see if
it's the same people every
day. You know, it shouldn't be though, should it?
Yeah, I was having a contrast bath on my
foot. So, my foot will be perfect by
bank holiday. But I'm sure out bank
holiday either [ __ ]
way mad to be
honest. Oh, this foot bad. Yeah.
had to look after the old
foot. Oh, scary. What? Yeah, that's
funny. Finger rude that session.
Nah. Nah. I'm done with the gambling,
bro. I've had no
urges. Oh, what did I do to my
foot? What scab
there? Wants to burn it on something. Strange. Very
strange. Yeah. Hi, man. How we doing?
lost life for a
month. Anyone else on here can't stand
women? Me can't stand them, mate. Can't
stand the ground they ground they walk
on. Can't stand them. They're
[ __ ] They're evil [ __ ]
bro. And I'm I'm brushing them all in
I'm putting them all under the same
brush. Every single one of them, lad.
them. Yeah. For a month, bro. I've got stuff to do. Can't
be with this [ __ ] Arsenal. Mark, for
[ __ ] sake. It's just the same [ __ ] is it?
Yeah. Slim, do you want me to go to
America and go and Scots
door? Should I go to America and go in
Scots door? Could do, but they'd get the
police. You might as well, bro. If
you're if you're doing something like
that, you might as well just kill
yourself. Not because they would kill you, because
like you you they'd get the law on you and [ __ ]
You'd be you're you're mad, bro, if you
It sounds like a good idea, but you
would literally get [ __ ] That's the
thing. Because they would they would
literally call the police. They actually
would. Like, that's not even an
excuse. Cuz you got to understand, but
if they were on here every day, or not
even every day, like sometimes egging me
on, bro, it would have already happened.
Me being on that
door, me being on that door would have
already happened. Like, it's not even a
joke. We wouldn't even be sat here talking about it.
Yeah, but that's what they would do.
They'd call the [ __ ]
police. They would call the police.
See, do you think I can afford to go
over there, Slim? Yeah, of course I can, mate.
bro. I can afford
to. Do you believe me? No, I actually can, bro.
Yeah. You're the poor one, mate. You
need to [ __ ] have a roommate. Who's
the one who's really poor? You are poor,
mate. You are [ __ ] poor. Not
me. You are actually [ __ ] poor.
go to America every month if we wanted
to. That's the bad thing about
it. That's the mad
thing. No, I wouldn't be going for the
right reasons, bro.
Uh if he
could none of them will come out. Like
even any even all the people she knows,
bro. They would they wouldn't win
against me. They really wouldn't. They
really really really wouldn't,
bro. Like just because people are from
America, it doesn't mean that they're
[ __ ] strong. You know
that? You know what I'm saying, bro?
Like that doesn't mean anything just cuz
what country someone's
from. But would you really waste
34,000 just for somebody to call the police? You
know, she's one of the reasons I can't
stand women. Her and her and another person as well. Yeah.
Can't stand him, bro. I actually can't
stand them. Like, even even when you've
had their body, it doesn't even make it
even any better, bro. Like, bro, I tell
you straight. I've had I've had the
bitch's body, bro. And people Some
people believe it, some people don't
believe it. It ain't even that, blood.
It's cuz I'm so used to
like I'm so used to kind of getting not
revenge on people, but sort of getting
my own back if the situation's that bad.
I'm so used to getting my [ __ ] own
back or depending on obviously how bad
the situation is and obviously when you
can't do that, you know, like it's
that's that's what it is,
bro. You know, it's like that Kenji
thing. He needed telling he needed
telling him about himself. You
understand? Yeah. No, I know. No, I
know, bro. I know. I get it. I get it,
bro. I don't even like the [ __ ] I
don't like the [ __ ] you know? I swear
to God, I do not like that [ __ ] But
it's just, you know, I
mean, I don't like that [ __ ]
[ __ ] Well, there's a
mouth, but it just goes to show how
[ __ ] up the whole um dating thing
is. Slim, why should we have to go out
and deal with negative
experiences? [ __ ] that,
bro. [ __ ] that. you
know, but I'm going to land in two months. Yeah. That's
it. Already booked the flights anyway,
so I'm off.
Yeah, we'll stay till my Sunday, huh?
Yep. Yeah, bro.
Did any of you go out today
drinking? You wouldn't be going for the right reasons.
But you know, bro, it's an ego thing,
ain't it, bro? It is an ego thing.
I mean, there's no point there's no
point even going there to go on holiday
and then do it because you're just going
to get nicked. So, there's no [ __ ]
point. You would 100% get nicked. Would
100%. You would definitely get nicked, bro.
You see how I didn't entertain them
today, bro? You see how I didn't go out
and entertain these [ __ ] today? Nah. One second,
lad. There better not been a maggot in
that [ __ ] port, brother. Better [ __ ] [Music]
Yeah, good day my thing. Yeah, it's good,
bro. I was waiting for some people to
come here, bro,
but turns out they're not.
Well, Bendy's back on YouTube then, isn't
he? That's funny. [Laughter] Yeah. Wait, freak.
Oh my god, bro. What the
[ __ ] Why is no one joining,
man? Come on, Scoop. We know you're
watching. Get a buzz when I see these
little accounts, you know. Yeah. Heat.
[ __ ] hell, bro. hell. [ __ ]
me. Chew chew.
That would make LJ so jelly over
there all that way to get nicked. [ __ ] me. [ __ ]
Imagine that. You go all that way to get
nicked. I'm in Newcastle before I went
all that way to get [ __ ] nicked. Oh, it's [ __ ]
like you want your
job. You on YouTube.
You still on YouTube,
mate? WB saying that above
Oh my god, bro. So [ __ ] up, dude.
How was the police tender? What are you talking about? Police
tender, huh? Oh, the pork chops. Nice,
but they kind of made me
ill. I think the mushrooms, but I don't
know, man. It made me feel
nauseous and [ __ ] dizzy,
bro. Yeah, I don't know why. [ __ ] those,
bro. I was a bit dizzy for a bit. It
might have been the mushrooms cuz
mushrooms make you high, don't
they? Yeah. That's all right,
bro. Yeah, Bill, we was just talking
about how evil women are.
Yeah. Well, in in the West
anyways, in the [ __ ] West, buff
boyfriend as in Musley. Nah, bro. He's
not busting me. Like, I could go there,
bro. Like, you don't understand that,
bro. The thing is I could go there next
week technically, but it's madness
because all they're going to do is call
the police. I can go straight on the
dad's door, bro, and call these bluff,
but they're going to call the police.
And he's a police officer. So, there you go,
bro. What happened to Charles? Well,
they obviously split up, didn't
they? I think I had something to do with that.
Yeah, I think I had something to do with
that. Cuz if you've got a body count of
20 [ __ ] five. Yeah. And you a you
ain't had 25 [ __ ]
boyfriends. So they probably find out
what she is and then they just dump her, I
guess. Cuz she is run through, man. Run
through. Yeah. I don't know what
happened to him.
Yeah, I can't stand it, bro. If I ever
find out his name somehow, I'll message him, bro.
Yeah, I'll message him. But I'm not
going to look for him, bro. [ __ ] that.
But if it comes up like when I'm b I
just message I'll just message him, bro. Straight in
it. Yeah, bro. Oh, it's a mad, isn't
it? Yeah, it's a
madness. But the thing is, I I would
tell her about herself in front of any man's
face. That's the difference. I would say
in front of any man's face, bro. I'm I'm
not asked. It's not about that,
bro. You know the laws are like
nowadays, lad. [ __ ] hell.
I reckon if you got arrested once over
it and then you got arrested the second
time, you would be [ __ ] Trust me. I
think by the second time you'd be [ __ ] Defo, bro.
Defo. But it's a bit like on here
though, is it? Like people want to play
big games, but they're the first ones to
run to police.
So, and they're no different. Their
family's no different. All right.
Trust. Yeah, bro. It's a
madness. But we
learn. That's why there's no point in me even
[ __ ] going out and speaking to
anyone. There's no point me approaching.
There's no point me doing any of that
[ __ ] There's no point in doing any of that [ __ ]
bro. There's just no [ __ ] point, is
there? Let's face it,
man. There's no point, lad.
Now I'm craving it, bro. It's [Music]
popcorn. Yeah, bro.
Charles has got someone else.
Yep. But you see how easy it is for them
to get into
relationships and how much harder it is
for men to get in
relationships. Even if you get one in the
end. It's crazy, isn't
it? You got to spend money. You got to
dress good. You got to deal with their
[ __ ] time and time again. It's
[ __ ] bad, isn't
it? If that doesn't tell you to give up, bro,
then I honestly don't know what will
What happened to her? What's that? Strange.
the left behind.
Thank God for coming to
death. All right. [Music] Oh
man. In fact roulette session. Yeah, boy.
That Morgan is [ __ ] stinking, son. [ __ ] stinking.
She is [ __ ] stinking,
son. [ __ ] stinking, son.
Yeah. A Charles left there,
man. Charles saw the light.
E. Good. Yeah. Good, man.
Now she's found some poor [ __ ] to probably [Music]
use. We need to stop talking about this
skinned loser, mate, in America. [ __ ]
hell. We need to stop talking about this skinned
loser. This broke ass [ __ ] as they
would say over there.
Yeah, we need to stop,
bro. God, these broke Americans,
bro. [ __ ] women are evil. [ __ ]
Kaye. Yeah, that [ __ ] in [ __ ]
America who used me, ghosted me. Then
[ __ ] Sh know the [ __ ] about me. Yeah,
I made her break up with her boyfriend
and look, she's found someone else.
Women have it so easy. Women can be
narcissistic evil. And yet they can
still find people. And then there's
normal people. And I can't even find
relationships. Can't even find willing
people. The world is [ __ ]
bro. Women are [ __ ] They're absolute
[ __ ] mate. I'm not even joking,
bro. It's [ __ ]
up. You still didn't message me on uh
you still didn't message me on
uh on WhatsApp, Katie.
See, I told you, man. I got some money
saved up. I can go to America next week
if I wanted to. I got my passport. I got
all my ID. I got my visa. It's not a
problem. But why am I going to spend34,000 [ __ ] pounds when when
[ __ ] I commented on your thing. I
commented then I deleted
it. I commented then I deleted it. So,
no one got my number.
But then [ __ ] they call the [ __ ] police. [ __ ]
that. They'll call the old bill,
mate. I commented on your thing. I
deleted it quickly. It should be on your notifications.
Well, this is my I'll tell you my number
now anyways because no one no one on
here is going to message me on WhatsApp
because they all use [ __ ] fake
um they all use fake
[ __ ] They all use
fake They all call off unknown numbers and
[ __ ] Yeah, my number is 07542
382759. hit me up on WhatsApp. There you
go. You got my
number. They're not going to message me
because they hide their numbers and they
can't hide their numbers on WhatsApp.
So, people here is not going to message
me cuz their number because then their
numbers their numbers will be put out
there. Do you know what I'm saying?
Yeah, but it's a WhatsApp number. Kayie,
they're not going to message me on
WhatsApp because they can't hide their
number. That's what I'm saying. I've got two
numbers. I've got a WhatsApp number and
I've got like a normal
number. And to be honest with you, they
had my normal number to be honest, but
then I just I just switched Sims and
then they just gave up in the end. They
just gave up in the end because I just
sw I just swapped Sims. So
yeah. Yeah, man. So yeah, message me in it. Come
on. No, I'm not out because I holiday two
months. I'm going on holiday in two
months. I've got like a foot injury
that's like 80% better. I had a foot
injury. So, it's almost 100%. And even
if it was 100%, I still wouldn't go out
today. My friend invited me. I can't be
bothered to drinking and the women
anymore, mate. He knows my
heading. And then like I had like a bad
some bad experiences in the past month
with dates and [ __ ] And then
obviously then you just go on this
Morgan's [ __ ] Facebook and you think,
"Bro, there's not even no point you even
going out and even speaking to people anymore.
Because the the game is so rigged
against you. Like look, a narcissistic
evil little skint dimwit can find
whoever they want clearly, right? And
then you could do what all you can and
you're still going to get the same
results and you'll have to go through
[ __ ] before you even find someone. It
doesn't make sense to me. That's why I
just gave up. But to be fair, I kind of
gave up before that anyways.
So yeah, I don't know when I'll be out
again. Not for a long time. Not for a
[ __ ] long time, bro.
Yeah, that [ __ ] was pissing me off. Shifty,
man. I was thinking about it earlier and
I was thinking about it yesterday.
Bro, but then realizing it's just a
waste of time because we all know if you
went to America, they're just going to
call the police. So again, like they
always call the police.
So So anyways, Katie, do you want to
meet or not? You got my number. So what
do you want to
do? It's basically fed up, lad. Bye-bye, [Music]
Terry. Yeah, shift me, man.
So, that's it, man. You might think,
"Oh, it's boring staying in." But, you
know, just sitting in clean clothes in a
nice house, cooking some food, having
money. It's all you could ask for,
really, mate. It's all you could ask
for. It's all you could ask for, mate. I
think no hangover, no make boyfriends,
ghosting. It's nice, you know, just
nice. Just peace, you
know. Can't be a bit of
peace. Priceless, you know, peace. Bit of
peace. Bit of peace and quiet. Yeah. So
yeah, but no, it was a ghost that done
it for me. shifty. I was speaking to
someone the other week for like 3 days
and we arranged to meet Oh, it was
Friday. It was a couple of days ago
before actually and then they just went
quiet and I was like, "Fuck this. I'm
not doing this [ __ ] again." And it was
just winding me
up. I think I was at my mom's
remember where I was. I was somewhere.
But yeah, it was just winding me up for
3 days. I think I was at my mom's. there
cuz I was trying to rest from
the rest from the [ __ ] uh
injury. So I remember Yeah, it was Yeah,
somebody wasted my time again. [Laughter]
Yeah, you still there,
Kayie? Yeah, I don't think Kale will get
with anyone on YouTube. That's good,
man. That's good. Now she gets with everyone on
YouTube. Talking [ __ ] about me, I talk
[ __ ] about you.
Yeah. I mean, you don't go for drug dealers,
Katie. You know, I hope you don't go for drug
dealers. Another thing I don't get about
these [ __ ] they say they want a normal
person, but somehow they always end up
with drug dealers.
drug dealers and people with [ __ ] domestic
violence. Yeah. Do domestic violence. So
they somehow end up with them
people. It's mad.
Eh, I'm sick of them,
mate. Sick of
them. Sick of them, bro. even block
me. Come on,
Katie. Come on, let's let's stop
talking. Everyone, let's talk on here.
Come on. I'm not going to be live for a
month after today.
So, you might as well just make it
count. That's what I'm
saying. You want to make it
count the riddle. [Music]
I don't ban everyone. Oh, I don't I
don't ban everyone. Just haters and self injectors.
No, I'm just here, man,
chilling. Kind of fed up, but I know
it'll be worth it. So,
yeah, I probably won't be out for about
6 weeks to be honest. When I stay in and
it's more than two weeks, I I I stay in
for ages. six, seven
weeks. It's just so nice having a break
from it all, you know.
Yeah. Women will never change. Never.
This country will never change
either. I'm leaving.
Yeah. No, people can disagree. There's
loads of people that disagree. Grievy
disagrees. Like they You can agree, you
can disagree. I only ban people that
self-p project their skintess and [ __ ]
onto me or just say the word m cuz it's
[ __ ] hating is it? People can agree,
people can disagree. I think you're a
troll by the way as well. I think I've
seen your name before. Spaceman. Yeah,
I've actually seen your name before. Yeah. Okay.
Well, yeah. I just basically saying that
all women are the same and I've had
enough of them. I've given up.
Basically, they're all the same in the
West. So, if you if you watch many
lives, then you know what I'm about.
Simple. Yeah, you should know what I'm about
then. Yeah, I'm basically on a
detox. Haven't been out for like two
weeks. Yeah, I won't be out for a long
time now. Long
time. There's no point me even going out
again. There's no point me even going out
drinking. There's literally just like no
point in it anymore.
There is literally no
point. There's no point at
all. You know, I can't see a point in
it. Maybe I'm the problem. No, I'm not
the problem. End of. You have your
opinion. I have my
opinion. So, good. You've never met
anyone that's had your problem. My
problems with women. Well, you you must
be living under a rock cuz there's loads
of people that's had these problems and
continuously have these problems. 80 90%
of these pe people have these
problems. And that's how you know that
when women say they've got boyfriends,
they're chatting [ __ ] No, they are
literally the problem. That's the whole
point of my approaching videos. Like I
was speaking to somebody for 3 days last
week and they disappeared out of
nowhere. That was them, not me.
Um, so no, it definitely definitely
definitely is them. Like you can have your
opinion. I know how it is. That's why
I'm leaving. So like people don't get
blocked for different opinions. I know
it's not cuz I know how I act. I've got
friends. I make friends all the time.
I'm a very liked person. I know it is
genuinely them. So, I'm not going to sit
there and just argue all day whether
it's them, whether it's me, whether it's
them, whether it's me. The fact that
most people struggle, it it goes to show
it goes to show that it it literally is
them. Cuz when you meet cuz cuz if it
wasn't them, people wouldn't be going to
Thailand. People would be struggling.
There'd be no such thing. If it wasn't
them, literally 5 to 10% of people would
be struggling. It's like 80% minimum now
struggling. So that goes to show that it
literally is them. Like I I go around
Yeah. when I'm walking around, I'm
seeing more and more people with Thai
women now. Thai wives. Why are people
going to Thailand and bringing back tie
wives if they're not the problem? Of
course they're the [ __ ] problem, you
know? Yeah, there's some people that get
them in like [ __ ] drug dealers and scumbags.
Yeah, I'm not saying that never happens,
but no, there's there is loads of people
that have these
problems. Most more than not, more people than
not. Only people only old men. No, they
don't. There's plenty of young people
that go to Thailand. No, there isn't.
There's plenty of young people that go
to Thailand. It used to be only old men.
It used to be only old young people that
go to Thailand
now. Yeah. No, no, no, no, no. There's
plenty of young people that go to
Thailand and it's not just Ant-Man. So that's
[ __ ] But no, they are definitely
definitely definitely are the problem
100%. Like they even do what they do on
purpose, like speak to somebody for 3
days, then ghost them randomly or meet
you even though they've approached you
and then claim within the first 10
minutes they don't feel the vibe. No,
that definitely is them. No, that that
definitely definitely definitely
definitely is them. Trust me, mate. I
know. I've I've wasted money on this
[ __ ] I've done this
[ __ ] And it's not even whether it's me
or them. It's It's not even that, man.
That's irrelevant. It's Why would you
put yourself through more negative
experiences? You've already seen it for
what it is. Some scumbag in America,
some absolute scum, just like a lot of
other narcissistic women can get in and
out of relationships. Yet you and other
men, you would have to go through
[ __ ] upon [ __ ] upon [ __ ]
It's not worth it. It's not [ __ ]
worth it. Doesn't really matter who it
is, you know? That's what you will be
dealing with. Whether it's you or them,
it doesn't matter.
So yeah, I start talking about having
kids with them. No, I don't. That's made
up. Nope. Don't talk about kids. Don't
do no funny voices. Again, makeup. Keep
making excuses for women, bro, and see
how far that gets you in life. Cuz trust
me, it doesn't get you very far. You
know, you haven't seen my messages.
You've seen one message. You've not seen all my
messages. I knew you was a troll. I can
smell your mile off. Stop defending
women. It's not going to get you very
far in life. Stop making excuses for
far in life. Trust me. You're like one
of them people that don't get no women,
but you think defending women will get
women. It's not the truth. It's not the
truth. You don't know anything, man.
That's why I'm not blocking you, cuz
it's not the truth. Cuz if it was the
truth, the truth would hurt and I'd be
blocking you. It's not the truth. And
you have commented before. I've seen you
before, bro. I've seen the same
spastics. I've seen you
before, you know. I have seen you
before. Stop defending women. It's
embarrassing. And it doesn't matter if
my [ __ ] cold approaching videos are
cringe. It shows all what women are
about. Bro, we've seen I've seen you
before. Yeah. I've got a good memory.
And it doesn't matter whether they're
cringe. Yeah. The pro it pro the thing is
right buggler. You know, you get this
advice from people on the internet,
Reddit or other people about women and
what they're like and what they do this
and what, but when you actually go out
in real life, it's completely different.
You complet you experience completely
different things to what you're
told. Like it's like a complete
opposite. Like I think women are [ __ ]
scumbags and and I've had them. Like
that that's my general opinion on them.
Like I'm leaving the country to get away
from them. I don't even go out anymore
cuz I don't want to deal with them. I
can't stand them. You know what I'm
saying? And what I'm saying is not
contradictory, bro. Cuz I I would be out
now. If I didn't feel that way, I would
literally be out now. And the last few
times I did go out, it was just to drink
anyways. So I generally feel that way,
bro. So that's the end, isn't it?
Yeah. That's it,
bro. They literally are scum of the
earth. But I would actually say that I'm
I'm a stable person. And I can't
understand how people can just sit there
and defend them. I shall never know,
bro. I should never know, lad. You know.
Yeah. Anyways, I'm bl I'm banning you
anyways cuz you've typed here
before. Bye-bye. Stop being a [ __ ]
white knight. But you understand, bugler. You understand? You
know you understand why me? But
yeah, the [ __ ] madness,
bro. I can't stand them, bro. I actually
can't I can't stand them, bro. I really
really can't stand them. They're all the
same. Been saying it for
years. Even when I was a [ __ ] virgin,
I've been saying it for years. They
literally are all the same. They're boring,
bro. these uh [ __ ]
Yeah. Don't say that. Yeah,
bro. [ __ ] hell.
I want to look up some
flights. I might as well know. I'm
[ __ ] bored. You know what I
mean? This is dangerous, bro. When
you've got more money than
[ __ ] you got nothing to lose,
bro. See, if I had children, I probably
wouldn't be thinking like this, to be honest.
I just got on it. New York flights £350 quid on
£350 just come up on a sale. One
second. I'm looking at the flight, but yeah. One
second. Austin Logan
International. Oh, that a bit massive
today. They're a bit more cheaper. Look here,
bro. Everybody know that you're a crazy
[ __ ] All living up to your [ __ ]
name, bro. [ __ ] me.
Cool. Live it up to your [ __ ] name. You understand
me? I might just put that quick. I swear to
God. 6 hours and 30 minutes.
Order of 37
quid. Look up lights.
What's the date of [Music]
that? I'm going to do L J proud, bro. I swear
that you're [ __ ] crazy, C. I swear
that I'm going to I'm going to do large
proud going to bring back a load of old
film. That's what I'm going to be doing. But
yeah, all these hotels,
bro. Yeah, but that's a [ __ ] hotel.
See, even if you book the hotel
separately, it's still very
expensive. That's the
thing. Oh, that's not
bad. That's not bad. that little
accommodation but it all works out
roughly roughly the same about 1,800 1900 you're
talking all in
all unless you stay in some [ __ ]
[ __ ] you stay in some [ __ ]
Yeah. [ __ ] hell. Oh
man. That is funny, bro. That is funny.
B. Oh [ __ ]
That's [ __ ] up.
Yeah, it's packed up. Oh
[ __ ] Yeah, it's passed out. That's not What's next?
He's a good cop. He's a good cop. Yeah.
Well, I'm glad, bro.
I'm going to I know.
Don't go anyways. Peace.