Yo, I know I said I wasn't going live,
but yeah, one second. I'll let some
people join. I don't even know why it
just surprises me. I just think it's
because it's just so bad, to be honest
with you, how much they reply to
negativity first thing in the [ __ ]
morning. Some of Some of them was
replied at 7 in the morning. Some of
them at 8 in the morning, like when they
literally just woken up, they reply to negativity.
I think we're going to have to stop
being I think I'm going to have to start
being a [ __ ] like every Saturday. I
think I'm going to have to start being a
[ __ ] man. Cuz it seems negativity
you're getting somewhere with with with negativity.
Yeah, I think I found the answers now. I
think I've actually found the
answers. Yeah, bro. [ __ ] 7 o'clock in
the morning. They're [ __ ] replying. Jeez.
[ __ ] hell. 7:00 in the
morning. That's a
madness. They reply straight away to
negativity. I think about 70% of them
reply back. Well, that's Reddit's advice
out the window. That's people's online
advice out the [ __ ] window then,
isn't it? See, people online would will
This is what I'm saying, right? People
will give advice on the
internet. This, that, this, that, this,
that, this, that. But when you actually
go out, you actually see what they're
actually like. You actually see what
they do. You even see it speaking to
them on [ __ ] line. It's crazy.
They're literally all the same.
You know, if one replied, I'd be like,
"Yeah, okay." They're just
argumentative. But 65% of them replied
back to the first negative. They smell
negativity and they jump on it. They
jump on it, mate. So, yeah. I think we
need to be a [ __ ] Like these drug
dealers, bro. I think we need to start
being like this.
Yeah. I think we have to start being
like them, bro.
and she's, "Oh, I've never gone for a
drug dealer." Well, if you've not gone
for a drug dealer, you've gone for
somebody that has previous for domestic
violence, somebody with tattoos. Like,
literally, all the women you see are
with [ __ ] Like, that's literally
all you ever see them with. Like, if you
actually like there could be drug
dealers, people with tattoos, violent
people. They they they they go for them
kind of people. Yeah.
Cuz look at it, it's not looking right,
you know? Like they should be
ignoring negative messages, but they
reply to negativity. It doesn't make
sense. So I bet they never tell you that
on Reddit. I bet they never tell you
that on the internet anywhere on the internet, you
know. [ __ ] hell,
bro. I even had a model reply. A model
who's 32. I said, "Don't delete the
message. If you got to say something, if
you want to say something, say it. Don't delete the
message." Some didn't reply, but 70% of
them replied. I think that says it all,
man. I honestly
think Yeah, that's crazy, bro. What the [ __ ]
all the same. I'm getting sick of them
or they're evil and then bam, I got loads of
replies. You know what I'm saying, bro?
Like, they reply straight away when you
write something negative about their
gender. That's backwards, bro. That is
very, very, very backwards. I love
somebody I would love somebody on Reddit
to tell me why they do that, you know? [ __ ]
hell. Yeah, man. [ __ ] hell. They're dousing,
bro. Some of them didn't reply, but most
of them most of them
did. Yeah. But the diff I tell you
what's not a gender issue. I tell you I
tell you what's not a gender issue.
That's women. Women keep complaining.
Oh, I can't find people. Oh,
yeah. Oh, poor me. And then you keep
going for the same people, the same
[ __ ] people. You know, that's not a
gender issue. That is a women issue.
Because if you see when you look around
Yeah. you see the you see the same men
struggling. Yeah. That is a woman issue.
Even if the other things are or or a
gender issue, that is a woman issue. But
I even said to this person in Sweden
yesterday, I'm just going to go out
every Saturday and be a [ __ ] That's
what I'm going to do. I'm just going to
be a complete and utter [ __ ] until I
leave. That's what I'm going to do now.
You know, there's no point even going
mad at this.
Yeah. I'm just going to go out with the
intention to get into their knick-knocks
and give them some back over the years
what they've gave us. Problem solved.
Problem completely solved. one day a week. Simple.
Yeah. They reply straight away to
negativity, which tells me Yeah. You do
not want normal people. You know what I'm saying,
lad? Bro, listen. Yeah. I I met people
two some people two weeks ago. I
messaged them. This is what I do, right?
I message them and then they I message
them once and if they don't reply, I'll
message them one more time via voice
note. And if they still don't reply,
delete their number. So yesterday, I was
pissed off. I was in a pissed off mood.
I thought, let me just write to these
women. I think all women are evil. And I
had 70% of them reply to me 7:00 in the
morning, 8:00 in the morning. I think,
bro, you need to stop being a [ __ ]
Like, you're you're on the right path
here because they don't like normal
people. They don't like negative. They
don't like positive people. And my bad,
maybe you haven't gone for a drug
dealer, but I know for damn sure you've
gone for somebody with tattoos, somebody
that's got previous for domestic
violence. They only go for these kind of
people. Look around you. Even celebrities, you
know, you need to you need to go around
and stop being an absolute [ __ ] It
will get you it will get you far in
life, you know. Defo, bro. Defo.
So yeah, they choose the people that
they moan about. That's a woman issue.
That is literally a woman issue. They
choose they choose the people that they
go for. And it's either drug dealers,
people with tattoos,
um people with
tattoos or just absolute just just Yeah.
scumbags. Yeah. Basically, they
literally go for these kind of men. They
choose these kind of men.
You know that is a fact that w that is a
woman problem. That is literally a woman
problem because at the end of the day
men are the ones that have to lower
their standards. So how can it be for
both genders? They're the ones that have
to literally lower their standards and
settle. Know what I'm saying, bro? the [ __ ]
morning. See, he hasn't seen my [ __ ]
Why is he not seeing my [ __ ] So
yeah, sometimes it still is unbelievable
how they reply so quickly to
negativity, but they ignore
positivity, you know, and then they try
to act smart. They're literally all the
same, you know. I was actually fed up
with them even when I was seeing that
person. I'm actually fed up. I I just
can't comprehend how people sit there
and and defend them. And I don't even go
out anymore like that. And they just
sit. I don't understand how they can
defend them, bro. It's madness.
Yeah. The only reason I'm not going to
[ __ ] America cuz I know they're just
going to call the [ __ ] police, you
know? I just said that to them as well.
Like, it's obvious, isn't it? It's
completely [ __ ] obvious.
How do I get myself in these [ __ ] sit
[ __ ] in these situations? Go tell
that to people on [ __ ] Reddit. Why do
they reply to
negativity? They reply straight away to
negativity. Oh my
god. Straight away in your [ __ ] DMs,
bro. WhatsApp. [ __ ] hell.
One or two replied out of 10. A lot of
them replied. That's
crazy. Be a [ __ ] on Saturday. Anyway,
it's going to it's going to be called
[ __ ] Saturday. I'm going to go out every
Saturday and try to get into their
nickn give give some of them back before
give some back over the years what
they've done to you. Do you know what
I'm saying? Yeah.
Yeah, that's what we need to do, bro,
before we leave this [ __ ]
country. Like your your your whole goal
should just be to go out and use them.
Literally, they're not people. They're
not nice people in general. Your whole
thing should be now just going out and
using them so you can still despise them
at the same time whilst you're trying to
get in their dicknocks. That way you
don't contradict yourself. Just be a
[ __ ] That's what I'm going to do. Yeah.
And if any of them say they want a
relationship, just just just just just
[ __ ] them around. Bit like what they do.
do. Go out. Don't expect anything. Just
be a complete and not a
[ __ ] you know? Because what goes
around [ __ ] comes around. Yeah. Yeah, one
sec. Here's the thing you're
understanding. It's the men that you go
for. Look, look, I'm sorry to happen to
you, but it's not because she's a woman.
Again, some men treat Yes. Yes. But it's
the men that you go for. It's the men
that you choose. It's not the men that
you come across. It's the men that you
choose. That's the difference with us.
It's the women that we keep coming
across with you. With these women, it's
the men that they are
choosing. It's the men that they are literally
choosing. You know, so no, it wouldn't
be fair for you to generalize all men
because it's the men that you are going
for on purpose. You know what I'm saying?
So then I can prove that from my
experience. You live in my area, you
don't want to meet
up. You know what I'm saying? So
banging [ __ ] headache. So, um, so you
know when I got some of them numbers two
weeks ago, yeah, I was in a pissed-off
mood yesterday, so I thought, let me
just message them saying, "All women are
evil. I've had enough of women. They're
negative." And so many of them replied
out of nowhere, like replied, replied,
replied 7:00 in the morning, 8 in the
morning. I woke up to a couple of
messages. I was like, "Shit, they really
do like negativity. They don't tell you
this on Reddit. They don't tell you
this." See, like I was saying to you,
Cactus, I know you're a troll and all
that. Is what people tell you on Reddit
or TSR or anything on the internet, it's
parallel to what you actually experience
in real life. You know, it's completely
different. Any advice that you get is
completely different to what you'll
experience in real life. Like it should
be the other way around. Them replying
to nice messages and them ignoring
negative messages. I even had a model
reply on my WhatsApp who I met two
months ago, a [ __ ] model who's 32.
She should know better. And then she
deleted a message. I said, "If you got
to say something, don't delete your
message." You know, if you got to say
something, leave it and say it. Do you
know what I'm
saying? So many of them replied to to
negativity. You know, it's all
backwards. It's all backwards, bro. Is it? Really?
Yeah. And she's like, "Oh, well, men do
it as well, but it's the men that you
choose." Yeah. I told them, "Yeah, that
like, oh, it's it's unfair for men and
I'm sick of it and it's negative and
that." And loads of them replied back.
Yet, they ignored normal messages. They
ignored normal nice messages. But these
same women, I tell you what, I said to
her, I tell you what is a woman issue.
You keep moaning about men and you keep
going for the same kind of men. Drug
dealers, um, scumbags with tattoos and
or people that have previous for
domestic violence. They're the only
people that they go for. She was like,
"Oh, I I've never been with a drug
dealer or anyone I know has ever been
with a drug dealer." Oh, sorry. My bad.
Well, you've been with a scumbag with
tattoos and somebody that's got previous
for domestic violence. I would put my
life on it because if you go around and
you see these women, right, you will
literally see them with the same
[ __ ] the same three or four
things. So, I'm just going to start
going out Saturday and being a [ __ ] now.
That's what I'm going to start doing.
I'm just going to start going out
Saturday trying to get people's
knick-knocks and just being a nasty [ __ ]
for the day. That's what I'm going to
start being cuz that's clearly going to
get you somewhere, you know? That's
clearly clearly clearly going to get you somewhere.
You know what I'm saying? No, it's not
chatting the same [ __ ] bro. It's It's
true. It's the truth. What I'm saying?
Yeah, I might have been chatting the
same [ __ ] for years. I And it shouldn't
even surprise me, to be honest. But I
just find it so backwards. It shouldn't
surprise me because they've been doing
this for years where they reply to
negative messages. So, to be fair, it
shouldn't. But it somehow still does
surprise me because they all moan about
men. They all winge about men. Yeah. Men
are the ones that lower their standards.
They they moan and wins about men. So it's
crazy. That's that's that's a gender
issue, though. That's definitely a gender
issue. That's definitely a gender
issue. Yeah. Yeah. Been there, done it,
worn a t-shirt cactus. All they do is
cry to bounces, run to
bouncers. I'd love to tell that [ __ ] in
America about herself, but we all know
what will happen. It's something
beginning with PO. [ __ ] PR, mate.
Yeah, I love to tell her about herself as
well. What? 34,000 just to get nicked? Nah,
mate. Just to get [ __ ] [Music]
nicked. Yeah, they are Germany evil, man.
Some people need to get some [ __ ]
life experience for a [ __ ] change.
I'm telling you, bro. They actually do.
They actually do,
bro. I'm saying I probably won't even go
out in this country again, bro. I've got
no plans to bors me, mate. [ __ ] bors
me. Some thingy, bro.
Yeah. Talking to people all the same.
Doesn't sound very fun, does it? Doesn't
sound very fun.
They reply straight away to negativity.
That one in Birmingham blocked me, by
the way. But I did ditch her, so I get
it. I did ditch
her. Yeah, I did ditch her. So, I mean,
she has she had a reason to that. But
yeah, they literally are all the same.
27 years and counting, you
know. Yeah. I said, no, I said to
somebody that she's being a bit of a
[ __ ] and I literally got banned. I tried
to get in there like, well, I got in
there three weeks ago, but then they
kicked me out. They're all the same,
bro. They're literally all the same.
Like, the only thing you should do is
just go out every Saturday, be a
[ __ ] Call it [ __ ] Saturday
every week and count down the days until
you leave this country. That's all you
need to do now. That's the only thing
that's left now. I think it's the only
thing that's left. There's there's
there's no positives. There's nothing.
Literally, it's the embo. It's over.
It's all over. That's it.
Yeah, stupid. Yeah, she was a Canadian
bartender and she was being a bit of a
[ __ ] Um, and I just said, "Oh,
she's been a bit of a [ __ ] in it to
someone, not to her." And then somehow
they knew and I got th Well, they they
didn't throw me out. They just said,
"Oh, you have to leave." Well, they got
thrown out, but they didn't like put
their hands to me. You know what I mean?
So, that's what they do. They like to
start [ __ ] with people that they see as
vulnerable and then when you give it
back to them, they all play the stalking
card. Oh, he's stalking
me. Stalking. They don't even say
harassing. They say stalking. That's why
there's no point of it anymore, bro.
There's no point. There's literally no [ __ ] point, you
know? All the same. It'd be nice to meet
people that weren't all the same, but I
think women are all the same.
I'm I'm living proof of it. 27 years and
counting and I'm living proof of it,
Cactus. I am living proof of it. I used
to tell them about themselves, bro. But
I had to be really careful back two
years ago cuz you know I don't want to
be getting [ __ ] nicked to that
getting a [ __ ] criminal
record. Know what I'm
saying? P is police. So that's exactly
what's going to happen if you go over
there and you know you go on the door.
They they're going to call the police,
bro. They're going to call the
police. Yeah, I was just talking about
women and how they reply straight away
to negative messages but ignore normal
messages, but they complain they can't
find a decent guy. They can't find a
normal guy, but yet they reply to
negativity. Strange that is it? you
know. Yeah. Apparently, not all women
are the same. Well, I got told I got
told pigs fly, but I've never seen that,
you know. I believe it when I see it. Yeah.
No, I am done with them. I am done with
them, bro. I am done with them. I just
woke up to their messages. I messaged I
messaged a few of them yesterday saying
all all women are evil and [ __ ]
they're negative. And then I had I had
them reply back. 70% of them reply back.
And I'm thinking, well, that's not
looking right. Because people say that
women like positivity and this and that
and this and that and this and that.
Yeah, they reply to negativity. As soon
as you're negative, they reply. They
smell negativity a mile. They love
negativity. They love drug dealers. They
love tattoos. They love domestic
abusers. They're the only people that they
like. And I'm living I'm living proof of
it. Like I generally think, yeah, these
people on Reddit have got no life
experience or any form for that matter.
They've got no life experience. You
know, you know what I'm saying? They're just
evil. Trust me, bro. If I knew that [ __ ]
in America weren't going to call the
police, I would be on that door next
week, bro. Like, believe it. Don't
believe it. Believe it. Don't believe
it. I know what I'd be doing, bro. I
wouldn't even worry about people on
YouTube calling the police. I'm worried
about them calling the [ __ ] police.
You know what I'm
saying? They were fire, you get [ __ ] burnt.
And but yeah, and like I said, bro, the
annoying thing is the is the ghosting
and the [ __ ] them meeting you and
then making up an
excuse. And then that goes to show my
point. They they complain that they
can't find normal people. That don't make
sense. Even that one that met me two
weeks ago, bro, it was annoying. God, it
was annoying, bro. Even though I didn't
like her, she was like a four out of 10,
she met me, she traveled an hour away to
meet me and she approached me, yet she
claimed that she don't feel the vibe.
And I thought, you know what? Yeah,
we're just wasting our time here with
this [ __ ] is it? They're clearly
disturbed. They clearly are [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah. I'll tell her
um the body count and obviously I've got
the messages as well, but I'm not going
to look for him. I'm not going to do all
that. But if if it comes if I look one
day and I see him, yeah, I'll message
him 100%. Of course I will, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. You want to be evil? You
want to laugh at being evil? Don't cry
when somebody does something bad to you
then. You know who the [ __ ] do you think
you are ghosting people? You could have
at least apologize and left [ __ ] on good
terms. All of the people that's done
that, I've never had a problem with
them. Never had a problem with them. And
I've had loads of people make up an
excuse and I've just laughed at it and
then moved on. Like you want to be a
[ __ ] but then when someone's a come
back to you, you want to play victim.
This doesn't make sense, bro.
You know, it doesn't make
sense. And she's probably the most
arrogant person I've ever come across,
Cactus. She's the most arrogant person
I've ever come across in my life. For
somebody that looks like that, for
somebody that's got no money. Like,
she's got a big ego. Wonder where it
come from. Don't think it was. You know
what I mean? What?
Dad. Yeah, exactly, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Exactly. Exactly,
bro. Yeah. Exactly, bro. I'll be there,
mate, with a load of [ __ ] I'll turn
up to the wedding, bro. I will turn up
to the [ __ ] wedding, bro, with a load
of red wine and start spilling it on
people all over the white dress.
And it's not jealousy, bro, cuz I don't
like her. Yeah, I do not like her. I've
had better before and I've had better
after. It's the whole principle. Yeah. I
don't mind if people in happy
relationships and people get married,
man. I'm happy for anyone. Just not evil
people, you know? Just not evil
people. Just not evil people. You know what I'm
saying? But then the dad's so surprised
when he gets messaged. Doesn't make sense.
Maybe raise your kids up [ __ ]
properly then. Is it?
Yeah. It's madness. Is
it? It's a madness.
E love to be a landlord, bro. Love to be
a landlord, bro. Just open that [ __ ]
door on it.
I open that [ __ ]
door. I mean,
madness. But you're going to spend
£34,000 and all you're going to do is
get yourself nicked. That's all that's going to happen. Yeah.
Uh they're generally generally evil
people. They're generally generally
horrible people in general. They really
really are. Do you remember that Mr. G
account? He was like, "Oh, they're nice
people in general." No, they're [ __ ]
not. No, they're [ __ ] not, mate. I
can't remember one that was that was
that weren't evil. I'm not even joking.
No. No. I can't remember one that weren't evil,
lad. Izzy was evil. But I admit I
brought some of that on myself. That one
in America was one in America was evil.
The people that waste your time, they're all
evil. I think we need to set up a camp a
campaign about this. And we also need to
set up a campaign of how they always reply to
negativity. That's a big thing. I want
to really get that out there. I really
want to get that out
there. Know what I
mean? And yeah, Cactus, why should you
have to go out every week dealing with negative
experiences? Why? Why? You know, the
game, you know, it's rigged against you.
So, what's the point dealing with
negative experiences, let downs,
negative experiences, let downs. That's
going to affect your mental
health, you know.
Nah, bro. [ __ ]
that. But I am done with
them. People like to be evil, but then
when somebody gives it back to them,
they don't like it. What's I have today?
Roast. Might go for a roast, you know? I don't know.
I don't really fancy pork. No, I'll
probably just get someone to make me a curry or
something. I need to get the [ __ ] Oh
[ __ ] Let's get to the
[ __ ] Oh my god.
I want a chicken curry, bro.
Yeah. But yeah, it's not the ignoring,
it's it's the
ghosting. And they do do it on purpose.
They literally do do it on purpose. They
do do it on purpose. Everything they do
is on purpose. Like don't let anyone
ever tell you, oh, you know, they didn't
feel. No, no. They they do it on
purpose. They definitely definitely do
it on purpose. Unless you message me and
they've just never replied. Of course
they do it on purpose. They're all
[ __ ] in their head. do
that. Can't believe
that. Yeah, it's a madness,
bro. And I've got too much pride, bro.
I'd rather just live off [ __ ] using
escorts. I've got too much
pride. I think that's what it come down
to in the end. Like I don't want to
degrade myself or humiliate myself for
them. You know what I'm
saying? Yeah. Some madness,
bro. What should I have for
breakfast? I've got a really bad headache. activity. Yeah.
6:00 in the morning. [ __ ]
hell. 6:00 in the morning, she
replied. [ __ ] I didn't even wake up at 6. Jesus.
Shoot as I was negative. [ __ ] hell.
Says a lot about women.
E don't let this annoy you, bro. You
know, I should be the bigger person, but
it's hard to not let it annoy
you. But it does. It is
Can't believe how quickly they reply to
negativity as well,
man. Oh, I got a nice
curry from you today.
Oh, maybe I go on Reddit and ask why do they
reply so quickly to um negativity. Yeah.
Imagine asking people if they're [ __ ] poor
when asking people if they're poor when
you can't even afford to rent your own
flat. You can't even afford to rent your own
apartment. Like come on, man. You're in
relationship. You're a broke ass [ __ ]
Think of it, bro. If there's two people,
you're telling me they can't afford to
[ __ ] pay rent together. Well, that's
that's just how you know that they're
just broke. They just skin, mate. Like,
honestly, okay, I understand if you live
in London and you're a single person. It
is quite expensive. I'd rather just live
with my parents if that was the case.
But you're in a relationship and yeah,
okay, it probably is as expensive as
London, but you're in a relation [ __ ]
ship. That's embarrassing to be in a
relationship when you still um madness.
Yes. You're in a relationship and you
can't even afford to [ __ ] That's
madness, bro. That is a madness. Yeah.
Yeah, like I said, all the people before
when I'd get their number, they be like,
"Oh, I'm not looking for anything." And
then they would just block. Then I would
just laugh at them, you know? I just
them. I just don't want them to ever
complain that they can't find men then.
I just don't want them to moan and
complain cuz they're not the ones that
lower their standards. You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. Well, I'll be back later anyways. See you.