[Music]
How we doing, bro? Yo, woman replied,
"You're not you, bro. You're not going
to guess, right?" Okay, let me let me
tell you a bit of the uh back. You want
to hear about a bit of the backstory?
Please tell me you got a bit of time.
I'll uh cuz I don't think I told you
about I don't think I told anyone on
YouTube about this
one. Oh, [ __ ] hell. 99% of them women
replied to to the negative comments.
They're all the same. Okay. Uh do you
want me to tell you what happened
quickly? They are literally all the
same. Every single and last one of them.
Oh, can I can I explain it?
I want to explain it, bro. Like, you're
going to laugh at this one. I don't
think I told anyone about this on
YouTube. So, about three months ago, I
approached this woman on the street and
she was from Italy. Now, I didn't expect
anything from her. I didn't even expect
to meet her again. Um, because obviously
she lives in Italy and I I just felt
like being in a good mood. So, I was
basically being a tour guide. I said,
"Do you want to serve showed around Chinatown?
T three months ago. I then messaged her
two days later. So I let them get back
home first. We don't need to pounce on
them. And I was only expecting for one
reply because obviously the context. I
showed her around. She was in the
country by herself. No reply. Lost in
transit in in in the Mexico transit. I
messaged her two days ago saying all
women are evil. Bam. She replied, She
replied with a paragraph saying, "Oh,
uh, yeah, I was going to reply to you.
Um, but I didn't want to lead you on.
No, no, no, no, no. You was going to
reply to me. You didn't reply for 3
months. As soon as I sent a negative
message, you was on it like a a
butterfly on [ __ ] on a hot summer's day
in Australia." And she was claiming how
she doesn't feel um the connection. And
basically what she's doing is she's
trying to victimize herself. So when
she's saying about how she doesn't feel
the connection, it's a way of
victimizing herself for being ignorant
and being ignoring because there was no
dating going on. So they they they're
actually trying to victimize themselves
by blaming something that can't be
helped i.e. a connection and then and
then I like you was going to reply what
in about 10 years time. So then I
message her saying oh um okay let's hear
it. It's funny. Why can't why don't you feel the
connection? Then she replied saying how
uh yeah you're uh she said that when you
asked me for my number I felt a bit
uncomfortable. I said yeah okay you
might have felt a bit uncomfortable
initially. You know you're you're in
London you're a woman by yourself. Of
course you probably felt uncomfortable.
But by the end of the day, I think I I
completed the deed where I showed you
that not every single man is a rapist or
a murderer or a kidnapper. You still had
your phone. I had your number. You
didn't reply to the message. That's you
being ignorant. Stop trying to victimize
yourself. And then she was trying to
say, "Oh, and I don't like your mindset
and that you're you're misogynist
comment." Again, victimizing yourself.
That comment is the reason that you
replied. If I did not write that
comment, you would have ignored it. If I
did not say all women are evil, you
literally would have never ever ever
reply that to me. Stop victimizing
yourself because you're claiming that
you don't engage with people that write
something that's misogynist. You've just
wrote me three paragraphs in the same
day. Make it make sense. Stop
victimizing yourself. And like I said,
it wasn't three women out of 10. It was
99% of them. That tells me all you need
to know about women. They're all the
[ __ ] same. If it was three or four of
them, I would have been like, "Okay,
well, maybe they're just [ __ ] and
they're just [ __ ] and not all women
are." But literally, all women are the
same. They always try to victimize
themselves. Like, they have no
intentions of replying, but then as soon
as you write a negative comment, they
reply straight away. That's what I mean.
there. That's been happening for years
though. That to be fair that that though
has been happening for uh quite a few
years. That's not like a new
thing. [ __ ] ignorance.
Yeah. That's why I gave up, lad. Yeah,
that's so I mean uh Brit blog. I
actually done a video talking about
this. It's about half an hour long. It's
dedicated to L because you always
promotes positivity, positive mindset.
Well, why is it that you get
conversations when you're negative? And
you know what I said to her? I said, I
wish you the best as well. I said, I
hope you fix your mental health problem,
your mental health problems, and you
don't feel that you need to only respond
to negative comments. See, I'm cheeky.
You see, I'm cheeky like that. I said,
"I wish you the best as well, and I hope
you're well, and I hope you fix your
mental health problems, and you don't
feel the need to only reply to negativity. You
know, I'm so cheeky, you know. I'm a
cheeky chappie, you know. I can't
believe that just goes to show they're
all the same. all different ages,
different countries. They all replied
back to negativity. The nice messages
got lost in the [ __ ] Mexican border.
They were never getting a reply back to.
But as soon as you write something negative,
they're there. Faster than me, mate. And
I'm quite fast. They're all the
same. They all are [ __ ] same. Every
single last one of them because they
wasn't. Why do they all do the same
[ __ ] Why do they Why do they all act
the same if they're not the same? But
that's a good argument, you know. So,
yeah, you don't feel the connection cuz
somebody asked for your
number. Are they Are they being stupid
on purpose? Like, I actually feel like
some of these people are being stupid on purpose.
What do you
think? They love negativity. [ __ ]
hell. Why would anyone love
negativity? Why would anybody love
negativity? Anyways, I'm going to post
this video up, I think. Yeah, I'll go
that live in a bit.
Yeah, we'll post this