Look,
48 hours ago. Whoa.
Nothing, bro. I just went to an escort.
The football hasn't even played yet, but
I just went to an escort and got my Todd
sucked. She was like, "Oh, you you don't
want to fuck." I was like, "No." They
get angry because some of them don't
like giving [ __ ] and obviously when
they're paid, they do it right, but they
want to [ __ ] as well. I was like, "I
don't want to [ __ ] I just want a
[ __ ] blowjob." But the football's not what started
yet. So yeah, I done it anyways. Even I
didn't win the football. I thought Let
me kill some time. 80
quid. Yeah. 80 quid it cost. Yeah. Yeah.
80. It was nice, bro.
Should have probably left it another day
though to be
fair. Yeah, I should have left it another day. I
reckon. Nope. I don't have [ __ ] with
Johnny. Some of them don't do it. Um,
[ __ ] without a condom. I never have a
[ __ ] with a condom, bro. It's [ __ ]
You can't even feel anything. Hell
no. Hell no, bro. You can't feel
nothing. What's the
point? [ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] with a
[ __ ] I haven't had a [ __ ] with a condom [ __ ]
ages. When I used to [ __ ] the escorts,
when I used to [ __ ] them, obviously I
used to just they used to give a [ __ ]
with with the
condom. Yeah, I don't like [ __ ] with
condoms. So, have to find somebody that
uh Yeah, she was nice. Yeah, I just just
wanted a [ __ ] I've not got the
energy nowadays to
[ __ ] No, I don't know why I'm so used
to [ __ ] I ain't [ __ ] for
ages. Yeah, she was nice. It was nice,
but it's just I don't know
why I need to get into [ __ ] again and
not getting [ __ ] I think that's
what it is. I'm too used to these [ __ ]
Yeah, but no more reacting to weirdos on
this channel. They want to stalk and be
obsessed with me all their life. Let
them crack on,
mate. Let them crack
on. So hopefully this football bet
wins. 40 returns 122. See, I don't do
long odd football bets.
That was obviously to pay for the
[ __ ] but I just got one anyways cuz
[ __ ] it in
it. [ __ ] it. Yeah.
this a double both teams to
score. Double both teams to
score. I will go live at some point in
the nightclub doing some approaches just
to wind these people
up like Peter Griffin and you know who
you know Peter
Griffin. Yeah, we all know who Peter
is. And that's and then when you look at
them, you see why they do what they do
every day on
YouTube, you know? No, I don't mind
paying for what I want. It is what it
is. And then if you actually see what
these people look like, you will
see Knots County versus Colchester
Markhamm versus Doncaster Rovers. Double
both teams to score. I think that's a good chance
me. Of course he has. And he's a he's
still a virgin just like Peter Griffin.
If you don't know who Peter Griffin is,
it's that Jamie
Thompson. Both virgins. That's why they
obsessed with me. That's why they're
obsessed with me every day on YouTube.
They're obsessed with me because they
want to be me. I I was speaking to my
mom about this. Yeah. I swear to God. I
was like, they are obsessed with me.
Like I I swear to God, my mom was like,
"Oh yeah, they're jealous." Like this
has been going on for years and years. I
said it's mad. Like these people are
really really obsessed with me. Like
even Timmy has not had channels
dedicated to him and he's been on it
longer than me and he's on the maddest
[ __ ] and he doesn't even have channels
that are dedicated to him.
That's a maza, bro. I think these people
lowkey want my want my ass, bro. I'm not
even joking. I said to my mom as well,
like, if these people are homosexual,
there's nothing wrong with being a
homosexual, you know, as long as you
come out, you know, I've got nothing
against gay people. I've come across gay
people in my time. It's okay to be a
homosexual, but not coming out is, you
know, is is the
problem, you know.
No, he's still a
virgin. I still can't believe that phone
call though, bro. Like, the things they
do is just so weird and unbelievable.
And they don't mess with anyone's head.
They don't ruin anyone's life, you know?
I don't know how many times like people
have to say that they don't bother no
one, but their weirdness never fails to amaze me.
So yeah, it's like there's nothing wrong
with being there's nothing wrong with being gay,
bro. There's nothing wrong with being gay. Nah.
Nah, but that's all we have in this
country really is football bets and
escorts. Unless you get extremely
lucky a woman that he doesn't even know
that doesn't even know me that's never
even met me, bro. She doesn't think
anything because she's disabled. You
don't understand? Like, you know, just Jamie Thompson,
um, this uh Sarah Desawn, they're all
disabled. You No, no, no. Like, bro,
they are disabled. Like I'm not saying
it like how these people say, "Oh,
you're, you know, you're disabled. You
know, you've got autism." Like these
people actually have. Like what they do
every day is not normal to anyone, bro.
You know, sat there stalking you on
Instagram, refreshing Reddit pages, even
though that wasn't even me on Reddit,
but you get the point. They have got
autism. I was telling my mom about this
as well. They have to have they have got to be
disabled. You know, it's they do it
every single day. They want your ass,
bro. I swear down. They want your ass.
They want to anally penetrate you. I swear to
God. A woman that he doesn't even know. You
know, I swear if I ever see that [ __ ] on
the street, I'm going to whoop his ass.
I swear to God, I'm going to whoop his
ass. And to be honest with you, I
probably get away with it in court. If I
show all of the harassment that they've
been doing over the years, I think I'd
have a good case. I'm not even joking.
like all in court if you went to court
with all of the [ __ ] he has been doing
over the years because of his autism.
Yeah, I I think you get away with it,
bro. I'm not even joking. I actually
think you would. At this point, you actually [ __ ]
would. You're still not been laid. Um,
bro, I've been laid a million times.
What are you talking about? Have I still not been
laid? I've been laid a million times, lad.
Well, then it loses, isn't it?
I don't care if it loses, right? If it
loses, it loses. I don't care. I didn't
care last week. I cared last week that
that [ __ ] in Manchester pissed me off.
That annoyed me, bro. It did actually
me. I was crazy last week cuz of this [ __ ] in
Manchester. This [ __ ] in Manchester,
bro, was winding me up, lad. Oh, keep it
real. It was winding me up. No, the
woman that I met, the woman that I met
from Manchester, the one that wasted my
time for three
days, it w me up, bro. I'm not going to
lie. It did actually w me up.
dinner. So, I've got people stalking my
Instagram and I've got people When are
the baiffs kicking me out? The baiffs
are not kicking me out because that
wasn't me on
Reddit. So, yeah, I don't post on the
advice subreddit. They've got my
Instagram, but they ain't got my
Reddit. So, I don't post on Reddit subreddits no
more. Not exactly a great life I'm living. Oh,
really? Coming from you, somebody that
got their kids took off
them. See, the thing is, right, Kaye,
these people have never ruined my life.
They've ruined your life. They've not
ruined my life. But trust me, they've
been trying for years. They've been
trying for years, but they never ruin my
life. They don't These people don't
bother me one little
bit. You know, all they can do is stalk
you and all that. You know what I'm saying? And
yeah, but you need to make these people
mad, bro. I swear to God when I go to a
bar or a club again, I'm going to I'm
going to make these people jealous. I
don't know when I'm going to go out again. But
yeah, but no bail kicking my door down,
bro. I pay my rent every [ __ ]
month. But it's weird that you're trying
to stalk me on Reddit. No, no, no, no,
no. See, with Reddit, I private message
people. I try to um private me I private
message people. I don't make posts
because of these stalkers. because of stalkers, you
know, you know, like because of these
stalkers. I just private message people.
I don't even post on subreddits most of
the time because of these people following me
everywhere. Like I get stalked to [ __ ]
by these people. Yeah. And they go for
me more than anyone else. Which is why I
think they're jealous of me because they
go for me more than anybody else. They
don't go for Timmy. They don't really go
for Monty. They go for me. And they
don't stop. They want to be me. I'm
telling you, bro. As delusional as that
sounds, it is
true. It is true, lad. I'm telling you,
it is true. You
know. Yeah. Because they don't go for anyone
else. They don't, bro. Not like they do
me. Not like they do me. Timmy doesn't
have no channels dedicated to
him. I think it's because they hate the
fact that you're better looking than
them and that you got more money than
them. I think that's what it is
personally. That's what I think it
actually is without like blowing smoke
up my own ass, bro. Like it's because
it's like what somebody said before,
you're better looking than them, you got
more money than them, and it kills them.
I think they were right. I generally
generally think they were right that
that Ronald Hump account
um and have a better life to them
because obviously you go out. I
generally think that's what it is 100%.
I think they were right,
bro. And they said you need to get off
this [ __ ] Yeah, I actually think they
were right for 100%. I think they were
right. You know, these little weirdos.
And they and they don't even make it entertaining
either. You know, I've got a life, Kaye.
That's the thing, Katie. Why don't you
get off YouTube and get your kids
back? That's not even me being nasty.
Why don't you get off of YouTube and get your kids
back instead of coming on here every day
entertaining these [ __ ] mongos, you know?
Well, that's what you need to be doing,
mate. Shouldn't be [ __ ] You've got
your kids. No, you don't have your kids.
How do you have your kids? You don't
have your [ __ ] kids. You
know, and that's it. You don't know your
kids. And that's not even me being
nasty. I'm just telling you straight. You
know, these people in here are [ __ ] weirdos.
I don't know why they do what they do
every day, man. It's so
weird. It's so weird, man. [Music]
I'm literally on here every day,
PJ. No, I'm not on here every day, mate.
I've been off of here for days, weeks, a
month before. No, I haven't. No, I
haven't, mate. No, I No, I'm not on here
every day, you know? And it depends what
you're doing on here every day. Like,
you people just self-reflect every day.
That's why you don't bother me. If I see
a comment, I just block the comment now
because I just know that all you do is
self-reflect. That's why it doesn't
bother me what any of these people say.
They're always going to do this
[ __ ] you know, cuz they've got autism.
Obviously, they've got autism, otherwise
they wouldn't be doing this every day.
It's facts, isn't it? Try getting laid
for once. I've been
laid. I've been laid, bro. Been laid. I
have been been
laid. Get laid. Oh, get laid for once. Yeah. Funny,
eh? What do you think about that person
from Manchester Joe? It was a madness, isn't
it? And she must be vulnerable. Well, disabled
because why would she be speaking to
somebody on the phone for 1 hour over 1
hour just that she doesn't even
know? So obsessed. I know that I know
that word is like overused but it is obsession, you know.
Crazy. But if I ever see him, bro, I
will batter him.
You people don't cause me no stress. You
people don't bother me one little bit.
You're just obsessed on YouTube every
single day. I'm the one that causes you
people stress. You don't cause stress.
You just repeat yourselves and do the
same [ __ ] Report people's benefits. You
don't cause anyone
stress, you know. Yeah. No, no, no.
Jealous me. They're jealous. They're
jealous of me because I'm better looking
than them. I've got more money than
them. I've had more women than them.
I've got better clothes than them. Look
at what I have compared to
them. You know what I'm saying, bro?
Like, yeah, they couldn't pay no one for
[ __ ] because they ain't got no
money. It doesn't matter whether you
paid for it or you don't. There you go.
There you go. You paid for it. So,
you've obviously got more money than these people.
Obviously, when was the last time you
people went 3, four miles away from your house? You
know, you people wouldn't even have
money to pay someone. What's wrong?
Money comes and goes. You pay women or what?
Like, okay. And and your point is
[ __ ] I'd rather go up the road and
pay somebody for a [ __ ] [ __ ] then
sit on YouTube all day
projecting like you [ __ ] little
mongos do. You ain't got a life. So
yeah, and that's it.
It doesn't matter. I'm not telling you
how much money I have. It's none of your
business. It's none of your [ __ ]
business. This is not about, oh, what
I've got, what I don't have. I'm skint
apparently. So, there you go, bro.
Yeah. And that's it, bro. Like at the
end of the [ __ ] day, it doesn't
matter what I have and what I don't
have, you know? That's not what this channel's
about. You people need to focus on your
own [ __ ] lives, you know, instead of
stalking other people and not and trying
to get into other people's business. And
you don't even know anything. It doesn't
matter what I have and what I don't have, you
know? [ __ ] all, man. Just chilling,
waiting for the football. What's the
time? It's almost 5 already.
Damn. This is not a money channel. This
is a gambling
channel. Yeah. So, there's gambling
content on my
channel. Yeah. And it's my And I don't
have to answer your questions. Yeah. And
I don't have to answer your
questions. You can do. Yeah. No problem.
But I don't have to answer your questions. So
yeah. Um I don't do gambling live. I do
videos on my old channel. I used to show
money. Yeah. I don't show these people
nothing no more.
guys. Cuz um cuz what happens with these
people is it's all part of you remember
I said earlier they've got autism and
they always repeat themselves asking
people show money, show money, show
money, show money and they always want
to see money cuz it's part of their
autism. Like Jamie Thompson, Sean, you
know, all of these people with autism
and then what happens is you show them
money and then they all run away and
then don't show you nothing. So that's
why I don't do it no more because they
ask you to show them out, right? Let's
say for example, you show them
£2,000. You show them £2,000, they all
run away and can't show you nothing. So
there's literally no point in showing
these people nothing. Um I No, no. To be
fair, I did say when somebody shows me
12 grand, I will play the money game
again. So the most money I ever showed was six
grand. Um, and I'm waiting for somebody
to show me 12 grand and no one ever has.
So, I mean, I'm I think I'm winning so
far. Maybe Mr. B has beat me, but that's
the only one. So, until someone shows me 12 grand,
um, I'm will never participate in ever
again. So, that's
it. That's it,
lad. And they tried to get people's
benefits stopped and all of that kind of
[ __ ] as well. They're proper weird
jealous people, bro. That's another
thing. Yeah. So, yeah. I would never
show these people nothing. I mean,
technically, I've shown them money, haven't
I? What's it like awaiting the baiff
daily? I wouldn't know because that's
not me that wrote that. So, I wouldn't
know, mate. I pay my rent every
month. So, I I wouldn't actually know
because that wasn't me that posted it.
So, couldn't tell you, mate. Anyways, I
think I think 12k I'm really looking for
the others person to have cash lying
around. Yeah. Well, go withdraw it then.
No one said you had 12 grand lying
around. No one said you had 12 grand
lying around. I never ever said that
anyone had 12 grand lying around, but
you could technically go to the bank and get it,
Tanya. You can go to the bank and get
it, can you not? So, there you go. So yeah,
man. I mean, technically you could 50, isn't it?
So, hey, notorious, I just got a
[ __ ] from an
escort. It's good, man. It's good fun, eh?
It was good fun, bro. I don't know
football. I was waiting for the football
bet to win, but yeah, I couldn't wait,
so just went to uh escort. See, they
always wonder, why don't you want to
[ __ ] Why don't you want to
[ __ ] Oh, come on. Let's [ __ ] I don't
want to [ __ ] Cuz a lot of people don't
like giving [ __ ] but when they do
it, they're paid to do it, but they
don't like doing it cuz there's nothing
in it for
them. Nothing's in it for them. You see?
So that's why they want to [ __ ] because
when they [ __ ] yeah, you're paying
them, but at least they get
something. It's nothing to do with me,
mate. It's just a little It's just a
attempt to try to get my attention.
That's nothing to do with me. I don't
post on Reddit. I private message people
on Reddit. And when I do, well, the rare
time I do post on Reddit, it's not that
subreddit anymore because of these stalkers.
So I would never go
bored. So that's got nothing to do with
me, bro. The Instagram
is The Instagram is Yeah. Defo [ __ ]
stalking that woman in Manchester.
[ __ ] weirdos. But that's about
it. Yeah, I have the Yeah, I've got to
do certain things cuz the stalk is
notorious. I can't post on Reddit.
Certain subreddits I can't post because
they find me. Instagram. I can't add women on
Instagram. That one was a one-off. That
wasn't from an approach because these
stalkers. So, every single time I I meet
someone, it has to be they give me their
WhatsApp or their Snapchat. Normally,
it's WhatsApp cuz WhatsApp's
encrypted. So, WhatsApp's encrypted,
right? So, they can't find me um on
obviously WhatsApp. So, when I'm
speaking to a woman on WhatsApp, that's
it. But I can't do Instagram because
they stalk me. I can't do certain things
on Reddit because they stalk me. So
yeah, but that post that definitely definitely wasn't
me. But I'm saying they do they do stalk
me. All right. It's Marcus
Samson. He can't get it up. Okay.
Bye-bye. So yeah, they all talk about
me, bro. They're obsessed with
me. Oh, notorious. They're obsessed with me,
lad. Obsessed with me. I've got I've got
four or five people that's obsessed with
me. Who is this person? Uh he's just
some [ __ ] idiot from Hackne.
Oh, I'm [ __ ] naked.
Me. Why am I so
tired? I'd catch you early as
well. But yeah, I don't really go out
and do the approaches anymore.
Notorious. I'll do it again. Oh yeah,
that who we call him Peter Griffin. We
call him Peter Griffin. Don't believe
Peter Griffin that says that he's got a
wife and this. He doesn't. He has
nothing in his life but obsessing over
me on YouTube. I have something he don't
have. Any plans for the summer? No. I've
got something he don't have. Don't know
what it is, but it's something that he
doesn't have. That's why he sits on
YouTube all day stalking
me. He does not have no wife. He does
not have no kids. He does not have no
money. Don't listen to anything that he
says. He was on Reddit trying to stalk
me all [ __ ] night
yesterday. Yeah, being homeless. Yeah,
I'll never be
homeless. But anyways,
yeah, they all obsess over me. All of
them obsess over
me. Yeah. Hey, sorry. I'll go live, bro.
At some point when I'm in a bar or club
or something, I'll hit the Wi-Fi on.
Yeah, I'll hit the Wi-Fi on,
bro. They have
nothing. They have nothing,
mate. You can't even go back to my
mom's. You don't even know where I am,
mate. Anyways, bye-bye now, you little
weirdo. I can go where I want, whenever
the [ __ ] I want, you little [ __ ] mong.
I've been to my mom several
times. Obsessed with me, bro. They're
very, very obsessed with
me. Um, why? I think it's because
they're jealous of me. I think this
Jamie Thompson, this nons legs, they're
they're jealous of me. This is what I
was thinking earlier when I was eating
um KFC is that Monty don't get stalked
like this. Timmy doesn't get stalked
like this. I get stalked like this. And
the only reason I get stalked like this
is because I'm better than them in every
way. I've got a life. I've got
confidence. You know, I get more money
than them. I'm better looking than them.
No matter what they say, they don't like
it. They don't like the fact that they
look like Peter Griffin and they're sat
indoors all day, every day, and they
can't leave. They're jealous of me. It
took me a long, long time to realize
this, to realize this. And I was saying
this to my mom as well, like there's
people on here that react and stuff
like, and I get why people do it, but
what I was trying to say to my mom is
that even when you don't react to these
people, they still won't leave you
alone. They will never ever leave you
alone because they're jealous of you.
You have something they don't have else
that they would leave you alone. But
they can't leave you alone. They're on
YouTube every single day being jealous
of you. Every [ __ ] and day. So think
about it like look at Jamie Thompson and
me. Look, I'm not fat. I'm not ugly. I
have got more money than them. I live in
a better city than them. I can go out
and do whatever I want. So it's mad.
So that's why it's it's because they're
jealous. Obviously they're jealous, bro.
Cuz they would just move on with their
lives, but they can't. They're obsessed with me.
So, I mean,
yeah. That's it.
No, there is li and here's the thing.
Yeah. You need to stop moaning about
women on this YouTube because it's
giving these people content as well.
Like, you know what you need to do to
piss these people off? Go get your hair
done. Go dress up. Go and space some
that that that Savage on you. Go to a
[ __ ] bar and be like Sean's anxiety.
Can never do this. And then just start
chatting up some women. That's what you
need to do. This is not the place to
rant for these little weirdos. You know,
I've noticed that as well. and be like
Sean's anxiety could never and have a
good and have a good laugh with these
women as well. That's what you also need
to do cuz we all know a certain little
virgin doesn't like it when you meet new
women because he's never been laid and
he's still indeed a virgin. Like you get
the point. I've got a nice turtleneck
that was bought for
Christmas. I was There's a nice
turtleneck that I was bought for
Christmas. Um Charlie Yeah, I got a nice
turtleneck for Christmas. I've still not
worn it yet. Go out with that. getting
your hair done, getting your beard done,
being like Sean can never ever do this.
Never. And laugh your little head off.
It'd be funny, bro. It'd be actually
funny. It'd be good, man. You should do
content like that. Maybe go to the gym or
something. Yeah. Go to the gym and just
piss these people
off, you know? That's what you need to
do. You need to do things that that piss these people
off, you know? I think you need to do
that. Not [ __ ]
moan cuz then they get ammo and then
they think their life is better, but
their life is not actually
better. Yeah, they will always stalk us,
mate. We live in their head. Unless
these people die or they go to prison,
they will never stop. Unless they're
unless they're dead or in prison, they
will never stop. It's like what Charlie
said. They will never ever stop. So, you
might as well embrace it. You might as
Yeah, they want you depressed, bro.
Like, but but these people will never
make me depressed. They never ruin They
never ever affect my life. Like,
literally, they really don't. Like, I affect their
life. Yeah, I'm going to I'm going to
I'm going to watch the Yeah, I am going
to watch I am going to wear the jumper
when I go out. When I When I go out, I'm
definitely definitely definitely
definitely going to wear the jumper. And
I'm going to wear the Stony as well. And
I'm going to wear the [ __ ]
Stony. So, yeah. Uh, my old nonsense.
Yeah, exactly. But these people will
never ever stop. These people will never
ever stop. Like look, he's even stalked
the [ __ ] woman from [ __ ]
Manchester. How weird is that? Stalking
the [ __ ] that woman from
Manchester. And he's trying to say,
right, he's trying to say that he's
going to call the police from me. Bro, I
would love the police to come to where I
live, but that's never going to happen
cuz you don't know where I live. And I
would love the police I actually would
love the police to come here because
then I could actually show them the
whole channel of what these people have
been doing for years and years and years
and years and years non-stop. You know
what I'm saying? And that's it. You
know? Yeah. And maybe that Jamie
Thompson as well. Maybe that Jamie
Thompson. Maybe Jamie Thompson too.
Yeah. Yeah. Cuz you got to understand
people like Jamie Thompson, Sean,
they've got nothing. Fat, ugly,
toothless virgins, they've got nothing.
[ __ ] all in their lives. And that's why
they come at it and try to make other
people feel the way they
do. You know, as much as it's hard to be
positive, even after all the bad
experiences, we have to be, bro. It will
piss them off. It will piss them off.
Believe you me in what I'm saying, bro.
It will piss them off. If you want to be
negative, be negative on a [ __ ] other
channel. Not for these little mongos.
Trust me, bro. I know how to w I know
how to wind these people up, you know?
Like, but it's weird being on a phone
call to that one in Manchester for 1
hour. Like, what info was you trying to
get? She doesn't know
me. Like, she literally doesn't [ __ ] know
me. Yeah, man. I know. Like she
literally doesn't even know me. She's
never met me. So what what can she say?
That I said I wanted to meet you and
that you was my type. Oh well. Like she
doesn't even know me. She hasn't even
met me. [ __ ] hell. Weirdo, man.
Weirdo. He needs
incarcerating. He needs section and
being put in prison. Somebody with that
deeply that deep amount of autism. They
need to be locked up. They need to be
locked up. I'm not even joking, bro.
They need to be locked up. It's bad,
bro. It's actually bad. I was telling my
mom about this. It's like they find ways
to stalk you. It's not like you come on
YouTube and you put your whole life on
YouTube and then they do things to piss
you off. Nah, no, no, no, no. They will
try to find you on Instagram. They will
try to find you on Reddit. It's autism.
It is literally autism. And that's and
that's why they that's why that's
why they call other people autistic
because they're autistic themselves. And
I said to my mom, you should tell these
primary schools and secondary schools
that when they're accused when they're
trying to diagnose these children with
autism, you need to show them Sha and
Jamie Thompson and and and Lord J as
well. Mate, I am almost sure now I don't
have autism. I used to think, yeah, h
maybe there's a 5% chance that I might
have some form of
autism. No way. I know what autism is
now. I know what autism is now. And
where I've come across so many people
with it, Virgin Legs, Peter Griffin, LJ,
some of the people on here, you
definitely don't have
autism. You definitely definitely
autism. Cuz put yourself in their shoes.
If somebody some woman come on YouTube
that you loved or you liked, would you
stalk them every day and make videos on
them? No, you wouldn't. It's autism.
That's what I'm saying to you, bro. It
is autism. It actually is. Sorry, but it
it actually is autism.
So, yeah, it
is. No, I don't. If I don't like
someone, I don't like them. It's like
that KSI. I don't really like him. I
used to like him, but I don't like him
anymore. You don't see me [ __ ] you
know what I'm saying? Saying, "Oh, [ __ ]
you." Yeah. You know what I'm saying?
And it's a hint of gayness. It's more
than a hint of gayness. It's more than I
don't know if it's they either I said to
my mom, it's like they either want your
anus, they want to be you, or they're jealous of
you. I think they're jealous of you and
they they want to [ __ ] you. That's what
I think it is. I think they're jealous
of you and they want to [ __ ]
you. That's what I That's what I think it
is. Cuz even when I was obsessed with
that Morgan, these people are 100 times
more obsessed with me. These people are
100 times obsessed with me than I was
with that [ __ ] And I actually met them
and [ __ ] them. So think about it, bro.
Actually think about the level of autism. Yeah.
Yeah, but he has never ruined a
relationship. Think about it. He's never
ruined a relationship cuz Sig I [ __ ]
off. Morgan went back to America. This
person in Manchester was a [ __ ]
Anyways, so he will never ever. And I'll
prove it as well, bro. I'll prove it
when I go out again. I'm going to go
live and I'm going to chop up some women
and I'm going to get some numbers. Watch
when I get a new phone as well, but I'm
going to rub it in their face. I'm going
to rub it in their [ __ ] face as well.
Yeah. I will rub it in their face as well,
lad. Well, I don't find it funny,
Charlie. I find it weird. I find it
weird. I don't think they don't affect
anyone's life. They don't bother no one.
They don't [ __ ] with you
psychologically. It's what they do is
unbelievably weird. That's That's what
it is. What they do is unbelievably
weird. That's the point I'm actually trying to
make. Unbelievably [ __ ] weird. So,
yeah. Don't know when we'll be out
again, but it'll be soon. So
yeah, hopefully. Yeah, it's a double
both teams to score.
So yeah, hopefully, bro.
Hopefully double both teams to score.
Hope it wins.
Eh, a double. Both teams to score.
Yay. It's only one
bet. But yeah, we need to start doing
different things on this channel,
bro. You know, but I know if I PM people
on Reddit that Jamie Thompson can't
stalk me. See, they don't know who
you're private messaging.
They're actual stalkers, bro. They're actual actual
stalkers. You know, you think you know
where people live, but you don't know
where people live. And if you do know
where people live, why don't you come
and when you actually knock on the door
and you'll realize that no one's
there. Uh not county versus Colchester
and Markhamm versus Doncaster
Rovers. What do you reckon the chances?
E40 returns 122.
What do you think,
bro? What was that burning,
lad? Don't it smell like burn [ __ ] in
it? That one was a good one, isn't it?
80 pound return.
2 [ __ ] How much was it?
270. That was a good return from 80
quid, wasn't it,
boss? Took me like [ __ ] eight
attempts. Yeah, I don't play Frankie or
roulette anymore, obviously.
Duh. We need to bring it back to old
school Peter Belly Charlie. Football bets, the
gym, toddling off to new places. Yeah,
you need to do that kind of [ __ ] and
just ignore these
weirdos. You know what I'm
saying? And just ignore these [ __ ]
weirdos on here. As hard as it is to
stay positive with all these bad
experiences, but what else can you do, man? You
know, what else can you actually
do? Nothing, bro. You know what I'm saying?
That's where we're
at. You miss old school Peter Belly, don't
you? Going to Wales unannounced. Do you
remember that time I went to Wales unannounced,
Charlie? Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro. You
remember when I went to Wales
unannounced? [ __ ] crazy [ __ ] was I,
mate? I was a crazy [ __ ] back
then. You know, with a 9 duffel bag,
mate. I kissed three people that night
as well. I think it was three people or
two people. I [ __ ] smashed it,
bro. Sure it was three. No, I'm sure it
was three. I'm sure it was
three. Maybe it was two. I remember I
smashed it the first time I went to
Wales. You know what I'm [Music]
saying? Nope. Don't [ __ ]
Yeah, I met him years ago. I didn't plan
to meet him, but he just tagged
along. I reckon she smells like Bo. [Music]
Yeah. You know what? I used to do these
football bets all the time and I
remember I won one every week for a
month. Maybe I think it was three times
in a row. So, I done it every Saturday
and I won three in a row. They're hard to win,
that nowadays. Yeah, he was crap. Yeah,
clapping. Yeah, he's [ __ ] embarrassing, bro. Yeah. Yeah.
He claps. He He rubs his hands and claps
the back of his [ __ ]
head. [ __ ] hell, bro. Hopefully it
warms up when I go drinking again, you
know. Yeah, he's embarrassing, bro. You
wouldn't want to meet him. But his
autism is not as bad as Nods Legs. Nah,
no, no, no, no, no, no. Timmy is just
obsessed with like gambling, but I think
he's got more than
autism. And I think Sean's autism is worse than his
Yeah. He's so jealous that I got with
that Morgan. Is it?
He's so jealous that I got with Izzy.
He's so jealous. So jealous. It's a
disease. It's like what my mom said,
jealousy is a
disease. So, let me tell you right now.
Yeah. So, you're not jealous. Okay. So,
it might sounds like it might sound like
I'm waffling. Yeah. Okay. Well, if if you're not
jealous, if you're not jealous, never
make another community post about me ever
again. Exactly. But you can't do that, can you?
So, so you like my daughter, do
you? You like my daughter, do [Music]
you? I didn't really apply there, bro. I
was taking a piss.
I got that from Ant-Man cuz he said he
applied for a job in
Morrison's. Why is it so cold today,
bro? [ __ ] hell. Freeze him. [Music]
Yeah, I was only taking a
piss. So, how is your night going, Antman? Boyfriend [Music] boyfriend. Boyfriend, bro.
an escort addiction. I spent about £400
last month for an
escort. It's a serious serious
addiction. I don't think you
understand. Serious addiction,
eh? You think it's just gambling about
what money goes on? No.
It's like drinking, gambling,
escorts, [ __ ] goes on everything,
bro. Yeah, I would give it a Well, I
me. Yeah, you need sex,
but it's mad, is it?
Like, it shouldn't have to be that way,
but it is that way.
I don't know. You have
to cuz it's very unlikely you're going
to meet someone in this country in it.
So the only thing you can really do is use
escorts. I mean I could go out
approaching today if I wanted to or this
week but I just can't be bothered about
hearing the make believe boyfriends. It's annoying
bro. It's just annoying.
gets boring after a while, bro. I can't
be bothered dealing with them, you know?
Be different if it was a bit warmer
outside. I can't believe offering money
didn't work, Charlie. I actually thought
offering money would have worked,
Charlie. I actually
thought, yeah, it does. It actually
does. These women don't understand. And
there's like, "Oh, you can't give up at
27." No, no, no, no. Like, they don't
really understand, do
they? They just don't
understand. They really, really don't
understand. This woman was trying to say to me
how one um how it dating is easier
nowadays because of social media. Like,
no, it [ __ ] is not. Hello, P. I had a
vision from the aliens.
Um, it's not a very good one, but you
need to know this. I've got I've got
I've got a question um to me. Yes, I'll
answer your question. I need to get this
vision out. I've had contacts from Pluto
um from the uh Plutoans. They said to me
that you're never going to get laid or
get a girlfriend ever again. Oh, really?
Yes. Timmy, what Timmy, what uh what
county is Manchester in? Lanasher.
No, it's not. You're wrong again. Yes,
it is. Yes, it is. PJ, isn't it? No, it
isn't. It's West Midlands. Okay,
PJ again. Okay, then. Okay, let me ask
you a question then. Where's Sketch
Nest? Where's Skagg Nest? Um, it's in
London. It's in Lancash. It's in Lancasher.
No, it's London. It's in Lasher. You
really Ask me another one. Okay, I need
to I've had another vision. No, ask me
another question. All these visions
negative about you, PJ. The aliens have
said that you're going to blow all your
incapacity benefit when you get paid.
Yeah, I don't like it. No, no, no. The
vision is you'll be you'll be eating another
Let me ask you a question. Why have we
never seen you in Manchester? Why would
I want to go to Manchester? Cuz you
travel to Gamble, so why would you go
there? But why would I want to go to
Manchester? Can you answer that
question? Because you go everywhere
else, you say. You know, I don't like
Manchester, so why am I going to go
there? I like Liverpool. I'm team
Scalers. Well, I've never seen you there
either. Well, I've been to Liverpool
loads of times, delay. Not on YouTube.
You haven't? Not on YouTube. Maybe not
on YouTube, but I always go to
Liverpool. I Where are you now? On the
toilets. No, but like what what location?
I'm not really on the toilets. What am I
doing now? You really don't want to
know. Well, tell us. Use your imagination.
Having a wank? No, I'm having sex with
my woman right now. Oh, so what happened
with that 52y old? Nah, it didn't really
last, did it? She was a hit. Huh? Oh,
mate. Yes. Yes. Cindy's loving it. No.
Why didn't it last? Go on. Well, you
know me, PJ. Wherever I lay my hat,
that's my home.
Timmy, Timmy, you're a typical virgin.
No, the aliens said to me that I'll
never be a virgin. Only you're a virgin.
No, you're the aliens have said I've
just had more content, more content.
Sorry, more communication from the
aliens. Do you know what they said?
They said you're going to die by Monday.
Oh, really? By who? Yeah. They said
by Pat L mustard.
Really? Timmy. Yeah.
So, Timmy, what
what does Liverpool come under? Oh, use
your initiative. Mercy side. Okay. What about leads?
Pardon? What about leads? Oh, Yorkshire.
Mhm. How do you know these things,
Timothy? Cuz I travel around this
country, PJ, and I know the UK at the
back of my hand. So do I, Timothy.
Okay, then I'll ask. I've been to I've
been to quite a few places. Where's
Portsmouth? What count is Portsmouth?
That's it. It's not. It's Hampshire. You
ficker. No, it isn't.
Oh, yeah. I remember. I I remember that.
Hey, Timmy. Do you remember that when
you was in Nottingham? Yeah. And these
lads pointed the picture. This man right
here, Pedo. I was dead. Yeah, but they
were scared of me and Money. Mike, they
didn't want to go outside. They were
angry and apologized after that to
Peter. This man right here.
Peter, I don't care. I'm a wind up
Martian, but if they ever want to go, I
always dance. Sorry. Do you remember
when I touched some boobies in Nottingham?
What the [ __ ] are you on about? Are you
going to unblock me, PJ? Are you going
to keep Okay. Okay, Timmy. Do you want
to go to Rock City in uh Birmingham? No.
You would look very odd. You'd be the
only old one there. You know what? I
don't do nightclubs anymore. I just do
traditional boozers, lad. No, I think me
and you would do good in a nightclub.
Okay. I'm going to ask you a question as
you want to talk about general
knowledge. What county is Derby in? Uh
what count? Uh East Midlands. No, that's
not a county. What actual county is it
in? Uh Darishia. Oh, well done. I'll
give you that one. What county is
Nottingham in? Nottingham share. Oh,
well done. You're getting a bit ahead.
Okay. What county is Leicester in?
Uh, is Leicester?
Well done. You're not as thick as
Mongol. Last question. Last
question. If you don't get if you don't
get if you don't get this one, I'll be
I'm going to call you thick. What what
county is Carl in?
Uh, [ __ ] knows. Um, um, Thumblandshire,
not Flandshire. Um, I know it is a
Fland. Okay, ask me more counties. I'll
get it. Go on. Yes, it is Fderland. I am
right. Yes. Okay, go on. Okay, I'll ask
you one more. What county is Bristol in?
Um, Farmerland. Northeast Somerset.
Okay. I've got Okay. What county is
Western Super Mar in? What county is
Brighton in? What county is Brighton in?
Oh, that's easy. That's Dorset. No, it
isn't. Yes, it is. No, it isn't. Did you
say Brighton or did you say Bournemouth?
So, okay. I apologize. I apologize. I
thought you said Bournemouth. Sorry.
Brighton. I can answer that one. It is
in Sussex. Oh, you know, Timothy. Yes. I
know everything, PJ. [Laughter]
Okay. And I'm going to ask you a
question, PJ. Where is a woman's hot spot?
Um, the gob. No, it's in the middle.
It's the centerpiece.
No, I just like [ __ ] It's the belly
button. Not really. I just like [ __ ] to me.
Anyway, before I go, Mongol because the
aliens have have asked me have actually
given me a vision. I'm a vision. They
said, "Why on earth did you send you a
picture to Kaye of you having a
blowjob?" How do you know I done that?
Because Mongol's told everyone today.
Cuz it was a love because it was a
lovely sight to me.
You can't trust Mongol with anything. He
will tell you your greatest secrets,
Peter. You should know this by now. So,
you admit that I've had a [ __ ] then?
You know what's Mongol's like? He's
triggered cuz we found out his new
address is 55 Columb Street, Mansfield.
Huh? It's 50. It's 55 Columbus Street,
Mansfield. He's moved back into that
gaff what he lived in four years ago. He
says, "We're not stupid, but it's
exactly the same house what he filmed
four years ago." Yeah, but someone sent
letters to his neighbors. Oh, that
happens all the time, PJ. Yeah, but it
never really happened to you, did it,
Monty? Timmy. Yes, you did, PJ. Do you
know what I did, PJ? My neighbors knew
who I was and I they totally ignored it.
And you know the the greatest secrets,
PJ, you don't tell nobody nothing.
That's why we end up trolling you cuz
you open your [Music]
GS. What the [ __ ] he gone? I've had a
vision. PJ's gone for a wank. Cuz he's a
virgin and he can't get sex. He can only
get a [ __ ] [ __ ]
Anyway, my work here is done. Dads,
enjoy your evenings.