out of the [ __ ] foot, [Music]
mate. Second just need to lift dip to
the L. I put my foot strap on. Oh yeah.
Second to the
L. It's nipping to the L. One second, mate.
Oh, yeah. No one really joined in the
morning, did they? Oh, is that him?
Yeah. Right. I'm just nipping to the L. One
second. How did that get lumpy like
that? No. Good for a
[ __ ] That's no good for [ __ ] mate.
Nothing worse than a
foot. I don't think there's anything
worse than a foot
ache. I can't think of anything.
of anything worse than a foot. One
second. Have a coffee today. I
think call me.
E [ __ ] school [ __ ] messing me
saying, "Oh, I'm around the area. You
should come." Nah, mate. Rather not give
you my money. I'd rather not give you my
money. My spondies. No thank you.
as a madness. [ __ ] hell. You moan
about [ __ ] men [ __ ] ghosting you.
You [ __ ] blocked me on [ __ ]
Reddit. [ __ ] man. You
know, doesn't even make sense, does it? Yeah,
bro. Some for later as
well, bro. Oh
yeah. Like a [ __ ] dog or something.
Talking to a dog. Jesus. Jesus Christ,
man. Just a nice life, you know, just
chilling under an electric
blanket, having some food cooked for
you. That's all you need, man. That's
buddy. It's all you [ __ ] need, man. [Music] Uh yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I'll be out for like 6 weeks, I
think. [ __ ] that. [ __ ] that,
bro. I might play The Simpsons here run
later. Got it downloaded.
Yeah. It's too negative. Yeah,
bro. There's a fake.
Yeah. So, you see me live on
Saturday, don't ask me if I've gone out cuz I
haven't. My mind started building up now
again as well. I'll be back to how I was
last summer. Yep. Back to how I was last
summer. I was actually reminiscing about
that just a moment. Okay. With them
sticky 50 stuck together brand new
notes. That's basically the level I'm
getting at again cuz I've not been out
for two weeks, you
see. But what happens is you get so used
to it. so used to not the [ __ ] Oh,
I can't be bothered. And then one day
you go out and it all starts again.
That's what happens. You
see, you know, watch the money
grow. And I've got that holiday as well.
So any horses in the cinema. Let me have a look.
I used to love going to to watch the Was
it? Let me have a little
look. I stitches out. Yeah. Yeah, I just saw
that. I can't believe how many of these women the
[ __ ] do that. Yo, I was saying I can't
believe how many of these women reply to
negativity. Jesus Christ. At least they
show what they're about
it. [ __ ] hell,
right? But I'm only into horrors. I'm
only into horrors, bro.
Wait, there's a hollow there. One second.
sec. Yeah, defin Bro
100%. My money's building up again now
as well cuz I've not been out for a
couple of weeks. I'm getting back to how
I was last
summer. That's how it starts, bro. You
get used to a nice
easy easy money life and then you go out
and drink again and you have anything to
do with women again and look, you're
about to square up.
It's like we're walking with a foot ache.
Eight. I'll have to look on these
uh Yeah, I do want to I don't know. I
just like the horror films, bro. I like
the goosebumps, the adrenaline rush.
That's why I only watch horrors.
There's one there. I'll have to look more into
it off this live
stream. When I'm off this live
stream. Yeah, I
think. But yeah, hope you watch my videos,
Shifty. They're pretty good, eh?
Yeah, man. We need to [ __ ]
defrost. I know what they're like. I
know what these women are like. But I
think what was pissing me off is how
they were messaging me back.
Like, yeah, obviously I messaged them
negativity and obviously they love
negativity. But I didn't think as many
would have replied in that way. I
thought they would have just replied,
but they replied back devious me and
trying to be funny and it was just
pissing me off. That's that's that's
what it was cuz obviously we know what
what they're about. Anyways, been doing
that for [ __ ] donkeys years, replying
to negative messages and ignoring nice
ones, but it's it's how many and what
they were replying
with. Good. Good. You just not just
should just not deal with them. There's
one right now. I'm in your area. It's an
escort, bro. Even if she even if she
offered it for free.
Um, I still probably wouldn't even meet
her. I'm anti-women. I think they've
turned me asexual, bro. Mothers, I think
they've actually like turned me asexual.
Seriously. And it's not like they messaged
back just they were messaged back like
trying to take the piss and it was it
was winding me up. right? They got
nothing to say when someone's uh
positive, right? But then when you're
negative, they're fast enough to come with a
message. This is exactly what I'm
talking about, bro. It just pisses me off. So
yeah, it's annoying, bro. It's how they
was what they reply with about send news
like they were trying to take the piss.
But yeah, I'm basically asexual now
pretty much. Yeah, I could go up I could
go up the road and and bang a [ __ ]
right now if I wanted to. Can't be
bothered. Even if she offered it for
free, can't be bothered. I'd rather wait
here and have my [ __ ] food cooked for
me and play some Simpsons
later. I don't give a [ __ ] though. I
You still want me to go Blackpool
Greezy? What day is it today? Could go Saturday,
but go overnight sort of thing. I could
go. Would there be any point though or
if the weather's [ __ ] The weather might
be [ __ ] That's another thing. It's
risky. The weather could be [ __ ]
Yeah, the weather could be
uh [ __ ] You go all that way still going
to say you got boyfriends. Yeah.
Um so when are you watching this ditch
film? You watching it soon? Yeah.
Oh, I love horror films. [ __ ]
hell. No, curry, man. Curry, I'm having
a curry cook for me.
Well, I'll have to uh I'll have to
[ __ ] watch I'll have to watch these
trailers when when I'm off the live
stream. Yeah. Go to Blackpool for
Greasy. Eh, go to Blackpool for good old Greasy. Imagine
that. Greasy would love the content.
[ __ ] cold weather,
eh? You're you're also invited to the
barbecue on Thursday, Grezy. It's an open
invitation. You say you don't want to
go, but mate, when you when you see the
meat on the barbecue, you're going to
want to go, man. You're going to want to [ __ ]
go. Doesn't matter who's cooking for me,
bro. People are cooking for me, though. That's it.
I was just reminiscing cactus how last
year I had all them 50 pound notes stuck
together going into a shopping mall but
I still have money now I still have
loads of money now so but it's still
like I don't know why I was thinking of
it not it's not so much missing missing
the days because I've still got money I
can still do what I want but I don't
know it was
just there those were the days man you
know walking into the casino hitting
that 11 I would never forget man that
Wednesday. I will never forget that
Wednesday, bro. I remember it for the
[ __ ] rest of my life.
So, just hitting that 11 with a
multiplier. [ __ ] hell. I didn't even
plan I didn't even want to go out
Wednesday. My army mate was like, "We
should go for a drink." I was like,
"I can't be bothered." Then he and at
the end of the day, we was chatting up
these Canadians. I think we got two
numbers. We was on our way back. I was
like, "Do you want to come casino? Come
casino with me." He said, "Nah, man.
Just going to go home." I said, "Suit
yourself." Went in with 150. [ __ ]
walked out with [ __ ] £4,000 in
cash. I I was the I was the ones to get
I was the one to get the first [ __ ]
50s, you know? I've still got a lot of
money. I've still got a lot of money.
I've still got a lot of money. I can
still do what I want,
but not as much as that. Maybe
like 80% there. So, I've still got
money, but it's like I don't
know. It was I don't know. It was No, I
missed them times because I was
constantly winning, going out, winning,
constantly winning. I still have money,
but it's I don't know. I think it was
the lifestyle as well. Going out
It was going out, winning, spending,
going out the next week, winning it
back, winning. Like that's I missed that
lifestyle, you know? It was a good man. You
know, I'm surprised I never done my
bollocks, to be
honest. I have nothing. What do you mean
I've got nothing? I'm showing money all the
time. What do you mean I have
nothing? What do you mean I have
nothing? I showed money the other
day and as usual, you show me
nothing. I have nothing. What could you
possibly know what I
have? What could you possibly know what I
have? No, I'll never gamble again. I
don't think. No, I'll never gamble again.
No. Yeah. I'm surprised I never done my bollocks
in. Surprised I never ever done my
bollocks in in that period to be
honest. Even when I want to grind, I
still had money left. So yeah. No, I'm not gambling,
bro. I won't gamble. I don't think I'd
ever gamble again to be
honest. If I was to gamble, it'd have to
be online roulette. But I'm not doing
it. I'm not doing it. I'm not doing it.
I ain't gambled for [ __ ] ages now.
I'm not doing it,
bro. The amount of time and money you
waste, [ __ ] that, bro. You already never
getting that back. So, no, I'm not doing
it. I ain't doing
it. But yeah, last summer I was the best,
man. Ball going out every Thursday,
winning, cleaning them up. I've still
got it to do, but it's not going to be
as rapid as that, you know.
I still got a good life. Still get
money. Still make money. Still don't have to
work. Have a gaff. Have new [ __ ] Like still good. But
yeah, it's making it sound like I have
no money when I do. I don't know. But it
was just fun because it was all new to
me, you know.
So yeah, I had like 5.7 grand in cash. I
was like, "What the [ __ ] I need to
spend some money, bro. Oh, all this
[ __ ] money. I need to spend some
money." And I took out £1,700 with me. I
just went to the shopping mall and I
think I spent about £1,200. Yeah. [ __ ]
hell. That is a madness.
But there's been times where I've gone
to a casino, I lost like 600
quid. [ __ ] hell,
bro. Yeah, it was a good life, bro. It
life. The reason I don't do it now is
cuz I'm leaving the country, you see.
So, I can't let anything jeopardize
that. I could still do this [ __ ] every
week and still have that life, but I
don't want to go out in this country
anymore. I could still live the high
life. I just don't want to go out in
this country anymore,
bro. You know, I could still do it. I
could literally still do it, but I just
don't want to [ __ ] just go out and
waste money in this country no
more, mate. I paid £250 for a [ __ ]
just because money didn't matter. Money
didn't matter, bro. So, I just spent it.
Nah, don't do that
[ __ ] Just because money didn't matter,
bro. it. I didn't give a [ __ ] in it. So
yeah, but I could I don't
know. I used to clean up them casinos.
That's the only thing I miss. I think
it's the actual winning of the money is
what I miss. It's not the money cuz I
still have money. So it's not it's not
that. It's the actual like you actually
going in there, bro. I I remember this
one time and actually taking money from them.
It was just I That's what you miss.
That's what That's what you miss. That's what it
is. Then you I remember this time I was
on this date with this person, right?
And I was I think I was 500 lb in 400
in. It was this date I went on. Yeah.
And I couldn't let it lie, bro. Like I I
went back. I remember I went back when I
dropped her off at the station. And this
is how I know dating's a waste of time
in this country cuz I've been there,
done it, wore a t-shirt, and it doesn't
pay off. And I tried to get in the front
door and he's a [ __ ] He he knew me. He
knew I weren't supposed to be there cuz
I self-excluded when I was 19. So I went
in and then uh no it's 500 in the end. I
think I was like I don't know how much
more but anyways to cut a long story
short I went I went through the other
entrance right I went through the other
entrance and I think I might have put
like 250 which I don't know how much I
put £500 in in total m I took out £1600
m to the dot mate they could have gave
you more without asking for ID you
should have saw the look on his face
because they can't take the money from
you if you're in and you won like he
he's a [ __ ] he is like he he used to
hate me, man. I used to go there and
clean up their M's rages, bro. Like, what the
[ __ ] And I actually spoke to him a
couple of months ago, you know, I was
like, "Let bygons be gut bygones." You
know, we we shook hands, but he hated
me, bro. He hated
me. You could just tell that he hated
me. He knew that one more often than
not, and he didn't like
it, you know. So, which, you know,
you're taking up I used to win so much
money in that Empire Casino. The bouncer
came out the toilet and kicked
you. Yeah. Do you remember? Yeah. Cuz he
banned me for three months. Yeah. He
banned me for three months. I remember
this. Yeah. I didn't even do anything.
There was a person I was with. He banned
me for three months. Yeah. The manager
banned me for 3 months. I still can't
believe I could never go that O'Neal
again. I do kind of miss it to be
honest, but yeah. And I was there at
five. I was like, "Okay, I'm not going
to get caught. I'm not going to get
caught." I literally walked out the
toilet as he was walking in and the [ __ ]
caught me, bro. That was [ __ ] human,
bro. But I would never be able to go
there again because the staff never
changed. The manager never changed and
about I mean technically I could go back
there, but I would just have to camp in
the toilets. I would have to actually
camp in the toilets for about 4 hours.
But yeah, that is a place I do miss
going cuz I didn't used to like it
there. But I found other
places. So yeah, but yeah, that's what
it was. It was the actual
uh momentum of the lifestyle and
actually winning the money. It was
actually the winning, not the not the
money, the winning the money. You don't
have money. So, it's like it's not like
you don't have money. It's not like you
can't go out and do it all
again. You know what I'm saying? So,
yeah, it was it was fun
times. Grand extra every week. It would
be just you just win. You would always
win. And then we can see those nine
times out of
10. Could never go back in them
again. [ __ ] hell. Don't depress me, bro. Good times.
Yeah. Whilst F can't even afford a pair of
trainers. Belly can't even afford a
[ __ ] pair of trainers.
So, and that's the thing like if you was
going to meet somebody, you would have
met someone by now. Like you said, I was
living the high life. Women have proven
to be all the same time and time and
time and time and time and time again.
Sometimes we go like two days a week,
three days a week, you
know. We used to go out a lot, mate. A
lot, you know.
So, but yeah, I've got money. I still have
money, but it's more of a case of it was
good winning the money. That's what it
was. But I just don't see the point in
gambling now cuz you're always losing in
the end. So that's why I don't do it now
cuz you're always losing in the end.
Waste of time and you just feel guilty.
That's why I stopped it. That's why I
stopped doing it. I mean, if I could
still get into the casinos, I probably
would do 150 at the end of the
night. No, I can still go in pubs.
There's loads of pubs I can go into.
There's loads of clubs I can go into.
It's only one pub I can't get
into. No, there's loads of clubs.
There's loads of pubs in London I go to.
I can get into 99% of them, you know.
Yeah. That's it. No, I can still go up,
bro. Just can't get into
O'Neals. But yeah, I probably would
gamble with like 150 or 200 pound if I
could still go in the casinos, but it
would be at the end of the night. But
there's just no point cuz you just never
win in the end. You're never stable and
you always lose in the end. So there's
no point even gambling.
Like that's why there's no
point, you know? I could do it online. I
could do it right now. You know what I'm
saying? But it just doesn't make no
sense. And it's all in euros now.
So it's all in [ __ ]
euros. And it's kind of scary like if
you look back in like 10 years thinking,
"Oh, I wasted a lot of life gambling.
Oh, I wasted a lot of money gambling."
And you never get the time
back. That had the mood swings as well.
So just no point doing it. yeah. So
yeah, be out again in 6 weeks just
before I go maybe. Yeah.
Yeah. How would my life planned out? [ __ ]
hell. I probably would have just
traveled the world to be honest. Well,
no, cuz I still live the life whilst
being on here. No, actually I kind of
thank this community to be honest. No, I
tell you what what positive come out of
this community is the amount of
traveling I done around the country.
Like even people my age haven't even done
that cuz obviously when bomb would piss
me off and so if it wasn't for people
pissing me off or you know stuff like
feeling I'd have to prove something I
probably wouldn't have done as much
traveling as I did. So that's the only
positive is I visited like lots of
places but to be honest with you it
probably wouldn't even be that different
because I just live my life on it
anyways. I live my life on it doing what
I do anyways just documenting it.
So yeah, if I didn't find this
community, I'd be with Izzy. So well
well actually saying that if I didn't
find this community, I'd be with Izzy
actually. That is a certain I can
actually say that because then Pat
Muster and all that would have been
sending her this [ __ ] So I could tell
you for nothing that if I were on
YouTube, I would have been with Izzy or
at least shagging her all the time.
So that's one thing I could definitely
say and I would have done as much traveling.
So I would have rather done the
traveling rather than keep [ __ ]
shagging her. So
yeah, maybe. Yeah, may
maybe. The worst thing I ever done was
gamble and come in this community.
That's the worst thing I ever done. I
can't stand gambling, bro. like, yeah,
there were some good times and you
should see it as the good times should
just be left in the past because the
problems that it causes, the mood
swings, the unstability, it's just not
worth it. It's just it's really really
just not even worth it. It's not even
doing. And what would make me feel
guilty is like you'd lose 150 and 200
pound and some people in your family
don't really have a lot of money. It's
the guilt. like it's the guilt like
that's that would [ __ ] with me as well
with the mood swings. So that's why I
just stopped doing it, you
know, it's the guilt and uh the mood
swings and it just it's just a waste of life. So
yeah, you always lose in the end as well. But
yeah, cuz I always said that, oh, what
would happen if I met somebody and I
wasn't on YouTube? Well, I met up Morgan
and I wasn't on YouTube and she [ __ ]
me over. So, you know what I'm saying?
So, a lot of them would have [ __ ] you over
regardless, you know, whether you was on
YouTube or you wasn't on YouTube. So, so yeah. Yeah.
them casinos. I'm sure. Yeah,
man. That's what I do on my other
channel. I do that on my other channel.
I've got some good content on my other channel. You
know, I used to travel to another
another city every week. Newcastle,
Newcastle, Birmingham, Nottingham. I
used to just go to different cities every
week. B had money. What can you sit
around all day? You know what I'm saying?
So, you know what I'm
saying? So, yeah.
That's what happened,
bro. It's good though. It Yeah, I do
have money. I still have
money. Not starving, but yeah, I miss
winning in the casino, bro. I do miss
winning in the casino, fingering
people. I think that was my best year.
But no, that the year I met Morgan was a
good year as well, cuz I don't know a
lot of fingering. But I don't think I
won as much money. But obviously I had
money. So, but I don't think I was
winning a lot of money back then. Was
I? No. I think the best year was last
year. That was the That was the killer
year. That was an absolute banger, I
think. But the year before that was
still good cuz I had a lot of dates the
year before that as
well. But I don't think I was winning as
much money. I think I was winning money,
but not as much money.
So, you literally could not go to
central London without going into a
casino, bro. It'd be very hard. Very [ __ ]
hard. Do you reckon if I went back in
like 3 years, they'd they'd remember me,
Cactus? No, I could never go in again
because even if I went in again, they
would find out. I mean, I could go to a
casino, but it'd have to be Nottingham or Blackpool.
So, I could technically
go, but it'd be risky and I'd have to go
like Nottingham or
Blackpool. And yeah, it'd be proper
dodgy and it'd be on edge all the time
in case I want money. So you could you
could do it. You went to a private one,
but um it's just not worth
it. Oh, I remember before this was last
year. I tell you what, no. I I I
actually got the last lot. No. Well, I
didn't really get doct. I think we ended
up even in the end. I remember the last
casino I went to. Yeah. Before they
stopped letting me in. I think I was
about 4 I think I was about 360 or 460
and I was down to my last 60 quid. I got it to
£1,100. Not even joking, bro. I got it to £1,100
quid. Not even joking, brother. And then
they stop letting me in cuz I didn't
realize I was bad. But yeah.
Yeah. I remember when I met that 19y old
the first time I spent about 700
quid. 700 [ __ ]
quid. Yeah. Do you know what somebody
said to me on YouTube before a cactus?
They said you're better looking than
these people. You've got a better life
than them and you've got more money than
them. And it kills them. I think they
were right in it. I think that's why a
lot of people go for it.
it and they said just leave YouTube and live your
life. Shout out Ronald Pump. There we
go. I think it's true, bro. Is it cuz
some people in here only have like 300
quid in it? They're like £300 a month.
Yeah. Pound a month, baby.
I remember that time that day I was
supposed to go to um America last
year. Do you remember the June that's
when when I won the four
grand and it was and it was like telling
me like you either go there or you don't
go there cuz obviously I was going to go
on the Thursday. I won the money on the
Wednesday. I think no I think it was the
same day actually cuz it was early hours
and it could have worked both ways last
year. It's like you either go
or you don't go, but you got all the money
back. So, I think it was basically
telling me don't do it. Even though I
tried getting the money back, I tried to
get the money back and everything, but I
tried rescheduling it cuz obviously if I
went there, then I weren't going to come
back. Like, I was going to stand my
[ __ ] ground. So, at the end of the
day, it's like a part of it was saying,
"Go. You've got more money to go with,
but then the other part of it was
saying, "Okay, just reschedule it.
Forget about the whole thing. And here
you go. You've won four grand." So, it's
like it was working both
ways. But kind of thought, bro, I'm not
going to I'm not going to come back. If
I go them
times, your whole life wasted them, bro. it
really your life would be
wasted. Yeah, I know, bro. I know.
So, that's where I was at basically. You
know what I'm saying? So, I didn't know
I didn't really know what to do. So,
yeah, you could have just went there and
not called him out, but I think it would
have still been dodgy going there around
them times to be honest with you. But
yeah, and the [ __ ] America is not a
[ __ ] It's not a [ __ ] cheap thing,
mate. You know what I'm saying?
So, it's not a cheap
thing. I still have money, but I just I
just missed my life last year,
bro. I just miss it
completely. Completely miss it. It was just so
good, you know.
But when I I noticed cactus that when
the wa dried out the women dried out. Understand
cactus. When the money dried out the women dried out. Yeah,
bro. Obviously was still making money from
the house. So
yeah. Yeah, I will, bro. I
will. But it's a good life. Like, no.
You had a good life last year. You know,
you don't need to do it again in this
country. This country is a waste of
time, waste of money. Women give you negative experiences.
So, you know what I'm saying?
Yeah, [ __ ] hell,
bro. What's that life again? It was
fun. Approach him three times a week.
Yeah. Anyone would think I've got no
[ __ ] money. By the way, I'm
talking. Offering money don't work. No,
I went out with like 300 quid offering
them money and they weren't they weren't
having none of it. I literally did it,
bro. A couple of months ago, I went on
the street even sober. Like, I don't
know where I found the courage to do it,
but I was offering them money. They
weren't having none of it,
mate. Literally, I I thought that would
have worked because a lot of people
don't have money. I generally thought
that would have worked. So, I tried it
for one day. It doesn't work. Money does
offered money doesn't
work. Trust me, I've tried it. I've literally tried
it. But I tell you what, it probably
would work eventually if you kept doing
it and doing it and doing it and doing
it. But it doesn't work,
bro. Doesn't work. I generally thought it would
work. You know that one in Liverpool
Street when she said she had a boyfriend? Yeah.
It's boyfriend. I'm I'm so glad I don't
have to hear that again for a very long
time. And they don't have boyfriends
because 80% of men are struggling and
single. So do the maths. And like I was
saying, what their boyfriends are
letting them in the nightclub 6 7:00 in
the morning [ __ ] dancing and slinging
it around whilst what what are their
boyfriends doing exactly at home
watching TV eating
popcorn? I don't think so.
So, it just doesn't add up. And I
thought I'd mention it in the video
because I'm sick of people saying, "Oh,
how do you know they've got boyfriends?
How do you know they don't have
boyfriends?" But like, use your
initiative. They talk [ __ ] Sorry. Yeah.
Yeah. So, yeah, they don't even want
one. Yeah. They want drug
dealers. They want drug
dealers that beat them by the looks of it.
So yeah, [ __ ] them anyways. Yeah,
bro. All right, Triple H
boss. You all right, boss?
I remember you and Fraser was best
mates. Yeah, I'd go to Birmingham and
help [ __ ] Monty with that bike and
Timmy, but Monty's a snake and there's
grasses on this community. So Monty's a
snake and Nat's a snake so they can [ __ ]
themselves. They're pretty much all
snakes on here to be honest except from
unworthy clock. I like unworthy clock. I
feel like he's down to earth. He stays
out the drama and you know I've met him
as well like he's actually all right.
He's you know I don't a bad word to say
about him but the rest of them like they're all
snakes. That's the thing with this
community is they are snakes. Like I've
caught that Ricky Milling thing milling
account snake me. Like he'd be coming on
here kissing my [ __ ] ass and then I'd
go on like a [ __ ] Red Star video or I
don't know a Tromino video and I'll see
this guy talking [ __ ] about
me. Yeah, I'm on a detox trip. I'm not
drinking for like five or six or six
weeks. I said I'm
done the barbecue on Thursday.
So, but yeah, that Ricky Mill, he's he's
another snake. I just said to him, if
you got something to say, say it to my
face. Simple. That's it. And uh
yeah, you still gambling, Triple
H. You still gambling,
lad? Do I reckon anyone would turn up to
the barbecue? Nope. I'm not even joking.
I'm actually having on Thursday. So, we
will see who actually turns up in
it. Nah, no one's going to turn
up. Yeah, I've quit the gambling beer.
Well, anyone It's an open
invitation. It's an open invitation.
The only person that's not allowed to
come is a woman and um Timmy because Timmy's a
troublemaker. Yeah. So Timmy's not
allowed. Everyone else is allowed. Bring your [Music]
friends. You can come in if you want.
Trip, have you been losing a lot
recently? Triple H. Yeah, I've had no
urges or nothing.
me. Yeah, I think I wasn't addicted. I
think I just used to do it. But I'm not
addicted. Obviously, you're not addicted
if you was just able to stop like that.
You know what I'm saying? One
sec. There you go,
boss. Okay with you, boss.
Hello. Yes, lad.
What are you doing? Killing, man. Chilling, bro.
You still goblin? Yeah, it's happening.
You still go? Nah. Um,
when a few weeks ago now, did you lose? Yeah.
Um, about [ __ ] 80. I think you said
Do you remember that time you said you
lost a grand? I did, didn't I?
Well, that's the most you've lost. Yeah.
Bookies in the bookies, in it.
Go on. Hello. Yeah. [Music]
The bookies yet? Um, no. I haven't been
in for a while, lad. Where where
where in the northeast do you live now?
I live in Darham still. Yeah. All right.
I'm I'm off Thailand in a few weeks. Do
you want to come?
No, I've got
Yeah, you can still go. So, yeah. Huh?
Say hello. Hannah.
Hello. Hi. You all right? Yeah. Hey yo.
Oh, I remember when I went to Newcastle,
Triple H, you all sounded like that.
Yeah. Yeah. When I went to Newcastle,
you all sounded like that.
You remember the little voice Trip H?
You used to love it in it. Yeah. Have
you been banging any Bear Clay?
No, I can't be asked with it, bro. No, I
just been chilling, bro. I haven't
really been out drinking for a couple of
weeks, mate. To be honest, what was I saying? Uh,
[ __ ] do you remember Adman?
I wasn't around when he was around. No,
but I've seen some of his videos. He's
gone. He went to Thailand three times in
a year. It's good, isn't it? He's wild, isn't he?
Oh, when he was smashing the pub up in
it. Yeah. You put that on, didn't you? Hi. Hi.
I'm Magnus. Yeah, bro. [ __ ] hell.
You're not at work.
Sorry. You know, you know how work? No.
No. I've had a week off, mate. I'm back tomorrow.
Okay. Nice, bro. Can't be ass, man. [ __ ] working.
Yeah, man. And I've not had to work for
a few years. I'm drinking sat me lad.
Yeah, I love Guinness, man. I love
Guinness, man. I like Guinness. He gets
you [ __ ] up, though. Yeah. Like you
could [ __ ] I I just stick to I just
stick to beer now because if I get on
the spirits, bro, I'm like [ __ ] for
like three days, bro. Like with anxiety
and [ __ ] That's why I just stick to the
beer. I try to anyways. It's You know
what I mean? She drinks gin. Yeah.
Do you go do you go out and drink? Where
you going? Newcastle.
Um not Dham normally, but if I go I've
been Newcastle, but
um have you been?
Uh not recently. No, I went to Darham
about a couple of months ago.
Yeah, Middles were [ __ ] bro. Do you
remember when I went and I done the
videos? [ __ ] on it.
Hello. Hello. Can you hear me? Yeah.
Yeah. Did you got any? No, I went I went
to Middlesbrough is a [ __ ] bro. Yeah,
it is a shy [ __ ] It is It is bad burl
like I Every other house is boarded up,
bro. And there's crackers on the street
and [ __ ] [ __ ] it is rough like what
what do you remember them? Do you
remember? Oh, do you remember? Is Isabelle Eldridge?
That was a love of your life, lad. No,
but do you remember do you remember do
you remember the account? Yeah, we that
Yeah, it's a sad it.
They still going about your sheets now.
Yeah. [ __ ] me, bro.
The burger. Yeah. You remember your Do
you remember the burger trip?
Sorry, lad. Yeah. Yeah. Remember the
[ __ ] Yeah. They They used to pick on
you over it, didn't they? Yeah. Cuz I
idiot. My girlfriend's asking why.
Why? Why did they pick on me? Oh,
because I I turned the camera on. They
had [ __ ] I had like a half eaten
burger on on the floor. They would they
would they wouldn't shut up about it.
They wouldn't let it go. No used to do
that. Was that banger?
Yeah. Yeah. They all used to do it
though to be fair. Trevor used to do it.
Like off a bag.
Oh, you know that Trevor Dawson? You
know that Trevor Dawson? He's an old man
for middles, bro. Is it?
I don't mind Trevor, actually. He's all
right. He's He's an old He's an old man
for middles, bro. Is it? Yeah, I think
he is. He's getting on. Yeah.
Of course, he knows him, doesn't he?
Yeah. Yeah. All that m that that Mike
and Timmy's going after Monty, is it?
Ah, yeah. Yeah. I think it's cuz uh I
think um I feel I still think Mike's
like snapped me like maybe. Yeah,
obviously, bro. Well, obviously because
why you why would you randomly go for
Monty now all of a sudden? Of course, it's that
obviously it's that, bro. [ __ ] hell.
Some madness, lad. Yeah, he he he loves
him, bro. [ __ ] Remember that when he
used to say that? We've tried him, but
he just won't get off that.
Yeah. Yeah. Who? Who? Who? [ __ ] Yeah.
Belly. He got nicked. Yeah. He got all
these devices and he still wouldn't get off YouTube.
Yeah. That Yeah, that fell. Yeah, he
never ever go off that fell. No, he
bought a new device to come running
it. Madness, bro.
Madness. You should have met me when I
come to Newcastle, matey.
Next time you rock up, I will. Yeah, but
I don't think I'm ever going to go
again. I'm in it. It's fun.
It's fun. It for you. It was like It's
good good track life. You remember the
first time I went there and I got
nicked. Do you
remember? H You live near West Ham
Stadium, don't you? like not far away
from there. Yeah. 10 minutes walking. 10
minutes walking, bro. Yeah. I was going
to show a tour of it the other day, bro. Yeah. Yeah.
Do you know West Ham?
West. You live like little 10 minutes
from there. Walk, bro. Yeah.
Oh, my lad. Do you like West Ham?
Not really. No. Well, they're quite
[ __ ] aren't they?
Yeah. What do you think of that Tim
Eldridge then? That mic's gotten bad on
the buzz and he they need to get off
YouTube is it? They went to Phil Monty
man in the What happened there? What was
all that over? I think that's me. It's
It's over Natalie G in it. I'm
guessing it. Yeah. Is this just you
watching? Just does. But there's a few
people watching and it
not really just goes what he does. He
goes live on YouTube and then [ __ ]
he's got a lot of haters. So they all
just watching and then look I'll show you look
yeah I'll tell you when he's watching
how many's watching I can't remember all
the comments like you've got people like
Jack and [ __ ] Brit Bogz the
burger the mother
this is what these people do you still
do you still use PlayStation no
I remember I remember when I used to
speak to you yeah you used to go out
drinking every week and like approaching
in it like talking to birds Did you ever?
Yeah. When you were single? Like when
you were single? Remember? Yeah. Years
ago, when I Yeah. Years ago, but
obviously you never used to get [ __ ]
with it. I never get you used to getting
out. No. Yeah. I Yeah, we never I Yeah.
What do they used to say? They had boyfriends.
I don't know. I was always up me.
Are you still on it? Are you still on
the sniff? Now and again like Yeah. Huh?
Now and again. Really? [ __ ] hell,
bro. I've not done it since I met
Fraser, you know. That was like three
years ago. Didn't you get on it with
Mike and them before? Yeah, but that was
before. Yeah, that was before it. They
said you went paranoid in that. Not at
all, bro. I went paranoid. That doesn't
even make sense. What the [ __ ]
Why did the dude just Why did the dude
just make lies up? They just make up
stuff. Timmy tried saying he chased me
around the boring. He's an idiot, bro.
Okay. Chased me around the ball ring,
bro. But do you remember Fraser?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Did you remember when
dad on the video he was laughing at that it?
Yeah. He tried, didn't he try to set you
up or something? Yeah. What happened
there? That would have been That would
have been That would have been a vicious
attack. You know what that means? Yeah.
Like a really nasty attack.
Do you know what these people do on
here? Bro, you shouldn't laugh yet
because LT was going to kill me on on on
YouTube. Is it insane? I'm telling the
funny you think it's funny. You know
what these people do on here? I'm
telling you what they do. He was
speaking to a girl called Isabelle.
Isabelle, what was her second name?
Chambers or something, right? So these
people made accounts in their name and
started messaging them like made fake
accounts. Made made fake Yeah. made fake
on YouTube there, right? And like you
used to message him. Is that weird or
not? That's [ __ ]
m How do you know what fishes means
though? What's that? How do you know
what fishes means? Fish means like
nasty. Yeah. Attacking it. Yeah. Could
you imagine that though? Triple H's like
getting killed over YouTube. People
coming to your funeral and it was over
YouTube. Imagine that.
This is what these people do.
Yeah. Imagine that though. No, mate. I
jump back in. I put my phone down. I
jump back in 20 minutes. Yeah, man.
Oh [ __ ] This needs a [ __ ] defrost,
bro. [ __ ] loadable.
Word of all No.
Good old northeast accent. I've not
heard a northeast accent for quite a
while. You know, they all sound like
that up there. You and your silly little
voice. Triple H, why didn't you meet me
when I came to uh Newcastle?
I've been there three times, you know. Yeah. Fishes [Laughter]
attack. I can't take this guy
serious. Oh man, you know what he's
missing? Sounds like this. She sounds
like them them in Newcastle who I used
to approach, man. [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? [ __ ]
man. How do we miss it a little bit,
bro? I always used to do all right when
I went up to Newcastle. You
know, I'm trying to think if I got I got a
boyfriend. Think I would have heard
it some point, but yeah, I I cleaned up there, bro.
That's the kind of place where you you'd actually get
a get a
uh relationship, man, if you stay there.
I think they're
for they still the games and [ __ ] but I
just I just noticed they were just less
stuck up and obviously one approached
me [ __ ] I actually remember that.
That's the time I was staying in [ __ ]
Middlesbrough. So yeah, they're just far
less stuck up than uh than they are
here. Yeah, London is difficult. Yeah. [ __ ]
I don't have a free recolation.
This Jamie Thompson has no life.
Yeah, he's got a wife, but he's on
YouTube stalking me every day. Something
doesn't doesn't add up
there. Something does not add up
there. We can all agree. Yeah. There's Yeah. [ __ ] it.
Yeah, I'll be back later, Maybe heavy.