[Music] There you
go. Live on
YouTube. Probably man and Timmy are
still arguing about
beating. I know you can argue for
[ __ ] a week about beating and the
beat is still not happened. That doesn't
really make a lot of sense, you know.
I think after tomorrow I'm leaving for a while. Yeah. that you
We can get That's
Was it? I'm having a [ __ ] Oh, you
know that escort, right,
Greezy? He kept like saying, "Oh, I want
you to come. I want you to come over." I
said, "Okay, if you give me £10
discount, I'll come." And she said,
"Yeah." So, I went there and ran my dick
down her throat.
Or you could My whole dick was in her mouth
greasy. Like my whole dick went all the
way down her
gob. There was There was It was just all there, bro.
Yeah. Women put on this earth to satisfy
Peter Benny's needs. Greasy. I spent
about 150 today. Me girl got a
takeaway. Living the life green. Living
life. Living the
life. I wasn't eating punani, mate. I don't eat
[ __ ] I don't eat [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] that. I don't eat pirani, mate. Not
me. [ __ ] that. That's some bet [ __ ]
Do you know what I was thinking about
Greavvesy? Yeah. You know when LT was
messaging USA easier than that? It's so
mad to think how mad the mad [ __ ] that
they can get into and I'm the one behind
it all. You know it's like when
someone's behind the murder grievy. You
know when when someone's behind a murder
and they get like the longest
sentence, right? And they get like
either do they get the highest sentence.
Sorry. Is there instead the one that's behind it
all? I'm the one that's behind it
all. Oh, I can soon fix that for
you. I can soon fix that for you. If you
wish you hadn't discovered this channel.
Isn't that right,
Greavves? But yeah, she said, "Oh, you
still don't want to have sex?" I said, "No, just
[ __ ] just blow
jobs. Yeah. She kepting me, so I
thought, "Fuck it." She wanted money and
dick. So there you
go. You got money and
dick. Think she wanted it so bad. Eh.
Yeah. How much did you spend in a
cinema, Grezy? It must have been quite expensive.
I've got a mouth era on my tongue. So I
wouldn't even go to the cinema for a
couple of days cuz I won't be able to
enjoy the popcorn properly because I've got mouth.
So well my tongue.
So yeah, you must have spent a little bit
£55. What? just for
yourself. [ __ ] off. You're having a
wank. You don't £440. I spent about 150 today.
Keyboard 440. How did you do that? gambling.
What? I don't gamble anymore. Do you believe me,
Grezy? You spent £55 in a
cinema. I spent about 60 quid on meat,
but people chipped in and [ __ ] So, that
barbecue is going to be ultra lush
tomorrow, mate. [ __ ] ultra lush.
Uh I saw about 150
today. The meat was about 60,
but people uh
uh but obviously I got people that's
coming that's chipped in. So for myself
probably 27 28 for myself. But it was
£60. But obviously people chipped in.
So, but I spent
uh spent about 150 today escort barbecue
meat Indian as well. So,
yeah. [ __ ] 50 53 quid. Bring all your
little mates. All your little
mates. And you LT bring all your little
Bring your friends. You remember that
quote? No. This Brazilian escort kept
messaging me saying, "I'm here. When I'm
here, you never want to see me." I said,
"If you give me£10 off, I'll come." Just
to shut her up cuz she wanted money and
dick. So, I just went there and showed her my
dick. That was a lovely
site. Bring your
friends. Bring your little mates.
Bring all your little
mates. Yeah, that's funny.
E, I didn't shag. I just got a
[ __ ] I just got a [ __ ] mate.
Ain't shagged in ages.
So So who is behind that whole USA easy
thing? cactus people messaging her, LT
messaging her and how this whole thing
come how all of this come
about. Who's the who's the one that's
behind it all? Like like the
conspiracy? Who's the one behind
it? Who's the one that's behind it
all? Oh, I love it, bro. It's funny.
Yeah, sorry about
that. Nah, a [ __ ] without condoms
better than a shag, you
know. Nah. Oh, I actually saw um one of
the workers from O'Neal's today cuz he
lives near me. I said, "Mate, I got
[ __ ] I got [ __ ] banned for no
reason." He said, "Oh, you must have
done something." I said, "I
never cuz he lives near me." So, yeah. I said,
"No." Do you remember that old man,
Cactus? Tall [ __ ] he
was. Tall [ __ ] he was, mate. The English
manager. I'm speaking to this woman in
New York. Yeah. She's 50, 55. Now, if
she says I can stay with her, I might
just go there for a couple of days. [ __ ]
it. Got nothing to
lose. Got nothing to lose, mate. In it.
If she's going to let me stay with her,
mate, [ __ ] it. I got [ __ ] all to lose, isn't it?
Yeah. To try with other people whilst
I'm there. I'm not paying for no [ __ ]
hotels. So, if they say yeah, I'm gone,
man. If they say, "Yeah, I'm
going." Uh-huh. Yep. I see him all the
time. Yeah, I see him all the time,
buddy. All the time, love. All the
time. I think he's got mental health.
Yeah, your mommy [ __ ] were laughing at
us. All you have to say, LT, bring your
friends. Bring your
friends. Can't believe you say Izzy's
boyfriend looks like me with tattoos. What a
tool, Greasy. What a
tool. You know, what a
tool. You're not supposed to [ __ ] get
with people that looks like your previous
um what do you call it?
Previous lookups, I guess. Yeah. What a
tool. What a tall
cactus. Taking a baby away from its
mama. From its
mama. It's mama. It's mama, not mother. So
yeah, yeah, the old man always talks to
me when he sees me.
So always talking about West Ham and
[ __ ] I just go along with
it. Yeah. I just I just I just go along
with it, bro. Just literally just go along with it. Yeah.
taking a baby away from its mother. They
need to put some new horror films in the cinema,
bro. Yeah. I had to use an escort for
ages, so I thought, "Fuck it. 80 quid.
Nothing in it." So,
yeah. He's a lonely old man, mate. The
neighbors complain about him. [ __ ]
[ __ ] He's been there from the [ __ ] from
[ __ ] day dot.
Bring your friends. Bring your little
mates. And I'm not even trolling. There
is a barbecue tomorrow. People know
where I am.
So, it's not even like I'm
uh it's not even like I'm trolling cuz
I'm actually being serious. So,
yeah. I might go out not this week, next
week. But that's only I'm I'm going to
be going out with people. A good old piss
up. I don't really care about it
anymore. This woman's serious. I will
just go and meet her and I'll just go to
America and [ __ ] stay with her. She's actually being
serious. Yeah, she's a 50 odd year old, but
[ __ ] Yeah, there's so much I could do
there whilst I'm there, you see.
So I'm actually I'd actually do it, bro.
She's actually being serious. That butcher. What
butcher? Every butcher has pork unless it's allowed
butcher. But I'm a Muslim anyway, so I don't eat
pork. Yeah. I went to um Morrison's has
gone [ __ ] you know. Yeah.
All the [ __ ] meat was black. The pork
was off. I had to go to the [ __ ]
butchers and spend more money, mate. The
Morrison Morrison's is finished, mate.
All the [ __ ] steak was black. [ __ ]
pork was off and everything. I was like,
"Bro, are you
serious?" So, I had to go to the butchers
and get cut. I've actually got some
pork, but I just had a I just had a takeaway today.
You can't beat cooking a load of old bill
sometimes. A plate of old bill. Can't beat
it. No, I've heard about it though.
Yeah, you pour coke on a pork and then
maggots come on it. Yeah, I've heard
about it. I've heard about
it. That man owes me He owes me
20. Yeah, he's backbound on the
gambling. I said, "Bro, you need to stop
this gambling [ __ ] man. You're going
Thailand soon." I've quit. You know, he
got to a grand and lost it all. Like,
[ __ ] that, bro. Them days are done with
me. [ __ ] that
[ __ ] [ __ ] that [ __ ] bro. I said
you need to actually stop, bro. Like,
cuz he's actually worse than
me. I got chicken and beef. Yeah. And
fish. I got fish as well. Oh, we
actually actually got fish. Yeah, but
the only thing you do pork on a barbecue
is is bacon. I never do pork on a
barbecue. Yeah, but I don't have pork on
a barbecue really unless it's bacon with
a burger, but I don't really do it. There's fish, beef, dam, chicken. Good
enough. There's actual fish as well. I
went to a fish butcher if that's what
you call it.
I don't really have the pork on
the well be
here. What kind of videos you want to see?
cactus. What What do you want to see?
Blackpool videos. What videos would you like to
see? Yeah, I don't I don't do pork on a barbecue.
Anyways, so I got a burger. I got t-bone
steak. Got some fish. I got some
chicken. Bring your friends. Bring your little
mates. Bring your little mates.
bring your little
mates around for some food.
Yeah. Yeah. I was like literally pushing
ahead of my into my dick in that,
bro. Pushing it. Pushing it. Pushing it. Yeah. [Music] It was
funny. They're laughing at us,
mate. Oh, I can't. Women are so evil,
man. They are bloody evil.
[ __ ] [ __ ] they are,
bro. I don't know when I'll be out
again. That means I've got to pay money
to get a haircut. Uh, and I feel like I
just can't justify it anymore. Sounds
like I'm broke. Believe you me, I'm not.
You can't really justify it, is it?
[ __ ] almost 40 pound getting groomed
just to hear about I've got a boyfriend.
I just don't have the energy for it anymore, mate. to
be out the energy. I'm getting too old for it,
man. There was one I like today in the
in the supermarket, but there's no point
even talking to anyone. They just say
they were boyfriends, so there's no point.
Yeah, they've all got my
friends. How's it going, Aunt Man? I
said to him, how's it going, bro? You
still in the lever spoons? How's it
going? They all got
boyfriends. I was dead. I was dead, bro.
I'll never forget
it. Ah, same old cat
boyfriend. Oh, I'll never forget that.
The best [ __ ] I ever had, Cactus, was
from that American in the alleyway.
Do you remember in the alleyway the one
that I met in the
O'Neal's? Yep. That's why O'Neal's
banned me cuz they were jealous I was
getting all the
punani and they didn't like it so they got
jealous. They put a ban on me. That's what happened.
Yep. That's what happened, mate. Yep.
There are some [ __ ] you can
remember, some you can't.
Yeah, the one that somebody gave me was
hot. Was quite hot.
Yeah, she can't come. She's got a she's
a she's got a
boyfriend. No, it's probably say a
Yeah, my whole my whole body felt it in
the in in in the early way one
cactus. I really want you, but I don't
think you want
me. I do. You can just tell that was
done with such
love, love and
affection. I was like, we can't do it
here. So then I just started fingering
her and I got my dick out.
I tried to book a hotel, but I wasn't in
time. A friend caught up with us, and
the hotel would have been like 300 quid
as well. So, I was happy just to get a
[ __ ] I bet you didn't tell your nan
about that on Facebook, did you? Having
someone's penis in your mouth, you
hoe. You bloody hoe.
Yeah, this morning one was good as well,
but she kept like getting her teeth in it.
Yeah. Yeah. No, she said, "I want you,
but I don't think you want me." She
didn't say like
you. She said, "I want you, but I don't
think you want me." I said, "I do." Yeah. Yeah,
man. Smiling one was okay, but a bit
teethy around the
dick. Can't believe she sucked my dick
in the [ __ ] Weather Spoons toilet.
These [ __ ] do anything for
money. I said to um LT as well, if I had
a baby with her, my baby and your baby could be
friends. cuz you got a newborn, so your
baby and my baby could be friends. How
cute would that be playing around in the
park? Ah, what a lovely
sight. I thought that would be a lovely
sight. Could you imagine?
Yeah, it's hot in it.
Cactus. People that lick women out are [ __ ] nasty,
mate. That sig Yeah, her [ __ ] vagina
stunk. I'm not licking you out.
Yeah, being friends
together and we can tell the kids when
they grow up how we met and how he tried
to kill me and I almost died that night.
Because if I was if I was in that room,
Cactus, it would have been a vicious attack.
It would have been quite a fish's
attack. And we can tell the children
when when we're older how like your
father almost killed
me. Yeah, that would have been quite a vicious
attack all over the same website you can
watch Tom and Jerry on. I'm sure the B
I'm sure the children love to laugh at that. Yeah.
What a lovely site. Yeah.
Yeah. Now I was in
Nottingham. No, I was in Nottingham. I
remember exactly how this happened.
Yeah. I was basically in Nottingham
coming back and I was starting on that
[ __ ] uh what was her face when
everyone thought it was a woman that
battals cuz she kept trolling people.
So, oh, I'm going to come in your
university. I'm going to come to your university. And
then he was like, "Oh, I'm coming to
break in your house and shit." So, I
come back and I was like, "I am not
going back to that [ __ ] house, mate.
[ __ ] that. I am not going back to that [ __ ] house."
And then I think I pulled an all nighter
in the casino and that madness,
bro. Yeah. And then the whole windows
got smashed. I got a lot of lucky escapes,
bro. I was like, I'm not going back to that
house for like a day. But [ __ ] that. I I
should have just stayed another night.
Not you, would
it? Yeah. He'll tell you the story himself.
And he went upstairs. Yeah. And he
thought he hit the jackpot in it. There
was somebody lying there. He thought it
was me. He said, "Yes, this is the
perfect moment." And then it was just a
tenant. Yeah. It was It's funny looking
back on it, but it's not funny back
then. Yeah. I already Yeah, cuz he said
he was coming, but so I was like, "Fuck
that." I was like, "No way, bro."
And then every time I'd look outside,
I'd see some black guy by the door
waiting. So, but then it kind of died
down after that. So, it was quite
dangerous. Quite quite dangerous, bro. Yeah. Yeah.
I've had a lot of escapes,
matey. We can all laugh about it now,
can't we? Me and
L. If I write a woman, if I write a
woman a nice message, cactus, what would she do?
Huh? They reply to negativity, don't they, Cactus? Yeah.
I'm trying to think of the Nottingham
[ __ ] I can't really remember it that
well, but I remember her not having to
use her hands and just coming
everywhere, but I can't remember it that
well. I remember making out with her and
kept putting my hand her hands on my
dick. Yeah, I remember that.
I could have got some more [ __ ] out
of that Nottingham one.
Definitely, but I kicked her out the
hotel room when I was done with her cactus.
Yeah, proper ignoras, lad. Proper
ignoras. Yeah, that Nottingham one. I
could have tried to get to suck my dick
in the morning if I just let her stay there.
I [ __ ] a lot of things up, you know.
Like I [ __ ] a lot of things up as
well. So this whole like other people
have been a relationships, it doesn't
really wash, mate, you know, cuz I have
I have [ __ ] things up, too. So yeah.
Yeah, it was £40. It wasn't £60. It was
Yeah. What do you think of USA? Easy,
Cactus. That guy's got to be really
desperate to get with her knowing that
body count, knowing what she looks like. That's [ __ ]
madness. Yeah. He's got to be desperate, bro.
It Yeah, but that's how bad it is.
That's what I'm saying. Like men are the
ones that have to lower their
standards. And that's what I'm saying.
Men are the ones that have to lower their standards. Hey.
Yeah, if I'm mad as well.
Izzy's never left me for another
guy. I'm the I'm the one that actually
went home with Izzy. So, yeah, that's made
up. Izzy's never left me for
anyone. I'm the one that went home with
her. No one else.
Uh oh. If you're talking about the first time.
Yeah. Yeah. That's because she rinsed
me. Cactus. The first time I met
Isabelle, she rinsed
me. She rinsed me. Bro, you remember
that time I won £300 on the [ __ ]
roulette, which was a lot of money back
then. I mean, it's still a lot of money
now. And then she messaged me all of a
sudden she wanted to get in on some of
that money. She [ __ ] rinsed me, bro.
Don't forget I didn't have as much money back
then. [ __ ] rinsed me the Yeah. Yeah, bro.
See, it's [ __ ] up. It's a hard one
because if there was no YouTube, the the
Izzy thing wouldn't have
happened. But obviously the USA is
thing, there was no YouTube. So we can't
blame YouTube. She's just a [ __ ] She's
just a [ __ ] [ __ ] Just a
snake. She's nasty. The the UK is one's
nasty as well.
She's actually sick in her head as well,
bro. They're actually both sick in their
head. I'm telling you,
bro. Another one that liked [ __ ] with
people's heads, but you soon run to the
[ __ ] old bill when someone comes in
your door. Don't Yeah, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, [ __ ] idiots.
But but Izzy's never never left me for
that energy live. That's what you're speaking
about. You know what I mean?
So, and it doesn't even matter. YouTube.
No, YouTube. They still do this [ __ ] So,
Bonnie and Timmy are still talking about
[ __ ] meeting. [ __ ] hell,
man. Oh, when is this happening,
bro? Bonnie was like to me yesterday,
they want to come up to Birmingham for a
piss up. I was like, I'm not backing you
up, bro. I ain't backing you
up. You snaked me. Natalie has snaked
me. I'm not [ __ ] backing you
up. I'll watch it. I'll watch the whole
thing. You know, Natalie snaked me cuz I've caught
her. Uh, and also he snaked me. [Music] So,
yeah. Why am I going to go to Birmingham
and back you up? [ __ ] that,
bro. You must be mad. [ __ ]
that. I'm not involved in the job either way. So yeah. [Music]
He's still there, man. Yeah.
So I think that USA is he deserved
everything she got if you ask me.
Yeah. Play with fire, you get burned, [ __ ] That's
it. You get [ __ ]
burnt. [ __ ] pair of
[ __ ] Cactus pair of [ __ ] mate.
Yeah. [ __ ] So
[ __ ] You remember cactus when you said
how when they meet me they don't know
what they're in for? Oh,
mate. Nah, I don't want to contact her.
She's an evil [ __ ] mate. I wouldn't I
would I don't like her, bro. Believe
that. I don't like the [ __ ] She
doesn't bother me. There's still ways
I've got her email. I remember I emailed
her a couple of months
ago. Nah, bro. It doesn't I don't want
to contact her. She's a coward, bro.
Yeah. What's there to say, bro? They're
never going to come out and say anything
to your face. They're never going to
reply back. It's Why would I need to contact them?
There's no way you're still messaging
me. Started messaging back with this ego and
[ __ ] you know. Now Scott's blocked me
on everything as well. He said, "I'm no
longer giving you a I messaged her mom
Instagram." Yeah, I messaged her mom on
Instagram. Yeah, I said, "Your
daughter's a scumbag, mate. All you can
do is make group chats, but we all know
face to face and only you about nothing.
That's why you talk about [ __ ] law
and people and [ __ ] You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Nah. Scott blocked me, mate. He said I'm
not giving you attention
anymore. Leave him alone, bro. Leave
Scott alone. He He's an old Syrian man.
an old Syrian pension. Old age Syrian pensioner.
Yeah. It's a [ __ ]
madness. I think she had so many one
night stands, bro, in Europe and she
just felt ashamed of
herself. That's what I think it is.
gave her body to so many people when
when she was over here.
Yeah. It's disgusting, isn't it?
Really, it's actually disgusting,
bro. Any normal, any person would have
run as soon as I heard 25th, but I was
in it too deep,
cactus. But would they really want run?
Uh, people said that as soon as they
kissed me and said, "You'll be my 25th."
I would have ran away. But would they actually
have? You know, you're drunk. You're
[ __ ] horny. Someone's coming on
kissing you. Would you actually be running
away? You know what I'm saying?
So would they
actually or they just saying this
[ __ ] No, I don't get attached anymore.
No, maybe the future. I never say never, but
no, I was about to, but the person
[ __ ] ghosted. So, yeah, I was about
to a couple of weeks
ago and some and the date I went on as
well, but they just [ __ ] ghosted.
So, it makes you think, what are they looking for? cuz
Yeah. Nah, he's not here. He
left. No, it wasn't four years. It
wasn't four years. It was about It was
about No, it's about two two and a half.
It wasn't four
years. No, it's not still going, bro.
It's not still
going. It's not still going, bro. I
don't like the [ __ ] I don't care about
[ __ ] I don't care about the
[ __ ] I just went I just went on a
Facebook the other day just out of
curiosity. I don't like the [ __ ] you
know. Even my
mama. Yeah. Women despise you as well.
That's why you're still a
virgin. Yeah, they despise you as well.
You're still a virgin. keyboard warrior. Bye-bye. So,
um, yeah, I'm a non. Come and call me
that to my face. You know where I
live. Yeah, you're calling me a nunch.
Well, you know where I live. So, why
don't you come and call me a nunch to my
face. Come on, man. Stop being a keyboard, boy.
Now, you know we Who's we? The people
that's never had a
woman. The people that's that can't get
a woman. Yeah. Okay, bro. Come on. So,
uh, yeah. So, that's why I just went on their profile
cactus. But you can't get attached to
people nowadays. And no one should be
getting attached to people because of
how women are. You shouldn't get
yourself attached to any of them.
Because look at what they do, bro. They
go on dates and waste people's time
intentionally. like that one that I told
you I went on a date with last month.
Everything was fine. Didn't say anything
wrong. Didn't do anything
wrong and apparently they're not feeling
it. So, it doesn't even add up. It
doesn't even make sense, especially when
they're the ones that approach you.
So, it's very um mentally unstable how
somebody can just change their mind that quickly.
We hear about people changing their
minds and [ __ ]
but not that quickly, bro.
So then it was like, "Oh, so is this
what's going to happen if you go on
dates?" So that's why the whole thing is
just a waste of
time. That's what I
mean. The whole thing is a waste of time.
And how many dates have I been on? I've
been on a load of dates. You know that one in [Music]
Newcastle? I've been a load of
dates. Oh, who are you? What? You're
You're calling me a non, bro.
Listen, you're calling me a n. Come and
call me a n to my face or stop writing
it on YouTube. That's all I'm going to
say, bro. Like, stop calling me. Stop
saying that I'm a nons on YouTube and
come and say to my face. Everyone knows where I
live. So you either come and say to my
face or you stop writing on YouTube. Simple as
that. How the [ __ ] do you work out? I'm
a nons. There's actual nons. Do you know
the [ __ ] up thing about this community
cactus is there's actual nonses on here
and these people never ever go for them.
Not mentioning any names, but there's
actual pedophiles on here.
nonses, right? Pedophile nonses. And
they don't go for them, but they're the
one they're called me nons. How [ __ ]
up is that? [ __ ] off, mate. Go and have
wank. Yeah, go and have a play with
yourself. There's actual nons on this
community. Yeah, there's actual [ __ ]
nons, right? And you're coming on my
[ __ ] calling me a n. Are you [ __ ] for
real? Get out of here,
man. Yeah, I do remember that one. Another time
waster. Yeah, another time waster, you know.
Yeah. People know that I'm not a nons.
Why do you think LJ doesn't even call me
nons? But there is actual nonses on on
here. Why? Why did I see you comment on their
channel? Why don't I see you comment on their
channel? Yeah, I said that stuff in
retaliation. You [ __ ] idiot. Stop being
obsessed. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I said
stuff in retaliation. Good for you. But
there's actual pedophiles on here that's
admitted it. They've actually admitted
that they're [ __ ] basically
pedophiles. I don't see you comment on
their channel. I don't see you comment
on their channel. And and you could say
all that stuff again. That doesn't mean
you're a [ __ ]
nons. You know, you're obsessed.
Anyways, bye-bye you little
repeater. But there's actual pedophiles
on here, mate. There is actual
pedophiles on here and I never see you
on their channel. Why don't I see you on channel? So
yeah. Yeah. We was I was supposed to go to Manchester,
but yeah, she [ __ ] around.
So obviously I didn't go to Manchester,
did I? So
Yeah. Did do you know what she done? Um
I noticed that she had uh we was arranging to
meet and then um I noticed that she
blocked me on uh Instagram. I said, "Uh,
why have you blocked me on Instagram?"
She said, "Um, oh, I just deleted it."
And we all know a woman doesn't delete
her Instagram. I was like, "You didn't
delete it. You blocked me." And then she
blocked me on WhatsApp. Okay. Yep. So,
yeah. Yeah. I thought that was looking good as
well. Yeah. That's no surprise, bro.
They all do that. So,
yeah. Yeah. Haven't I fought loads of
people was the one,
bro? And this is how I know about women
going on dates with you and wasting your
time because I've gone on a date with
somebody before, not like them, then
ended up liking them when I spent more
time. So, it takes a while to know that
if you vibe or you connect or you don't
connect, you don't know within 20, 30
minutes. It's literally impossible
because you barely know the person.
Think about it. If you approach somebody
and you spend 20, 30 minutes with them,
it's not long
enough. It's not long enough. You
understand? So, it's like when you if
you meet a woman and in 20 minutes she
says she doesn't feel the vibe, it
doesn't make no
sense because it takes a while to
actually get to know someone and see if
you vibe, etc. And feelings can change.
So, that's how I know from my own
experiences. And obviously, my own
experiences from [ __ ] lowering my
standards. So, it's all
[ __ ] Yeah. You think loads of
people are the one, bro. That's just
that's what happens.
But I thought the one in Newcastle was
the one. She had the same date of birth
as me. Same date of birth. Approached
her on the street sober. Got a date. I'm
thinking, "Oh yeah." Come out the
[ __ ] police station. The next day I got [ __ ] blocked.
So yeah, that was when I went in
Newcastle. The time I got nicked. So yeah.
Yeah, I will never meet anyone and
think, "Oh, they're the one anymore cuz
of obviously the [ __ ] that they do." Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Another one that done what she
done on purpose.
Yeah, I actually met her on
Instagram. You remember Sig Cactus? Good old
Sig. Good old Sig.
Good old Siggy. Eh. Yeah.
Obviously, it drives me mad, bro. I was
going to go Manchester and put up
[ __ ] post, bro. The one that drove me
mad was when I was at my mom's a couple of weeks
ago. There was this one. Yeah. with big
boobs and that. And I met her on um I
think it was a Sunday I met her actually
and we was talking. We were supposed to
meet on a Friday, the the the previous
Friday, the Friday coming, not the one
coming, the next one. And then she just
[ __ ] ghosted me. I said, "Yo,
ignore." And then she blocked me. Yeah,
it is annoying. That That's the [ __ ]
that annoys me. Of course it [ __ ] Of
course it made me mad, bro. The [ __ ] Obviously,
bro, annoying as
[ __ ] but it's Yeah, it is the ghosting.
There was a Romanian I met in Stratford
like couple of months ago. Got her
number talking fine and bam,
disappears. They literally just disappear.
So, yeah, man. Yeah. Yeah. Heat.
Yeah. Yep. She only responds to
negativity, but she said she was going
to get round to responding cactus, even
though it's been 3
months. And then she's like, "Oh, well,
yeah, I don't want to associate somebody
that has that view on women." Yeah,
that's the whole reason she replied in
the first place is because of
that. They're such narcissists, isn't
it? It's like that Morgan. She soon
[ __ ] replied when I started messaging
her [ __ ] family, is
it? soon replied when I started
messaging your [ __ ] family. Pair of
[ __ ] Pair of [ __ ] mate.
Yeah. Pair of
[ __ ] Thank you, [Laughter]
[ __ ] There you go, [ __ ] Thank you,
[ __ ] [ __ ] man. Yeah. [Laughter]
Yeah. Thank you, [Laughter]
God. Oh, mate. She only responds to negativity. Yeah.
Oh yeah, definitely. You know what's so
mad? Yeah. Um I've actually had it
before. I had it when I was in Scotland
as well. Yeah. Is I've actually had
women straight up ask me for
money. Right. Like they've they've
they've just said, "Oh, can you send me
money? I want money. I want money." Now,
the saying goes, "Women don't owe you
anything." Right? But why are women
never told that men don't owe them anything?
That's a bit double standard standardy,
isn't it? They're never told how they
don't owe them
anything. Yeah. So, what happened to men
not owing women
anything? Yeah. They soon reply
them. Soon reply them, mate.
Yeah. Money, negativity.
Yeah, baby LT and baby Peter. Uh
it Simpsons here, man. We'll be playing that again later.
Yeah. Oh, I love the I love the little
Simpsons characters. Greasy Simpsons here and
run. They're lovely little
characters. They're lovely little
characters, mate. Yeah, I like Bart Simpson.
Simpsons is very old, man. Simpsons is
old. Thank you,
man. Yeah, Simpsons is very old,
mate. Yeah, Simpsons did it. Simpsons in
it. I was watching some 24 hours in police custody.
Cactus, you've watched 24 hours in
police custody, haven't
you? [ __ ] hell,
bro. I can't believe that guy that got caught with
£250,000 cash under his bed and all that
drugs. Oh my god. Got in it. Imagine
that. [ __ ] hell. Going prison for 6
years and coming out with nothing. [ __ ] that,
bro. All cuz he decided to download child
porn. All because he down he decided to download child
porn. That is [ __ ] mad,
bro. All them all that money, all that
drugs. That's [ __ ]
bro. Nope. Nah, man. I got nicked to
where is it? The
one I was
fine. I wasn't fine. I was pissed off. But yeah.
No, I even went on a sweat box to
court. Sweat box. I went to court. No, it's fine, bro. Yeah.
stiff mattress, mate, and a pillow. It was
[ __ ] And they told me, "Oh, we're not
bailing you." I said, "Why?" And they're
like, "You broke bell conditions." I'm
like, "No, I
didn't." No, I [ __ ] did not. So, I'm
having to like, "Oh, yeah. I contacted
the police again today about my report.
I'm having to follow up about this
report every week. So yeah, since these
people like calling the police, I'll
call the police on them and I won't stop
until they do something as well. So
yeah. Then and I remember staying up
from 9:00 in the morning till 9:00 at
night to 9:00 in the
morning. Had to get sweat box to court
and then the court let me go. Yeah, it
was [ __ ] bad, bro.
Yeah, it's not a nice but
yeah I still came back to my phone in it.
Yeah, I've got all my reports anyways, bro.
Yeah, see now you know one of these
people and I'm not talking about one or
two people. Yeah, they they'll start
calling you grasses now. I was like, no,
no, no, no. These people wanted to start
calling the police on people. Now I'm
doing it back. You can't cry when
someone does it back to you or say, "Oh,
grass when someone does it back to you."
This was a normal
community. And then people wanted to
start calling the police time and time
and time and time and time and time and
time and time again. So, no one should
cry when it's done back at back to them
in my opinion, bro. Like you can't you
can't cry now, bro. Like that's
it. Why would I get a panic attack? I'm
used to them, bro. I've been arrested so
many times over this stupid community,
so I don't give a [ __ ] You
know, you can't grass and grass and
grass and grass and then cry when
someone does it back to you. It's not
the way the world works. Or then even
call them a grass. You know what I'm
saying? like no one even says anything
anyways cuz they know
like that these people how many times
they've called the police time and time
and time and time again. So
yeah, I think you two's never been arrested. I'm guessing
uh it's not nice being arrested,
matey. The time seems to go quite fast, surprisingly. Yeah. Quite scary,
matey. I just remember swearing at the
police the whole
time. Swearing at them. Swearing at
them. Calling them [ __ ] pigs and all sorts. Yeah.
Proper. It's what these people tell
them, bro. It's what these people tell
them. You know, it's what these people tell
them. You know what I'm saying? But
yeah, it'll be dropped in three and a
half years anyways.
So, and I'm going to keep up with my
reports every week. So,
yeah. Yeah. Because it's what they tell them,
bro. It's what they tell them. So, I
admit it. I'm going to the police every
week. I admit it. Like, no, no one's
going to come on here and even try to
call me GR. No one's even going to come
on here and try and call me a grass. I
admit it. I will be going to the police
every week. And I've been doing it. You
know, it took 6 months for me. So, I
will keep doing it and doing it and
doing it and doing it and doing it and
doing it and doing it. I made another
report today. I said this this person on
YouTube's been giving me panic attacks,
anxiety, all sorts. I can't leave my
house, you know. So yeah, I'm not going
to stop reporting it, bro. They wanted
to get themselves involved. The police
wanted to get themselves involved. Stay
involved. Yeah, they offer you food, but
I didn't eat. That's how I [ __ ] my
foot up as well. So I just said, "Yeah,
I've got anxiety, panic attacks, I'm disabled."
Yeah. Yeah. Took him about I done
another report today when the end of the line. Yeah.
It's what people on YouTube wanted. It's
what the police wanted. The police have
got involved time and time and time and
time and time again, you know. Let's not
go back on it now. You
know, yeah, it's like Trao as well. Say
Trao gets nicked. He'll be the first one
crying. Oh, you got me nicked. Oh, like
as an example. Yeah. He has called the
police about how many times on people in
this community. So it is funny, but
don't cry when it happens to you. You
know, it is funny. It is entertaining.
Yeah, I admit it. It is quite
funny. It can be seen as entertaining,
but don't cry when it happens to you.
Don't start moaning when it happens to
you. That's all I want. You know what
I'm saying? Like that's that's
it, you know?
Yeah, bro. No, no, no. More than that,
Tactus. More than that. Cuz for them to
act, you need to be hounding them and
hounding them and hounding them. So, I
know this stuff because I've had to
follow up a couple of times with this
police woman who's called me. So, they
have to which also proves they ain't got
which also proves these people have not
got a life because they have to keep
following up with the police cuz I've
had to do it. And I know how frustrating
it is, but obviously I've got to do it.
I'm not going to stop doing it because
it also helps my case as well. So, it
helps my case. So, obviously, and that's
it. So, yeah, you need to really be
hounding them really next level, bro,
for them to come out. So, yeah, I just
said, "Yeah, I've got panic attacks, anxiety, depression,
um I'm being bullied
online, you know." So
yeah, report it all. I found out I
emailed today as well. I emailed her. So
yeah, trust me, people are going to be
getting nicked, mate. They put it all on
them. These people put it all on
themselves, bro. I've gave the Red Star
channel and everything.
They could have just [ __ ] left it and
just carried on winding people up, but
they wanted to get the boys in blue
involved. So, I'll do the same
thing. You know, I'll do the same thing. Yeah.
So, I follow up every
week. Yeah. Not a problem. Yeah.
People in this community want to act the
big man cactus but then want to go
running to the police crying behind
closed doors and then they claim they
won. Okay, bro, whatever. you know.
So, yeah, it doesn't make any sense,
it? And that's exactly why I pled not guilty,
practice. That's exactly why I pled not
guilty, you know.
So, I'm not stupid, bro. I know these
things. Shouldn't plead guilty,
bro. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. It's just easy for them to do it.
It's like when when police offer you a
caution. If you refuse a caution, most
of the time they're not going to
actually take you to
court. They try. I've actually been
arrested for criminal damage before, but
um I just I just refused a caution. It
was my own [ __ ] door. So, I've had
this mad history with police coming on
this door time and time and time again.
I thought that's the last [ __ ] time,
mate. You want to get yourself involved?
Stay involved now. But I keep following
up with my
reports. Three and a half years. Yeah.
Yeah. Three and a half
years. It's actually three and a half years. Yeah.
It is long, bro. It is long. But there
was no way I was going
guilty. Especially the amount of
evidence that I've got. So, it's like
there's no way, mate. If they want to
find me guilty, they can find me guilty.
But I'm not pleading
guilty. I don't know, man. Probably
because it's going to get
dropped. Well, it doesn't matter if it
gets dropped or not, mate. I'm still
going to keep reporting every every week.
So, so following up every week, making new
reports, you know.
So, don't know why it is that far
away. Maybe because they're trying to
drop it. I don't know. [ __ ] know. It's
quite far, is it? Who
knows? Probably a
fine. Probably a fine. Suspended
sentence. She won't go to
prison, but we're talking 3 and 1/2
years later. So, yeah, probably a fine,
ma'am. But I won't get found
guilty because the doctor cuz they said
basically if you keep reporting it, what
will happen is you're both going to end up in
court and then the judge is going to see
it. And I was like, I'd rather that. Yeah.
So, and it probably gets dropped anyways.
So, I mean, they're not going to put you
in [ __ ] prison, especially after that.
So, yeah. Well, they say three, it'll
probably get dropped within a year, to
be honest. Three and a half years. cuz
it will probably get dropped within a [ __ ]
um and the solicitor basically said just
send all the stuff that they've been
um they've been you know been doing and
stuff. So I said that's not a problem.
I've got everything on my phone so it's not a problem. So
yeah. Yeah. probably a fine maybe
suspended sentence. They have to go by
certain guidelines, you know. But
yeah, they can't put you in prison.
That's what the solicitor said anyways. So
yeah, there was no way I was pleading guilty,
bro. No way. I thought they were
actually joking when they were actually asking
that. No way am I [ __ ] pleading
guilty. I'd rather get to I'd rather get
sent to prison in three and a half
years. That's how bad it is. Not that it
would happen, but I I'd actually prefer
that. Yeah, cuz the system's changed,
man. It's in Crown Court, but it should
have been in at a magistrates. But the
system is all changed now. It's all
changed. Like Crown Court is they say
it's serious things, but it's
uh it's more
like it's all changed now. They [ __ ]
the courts up and all and all sorts, but
yeah. Yeah, it's they [ __ ] up. They
[ __ ] up somewhere.
Yeah, they [ __ ] up somewhere, lad.
definitely. And the only bell condition
you have is to not get yourself in any
more [ __ ] or wind yourself up, which is
a good thing really. Can still leave the
country, can still [ __ ] go out, send it. So
yeah, not on no curfew. So I'd rather
take that to be honest,
mate, you know.
So yeah, did
that which is mad how he suggest to
plead guilty when
um it was probably going to get dropped anyways.
So but then the reason they tell you to
plead guilty is it's just easier for
them. You see, we just plead guilty and
it's over and done with. But
nah. Nah, mate.
Yeah. Anyways, I'm gone, bro. So, uh,
talk to you tomorrow when I do the barbecue. Bye.