Sorry about that, man. I was on the
phone to someone going to go back live. [ __ ]
it. Made a [ __ ] B of it. Mhm.
No, no, no, no.
This mouth also is high. Yeah.
I'm playing some Simpsons here running
about an hour.
Grezy, I'm just having some popcorn
here. [ __ ] mouth are [ __ ] hurt,
Squeezy. You know, mouth pulses, they're
[ __ ] painful, aren't they,
bro? Oh, painful, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. Lovely little characters. Do
you remember Stu? Little Grezy.
Oh. Oh. Stew it
little. Stew it little
greasy. Oh, do it little
greens. I love
Ste. You love him.
What's Harry Potter, Grezy? I've never
heard of Harry Potter. I always hear
people talk about Harry Potter. I've
never heard of
that. Must be some sort of cartoon.
Oh, yeah. He's clearly just do it
there. Oh, I'll never forget that. Yeah,
George. I remember the names. George,
you're going to meet your new brother
now. And then the door rings or they
even ring the door. They knock the
[ __ ] door and he's looking and he
look down and there's to a little Oh, that's [ __ ] cute.
Oh, I've never heard of Harry Potter.
Never heard of it,
bro. I was listening to the Tom and
Jerry theme. The Tom and Jerry
theme. The Tom and Jerry theme earlier.
D. It still gives me goosebumps to this
day. Oh, how it will
never Oh, it will never die.
Grezy. That will never die. It still gives me goosebumps. Remember, Greasy. Oh.
Grezy, we're such kids. You know that,
Grezy? Me and you are such
kids. Hi, I'm Chucky and I'm your friend
to the end. Do you remember that, Grezy?
I'm your friend to the
end. I've actually got a projector here.
I might watch a film
later. And I'm your friend to the end. Hideyho.
That be funny as
[ __ ] and I'm your friend to the end.
Chucky. I like
Chucky. He's having some popcorn.
You know what though, Gy? I've never
been on a date to a c in
a I've never been on a date to a cinema in my life.
Never. Never ever been on a
date. Not to a cinema.
Nah. Yeah, that's why I don't do it. I
always go to cinema by myself. I don't
think I've ever been with anyone else.
Well, except when I was a child,
obviously I'm with my mom, but nah, I
like going by myself because as soon as
something is out, I want to watch
it. I don't want to be with someone
else. I want to be by myself,
bro. Yeah, [ __ ]
that. No, I prefer going alone, mate. I
like being the only one in the cinema as
well. Like I told you before, Greg, that
last time I went to the cinema, I was by
myself. It was so nice being the only
one in that cinema. Was amazing, mate.
Oh my god. It was a Monday. Yeah, a
Monday. It was a Monday. Um, the first
showing, I think it was called Love
Eyes. Oh, that's probably why there was
no one there because uh they were all
[ __ ] on a Valentine's date. But yeah,
it was [ __ ] amazing, bro. I was the
only one there.
Next time you go watch a film, well, I
don't know about Stitch. I don't think
you'd be the only one in Stitch because
it's quite popular. But if you ever want
to watch a horror film, go Monday, the
first showing on a Monday. You should be
the only one
there. It's just it's it was just so
nice having it all to yourself. You can
even have a wank if you wanted to. You
know, if you really wanted Yeah.
Excuse me. Do you like Miss Mickey Mouse's
clubhouse? You like Miss Mouse's clubhouse,
Dad? That's another old school uh old
school run. That
ain't That's another good one. Oh,
imagine that though. Greasy [ __ ] up
into the limp on a [ __ ] date like a
spacker. Just weren't that woman from
Burton who said you're walking like a
spacker, mate. I was walking like a disabled
person. I I think I needed to be in a wheelchair, lad.
Oh, it's so nice. It's gone for the most
part. This is the time it would call up.
The foot pain would start nowump
greasy. It woke me up at 4 in the
morning. [ __ ] hell,
bro. It was quite I said it was quite vicious. Yeah.
It's nice just chilling, you
know. Do you remember when I used to
live with Laney Greasy?
Nah, I like living without Laney. Me and
Laney are still cool though.
What's up? I don't know who you are,
buddy. Probably some troll.
Ah, just chilling, man.
Uh, we did love
se. Yeah, he loves see ball. He does.
Yeah. Molly wanted me to back him up in
Birmingham. Greasy. Yeah. Well, he
didn't say directly. He said it
indirectly. Oh, let's go to Birmingham
for a piss up, mate. I'm not backing you up, bro.
You're a snake and Natalie G's a snake.
Am I lying,
Grezy? Uh, Timmy Eldridge is, but Toasty's not.
No. Am I lying, Grezy? Like, you've
heard them talk [ __ ] about me in my
absence as well. Do you remember that
time I was taking a break off of
YouTube? When I went back on the live
streams, I've caught them talking [ __ ]
about me and I weren't even on or saying
anything about them. So, [ __ ] them, bro.
I'm not [ __ ] backing them up. [ __ ]
that. You're by yourself, mate. [ __ ]
snake. That's the one thing you'll find
with this community,
Grezy, is they're all
snakes. Obviously, you don't you don't
you don't get involved with the drama. I
get it, bro. But they are all snakes on here.
like you know you know that Ricky
Millington thing I've I've heard him
talk [ __ ] about me. I've
heard I've heard
uh Bingy talk [ __ ] about
me. Uh Ricky Millington I've I've heard
him talk [ __ ] about me. Uh Natalie spoke
[ __ ] about me. Bonnie snaked me all for
no reason. You know I've caught them
slipping. And I told that Ricky Millan,
if you have got anything to say, say it
to my face. He soon shut up, didn't he? [ __ ]
snake. But the only one who's not a
snake is unworthy
clock. A worthy clock's a decent guy,
man. He just stays out of it. And to be
fair, Tiger's all right as well. You
know, Tiger only went because [ __ ]
Timmy influenced him to come to come to
London and that. You know what I mean?
Even Timmy even Tiger's okayish. He's a
creep and he's a weirdo, but he's still
all right compared to a lot of the
others. Yeah, they are
snakes. Yeah, it ruined his life, didn't it,
Cactus? Imagine losing your children
over YouTube madness.
to these people. Have they ruined my life on
here? Uh, not really. They've caused
inconveniences, but they've never ruined
my life. Like, I moved out of my mom's
for different reasons. We was having arguments,
so not really.
They were never able to stop any of my
money. So, his life actually got ruined.
See, when I moved out, my mom's I had
somewhere to go. But, I mean, I was
sleeping on the stairs for a bit and I
was almost not almost homeless cuz I had money.
So, but a lot of that was cuz I lost my
phone as well. So, no, not really. They
don't ruin my life cuz I still had
money, you know, I still had a gaff. So yeah.
Um, so I wouldn't say they ruined my life. Yeah. Yep. You bet.
Yeah. Going all the way to America to to
confront a woman
cactus all over. The same website you
can watch Scooby
on. Same website you can get killed on.
Yeah. It's mad, isn't it?
Yeah. Remember if I when I go there
cactus and I go on Scots door all the
attention is going to be on my channel isn't
it? All the people from Lord Jay's
channel is going to go into my channel. Leave me
alone. I'll show you a proper lodge and in
charge lo and in
charge. I'll [ __ ] show you lodge and
in charge. I was saying to my friend as
well, I was like, "Bro, do you want to
go America for a day and come
back? Show them country who's
boss." You know what I'm saying? Show
them who's boss in it, Cactus.
Yeah. Let's just go for a day and come
back in it. They're five hours behind.
E Scooby, you know I love Scooby. Is it?
You know I love Scooby.
Yeah, you know, I love [ __ ] Scooby in
it, bro. So, uh, yeah.
Yeah, you can always message Scott in it,
Cactus. Remember, Cactus, I'm part of the family
now. I'm part of the family.
I'm part of the family, baby.
Yeah, that is funny as [ __ ] bro. Yeah. [Music]
I might do some streaming on the
Simpsons Hill run. Go live on the
Hun. I'm not sure how I could do it,
but I've got a I've got a [Music]
PS4. I'm sure I could Oh, I probably
could do it. I'd have to buy it from the
store, though, would I?
I'd have to buy it from the actual
store. Yeah, there is a way I could do
it. I'd have to buy it from the PlayStation store. Drive
around. I got a projector and a
PS4. Do you remember when they done
posters of Monty
Cactus? Do you remember when they done posters of
Monty? Uh, yes. I played it.
Yes, I played it. Yep.
I played all of the Simpsons game, lad
games. A I just miss them days, you
know, staying up until 6:00 in the
morning. The 10year-old Peter Belly. Not
a care in the
world, cactus. Not a care in the world.
Not a bit, not a hair on my
face, not a stress in the world, you
know. Staying up all day and all night hearing the birds. Yeah. I
cactus. Remember Scott? It's been two
years. What caused me to
stress? What caused you to stress? No.
Bill. Oh, well,
Bill's life. Figured out what I'm going
to do in the future.
Well, I don't have any money worries,
but yeah, no money
worries. Any worries at
all, which is good, eh?
Nah, mate. I'm not been skimp for [ __ ]
ages. You don't add You don't get skin
on the kind of money I'm on, matey.
I've only got about three things to pay
out for. That's
it. How much do you get a month,
Tony? How much do you get a month?
God, that mouth is [ __ ] stinking,
bro. [ __ ] stinking. It is. How
much? Yeah, I get 3K a month, but I don't
work and I have like two outgoings, three
outgoings, and I get about 3K a month.
Uh, my outgoings is
about maybe 16 150
maybe. Yeah, about 150. But yeah. Ah. Yeah,
bro. I don't struggle on it, but it
seems to go fast. But probably half of
yours goes on
rent. Half of yours probably goes on
rent, I'm guessing. Right. I wouldn't
say I'm I struggle on it.
I mean, most of it is mine, but when you
have a high life in
London, you get used to it. I think that's the
word. Like, I live quite a high life or
I did. So, 3K a month. I'm used to
having thousands. So, you know, you
don't struggle, not struggle. You can't
struggle on three grand a month, which I
aren't going, but
like I'm not sure how you can struggle
on three grand a month, bro. Unless half
of it is obviously rent or you might
have kids. Do you have kids
or Well, for a single person, you would
not struggle on that
money unless you got cars and [ __ ]
you know, rent and [ __ ] which we
probably do to be fair. Most people do. Yeah. Yeah.
So, how many out Okay. So, how many
outgoings do you have a
month? How much outgoings do you have a
month? And you got [ __ ] really living
off 300 quid a
month. Barely living off
300 [ __ ] pound a month. Yeah. That's self
projection. I've not got a single pot to
piss in. That's
selfjection. I've not got a single pot to piss
in. Oh, you wish, man. You wish. I've
not got a single pot to [ __ ] piss
in. Yeah, bro. That's why I spent over60
today. Barbecue food.
I spent about [ __ ] I spent about
1,500, 1,500, bro. You just I spent
about £150 today. Yeah, you're talking
about yourself. Not a potent. That's
your That's your own life you're talking
about. You're confused,
lad. Yeah, man. I know what you mean.
Yeah. Yeah. I only I only have about 150
going out of free grand, Tony.
I've only got about 150 to pay
out and then it's
mine. But obviously if you go out
drinking and [ __ ] it
goes. Yeah. You can you can hardly save.
Yeah. You need to live with your parents,
buddy. That's the only way you can save
unless you're on like [ __ ] 10 grand a month. Yeah.
What? Oh, wow.
Yeah, sorry about that. Yeah.
Oh, these people in here are self projectors, lad. proper self
projectors. I got a pop to
piston [ __ ] elves.
Yeah, I got a nice barbecue video coming up tomorrow.
Slim. Good old barbecue video. Yeah,
lad. Some money's gone into it. All right. Yeah,
that's Yeah, you're going to see it tomorrow.
How much money do you get a month, Slim?
Please don't tell me it's
£300. We was talking about how much money we get.
Yeah, I get 3K. He said he gets 3K.
Yeah, but I'm I'm so used to 3K a month
now. It's not even like it's anything
because I'm so used to
it. And I've only got about £150 out
going. But I'm so used to it. I feel
like I'm so used to that money now. It
doesn't even feel like anything special.
which is quite a lot, you know, three
[ __ ] grand a month for doing [ __ ] nothing. But,
uh, doesn't seem like anything
special. I'm used to
it. See, I'm used to it, you see.
So, what happens, mate? Yeah.
because I've lived a very high life, you see. So that's it.
Yeah. Yeah. It is impossible.
Even £1,000 is is [ __ ] a month. Pin it
slim. What do you think about
£1,000? Say £1,000, but you got no
outgoings. It's [ __ ] in it. I mean, it's
a good start to to find other ways to
make money. I guess £1,000 a month is
okay to start finding other ways to make money.
I get 3K a month and I basically don't
have any outgoings,
Tony. And I feel my money goes as
well. I was able to save
£1,000 this month. But
uh even when you don't have any
outgoings, when you live a high life,
Tony, you get used to any amount that you get. You
know, I I have no I basically have no
outgoings and I get 3K a month and it
still seems to not all go like you don't
you not skid obviously but it still
seems to sort of in London
vanish cuz I used to have thousands and
thousands so I'm used to that high life.
So yeah, so if you had a grand a month
and you don't have that, you don't have
any outgoings, then you can turn it into
ways to make money. So it's not the
worst. You wouldn't be able to go out
drinking every week or go on holiday,
but you'd still
survive. You'd still survive on the
ground a month. You'd still
survive. It's not the bad. It's not the
worst. Yeah, I had a today, lad.
Yeah, I had a nice uh I had a mad dress
today. I spent £150
today. Um well, last year, bro, I had
thousands. I was going out every
week. [ __ ] I was spending £700 on
dates, always winning the money back. I
went to a shopping center, spent 1,200 quid.
[ __ ] that's the high life, bro. I was
living it on going to restaurants almost every day.
So three grand is a lot [ __ ] a month
if you have basically no votings.
But it don't seem It seems like I'm used to it. So yeah,
yeah. I was getting literally with loads
of women last year as well. I had loads
of women last year, but more than I did
this year as well. Quite a good life, bro.
Yeah. Yep. That's it, bro. you know.
Yep. So, you going on holiday this year,
Tony? I'm speaking to this woman in New
York, and if she's serious, I'll go over
there and just stay with
her. She's in her 50s, like, well, early
50s, but it's better than staying [ __ ] here.
I can try and get some more [ __ ] when
I'm over there, I
guess. I don't know. I really want to go
to Asia, though,
man. I booked Thailand for 7 weeks. I
really wanted to go Asia.
So, yeah. How much did it cost?
cost? Yeah, my friend was saying it's
[ __ ] now. It's becoming westernized.
Like the women are kind of becoming
[ __ ] Yeah. How much did it come to the Cypress holiday?
Yeah. I bet you can't afford America
though, can you, Tony? Could you afford
to go to America,
Slim? I can't afford it again, but it'd
be it'd be a challenge. I could do it.
But it'd be a challenge because you're
talking about four or five grand for one person. So
yeah. So yeah, it's it is
expensive. Yeah, America is
expensive. Used to live in America.
£1,800. I assume you paid it off, right?
I assume you paid the holiday off though,
right? I'm guessing you obviously paid it off.
Yeah. Well, I booked to go to [ __ ]
Boston and it was
£2,000 for the flight and the
hotel. flight hotel and then by the time
you've done your spending money for
Yeah. You're talking about four grand,
four or five
grand. You're talking about Yeah. And
that's one person for a week. So if the
flight to the hotel is two grand, let's
say you give yourself two grand spending
money, that's four grand done for one person.
So yeah, it's super expensive.
No, I mean, did you pay it off bit by bit?
Yeah. I mean, did you pay it off bit by
bit by bit? That's what I
meant. Yeah, it's expensive, man.
But surprisingly if you go in Miami it's
a lot cheaper.
So yeah the tipping
culture that's the thing. Yeah.
Okay. Have you been Have you been to
Amsterdam? Have you been to Amsterdam,
lad? I've been to
Amsterdam. I went to Amsterdam by
myself. Slim. Do you remember them? Remember that
day? Went to Amsterdam all by myself.
Yeah, quite remember this. I remember
banging a couple of escorts, smoking
weed, and then coming
back. Oh, how brave was I going by myself?
E, I can't believe I actually went by myself. Yeah.
Sounds about right,
lad. Yeah, I went to Amsterdam by myself
about 3 years
ago. I was a crazy [ __ ] back
then. Crazy crazy [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm so brave. Oh.
Oh. Um, no. It's a [ __ ] bro. Full of
rats. It's just like, it's just like
England. Tony will will tell you this as well. Um, Thailand.
because Whoa. No, no, no,
no. Thailand and
Japan cuz Thailand the culture just looks so
good. And Thailand because I don't like
westernized women because they're all stuck up
[ __ ] I'd say Thailand. Thailand
Japan. Thailand and Japan.
Deer and [ __ ] Sony comes from Japan as well.
So it looks so
mad different, you know? So I'd say
Japan, maybe New
Zealand. If you're talking about dream destinations,
just going Thailand, Tony are not here
and I've got a boyfriend. Not dealing
with stuck up women being treated how a
man should be [Music]
treated. Nah, nothing's worse than
British women, mate. Nothing's worse than British
women. Asian women are lovely, mate. You
get them here as well. They're nothing
like British women. British women and
American women are the worst. But yeah,
Japan, Japan, New Zealand,
maybe. I'd love to go Japan, bro.
It just the culture just I've seen stuff
about it, you know. It's like I'd love to go
there to stay in a hotel. It just seem
bad, unreal, you
know. But it's very
expensive. Trying to think where
else. Brazil would be okay as well
because the women there
are a bit
different. I can't stand westernized
women. Yeah, I'd love to go
Japan. Australia it just wouldn't be
worth the travel because they're just
it's just the same as English people.
Yeah, but they're easier, bro. Here,
Tony, you can't even speak to a woman
without her pretending she's got a
boyfriend. What do you think he'd say? I don't [ __ ]
know. See, America's not a dream destination.
greasy. I'm trying to think where else.
Um, somewhere else.
Stephanie, maybe Miami. Maybe
British women are
easy. Good one, bro. That's the funniest
joke I've heard all year, Tony. Yeah.
Yeah. When you approach British women,
they pretend they got
boyfriends. When you get their numbers,
they don't reply or stop replying or
they ghost you. Yeah. It's so easy, isn't
it? Yeah. They're so easy, isn't
it? Yeah. Yeah. They don't pretend they
got boyfriends or nothing, is it? Nah,
bro. Oh, yeah. Mexico as well. That's another one. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Mexico. That's another
one. Maybe Miami, too.
even though I said not America, but Miami looks
good. I think New Zealand looks
good, bro. Tony, listen, bro. They're
just not interested in this
country, you know? I I know more than
anyone. I've tried with women in this
country and they're just [ __ ] [ __ ]
which is exactly why I'm going
Thailand. Nah, they're just
[ __ ] I don't I can't be bothered
talking about it, bro. I'm done with
them here anyways, so I don't really care.
No, I I can't be bothered talking about it,
bro. The barbecue's tomorrow.
Well, it'll be better than hearing and
I've got a boyfriend, mate. It'll be
better than hit with stuck up
[ __ ] that pretend they got a
boyfriend. Yeah, it be better than hearing
that. And I think it would just be a
nice thing to say that you've gone Asia.
What do you think, Bee? You're just
saying that you've gone to Asia.
Nah, Timmy's not invited, mate. He's a
troublemaker. I told you this,
buddy. Oh, [ __ ]
hell. The nest to
call. No, I don't like they're just
[ __ ] in this in this country,
Tony. But just being able to say you've
gone Asia. I'd rather go Asian America.
I actually would rather go Asian and
America, you know. I I think I just
would to say you've gone Asia and Yeah,
I' I'd rather Yeah, I I' I'd choose Asia
and I used to be obsessed with America.
I want to go
America when I'm older. But nah, the
women are terrible in America. Trust me,
I've met them here. You get Americans
here, they're just they're not nice. I
just don't like American people as well.
So, I'm going to Thailand in seven
weeks. Well, six weeks
now. Nah, Asian women are completely different,
bro. It's just so so different. Trust me.
So, I don't like I just don't like American
people, you know? That's it.
I'm sure Greavves you can um agree with
me on this
one. It's very
rare. I'm going
Bangkok. It's like you greasy. Would you
rather go America or Thailand? You'd pick Thailand? Yeah.
Yeah. Pick somewhere L J's never been
to. Nah. What's in America? There's
nothing in America for
you. There's nothing in America for you,
Grezy. The only mad thing is if you go
to America Yeah. like New
York, you'll wear [ __ ]
You're where Tom and Jerry was made.
You're where Friends was made. You're
where Chucky was
made. It's mad. Like you go six hours on
a plane. Yeah. 6 and 1 half hours on a
plane and you're basically where everything was
made. Does that seem mad to you,
Greasy? Yeah. But McDonald's is
[ __ ] McDonald's is [ __ ] bro. And
there's better McDonald's.
You do realize America don't have the
best KFC and McDonald's. You do realize
that? Yeah. They have a Simpsons um in
uh in Florida. They have in in the
Universal Studios they have a Simpsons
thing. Yeah, I know he is. Yeah. Yeah. They've got
a they've got a
uh but you know McDonald's even though
it's American and KFC is American, it's
not the best in America. You do realize
that? And yeah, I'm not tasting it
there. But bro, I know this stuff. It's
the best in like [ __ ]
Germany. [ __ ] Where's the other one?
Germany. There's other bro. I remember I
went to be I went to Burger King in
Belgium and it was next level nice. Way
better than here. Jamaica. I think KFC
is the best in Jamaica actually. Say
that. That's the
one. Have you ever been to um Thailand
as Have you ever been to Asia?
But yeah, the best KFC is in Jamaica
from what I
hear. Yeah, Jamaica, bro. It's not
America. Even though Even though America made
it, my mom said she'd never go America
ever. She said it's a fish's country.
Yeah, that's good enough. Right. But
would you like to go Asian
Daz? Even if it was just Japan, it
wouldn't even need to be
Thailand. Even Japan, China, just
anywhere you could save in
Asia. [ __ ] hell,
bro. Yeah, Daz has got loads of money,
bro, to be doing that [ __ ] I remember I
went Liverpool once about three years ago,
bro. I went to the lobster pot. It was
[ __ ] stinky, bro. I was staying in
the hotel by the sea and across the sea
is the rural. It cost me £26 for the
night. £26 for the [ __ ] night,
bro. Imagine that.
That's the only time I've ever been.
Probably be the last time I ever go as well.
Yeah. Look at this. How much is this?
This is what Timmy put up. If I was to
play the money game, bro, a lot of
people would be getting [ __ ] owned.
A lot of people would be getting owned,
mate, if I [ __ ] start playing the money game.
Yeah, they be getting owned, lad.
Me and Greez, we can go to Florida
together and see all the little
characters. All the little characters, can't
we? That'll be sweet,
mate. I want to see Mickey Mouse. Yeah.
You should go abroad, man. You're the
same age as me. You've never been abroad.
Yeah. Should give it a go, man. Give it
a try. You might like
it. Start saving your [ __ ] pennies, eh?
you're going to end up like thingy. He's
just gone to Amsterdam. And I'm thinking
that's mad. I done that seven years
before then. It's mad to think they're
seven years late cuz I done this seven
years ago. Going [ __ ] Amsterdam. I
went Belgium. I done that seven years before
then. That's actually a madness, isn't it?
But I guess some people don't have the
money, some people are
scared, you know, like some people don't
interest. But it should it should
interest you to want to try it once, you
know, and see if it is your thing. Yeah. Bless
you. Bless you though. Scott, bless you Grezy, bless
you. USA is he came all the way here to get [ __ ]
Greavesy and I said to that damn well
the dick must be bad over there bro for
somebody to take it I'm I'm cheeky on I
know though Gregy I'm cheeky I said the
dick must be bad over there man for
somebody to take it upon themselves to
want to come to a foreign country to get
some to get some foreign dick the dick
must be not hitting it right over there
bro I was I was [ __ ] I I Just being
cheeky, weren't I, Greasy?
Cheeky. I'm [ __ ] cheeky, aren't I?
Greasy. You love me. Really, bro? It
So, Grezy, who who was the root cause of it
all? All of this
[ __ ] Griezy, who was the root cause of it all? King the Rifter.
Oh, imagine Kingdom
Rifter. It's Timmy's, bro. It's
Timmy's. Yeah, Daz. It's
Timmy's. Daz, what do you reckon will
happen if I go out Saturday
approaching? Do you reckon I'll pull or
what? What do you reckon they'll
say? Greasy loves King.
Yeah, I can get out 2K now if I want.
Yeah, I get about 2K if I want, bro. Right about now. No
problem. What do you think will happen,
Dad, if I go out approaching on Saturday?
Yeah, I get about 3k a month, bro. But
I've been saving a lot,
so I've already been out drinking and
[ __ ] so I don't gamble no more, bro.
So yeah, I don't gamble now.
So you reckon I'll pull if I go out Saturday?
Daz. You reckon I'll
pull? Daz is a pulling expert. Do you
reckon I'll pull
Greavvesy? I need to start a work soon,
Greavvesy. I'm not even joking,
mate. I tell you the ins and outs, bro.
If it was a normal
community, wear a nice t-shirt you might
pull. Worth a wall.
Worth a while, mate. Worth. Yeah, I've
got I've got a uh t-shirt. I got a
uh your t-shirt, Dad. And I went out in
it two weeks ago. Do you remember
Grezy? I think Grezy was watching the
live stream. Actually, they said they had
boyfriends. Dad, I was wearing my nice after shave, too. Yeah.
Yeah, I stopped gambling, Dad, cuz
uh let's see. It's in the wardrobe,
bro. I'll show you when I go out again.
But yeah, I stopped gambling cuz it's
like uh it's a waste of life. It's a
waste of money and you always lose in the end.
So, and it's causing too many mood
swings and [ __ ] And somebody like me
shouldn't be like somebody like me
shouldn't be gambling if you don't like
losing stress. And yeah, it's just a
waste of life. But I just stop,
bro. Yeah. Every day, bro. And I've
quit. Like I I literally don't do it
anymore. And he does it every
day. Every day, bro.
Yeah. What's the most you've ever lost gambling,
Daz? I used to always go drinking, Daz,
and then go come back and then gamble
online, do like 200 pound
spins. I was [ __ ] crazy about back then,
bro. Crazy [ __ ] I
was the most I ever lost was
2K. I lost two grand before.
Yeah. Yeah. You hate it. Yeah. [ __ ] I
don't do it anymore.
No, I met him once and then the second
time he come to
London. Yeah, gambling's a mug's game,
bro. I remember I approached this woman
in the club, Greavvesy. She says, "What do you
prefer, B or boobs?" I said, "I like
boobs." And then we started making out.
Greasy and I started touching
her. Yeah. Monty man wanted me for
backup. I'm not backing him up, bro.
He's a snake. He's a snake. Natalie G's
snake. They're all snakes in this community,
Daz. Except Greavesy. An unworthy
clock. I like Grievy. He's a pretty good
[ __ ] if you ask me.
Yeah. Yeah. Gambling's not worth it.
Antman's on it bad again, but I just
don't see it as worth it to
me. See, I can stop [ __ ] if I really
want to stop
[ __ ] And I need to be saving now.
Anyways, I'm going to tell you why, but yeah.
Yeah, Greavves is obsessed with women. I
think Greavves is obsessed with women as
well. Are you obsessed with women, Greavvesy? Yeah.
So, should have 3K. I think I should
have like three
Just savings. Hey, Grezy. Just savings. Yes,
Timy's. Yes, Timmy's bro. Timmy says he
gets about £800 a month and it's not bad.
on. Well, I'll be going back at some
I'll be going back down to that money at
some point. About a grand a month
probably. I'll probably be back to that,
but I'll just have
to work or something. I don't know. I'll
make money somehow. box.
Yeah, you really have to budget to
save, you know. You really have to budget to
save. But it doesn't really matter. It's
money. No matter what money you get,
money is money to an extent. [ __ ] not
300 pound a month, sir. Not 300 [ __ ]
pound a month.
Yeah, I had 5.7K in cash last year. I
went in a casino with 150 and I won four
grand. It was on a
Wednesday. I hit a multiplier on 11.
I've had I've had about 5.7K in
cash. A lot of it was winnings and [ __ ] Yeah.
I spent it on clothes, more gambling, dates, restaurants.
Oh yeah. I went in one night when I was
coming home drinking 150 in a casino.
Got it to four grand, bro. I just had
four grand in cash. It was the new 50
notes. It was good,
man. Yeah. I think the most I've had is
maybe seven grand, maybe.
Yeah. How much do you think is a lot?
Anything past about 1,500 in
it? Anything past 1,500 is a lot in
it? I think so. Yeah.
What do you think? Yeah. [Music]
Yeah, I had about five grand, but spent
it, bro. I had a good year last year.
That's gambling, spending money, women,
[ __ ] I was living a high
life. The high life, matey. But
um do you know any ways to make money,
Daz? Do you know any good ways to make
money? Nah, there's no ways to make
money, bro. You either win it or you save
it. There's no ways to make money.
Nah. Yeah, but if you get caught, you
get done for it and you go you get years in
prison. There was this thing on. Have
you ever watched 20,000 police custody? Custody,
Daz, you ever watch 20,000 hours in
police custody? I'm sure you've seen it,
right? I never do that. I don't want to
go to prison. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, there was this guy, man. He he was
downloading child porn and they went to
his uh house. He had
£250,000 under the bed, cocaine,
everything, mate. They took
everything. He got six years in
prison. Lost everything, mate. All that
money, all them
drugs. [ __ ] that. [ __ ] that, bro.
He had he had it all under the bed. I'm
sure you've seen
it. That's [ __ ] nuts, bro. So when
you come out, you're coming out with
nothing. No, it's called um No, it's not
a new one. It's a few years old
actually. All cuz he downloaded child
porn. If he didn't download child porn
and they would have went on his door and
they would have found all the
drugs like a drug house and that in it
[ __ ] madness mate and that must have
been all the money. 250k it must have
been all the money in it. Yeah. Under
bed. You should have saw his face mate
when they when they caught
him. [ __ ] you hell. Yeah.
250 in the bed.
Yeah, I can probably link you it want to
watch it. And let me send you
it. It was 250 under the bed,
bro. Let me get
Yeah, you need to skip a little bit. Not
the first case. You need to watch the
second one. One sec. Just watch all of
it and come back.
I think I want to link it to you now. Hold
on. I think that's
it. Yeah, there you go. [ __ ] that,
bro. So you come out of prison in three
years and then you got
nothing. Yeah, he
is. He [ __ ] is, bro.
Yeah. I couldn't go to Greavves. I'd
cry. I'd want my mama and my
Coca-Cola. I'd want my
mama and my
Coca-Cola. Greasy. I'd
cry. Ah, my [ __ ] leg is itching me, bro.
[ __ ] Oh man, I'm itchy.
[ __ ] An itch that can't be scratched. Literally, bro.
Yeah, my mommy would have to come and visit me.
Yeah, Daz is watching that. Yeah.
There we go.
All these [ __ ] things,
bro. Bring your little
mates. One sec. What? Sir, Yeah.
I'm going sleep, right? See you
later. Yeah. See you later.