[Laughter]
How do people on Reddit say they're
going to give you advice then they don't
[ __ ] block you? I don't get
that. Doesn't even make any sense. So
they just [ __ ] block
you. Just randomly blocked you. You can
see when they blocked you as well. Did
their comments don't show up. [Music]
Yeah, it would be.
Yeah, man. And it's going to be busy
today. It's back holiday Monday. Some
money early as well. Yeah, I can't be bothered.
randomly go from Come
on. It's funny, man.
Funny. I could go out today if I wanted. I can
go. But there's no
point. What would be the actual point? None whatsoever. Yeah.
[ __ ] How's life? Um, well, I've saved a
lot of money,
so yeah, I had a barbecue yesterday. It
was good. Yes, bank holiday Monday.
Won't be out today and I won't be out
tomorrow. I think I actually meant it
when I said I give up in this country. I
actually think I fully meant it, bro.
Definitely. I think so, man.
Yeah, man. I think I meant
it. You'll be busy today and tomorrow
Sunday. You'll be busy for three days.
I'm just chilling, man. I can't be
bothered with this country
anymore. So, I'm just going to stay stay
in maybe for a walk. I won't be going out drinking.
going out spend money on a haircut just
to hear I've got a boyfriend. Oh
god. [ __ ] that. It's pointless. It's
literally pointless. Oh yeah, I could go
out today. Yeah, I can go out tomorrow
and still save money. Go out every week.
Still make money. But there's just no
point in even going out.
There's just no point in even going out talking to
anyone. Ah, long
story. Yeah, long
story. But yeah, I had a barbecue
yesterday, had some ice
cream, play some
Simpsons, you know. And if I went out
today, that means I have to go to the
barber shop, sit on the chair for an
hour, spend like
£40. This is [ __ ] pointless, isn't
it? It's just pointless. Pointless. Pointless. Yeah.
How many I've Got a boyfriend do you
reckon you'll get today if you go out? A
lot. You get a lot of I've got a boyfriends.
Yeah. A lot of effort,
bro. And if I went out today, I'd be out
tomorrow as well cuz she got haircut.
So, no point.
No, there's no point,
mate. If you was going to meet someone,
you would have met someone by now in this country. So,
yeah. And this woman on Reddit, right,
she says, "Oh, yeah, she's going to give
me advice." I told her some stuff and
then she just blocked me. So, I said,
"Why tell me you're going to give me
advice and then just randomly block me?" doesn't make
sense. They do on Reddit and then they
just randomly block you and you can see
where they blocked you as
well. So no, man. It
varies three to about
seven. But it's pointless anyways
because it doesn't go
anywhere. Numbers don't mean anything.
Dating in this country is just a [ __ ]
huge waste of
time. Huge waste of
time. Really is sick of him, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Three to about seven numbers, I
think. And they only reply to negativity
as well. Red
flag. That's a [ __ ] red flag that
they um reply to negativity in it, Shifty.
Or you go on a date with somebody and
they'll claim they're not feeling it or
something will happen. Something will
happen. Something negative will
happen. Definitely something negative will happen. No, no,
no. Even if people donated, buddy, I
still wouldn't go
out. Still wouldn't go out.
pointless. And like I said, I have to
get my haircut. So, yeah. Yeah.
That's where we're at, man. That's where we are
at. Yeah, we busy today and we busy tomorrow.
You think we should go out and give it a whirl?
Nah, I need to rest my foot a bit more
as well to be fair. Flareing up again.
there was an actual point in going out,
then I would understand it. But I know
exactly what's going to
happen. I know exactly what will happen.
I've got a boyfriend. I've got a
boyfriend. I know it. I [ __ ] know, bro.
I know it, bro. I know it. [Music]
[ __ ] Finally decide what to do.
If I went out today, I'd have to go out
to buy as
well. We're talking spending money.
I'm not going to the barbers. So that's
long. I'm not going to no [ __ ]
barbers, bro. That is long.
I don't know what to
do. Nice to have a repair, but
Just trying to figure something to do today.
No one come. I'm just trying to think
what to do today. I got some money
early. I don't really want to go out,
but I have nothing better to do and I
don't really want to get my haircut cuz
it's long. Sat on a chair for an hour
spending money. Don't know if I can be
annoyed with all that today,
bro. And if I went out today, I'd have
to go out tomorrow. So, bank holiday and all that.
So, yeah, the barbecue was nice.
No one came
mate but people I already know.
So I just don't see there being no point in going
out. I just see it as a complete waste of
time. It's going to be
busy. Going to be busy today, tomorrow, and
Sunday. But there's no point because
it's just going to be the same old
And then your mental health is going to
be affected by it by the bad experiences.
So yeah, I could go to Blackpool today
if I really wanted to. I could actually
go to Blackpool today if I wanted to.
Got the time, got the
money. But I did I don't really want to
waste money in this country. See, when
you go out in London, you're only
spending what on beer? 50 to 80.
Obviously, you get your haircut, but I
mean that's just personal hygiene, but
you know, you go to Blackpool, you're
going to be spending a couple hundred
pound. You don't want to be spending a
couple hundred pound in this country. I
spend the bare minimum in this country
now. Why do you think I have so much
money? I was able to save
loads because you can't justify spending
that kind of money in this
country. So, but I could go that I could
go anywhere today if I wanted to.
Yep. But there's no
point. Yeah, I'm not going to do that
today. I'm going [ __ ] Thailand in six
weeks. I'm going Thailand in six weeks.
Well, yeah, if you go in London, you're
only spending about 60 to 80 quid, so
you can sort of justify it. But you can't justify spending, you
know, maybe I won't go out this week.
Maybe I'll go out next week. I don't
know. It's not about the money. It's
just about the wasting
time. So long away. Because I booked it in
advance. like a normal person does. So,
yeah, I'm staying for two
weeks. Yeah, two
weeks. Yeah, I was thinking of going to
Springfield, Joe, and ripping Bart
Simpson's head off in front of his mama,
Marge. Yeah, I was thinking of doing that.
Yeah, I don't even uh I don't even gamble
anymore. I don't gamble anymore. I don't
drink anymore. I just have fun in the
yard. I mean, I can go out today and
tomorrow basically lose
nothing. But it's just a but time is
just a waste of time. That's the only
thing you're losing because it is a
waste of time. Cuz it is going to be the
same old [ __ ] And no woman's going to
prove you that they're different. So
there's there's literally no point in even
trying. They've already shown what
they're about time and time again,
replying to negative messages, which
your your what you said, Joe, don't make
no sense. It's it's human in
instinct to reply to negative messages.
No, it isn't. Cuz if that was the case,
then YouTubers would be replying to
negativity. But they don't. They even
turn the comments off to stop people
writing negativity. So, that doesn't
really make a lot of
sense. They ignore positive messages and
ignore negative messages. That tells me
all I need to know. There's literally no
point in even going
out. But it isn't
though. But it
isn't. Because if that was the case,
then why don't big YouTubers reply to
negativity? You know, why can they why
can they ignore negativity? Why can
people ignore negativity but them? Bro,
uh they're just
[ __ ] They're just [ __ ]
mate. That's what they are. Just
[ __ ] They've proven what they're
about. They've proven to be all the same.
So why what's the point in going out
talking to any of them? You know what
they're going to
say that they've got boyfriends when
they don't. So this doesn't make a lot of
sense to even want to try. You
know, got a way I can make money. Now
I'm not going to tell you what it is cuz
jealous grass is on here, but so it's
nothing to do with that. It's about the
whole waste of
time. That's boring, mate. I'm sad.
Yeah, it would anyone if anyone if
anyone had bad experiences like I did.
It's like the other day. Yeah. What was
wiring me up is how they were replying
trying to be clever. They were replying
trying to be smart. It's not the fact
that they replied. I said, "Oh, so you
reply to negative comments but you
messages but you ignore positive ones."
I swear to God, bro, if I had any one of
their addresses, I would have went on
their [ __ ] door, mate. I would have
went on their [ __ ] door, bro. I'm not
even joking. Don't message me back
trying to think you're intelligent.
Yeah. Like, who the [ __ ] do you think
are, right? They were trying to be
intelligent or victimizing themsel. You
know what I'm saying? It's lucky I
didn't have one of their addresses,
mate. Cuz I would have been getting
nicked. I'm not even joking, bro. It's [ __ ] annoying.
Yeah, it was pissing me off because you
wake up in the morning. Yeah. You look
on your phone, you don't expect
much. And then you having these You're
having these women thinking that they're
smart and they're not. That's what was annoying
me. That's what was [ __ ] annoying me
is who the [ __ ] do they think they
are. It's how it's actually how like two
of them were
replying trying to say, "Oh, landlord
shouldn't um be asking people." She was
trying to be clever. I said, "Listen,
yeah, I understand you, you know, you're
from York and from what I understand,
it's a nice area. Um, you know, you went
to university, but please stop trying to
act intelligent because it really
doesn't suit you." Can't stand people
that think they're more intelligent than
are. Drives me mad, bro. drives me [ __ ]
mad. And um and then the other one
pretending that they were going to reply and
Yeah. Yeah. They should reply to
negativity, don't they? It weren't even
abuse. It was
negativity. You know what I'm saying? It wasn't
Yeah. Obviously, I didn't write abuse
cuz you got to be careful what you say
nowadays. Who's the piece of got nothing
better to do than to go people's doors for
um petty [ __ ] that people say
online have to be very careful. Oh, I
got banned on Instagram for seven days.
Um Oh, I didn't I forgot to tell you
that. Yeah, yesterday I wrote Oh, I
wrote to this woman, women are evil, and
I got banned for that. I was like, bro,
it's going to get to a point now. Yeah.
where you're not even allowed a different opinion, you
know. [ __ ] it
hell. No, no, no, no, no. Joe, I think
you got it the other way around. They
think that the the men that they argue
with can't be more intelligent than
them, and that's why they start [ __ ]
that they can't finish. Have you noticed
that these women will start stuff, but
they'll either a play victim or b just
run away when they've lost the argument?
That's actually you're actually meant to
be saying it to them.
So there are more pe people that more
intelligent than me, but it would take
uh it would take
some some special kind of person. But I
don't act like I'm intelligent because
I'm not a [ __ ] But you know, I I
can bring it out of me if I want to. You
know what I'm saying? So that's
it. So yeah.
Um, and you get evil women like Morgan
that can just get in a relationship. But
that was like only 5% of why I gave up.
That I'd already gave up anyways. But
it's like you're playing a game that's
just rigged against you. It's just literally
pointless. Pointless. Really is
pointless, mate. you
know, and it doesn't dictate my mood and
it's the it's the ghosting and the way
and the and the time wasting dates. It's
not even the boyfriend. Yeah. Like I
said in the video, it's not even it's
not even that. It's the whole like them
wasting your time on purpose. That's
what pisses me off. That's what gets me [ __ ]
mad, you know? Especially when you got a
[ __ ] foot injury and you've had to
make it to that [ __ ] date.
I was dumb from that Thursday. Anyways,
to be fair, I just stayed out cuz I was out.
So, it's not, like I said, it's not
really that I've got a boyfriend. It's
not even just that. That's just minor,
bro. They go on dates to waste time.
They ghost on
purpose. That's the thing that annoys
me. That's the thing that really annoys So
yeah, cuz I hadn't been on a date for so
long, so I just forgot how bad it really is.
So that's why I had to give up gambling,
Joe. I told you I gave up, bro. And I
was being deadly serious when I told you
I give up because of
the feeling guilty, losing money. I
don't like losing. It's a waste of time. You
know, we can't be positive, bro. Not
when it's to do with women. We can't be
positive. How can you be positive when
all you see is negative? Eminem done.
Uhoh. I've got lots of money again.
Yay. Yay. Hey,
it's good, isn't
it? I could play the money game with
these people and
win. Yo, take you lost a lot of money.
Yeah. I just like the thing that was
doing it for me is that I'd get these mood
swings then I'd lose the money and I
feel guilty and I think oh well like
there's people in your family, you know,
£150, £200 a lot to them. You've just
lost it. Um, it fuels negativity and
it's just a waste of
time. So that's why I just gave up
basically. Got money in my account right
now. I can play online roulette anytime
want. Anytime I want, but
nah. Antman's gone bad on it
again. Yeah, I don't think I'll ever do
it again. Maybe just a football. But
yeah. Yeah. So why are you not why are
you giving up until the football season again
then? Yeah. But it's not paid for really
good days and all stuff because overall
you always you always lose.
So, say for example, I won four grand, I
would lose six grand a month after.
So, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. You're
forgetting, bro. You lose more overall.
You lose in the long run. So, today's
wins is tomorrow's losses. Even though
you might have won, that's paid for
stuff, you've gained that money
back. So, yeah, you're always at an L.
You're always at an
L. Trust me, you can save. And
everything that you got, you would have
if you just saved. Trust me, mate. Trust
me. Cuz you're always your overall
always going to be
down. So that doesn't even make any
sense unless you won like a [ __ ]
million pound or
something. Yeah. Yeah. That's like I
think that's what I can't you can't play
a fair game of roulette. If I could play
roulette, maybe I could I'd
reconsider. Yeah, I can't even play a
fair game of [ __ ] roulette.
So yeah, can't get into any casinos. So
yeah, this woman on Reddit said she was
going to give me advice, then she
randomly blocked me. John, don't know
why these people on Reddit just randomly
block people when they said they were
going to give advice.
Strange. [ __ ] strange,
eh? Yeah, that's what I'm saying. So
even if you won money today and it's
paid for something, you will then be
lose all your money next month and then
be scared a lot of people. So you all
you would always lose. You always you
So it's like Antman, he doesn't get as
much money as me and he was winning
winning and then two weeks ago he lost
three grand. Obviously three grand's a
lot to him, which a lot to anyone, but
he doesn't just get three grand out of
that. So that was awful from winning
because he had won and one and one. He
was putting like a grind on the
football, all sorts. So that's what I
mean by you always lose. So
yeah, that's it.
If you don't find Chevo attractive, Joe,
you're [ __ ] gay, lad. Oh [ __ ] I
shouldn't say gay. Oh, I got I'm going
to have piece on my door.
[ __ ] Oh yeah, in that way. Yeah, in
that way. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. In
that way. Yeah, I get what you
mean. you would have knew unless you had
saved because you couldn't justify.
Yeah. But overall, overall it's a
negative because you're always losing in
the end. The mood swings. It's a waste
of time. There's just no point doing
it. I actually shouldn't even say gay to
be honest. Probably get that be enough
to get you nicked to be
fair. Yeah. You don't say stuff on
social media anymore, matey. Get
yourself nicked. end up in court.
Yeah. Well, there's a few ways to
replace the bug buzz. You can go to the
gym, you go cinema,
um you can have barbecues. I have
barbecue with my friends.
So, this escort kept pestering me
um the past couple of days. She said,
"Oh, come come
come." And I was like, "Oh, she wants
dick and she wants money." So I just
went there to shut her up and run my
dick down her throat. I was like,
"What's 80 quid?" You know, we saved up
all this money. So what's £80? You
know, can we not say little whiffer?
Huh? What are you talking
about, mate? I got banned on Instagram
for saying women are evil, which is not
even a hate crime. That's just a [ __ ]
opinion. But that got me banned for seven days.
Wow. Crazy, is it?
[ __ ] system is [ __ ] backwards in
it. I was watching that 24 hours in
police custody again yesterday where
that guy protected his house and he's
the one that went to
prison from them burglars and I said and
then he was like, "Oh yeah, they ran
away." Yeah, they ran away but they
could have come back. They tried to
burgle the guy's house. Yes, they ran
away but they could have come back in
their shield and then he's the one that
went prison. It's so backwards, isn't
it? It's so [ __ ] backwards. This the
system is is backwards in this country.
I'm telling you, bro. It really
is. The police was like, "Oh, yeah. They
run away, so there's no threat." Yeah,
but what if they come
back? They could have easily just come
back. Just cuz they've run, it doesn't
mean they're not going to come back. You
know what I'm
saying? That's [ __ ] up, bro.
They go after the wrong people. I'm
having to follow up with this police
report. I followed it up um few days ago
and the police called me
again. So I'm having to [ __ ] be on
their case every [ __ ]
week. I'm having to follow up with these
police reports for [ __ ] sake, Joe. But
it's worth it, bro. It amount of times
these people on here has called the
police and we can't deny that it's entertaining.
Like people used to say it's
entertaining. Okay, fine. But don't cry
when it happens to you. You know, that's
all we we don't want is you cry when it
happens to you and you people start getting
arrested, you know. That's also
entertaining. So don't start crying when
it happens to you. You know, fair is
fair. I found her email as
well. I said, "Oh, these people are
still harassing me. They're harassing
me. They're harassing me." You know how
do you think people don't post [ __ ]
about me anymore cuz they know I'm just
going to go to the police? Simple.
Yeah. Straight up, bro. Straight up. Go
to the [ __ ] police. I'd love to tell
you what jobs I can do now and stuff,
Joe, but we got too many grasses. Too
many grasses. Too many jealous grasses,
lad. Too many jealous grasses.
Too many glasses,
man. To myself,
e piss. Oh, [ __ ] hell. Too much
Coca-Cola. Nah, I can't, bro. Too many
Too many grasses on there.
The likes of [ __ ] red
[ __ ] The likes of red
[ __ ] Likes the grass on people. You
know what I'm talking
about. Too many grasses,
mate. It could
be. Could be, John. Could be. could be
right. That's a P. It's just peeing. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
hell. Such a clever whiffer. He's such a
clever whiffter. It's been so good since
moving out of ladies. I do see Laney and
I speak to Ly every day, but it's just nice
being by yourself, you
know. You know, I don't
know. I went there a few weeks ago for 3
days to rest my foot cuz I couldn't get
any peace. That's the last time. Oh,
mate. Kind of like this area better to
be honest. You don't get people in your business.
That's the problem where my mom lives is
everyone knows each other and they talk
they talk people's business.
So you can keep guessing, mate. I'm not
telling you what it
is cuz a red [ __ ] So
yeah, got £15 here.
money someone gave me towards
something. Got money coming from all angles now.
Yeah. But yeah, I just went with the
escort to shut her up cuz she kept
messaging me, "Oh, whenever I'm here, you don't
come." So I was, "Oh, [ __ ] it. I'll just
just go then." Is it?
Yeah. Well, he doesn't he doesn't
dictate um what I can say, but I dictate
what he can say. He will never tell me
where he is. And he cuz he knows better.
Cuz he knows better. He will never tell
me where he is. He will never tell
anyone on here where he is because he
knows better. He's a good little
boy. I've got him under my wing. And
there's no court order, you know.
There's no court order that stops you.
So, it's me actually stopping you, you
know. So, I'm actually controlling you
because you will never say ever where
you live. Same with All Night, Mike, cuz
you know better. You're a good little
boy. That's all I say back to them. When
they say that we control you, I say I
control you as well. You will never say
where you are and you can never say
where you are.
So that's how I control you because they
know if they do, I'm just going to go
there and go live and embarrass them.
And whenever they wherever they
um and whenever they try to come into a
live chat, they're just going to get
[ __ ] with. So So I control them in
many ways, trust me. Yeah. So
yeah, crazy, eh?
We don't really get many haters
anymore. I think a lot of these people
maybe died died of old
age. What do you think? Yeah.
Yeah. Still searching for these women
that are different. 27 years and
counting. It's like trying to find a
needle in a hay stack.
Can't find them on the street. Can't
find them in the clubs. Can't find them
in the pub. Where are these so different women?
Maybe a different country.
Yeah. Yeah. I don't know where they are,
bro. I don't think they exist.
You don't know all women, Joe. I said I
know [ __ ] more than you can. That's
what I used to [ __ ] say. I know more
than [ __ ] you. Cuz don't forget I've
got more life experience. What somebody
is doing that holiday, right, that it
took being 30 years of age to go on? I
was doing that when I was
23. So that's why I'm saying I've got
more life experience. I'd done that when
I was 23.
I'm going [ __ ] further [ __ ] field
now. Some people really are backwards,
bro. Really are
backwards. You remember I done that when
I was 20 [ __ ] three. Done that same
thing. But it's pretty [ __ ] to be
honest. Yeah. Same as It's just
basically England, isn't
it? Amsterdam is basically
England. What do you think, J? I think it's basically
Yeah. What do you think? I think it
is. Basically, is it's basically
England. It is really, isn't it? I don't
know if you ever been to Amsterdam, Joe.
I assume you haven't. But yeah, it's basically England
really [ __ ] Yeah, I done that when I
was 23. All by myself.
Joe, do you miss them
days? Do you miss them days, Joe?
Wonder what happened to that Somalian
woman, Joe? The
Somalian. Imagine I made a baby with
her. Baby Peter from
Somalia. Baby Peter from
Somaland. What a lovely site. Yeah.
There would be a lovely slight Yeah.
I can't believe she sucked my dick.
Yeah. Like [ __ ] three times and she
went to meet this guy. But I was telling
her to go. Like she wanted to stay in
bed with me, but I was like, "No, just
just go. Just go go go." So I could take
the cash and do a runner, Joe. You
know? Yeah. She [ __ ] like three
[ __ ] times. What the [ __ ] I said
I've got no sperm [Laughter]
left. I got no sperm left,
matey. [ __ ] hell, bro. Must be
cocaine. makes people horny. I didn't
think No, I don't think she took any
when she was with
me. Yeah, I kind of felt dodge being there,
Joe. You know, I don't like to be around
cocaine and stuff.
Dang. You know, it's quite kind of a
scary area. And then when she was
telling me about her brother that
randomly comes and pushes his way in and
beats up anyone that's with her, I was
like, "He better not [ __ ] come
today." [ __ ] hell, cuz I'll be out that
window. I was just thinking that the
whole time. I was like, "What the [ __ ]
No, mate." I said, "My luck. You'll
probably [ __ ] come
today. [ __ ] me.
Oh, you should leave Scott alone, dojo,
Joe. You should leave Scott alone. Leave
the old Syrian man
alone. Leave the old Syrian man
alone. Yeah. Yeah. How could I forget?
Yeah. Um, none of them, neither of them
can fight. He was telling me to come to
um, Birmingham, Joe. Um, um, Monty, and
I'm thinking I don't really want to cuz Natalie's a
snake. Um, cuz I've heard her talk [ __ ] about
me behind my back. So, why am I going to
[ __ ] go there?
Yeah, you'll notice that with 99% of the
people in this community, they're
snakes. Except from unworthy clock, he's
a he's a cool guy on Worthy Clock. Even
Ben's a snake that Ben Furvy, he didn't
snake me, but yeah, he's a snake. So,
the only one is on Worthy Clock I've
actually met on Worthy Clock. He's
actually he's actually a cool guy,
man. But um all of the rest of them,
they're all snakes. All of them are. All
are like I call that. You remember that Ricky
Millington? He used to come on here
trying to lick my ass. Then I'd catch
him, talk [ __ ] about me, trying to say
how it's not women, it's me. How would
you know that? You don't deal with women
in this day and age. So what the [ __ ]
would you know about [ __ ]
women? Nah, you wouldn't want to meet
Timmy, mate. Timmy's a [ __ ] N. Nah,
you wouldn't want to meet Timmy, mate.
No, no, no, no, no, no. I'd never be
seen with that clown. Even the first
time I met him, I was meant I was meant
to meet Mike and he just showed up. I
would never meet him, mate. He's
embarrassing. He is [ __ ] embarrassing, mate.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
go to meet
him. Could you imagine trying to cold
approach somebody when you're with him?
The likes of
him. I'd rather meet [ __ ] Tiger than
meet [ __ ] Timmy. But imagine in a pub
with him. How
embarrassing, you know? And he's like
rubbing the back of his [ __ ] head.
Yeah, he's he's sick and
twisted. I can't explain with him. He's
he he seems normal, but he's weird. He
does a lot of trolling behind the
scenes, and he's just he's just twisted.
He's just he's just sick and twisted.
There's no there's nothing else really
to say about him. He's just sick and
twisted. That's what he
is. I know. I've met him and I know what
he does. So I met him twice. He's just thick and twisted.
yeah. Yeah. I never done that to one of
the tenants, Joe. So I I wouldn't know,
man. I've never done that. I never done
that with one of the tenants a long time
ago. Nah, not me.
I've never done anything like that,
Joe. Nah, not me, mate. Not
me. Oh, he was sniffing her
knick-knacks. How weird was that? Sniffing her
knickknacks. What? Her knickknacks. Yeah. And
knickknacks. Yeah. I've never stiff
knickers. That's [ __ ]
weird. That's very weird,
lad. It wasn't my sisters. It was your
No, but it was
yours. I'm so
cheeky. No, it was your sisters, Joe.
Yeah, I'm so
cheeky. Joe, if I go out today and I
approach and I hear I've got a boyfriend
once, I'm never talking to
you. I'm never talking to you ever again.
boyfriend. They've all got
boyfriends. Yeah. Do you remember when
that man said that? Ah, they've all got
boyfriends. That's how it's
going. How's it going? And how's it
going? They've all got
boyfriends. Funny as [ __ ] mate. got.
Yeah. Nah. No, he's not. There's no
point me going out today because they're all in
relationships. It all of these women in
clubs have got boyfriends, Joe. All of
these women on the street have got
boyfriends. So, I don't why would I want
to bother um women that are in
relationships? Apparently, they've got
boyfriends even though they're in a club until
[ __ ] 7:00 in the morning. Why would I
want to bother people that are in
relationships? Yeah, I went on the
thingies. Uh he was trying to be clever
about Morgan. Maybe she's one of the
millions of women that are in
relationships that actually do have
boyfriends. I was like, we we still
doing this? Are we still doing this?
about the whole that do they really how
do you know they don't have boyfriends?
Are we really still doing this? Just
just just think common sense for a
moment? Like are we still doing this?
How do you know they don't have
boyfriends? Come on, man. You can't be that
naive. Joe, it's common
sense. It's common sense. How do we know
they ain't got boyfriends? because
they're in a club till [ __ ] 7:00 in the [ __ ]
morning. [ __ ] their partner's not
going to be happy about that if he
actually existed, which he doesn't. Come
on. They're [ __ ]
NPCs. These women are NPCs,
Joe. There's no point talking to a bunch of [ __ ]
NPCs, you know? non-playing characters.
Yeah. Doesn't matter what city you go
to, they're still going to say they got
boyfriends here. They're
NPCs. You don't know what that means, Joe? NPCs. Yeah.
NPC. Oh, here you go.
going to make a cop in a minute.
Yeah. Very funny.
I see these women showing off on Instagram,
Joe. Showing off their bodies on Instagram. They're
pathetic. These [ __ ] They're [ __ ] pathetic, lad.
What is wrong with that? B.
Yeah. I passed a criminal record check.
Yay! I passed the criminal record check.
Yay. I can make £100 a day easily, Joe.
If I wanted to easily easily easily matey
easily not be on a grand a month mate
don't want to be on a grand a month
matey grand a
[ __ ] hell. Grand a
month. You just get addicted to save
him. Soon as I've got food in my belly,
a cup of [ __ ] I can and listen to some music. I'm fine,
me. So, I used to think if I didn't go
out, Joe, I'd be missing
something, you know. But nowadays, I
know I'm not. I'm just missing make
believe that never with them that are
never with these
ladies. So many boyfriends,
but yet not one of them or ever with their boyfriends.
Makes you wonder, doesn't
it? Makes you wonder.
Anyways, I'll be back later.