Yeah. [Music]
Yeah, then I'm hungry or not. Yeah. best
day. Can't put a price on
estimating. Oh, no. You can't
Got people watch but no
comments. That's funny. That is
What's your takeaway? I don't want to
waste the money. I want to waste Yeah.
No. It makes it sound like I'm skint,
but I'm really not. But
Yeah. When did I last have a take
away? Was it yesterday? I had a
barbecue. I don't think it was the day
before. If it's been three days, I'll
get a takeaway. If it's not been three
days, then I'll get
um I just have some macaroni cheese or
something. Some microwave macaroni
cheese. It was two days
ago. How am I going out? Uh, what part
of I gave up in this country? Don't you
understand? I literally told you I gave
up for a minimum of six weeks and you're
asking me if I'm going
out. Did anyone come to my barbecue? Not from YouTube.
No. No. It's been two days. I can't get
a takeaway every two
days. No, I can have one tomorrow. Yeah,
it's bank holiday Monday. I got my money
early and I don't care. I'm not going
out. I told you I'm done for a minimum
of six weeks. I told you. I'm
done. It can be bank holiday what it
wants to be. I ain't going
nowhere. Isn't that right,
Grezy? I got a takeaway two days ago. I
guess I could get one,
but two days, haven't
it? What do you think,
Greezy? Two days. Every two
days. Nah, we'll get one tomorrow. [ __ ]
it. Yeah, get one tomorrow.
No, I don't really like Five
Guys. Yeah, it doesn't matter, bro. What
day it is, Monday, Tuesday,
Wednesday, bank holiday. It doesn't
really matter what it is, bro. They can
They're still going to say they got
boyfriends. It's still the same people out.
Yeah. I ain't going out today. I'm not
going out tomorrow. And I'm not going out Sunday. That's
it. No, you know what? I got McDonald's
yesterday. No, actually I did. Actually,
no. I got McDonald's yesterday. I can't
yesterday. I got a Philly steak burger.
Yeah. Yeah, it was yesterday cuz I was
hungry. We had a barbecue. Yeah.
cost me 30 [ __ ] [Music] pound 15.
Uh, I might just get a take
away. Yeah. I'm just going to order some
Indian food. [ __ ] it. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm just going to order some Indian
food. 15 as well.
So, should have a couple of thousand now,
Grezy. Couple of thousand saved in a
month. Hey, it's good, isn't
it? Haven't been out for a couple of weeks. So, that's
good. That's good.
Eh, it is the one for me, mate. It's the
one for me.
It is for me,
mate. And it clearly is for you because
you're on YouTube speaking to me. So, if
it wasn't that I quote one, you would be
out yourself. Isn't that right,
Greasy? No, I'm not talking to any of
them evil [ __ ] for at least 6 weeks.
There's no point me going out, Grezy.
There's no point. There's literally no
point me going out. I don't even think
it's to save the money because I can
still save money and go out. I just
There's just no point in going out. You
know, if anything was going to happen,
it would have happened by now. You're
going to have the same negative
experiences. So, what's the [ __ ]
point? You might as well just you might
as well just not do
nothing, you know? So,
Well, that's on you, bro. But is it? Me
and Greavves, you're
different. There's no right grieving. Me
and you are different.
Yeah. I got to order some food. Yeah.
One second. Give me two seconds.
I just ordered some
food. I do feel better. I do feel way
better. No, I'm going to Thailand to see
what it's like. I don't still want
women. If I still wanted women, I'd be
out now. I'd be out every week if I
still wanted women.
But I would be out every week in this
country because I'd still be able to
afford it and save if I wanted women.
That's how strongly I feel against them
that I didn't go out today or the [ __ ] I
didn't go out last week, didn't go out
the the week before
that. There's no point when they're all
the same. Why would you want something
that's all the same and the last person
was the same, the last person was the
same? So yeah, there is a I do feel a lot better.
No ghosting, no ignoring, no time
wasting, no narcissism. I feel way
better, man. Way [ __ ] better. No more mood
swings, no more mood swings, no more
problems. You remember the other day,
Greg, when I was all agging that when
they were replying um to the message,
trying to be funny. None of that now. No
mind [ __ ] Just peaceful. Just
peace. Why is that then? If women are
not negative, why is
that? See, I feel way
better. Way [ __ ]
better. And even if people don't want to
give up permanently, no one's saying
give up permanently, but you need to
give up for a long
time. A long time, bro. You You know, it's Yeah. Cuz
Yeah. You need a refresh.
could go out tomorrow if I wanted to.
Grezy. Got got a couple of K saved. Not
problem. Got nice clothes, but what's
the point? They're all the
same. All women are the [ __ ]
same. Yeah, I just ordered an Indian.
Like, so what's the point? [Music]
Yeah. How can you give up? um by not approaching
women. And it's not give up in quotation
marks, it's give up. I've literally said
give up. There's no quotation mark about
it. It's called give it
up. There's no quotation marks to it. It
is given up because you're not approaching. So,
no, you you you give up by not approaching
women. What the [ __ ]
Doesn't even make any sense what you
just said. You give up by not
approaching women and not going [ __ ] clubbing and So
yeah, mad how they only reply to
negativity as well. I think that's what
done it for me. There was probably a
chance that I would have went out this
week, but there's no point because they
only reply to negativity. Why would you
want to be associated with people that
can only reply to negativity,
Greavvesy, and ignore
positivity? That seems very backwards to
me, but each to their
own. Yeah, that seems very backwards to
me. They are normal nice messages and
reply to negative ones.
Strange. No, they wouldn't. No, they
[ __ ] wouldn't. No, they wouldn't. I
said women are evil. Yeah. Why don't you
just keep ignoring like you've been
doing? Why don't you
block? So, no. No. Even if you wrote
something else that was negative, they
would still they would still reply. Even
if it was something completely
different, like if you said, "Oh, I
[ __ ] can't stand
my reply. Anything that's negative, they
will reply to. It could be anything.
Trust me, any bit of drama, that's how
[ __ ] up and sick sick in the head they
are. Anything that's drama or anything
negative, they will reply to
it. Anything you can think of, they'll be
there. They'll be there, mate. But
normal nice messages, nah, they get
ignored, mate. They get [ __ ] ignored.
They get lost in the [ __ ] Mexico um
cartel. This as if you didn't even send them. So
yeah, and to be honest with you, bro,
women just make me sick.
Don't know about you, but they actually make me sick.
Yeah, don't know about you,
Greasy. [ __ ] make me sick. Evil
people. Yeah, I've got a cowing partner.
Myself. Yeah, myself.
I don't think I'll ever go on another date again.
Gez, I don't actually think I'll
ever go on another date again if someone
offered cuz I already know how the
cookie crumbles. I know how it goes, you see.
So what's the point? You
know, I think most of them just throw
dates to use you as a rebound personally.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm happy about myself,
Goozy. I'm happy about myself.
All women are the same.
All the body
saying that all did daddy do
matey. That all did daddy do
Imagine that happened to limp to go on a
[ __ ] date and they just wasted your [ __ ] time,
bro. Wow. Imagine that.
E, that's [ __ ] limp to go on that
[ __ ] date. Would you be pissed off, Grezy?
Yeah. Pissed me off. that
did probably if I'm staying on a [ __ ]
bag on [ __ ] bag holiday.
But at least I'm not the only one. I've got
grievy. I've got Grezy with
me. B Simpson, respect your mother.
She's not the one that used to strangle
you until your tongue come out. Yep. I
used to watch you get strangled but when
I was a child as
well. I'm going to go to
Springfield. Greavvesy. I'm going to go
to Springfield and teach Homer Simpson a
lesson. That's what I'm going to do.
Teach him a
lesson. That's funny. Come
on. I'll wait for this
Indian. Going to be
nice. Going to be nice, mate.
They ignore normal nice messages and
reply to negative ones. Cactus. Wow, that's
crazy. So they like negative people.
Seems that way. Yeah. Wow. Yes.
And it's not that they just
respond. It's that they try to victimize
themselves. When they respond and they
try to be
clever, they try to victimize
themselves. Oh, I was going to get round
to replying. Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Like, they tried to victimize
themselves. That's how you know they're
just sick in their head and they're just
not worth dealing with. Yeah.
Yeah. Pop a stick in the head.
Yeah, they're soon there when you're
negative, mate, ain't there?
Italian one blocked me.
Looks good. I can read her number
now. Yeah. I said to her back when she
said, "Oh, I hope you you can change
your mind in the future." And I said I
said to her, "I hope in the future you
your mental health is not so bad that
you feel you only have to reply to negative comments.
I'm so cheek in
it. Yeah. I hope in in the future you
don't only reply to negative comments
that people send you, negative messages. So
yeah, just [ __ ] [ __ ] aren't they?
this. Ignore this.
back on my phone actually. One
second. That's what I'll be dealing
with. If I went out today, Grezy, I'd be
dealing with it all over again. You
know, I'd be having more and more
negative experiences to add to the list.
Why do I want negative experiences? Why
would I want to choose to have negative
experiences? Doesn't even make
sense. Cuz these people come from the
the women that you've
approached. This whole replying to
negative messages, thinking they're
clever and [ __ ] you think life's too
short to be dealing with that all that
[ __ ] had done it worn the [ __ ] t-shirt, you know. Yeah. That's sick.
I get a lot of email today, you know. Yeah.
I'm going I might be back live later. Who knows?
Maybe, maybe not.