Yep. Back for a little
bit. Oh my god.
Wonder if it's hot or cold. Yeah. sir. This sucks. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, just trying to find something to do tomorrow.
Yeah. Yeah. I just watching LJ. I don't
really go on LJ's anymore. He's the same
people every day.
He was saying that how
um he's going out
tomorrow. I could go out, but it's
pointless. It would just be pointless. Complete
pointless. I could easily go out over
the bank holiday, spend £500
comfortably, but there'd be no
point. There actually be no point in it.
you're just going to get the same [ __ ]
So easily you can spend 400 500
comfortably more than that but there as
example what's the [ __ ] point you know nah Ah, another
point. Do I got to sit in
Fel? Sit in the F your [ __ ] self,
mate. You know. Yeah. Mhm. Yeah.
I'm not much entertainment when I'm indoors, am I? No. No.
Am I going out? Um, did you ignore me
when I said I was done for 6 weeks minimum
or did you was you was you there? Cuz I
said about a million times I'm not going
out for about 6 weeks
minimum. Said I said six weeks
minimum. So no, not going out today, not
going out tomorrow. Yeah, I stick by my
guns when I say [ __ ]
I stand by what I say when I say
[ __ ] Oh well, yeah, I'm done for six weeks
minimum. Yeah, I could go out tomorrow.
I could easily go out today, tomorrow,
tomorrow, Sunday, spend £600, no
problem. But there's no point because
it's just going to be the same
[ __ ] Yeah, it's bank holiday. It was
bank holiday last time as well. One of
the last times I went out was bank
holiday. And your point is the sky [ __ ] blue,
mate. What's that supposed to mean?
Okay, it's a bank holiday, right? It was
a bank holiday last time I went
out. Nothing happened. And I went out
two days. I think I done two days. I
think I did. Yeah. Nothing
happened. So yeah, it can [ __ ] stay bank
holiday. It can stay bank holiday as
much as it wants to.
Yeah. No, I didn't pull anything. I had
a date that wasted my
time. That's what happened. No, I had
somebody approach me, give me their
number, and wasted my time when I met
them on a date. That's what That's what happened.
Yeah, that's what
happened. You should tell the story, don't you?
Yeah. If that's your idea of pudding,
mate, then [ __ ]
hell. Getting your time wasted on a
[ __ ] date. Happen to limp to a date
and getting your time wasted. If that's
your idea of pudding, then wow, man.
That's all I can say. So
yeah, [ __ ] just sit on a chair for an
hour getting your hair
done. Boring, is
it? It's got like 40 quid. I just can't
justify it anymore. I just can't justify you
know, I really just can't justify
it. Can't I really
can't. And it's not about the money cuz
let's just say,
yeah, that I put £300 on black right
now. Yeah. Let's just say £350 to go out
for 2 days in a bank holiday as an
example. Say I put £350 on a car and it
come in. I still didn't go out. Say I
got £700. I still didn't go out when I
had it paid for. So it's not the
money. But at the same time, it's a
waste of money going out. Does that make sense?
That's just one of them reasons, but
it's not the main
reason. Yeah, that's it.
If I had already had my hair cut and then you
know maybe won a football bet then
maybe but nah it's pointless
mate. It's pointless.
Yeah. Yeah, bro. So, um
and I don't want to associate with
people that only reply to negativity as
well. I don't want to be associated to
them kind of people.
So, I might just stay in and play the
Simpsons hit and run with my friend or something.
Um, Marvel isn't dare to celebrate a bank
holiday. I just don't want to deal with
women anymore. They've shown their true
colors time and time and time and time again.
See, Ant-Man doesn't understand because
he's not been through as much as I have with
them. You know what I'm saying? So he
wouldn't he obviously understands but not
fully. Oh yeah.
I have this escort always message me
saying, "Oh, I miss you. Come around.
Come around." What's that? 70, 80
quid. Rather than [ __ ] going out,
putting all that effort in for what?
Nothing. Pointless, man. I don't know
this cuz she kept messaging
me. Yeah, bank holiday makes no
difference, bro. It's just a holiday literally. Oh,
there's something. Yeah. [Music]
That just can't justify going to the
barbers and trying again.
I just can't justify
it. Got a Dior t-shirt. Got some G nice
jeans. Nice trainers. I just can't justify it.
There we go. [Music]
Yeah. Yeah, bro. So, that's basically
where we're at.
Oh, just itching my
[ __ ] There's someone for everyone.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that,
buddy. You keep telling yourself
that. It helps you sleep at night,
buddy. Do you know what? If I was going
to do anything tomorrow, I'd probably do
something to make money.
that and Sunday. I'd probably just make
money on them two days. If I needed
money, I'd probably just go out and make
money. I wouldn't even go out drinking to be
honest. No, them breaks are imperative,
bro. There's not someone for
everyone. That's the whole point is
there's not someone for
everyone. There's loads of people even I
can see that they're just compatible
with no one.
There's just not someone for
everyone. I don't believe
that. I don't believe that at
all. I don't even believe people even
even people that have been in relation
been in relationships, there's not
someone for them because they they
obviously broke up for a reason. So I
don't believe there's someone for
everyone cuz if there was people would
have found him by
now you know traveling you've done
approaching if there was someone for
everyone you would have found them by
now that's it that's all I really got to
say to that nothing
else someone for
everyone that's ridiculous this. So yeah, s
There's nothing in the [ __ ] cinema.
That's a horror film. Otherwise, I'd be
on that. That's probably what I'd do to
be honest. I'd probably work a couple of days,
then probably go cinema if there was
something in the
cinema and that would be my bank holiday. Yeah.
Yeah. So, I've given up
anyways because of the [ __ ] you have to go through. Yeah.
Yeah, definitely definitely get up.
The only day that I do go out is, and I
always have to, is my birthday. If it's
my birthday, I'm 100% going out. It
doesn't matter what what it is, I'm
definitely going out on my birthday. But
[ __ ] bank holidays and
[ __ ] who cares?
Yeah, that's a day you have to go out and do
something. She's her birthday, you know. What's up? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And besides, even if you got a number
and then you go on a date, you know what
happens on dates. So what's the point? You
know, people that are clearly not
compatible with someone else should just
give up. She just throw in the
towel. People that are not compatible with
anyone. That's what a lot of people need
to start doing. I said
That's [ __ ] up.
Uh, well, it's what I'm doing,
so it's an option for
me. Oh, what the
[ __ ] It's an option for me. And I feel
like uh weight's been lifted off my
shoulder to be fair.
Well, it's the option that I'm I'm
doing. Yeah, giving up is definitely an option for
me. It's what I'm doing, mate.
Yeah, that's what I'm doing.
Good option for me, matey. Yes,
matey. I should have gave up a long time
ago, to be
honest. I should have gave up like a
year and a half ago. Jesus.
But never giving up now.
Anyways, you can't keep going out every
week expecting it to be
different. It's never going to be
different. It's never ever ever going to be
different, you know.
Yeah. It's not an attitude, it's
reality. Your attitude comes from your life
experiences. Yeah. Your attitude is
based on your life
experiences with whatever it is you're
[ __ ] talking about. Like mine with
women, time wasting them replying to negative
negativity, going on dates to waste your
time. That's what gives you the
attitude. Oh, it's not it's not even an
attitude. It's common
sense. It's not an it's not
an it's not an attitude. It's being real.
It's being real with yourself. What you've experienced.
Yeah. If you had some better
experiences, you wouldn't be like this.
You wouldn't be thinking like
this. Yeah. They're the ones.
So that's why I can't be bothered with anymore.
People are married. Good for them, man.
Good for people if they're married. Good
them. I don't care about other people,
bro. I don't compare myself to other
people cuz it's just a complete
pointless waste of
time comparing yourself to other people.
The ghosting that pisses me off. The
ghosting. The ghosting the time wasting dates. You know, it's
pointless saying about other people and
what other people do cuz it's just it's
pointless because everyone's in
different circumstances. Everyone's
different. Times have changed.
So there's no point like uh
Yeah. Yeah. No
[ __ ] It's like what Antman says. I was
about to block him the other day. Oh,
but there's other people. There's
There's no me and you, bro. Cuz I don't
care about it
anymore. Other people. Other people. Why
do you live your life based on other
people? It doesn't even It don't even
make sense. And I mean with like
anything, it doesn't make
sense. Other people is not you. They're
others for a reason. [ __ ] hell,
bro. I don't know why he says that. It's stupid. The
madness. Yeah, they are entitled
here. No, it's not only the UK, bro.
It's America. It's Canada. It's any
Western nice country. Look at that
[ __ ] Morgan. She's about a three out
of 10. She thinks he's better than
me. [ __ ] American, bro. [ __ ] me.
I see skin as
well. No, it's a few places. It's America,
Australia, New Zealand, and Canada.
They're all the
same. All the women there are the same. Yeah.
Yeah, South America is
different. I've been with a few
Brazilian women. There's a Brazilian
escort I go and see. They're completely
different. Yeah, it's easier
there. But anywhere that's the west, it's it's
impossible. Well, almost. Yeah. So,
yeah. I went on a date with a 32 year
old woman who was about five out of 10
and she still thought she was better
than me. And the reason I say 32 cuz 32
is old to me. I'm still in my 20s. 32 is
old to me. So, and it's just them kind of shitty experiences, you
know? I can sit and moan. Watch me. I'm
doing it. I can sit and moan because I'm
sitting and I'm moaning.
I'm sitting here and I'm moaning. Bro, I
can because I am because I just did.
Bye-bye. So, yeah. 32 32 old woman is old. Yeah.
So I guess not the point anyways. It's
uh these are the experiences you're
going to have in this country, you
know, and it's never going to stop. Never.
So only option is to give up here. Yeah.
What have I done from 22 to
27? Been to different countries, been all over
England, got loads of money, bought new
clothes, made new friends, went to different
places, found the
relationship, even if it was for a little
while. So, yeah, I like that.
So, I've done a lot in five
years. Yeah, I've done a lot in five
years. A hell of a lot. Try went to
different restaurants, met so many
people. So, it's quite
a I've done a lot in five years. I've
done a lot in a
year. Last year, I should have put a my
year. I done so much in that year.
This year I don't really do much. Really
much because I'm trying to leave and I'm
leaving in six weeks and obviously I'm
not wasting my time or money here
anymore. So that's why I haven't really
been doing anything here. Yeah. Yeah.
They used to put things.
Anyways, yeah. So, that's why I'm not
going out to
my let me see if there's anything on
that channel cuz I'm going to run I'm
going to go to the police again if there is. One
second. I see anything on that channel.
I'm going straight to the police
again. So, yeah. Just had some more
stuff to show them. I've already shown
them so easy for me.
Um, yeah. So, that's it.
Frenchie, pretty much.
Yeah, I could go there next week, bro.
You know, the maddest thing is I could
go there next week if I wanted to. Like,
straight up, bro. I could literally go
there next week and go on her dad's
door. I can afford it, but there's no
point cuz you're just going to get
nicked and I don't care about the
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying, bro? Like,
I was talking to someone on my phone.
Um, yeah, I could go there, bro. Could
there. We all call the police. What the
[ __ ] would you mean for doing that, bro? Yeah.
Sorry. I can leave the country whenever I want, mate. Yeah.
Yeah, don't worry. These people will be
getting arrested too anyways, mate. It
takes time, trust me.
So, yeah, it's just stupid
£3,000 and then there's women
everywhere, bro. un uninterested women
everywhere. Are you forgetting that I've been to
Scotland? Here we
go. More evidence for me. Thank
you. [ __ ] subway surfer. Nice
try. More evidence for me. Thank you.
Someone's getting soon.
Frenchie. Mark my words, somebody is getting nicked
soon. Trust me,
buddy. I followed up the report two days
ago as well. Anyways, yeah, back to the
women [ __ ] Yeah, there's women everywhere. Disinterested
women. That's what they are. Disinterested
Oh, no. I'm not a male.
No, I'm not on bail. And I'm not getting
into this conversation. We're talking
about women. Yeah, there's women in
Scotland and I've been to
Scotland. No, no, I'm not on bail. Not
at all. So, anyways,
um, yes, I've been to Scotland
before. Don't know why they say that.
Don't care why they say that. stick to
the subject cuz people on here are
retards. They talk [ __ ] Anyways, yeah,
Scotland. I've been to
Scotland. Why are you talking about
Scotland? Why are you talking about Scotland, bro?
Huh? Why are you talking about
Scotland? People are making stuff up so
I going bad so they can try and get
police involved again. It's what they do
instead of little tactics. That's why I ignore
it. Yeah. Small. Yeah. Because a small
town, they're suddenly not going to say
they've got boyfriends, right?
Yeah. Yeah. Suddenly they're not going
to say they got boyfriends because it's a small town. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. So, so they're suddenly not
going to say that,
right? Really, bro? They're not going to
say that in small
towns. Yeah, the girls are
easy. Yeah. Okay, bro. Keep telling yourself
that. Oh, you are you forgetting we're
still in the
West? [ __ ] You do realize Scotland is still the west.
Yeah. I won't listen to you, bro, cuz you're talking
[ __ ] I won't listen to you cuz you're
talking absolute [ __ ] Uh 40 stuff 40
drink. There we
go. 27y old. Anyways, moving on. As soon
as you start talking about other people
or you bring up other people, I just
completely ignore it because it has no relevance to
anything. This just has no relevance.
It's the most pointless argument
ever. You know, pointless,
boring, doesn't mean anything, not going
to help you in the future. Not going to
I think the main thing is it's not going
to help you in the future. It's like
knowing someone's a millionaire. It
doesn't mean you're going to be a
millionaire. It's pointless. Comparing
is just utterly pointless. And it's
never going to get you anywhere in life
if you compare yourself to other
people, good or bad. It's just a waste
of time. And man's got an obsession with
it as well. I say to him, bro, like if
you want to go on about it, it's cool,
but don't bring me involved with your
with your like me and you and how does
other I don't care about what other
people do because it's completely
pointless. And and I said to him, right,
I've actually said this to him too. I
said to him, why don't you ask these
people how they were relationships? I
know how they're in relationships, but
you don't want to listen to me, so
there's no point. But I say to him,
like, if you're so concerned, ask them.
But then he would turn around and say
that, "Oh, it's weird." I said, "Well,
it's not weird, right?" Because you're
wondering how other people do it when we
all know how these people do it,
right? But then you don't want to ask
them. So, you want to just keep winding
yourself up. Like, I don't know, bro. I
just say to him, "I'm I'm a big loser.
I've never been with a woman. I don't
know anything. I'm stupid. I'm a 27 year
old. I'm a 27 year
old for me. Thank you. Um I'm a 27 year
old. I don't know anything.
Um I don't know anything. So why are you asking
me? Why are you asking me? But that's
what I say to him. Why are you asking me?
I'm not under no bail either. I can
leave the country whenever I
want. Yeah, I need to leave the country
on B as well. So anyways, I'm just
[ __ ] ignoring that idiot. So yeah, my evidence for me.
So boring out. So anyways, that's why I
sent to man anyways basically that like
um yeah, just ask these people, man.
There's no point asking a loser. You
never been with a
woman if that's what I apparently am. I
can't help you. How's someone supposed
to help you? I don't know anything. I'm
a 27y old and don't know nothing. That
is played up. So like there's no point.
You know what I'm
saying? It's stupid. But obviously
there's going to be people in [ __ ]
relationships. That's the whole point of like Um,
yeah. So, yeah, like obviously there's
going to be people in relationships, for
[ __ ] sake. You know, there was a thing
before [ __ ] Instagram and there was a
thing before [ __ ] Tik
Tok. But then women that say they've got
boyfriends, ah, they're full of [ __ ]
Oh, they're full of [ __ ] bro. Sometimes
it winds me up when people say, "Well,
how do you know they don't have
boyfriends?" No. Jack the Lad is letting
their [ __ ] girlfriend slag it up till
6 7:00 in the morning whilst he's in bed
by himself or he's watching TV by
himself. Get [ __ ]
real. Literally, get real. And like when
when you go to Weber Spoons, right, you
see that there's Yeah, there are people
there are some people in relationships,
but trust me, more people are single
than than than in relationships. I
guarantee you that right now. I
guarantee you that right now, bro. Look
all over Facebook. Look all over.
There's feminists out there. There's
women that hate men. You know, a lot of
women that hate men. So, the maths don't
add up. So, the the math really does not
And there's a lot of people nowadays
that are by and lesbian. So the maths
just doesn't add up. They all claim to
be in relationships, yet they're coming
till 6 7:00 in the morning and they're
never with their boyfriend. It's
[ __ ] man. Come on. It's [ __ ]
I've got sisters, right? I I should know
these things, you
know? And they they go out rarely and
when they go out, they're not going out
till 600 7:00 in the [ __ ] morning,
mate. Let me tell you that. So, it's
[ __ ] Again, just clearing up if
people want to say, "Oh, how do you know
they've got boyfriends? Boring, boring
conversation." Just use your brain if
you actually had
one. So, that's it. You
know, there's a lot of people in the
world nowadays that are um that anti men.
So anti-men you
see delete my videos. I
think I feel good for giving up.
Definitely feel good. There's nothing
worse than [ __ ] waking up to people
that [ __ ] reply to negativity and
then trying to outsmart you. [ __ ] that.
Who wants to be dealing with all that?
It's [ __ ] madness, man. You
know, it was
lovely. Yeah, Greavves. I have
definitely given up. Definitely given
up. I don't want to [ __ ] speak to
people that only reply to negatively. I
can go out, man.
Yeah, I literally Oh, more evidence for
me. Big nose. Have you seen your [ __ ]
self, you ugly [ __ ] Have you seen
yourself, you ugly [ __ ] I've got more
money than you will [ __ ] ever have.
Yeah. Have you seen yourself, you
[ __ ] ugly [ __ ]
Yeah, that's that's that's you. Um,
anyways, more evidence. Um, yeah, agree
with you. As I was saying, uh, I can go
out and literally spend
[ __ ] £500 in two days and not have to
worry about spending £500 in two days.
Literally, I can spend £500 in two days. Um, and
um, yeah, it wouldn't bother me, but I
just know I'd be wasting my time in this country,
so I'll be following this up again in a
couple of days. This police report So
yeah, trying to call me skin. I've got
more money than you would ever have. You
got sh money the other day. You will run
away again. Greg will be my witness.
Remember the pup greedy show of Wonga
run away. You want to run away? Yeah. You remember,
bro? I'm sure you do remember, buddy.
Everyone remembers. Two weeks ago. Two
weeks was two weeks ago.
Anyway, I'm [ __ ] leaving YouTube soon
anyways. Yeah, I'm leaving YouTube soon
Definitely. I just came here to
basically just [ __ ] rant, man.
Yeah. Yeah. To be honest, it's like
therapy session queasy.
Yeah, might have to do a fresh one to be
fair. Sados on
YouTube for the
sados. Ain't got a
life. Ain't got a life.
I ain't got a life obsessed mentally. I
think that person was right, you know,
like a year ago. You should just come
off YouTube, live your life, legally people to
it. I think they were
right. I think they were definitely
right. Yeah, you're talking about
yourself. Yeah, stop talking about
yourself, man. It's quite nice to talk
about yourself like that. My phone's on
2%. Yeah, you need to stop talking about
yourself. It's not good for
you. Stop describing yourself on my live
stream, buddy. Come on, mate. It's a
[ __ ] Friday. Stop talking about
yourself. Isn't that right, music?
Yeah, bro. I'm I'm I'm bored and I've
got a big nose. Yeah. Just like you call
people skin and they show you money and
you run away. Just like people showing
you them tons of women and you run away.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm skinny and I got a big
nose. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But yeah, bro.
Yeah, man. You sure you're not describing
yourself? Nah. You're describing
yourself, man. Talking about yourself like
that. Probably dementia or something.
Nah, these people are definitely talking about
themselves. Just like when they call
people skint and [ __ ] They're just
self-reflecting. My phone's about to
[ __ ] die. One
sec. Oh, they talk about themselves every
day. They're literally talking about
their own lives. Oh, they need to stop
getting themselves confused with me. Oh,
motherfucker's going to die. [ __ ]
Yeah, they need to stop talking about
themselves every All right. my
[ __ ] man. Yeah, stop talking about
yourself anyways. Calling yourself a big
nose and skin. Stop talking about
yourself like that. It's not good for
your mental health. Anyways, Grizzy. Yeah. So,
um, yeah, but I don't really want to be
associated with people that can only
reply back to
negativity. It just seems strange to me
how people can
only reply back to um, [Music]
negativity. That's not cool, is
it? That's not cool, is it, bro?
only reply back to
negativity. Red flag after red flag
after red flag. Do you know a red a red
is? You know what a red flag is?
No. Red flag is crazy.
I'm sure you
do. That's a red flag. I don't speak to
people that can only reply that to [ __ ]
negativity. No matter how you try to
justify, oh, it's it's
it's oh um yeah, it's uh
yeah, that's not normal, mate, to reply
back to negativity and ignore normal messages.
Nah, that's not normal, mate. No matter
how you try to justify, that is not normal.
That's not [ __ ] normal. Especially
when you're moaning and winging that you
can't find a normal man, you can't find
a normal guy. You moan and winge, but
then you reply to negativity, which
means there's a
um so yeah, they they like negative
people. Negative people.
Why would you like a negative
person? And I Okay, it doesn't matter
why they replied. Why do they try to
victimize themselves, Grezy? Oh, I was
going to reply. That's how you know
they're [ __ ] up in their head that
they tried to victimize themselves um after
ignoring. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Like grief to me is no rap. Yeah, I get you.
Yeah. Yeah. But then they try to
victimize themsel as
well. It's not even like they've
messaged back asking like why you feel
that way. They're literally victimizing
themsel or trying to victimize
themsel which is [ __ ] up after
ignoring after all that time. [Music]
Yeah. So, yeah, they're just
narcissists. All of them. That's what
they are. They're just [ __ ] narcissists.
And women have this tendency to argue
with people that they think they're more
intelligent than. And then when you
whoop their ass in an argument, they
play a victim or they just run away. [ __ ]
pathetic. Absolutely [ __ ] pathetic.
Really? They They've turned me [ __ ]
asexual like you, bro. I only went to
that escort the other day cuz you kept
[ __ ] messaging me begging me, bro.
Begging me. she
was to come
around. She wanted money and dicks. So I
thought [ __ ] it. Yeah, I'm asexual like you,
buddy. That's I think I'm getting that way,
bro. Stop talking about stop talking
about yourself again. Enough of that
talking about yourself on my channel.
It's no good for your mental health.
Stop talking about yourself.
It's not nice to keep talking negatively
about yourself on my YouTube
channel. Please stop talking about
yourself. How's your mental health ever
going to get better?
Jeez. Uh, I done it as an experiment. I
done it as an experiment before I went
to bed after I had pork chops. I just
wanted to see how many of them would have
replied. And [ __ ] hell, I think I got
my [ __ ] answer. It was just an
experiment. And then when they um
replied and what some of them were
replying with, that made me think, do
you really want to be dealing with these
narcissistic women? Do you really want
to be still dealing with this your whole
life? And I said to myself, no, I don't
want to be dealing with this
anymore. People that can apply to
negativity. Well, they [ __ ] replied.
So, it's not the point whether they
[ __ ] cared or they don't care. They
replied, you know? So, they obviously
[ __ ] did care enough to want to
[ __ ] try and argue with
you. You know what I'm
saying? Stop talking about yourself.
Stop talking about yourself. Oh my god.
Next thing you're going to call me is [ __ ] skint
again. Oh, stop talking about yourself.
Please stop it. It's boring.
Stop making fake accounts to put
yourself down. I'm starting to really
feel bad. So yeah.
Um yeah. So basically, uh that's
basically what it is. And and yeah, like
I said, it wasn't just the fact that
they replied, it was what they were
replying with trying to victimize
themselves. I just said women are
evil. And I had this one from that's
literally all I said. Women were evil.
and they just started replying. One
said, "Oh, I was going to message you."
Even though it had been three
months and she tried using that as a
reason as why she didn't reply again,
victimizing herself or at least trying
to victimize herself. That's literally
all I said was women are evil. I never
said nothing else. That's literally all
I said. And [ __ ] my phone was rolling,
bro. Like a drug dealer's phone. They
really get off on negativity, mate. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, most of them replied for like 90%. I thought, [ __ ] That's
crazy. They're nowhere to be seen, but
when you say something negative, they're
they're there all of a sudden. Crazy,
eh? I don't want to associate with
people that can only reply to negativity
and people that have victimized
themselves, you know.
Um what why do you what do you expect
them to say when you say just carry on
just carry on ignoring like you have been
doing just carry on
ignoring you know what I'm saying just
carry on [ __ ]
ignoring just carry on ignoring like
you've been doing I mean it wouldn't
hurt you would it and why why are you
victimizing yourself as well pretending
that you was going to reply when you
hadn't replied in 3 months. Anything to
try to victimize themselves. That's the
[ __ ] up thing about it. Like that's
how narcissistic they are and selfish
they are. They have to literally try to
be a victim. That's what they like to
do, Gre. They have to be a victim. Oh, I
was going to reply, you know. Yeah, [ __ ]
off. That's why you replied as soon as I
said all women are evil. And that's the
only thing I said. [ __ ] off. You
know, that's very concerning,
bro. What do I expect them to say?
Nothing. And just keep ignoring like they've been
doing. What would have hurt them doing that, you know? Yeah.
But they're just [ __ ] But it's it's
the it's them. It's trying to victimize
themsel I found [ __ ] up, you
know. I haven't been trying to get one
so hard for so long, bro. I gave up. No,
no. I tell you what. Yeah. When I
started going out for the past month, I
was, "Okay, let me just see what this is
about." Then I went on this date and
they wasting my time on the first day
and I thought, "Okay, this is the last
day I'm out now. is this [ __ ] wasting
my time? And then then I went out again
two weeks later because it was a bank
holiday. And the last time I went out
was that Sunday and I was like, "Fuck
this. I am not doing this again." And
that was about 2, three weeks ago. Was
the last bank holiday. I'm not doing
this [ __ ] again. [ __ ]
this. You know, I could deal with the
I've got a boyfriend [ __ ] I can deal
with some of the [ __ ] But the ghosting
and the time wasting on dates and then
the replying to negativity and then
trying to victimize yourself. I'm done.
I'm literally done. That was literally
the icing on the [ __ ]
cake. That legit was the icing on the
[ __ ] cake, bro. I think I was like,
that is me, bro. For real. I was even on
that Thursday, but I thought cuz it was
a bank holiday two weeks after, I was
going to go out for a drink anyways. But
yeah, you don't want to you don't you
don't want to associate your [ __ ]
self with [ __ ] evil, bro. You know
what I'm saying?
And that's how I [ __ ] my foot up. So yeah, bro.
Yeah. I was like, it's just going to be
my life really, you know. But I don't
Yeah, I can go out tomorrow if I wanted
to. Could try tomorrow, but I don't want
to try with evil
people. I don't want to [ __ ] [ __ ]
with evil people, bro. [ __ ] that evil
people that have to try to victimize themsel, you
know. Yeah, I'm good,
bro. I'm all right. I'm
done. I'm just going to
chill. You know, I genuinely do believe
it, bro. Cuz I would have been out
today. I would have been out today. I
would be out tomorrow.
But I'm not going
to don't want to [ __ ] deal with them. that.
Yeah. Nice to meet you. So, [Music] yeah.
Yeah. But they are all evil.
It's not that they just It's not that
replied, it's what they replied with
trying to be smart, trying to be
clever and then [ __ ] trying to victimize
themselves. Well, imagine waking up to
them messages like first thing in the
morning, them trying to be funny and
[ __ ] and trying to be play a
victim. Like that's me done, bro.
There's there's nothing left to say. the love letter.
Yeah. Yeah. Probably, bro.
Yeah. I was an idiot back then,
bro. Yeah, I was an idiot back then. Now
I'm different, you know.
Yeah. Yeah, but I was an idiot back then.
Oh. Hey guys, what's your plans for
tomorrow? anyone who's
watching. I'm just
chilling. I wasted a lot of time trying
to find a woman that was different cuz
in my head I was always told that
they're not all the same and
no, even though at 17, 18, I was
convinced that they're all the same. I
don't know why I was convinced they were
all the same, but I must have knew from
a very young age.
But uh somebody used to tell me, "Oh,
you don't know all women." No, no, no,
no, no. Even though I knew more women
than them and I know more women than
them. Um he would still sit there and
say, "No, you don't know all women. You women."
Huh. Well, I know more than you.
So, I meet women quite frequently and
they never fail
to amaze me.
So they're all the same, mate. They're
all the [ __ ] same.
Yeah. Ghosters, piss
takers, you name it. Yeah.
Yeah. No, I don't block everyone that
disagree. Uh Gregy disagrees with me on
a lot of things. He's still here. We
don't even we don't agree on much to be
fair, you know.
Nah, I just blocked the self projectors
that say like skin and cuz they're just
talking about themselves and they just
ruin the chat. But no,
no, but I am always right when it comes
to women and that's because I deal with
women. I've been out with women. I know
what they're like. So me of all people
would would know what they're like. It's
common sense. It's it's literally common
If someone like me has been dealing with
them for so long and deals with them
frequently, obviously, you know what I'm
saying? I I I know what they're like.
You've never been in a relationship. So,
what does that tell you? Um, I have been
in a relationship. Wrong again. I'm
smelling Lewisville slugger here. But,
uh, yes, I have been in a relationship
and I've had chances to be in several
relationships. Try again. And you do
realize that when you're in a
relationship, you're in a relationship with one
person, which is what I've tried saying
before, but no one's actually understood
it. A relationship is with one person,
not multiple women. So, I would say I
know more about women than one person
that's been in one relationship in his
life that's been in a relationship for about five
years. A relationship is one woman. And
yes, I have been in a relationship and
I've had chances to to be in more
relationships. There you go. Louisville
slugger. So yeah, try again. But yeah,
someone that's been someone that's been
in a relationship for 5
years and only one relationship and then
you got me, I would know more than them.
So when you when you say that
relationship stuff, you just kind of
give yourself away as Lewisville
slugger [ __ ] there's another
account. Whenever that relationship [ __ ]
is mentioned, it's something from that.
It's some from that side defo, you
know. So yeah, I've been on dates,
several dates. I've had women that are
friends. I've had one night stands, but
I wouldn't know what a woman is like
because I've not been in a relationship.
Even though I've been in a relationship,
but let's just say I haven't been in a
relationship. So, so what I'm saying is
right, so even though I've had one night
stands, I've approached people, I've had
women that are
friends, had dates, I have sisters, but
because I've not been in a relationship
for say a month, that means that I don't
know anything about women. Bro, do you
hear yourself? Do you actually hear what
you're saying right
now? You know, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. You are literally Louisville
slugger because you give yourself away.
Whenever you mention that never been in
a relationship, it's clearly you because
everybody knows that I have been in
one. And yeah, it's literally you. But
either way, it doesn't matter. [ __ ] all
that. Whether whether it is or whether
it isn't. I've got sisters. I've been on
dates. I've had friends that are women.
I've met women literally multiple times
a week. But I don't know what women are
like if I have not been in a
relationship with one. Bro, please stop it. It's
embarrassing. It really, really, really,
really, really, really is
embarrassing. And you need to get better at [ __ ]
um it doesn't matter how long and
widened she leave. We're not talking
about that. Do you really think that you
need to be in a relationship to know
what women are like? Bro, that doesn't
even make sense. I've got a mom. I've
got sisters. I've been on dates. Been on
dates where I met people a couple of
times. I go out and I approach and
they're literally all the
same. So yeah, that relationship thing
doesn't even make any [ __ ] sense.
Does not make no sense
whatoever. Women are all the same. And
even when I was with her, I could sense
the entitlement. I could sense I could
literally sense the entitlement even
when I was with her. And I was like, "Oh
[ __ ] bro. This is bullshit." I could
actually could actually sense the
entitlement. [ __ ] hell. Oh, crazy,
man. I'm going to be called [ __ ] Skid next. Yeah.
I'll be called Skid Next, mate. Believe
that. If I truly didn't believe women
was all evil, I'd be out now in a
nightclub. It's almost 10:00. I would be
out tomorrow in a nightclub. If I
generally generally thought I was wrong
and I was lying to myself, that's what I would be
doing. That is literally what I would be
[ __ ] doing. But I'm not.
Oh, every man on earth would be single.
No, not at all. Not at all. No. It's how
I just told you how women have acted.
I've just told you that they've replied
to negativity and then they've tried to
victimize themselves and then you're
[ __ ] making up stuff about the way
that I act. No, it's literally women.
And just because there's people in
relationships, it doesn't mean anything.
I know men that are with evil women.
Just because people are in
relationships, that doesn't mean
anything. That doesn't that doesn't um
that's not what's the point? That's not
um that's not
um that's not um what's the word? That's
not um relevant to me. Other people are
not relevant to me. Nothing to do with
yesterday. Nothing to do with other
people. You know what I'm saying? So,
no, it's literally women. As soon as
they as soon as I found out that they
reply to negativity, trying to victimize
themselves. Like, why? Let's give you an
example how [ __ ] up they are in the
head. It's like that Italian one. Why
not rep Why just not reply? Why reply
trying to think that you're intelligent
and then when somebody shows you they're
more intelligent than you, you run away.
Why do you come trying to be a victim
when your ignorant assign Ignorant ass
has been ignoring for three months and
yet as soon as something negative is
sent, you're here trying to be smart and
trying to be a victim. That screams sick
in the head and evil. No normal person
does that. I could I could message I
could and I and all I said to her was I
hope that you learn that you shouldn't
have to feel the need to reply to
negative messages. I I I said, "I hope
that you sort your problems out and you
don't have to keep replying to
negativity." That is sick. And the other
one from York as well. Don't [ __ ] try
and tell me about, "Oh, other men in
relationships. Other men. I've literally
just told you what I've experienced,
idiot." For [ __ ] sake. That's why 80%
of men are [ __ ] single. Is it? That's
why [ __ ] That's why more men are
going [ __ ] Thailand nowadays, isn't
it? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. These men that
you're talking about in relationships,
mate, you're talking about people that I
met years ago. You're talking about a small minority. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Would you would you try to victimize
yourself, you know? Yeah. But would you
would you try to victimize yourself? I
would. And I would just [ __ ] block
them, you know? And this whole thing
about other people in relationships, it
doesn't mean anything. There's plenty of
single people out there. Plenty of
single people out there. You know, when
I've gone out, I've gone out drinking
and [ __ ] I've obviously met normal
people and they they have the same
problems with women. Not all them people
can be wrong. All them people that are
not related to each other, that don't
know anyone is saying the same thing.
For [ __ ] sake, I've even met [ __ ]
virgins, for crying out loud, in normal
bars and clubs. So this whole Oh, other
men, other men, it's completely
irrelevant, good or bad, you
know. Well, you have now they are all evil.
I I generally believe they are all evil
and I and I believe that they're sick in
the head. Ignorant, stuck up, entitled,
sick in the head and evil. That's
generally my opinion on them. So, you've
met me. Well, you haven't met me, but
maybe on YouTube and I think by that.
So, yeah, I generally do believe it.
They're evil. They don't care about
anyone's feelings. Every single woman.
Yeah. Every single
woman. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Not. Yeah. I
said all women. So, yes. Every single
woman is like that. All women.
Tony. Every single one of them. 27
years. And I'm still counting,
buddy. I'm still find I'm still trying
to find this. Well, I gave up now, but I
was still trying to find this woman.
That's different. Can't find him anymore,
bro. Not found. Listen, Ricky, that's
another thing. What would you know about
women? You don't even leave your house,
right? I seen your comment on another
channel, right? You don't even leave
your house. You don't know anything
about women. So, when when I see you
comment Yeah. trying to say, "Oh, it's
not the women. It's you don't know about
women." Like, I'm not sat there saying
that you've never been with a woman or
you're a virgin. No, no, no, no. What
I'm trying to say to you, my man, is you
do not go out your house dealing with
women. I do. So, I would know what they
are like rather than what you what you
would know. Doesn't mean I think I'm
right about everything. I genuinely know
how it is. I went out two days bank
holiday, had to go this date. I wasted
my time. I know what these women are
like, which is why I stay away from
them, obviously, you know.
So he's not talking no [ __ ] facts,
mate. I would know more than anybody
nowadays that's on this community
because I go out and I have to deal with
them. Well, I used to, but you know,
I've given up
now. So that's
it. Okay. Well, you can think it's a
little bro. That's that's up to you. You
know, I generally do think they're all
evil, Ricky, because they wouldn't
adopt. They wouldn't do what they do.
They're wasting your time speaking to
you for three days, then ghosting on
purpose. The traveling an hour to meet
you just to waste your time. That is
some kind of mental health and other
things, you know. You know, there's
other things that they do on purpose,
you know. So, obviously, they're sick in
head. No [ __ ] man will do it. So, no,
they are generally sick in the head.
They really are sick in the
head. So, do you not even go on
hookups? No, bro. I've given up. I gave
up. Totally. Uh oh. This guy's probably
been on the years. Basically, a month
ago, right? I had this person approached
me. They approached me. They gave me
their number. I thought, "Okay, I've not
been on a date for [ __ ] um you know,
probably like a year or so to be honest.
I had a lot of dates last year and I had
this uh foot condition so I had to limp
to the [ __ ] date and then she wasted
my time. It was a Thursday and I
thought, "Fuck this. After today, I'm
done." You know, I'm going to keep
approaching. I'm going to keep
approaching today. And then after today, I'm
finished. So then on that Thursday, I
met someone else who tried using me.
[ __ ] her off. Then I went out again
two weeks after that. Was planning to
meet somebody on a Friday. Speaking for
3 days, suddenly ghosted. I thought,
"Fuck this. I'm not doing this over.
[ __ ] these women." So, yeah. I just
thought, "Fuck this, bro. I ain't doing
this again." Yeah. [ __ ]
pissake. So, yeah, bro. I don't I don't
bother with them no more cuz I truly
believe that they are evil. And I would
say I'd be in a nightclub right now if I
didn't believe it. So, it's not even
like I'm contradicting myself. At 27
years of age, I would have found someone
who's not like that.
Bear in mind, I probably met more women
than all the youth combined, bro. I used
to do this practically poor [ __ ] job.
And I generally believe they are all
[ __ ] up. They're generally all
evil. And guess what? They want to try
and talk about double standards, but
guess what? They get lesser
sentences. Yeah. You know, women that do
murder, they don't even they don't even
go to prison for life. How about that
one? How about they can commit a crime
and get a way lesser sentence? And yes,
it does happen because I look these
things up. I watch
documentaries, but I do generally
believe they are
evil. Time wasting evil. Um, they go for
scumbags, drug dealers, regardless of
what color they are. I generally believe
it. So, yeah. Ignorant, stuck up. Yeah.
And I'm I feel so strongly about it as
well cuz I thought Yeah.
No, cuz people said it for so long. Nah,
it's not them. It's not
them, you know. No, you haven't, Tony.
No, you haven't, buddy. No, you haven't,
mate. Trust me, mate. I've been all over
the country. I've been to Scotland and
Wales. I have been on many, many dates.
No, you have not. No, you have not,
Tony. I have met more women than you, buddy.
Right. Yeah. I would start looking at
myself, but the problem is not found is
I've got all of these friends. I've got
friends that look up to me. I have
friends that say that I've got a good
personality. Um, so I have looked at
myself and it's got to be the women. I
even have people that disbelieve me.
They're like, "What the [ __ ] You look
decent. You got money. You got a good
personality." No, no, no. Defo. I have
looked at myself and no, it's definitely
definitely the women because as my
approaches show, when you go and you
approach a woman, they pretend they've
got a boyfriend because of their stuck
upness in their ego. It's the women.
That's exactly why I'm going Thailand.
Well, listen, you can't guarantee it,
Tony. I have met way more women than
you. I'm a thousand% certain. I'm a
thousand% certain. I have been with way
more women than you, mate. I know
exactly what they're like. every single
last one of them. You're not 100%
certain because I've been with way more
women than you, mate. Trust me. You know
how many [ __ ] dates I went on last year.
So, so yeah. Anyways, so yeah, not fam.
To answer your question, yeah, I'm
thinking, right, this doesn't logically
make any sense, right? You got, oh yeah,
my approaches are weak. Always blaming
the man. You've always got to blame the
man. I'm a million% certain that I've
been with more women than you, mate, and
they are all the same. Anyways, yeah.
So, not found. Basically, I've got
friends. I've got people that look up to
me. I've got friends. I, you know, when
I was saving money, it got to a point
where I had to start making stuff up
while I couldn't meet them cuz obviously
I don't want to seem rude. You got all
these people that look up to you. You
got these friends that disbelieve the
fact that you can't find anyone. It's
got to be these women. I know. I know. I
know you don't want to blame these
women, you know, these westernized
women. It is these women 100%. these
women and every single approaching video
that I've done has proved
it. Mate, you can bet your life on it,
bro. I'm telling you I have. And I'm not
going to sit here and argue with you.
I'm not going to sit here and argue with
you, bro. Just like I'm not going to block
you, you know. No, I'm not going to get
into it. No, fans. I'm not going to get
into my friends and what my friends were
like, what my friends were like. You
asked a question which was which was
quite a sensible question and I answered
it. And I answered it, lad. Yeah, I've
got no game. Okay, buddy. Yeah, I've got
no game. Yep. Whatever you say, bro.
Yeah. Okay. Whatever you say, bro. Yep.
I'm 27. I've got no life experience.
I've never been with a woman. I don't
know what I'm talking about. Is that
what you want me to say? Like, you're
accusing me of blocking people that's
got a different opinion than me. I've
literally gave you the time of day. I've
answered your question. When I answer
you, you're telling me that I've not
been with more women than you. When I'm
literally telling you that I have. I've
not worked for three years, right? I've
had all this time to go out, meet women,
meet new people, build up my social
circle. I'm literally telling you that I
have and you're telling me that I
haven't. So, there's no point to sit
here and argue with you. There's point
in this, bro.
But anyways, we're not going to get into
my friends or what my friends are like
or whatever. You asked the question and
I answered it to my best um ability. It
is the women in this country one
million%. I know it. That's why I'm
leaving. Like I I actually think that we
should all agree to disagree, right? I
am leaving. I am leaving this country. I
am done. That's how certain I am to the
women in this or any westernized
country. It does. It's not even just
England, you know. So, yep. Whatever,
bro. Like, yeah. I've never met a woman
in my life. I'm a 27 year old virgin. I
don't know what I'm talking about. I'm
just a [ __ ] idiot. Yep. Whatever
floats your boat, bro. I'm just going to
agree with you, you know? I don't I
don't want to argue with anyone, bro.
Yep. You're right. I've never been with
a woman, never seen one, never left my
house, never been on a date. I don't
know anything. I'm a 27 year old with no life experience.
Yep. I don't know anything. I'm a big
idiot that's never been with a woman,
never been on a date. I'm still a
virgin. Never kissed anyone. Yep, that's
me. And Mr. Tony knows everything.
Tony's been with all these women. And uh
well, let me tell you something, Tony.
My friend has been to Thailand three
times in a year, and guess what? He's
never had a problem. He has never had a
problem. He's never had I have a
boyfriend over there. He has been
nothing but respected. He has been
nothing but women has got with him. My
friend's been there three times in a
year and he's going there in two weeks.
So I think I'm going to believe him more
than I believe you, you know.
So I haven't even been m I've been I
haven't even been anywhere. Okay. I've
got a friend that has been to Thailand
three times in a year and he's never had these problems.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But guess
what? I've got a friend that's been
there three times recently and he
doesn't have these problems. He doesn't
get, "Oh, I've got a boyfriend." No. No.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
So, I'm going to believe him more than I believe you. yeah. But
yeah. But yeah, I'm just going to
believe him. But I've never met I've
never met a woman. I'm a virgin. Never
been on a date. I don't know anything.
Me I'm silly
[ __ ] Yeah, I'm as silly as
[ __ ] Me? I'm stupid. Never been
with a woman. Never had one. Never been
on a date. Never kissed anyone. I I
don't know nothing. Homie knows everything. Don't
say what I'm saying. The women there
don't say I have a boyfriend because
Yeah. It doesn't matter. Well, it
doesn't matter why they don't say it.
They don't say it. So simple. Thailand
works. Whatever reason it works, it
So yeah, but that's like here though. If
you don't have loads of money, the women
here won't be interested. But obviously
the money here is different level. So
yeah, that's just like most women you're
describing. If No, I might actually
quote this on the t-shirt. If you don't
have money, the Thai women will not be
interested. Uh you you need to remove
the tie and just put women because it is
it is women. It's not just Thai women.
It's women in
general. Yeah. If I had game in the UK
would work. Yeah. You keep telling
yourself that, buddy. You're just one of
these people that will never admit it's
women. And I'm not going to try and
change your mind. Just you're not going
to try and change my mind. And you know,
it is a good thing that you can come on
here and we can agree to disagree.
They're either interested or they're
not. There's no Jedi mind tricks. But
some people like you ain't got no bad
words to say about women. So it's just
falling on deaf ears to be fair. So
yeah, bro. Like you know, it is what it
is. You can't change someone's mind.
There's nothing you're miraculously
going to say that's going to make somebody like
you. But you're just you're just I'm not
going to call you S. You're just someone
that's never going to say anything bad
about women. So, there's no
point. What did you just say? You are
broke. Hold on a minute. Hold on a
minute. Hold on. You are broke, bro. I
get more money than you every month.
What are you talking about?
We had this conversation about money the
other day. I've got more money than you.
What are you talking about? You're the
one that says that you're left with a
grand. I'm broke. You literally don't
know anything about me, bro. You don't
even know how much money I have right
now. For [ __ ] sake. I've got a
wardrobe worth more than your whole
life. I get more money than you and I'm
left with more money than you every
month because you told me how much you
get. I'm broke, bro. I get more money than you.
I literally get more money than you. I
have more money than you. What are you
talking about? You absolute
clown. And someone tried saying that
you've been on here for [ __ ] years,
mate. Shut up. I'm sensing [ __ ] G. I
swear to God. Yeah. You ain't been no
Thailand six times, bro. Get out of
here, bro. Get out of here, man. Please.
Oh my god.
Like at the end of the day, bro, I can
go I can go to the bank tomorrow and get
out thousands and show you it. Just shut
up, bro. Stop embarrassing yourself.
You're the one that has to be someone's
[ __ ] You're the one that's got no
money, you know? Not me, bro. Shut up,
bro. And you don't get three grand a
month either. Don't force it. Tony,
where Hey, Tony, why don't you tell us
where you live, bro? Don't force it.
Don't force it. Stop it. Don't force it.
You don't even live in London either,
for [ __ ] sake. Probably somewhere like
[ __ ] Middles, bro. Don't force it,
bro. Don't force it. [ __ ] hell. Stop
exaggerating. It's not good, man. You
live in Grinidge. Yeah. And and and you
know, you know why three grand is not is
not a lot of money to you? It's because
you pay half of it out, you [ __ ]
idiot. You know what I'm saying, bro?
It's because you have to pay half of it
out, you [ __ ] dweeb. You're probably
not even left with a grand left. No
wonder you say that it's [ __ ]
nothing, you idiot. No wonder you say
that it's [ __ ] it's nothing, you
idiot. Cuz you pay more than half of it [ __ ] out.
Obviously, I get more than that and I
can make even more if I wanted to, but
I'm a bit lazy and I have 150 outgoings.
So, bro, again, stop comparing your
situation to everyone
else's. I could probably make about five
grand a month if I wanted one or two,
but I'm a bit lazy in it. So,
yeah. There will come a day though, bro.
You're paying half of your money on
rent, you [ __ ] idiot. No wonder it's
[ __ ] nothing. Who [ __ ] does that?
Or whatever it is you pay or whatever it
pay. So, yeah.
Yeah, it is nothing. But three grand a
month for doing nothing is nothing.
Wait, three to get three grand a month
for doing nothing is nothing, bro. Do
you hear yourself? Like, do you
literally hear yourself? Stop it, bro.
Stop embarrassing yourself. So, getting
three grand a month and pract and
practically having no outgoings a month is
nothing. That's pretty much almost a
grand a week,
bro. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Wait,
so you got no outgoings but like 150 150
rather? That's almost a grand a
month. That's almost a grand a month.
What are you talking about for doing
nothing? A grand a week, sorry. For
doing nothing. What are you talking
about about it?
Nothing. You're an idiot, bro. Go get
some life experience, you fantasist. And
stop defending women. You might actually
get somewhere in
life. Okay. So, how much? Okay. So,
you're how Okay. Okay. So, out of your
£3,000, how much are you left with every month?
No car, no job, no home. Stop talking
about yourself. Got a job, got a home,
got money. Stop talking about yourself.
Anyways, um, on to you, Tony. I do have
algorithms. My algorithms are nearly
Yeah, [ __ ] That's why you think
three grand a month is nothing because
2K of it goes out. More than 50% of it
goes out, you [ __ ] idiot.
No wonder it's nothing to you. I've just
told you I have literally basically no
outgoings. Basically no outgoings. You
[ __ ] dweeb. Yeah. So that's what I'm saying.
Yeah. You're an idiot, bro. Imagine
that. Working to get three grand a
month. Yeah. To get three grand a month. Yeah. And
[ __ ] more than half of it's going
out. That's embarrassing, bro. That's
how you know you failed in life. That's
how you know at your age if you're still
being someone's [ __ ] Yeah. You just
know you failed in life, bro. Yeah. You
want to You want to preach? Yeah. Let's
let's let's talk about this, bro. Yeah.
Yes. Listen listen. Let's run. Why you
Why are you working for someone, bro? If
you're so small and you know all about
women, why are you still being someone's
[ __ ] at your age? You think I'll ever
be someone's [ __ ] No. Cuz I've got a
brain. I've got a brain, brother. Yeah.
I don't need to be someone's [ __ ] You
understand? Yeah. [ __ ]
me. What I do? Well, how can I claim
benefits and have and have all that
money then? So I So I claim Well, I'm
doing some I'm doing good for somebody
that claims benefits, don't
I? When I can show thousands of
thousands of thousands and I've shown
thousands and thousands of thousands.
Well, maybe you need to get on benefits
then, shouldn't you? If that's how you
think I get money, you know. [ __ ] off,
man. You people on benefits yourself.
You've done the same thing with Seaside
Mark, bro. Listen, with Seaside Mark,
you used to do the same thing to him.
Oh, he's claiming benefits. He's
claiming benefits. All because he's got
more money than you and you ain't got a
life. That's what it is. Yeah. You ain't
got a life. Your job pays [ __ ] if you
got a job. And you used to do it with
Cai Mark. You used to do it with Casside
Mark. Well, let me tell you what I won't
why I won't be at your age, Tony. Being
someone's [ __ ] defending women on
YouTube. That's what I won't be doing.
Oh, why don't you tell us how old you are
anyways? Why don't you actually tell us
how old you are? You should tell Why
don't you tell us how Why don't you tell
us how old you are? Come
on. Why don't you actually tell us,
right? Why don't you tell us how old you
are? Come on. You can't even do that.
Why don't you tell us how old you are,
mate? You're a [ __ ] idiot. You're an
absolute [ __ ] idiot, mate. I won't be
I won't be at your age on [ __ ]
YouTube being someone's [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah. Getting a save. Think of it like
this, right? Okay. Okay. Tell us how old
you are and I'll compare it. You're 47.
How does it feel that a 27y old gets
more money than you? Okay. Okay. Let's
talk about people failing in life. Yeah.
How does it make you feel that 27 gets
27 year old gets more money than you?
I'm 30 years younger than you and I get
more money than you and I got a better
life than you. How does that make you
feel, bro? So, God only knows where I'm
going to be in [ __ ] 5 years. 47, a 47
year old man and bro, I get more money
than you and I'm left with more money
than you at the end of the month. So,
bro, if I'm getting [ __ ] benefits,
mate, then that's [ __ ] good, isn't
it? Come on. Keep be real with yourself,
bro. Come on. It's embarrassing. It's
embarrassing. It's really embarrassing,
bro. My man's 30 years older than me on
the dot. Yeah. I'm coming out with more
money than him and I'm left with more
money than him and he's trying to
preach. He's trying to [ __ ] preach. That's embarrassing, bro.
[ __ ] Yeah. Of course she did, bro. Cool
she did. Of course she did, bro. Yeah.
You keep telling yourself that, man. You
keep telling yourself that.
Yeah, you're [ __ ] Oh, yeah. 20 years.
Yeah, it's 20 years. My bad. You're 20
years older than me, bro. And I'm
getting more money than you. How? How?
You know, at your age, if you were
successful, you wouldn't have to. You
wouldn't need to work. You said that
you've got assets worth a million. Why
are you still working then? Why are you
still working? That doesn't make any
sense. Why are you still working? Yeah.
If you were so successful back in the
day, No, no, no, no, no, no, no. You're
an old man. Why are you still working for
peanuts? You said you got assets worth a
million. No. No. No. So what the [ __ ]
bro? It doesn't even make any sense.
Worth 2 million. So why are you working
for nothing every month then? Okay. 3K a
month is nothing. Yeah. Yeah, it is
nothing. So why are you working for
nothing every every
month? Why are you working for nothing
every month? That doesn't sound very
successful. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Listen, why are you
working for nothing every month then,
bro? Come on. You're 47. You should know
better. You're a [ __ ] [ __ ] mate.
Honestly, you're a [ __ ] twit. You're
a twit, aren't you, buddy? [ __ ]
twit. Anyways, I'm going to go now. Make
myself a cup of [ __ ] Losers.