I [ __ ] woke up late today, mate.
[ __ ] 11:00. That ain't like me, buddy.
Yeah, that ain't like me.
11:00. Yeah, I woke this [ __ ] a long ass [ __ ] hour,
bro. Being deadly serious as well,
mate. What are they? 5 hours behind. 5
hours behind. What is that? 3:00 in the
morning. Yeah. Probably like woke up at 11:00,
bro. That is not like me, mate.
But I just wanted to ensure that there
weren't going to be a load of old Bill
because there's no fun in that log when
there's old Bill. There's piggies. That
just takes fun out of it.
So watch some long ass paragraph,
bro. I'm being deadly serious, bro. You
know where I've not gone out. I've saved
this [ __ ] money and [ __ ] and
I Yeah. I just said, uh,
uh, two days next week, give one. We'll
see you the keyboard
warriors. That's it.
Yeah, I know what made me write that
photo. I was just pissed off at like
3:00 in the morning. See, this [ __ ] keep
commenting time and time and time and time again.
Yeah. I said, "You're fast enough to to
beg the black man in England." You're
fast enough to beg the black man in
England. Am I alive? No. So, let's see
what you're about when someone's
actually in your country. And this time,
don't pretend you're in [ __ ] you're
in the other side of the [ __ ]
country. You know what I'm
saying? Beg the black man. Beg the black
man. The real question is why haven't
any of your people done
anything? You know, why have you changed
your number? Don't [ __ ] start begging
[ __ ] black man in [ __ ] England.
You know what I'm saying? Sneaker
[ __ ] But whooping ass, bro. You have
your [ __ ] chance if you give a
day. I said bring your mouthy X with you
as well. That's what I said. [ __ ]
Yeah, we caught them on a couple of
sites as of recently as well.
A couple of sites, man.
No. Hey, bro. I wrote that bits of
message. Do you want to know what I
wrote? No. No. No. No. No. All
right. Right. Let me read it out to you quick,
brother. This [ __ ] was pissing me off. Yeah. One
second. No, here it
is. That's what I wrote.
Yeah, I need to minimize a bit more.
Why? You stupid coward little [ __ ] I
noticed you have you s haven't replied
to my email and laughed my ass off.
You're such a lame keyboard warrior
[ __ ] like Daddy Jobert. All you can do
is make group chats about people, make
up stories, then block. It must run in
the family. Funny how you was begging a
black man on Instagram to do your dirty
work because I spoke about I quote he's
kids in an argument I had [ __ ] all to do
with you. Listen up, [ __ ] I've
violated you. I made you change your number.
I made you change your number and your
family countless times and you and no
one has done a thing about it but keep
blocking every time I've tried to meet
you. You even told your father to tell
me you was in California when I said I
was there last time. The fact also has
your new boyfriend found out how much of
a hoe you are yet and that's why no man
stays with you just like how Charles
left you. It's so bad. I wouldn't even
need to lie about anything I say about
you. All I need to say is your body
count and you told me you had an STD.
Does he know you can't afford your own
food and weed? Listen, I'll show you and
your pig dad how much of a keyboard
warrior I am. I'm prepared to come next
said day and the other said, I'm not
going to say which day I said in case
they they say yeah. We're saying word
for you and bring your stupid dad and
your Mexican looking boyfriend and see
if any man stops me putting you in your
place and teaching you some manners. Oh,
and tell your short ass ex Damon to come
as well since the fact he tried getting
brave with his stupid whiny accent. and
let's see what you or anyone you know
will do before preaching to others about
what they should be doing to me. You're
just a broke ass worthless skank and I'm
not scared of you or anyone you know and
I'll make sure by the time I come back
to the UK everybody in America knows
what you're about. Anyway, pick a day
next week and I'll be there this time.
Don't pretend you're in California for
[ __ ] sake. Let's see. Let's let's show
your father who the real keyboard
warrior who is a who who the real
keyboard warrior is and what you or
anyone you know would actually do when
I'm in your country instead of begging a
black man in England. You kimp. Anyways,
next Anyways, day next week. Chop chop.
Don't be a keyboard warrior like your father
says. That's what I said, bro. I'm being serious as
well. I'm actually being serious, bro.
As soon as they say a day, I'm going
next week. Did you like that little paragraphy?
Yeah. 100%, bro.
100%. 100%, mate. I'm going to make LJ
go back on this [ __ ] channel cuz he's
been quiet recently. Recently, I don't
like it. I said, pick a day out of two
days next week and I will be there.
Trust me. Yeah, you [ __ ] kind. I've
seen you on different social medias as well, mate.
Yeah, I've seen you on different social
medias. You're begging LT. You're
begging a black man to do [ __ ] And let
me guess, none of your black people are
going to be around when I'm there. So
why are you begging someone else to do
your dirty work about whoop your ass,
mate? Listen, even your ex trying to say
he's going to cut my dick off, bro. He
can't He wouldn't even be able to reach
my dick. He's that short. He's that
short. He wouldn't even be able to reach
my dick. For [ __ ] sake, please stop
it. You know, it's embarrassing, mate.
And that's all I said. and nothing
nothing abusive, you know. That's it.
You stupid little [ __ ] [ __ ]
mate. That's it. Talking about
yourself. So, yeah, bro. Yeah, the girls
are waiting for you. Yeah, I'm waiting
for this girl to [ __ ] reply back so I
can come next
week. Let's see who the real keyboard
warrior is. Let's see who the real
keyboard warrior is. People always are
people that [ __ ] make group chats but
won't [ __ ] meet anyone. You know what
I'm saying? [ __ ] idiot, man. [ __ ]
off. You're not about
nothing. You're not about nothing, mate. Trust
me. Yeah, he invites me out, but very
rarely because he knows I don't go out
with him anymore. So, yeah. Saturday.
You can stay Saturday all at once.
That's Yeah, you are still on there, you
little coward. Let's get rid of
her. Yeah, you are. You are still on
there, you little coward. Let's get rid
of you. You like that one, Grezy? Yeah,
the coward is still on here. I've had to
get rid of him. That was a good one, is
it, Grezy? Come on. You have to admit
that was a good one. Yep, the coward is
still on here and I've just got rid of
it. Biggest coward going. Look, he's gone now.
Is this is Saturday when all the
spastics come on or
something? No, I'm all right, mate. I'm staying
in. Might get a McDonald's, but no, I'm staying in,
mate. I'll be staying in, mate. I don't
want any more bad experiences, Greasy. I
was up at 3:00 in the [ __ ] morning
typing that [ __ ] paragraph. All
because of a cold approach, Grezy.
Yep, there you are. YouTube's biggest
embarrassment. Bye-bye now. I'll stop
you embarrassing yourself. Saturday must
be the day the spastics come on the self
projectors. H We've never had this
yesterday, did we? Grezy, really? Or the
day before? Saturday must be when all
the spastics come out and self
project. Strange. I'll keep that day in mind.
But I won't be going out,
mate. If this [ __ ] says a [ __ ] day
I'm going next week, 100% I'm there. So
at the end of the [ __ ] day. Yeah.
Like this is because of a cold approach.
This is the problems that it's caused
all of this. So why the [ __ ] would I go
out and speak to women again when I know
that they're [ __ ] evil? Every single
last one of
them. It's [ __ ] ridiculous,
bro. [ __ ] time wasting. Evil. [ __ ]
that. I'd rather do nothing.
I'd ra I'm just going to get a nice
McDonald's today. That's what I'm going
to do. Get a nice
McDonald's. You got to do
something. I told you I
was meant it.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Skinn virgin mate. How
many times have I showed you people
money and you've run away? Stop self-p
projecting your own life, mate. You're
in your 40s. You've got no money. You
are a virgin. Yeah. Stop talking about
yourself. You got showed money 3 weeks
ago and you ran away again. You have
been shown money time and time and time
again and you run away. Stop talking
about yourself. You're skin virgin.
Yeah. Just like if I was to go to the
bank right now and withdraw money, you
run away just like you always do. Go
self-reflect on another channel,
loser. Stop talking about yourself,
loser. Loser boy. I have not been
skinned. Literally for about three
years. Literally for about 3 years, I've
not been skinned. Stop talking about
yourself, mate. Money is everything to
you people because you ain't got no
money. Yeah. I'm going to go to America
next week if this country gives me a
day. Do you know how much that's going
to cost me? Huh? It's going to cost me a lot of
money, right? So, stop talking about
yourself, man. Come up with a different comeback. Stop
self-rejecting. [ __ ] it. Now, how many
times you people been showing money,
bro? [ __ ] millions of times. And
every time you get show money, you run
away, bro. Stop embarrassing yourself
now. You people asking that's why you're
on YouTube all day, every day
hating. And I think that's
um that was important to put it that
way. is you're the one you keep
hating cuz your own lives are [ __ ] You
know, you don't see me coming on here hating
anyone. Do you understand?
Well, yeah. I remember I told my sister
about this cactus. She says, "No, you're
taking it too far." I was I'll tell you
when [ __ ] up, mate. just so I said
next week so they couldn't try to make excuses again. You
know, I just think the whole world
should know what you're about,
bro. Talking about yourself
again, mate. You're getting me confused
with yourself. I don't know how many
accounts I'm going to have to keep
blocking. Stop talking about yourself.
It's no good for your mental health. It
really is no good for your mental
health. See, the thing is, catch is even
if I had like a wife and I had children,
I would still do this because it's not
jealousy. I just don't like the person.
And I just want everyone to know what
they're like, what they're
about, you know? Like, you understand? I
could I could have a [ __ ] mansion. I
could have a [ __ ] wife. I could have
kids and I'd still be doing
this because my opinion people should
know what this country is actually like. Do you
understand? So that's my bro. So
yeah. How was the barbecue? It was good,
bro. Yeah, it was very nice. Very nice.
Had some Ben's ice cream as
well. So, let's see if this talk replies
back to this message. You're not about
nothing, mate. And I even told you to
bring two people, your ex and your
current boyfriend. And not one man is
ever going to stop me, bro. Trust me. So, that's
it. Yeah, I'm just chilling today, bro.
I might get a McDonald's. I don't know
what I'm doing yet. Should we be getting
take away again? But apologies to be
fair cuz I like the coke. But I don't
know what I'm doing
yet. I woke up late, bro. I just not
like me to wake up at 11. Every time I
sleep in, I get a
headache. It's cuz I'm up to 3:00
writing that kind of
message. Yeah. [ __ ] wrote a nice paragraph, mate.
I completely bodied them in that
paragraph G. I completely bodied them,
mate. In it. I completely body them,
lad it. I [ __ ] bodied the [ __ ] Literally.
Yeah. [ __ ] madness, isn't
it? So, that's where we're at, bro.
That's where we're
at. At least I'll be spending about 13
pounds a day on
McDonald's and not
[ __ ] you know not [ __ ]
uh um you know 100 150 going out
drinking hearing about make
boyfriends. That's a that's a positive
is it Greasy? Yeah. See Greasy thought I
was going to go out today. Nah, nah,
mate. Nah, mate. I told you I was I was
serious, bro. You should believe people
with this when they're serious. Believe
me when I'm serious. Yeah.
Yeah. But you do believe you do believe
me now, when I said that. Oh, [ __ ]
me. Yeah, you can.
Yeah. Can't stand women. They're all the
[ __ ] same, mate. Every single [ __ ] one of
them. Yeah. Every single one. All of
them. Every single one of them. All of
them. All of them. All of them. Yes.
I won't say
it. So, yeah, that's
Yeah, probably got to make some money to be
honest, but got enough money. So,
You understand, don't you,
Grezy? Might even get a McDonald's now,
Grezy. But more I have
later. Might just have a McDonald's now,
though. We're just talking to McDonald's
making me want one.
Um, no, not yet. It's a bit too early. I
don't know what I have
later is the thing understand later.
Yeah, M's a bit hungry now, but then I'd
have to eat something later anyway, so
I'd have to
wait. Don't know why these people tried
to call me skin greasy when I probably
got more money than anybody on this
community. That's how bad it
is. Cuz they're self objecting, isn't
it? They've got to be talking about themselves,
lad. Yeah, that's the truth, man. But
I'm not going out today. I give up with
women in this country, Desmond. They
just cause nothing but trouble. Or
America or Australia, they're all the
same. All the same [ __ ] All the same
I'll [ __ ] go there next week and be
her new daddy, mate. And that's not even
being a keyboard warrior, we actually
being [ __ ] serious, mate. And you
know when I'm being serious as well,
I'll be her new daddy. Teach her some [ __ ] manners, mate. You
know, teach you some good oldfashioned manners.
I can't be bothered to cook today,
lad. Yeah, but the stupid [ __ ] was
trying to say that she was in [ __ ]
California last time. So, I said to her
yesterday, just give me a day next week
and I'm coming. Simple. Not this back
and forth Monty Timmy [ __ ] Two, I give
you two days next week. Yeah.
Or Yeah. Two days. I'll add a third one.
Tell me when you're free and I'm I'm
coming. and let's see what your people do about
it. Let's see what your people do about
it. You know, I said, "Bring your
[ __ ] Mexican looking boyfriend as
well." That's what I said. Not scared of
you or anyone you [ __ ] know, mate. Understand
that [ __ ] Yeah. And this is was from
a cold approach and other things that's
happened recently. So, is it really
worth pursuing these people? Nah,
they're [ __ ] Absolute [ __ ] mate. [ __ ]
[ __ ] about how people should whip my
ass. People should whoop my ass,
mate. No, it's not California. It's
[ __ ] Boston. I'm going. And I've got
somebody that lives in New York as well.
I've got a friend that lives in New
York, so it won't be no problem, mate.
Probably about 7800 pound of flights.
It's not a problem, man. And I'll just
stay with them.
You know, I could even say for 5 days,
really, 5 days, a week, whatever. Just
let me know the day, [ __ ] And then
you'll have your [ __ ] chance to get
people to whoop my ass. Stupid little
snaky little [ __ ] Soon, shut the [ __ ]
up, though. And I [ __ ] come and
right, don't you, you [ __ ] you know,
messaging other people. [ __ ] [ __ ] mate.
Yeah. Doesn't matter how much it costs,
bro. It doesn't matter how much it
costs. It's not California. It's They
were saying they were in California.
That's what it
was. Yeah, I know about it, bro. I know all about
it. I just put this [ __ ] in her [ __ ]
place, bro. Once and for real
life. See, G is a crazy [ __ ] like
me. I know about it, bro. people people
I know the history behind it and all
that. It's like the um Canadian most of
the people in Canada are
French native because the French
uh family or immigrated
it. Yeah. But you know I'm serious
though. Is it Greasy? Yeah. You know I'm
serious. I'm a Yeah. I'm a crazy
[ __ ] Yeah, but we're both crazy
[ __ ] Why are you typing [ __ ] on your
Facebook, man? Apologize. Say sorry, you little
[ __ ] Yeah, it's like the French were
Canada. Yeah, the Irish went to Boston.
Yeah, I know. They immigrated. They
found it. I know the history, bro. You know, not
stupid. Grey, if they give a day, bro,
I'm You're going to see Apple videos.
You're going to get all you
wanted. You're going to get all you wanted, lads.
Yeah. You can just tell Guji is just
going to sit there with his popcorn, is it?
Yeah. Oh, I love it, man. I love
it. She would never say anything to
anyone's face. She's a [ __ ] coward. She
is just like her dad. How can I be the
one that's a keyboard boy when I'm
trying to say it to their face and
they're the ones that have to hide behind group
chats? I'm innocent in this, aren't I,
Guzy? Nah, it's to tell her about
herself to her [ __ ] face. And I told
her, bring your boyfriend as well. Try
and bring your boyfriend and see what
happens. See if that stops me. Even
bring your boyfriend as well. Bring your
[ __ ] boyfriend and bring your your
[ __ ] ex, you know? That little murky
[ __ ] That fat Homer Simpson.
Yeah, mate. Americans are weak, man. The
O'Neals. How many people got banned from
the O'Neals in central London because
they used to [ __ ] up the Americans?
They're weak, mate. Trust me. Without
guns, they're weak. They're proper
weak. She's Syrian.
Yeah, the proper proper week, bro.
Proper week. They're not about nothing.
Trust me, they're not about nothing. And
it's not even that I'm wanting them to
reply back. I just want a date. Even if
you just said a date, that's a date. I
don't want you reply back, Jim, just
with a date, you
know? I'd have to put this on my main
channel as well, mate, because Yeah, I'd
have to put this on my [ __ ] main channel.
That should get like a million views.
Yeah. I'll jump on a little train, Greg
to the airport, and before you know it,
I'll be up in the
air. Uh, I think you need to chill
out. Yeah, everybody knows that you're a crazy
[ __ ] Yeah, I can't stand women,
Desmond. I can't stand [ __ ] women,
mate. And I was like, what what person
to take it out on than than her? You
know, we should take it out on this
[ __ ] And I said, if I find out who
your boyfriend is, I'm just going to
tell him about your body count and [ __ ]
I'm not going to make up stuff. I don't
need to lie. I don't need to make up
stuff. Know what I'm saying? So, I'm not
going to search for him, but if I come
across him on comments, he's getting
messages, mate. Yeah. Let me stop being
a [ __ ] to you until you can face me. Let
me stop being a [ __ ]
Yeah, [ __ ] [ __ ] No reply. I
checked when I woke up as well.
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] bro. She was
trying to tell London Taylor to whip my
ass because I said stuff about his kids
in an argument that's got nothing to do
with him. Yeah. Why don't you [ __ ]
whip someone's ass? How about that,
Grez? How about anyone you know whip my
ass, bro? It would never happen, mate.
And remember what I said, Grezy, when I
go over there, bro, it's me or them. You
know that in Grezy? Yeah, it's me or them, mate.
Simple. It's me or
them. Yeah. Yeah, I want to tell her how
much of a cowardly little [ __ ] she
is. I will make sure, bro, I will make
sure that any relationship she gets
into, everyone knows what she's like.
Cuz I feel like that people like that
should die alone. Even if I'm in a
relationship, even if I've got kids,
doesn't matter where I am in my life,
I'm still going to do it because people
like that shouldn't be allowed um to be
with anyone greasy.
Unless it's a really toxic
relationship. Like doesn't matter if I
was single, not single, I've got kids,
I've got money, I'm scared, I would still do
it. You know, in a way I'm protecting
society. If you think about it, bro, I'm actually protecting society for
more heartbreaks, I
guess. I don't know, bro.
You was the same with your narcissist, Grezy. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, you was the same with your [ __ ] narcissist,
lad. Nah, I just don't like [ __ ]
mate. Not even obsessed. Not even, bro.
You know, [ __ ] [ __ ] Just give me
the day next week and I'm getting on
that plane. End of. I'm going to get LJ
back on this
channel. See, me and LJ go way
back. Isn't that right, Greasy? Me and
LJ go way
back. Well, your your one or my
one? My one. Yeah. I don't care about it
anymore. I don't really ever go on their
Facebook. I just done it last night cuz
I was bored. Yeah, but I'll still smack
them up if I ever see them. So, it's not
like it's not die down. You see how me
and LT the thing died down or with me
and the neighbor, it's died down. Some
things never die down. That's what I'm
trying to say to you, bro. Some things
like never die down. And if they do die
down, they don't fully die down. Like,
say you wanted to go and I guess break
into someone's house and you don't do it.
But I would still if they moved here, I
would go on their doorstep. But I guess
you just wouldn't maybe care as much.
But you would still do
something. Yeah. I don't think it dies
down, bro. Not that kind of
stuff. With my mom's neighbor, he didn't
really know me, so it's nothing really
there, you know. But with
that, I would I would never walk past
them. Like if you ever seen if you ever
saw them on the street, would you walk
past them grooves? I wouldn't walk past
them. I would make a [ __ ] scene. So,
but I don't care. It's two years. I
don't care. I don't think about it. But
I was just bored yesterday and I thought
I just write that, you know, cuz I
couldn't sleep. But I was being serious.
I will back up my talk at the same
time. You know what I'm saying?
Cuz them kind of people, they ruin
dating for a lot of people. You know
what I'm saying, Grezy? They ruin dating for
people, you know, and other women, they
ruin it for
people. So, it's no different than um child
abuse, you know, where people are
affected for years after. You know what I'm saying?
Imagine that mate sitting down on the
table Thanksgiving eating food
right and then them going on about me
greasy. Oh, have you got a message from
this person? Have you got a message from
Yeah, that's funny, bro. That's funny,
bro. H But
yeah, they all like to I I don't bother
with them anymore. They're just
evil. I don't bother with them anymore,
Desmond. They're just evil, lads. You
know, I went out um last bank holiday. I
think it was a month
ago. I don't know if I told you this
story. I had some woman approach me. I
hadn't been on a date for ages. So then
she traveled an hour to meet me. Date
was fine. Bought each other rounds. I
said, "I've not been on a date for ages.
[ __ ] hell. Let me give this a little
whirl. Let me give this a try." Then it
was a Thursday. I said, "Oh, when do you
want to meet again?" Then she said she
doesn't feel the vibe. I was like, "You
don't feel the vibe? What? What are you
talking about?" I was thinking in my
head and like I said in my video that's
a taste of what my future dating life
was going to be in this country and I
was like [ __ ] this then I started doing
the approach on the Thursday met someone
else that tried using me then I went out
again in two weeks after then
um two weeks after and then
um yeah I messaged and got ghosted so I
just gave up after that
really I just gave up from there just
knew was was just going to be a waste of
time. They're all the same. They're all
evil. So, there's no point pursuing them
or having anything to do with them. You
know, they say not all women are the
same. But they say pigs fly. So, and
I've never seen one of
them. Yeah, they're [ __ ] I can't
stand them. Literally can't stand it, mate. A
wankers picking a wanker.
Yeah. That's where we're at,
mate. I didn't know it was two years ago,
lad. Listen, I didn't know yours was two
years ago, Greavves. I don't know. I
didn't know it was going on that long.
[ __ ] hell, mate. You really are a crazy
[ __ ] No, I don't think about it every
day. I just don't bother. I don't bother
with them no
more. I just don't bother with them cuz
they're all the same. I don't I don't
think about it every day. I just gave up
cuz they're all the same. I'm going
Thailand now anyways in six weeks. So,
doesn't bother me, mate. Doesn't bother
me one little bit.
So, doesn't matter what's the longest
relationship I've ever
had cuz you wouldn't believe it anyways. So, doesn't
matter. It's not relevant to anything
we're talking about. So, so
yeah, they make you that way. Desine
deeds. Love the picture, bro. They make
you like that.
They make you like that,
mate. And you asking why did you go to
Thailand? I guess it's just something to
look forward to. Uh Grezy, I can go out
today, get my haircut, spend £80, still
save money, still can make money, but
there's no point in me even going out
cuz they're all the
same. And I could be like, "Oh, I got
six weeks to go, five weeks to go." Like
people count down their prison
sentences. But I despise them that much
that I don't even want to associate with them anymore.
That's how you know like you are [ __ ] Trust me.
Yeah. I think once you meet them and you
realize they're all the
same then cuz they are all the same then
what's the point of talking to people
and associating with people that are all
the same. It's pointless you
know. Yeah. The worst country for dating
is [ __ ] England, America, Australia, New Zealand, Canada.
Um, that sounds like you sound like a
sassy. They struggled to convince girls.
Here they are, creeps. You just sound
like a s. Anyone that says that stuff,
they just sound like a s.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's the men
that are creeps, isn't it? Yeah. It's
not the women that are stuck up, time
wasters, leading people on, boasting.
Yeah. It's the men that are all all
creepy. Yeah. It's not the women. No.
No. No. Women are perfect. They're
angels. Yeah. It's all It's all All of
the men are creepy. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Just like when you go up to someone and
you start a conversation, they pretend
they got a boyfriend. It's cuz you're
creepy, isn't it? Yeah. It's always the
man's fault, eh? Sucks to be the people
that go to
Thailand. I see these people desperate.
I just go along with what they say
because I know that they've got no
recent life experience. I would say no
life experience period cuz I assume
they're older than
me. Do you know what I'm saying, bro?
They're older than me. But there's no
point trying to like sit here and
explain what women are like to these
people that don't even leave the house,
that don't interact with women. What
person what person would know more than
me, Desmond? I used to go out every
week, twice a week sometimes, dealing
with these women, have to go on dates.
Like, who who would know better than me?
In this day and age, in this day and
age, I mean, you know, women do that to
creepy guys. Oh, okay. All right. Oh,
it's fair enough. Oh, it's cuz the guy
are creepy. Oh, okay. You just sound like a
s. No, it says a lot about their
standards. No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. It says a lot about them being
stuck up and their standards being high.
And I'm not explaining this to you.
There's no point trying to sit here and
explain to somebody that doesn't leave
the house and speak to women what women
are like. It's it's a waste of time.
It's like trying to explain the color
yellow to a [ __ ] blind person. will
be here all day. If these people want to
simp over women and pretend all women
are innocent, leave them to it. I'm not
even going to ban them, you know? Let
them see how that gets them in life.
Let's see how these people sing women
will get them in life. Nowhere. So, just
let them crack on, bro. You're never
going to stop simps anyway. So, just
leave them. Leave them to
it. Let them keep defending women. It's
their life, bro. Ain't it? So yeah,
anyways, end the
conversation. Yeah. And you know this
person, right, that's writing this. He more than
likely hasn't been with a woman for like
a decade, if ever. But this is what
these people do. They do it in
nightclubs as well, bro. They simp over
women. They white night women, but they
still don't get women, and women don't
like them. But they don't have a bad
word to say about women. I know it's
embarrassing, bro. Really embarrassing.
They stick up for women even though
women don't like
them. Again, what people say on the
internet and what you experience in real
life, two complete different
things, you know, two complete different things, matey. Yeah. What's up? Yeah. One second. My
boyfriend. Oh, I just watched an
approach video. That's not gonna work.
I've got a boyfriend. [ __ ] off. I don't
You know what? I don't even like
watching it. Even when it's not
happening to me, I don't even like watching
it. [ __ ] hell,
mate. I swear. I think if I hear that
one more time, I think I'll have a mental
breakdown. Um, anyways, I'm not talking
about this with you, bro. I'm not even
giving you the time a day. I'm not
giving you the time a day. There's no
point trying to explain to somebody they
don't even leave the
house. Like I'm not going to sit here
and explain this to you. Like if you
can't figure it
out, right? Oh, I just watched this
black guy approach this woman on the
street. I've got a boyfriend. Where's
your boyfriend then, man? Where is your
Where were their boyfriends? I just
watched this on Instagram. Where's your
Why are they never with their
boyfriend? Yeah, there's no point
explaining it to him, Desmond. There's
no point trying to explain it to him
that. Sorry, bro. Got a bit of a [ __ ]
cough, brother. There's no point trying
to explain it. Just let him keep
defending women and let him s women.
Just leave it. There's no point, bro.
Just leave them. Leave them, lad. And
you know what I think, Desman? I think
when they go on dates, they've got
unrealist unrealistic expectations on a
date as well. I think they're expecting
some kind of Romeo and Juliet type [ __ ]
And then when they don't get it, that's
when they say they don't feel the
connection that they they have
unrealistic, but there's no point trying
to explain it to this guy, bro. He won't
get it. So there's no point. Just leave
it, bro. You're wasting your time
typing. Like, just leave it, bro. All
women are innocent. They ain't got unrealistic
standards. So anyways, stop being this
guy is just a s. He thinks doing all of
this is going to get him laid,
embarrassing, defending women. He thinks
all of this is going to get him laid
when he's probably had less women than
me and you. It's [ __ ] embarrassing.
But there's so many of these people,
bro. You get them in nightclubs as well.
You get them in real life. Ss, white
knights. You get them everywhere, bro.
They defend women because they think
women will get with them. But they hate
them just as much as
they hate us, you know?
Where's her boyfriend anyways? This
black guy, I just seen him approach.
Isn't that mad, Esman? How they've all
got boyfriends, but they're clubbing
until 600 7:00 in the morning. 6 7:00 in
the morning, but they've all got
boyfriends. Isn't that a
madness? Yeah. Isn't that a madness? But they've got
boyfriends. Why is their boyfriends
never with them? That's what I wonder
when I watch these approaching videos.
Their boyfriend's never with them.
[ __ ] hell. I spell
[ __ ] Do you know what? Since I said
that, yeah, no one ever come back and
try saying anything. [ __ ] boyfriend.
And they wouldn't even say boyfriend.
When you get to a certain age, it's not
a boyfriend. It's a partner. It's a
[ __ ] husband. Not a [ __ ]
boyfriend. No one uses the word
boyfriend in their [ __ ] 30s. They're
just [ __ ] mate. You'll probably
get the same people in their [ __ ] 40s
saying it as well, bro, to be fair.
So yeah, they're just they're just complete [ __ ]
mate. That's what they
are. I don't even like hearing it happen
to other people. It's boring,
mate. [ __ ] boring. That is.
Yeah. Anyways, I'm done arguing with you,
mate. I'm done arguing with you, S.
One second. Yeah, I understand, man.
Sorry about that, bro. Um, you know,
it's not that I probably am right. I am
right. There's no probably about it. I
am right. Just based on the maths and if
they actually did have a boyfriend,
would they be happy with their
girlfriend coming home at 6 7:00 in the
morning? I'm not discussing anything
with you anymore. Bye-bye now. you're banned. So
yeah, there's no point of having someone
on there just to argue and argue and
they don't listen to what you say and
then they're just going to simp over
women. There's no point. That's not even
somebody having a different opinion.
That's just a [ __ ] simp. It's not
even somebody having a different opinion.
This is someone that has no life
experience trying to tell you how it is
and then you're just disagreeing. So
there's no point in them. There's no
point having them on
there. But yeah, it's not that I'm
probably right. I am [ __ ]
right. 70 80% of men are single. 95% of
women claim they've got boyfriends, but
they're never with their boyfriends. Use
do the math. So
yeah, anyway going like this anyways
going to be live again later.
Yeah, people should join in.
Yeah. Yeah. Anyways, I'll be back later.
Yeah. Is there even a point having a
woman? No, there's there's there's no
point. There is no point. That's not
that's the whole point. There is no
point. Like, I don't even get a sex
drive anymore. No, there is no point.
There literally is no point,
bro. No, there is no point, mate.
There literally is no
point. They're just [ __ ]
evil. Evil stuck up. Yeah. But yeah,
they do have unrealistic standards. Desmond. It's
like they [ __ ] in this country. You use
the dating apps, they don't work. You
approach, they pretend they got
boyfriends. Even when you get dates,
they're time wasted. They've just got
unrealistic. It's like But it's like
what you said, unrealistic standards. Um it's
uh it is
unrealistic. And that's what I told you
right there. Someone's approached you,
they've gone to meet you, and then they
said in half an hour they don't feel the vibe.
So, it's obviously they've got
unrealistic standards, unrealistic
expectations. I like to say expectations
rather than standards because look, you
can look decent, you can smell good, you
can be outgoing, I'm outgoing, and then
they somehow will claim they can't feel
the vibe. So, it's got to be they've got unrealistic
expectations. So, that's an
example. Of course, it's unrealistic.
And what's the point of trying to match
people's unrealistic expectations? It
don't make sense, bro. So, I just can't be bothered, you
know? But I don't even get any cravings
desperate to go out
anymore. I've saved so much money. Why
do you think I'm able to [ __ ] go
America next week if this [ __ ] wants to
[ __ ] run up her [ __ ] mouth?
Yeah. Like I said, if I was going to do
something today, I'd be out making
money. I'd just be out making money.
I've got ways to make money. I just I'm
not going to get into it, but legal
ways, you know, I wouldn't even be out
drinking. I literally wouldn't even be
out drinking. I'd be out making
money. So, and then just have a
McDonald's or something and then just
chill. I wouldn't even go out, bro.
These breaks are
imperative. They're imperative. these breaks,
bro. I said six weeks minimum, did I? So, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Women can't cook. Trust me.
You know, I got friends. Yeah. And they
cook for me. And their cooking is
banging, mate. It tastes way better than
[ __ ] um a restaurant. How a woman
cooks. Women can't cook. Trust me, bro.
Trust me. You know, you you go to like a
a man from India or Jamaica or whatever,
not a restaurant, and you get them to
cook for you, bro, it's another level. It hits
differently. It hits differently, bro. Trust
me. So, women can't even
cook. Nah, they can't even cook, mate.
That's the thing. They literally can't
even cook, mate. Not like a black man, bro.
Trust like an Indian man. They can't
[ __ ] cook. But trust it's different
me. I get my friend. Yeah. He cooks me a biryani.
Yeah. And it's different, bro. It's
different. Yeah. And then when I go to
my mom's and then I get and then I get
one from the restaurant, it tastes like
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying? When you
have proper food cooked for you, right,
you're nervous for your [ __ ] no cooked.
Yeah. Anyways, I'll be back later, by
the way. Yeah.