Oh yeah, I just left out. Went to
PC last cheese. You know what?
Now, you know, again. Good
old SC. Good
treat, mate. Got better things
to my money on. Yeah,
deleted my comment as
well. Delete my comment. [ __ ] [ __ ]
You know about that
life. Not about that
life. You know about
for a little longer. Yeah. [ __ ] Itch.
Itch. Nice pipe with a couple of ice
cubes. Oh, can't be that [ __ ] headache,
mate. I got a [ __ ] headache. Get some
post [ __ ] headache, mate. out there. Yes. Sorry, matey. Well, yeah. What's Where Oh,
no. I could have made 150 quid
today. Generally think I could have made
150 quid today, but getting so but
yeah I'm not in a rush don't need money
right now money but even
still no point in going out in this
country anymore to be fair like
But you can't go out
like know the [ __ ] I'm saying. So we
can't go out,
right? I think three days I could have
definitely made about 500. Definitely. Yeah.
trainers are like 175 now. Going to buy
some new ones, but my vapors are still
semidecent and I got some Harachis, but
who cares about
thousand had to
go? I need to spend a lot of [ __ ]
garments. You know what I'm saying, bro? [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm going to have a bath. I reckon
I'm going to have a bath. Me
thinks right. Anyways, I'll be back later.