I'm
fat. Are you proud of me, Brit not going
out for a couple of weeks? It's been
nice, you know, man. It's actually been
nice, bro. Not hearing about I've got a
boyfriend. It's been It's been good.
It's been a good
break. It's been a good break, lad.
Yeah, my friend was, "Oh, you didn't go
out yesterday." I was like, "Nah, what's
the point? You're just going to get I've got
boyfriends." Yeah. I don't want to be I
don't want to be bothering um women in
relationships, right? If every single
woman in the world has got a
relationship, why would I want to be
bothering them? You know, who needs that
kind of bothering when apparently
they've all got
boyfriends? Even though they go to
nightclubs till 600 7:00 in the morning,
they're never with their boyfriends. But
yeah, anyways, why would you why would
you want to bother people relationships? [ __ ]
stupid. I'm being sarcastic. If you do figure it
out, I'll go out
again. Don't know where I'll go out
Save lots of
money. Save lots of money,
dad. I'm about 2k in savers
now. Oh man, it's pretty good for
somebody who doesn't do anything, is
it? I was in JD yesterday. I was going
to buy myself a new pair of trainers and
a jumper, but I thought, let me wear the
trainers out first that I've got and
then then I will.
Yeah, I haven't wor trainers since last
summer when I won that
money. So, since I won that [ __ ] four grand. So,
yeah. Yeah. Who the [ __ ] goes out
drinking just to go back into a [ __ ]
hot tub drinking? It's
crazy. But as you get older, you just
don't care in it. I don't really care
about these [ __ ] no more. If I go out
again, it's because I want to go out.
It's not because of them. Otherwise, I'd
be out approaching on the street [ __ ] sober.
You're [ __ ] evil,
son. I've got more than Lord J, mate, in
every [ __ ] way. I get more money than
him. I've got hair. He doesn't have
hair. He He is He is He is skinned. He
definitely is skin. Definitely is skin. That
L most people here are skinned to be fair.
cuz that's why they're on there every
day. I just use this as like therapy
sessions. I actually use this as therapy sessions, you know. Yeah.
Yeah. Women are evil, shifty, [ __ ] evil [ __ ] They are
evil. I've calmed down a bit from the
past couple of
days. This is why um this is why I said
the breaks are imperative because you
literally need to like take long
breaks. He's got kids. Something I'll
never have, mate. He doesn't even spend
time with his kids. And I can have kids
if I wanted to. Yeah, he has kids, but
he's never with his kids. Yeah. Some
father. Yeah. Yeah. He's got kids, but
he's on YouTube all day every day. Yeah,
I know. I know.
Yeah. Yeah. He's got kids, but he's on
YouTube every day. Yeah. Makes sense, it
uh No, cuz I've given up Hell's
Bells. I've got more money than him.
I've got hair. I'm better looking than
him. Okay. He's got kids that he doesn't
even see cuz he's on YouTube every day.
Wow. And I don't want kids. And I've
never wanted kids ever. So what does
that even mean? I literally don't want
kids. Never have, you know, for when
you're young, if you want kids. But I
got something that he don't have. More
money and more
freedom. I think I had too much sugar in
the [ __ ] morning, bro. Heart's
pumping. You got you got a number
yesterday. That's nice, man. Glad to
hear. I've given up with the dating [ __ ]
Yeah, having kids is not a good thing,
you know. It's actually a drain to your
life having having a
kid. I never want kids ever. I'm too
selfish. Like, you're saying it like
it's a flex having a
kid. That's just a drain in your life.
Everyone I know that's had kids, right?
Right. Everyone I know that's had
kids, their lives are worse than mine.
Um, have you looked in the mirror,
Hellsb? No. No. No. I think there's
somebody that's been rejected more than
me. Uh, have you looked in the mirror lately,
mate? Do you know what's so bad,
Notorious, is that I've been seen with
more women than anybody on this
community. And then they still talk [ __ ]
about me and they still try to def Like
whenever you say things that other men
are scared to say, you get [ __ ] for
it. Have you noticed that? You get [ __ ]
for it, bro. It's weird. Even though
I've been with more women than these
people, they still
[ __ ] they they still give you
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying? Do you
think I give a [ __ ] that LJ's made some
ugly kids that he doesn't see? What does
that mean, bro? I live in London. I get
more money than him. I've got more money
than him. You think I care that
someone's got some ugly kids that he don't see?
What would why would somebody be jealous
of somebody having ugly kids
ugly disgusting kids that he doesn't
even care for? Please, bro, give your head a
wobble. Yeah. Sorry if I insulted your
little boyfriend by calling him skint.
But he is [ __ ] skint. He literally is
skint. Yeah. Who sits on YouTube on a Friday,
Saturday [ __ ] all day long drinking
in a gap if you're not [ __ ]
skin? Come on,
bro. But I can't I don't like women
notorious. I can't stand him, bro. I
literally can't stand
him. Like, so I'm probably not the best
channel to go on, bro. If you're looking
for like positivity, I can't stand
them. Like, the other day, bro, I was I
was very I was close to doing something,
bro. if I knew where one of these people
lived. I even gave that Morgan [ __ ] um
two days ago at 3:00 in the morning,
bro. Not abusive, not keyboard warrior
[ __ ] but just basically saying if
you're about it, give me a day next week
and I'll go there because we're not all
skin like L J. I gave her some mad like
just telling her about herself again,
you know, really didn't hear anything
back. Didn't expect
to. I just basically say that you're
fast enough to beg the black man in
England to do your dirty [ __ ] work,
but we all know you and nobody that
you're associated with is about
anything. You know what I'm saying? Just
just just it wasn't abusive. Like, oh,
you're this, you're that, but it's just
facts basically in it, bro. But I'm glad
you're you're doing it again, bro. I
don't think I will try again in this country.
If I could see a point in doing it in
the tourist, then I
would. Sitting on a chair for an hour,
spending4 to get your hair, your beard
done just to hear I've got boyfriends.
It just seems like a waste of
time. You know, I live in a, you know, I
have my friend, he cooks for me. Um, my
friend cooks for me. I get to go on
walks. I don't need that in my life
anymore, bro. you
know, they only reply to
negativity. Um, so why would I want to
be associated with them kind of people?
Why do I want anything to do with them
people? You know what I'm
saying? Yeah. But yeah, that shifty is up
ass. Yeah. Just like when Bomb used to
say that he's got kids and kids is
something that I'll never have. And look
at the state of it, bro. These people on
here, notorious are just they're just
losers. These people are here. Just 40 year old
losers. Late 30s, late 40s. Just losers.
They ain't got a life.
Yeah. I would have just went there next
week and just rented a [ __ ] apartment
for a month to be fair, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Why don't you text the number? Do
you know what, bro? Don't even Don't
even tell me about it, bro. Cuz I know
what's going to
happen. You're going to text a number,
they're not going to reply. They're
going to reply and then stop replying. I
don't want to hear about it, bro. To be
fair. It just pisses me off hearing
about it. Even when it happens to other
people, cuz that is what's going to
happen. Let's face
it. It's annoying, mate.
It's annoying even hearing about
it. Yeah. Not one girl online has ever
said you are attractive. You're talking
about yourself again. I've been seen
with uh multiple women on my YouTube
channel. Um bro, you need to stop
getting yourself confused with with
me. You need to stop getting yourself
confused with me, bro. It's becoming
ridiculous. You need to stop getting
yourself confused with me, bro. You're
more than likely in your late 30s, 40s, still a
virgin. Stop projecting. Trust me, it
gets you nowhere in life. Stop
projecting your life onto me, you little s. Yeah, that's
it. So, yeah. Stop talking about
yourself. You more than likely don't
even leave your [ __ ] house. Most
people they don't leave their house. Am
I wrong? No. No. No. No. No. No. You're
right. You're You're talking about
yourself. You're right about yourself.
Yeah. But not me. Yeah. No. No. You
You're right about yourself, but you're
wrong about me. Yeah. Yeah. So,
technically, you are right because
you're talking about
yourself. So, you're not completely
wrong because you are talking about
yourself. But you're not talking about
me. Notorious. Bro, even the other day I
had people come in say that I'm skinn.
Even though I've got more Even though
I've got more money than most people in
this community, they still say that
you're skinn. Bro, they've just got
themselves confused with me. That's all
I put it down to. They've just got
themselves confused. It's just a big
confusing confusion. You know what I'm saying, bro?
Like they are
literally they are literally talking about
themselves. No, no, I'm not saying I
know you you are said but what am I? No,
no, no. I'm saying that you're literally talking about
yourself. Brain dead. Yep. You're
talking about yourself again. Stop
talking about yourself. Okay. Okay. So,
why don't I put the link up and you join
the hangouts then? Why don't I put the
link out and then you join the hangouts?
Huh? I'll put the link up and you can
join the hangouts. Then if I'm wrong and
I'm immature, then join the hangouts and
show us your
face and we will understand why you're
on YouTube doing what you do every day,
you [ __ ] or you're going to run away
again. So yeah, if you're not willing to
do that then yeah. Have you got nothing
better to [ __ ] do than to sit on
YouTube all day every day projecting
your [ __ ] life onto people? Like
seriously, man. Got nothing better to
do. Been doing this for years
now. I swear these repeaters have been
doing this for years.
Notorious. For absolute
years. Yeah. They just self project.
That's literally all they do. They self
project. All they do is talk about their own
lives, you know.
[ __ ] boring, man. Really is just
self-reflecting. That's what it
is. Self-reflecting their life onto other
people. I look a bit like I look a bit
whack now, but I'm not going to lie to you. Was it? Oops.
I look a bit whack now, bro. Look, I
need to go for a little shave and that. Anyways, you're
banned. Yeah, bro. I need to go for a
little haircut cuz I've not been going
out and that started to look like Len again, man.
Yeah, I don't approach anymore, bro, cuz
I'm sick of hearing about [ __ ] boyfriend
boyfriend. You know what I'm saying, bro? So
yeah. Yeah, bro. I just can't be
bothered with it
anymore. I'm not scared to show my face like these
people. And look at me, bro. Look, I'm
[ __ ] hairy as
[ __ ] I'm not scared to show my face
like these people,
bro. Really not. just get my eyebrows
done as well. Look, it's going back.
Don't be [ __ ]
It's very expensive getting groomed
notorious. And uh it doesn't make a difference. Anyways,
so if you want to tell me about myself,
come and tell me about myself to my
face. I think that's a that's a good
idea. Yeah. If you if you're going to
keep making accounts, right? Yeah. Why
don't you come and tell me about my fa
myself to my face? Maybe the first thing
you need to ask is if they have a
boyfriend. Yeah, because that's really
going to make it. Bro, listen. The thing
is, notorious. Yeah. There's no point
trying to figure this out, you know?
Like, you should say this, you should
say that. They're just not interested in
this country unless you're a [ __ ]
drug dealer or a [ __ ] tick pocket
[ __ ] tick tocker. End of. There's no
point trying to work this out. You don't
want to spend years of your life trying
to figure it out when in the end it is
it is them. When in them years that
you've wasted, you could have been going
other places. You could have been doing
things. There's no there's no Jedi mind
tricks. They're either interested or
they're not. You understand, Notorious?
There's no Jedi mind
tricks. They're all NPCs.
NPCs. I've got a boyfriend. They're
[ __ ] NPCs, bro. That's what they
are. Stop talking about yourself.
Talking about yourself
again. Yeah, you're calling me skin even
though I just told you how much I've got
in savings. But yeah, apparently I'm
skin. Stop embarrassing yourself. Get
off your YouTube, man. For [ __ ] sake.
You got showed money [ __ ] two. You
got showed money two weeks ago, mate,
and you went running away again. Stop
talking about yourself. Every single
time you get shown money, you run away.
You are the skin m who will always be
alone. Stop talking about yourself. It's
no good for your mental health,
man. Skin, skin, skin, skin, skin. Isn't
it mad how they call people skin, but
they can't show anything? Stop talking
about yourself, man. [ __ ]
sake. You know, stop talking about like
I could go to the bank right now and put
out a couple of thousand pound
notorious, but there's no point because
these people will show you nothing
because they asking, do you understand?
It's they are talking about
themselves. Or they say, well, I can't
say cuz actually the bank's closed, but
like for example, I can go out tomorrow.
I could even show my bank balance, but
they're still going to call you skint
because they're talking about
themselves. It's they're confused with
them. They're confused with
themselves. For [ __ ] sake, I've got
more money than these people. I'm better
looking than these [ __ ] people and
they still hate. [ __ ] sake, man. What
else do they want to [ __ ]
see? If I'm the skint one, listen,
listen. They're the ones that are
calling people skint notorious. Yeah. So
why are they on YouTube every day
hating? Ask yourself this question,
right? They've got all this money in the
world. I'm skint, right? Whatever that
[ __ ] means. So, why are they the ones
on YouTube hating every day? Shouldn't
they be in the [ __ ] Caribbean? Should
they be retired in the Caribbean like
[ __ ] uh Richard
Branson or traveling the world instead
of coming on YouTube hating?
Exactly. Exactly. What person with all
this money would be coming on YouTube
every day hating? Think about it, bro.
Making new accounts to get
blocked. Sados, bro. Absolute
sados. You know, you can just tell
they've got no life experience. The way
they talk about women, they got no they
ain't got a clue. Most of these people
and people even that give advice online
for that matter, notorious don't have a clue about
women. They have no clue because when you go
out, you have a completely different experience. Yeah.
But anyways, bro, text her number and see what
uh see what she
says. I don't like hearing about it anymore,
bro. Unless it's something positive. I
don't want to hear about it. Unless it's
she's replying back and
um you've got a date, I don't want to
hear about it, to be honest.
I gave up to get away from it, you know.
Anyways, I'm off for a bit. I'll be back on later.