Yeah. Back for a little
bit. I need to get off YouTube, man. [ __ ]
hell. Definitely need
to That's what happens when you don't go out [ __ ]
drinking and approaching. You get on
this Reddit [ __ ] again and [ __ ]
YouTube. My friend invited me out today.
I said, "Nah, bro. I'm taking a break
from it all." It's the same friend that
was done for a couple of uh
weeks and I said, "Yeah, I'm not going
out today, bro. I'm just going to go get some
food. I ain't going out drinking, bro.
[ __ ] that." Yeah, Monty, I was live earlier,
man, and this account called me skin. I
was I didn't know how, you know, how
much my body I've got in my
bank. These people will never get fed up
with talking about themselves, will
they? How they can sit online and
project for years, man, is mad, bro.
Like, you would have thought they would
have got bored of
it. Yeah, they love talking about themselves.
Morning. Why do these people talk about themselves every
day? They talk about themselves for a
living. It's mad, isn't
it? Jeez. How long has that been going
now? Skin. Skin. Skin. How long has that
been going now, Monty? [ __ ] hell. How
long has that saying been going? long time,
man. I think these people have me confused with themselves.
Yeah, I haven't seen it
yet. Yeah, exactly. It's their lives.
I've not seen it
yet. I ain't seen it.
Let me see.
I think it's a stupid song. Yeah, I've
just listened to it. No, I think it's
stupid. Yeah, and I don't have a big nose
either. Money, you're getting like these
repeaters now, lad.
Yeah, I don't even have a [ __ ] big
nose. The only people that say that are
people that uglier than me. Somebody who
uh me and you both know. We're not
mentioning any names, but uh
yeah, these people on here are
[ __ ] way worse looking than they call
anyone else, bro. I swear to God.
Yeah, I'm going to be doing the Simpsons
thing soon. Grezy, for you.
Yeah, you like that little voice um last
night, didn't you,
Grezy? Yeah. Leave your mother alone, B
Simpson. It's your dad that used to strangle you. Ah,
Nelson, Chief Rick
Wiggin. Yeah, me and Monty used to play the Simpsons.
on PS3. New money. Yeah. Yeah, man. Yeah,
bro. What's for dinner today,
Grezy? I'm going to go to the butchers, get some
chicken. I'm starving. and I haven't had
breakfast. My friend invited me out.
He's like, "Oh, we should go out today."
I said, "Bro, to be honest, I just want
a break from it all." People think it's
boring staying in. Yeah. But it's it's
really not having food cooked for you,
no hangover the next day. It actually
doesn't even seem boring to be honest.
If you got YouTube, mate, you know,
like, trust me, it's not boring.
It's not boring, bro. It will get boring
eventually, like after a long time, but
it will take a while before you get that
bug in your stomach that wants to go out
again. You know what I mean? So, trust
me. But all jokes aside, the reason I'm
not going to the cinema to watch Stitch
is I don't really care for
Stitch. He's cute and that, but I want a
good film to come out in the cinema, man.
then I would have went today, you know.
Yeah. I don't really care for
Stitch to be fair, man. It's not a
horror film, is it?
So, Oh, you're not having a McDonald's later,
Grezy. You're not having a McDonald's later.
I'm [ __ ] starving,
mate. Horrible drinking tea on an empty
stomach as well. Grievy. [Music]
How many times a week do you have
McDonald's? We should stop talking about
food, bro. I'm hungry. I mean, I brought
it up cuz I'm hungry, but keep talking
about it. It's making me [ __ ]
hungry. Oh, so you only have a takeaway
once a week. I have a takeaway maybe
every four days, which I don't think is that bad.
Yeah, I'm hungry, bro. I am hungry. You
know what I've not had in ages? Nandos
cuz it's so expensive.
Greasy. I do like Nano but it is expensive you know so
yeah let's have a chicken curry
today that's going to be
Yes. Could I get away with eating just
once today, Grezy? Yeah. Yeah. If I have
the curry at about 6 or 7, that'll do
me. Sometimes I eat um once a day to save
money. Yeah, he's a he's a snake. I've
always said Monty's a snake. And
Natalie Bonzo, my nose ain't even [ __ ] big, you
know. [ __ ] hell, man. My nose ain't
even [ __ ] big,
brother. Don't know why they say my nose
is big. It's not even big. Doesn't make me
insecure. Doesn't Doesn't make me
anything. It's just
childish. cuz we all know that I'm
better looking than everybody on here
that's shown their face. So, you know,
the only one that says I've got a big
nose. Have you seen his
face? Like, have you actually seen his
face? It looks like it's
melting. His face actually looks like it's
melting. And they're the only kind of
people that say that I've got a big
nose. People that are literally but
ugly. It's called jealousy. Oh, [ __ ]
hell. So, um,
yeah, he is a snake and Natalie's a snake as
well. That's why he was like, "Oh, come
to Birmingham." I'm not coming to
Birmingham, mate, to help you with
[ __ ] Timmy and Money, Mike. Yeah,
I've caught him. I've caught her talking
[ __ ] about me on a live stream as well,
like a few weeks ago. They're all snakes on here.
All of them more snakes, bro. You
know, they're all
uh they're all
snakes. Yeah, exactly. Bomb said it. And
look what he And look at his face. Yeah.
face. And look at all these other
people's face. And look at their face.
If they ever show their face all fat,
all horrendous looking. That's what I'm
saying. But they talk about themselves.
That's why it doesn't bother me what
people write on here because they're
just they're just self-
projecting. Just like when they call me
skin. How the [ __ ] can I be
skin? Doesn't even make sense. How can I be
skinn you know? So they just talk about themselves. So yeah. Strange, isn't
it? Yeah. My friend invited me out today, Slim.
Uh, and I was like, I don't want to go
out. I'm taking a break from it all.
People think it's boring staying in, but
I don't feel like it's boring, bro. I'm
going to go for a walk later, get some
food, get it cooked for me. I think it's
quite It's nice to have a break. It just
feels like you're having a nice break.
That's maybe why I don't feel like it's
boring. I don't find it boring,
bro. To me. I don't find it
boring. Having a break is fun,
but it's nice, bro.
Chilling. Waiting for some more money to
come in. So, yeah. Yeah,
bro. I mean, yeah, I could go out today,
but that means get my haircut and
spending money to get my haircut. It's
just all a waste of money. Waste of
time, waste of
money. But I generally believe in even
even if I doubled my money, I still
wouldn't go out.
So, yeah, I know. I saw it, man. He's a
snake. Yeah, it can be. It can be out to
It can My friend said, "Oh, do you want
to come? You want to come and play
cricket?" I said, "I'll play basketball with
you." I'm not playing cricket. I'm I'll
play basketball with you. But yeah, I
need a long
break. A long break. Like six weeks,
bro. I'm not even joking.
cuz you know this house is so nice now.
This is why I stay in it. Obviously I go
out but like
Yeah. So go to the barbers, spend £40 to
get my haircut, sit on the chair for an
hour, go out, spend more
money, spend more money. Self
projecting. Spend more money. and then um
yeah to get
nothing. But yeah, I've caught um
Natalie snake me trying to say, "Oh, I
can wear what I want and I and I still
won't get women." Even though I've had
more women than anyone she's been with.
All of her exes. I've been with more
women than all of her exes I've ever been
with. Yeah. I said I'll play basketball
with you, but I'm not playing. I don't
like football and I don't like
um uh cricket. So, but he doesn't like basketball. So,
yeah. Yeah. They're just snakes on here.
The only one that's a cool guy is Unworthy
Clock. He's a cool guy. Nah, bro. Nah.
Uh yeah, I generally can't stand women
slim. I actually despise them. See, I
didn't contradict myself cuz I'm not out
today. I hate just
basically it's [ __ ] you know? I despise
everything about them. They're evil.
They're time wasters. Everyone defends
them. They make it just about how you
want sex when that's not what it is. I
just can't stand them, you
know. And that's how my friend was. So,
he gave up for a couple of weeks, but he
wants to go out today. But, um, I'm
still on the break.
So, I can't see me going back to it
anytime soon, lad. I don't need I don't
know if I will go out again. This is what I'm
saying. Probably, bro. Yeah. Probably.
Yeah, probably. I just don't see no
point in going out in this country
trying. I just
see literally no point, you
know, cuz it's just going to always be the
same. Someone's like, "Oh, yes, but it's
bank holiday. It's going to be busy."
But bro, at the end of the day, it's
we've been out bank holiday before. Bank
holiday doesn't make a difference.
Most of the people that go out in this
country aren't even from [ __ ] England
because they're skint. You know, in
London when people go out, right, you do
realize most of the time they're not
English people because they're skint.
Where do you think the money comes from?
It comes from people abroad. It comes
from tourists. You know what I'm saying?
Like doesn't matter if it's a bank
holiday or not. And today is not going
to be busy. Even though it is a bank
holiday, it won't be busy cuz I went out
last bank holiday Sunday. Monday went
out on a Sunday and it weren't busy at all.
There's a few people about, but it weren't
busy like I thought it would have been.
It was a waste of time. So
yeah, I don't feel like I'm missing anything either.
I think the whole them replying to
negativity and that done it for me, bro.
I think that done it for me.
Slim, it's just the people you really
want to be dealing
with for what? A bit of sex. Come on, bro. You know? Nah. No,
bro. People always defend them. Some
idiot on [ __ ] Reddit. Do you know? Do
you want to know what this person on Reddit
said? I'll read it out to you if you want.
Who is that to me?
Yeah, the drinking's not even fun anymore.
So yeah, that is rumbling boy.
Yeah. Yeah. Monty's a snake. I remember
that time. Yeah. Monty snaked me. Yeah.
And he went on the Discord and
then then they um they switched on him.
And then he tried coming running back to
me. Yeah, he's a proper snake that one.
So he moans about me on PlayStation
switching sides, right? But that's
exactly what he does. He does exactly the same
thing. He does exactly the [ __ ] same thing. Yeah. He's a
[ __ ] He's a [ __ ] idiot. Yeah.
Yeah, I said to my friend yesterday, I
actually despise them. Like, I'm not
going to say the actual word. I was
sitting down with him saying, I actually
despise them. Like, you don't
understand. I don't think you really
And it's only right, you know, it's only
right to feel that way, you
know, after your experiences. It's only
right to feel that way. And it also goes
to show that if women really were
different, then you would have found one
by now that wasn't like that. So that's
how you know they're all the
same. Every single one of
them. That's why they use the same
excuses. They're all NPCs. They've all
got the same
attitude. They walk around with the same
attitude because they're all the same. That's why, you
know, I said to my friend, you know, go
out, you know, tell me how how it went.
I already know it's going to be the
same. I've got a boyfriend. I've got a
boyfriend. Same old you know.
Yeah. Witness, bro. Witness. What the [Music]
I can wait 6 hours,
man. I cannot eat for 6 hours. It's not [Music]
problem. [ __ ] hell.
So you can technically
eat once a
day or is it something big, you know? Uh
Yeah, that shifty is a snake as well. So
many snakes on this community. [ __ ] hell. It's
crazy. Imagine saying that to someone.
You will never have kids. That's That's
like Christmas coming early, brother. If
somebody told you, right, you you're
never going to have kids, right? That's
like [ __ ] the best news
ever. You know what I'm saying? If
somebody said that, you know, even if
you have sex, you know, you can't have
kids, mate, that's Christmas come [ __ ]
early in my book and a lot of other
people's books. [ __ ] hell. [ __ ] that. Yeah.
Again, that person behind that is
probably still a
virgin self projection. All it comes
down to in this community is a bunch of
angry people in their late 30s, late 40s
hate their life. So, they come on
YouTube with hate. Hate and
jealousy. That's what it comes down to.
Yep. That's what it comes down to in this community. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, this tea is
nice. I have loads of cups of tea, me.
Yeah. Who fancies a bit of roulette? Online roulette. Nah.
Nah. Like I said, maybe if it wasn't
euros, maybe I would try, but nah. Foo
that. Completely fooked that, mate.
been playing online with that for a long
time. Been gambled for a long time
really. Yeah. And guess what? It's good
that LJ's got kids because I wouldn't
want to have shitty kids like him that I
can't [ __ ] fend for. Yeah, bro. I'd
rather be sat here with more money than
LJ and actually have hair unlike [ __ ]
some baldy freak with shitty ugly kids
that he can't even look after. So yeah,
that is something I'll never have.
Shitty ugly kids that I can't look
after. Yeah, you're right about that.
Yeah. Yeah, you're right about that,
mate. I'd rather be sat there with more
money, not obese, actually have hair on
my head than be [ __ ] sat there with some ugly
kids. So, yeah, it is something I'll
never have. You got it right there,
buddy. First time I've seen you say
something right. I think you left early
before I could actually
respond. So, yeah, man. You're all rats.
You're all [ __ ] You're all
snakes, you know. I've I've seen, like I
said, that Ricky Milling that Millington
account. You're all [ __ ] snakes.
rats. You know what the
[ __ ] Natalie's a rat. Natalie's a
snake. I've seen her talk [ __ ] about me. You
know, and then you expect me to come up
to Birmingham to back you up. I'm not [ __ ] doing
that, you know. [ __ ] that. Are you mad? Not
[ __ ] wouldn't say I've got standards
anymore. I despise
women. So what the [ __ ] man? yeah. Yeah. [Music]
Yeah. Any of you out today
drinking? No, it won't be. Yeah. Mhm. [Music]
I don't think I'd ever [ __ ] talk to a woman
again outside of the
family. Let's just say the women in your
family kind of have to speak to you and
have to love you, but them as a whole
are all the same.
Yeah. Yeah. It's better than [ __ ]
going out [ __ ] dealing with women.
I'm happy I don't I no longer have that
problem. Yeah. And why are you speaking
about LJ's ugly kids? About that's
something I never have. I don't want
kids. I don't want ugly kids. Like he's,
you know, the last person that kept
going on about kids over and over and
over again. We all turn out to see what he looked
like. So, stop self-reflecting, bro.
You're probably sat there still a virgin
and you're talking about people not having kids.
So, I don't want no ugly ginger kids
that's got balding in their f in in
their family, bro. You know what I'm
saying? Stop being an [ __ ] I said
one thing. The guy's skin. Yeah, cuz he
is skin. That's facts. That's not projection. That's
facts. You know what I'm saying, bro? So, what?
Yeah. [ __ ] hell.
I'd be ashamed, mate, if uh my father
was on YouTube all day, every day, mate,
talking to a bunch of scared people
that's never going to meet him, even in
a friendly way. That's embarrassing,
mate. He's not going to win no [ __ ]
father of the [ __ ] year award, is he? No. You
know, you people just come on here and
you hate every day. Your life is hating
on other people. That's what it is.
That's how we know you live
sad [ __ ] [ __ ] lives because you live
to hate on other
people. So something's not right there, man. You know. Yeah.
yeah, I've been dealing with women for a
very long time.
Dad, you know, you get to a certain age
and you know, you know that they're all
same. So what's the point of dealing
with people that are all the
same? Women are all the same. So why do
you want to, you know what I'm
saying? Associate with people that are
all the same doesn't make much sense, does it?
People could say they're not all the
same, that you've not met every single
woman, but people can also say pigs fly.
What does that mean? You know, so
yeah. What do you got out say, bro? I go
out for a few drinks. What's stopping you?
H notice how you didn't reply to the um
thing about LJ's kids.
Uh you little rat. Yeah. Don't try and
be smart with me, bro.
because I will body you in less than 5
seconds with what I say back. What can
you say to that really? Like what can
you actually say to
that? There's nothing you can say to
what I said back to you. There's nothing you
know you're just a large you're just a
large ass licker by the sounds of it. Yeah. Yeah,
bro. Nah, he's just a large ass slicker.
Yeah. Why do people even go on that
channel? I stopped going that channel
ages ago. Just the same repeating
people. That's why I stopped going on
that channel [ __ ] ages ago, bro.
[ __ ] That channel was dead, man.
Just the same repeaters, same
people every time he goes live, same chat, same
atmosphere. Not good, bro. All right,
let me see.
Anything in the cinema? Have a look. Um.
Oh, there's a new Peppa Pig out. Greasy.
Okay, there's a new Peppa Pig. [Music]
Okay. Still no [ __ ] horrors. What's
going on, man? Peppa
meets the baby. Oh, that's
cute. An hour and five minutes.
No, I still don't know who it is. [Music]
I'll be back later.