ban this [ __ ] site as well, bro. One
second. Something Let me do
it. It's such a rigged piece of
[ __ ] [ __ ] I was even doing playing
this [ __ ] This rigged [ __ ]
again. There we go.
had to pay the computer one. God, it's
[ __ ] rigged. The house Eds can't eat
you up for that long, bro. [ __ ] me.
months ago. The same conversation I told
you all them months ago because it's
rigged. That's the That's the
clarification. What the [ __ ] was I doing
even [ __ ] playing that? I shall never
know, bro. What the [ __ ]
Nah. What did What do they say? In my
opinion, what? In my opinion, it's about
to ritual. No, [ __ ] off. I've been
losing for months. That's exactly why I
quit. That's exactly why I don't gamble
anymore. That was just a oneoff, bro,
with [ __ ] I was just lying in bed
bored. It's It's literally rigged. I
just played online
roulette 150. It's so rigged. I ain't
gambled in about a month. I thought,
"Oh, let me try it." It's the same
rigged [ __ ] It can't be luck. People
cannot be unlucky for that long. It doesn't make
sense. Tell me it's luck. No. Suck your
mother. This is exactly why. Yeah, when
you try trolling me as well, shifty, you
little [ __ ] So, shut the [ __ ] up. I
don't want to have [ __ ] ugly kids
like LJ. I don't want to have ugly
inbredad kids that I can't look after
like LJ's [ __ ] Do you think I care
that he's got ugly disabled kids? I said
this to you yesterday as well. Do you
think I care that he's got ugly disabled
kids? I don't want that. Nope. It's not
entertaining at all, mate. I just done
my limit. £150. I'm not entertained. I feel
disgusted. I'm not into entertain one
little bit. I think it's [ __ ] rigged.
And that was my limit. I ain't even
gambled in a month. It's definitely definitely not
entertaining. Nope. I'm not entertained
in the slightest. I'm actually pissed
off. I've just closed my account. Well,
I'm trying I'm in the process of trying
to close my account down right now. Um,
I don't find it entertaining one little
bit. And that 150 was my limit. I've got
all my bills paid. I've got plenty of
money. So, I can
speak. Listen, shut the [ __ ] up, you
little mug, bro. If you've got something
to say, say it to my face. Yeah, skin.
I've got more money than you will ever
have, you little [ __ ] Now, go suck
up LJ's kids because you're so obsessed
with people's kids. Go and suck up his
kids and stop coming on my channel, you
[ __ ] virgin. Go suck your mom, [ __ ] Anyways,
um, no, the spins are not too big and I
just done it now. It was 150. Yes, I
don't gamble anymore. I thought, let me
just do a
oneoff and yeah, I'm just just closing
my account now. Now you're calling me
skin. I've got more money than anybody
in this community, bro. Stop talking
about yourself and go suck LJ's kids
since you're so obsessed with bringing
up [ __ ] kids. Why does this community
always have to [ __ ] I'm on GameStop.
It was another
uh It's not
l to play. It's not luck. It's rigged. I
don't play anymore. That's why I stopped
for a month. A [ __ ] whole [ __ ]
month, bro. Cuz it's boring. And I just
done 150. A shitty 150. And I'm closing
my account. Bye. Done. And yeah, I can
speak first. I can speak on this right
now about how it's not entertaining,
right? Cuz I've just took a month off. I
just done 150. Still got plenty of money
left. It's still affecting me. And
that's This right here is a good
example. This right here is a good
example. Even if somebody done 150 every
[ __ ] month, this right here is a good
example. Good example. All your bills
paid, got plenty of money. um lost what
you could afford to lose and it's still
affecting you. Yeah, this is a perfect
example of why you do not gamble,
people. And why you ask me if I went out
yesterday when I literally told you I
wasn't going out for 6 weeks? I
literally told you I was not going out.
So why did you ask me if I was going
out? If it was rigged, nobody would
gamble. No, that's not true. It's something called
addiction. It's something called
addiction. So, no, people would gamble.
It is 100% rigged. It is 100% [ __ ]
rigged, bro. And I That was the first
time in a month. That was the first time
I thought, let me just play a little bit of live
roulette. Um, but
nah. Nope. Didn't even let me play live
roulette. I had to pay the computer
rulet. That's just ruined my whole day
and my whole
mood. And that's a prime example of
gambling money you can afford to lose
and it's still affecting you. That is a
prime example. You know, even if you was
to do it every month. Yeah. Right.
Hopefully they've closed my account
down. Anyways, it controls your whole
body, your whole mind, your whole mood.
There you go. That's that's that's a
good example. That is that's a very good
It's not a lot to me, mate. I've got
loads of money. There's no point saying
150 is a lot to lose. I can afford to
lose 150. I can afford to lose it. I
just lost it. It would You stop saying
it's a lot to lose or what it can get
you or what it can get you. You know
what I'm saying? Because, bro, I
wouldn't lose it if I couldn't afford to it. Yeah.
Simple. God [ __ ] hell, man. Well, at
least it was something different this
time. Hopefully, they've closed my
account down cuz I will not be doing it again. So,
yeah. No, it's not a lot to lose, mate. I've got
money. But, um, yeah. See, that's a
prime example. It doesn't matter. See,
you remember when you when when Seculus
used to say,
right? Yeah. And you're banned. Um, do
you remember when secular um, stocks
used to say, uh, oh, if you gamble money
that you can afford to lose and you've
got your bills paid, it's fine. But it's
not fine. That's the difference. It's
not fine. And I'm a prime example of it not being
fine. You know, I'm a prime example of
it not being as it not being fine. You
took a month off. You've just gambled
money you can afford to lose, which is
basically nothing, and it's still
affecting you. Question mark. [ __ ] There you
go. But there's no it's pointless is
trying to explain this anyways. His
point is trying to explain this to
people because what people on here don't
understand is you have to lose a lot of
money for it to affect you. You have to
be skinned for it to affect you and it's
not like that at all. You know, so don't
even know why I even bothered even
playing it to be honest. What a [ __ ]
idiot. God to think it was really going
to change after all this time. It's
never going to change.
never [ __ ] change.
Never. It will never change. This is
[ __ ] Just like the shitty ass
women, it will never change. A leopard
never changes its
stripes. Calm down as well. [ __ ]
[ __ ] It's so rigged. It's unbelievable, bro. Close my
countdown. It is definitely rigged 100%,
mate. You can't lose
that lose that many times in a row. No
matter who you are, there's no
way. Close my account, please.
I was thinking about it today, you know,
it's a bit it it was a bit boring. So, I
thought, "Oh, let me try some roulette."
I've not played online online roulette
in a long time. Same old [ __ ] Same old
Boring. Old [ __ ] Boring.
Yeah. Going to try and um get rid of
that account as well. Well, I'm not
going to put any more money in either
way. Even if it takes to ages to to
Yeah, it's [ __ ] mate. [ __ ]
[ __ ] It is
[ __ ] Yeah, it is proper [ __ ]
Ruins the whole mood. Ruins the whole
vibe. Not [ __ ] rig my [ __ ] ass, mate.
stick community again. Monty, it's only
because I just lost 150 pound on
roulette. I weren't even going to go on
this community again cuz it's just for the
spastics, you know? But I feel like when
I'm in a mood to rant about this
gambling [ __ ] I should rant about
it. So yeah, usually pay out. I've lost
about six months in a row. That's why I
don't gamble anymore.
I lost about five, six months in a row.
But people still say that you can win
from gambling. You can win. You can win,
but you can't win. Because I'm living
proof of it. The amount of money that
I've lost in the past 6 months, right?
Gambling about £500 a month. There's no
way in a million years, you know. And
that's why I just thought I would just
stop doing it. That's why I stopped
it. Still have like three grand left, so
it's not a problem.
Well, it is a problem because it's
annoying watching it. It's
disgusting, you know. Yeah, bro.
Subzero, stop it. You stop trying to
troll on my channel. It's not going to
work. Just stop your [ __ ] and go back to
L's channel. I'm not Money Man or Timmy.
Uh, you can never win. Ah, I've lost.
I'm not going to get into this anyways.
I know it's rigged. I shouldn't have
done it today and I done it. End off. It
won't happen again. Simple. I'm not
going to sit here and try to be
convinced that these things are not
rigged. It is rigged. I lost £150.
That's it. I'm done. There's I'm not up
for a debate. You're not going to change
my mind and I don't want to change your
mind. I know it's rigged and that's good
enough for me and that's why I don't do
it anymore. Simple. So, except from
today. So, yeah. Well, just now, not even today.
Prime example. That is a prime
Yeah. So, I'm on here just ranting about
that. Basically, I don't bother with
this community no more. [ __ ] It's just
full of self projectors, silos, and
life. Don't bother with you, Monty,
either or snakes. So,
yeah. How the [ __ ] did I Why did I even
do that today? I must have been really
bored. I must have been really bored.
But I should get £500 today anyways. So
yeah, what the actual [ __ ]
Yeah, that's a madness,
bro. Could have been worse.
Eh, it's not about the money. I don't
know why I'm saying it could have been
worse. It's not about the money. This is
what I try to explain every time. It's
not about the money, but people seem to
always think it's about the money. It's
the whole losing on it. But people don't understand that.
So, there's no point.
Um, I know when this side open, I want it closed.
Yeah, I think that just goes to show
it's not about the
money. It's never
about never about the money, mate. Never
money. Just puts people into a
depression. Yeah. Puts me into one as
well. I don't know about anyone
else because I know I know the history
of it. You see, I know the history with
this [ __ ] and it's [ __ ] boring
now. Really is really getting boring now, you
know, really getting boring. But I guess
that was just a bank holiday. That's the
money you would have spent on bank
holiday. Well, half of it anyways.
So yeah, that's the way you should see
it really. Same
old. Yeah, same old. It will never
change. These rig sites, just like these
women will never change. They're all the
same. Yeah, I forgot the [ __ ] um
casino site to be fair.
That's how you know I'm not addicted.
You see, cuz I had a limit. I stopped
been having money in my account. Been
having money in my account. You know
what I'm saying? Been having money in my account. You know,
so just the same old same old [ __ ] and and so
yeah and there's no point in saying oh
what 150 would have got you cuz I would
have spent £300 over the bank
holiday so I don't know why you use examples like
You shouldn't be gambling if you if you
use examples like that. Just like I
shouldn't be gambling if this is how it
gets you. Which is why I don't gamble.
You know, you know what I'm trying to
say. And this is why I don't [ __ ]
gamble because of it. Because of the
same old, same old, same old. And then
you go around in circles and people tell
you that's just gambling. But you still
never ever ever ever ever ever win.
Nothing. Not even your money back. So
it's just boring.
Just lost 150 pound on online roulette.
Ain't done it for a month. I fancied
playing it cuz I was bored. I found a
site that had pounds. It didn't let me
play um live roulette, so I just played
the um computer roulette. A leopard
never changes its stripe. Still pissed
off. Still annoyed. Same old mood
swings. Never changes, does it? never
changes. I am the prime example of
gambling responsibly today. I am the
prime example. I am the prime example of
gambling responsibly today. Yep. I'm the prime
example. Lost money that you can afford
to lose. Got more than enough money. Got
your bills paid and it still affects
you. I'm the prime example of
it. Yep. I'm the prime example of it, man.
Let me see if they've closed my account.
They should close my account. I asked
for my account to be closed.
No. Yeah, cuz I' got my bank [ __ ] in it.
So, just the same old rig [ __ ] basically, Joe. You
know, it's just the same
old. But I would have spent £300 over
the pass over the back over the bank
holiday. I would have spent about £300,
maybe £350. So, it's not the point. It's
annoying. We would have had to do something. It's
annoying. Doesn't make a difference,
mate. It's annoying. I don't like losing.
continuously. They not closed my
account, man. I've literally asked for
my account to be closed
down. Yeah, that's me done, bro. I won't
be doing it again for another two months, maybe. Yep.
Just like I gave up with shitty
women, I can try to justify the loss
because it's money that I can afford to
lose. It's £150. But if I have money, if
I didn't have money, I wouldn't do it, would I?
Obviously, how I lost is you would have
spent £300 hearing about make believe.
you would have you would have um spent
£300 hearing about I've got a boyfriend.
So in that way you can kind of justify
it to be honest. It was a bank holiday.
You done 150 on roulette. You would have
heard about I've got boyfriends. You
would have probably spent about 3400
[ __ ] quid. That's a good way to
justify it I think.
done some food
shopping. I had
5050. I had 1,550 in one account. Now
I've got 1,400. So
yeah, I should get £500 today.
£500 in a few days as
well. No, she shut her mouth. I told her
about herself the other day. That Morgan
again, Joe. I said, "I'll come to
America next week if you just say the
day, you little [ __ ] and we'll see who
the keyboard warrior is." Obviously,
I've got savings and stuff in it. So, I
can obviously afford to go there, but
[ __ ] shut her mouth. So, this is like
[ __ ] a few days ago, bro. Like 3:00
in the morning. I said, "Let's show
everyone who the keyboard warrior is, [ __ ]
No, I'm not trying to escape the women
stuff. Not at all. I was just lying down
a bit bored. That's all it was. And I
think you can actually justify it when
you've not done it in a month. I was just
bored. You know, I've not been out in
about 3 weeks drinking. I was bored,
bro. [ __ ] sake. That's why I went on
that roulette with
150. It's bad cuz I should really be saving. But
yeah, they don't dictate my mood. It's
just I just I just can't stand them.
Literally just can't stand the
[ __ ] Yep. My sister's birthday soon.
I'm going to give her
£50. Yeah. I don't do it. I don't do it anymore,
bro. I don't do it anymore. I just done it today.
I said, "Listen, you can bring your
Mexican boy looking boyfriend and you
can bring your [ __ ] dad cunt."
Yeah, she's putting up she's subleting
her apartment. So, what I could have
done was Yeah, just pretend to be
somebody interesting in it and then just
go there, bro. I'd force my way in the
house. I'd lock the [ __ ] door and
say, "What you saying now, you little [ __ ]
skank?" Yeah. I said, "Bring your
boyfriend and your dad as well. I ain't
scared of no man, bro." Yeah. Straight.
[ __ ] straight. It is a mug's game.
That's why I don't do it
anymore. I think I ain't done it for
like It's got to be almost a month. It's
month. Same old [ __ ] And I had to play
the computer roulette as
well. Yep. Was going next. Next door to
my numbers as
usual. It's bad, is it? really bad.
But you would have spent money either
way. I reckon you need to justify it
that way. You would have spent money
either way. You went through the whole
bank holiday. You didn't go out. You've
only bought food shopping. So, you know, to spend
150, you know, would have you preferred
to spend 150 or [ __ ] 350. So, you
have to see it like that. When it's
times like this when it's not been a
month, it's bank holiday. You can sort
of justify it. I think you can even if
it's every month, you can justify
it. It's like Saturdays how I used to
justify it, right? If you lose 60, yeah,
okay, you might have lost 50 60 pound,
but you would have spent £160 hearing
about I've got
boyfriends. So, you know, it depends how
you look at
it. But I really need to be saving more
saving up more money, you know. So
yeah, had 1550 in that account. Now I've
got 1,400. So it's not good, is
it? Sorry. Ain't good at
all. Like I said, I get 500.
Yeah. Don't know what possessed me to do
that. Don't know what possessed me to do that,
matey. Yeah, but I'm not like [ __ ]
Antman. I'm not going to lose all my
[ __ ] money. So, I think there's a
[ __ ] difference. So he can't turn
around and say to me, "Oh, well, you
said you was going to stop gambling.
Okay, yeah, you've gambled now, but
we're going to stop. We're not going to
do it all to all our money's gone."
Yeah, he done it two [ __ ] months ago
or a month ago, and he lost all these
money. So, at the end of the day, like
you you can't even say as it's like you
should be disappointed because you
haven't kept doing it. You're not going
to lose all your money, you know? So, in
a way, it's like you basically haven't even done
cuz there's nothing to be disappointed
of. It's just annoying losing, you know? But
yeah. Yeah. I just stopped on the 150. I
was not putting any more money in. [ __ ]
that. Them days are done, bro. [ __ ]
that. I used
to I lost £2,000 before. I remember
£2,000. £2,000. I think the most I've
ever lost. I've lost a,000 pounds a
couple of times. Nah, bro. I'll never
get like that again. No
way. And I won't leave her be, bro. Just
cuz cuz she's got a new boyfriend, bro.
If I find out who the guy is, I'm going
to start messaging
him. You know what I'm saying, bro? So
yeah, I'm not I'm not drunk. I'm not
drunk for like 3 weeks.
So yeah, got 1,400 in that account.
Still a lot of money in it kind of. So yeah.
I don't even tell my
mom cuz even though it's not a bad thing
you've done, it's just like you feel
like you just let people
down. But yeah, I don't know. I thought
150 was a good amount to try on the
online roulette. But yeah. Oh
well, just call it a flare up in
recovery just like the foot thing was.
See, I told you I could stop. I told you I'm addicted, you know.
Yeah. Was it raining out there or something?
Yep. Yeah. But yeah, if I ever find out
who her boyfriend is, I'm just going to
[ __ ] up the relationship, Joe. That's
the whole point. You know what I
mean? Stupid little
slag. I'll just [ __ ] up the whole relationship. Yeah.
Well, I won't even lie, bro. You know what I
mean? I won't even [ __ ]
lie. Stupid little entitled
[ __ ] You know what I
mean? Joe, um, I'm not Money Man or
Timmy. Please refrain from doing this on
my channel. You're not going to troll me,
bro. Nah, bro. You must be severely
stupid or you're [ __ ]
trolling. So yeah. Yeah. When you're 46
and you don't have a penny to your name.
So yeah. Stop
rejecting, bro. You must be really
really stupid or you're
trolling. No, thank you,
bro. Um, so yeah. No, I'm good.
Definitely good. You can if you
want 3k 3k is a lot of money, bro. Well,
no, it depends. Again, it depends. I
don't have no outgoings, but for some
reason, it doesn't work to be getting
free grand. It is a lot of money. Would
you want me to have a million pound? You
got to understand it's all relative to
what people have to pay out and what
people I don't have to pay nothing. Got
all my bills paid everything. So just to
have that it is quite a lot of money.
Anything above like 1,300 is 1,200
yeah. But these people here don't have
no money. That's why they talk about
money not being this money not being
that because I ain't got no money and I
can make more money if I want. So yeah,
3K have nothing, mate. They're all [ __ ] the
[ __ ] your financial circumstances to
others. You have outgoings. I've got
about £150 outgoings. So, go figure.
Yeah. Do I get One sec. It depends how
much outgoings you have.
Like it's barely enough for me because
I've got a high lifestyle, but it's not
nothing how these people are going on
like 3K a month, 150 outgoings for doing
nothing. It's a lot of money, but I'm
used to having thousands and thousands. That's
why. Well, it depends how much money you
have after um after your outgoings, don't it?
I mean, I have three grand.
So, two Yeah. So, it's nothing then.
Yeah. So, what you get is nothing. What
you have is
nothing. Yeah. 2K out.
Yeah. So, no, it's not really a lot.
No. No, it's not a lot then.
No, cuz that's divided by two people.
with mine it's 3k and I have like one
[ __ ] one out going. No, not one out
going. I got a phone bill. I got an
internet bill. I need to sp gas and
electric then it's all mine. So
yeah, depends but everyone's
circumstances are different. If they got
kids, how much outgoings they've
got? I have nothing but them free.
phone bill, internet [Music]
bill, and then
Yeah, because it's because I get 3K just
for myself. That's how because you get
5.1K. Yeah. Yeah. And the 2K bills. So three
3K. So no, because it's between both of
you. I get 3K a month and even sometimes
I feel I could get I could have a bit more
money. I feel I could have a bit more money, you know. So
yeah, that's why I've done something to
get more money. So, I'm not going to
tell you what, but
yeah, it's all
um what's the
word? It just depends what you're trying
to do, bro. Like, you know what I'm
saying? 1,400. Yeah, that is a lot of
money. You got no outgoings. Anything is
you got no outgoings left. As long even
if you had £500 in your account with all
your bills paid, even that's a lot of
[ __ ] money. How many barbecues I've
had? Do you know how much food I eat? You
know, that's how much I have a month.
3K. Yep. I just done 150. But yeah.
Nothing about that, bro. Yeah, get some
money today and in a couple of days.
Yeah, I haven't lost reality of money,
mate. I know it's a lot of money, but
what I'm seeing is say you wanted to
travel the world. It's not it's not a
lot of money. Think about it like this,
right? Say you wanted to go say this
little [ __ ] says, "Oh yeah, come to
America." Yeah, it's going to cost me a
fortune, mate. even getting 3K a month.
Yeah, I can afford it. But even you
still have to save up for things. Even
if you get 3K a month, you know, because
say you booked to go to America or
holiday, wherever it is, doesn't have to
be America. Yeah. You wouldn't be able to consistently
travel. You wouldn't be able to
consistently travel on that amount of
money if you wanted to be a world
traveler. But yeah, it is a good it is a
lot of money. But even America, you'd
have to save or you know, it took me
like a month, two months to pay it off the first time. So yeah. Yeah,
man. No, the hotels are more than £100 a
night. No, no, no, no. The flights are
about three to about £600. You can even
get them for £400. It's not about the
flights. It's about the accommodation.
That's what it's about. I'd probably,
you know, to be honest with you, I'll
probably just book a [ __ ] I'll just
probably book an
apartment, right? I'll probably just
book an apartment, right? U stay for a
month and then just book an apartment. I
don't even think I'll pay for a hotel.
I'll just rent an apartment. It just
makes more sense to just rent an
apartment and just stay for a month. It
makes it just makes more sense to do
that than than just to go for a week. To
be honest, no, it's more than that. For
a flight in a week stay, you're talking
you're talking two half,000. Then with
the spending money, you're talking about
£4,000. You're talking about £4,000,
mate. With the spending money for one
person, do your research. If you went to
somewhere like Florida, it might be a
bit cheaper. You're still talking a good
three to four grand. Any American
holiday, any American holiday, you're
you know, you're you're looking at about that.
Yeah, you're looking at about [ __ ]
three to four
grand. So, there's no way it's two for a
week for one person. Yes, it is. Go look
it up right now, brother. Listen, I
booked it myself. Yeah. Out of my own
money, I know exactly how much it is.
Okay. Go look it up right now.
Booking.com for example, New York or
Boston or New Jersey for one week with
the flights. Yes, the [ __ ] it is. It's
about two to about 3k without the spending
money. Honestly, it is. Okay. Okay. I'll
look it up right now then. Right. Okay. Stay
put. Honestly, it's not. Honestly, it
is. I know cuz I've paid for it. Right.
Okay, let's have a little look. Right. London
to put New York. [Music] Yeah.
Right. Okay. Let's say we want to go
July 17th, Thursday to the Thursday.
17th to the 24th.
Right. Right. London Heathro.
Right. Let's have a little
look. This is a three star hotel. How
much is this three star hotel?
Right. And even if it's two grand,
that's still a lot of money. Even if
it's two grand, because you're still
talking about four grand.
So, one second. Let's load
them. Here we go.
£1,922, which is basically 2 grand. And
then you're going to need about £2,000
for the spending money, which equals 4
grand. Yeah. Here's one here. 2.1K. Yeah. 2,000. 2,000.
Yeah, it is, mate. Trust me. I've just looked it
up. This one here is 2.2.
Yeah, this one looks good. 1,500
pound. That one looks all right.
That's a fourstar hotel, but it says
pleasant. No, it's not for two. It's
just for one person, one traveler, one
room. Yeah, you're talking about two to
about 2.2K and the spending money. So,
you're talking about £4,000. No, it's
not for two people. It's for one person. Yeah.
Look, it's not for two people. It's for one person.
But obviously if this [ __ ] run up her
mouth, I would go there next week. You
know, I've got the [ __ ] money, so
it's not a problem. And here you go. I'll show
you. There you go. If you can even read
that. One traveler, one room. It's
expensive. It's expensive, bro.
That damn L thing pissed me off,
bro. I can't lie.
Why did I even do that, bro? What the [ __ ]
Jesus. Jesus, bro.
They're still not closing my account though, are they?
No. Okay, bro. I'm lying. I don't know
what I'm talking about. I've not just
looked it up. Yep, you're right. And I'm
wrong. I don't know anything. Yeah,
you're right, bro. Like when I booked to
Boston, when I booked Boston the first
time, it didn't cost me
£2,75. Yeah, you're right, bro. I'm
wrong. You're right. And I'm wrong.
Yeah. Yeah. I don't know anything. I'm
just going to agree with you, bro, cuz
there's no point sat here arguing with
someone, bro, when I've literally know
what I've paid for and I know what I've
just seen. But okay, bro.
Okay. Yep. You're right and I'm wrong.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. I've just shown
you as well. You
[ __ ] So yeah.
Have some nice pork chops
today. Yeah, I was having cookie dough
almost every day. I got to stop this,
mate, because I'll be fat and it's expensive as well. £150, eh?
Wow. Didn't even get up
once. Well, I didn't even get up once.
How depressing is that?
Eh, how [ __ ] depressing is
that? But secular slot says that if you
have your bills paid and you've got
money. Um, see, look, I've got a roof
over my head, just washed my clothes,
got my bills paid, got food, got money,
but it still affects me.
So yeah, I think the secular slots guy is
uh completely full of [ __ ] if you ask me.
Yeah, I think he's full of [ __ ] J. Yeah.
What do you
think? And the reason I can't let her go
is because she's a little [ __ ] That's
why Joe is because she's a little [ __ ]
go out this week, but I don't know if I will now,
mate. That's kind of killed the vibe, is
it? Yeah, that's kind of killed the
vibe, man. Not going to
lie. Yeah, that proper killed the vibe.
Yeah, I killed a V that [ __ ] Kill the
vibe. Yeah, proper
did. Proper did that, Joe.
Yeah, they better close my
account. It was negativity.
you know, even month is I wouldn't even
say it's a waste of money doing it every
month to be
honest. Still haven't banned my
account. They just want people to become
addicted in it. That's what it is with
these gamblers gambling companies. They
just want people to become
addicted. I see what they do, but it's
not going to work. I'm not putting no more money in.
Nope. So, but it's nice. It's a nice try
what they what they do.
Eh, no, you're not banned.
50 power. [ __ ] hell.
I think I've got about
uh your video. I'm not going to your video, bro.
so many accounts. Well, let me see.
Yeah, but that's a [ __ ] hotel. That's
what I'm saying. They're [ __ ]
hotels. They're [ __ ]
hotels. You need to lose some weight,
bro. I can hear your deep breathing. I
can hear your fat ass, bro.
All the way from there. [ __ ] Damn
you. You [ __ ] hear your fat ass, man.
[ __ ] me. I can hit you hear your fat ass
on my off, buddy. Yeah.
Imagine that. Losing 150 on a shitty
roulette. That's probably going to put
me in depression for about a week now, I reckon, mate.
Yeah. No, I never said anything about
your looks. I said that you, you know,
you can tell you're a fat ass. Nothing
to do with your looks cuz you're like this.
What Pat Mustard used to do. Heavy breathing,
eh? I can't let her go cuz I don't like the [ __ ]
bro. I don't like the [ __ ]
And I think any potential relationship,
to answer your question, any potential
relationship she's getting, people
should know what she's
like. So that's it.
I've got no idea about
what see somebody say to a woman
yesterday on Reddit, "Men don't owe you
shit." And I was like, "Amen."
Praise the Lord. That's the first time
I've ever heard that. A [ __ ] men.
Jesus. What did I have a cue about,
bro? I said [ __ ] amen, bro. That's
what I said.
What don't I have an idea about, buddy?
H more than I have an idea
about. So you think 3k disposable a
month is a lot, Joe? 3k disposable?
Yeah. You really think that's a lot, mate?
Yeah. London's expensive. You
see, London's expensive.
I can't believe that, bro. Wasted
£150. [ __ ] man. Nothing. Yeah.
for a week at 6 point. You you you make
stuff up to justify. No, it's it's 1.6K
with a [ __ ] hotel. Yes, it's 1.6K. And
even if it was 1.6K, 6K, bro, for a good
hotel. You're still talking about three
grand with spending money. So why why
does it matter if it's 1.6 or two? I
1.6K with a [ __ ] hotel maybe. Yeah, but
not with a good hotel. But does it
really matter? Because it's still going
to be 34 grand either way. So does it really
matter? I don't think it really matters
because it's still going to be about [ __ ]
three4,000 either way. So [Music]
yeah, women are [ __ ] evil, mate.
So yeah, but then you Yeah, but what
about eating food? What about your food? clothing?
So no. So what? You can just spend all
your money and then come home with no
money? Bro, use your [ __ ] head. God,
you're an idiot.
Yeah. What's bum change,
doggy? Oh, you're an idiot, bro. You're
an idiot. There's no point trying to
There's no point trying to justify this,
bro. You're an idiot. You're an idiot,
What's bum change? Everything's bum
change to you skin people on YouTube
because you ain't got no
money. That that sounds like people that
ain't something that people that ain't
got money would say. These people in
this community ain't got no money, man.
You can tell the way they don't have no
life experience. The way they talk about
women, money, they don't really know
anything, do they? These people in this
community really don't know
nothing. Yeah. I just played 150 on online
roulette and I lost it. I just feel like doing someone
in. I feel like just going out on the
street and just doing someone
in. Yeah. And I can I could afford to
lose it as well, Slim. That's not a
problem. I can afford to lose it. Still not the
point. It's not the [ __ ] point, is
it? Losing is annoying, bro.
So hey, But I'm probably not going to go out, bro.
Yeah. What's the point of um talking to
people that only respond to negativity,
Slim? Why would you want to be
associated with people that only reply to
negativity? Yeah, I don't think I'm
going to go out this week either, to be
honest. I'm going to call that 150 me
going out and the bank holiday cuz I
really need to be saving some money, you
know. So, I probably won't go out this week either.
Yeah, even I would have spent more
during the bank holiday and that, but
you didn't really get your money's
worth, did you? [ __ ] sticking it.
M my friend invited me out yesterday,
but I just didn't want to go out. I
can't be bothered hearing about the I've
got boyfriend [ __ ] and that and Yeah.
Yeah. 150 gone in what, like 10 minutes? Madness. [ __ ] pathetic. [ __ ]
pathetic. But that man's worst. He lost [ __ ]
£3,000. He was winning. He got to He had
£3,000. He lost it
all. [ __ ] me. That's a madness,
bro. That actually is a madness.
[ __ ] hell. I I've never even lost that
much. And even if I was going anywhere,
I still had money coming in. He didn't [ __ ] mad,
bro. That's more than I've ever lost.
The most I've ever lost was 2,000, but I
still had money. Yeah. [ __ ] that's mad.
And I said to him like, "You really need
to stop cuz I just done it. But I'm not
going to do it
again." And then he turned out like,
"Yeah, nothing. I had to borrow him
money." And that [ __ ] that, bro. That's
never being me
again. No way. That's never being me
Yeah, I [ __ ] up today and that, but you
know. Yep. I just thought I'd try
150. So now in one saving account, I've
got 1,400 instead of 1,550.
Yeah, it doesn't seem like a lot to lose,
but I could have done without not losing it, you
know. I could have really done with not losing it,
mate. So, I don't think I'll be going
out today. Um, this week I'll probably
have to make the money back to be honest.
But then like I said, you would have
spent more over the bank holiday.
So you would be in the same
position. But I can't justify it by
saying you could have won from gambling
because you can't win from gambling. Now
I've been losing months and months and
months and months and months from gambling.
Yeah, it's shitty,
mate. No, Antman done 3K and that was all his
money. I think if I done 3K and it was
all my money, I think I'd commit
suicide. I'm not even
joking. I think I would actually commit suicide.
No. Why Thailand be off? I already
booked it, you idiot. Why would it be
off? Women only reply to
negativity. Nah, nah. It's not what you
could have bought with it, mate. Cuz you
can't really buy a lot with
150. Nah, not even. Nah, not even. It's
not even that. It's not even that.
Because you can't really buy anything
with 150. It was like a thousand. Yeah.
No, not even
that. But if you didn't lose 150, you
would have went out bank holiday and
spent £300 and hear nothing but I've got
a boyfriend. So it would have been the
same. It would have been the same
outcome. Not with 150. If it's like a
thousand, you could be like, "Oh, I
could have booked to go to I could have
booked some flights or even 2,000." But
not 150. And there I done food shopping
today. I done food
shopping. I bought my clothes and
everything. So now you can't think of
what you could have done with 150,
man. Yes, but I can go to Nando 600
times if I wanted
to. Yeah, but I can go to Nando 600
times now if I wanted to. So the only
time that's necessary is when you lose
all your money. You
know, so that only makes sense if you've
lost all your money. Oh, I lost my last
150. I could have went to Nando, but I
still have money. That's the whole point
I'm trying to get across to you is I've got
money with something you seem to keep
forgetting. Both of them are annoying.
Both of them are bloody
annoying. That's why I don't go out
anymore and approach cuz of the
boyfriend [ __ ] Boring,
mate. And they only reply to negativity
as well. So why would you want to be
with people that only reply to
negativity? Been saying this [ __ ]
ages now, bro. So
yeah, I save three guys. We have like 2.8
2.7. I still have 2.7 left maybe.
If you don't go out this week, we'll
definitely justify it. If we don't go
out this week, I can definitely justify
it. You didn't go out bank holiday. You
haven't gone out this week. You still
saved money. Yeah, you might have lost
150, but you still saved money, you
know. So, that way you would be able to justify it.
I don't know. I'm just sick of hearing
it, mate. I might just go swimming on um
I might just go swimming,
maybe. I might just go swimming on
Saturday, maybe or something. Oh, no.
It's my sister's birthday. I have to go
out. Oh, I forgot. Yeah, I'm [ __ ]
either way. I've got to go
out and I have to give her some money as
well. I'll probably give her like 50
quid. Oh yeah, I'm
[ __ ] Few drinks and like the weather
spoons. Yeah. I don't think I'll be
going out this week either to be honest.
I could just give her £50 and then just
drop her out. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. [ __ ]
it. [ __ ] B.
Yeah. No, I'm going to give her £50
because it's her birthday. But yeah, I
don't want to go out, mate. I'm sick of
these women. I told you I was dumb, bro.
I told you I was I was deadly
serious. I told you I was deadly [ __ ] serious. So
Yeah. Yeah. I have my M 3K, but I don't
want to waste money in this
country. That's the whole point.
So, I'm not skinned, mate. I'm not
skinned. The worst thing is it will be a
few Rollers weekends out. I don't give a
[ __ ] mate. I didn't go out bank
holiday. My friend invited me.
My friend invited me out, but I didn't
see no point in going out because it's
just the same. I've got a
boyfriend. So, there's no point going
out of bank holiday spending
£300. And yeah, it doesn't matter if you
got 3K, man. I'm not wasting money in this country.
Simple. I just one lost 150. But you
would have wasted more going out. So in
a way you're still saving money, you
know, cuz you would have spent 40 on
your haircut, so you would have you
would have lost anyways. Yeah. Yeah.
Doesn't matter if you got 3k,
mate. It doesn't matter at
all. Don't want to waste money in this country, do I? Yeah. [ __ ]
it. It's proper [ __ ] up.
It's bad, is
it? It's bad, lad.
Bad. Yeah, but you people are just
talking about yourselves cuz you're all
skinn and you're all single. So, you're
just talking about
yourselves. Like, you do realize that
you people just come here and you just talk about
yourselves. You're probably gambling
addicts as well. You probably gamble
anytime you get
money. You're just talking about
yourselves, man. That's why you're so
obsessed with skin people cuz you
asking. That's why you continuously go
on about money time and time and time
and time again because you people are
skin. That's why you're obsessed with
the word skin because it's what you
are. Not even trying to be nasty, but
it's the truth cuz you are skin. You are
single. You are
friendless. It's the truth, man. You
just come on here and hate people in
their late 30s, late 40s. Ain't got a
life. Nothing but YouTube. It's the
truth though. You know what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah. I think that that proves the point really, bro.
that it's not about how much money you lose or anything like
that. Losing just ain't an option, is
it? Is it
matey? Losing just ain't an
option. I'm trying to close the account now.
Still took me ages to save up that 3k as
well. A month, but still. Yeah. [Music]
could have given her a 50 and I'm not
going to go out I think. Yeah. Yeah. Heat.
It's hard to come by now, buddy. As
well, hard to come by
nowadays. It's always that guilt, I think. Is
it? See, this is the psychological thing
it does. It [ __ ] with your head.
Doesn't matter if you still got money.
Doesn't matter. These things don't matter,
mate. You know, even if you had just
1,400 pound, that's that's enough to
last you a month with no outgoings.
That's more than enough. Say you got
food and you got £1,400. That's more
than enough. There's some people that
don't even have £200 in their account.
It's not the point. It just
psychologically [ __ ] with your
head. That's what it does. And
obviously, that's how it's not a form of
entertainment cuz form of entertainments
don't do that to people. That's what I'm trying to say. So,
yeah. Yeah. But just remember, you would
have spent more than that on a bank holiday.
Still seems like quite a lot of money to
lose. Even though it's not really, is it Yep. Yeah.
Yeah, they're closing the account.
They're still closing
it. Yeah, I'm just going to go
swimming. I don't think so. Yeah, nah,
bro. This person wrote, "Listen to 2
minutes. Women like positivity because
women are drawn to success." I just
wrote I literally explained I had women
ignore positive messages. Then as soon
as I wrote negative messages, they
replied straight away.
So that's completely opposite of what
you've just said because they reply to
negativity and ignore positivity.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm fed up, man. I'm actually fed
up. Properly fed
up. Probably go to sleep for a week now.
Oh, use wrong again. Secular
slots wrong again. Secular slots.
Yeah, I'm fed up, man. Proper fed
up. I can't be
bothered. Enough to depress anyone in it.
Have to put anyone on a
downer to put anyone on the [ __ ] down. That
is positivity. They like negative
people. That's why they reply to
negativity and ignore positivity because
they like negative people. They like [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah, it's
bad. But you win some, you lose some, they
say. So they
say you win some, you lose some. But you
never actually win some though. That's
the thing. This has been going
on. It's been going on for months. This
has these rigged [ __ ] gambling sites. And
yeah. Well, hopefully I'll go to sleep
today and not wake up. That'll be the best thing.
Uh, let me see if secular slot still
posts. You reckon he still posts?
Maybe he still
posts. It's mad. He gambles all that
money yet it doesn't affect
him. H something tells me that he uses fake
money. Yeah, it's enough to put anyone
on a [ __ ] down, mate.
that positivity. That's [ __ ] made up.
That's [ __ ] They're like negative people and [ __ ] Yeah.
You win some, you lose
some. What they say? They
say I'm not so sure.
simulations. Anyways, I'm going to make
a couple of cut. I'll be right back.
Sir, big damn shitty [ __ ] thing
by No, I don't I don't approach anymore.
I gave up the women [ __ ] I just played roulette with
£150. Didn't win anything. pissed off
depressed mood even though I've got
money. So no, I'm not dealing with it no
more. I've not been out for three weeks
before we'll have a go on some online roulette. Lost £150.
Yay. Nah, women are not women. They're
NPCs. Mhm. Yeah. Women are not women.
Nah, they're NPCs. non-playing
characters. So, no, I haven't I haven't been going
out. Yeah. Uh you know that secular
stock, right? He says that oh, if you
gamble money that you can afford to lose
and you've got all your bills paid,
right, and it's only disposable money
that you're playing with, it's okay. But
it's not okay. And I'm living proof of
it because I just lost 150. I just sat
on this [ __ ] bed, bored, just played
150. I'm not entertained. I'm fed up to
be honest. I'm fed up with it, mate. And
I've got more than enough
money. So, I think I'm a prime example
of you can't gamble responsibly because
it will just affect your moods every
time you you think you're gambling again. So,
yeah. Yeah. I don't do it anymore. I
haven't This was the first time in a
month. I don't approach
anymore. I don't gamble anymore
really mostly. Yeah. Even though I did
just now that was first time in a month. So
yeah, and I've got money. I had I had
1,550 in one account. Now I've got
1,400. All my bills paid. I done some
food shopping. So I'm more than
okay. I'm more than aok. Okay. Do you
understand? It doesn't make a
difference. But saying that, if I went
out bank holiday, I didn't go out this
bank holiday, I would have been spending
£300. Yeah, I would have been spending
300 quid. So, depends how you look at
it, mate. Is that a step in the right direction? Could be.
So, yeah. I've just been playing
Simpsons hit and
run. Yeah. I don't even bother with
women anymore. They're all the [ __ ]
same. Do you know what stopped me um
bothering with the women anymore? More
cold is they go on your dates. They go
on dates to waste time. They ghost you
and they only reply to negativity. So
when you write normal messages, they
ignore them and as soon as you're rude,
they reply straight away trying to
victimize themsel. And I just thought
one day, [ __ ] this, mate. [ __ ] this.
No, I don't drink anymore
either. Yeah, I haven't drunk for like a
month. I haven't gambled for a month.
So, the first thing was I gambled and I
closed the account
down. Yeah. Now my friends messaging me
I'm too pissed off. You know what I'm saying? But yeah.
Yeah. Mhm. Yeah. I don't use dating sites.
I had a woman last month. She went on a
date with me. Cold
Stella. I had peranal tentinitis.
Tentonitis if I even pronounce it
properly. It's his foot condition, bro.
And I had to limp. I don't know if I
banged it or
I or I overused it. basically
um uh I was basically limping to go on
this date and uh the [ __ ] wasted my
time. Even though she approached me, she
gave me her number and she wanted to
meet, she's claiming how she didn't feel
the vibe. And I remember that Thursday I
was like, "This is me done. This is me
literally done, right? This is actually me
done." Then I just sent it. Then I went
out two weeks after that and then that's
when I was fully done,
bro. And I had to limp on that date. It
weren't no joke, mate. The pain was not
no joke. So, and then obviously I stayed out
because because of um obviously I was
out anyways even though I was in pain. I
was like, I might as well just send it
now. I'm out. They've got me out. So,
for [ __ ] sake. So,
No, it's just like this [ __ ] in America
code. I messaged the the [ __ ] last week
at 3:00 in the morning. I said, "Listen,
tell me what day and I'll come to
America next week." I I gave her the two
days now. She's a [ __ ] I said, "First
or Friday. I'm free on both of them
days. I have no problem coming and
whooping your ass in front of your
[ __ ] boyfriend and your dad. And
we'll see who the keyboard warrior is,
bro." Cuz they were pissing me
off, you know?
I would have I would have went 100
motherfucking% I would have [ __ ]
went, bro. Pissing me off. I swear to
God, it's all negativity. Nothing good
has come out of this this women [ __ ] you know.
So, I can't stand in me, bro. I'm not
even going to say the word. But
yeah, I was going to go out this week,
but I won't bother now. I don't
think. No, we got the Simpsons game downloaded and that. So,
yeah, I just can't stand women. I despise
them. And no one's ever going to change
my mind, bro. They've had many chances
to prove that they're a different cold
seller. You know, they haven't.
So, I won't be wasting my time anymore, mate.
Yep. [ __ ] 150 [ __ ] pound. What the
bro? Yeah. And they only reply to
negativity as well. So
yeah, no, even if you have something to
offer, mate, they don't even get to know
um what you have to offer before they
reject you. I've got money. I've got a
yard, you know, be working soon. I've
got [ __ ] to offer. It doesn't make a
difference unless you're a drug dealer
or you're a famous Tik Tocker. They're
just not interested in this country.
And you know the thing that keeps like
putting me off going out is that I know
that I'm going to have to go get a
haircut, spend money getting a haircut,
being sat on a chair for an hour just to
hear the same [ __ ] I'm not doing it.
I'm not [ __ ] I probably won't even do
it this week to be honest because it's
just the same old sat on a chair for an
hour, get your hair done, spend money,
go out, get numbers, they don't reply or
they reply, I'm just bored.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Yeah, they
reply straight away. They're nowhere to
be seen when there's positive messages,
but when there's negative ones, they
reply straight away and they try to
victimize themselves. I tell you one, a
funny one I had.
Yeah, there was this woman that I met
three months ago. I didn't tell you
this. I told these people it there's
water coming out this blister. Uh 3
months ago, and she was from Italy and I
was kind of being a tour guide, right?
Like I didn't even expect anything to
come out of it. Just said I was just
walking talking. Got her number and that
obviously messaged her two days later.
Never even replied as oh I got back. Thank you.
Rare. Um and then 3 months she didn't
reply. So I was like oh she's a good one
to do this experiment with. So I wrote
to her saying oh all women are evil. Bam she
replied. Bam. She was there trying to
say, "Oh, I would have replied, uh, but
yeah, you would have replied even though
it's been 3 months." Trying to victimize
herself. Then she was trying to say how
she didn't reply because I'm I was
writing misogyny stuff. And I was like,
"Darling, you reply to the misogyny
stuff, the normal nice messages that you
ignored." So that's what they do. They
they also the way they victimize
themselves is if you get a
number, right? If you get a number,
they'll ignore you and as soon as you
write nasty things, they'll reply
straight away and try to victimize
themselves. They do it all the time,
bro. They've been doing it for
years. Um, and I think the context it
was kind of rude to ignore cuz I spent
an hour with them. They could have just
messaged back once, but they're so
entitled and they're such [ __ ] um
that they don't like, who the [ __ ] do
they think they are? So, I had to stop,
bro, cuz it was just a negative, you
know? It's just the same old story with
them, bro. They're
boring. I should have gave up after that
Morgan [ __ ] to be honest with
you. But for some reason, I carried on.
So, yeah, I feel the same, bro.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] evil as
well. They're evil, too. Um,
cold. I say to them, I say to people,
"Women are evil." They're like, "All
women." I said, "Yes, [ __ ] all
women." That's what I say, cold. I say
every single [ __ ] one of them.
Yeah. Yeah. I lost 150 cold. It's [ __ ] in
it. I'll probably be depressed for a week
now. So now people seem to think cold.
Oh, you got no money left. Oh, you lost
a lot of money. People seem to think
that for gambling to affect you. Yeah.
Um, you need to lose all your money or
um, you have no money
left. You know what I'm saying? People
seem to think that when that's not the
case at all. I don't know about with
you, but it goes deeper than that. You
know what I'm saying? And they seem to
think you need to lose lots of money or all your
money, you know, and they talk like
you've lost all your money. I lost 150
today, cold. And people's like, "Oh, you
could have got nandos with that. You
could have got [ __ ] this with that.
You could have [ __ ] that. You could
have bought this with that." Knowing
that I've already got more than 10 times
the amount that I
lost. You know what I'm
saying? You know what I'm saying? Bro,
even though I've got 10 times the amount
I've lost, people still use it as an
example. Well, in one account. You know
what I'm saying,
bro? Oh, you could have bought this. Um,
are you forgetting that I still have
money? The [ __ ] They seem to think you
need to lose all your money for it to
affect you. I don't know why, bro. I
don't know where they got that from.
You know what I mean? Bro. Yeah.
Yeah, it's made me fall out with my M
and all of that. I'm not even going to
tell her I gambled even though it's not
all my money and obviously it's a little
amount of money. It's just I don't
really want to be starting people off
thinking stuff again. You know what I
mean? So yeah, and then you get people
like secular slots that says, you
know, I have quit gambling. I stopped
for a month, bro. you know, and obviously. Yeah.
Nice. Even if you lost 150 a month, it's
nothing, can it really? But
still, it's just bad, is
it? You know, it isolates you as well.
There's no such thing as responsible
gambling cuz I just gambled
responsibly. I just gambled responsibly
today. Cold Stella. Okay, let me ask you
this. Right. You got 1515 one account.
You got all your bills paid. You just
done food shopping. You just washed your
clothes. You know, you eat good. And out
of that one, say you got 1,550 left and
now you got 1,400 left. That's a lot of
money, huh? As in one account. So you
are you are gambling responsibly. You
got all your bills paid
um this month. You
know you got 1,400 left in one account
not 1550. So you see that I in my
opinion that's gambling responsibly though you
know. Nah bro benefits [ __ ] I can't
live off a,000 pound a
month. That'll probably be a time where
I'll have to again, but I'll have to figure something
out. Nah, bro. £1,000 is [ __ ] a
month. You know what I
mean? Nah, it's [ __ ] bro. Because
£1,000 a month is not a lot. You
know, it's kind of [ __ ]
How much money do you get a month? But
you didn't answer my question. That's
responsible gambling, isn't it? If you
had $1,550, you lost 150, you got 1,400
left, you got food, you got gas,
electric, and all your bills paid.
That's responsible gambling, isn't it?
That's gambling responsibly.
No, I think it's gambling responsibly,
huh? Yeah, that's gambling responsibly,
bro. And you still got more money coming
in. I think it's gambling responsibly.
So that secular slots is full of [ __ ]
cuz I took the breaks as
well. Yeah. But how much do you have to
pay? How much housing benefit do you
have to pay? So I'm a prime example of
somebody that's just gambled responsibly.
So what I just explained to you, yeah,
that's gambling responsibly. No,
yeah, I think it
is. I get 500 today, 500 in a couple of
days, and 350 in a couple of days. So is
that responsible gambling?
That's responsible gambling, is it
not? Would you say that's responsible
gambling? I think it is.
No. What do you think?
There you go. It sounds responsible, but
it still giving me these mood swings. It
still put me in a depression. So when
people like secular slot say, "Oh, as
long as you've got money and you paid
your bills," it's not about that. It's
the whole losing on
it. It's the whole losing on
it, you know? It's not an option,
mate. Yeah, I'm not chasing it, bro. I
just I'm not chasing it. That was
literally just me, bro. Like, I was just
bored, so I done it. So, I won't be
chasing. No way am I chasing, bro.
No, but that's my point is that you
can't gamble responsibly cuz look.
Yeah, it's just [ __ ] in
it. [ __ ] mate. Yeah.
Yep. Life [ __ ] sucks on it.
See, if gambling was a form of
entertainment, you wouldn't be feeling like
this. You know what I mean? You
know, pretty much have 3k
disposable cold. I pretty much have 3k
disposable money with all my bills paid
and I lost £150.
So how much is that out of your money?
What? It's not even 10%, is
it? So there's no such thing as gambling
responsibly. What is it? It's not even
[ __ ] It's not, is it? It's not even
10. It's not even 10%, is
it? It's like 5% of your money now.
Maybe something like
that. Maybe it's 20%, maybe. I don't
know. I don't know what it is. Maybe
20%. Maybe 10. I don't know. But
yeah, I say you got 3k disposable and you've lost 150. Uh sticking in
mate. Yeah, I just lost 150
greasy on roulette, mate. So, help
yourself. Yeah, I couldn't do it. I
couldn't That's why I couldn't work
because if I lost money, I would just be
too depressed to go to work. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm having um I'm having pork
chops for dinner
today. Oh, by the way, I'm going to
cinemas on Friday.
Grezy, I'm watching um Peppa Pig meets the Baby. Yep.
Yep. Have you seen that one?
Yep. Yeah. Grec. I lost
uh 150. I've basically got about 3k
disposable. About 3k disposable. And it
still made me depressed.
still puts me down in the dumps. Got my
bills paid, got
food, been eating good recently. Still
puts you down in the
dumps. Yeah, these streamers are
definitely um trying to promote
something for a business.
Definitely. Cuz there's no way, bro, you can [ __ ] Yeah, around that.
So, there's no
way. There's no way, bro. There's no
way. It's not a mental condition, mate.
condition. It's gambling as [ __ ]
No. So, you got around 3k. I'll give you
an example. G in one account. I got all my bills
paid. Uh, all my bills
paid. All my bills paid. Got food. Got
gas, electric, got washing stuff,
toothpaste. Had to buy the other day.
Clean clothes. I lost 150. So, that
leaves you with 1,400 in one account. Still depressing. Still [ __ ]
depressing. I don't go back to my own
ways. I hadn't gambled for a month,
Greg. I just thought I'd give it a try
cuz I was bored. Wish I [ __ ] never
now. Wish I [ __ ] never. Even though
there's no difference.
15,400 doesn't make a difference really
though. Does it greasy?
But it's just annoying.
Yeah, it's just annoying and
it isolates you as well. My friend's
been messaging me to go and play the
Simpsons and run with him. It isolates
you as well. This gambling I notice. It isolates
you. It isolates
you. You know what I mean?
Yeah. Yeah. But it's just gambling. You
win some, you lose
some. So they say
e. So they've been saying since
Christmas and we're now in May. Oh [ __ ]
Where did them six months go?
You win some, you lose some. Just
gambling. So they say, you win some, you
lose some. Yet you've not won nothing in
six months. But you can win and you do
win sometimes. So they say, but it's
been 6 months haven't won nothing, which
is one of the reasons I
quit, why I didn't I stopped doing it,
because of the same [ __ ] happening time
and time and time and time and time and time again. So
yeah, I've got pork chops for dinner
today. So yeah, I went to um get some
stuff. Got some burgers and pork chops, some bacon.
Greasy. It's still good to have in it.
2.8K, 8K 3K in it. Greasy disposable
now. I should get another [ __ ] I should
get like 600 in two weeks as
well. But I need to buy in stuff before
I can start this job. You see? So it's
not all I need to buy a phone.
So, probably get one for like
250. It's not ruined the way I
socialize, but it's ruined the way other people have.
Yeah. What do you think, Reevesy? 2.8K,
3K to have disposable is quite a lot now.
We're going to have to go back to living
off a grand a month at some point.
Grievy, don't know how I'm going to manage
that. That's going to be very hard.
£1,000 a month. [ __ ]
me. I'm not even taking a piss. If I
have to live off that money again, mate,
[ __ ] hell. Be depressing, isn't it?
What do you think a £1,000 a month cold?
It's quite depressing, isn't it?
Really? You literally have to just
eat. I'll be [ __ ] I have to [ __ ]
The only thing you could do is eat food
and try and save money.
What do you think, Grezy? I'll be
[ __ ] I'll be
[ __ ] Will you be [ __ ] on the ground? Greasy.
Yeah. Well, you get 750 a month, don't
you? People get less,
but yeah, it'll be hard to live off that
and then save at the same time.
What do you think?
We is a good
amount. Well, it is something cuz £1,000
a month, but uh yeah, again, I won't be paying rent.
buy a,000 pound a month. I mean that
whole,000 pound will be mine. I get 3k a
month. I get 3k I have I have 3k I get
3k a month and I've got like 150
outgoings. That's why I'm needing to save money now. So
yeah, I don't have no rent. I don't have
nothing, mate. I've only got about 150
in outgoings. Gas, electric, internet
bill, phone bill,
done. Rest is
mine. So, no, it's not bad in London.
If by not bad, I mean, it's not bad
compared to £300 a month,
but yeah, you won't be able to go out
drinking every week. We if you get a,000
pound a month I get 3k cold and I've got
150 outgoing 150 pound out
going 150. Yeah, I have out of 3k and
then the rest is mine. So pretty good is
it? Maybe one day it will end.
day won't be able to go to America on
that, would you, Greasy? Yeah, you
could. I reckon you could say if you got
a grand a month, you can go to America
in maybe five
months. I was thinking of starting this
business, Greasy. Right. But it's about
2K to start it. I've got the money to start it,
but it can sort of
[ __ ] then if it goes tits up, then
I'm down two grand. That's the thing.
with with businesses it's a gamble you
see it's a big gamble
so but with this business I'm thinking
of doing we could go you can get 6700 pound a
day 600 700 pound a
day never you mind I've Got my ways cold
stellar. Not I'm not talking about how I
live, where I live, what I do. Don't
mind talking about money and that, but
no, I'm not saying that. But yeah, 600
700 pound a day.
Greasy. Imagine that, mate. Three days a week. [ __ ]
me. Imagine getting that about two grand
week. Nah, mate.
Nah, not turn
anymore. My little
secret. How much disposable above do you
think is good
cold? A,000 2,000
3,000 3.8 I think I have which is the
most I've had in ages. But I stopped going out.
So yeah, it is a
lot. Nah, mate. You wish I [ __ ]
did, but I need to start making money
soon. So I'm not going to go into the
ins and outs of things, but
yeah. Yeah. And to give my sister £50
her birthday, so I give
her£50 and Yeah.
Yeah. Could you save up to go to America
Cold Stellar? Yeah, you can do it on
benefits. You can do on
benefits. I'm not saying what it is,
bro. Yeah, you can on benefits, but it
would take about 6
months. Grievy could even do it. It'd be
about 6 months.
You'd have to live on like 50 pound a
week. Uh be depressing
though. I could afford America. Somebody
that I had a one night stand with Cold
Stella. I said to the [ __ ] "Let me
come to you next week in it on a
Thursday, Friday, and I'll bag you up,
bro." In front of your [ __ ] boyfriend
and your dad. Yeah, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
house. Yeah, bro. It would have been
like a grand for just the flights, isn't
it? Oh, [ __ ] it, mate. Yeah.
So you'd have to live on 50 pound a
week. So it would be a depressant life
for about 3 to six
months. [ __ ] knows,
man. Yeah, it's the truth. I think it's
OCD. I've got Sunnyside. Listen, bro.
Yeah, I had 150 in Sorry. I had 1550 in
one account. Sunny side up. I just
gambled the first time in a month and I lost
[ __ ] I've got 1,400 pound in that
account left. Got all my paid got all my
um got all my um bills paid, got food
and everything and I can't stop thinking about
it. No, it's not that, mate. It's also the
hotels. It's also the hotel. It's like
four grand. America's about
£4,000. It's about
£4,000. No, I will break free. I'm not
addicted. I'm Bro, I stopped for a
month. I'm not doing it again. That was
just a one off. I was just lying in bed
b I didn't go out the bank holiday. You
see, I haven't been out for 3
weeks. So, the hotels are like £300 a
night. What I would do is I'm just going
to rent an apartment.
If the [ __ ] says, "Yeah, I'll just rent
an apartment 18 to 2,000 for the month
and I'll just stay there for a
month." I think that just makes more
sense than staying for a week and paying
for hotels. You might as well just just
get an apartment. I think it makes more sense.
No. And um you could probably work out
there as well and make money. So there's
no point going for a week and spending
£2,000. You might as well just stay
there. And obviously you'll do your
restaurants every week and then you just
do food shopping. I think it makes more
sense to me if you're going somewhere as
big as like America. I think it makes
sense. So if you can rent an apartment,
I think it just makes more
sense. But yeah, the point I was trying
to make study side is I gambled
responsibly and it still affected me. It
still it still has affected me, you
know, and I was only 150.
So, but yeah, if I go and I'm just going
to I'm just going to rent an apartment
and I can just do food shopping, you know, every
week. You you're best off to stay there
for a month, I think, rather than
staying for a week and spending the same
amount. What do you
think? Do some exploring, eh?
Yeah. Yeah, that's the point.
Sunside 2.8K disposable and it still
affected me. Eh,
mad [ __ ] madness.
That's mad, bro. I think I had 1,600 in
that account the other day, but I bought
some food and
stuff. Yeah, I bought some food and
Uh the past few months I didn't really
have a lot of money cuz I just kept
gambling and that's when I thought I
need to learn my lesson now. Well,
obviously I just done 150
but not that bad, is
it? Yeah, I have, bro. And I would have
I wouldn't even I wouldn't go back on it
anyways. I wouldn't go back on it
anyways, bro. be
there. I'm going to go back on
anyways. I'm waiting for them to close
to close my [Laughter]
account. They still closed it. No,
never. I've been to court though for
calling somebody um a gay
virgin. I've been to crown court for
calling someone a gay virgin though, if that helps.
No. No. I've never had
that. No. I've had police come on my
door and arrest me for breaking my own
door. I broke my own door and they
arrested me for breaking my own
door. Yeah. And they tried to call me. I
told them to [ __ ] off. Yeah. They
arrested me for breaking my own
door. Don't get me started on the
police, mate. Oh, I can't. I hate them.
modern women. Trust me. Don't Don't even
get me started on them [ __ ] peaks.
Seriously. Yeah, I believe you. It
happened to Money Mike. Well, I believe you. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm having to follow up a
report about that every um every week. Uh,
Sunnyside. Yeah, I'm I'm I'm I already
made a police report cuz obviously I
need to back up myself because
obviously, you know, if it does go to
court in 3 and 1/2 years and I've been
reporting and I've got all this evidence
and the police haven't done anything, it
doesn't look good, which it probably
won't go to court in three and a half
years, but you know, it's like the
police need to understand it's not one
rule for one, one rule for another. So,
I'm having to follow this up every week.
And I said, "Bro, this person is
harassing me. I've got all of what
they're doing. If I have to come back
every week, I will come back every week
and I'm not going to stop cuz I've had
enough of them keep coming on my door
time and time and time again over this
website." You know, they got to a point
where like they would just make up
charges to come on the on the door. So
now like anything they do, I just
screenshot and I just keep running to
the police, you know, this police woman.
I found her email as well. I said,
"Look, yeah, I've got a whole album of
harassment. These people keep harassing me."
Yeah. So, yeah. No, I've got everything,
mate. Even even new stuff that they've
done. So, I said
basically and then when I go there and
they say, "Oh, uh yeah, uh
um reporting to YouTube." I say, "I'm
not reporting it to YouTube. I'm
reporting it to [ __ ] you." I have to
keep saying that. It's not a YouTube
matter. It's a police matter. Yeah. Like
you keep coming on my door a million
times over [ __ ]
YouTube, you know? So that's why I just
tell them like I'm I'm reporting it to
you. Yeah. Practice what you preach.
It's not a YouTube matter. It's a police
matter. Evidently, it's a police matter.
How many times you've come on my
door, you know? So, and that's one of
the reasons I don't really come on here
anymore, Sunny. Is the grass in they can
give it, but they can't take it. They
always run to the police in the end.
They're [ __ ] losers. But because I
lost money today, I thought I just while
I'm in this mood, I should tell people
what it's like even if you have money.
They always run to the police in the end
of [ __ ] losers. So I'm having to do
it to safeguard myself. You understand?
I've got to
like Yeah. It's It's a police issue when
it's when it's them. It's a YouTube
problem when it's Yeah. Is that No.
Yeah. It's a police issue when it's me
and when it's them, it's a YouTube
problem. Yeah. I was like, "Let one of
them try to get [ __ ] rude to me today
and see what happens." Yeah. Cuz I've
had enough of it, bro. Yeah. Like, I've
had enough of it. And it's not even just
one thing. So, I was like, since they
want to get involved, get involved now
then, you know, get involved now. Simple.
So it's yeah it's a YouTube it's a it's
a it's when it's me but when it's other
people it's it's a YouTube
problem like the [ __ ] bro
like you know that's what I'm saying
like it's only called the police on me
right now bro I'd have the police on my
door in two
seconds you know what I'm
saying you can't even have an opinion on
social media anymore bro it's [ __ ]
pathetic you know what I'm
Yeah. So, they don't have a head start,
mate. The evidence I've got on these
people is is is ridiculous. Trust me. So,
yeah, just mad this way.
Yeah, they all they all report people,
bro. They give it, but they can't take
it. You know what I'm
saying? So, I've got to go to court in
three and a half years. [ __ ] hell.
Three and a half [ __ ] years. E.
That's funny, though. I'll be 30 [ __ ]
two. Yeah, they're [ __ ] idiots,
bro. It's not going to talk about
anymore, bro. It's negative in it.
There's no point talking about it
anymore. But if they ever came on my
door again, I just would on to it. I'll
just move house.
to be honest with you. Not that they
would have come to my door because I
haven't done anything, but say like they
did, I just wouldn't open the door to
them. I tell them to [ __ ] off and then I'd move
house. Yeah, you'll be wanted and stuff,
but I wouldn't give them the
satisfaction of arresting me
again. But I just wouldn't. So, I just
would then have to find
me. It's not like you killed someone, so
it's not like they're going to go on a manh
hunt. You know what I'm saying? That's
what I would do personally. Me, unless
they deal with things that you've
reported, tell them to [ __ ] off. Know
what I'm saying?
Yeah. Yeah. I've seen it, bro. I've seen
it. I've seen it. I've seen
it. Oh, you rocky
ride, Sunny. Oh, you You're Rocky Ride, aren't you?
Yeah, I was even going to reply
indirectly today, but there's no point
entertaining them, bro. They're grasses. There's no
point. There's no point entertaining them,
man. There's just no point entertaining them.
Trust me, there's no point entertaining
them. [ __ ] if you don't find shovel
co attractive, you're gay. [ __ ]
copycat. What's funny about a [ __ ]
copycat? You know, [ __ ] shovel car.
That's just copy and that is you got an
Eddie TSR [ __ ] for bro. She the same
[ __ ] Yeah, bro. Let's just let's just
change subject, bro. They're boring. But
yeah. Yeah. I told that Morgan [ __ ]
about herself 3:00 in the morning the
other day. I said, "Bitch, are you free
Thursday, Friday? I'm thinking about
coming to you, bro, and [ __ ] telling
you about yourself in front of your
boyfriend and her [ __ ] dad and your
dad. [ __ ] [ __ ] cuz I've saved this
money rocky ride because I've not been
out for a while drinking it out in it.
So, got an extra payment. So, yeah, I
thought [ __ ] it, mate. Is
it She's a [ __ ] She's a [ __ ] house,
mate. Proper [ __ ] house. Her and her father.
Yeah. Um, he broke up with her cuz he
knows what she's
about. You've been in this relationship since September.
They broke up cuz of me,
bro. Yeah, cuz of me,
matey. Yeah, cuz of me,
matey. He's still on Instagram, but
yeah, he's with someone else now. So, yeah. bad this.
Yeah. Yeah. It's [ __ ] up, bro.
Yeah. 150 g on roulette rocky ride
big. Still waiting for them to close
this countdown. What's going on, bro? [ __ ] hell.
that N G's a snake as
well. [ __ ] you know she's a snake
too on here. You have to understand
there was snakes on here.
Um good because the Izzy thing was kind
of my fault because of uh the whole
YouTube thing. So the yeah that stupid
[ __ ] in America cuz there was no excuse
why she done it cuz she wasn't a part of
YouTube. Izzy was kind of young and she
had Pat Mustard messaging her and you
know and she was [ __ ] 18 years
[ __ ] age not [ __ ] 28 years of
[ __ ] age you understand me
so it was kind of me bro with the easy
one you know
so if there was no YouTube there have
been none of this you understand if
there was no YouTube it would just been
like me with a 19year-old nothing would have
You know what I'm saying?
So, you watch somebody who was young on
YouTube. They've got a bunch of weirdos
messaging them, showing them [ __ ] about
you. You know what I'm
saying? Yeah. Exactly. Yeah. She was He
was saying to me, "Oh, you should come
to Birmingham." I'm not coming to
Birmingham, mate. What? To back you up
against Money Mike and Timmy. [ __ ] off.
Yeah. You're a snake and so is Natalie G
a snake. I've caught her talking [ __ ]
about me. [ __ ] off, man. Go [ __ ] your
own battles, you [ __ ] You [ __ ]
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying? No
way am I
[ __ ] How much money do you have now,
Rocky Ryan? How much money do you get? I
told you how much money I get. 3K a
month and I'm about 2.8 now, but I need
to get up a little bit more. I was
thinking of going out drinking this
week. It's my sister's birthday, but I
don't think I'm going to.
Yeah. Your kind of skin, I'm guessing. Is it?
Yeah. So, yeah.
Uh yeah, she's a user,
bro. The first one uh she went for.
Hey. Yeah, but Izzy would have been all
right if there was no
YouTube. He's still gambling. See, I
hadn't gambled for a month. I don't
really do it anymore. But the thing is,
Rocky Ride, I didn't go out this bank
holiday and that would have cost me
about 3 350. So, in a way, you're kind
of making positive steps. Okay. Yeah,
you might have gambled 150, but you
didn't lose all your money. You're not
going to gamble again for at least a
month. And you didn't spend £350 hearing
about I've got a boyfriend. So, in a
way, it kind of is a positive
though. It It is kind of a positive.
Even though you lost it in 10 minutes. I
mean, you're getting there, aren't
you? You might gamble. You still feel
like you're getting there, isn't it? As
ridiculous as it sounds. You know what I'm
saying? £50 a haircut. You went out two
days. Let's say £300 minimum you would
have spent. You'd lo
150. I was feeling bored cuz I didn't go
out of the bank holiday. You see? So, in
a way, it's a step to uh it's a step further. You
know, I must have been the only one in
England that didn't go out this bank
holiday. Yeah, I'll be back to that
soon. Probably 1.1K income. I'll be back
to that [ __ ] money
soon. Uh, Rocky
Roid, I'll probably be down to that [ __ ] money again.
Like I said, I'm thinking of buying into
a business. It's about 2K, but what if I
give the 2K and it [ __ ] goes tits
up? Yeah, I've not won for ages. One second,
Sorry about that, bro. Yeah, I just said the voice not. But
yeah, that's where we're at basically, bro.
Uh, you should try other ways to make
money. Uh, Rocky
Ride, there's a thing I'm going to start
doing soon, but I can't tell you what
cuz the grass is on the
community. Yeah, maybe get myself a plan
B, bro. You know what I
mean? Nice plan B. cuz
Yeah. 1.1k. That's on That's benefits,
isn't it? You get Yeah.
Yeah. I'm going Thailand in [ __ ] 6
weeks as well. I to go Thailand in 6
weeks as well. Rocky roid.
So, I need to keep some more money for that,
too. Yeah. Smell weed. Someone smoking
weed out there.
Listen to some music in a minute.
Yeah, this is a music.