Oh, Yeah,
man. Proper gaming chair. This is, mate. [ __ ]
hell. Proper gaming chair, brother.
Yeah, it's a proper gaming chair.
I just noticed that Desmond Mund is a Lewisville
Slugger. Yeah, that's that [ __ ]
Lewisville Slugger. I was walking to the
shop. Yeah, I was thinking, "Oh, that's
that [ __ ] isn't
it?" No, it's definitely that spacker. I
can smell him a mile off. And I'm not
going to tell you how I know it's him
because then he will stop trying to use
that um stop trying to he will stop
trying to um type in that way.
Yeah, that's I know who that is. That's
that spacker the low life Louisville
slugger on the one on that two account. Oh yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I clocked I clocked when I
was walking to the shop. I was thinking
about it. [ __ ] me, man.
Yeah, that uh Desmond Deeds is Lewis
Bill Schlugger by the way. I can smell
him a mile off. He's a low life. He's
got about a billion accounts of uh uh a
million accounts on
YouTube. Yeah, he can't afford
it. Yeah, there's a certain other person
that can't afford it
either. Grand a month, boy.
You can't afford it either. Oh [ __ ] Gab,
man. Yeah, I've got my Saturday lined
up. Nice McDonald's. Nice San Andreas. I
got my Saturday lined up for sure,
man. I'm not even going out this week
either. You're not missing nothing,
mate. I'm done in this country. [ __ ]
this. [ __ ] that, mate. [ __ ] this. [ __ ]
that. I'm legit done in this country,
bro. I'm not even joking.
Yeah. Should have gave up sooner, it [ __ ]
today. Yeah. I'm going to be I was going
to go out this week, cactus, but I
thought um I'm just going to play San
Andreas with some McDonald's. Save [ __ ]
tons of money, bro. I've saved so much
money, bro. not going out. Yeah, I lost
150 yesterday on the roulette, but
[ __ ] hell, bro. I've saved a lot of
money not going out, bro. So, keep it
that way, bro. I got Thailand in 5 weeks
now, so I'm happy, bro. Should have gave
up in this country
sooner. Yeah, I should have,
mate. This country is is [ __ ]
Somebody was like, "Oh, you're generalizing all
women." I was like, "It is all women."
Because if it wasn't all women, you
would have met somebody that wasn't like
that at 27. Of course, it's all women.
For [ __ ] sake. They're all the [ __ ]
same. They all give you negative experience. Cactus.
Yeah. Yeah. I played roulette yesterday.
Cactus £150. It went nothing.
Yeah. Well, at least I saved 600 pound
not going out 3 weeks, eh? So
yeah, it's good, isn't it? Or some nice food on Saturday.
Yeah. Sit with the computer. be
nice. Not Peter Belly's
mama. It's not Felly's
mama. Oh, I love that,
bro. I love that.
The sevenfold coming out
um should be coming out maybe next
month. So I need to buy that.
Yeah, I'm getting that sevenfold as soon
as it comes out. Maybe. Yeah.
Yeah. Wonder what Thailand's going to be
like in five weeks, eh? Be
good. Something to do,
eh? Got something to do, mate.
something to [ __ ] do,
bro. No, no,
no. I still don't No, they ain't closed my one
sec. Still ain't closed my [ __ ]
account, man. Update
accounts. idiots, man.
The [ __ ] I asked for my casino account
to be closed
down and it's still
open. The [ __ ]
bro? I done it yesterday cuz I was
bored. Tree spins it. something like
that. I'll be playing it
anyways cuz I was extremely
bored. My little candle
might even buy a [ __ ] pair of
trailers with 150
quid. Oh yeah, that account is
definitely Louisville Slugger. I can
smell that [ __ ] spacker mile
off. He says man after every sentence
and he thinks he's clever. He tries to
troll people but really he's just as thick as
[ __ ] right? And that just goes to
showing more about them that they have
to come on YouTube doing this every day.
It it says a lot about their life, you
know. It doesn't say anything about your
life. Um it
says stuff about their life that they
have to come online every day doing this
behind a million different one accounts.
Have I been laid yet? Have I've been
laid more times than you've had hot dinners,
mate. Yeah, that Desmond Deed. He's
still doing it this pastic. It's
Lewisville. I was walking to Tesco's
earlier and I was thinking that's him in
it. I just clocked on. I wasn't really
paying attention. He's a [ __ ] bro.
He says man after every sentence and he
claims he's married. That guy must live
a really sad life. Really, bro. At least
with this cactus Jack. Yeah, he's
mocking you. I sound really skin talking
about yourself. Um, go repeat on another
channel and self-reject on another
channel. See, with this cactus here,
he's mocking me intentionally for, you
know, as a laugh. You know, it's kind of
funny. But this Lewisville slugger, he
thinks he's so clever with what he's
doing. But I can sniff him a mile. I can
smell him like burnt popcorn. A mile
off. He's a He's a And it says a lot
about his life as well to to come on
YouTube doing this. Sad little bastard.
He's done it on Monty's as well. He's a
sad little loser, mate.
Yeah, sad little loser and got a life.
You've done it under a few accounts as well,
bro. Oh, and that's I've got a bone to
pick with you, Daz. You were saying to
um Oh, I've caught you as well,
actually. Snaky community. Um you said
to Timmy that Oh, don't forget that you
met PJ. Yeah, he met me. And what?
Yeah. Yeah, he met me, bro. And what?
And and and what he was talking about
nons, right? So he's like, "Don't
forget, lad. You met PJ." Yeah, bro. He
met me. And what? Yeah. Cuz there were
actual nons on this community that you
don't even target. So I wouldn't be
bringing up my name, mate, because
there's actual um there's actual nons
that you don't even
target. So, and I don't need to mention
them, but we all know who they are. So
So what if you met me, bro? I said stuff
about LJ's kids to prove a [ __ ] point
that he's not going to be fast enough to
come for me. Everything I've said to
these people. Yeah.