Oh, I don't know. [Applause] [ __ ] hell. Yeah. Yeah.
This is my last live stream.
Anyways, I won't be going live again after this
one. Thought I had to do the last one,
but I was a bit
busy. Yeah, man. defin
100%. This mongafi community. I'm a part
of this mongafi community, matey.
Little self projectors. Bit of self
projectors. Got to talk about himself every day. Yeah. [Music]
Yeah, that roulette was [ __ ] ultra rigged.
Jesus. Ultra [ __ ] red,
mate. Oh well, it's only 150. Underline.
What I got See? [Music]
You know my name. Everybody knows my name. You
spacker. Everybody knows my name. Bye-bye.
Weirdo. See you
later. This community is full of
[ __ ] This community is full of
[ __ ] disabled people.
Honestly, swear to God, bro.
Everyone know everybody knows my name.
Bye-bye, weirdo. Get life. Get off YouTube. Spack
up. This disabled community is [ __ ] man.
Where is it? What's up?
Lost all my
Nowhere near all my money, mate. I got a
couple of thousand pounds saved. Try
again. Try again, buddy. Never lost all my
money. Try again. Oh, freaking man. You
don't need to put a picture up of me,
bro. I know I'm better looking than you,
but you don't need to get jealous
now. Like, bro, come on. We've all seen
what you people look
like in your 40s. Bald, ugly, skinned,
disabled. We've all seen you people,
man. You little self-projecting disabled
[ __ ] How long are you going to keep
this up for now, bro? Come on. It's
getting boring now. You lose at
everything in life. You got no money.
You lose at the money game. You're all
overweight. You're all stinking. How
many times you going to keep losing,
bro? It's boring. Boring now.
It's boring, mate. It's actually boring.
I don't have a bed, mate. What did I
tell you again about being a disabled
[ __ ] Stop being disabled, bro. Come
on. Stop being
disabled. New people talk about
yourselves every day. I'm surprised you
don't get bored. Seriously, talking
about yourselves, it's some madness. I
don't have a bed. Yeah. I don't have a
bed, bro. Yeah. Yeah. I don't have a
bed. I got no food. I got no money.
Yeah. Yeah, bro. Okay. You keep telling yourself that.
Yeah. You keep telling yourself that, pal.
Pow. Yeah. I don't have a 500 pound bed.
Nah. Nah. Not me, mate. Nah. Nah. Nah. [ __ ]
off. You people talk about yourselves every
day. Nah, that's you, Fruit King. You're
the one that lives in Liverpool, not me.
You're the one that lives in Liverpool, not me,
mate. Nah. Nah, you people are skinned,
though. That's why you spend all day on
YouTube. It's cuz you people are the
skinned ones. You ain't got a life but
YouTube. Yeah, you people are the skinn
ones for sure. That's why you sit online
every day talking to each
other. You ain't got a life. You ain't
got no money. You ain't got no friends.
You ain't got [ __ ] all. You got nothing but self
projecting. Really? really ain't got
nothing in your life but self
projecting. Sad, bro. It's
sad. Yep. I'm probably going to play the
projector on Saturday. I won't be going
out this Saturday either. I actually
think we're going to I think,
bro, I think we're going to actually hit
the target, bro. The six week target and
give it up. I think we're going to I
think we're going to hit, bro. 100%.
Well, it's going to be four weeks this
week. I'm not going out. So
then two more weeks.
Yeah. Yeah. I said six weeks minimum,
didn't I? So yeah, I'm not going out
this week either. Can't see
happening. Yeah. Yeah. You keep telling
yourself that, Fuku. Yeah, yeah,
yeah. That's why you people call the
police on me every time, isn't it? Yeah,
yeah, yeah. Running to the police about
somebody is bullying them. Yeah, bro,
I'm well and truly
bullied. Well and and truly
bullied. Yeah, well and truly
bullied. White people have to run to the
police. I've noticed that about you
people as well. You always run to the
police in the end, you losers. I noticed
that. No matter what
happens, the end result is you always
run to the police because you're losers.
Yeah, you're [ __ ] losers. I've noticed
that. Proper loser community, mate.
Proper proper loser
community. Proper proper loser community. Yeah.
Bunch of virgins if you ask
me. Bunch of [ __ ] virgins if you ask
me. But then again, the police are are
nons lovers. Racist nons lovers.
[ __ ] racist nuts lovers. The police
in this country, mate, you all call the
police. You all call the police. That's
why I'm not coming on here no more.
Police informants, disabled people, projectors.
So, I lost 300 pound in the past three days.
It's not good, is it? I won't be doing
it again. I got my friend to change the
password. Not that I would lose all my
money, but just to be just to be on the safe side.
Yeah. But at the same time, I can't go
out drinking this week cuz I don't want
to hear about I've got a boyfriend. So,
that's not an option.
Um, yeah. I think we're going to start
the gym. I think I'm going to start the
gym all over again.
Don't end up like these people. Yeah,
literally. Probably just start
that. We'll go to Thailand in five weeks.
So, it'll be amazing,
bro. Yeah. Yeah. They bully me, bro.
Remember, man, Red Star can never tell
me where he Well, that Red Star is
Terry. I don't know why we keep saying
Red Star. That Red Star is Terry. And
the last thing I can remember is I went
to his area and he didn't show up.
Bro, listen. You people don't bully no
one. You're just disabled keyboard
warriors and that's what you'll always
be. You have been well and truly bullied
all your life in real life. All of this
bullying that you think you do on
YouTube, trust me, life has bullied you
since you come out of your mom's [ __ ]
And I assure you, you don't bully no
one. Any bullying that you seem to think
that you do online is nothing in
comparison to the bullied to how bullied
you people have been all your life. And
that's what it is. Like you people,
you've been bullied your whole life.
That's why you come on here with your
skin [ __ ] lowife selves cuz you've
been bullied your whole
life. That's why you come on
here. You you would know all about being
bullied, bro. And trust me, it's more
than just words. I mean, look at what
most of you people [ __ ] look like
when you get exposed. Look at the state
of you. The state of yourselves. Bomb
[ __ ] gray cat. You all fat and ugly.
Why are you all fat and ugly and old?
Every time you people get
exposed, why you people all fat and ugly
and old? Answer that question, bro.
Yeah, they bully me, right, bro?
No one on this community has ever
bullied me. No one ever has and no one
ever will. You bully me, you can't even
come. I can give you my address right
now and you will never come. You don't
bully no one. You're a keyboard warrior.
That's what you you are. You can't bully
anyone behind the keyboard. And me and
London Taylor went to Liverpool and you
kept quiet. So mate, we've bullied you
in your own
city. Yeah. And guess what? Me and
London Taylor has bullied you in your
own city, so I wouldn't be [ __ ]
talking if I was you. You got bullied in
real life, though. That's the
difference. Fruit King, you actually got
bullied in real life. You got bullied
out of your area. You knew to keep your
mouth shut and not to and not to do
anything cuz you got bullied in real
life. Not just YouTube, in actual real
life. Like, do you think some [ __ ]
northerner could ever come to my city
and make me shut my mouth like we did
you? Everyone's seen it. Everyone's seen
it, mate. You shut up your mouth. When
When I was in Liverpool, bro, you
listen. Let me tell you how much you
people bully people. When I went to
Liverpool, you all kept your mouth shut.
The so-called bullies, right? Because we
know that a lot of you people live in
Liverpool. You shut up your mouth. Yeah.
So, let's not start talking about people
being bullied here, you know? You're a
[ __ ] [ __ ] Hi, behind my mom. I live
by myself. I live by my [ __ ] self.
So, yeah. Oh, yeah. Behind your mom.
Same excuses. Bro, listen. You're not
about nothing. Shut up. You're not about
nothing. Just like Arsenal Mark is not
about nothing. Just like Terry's not
about nothing. You're not about nothing,
Conia. And I live by myself. So, yeah.
Next excuse, please. Bro, was I hiding
behind my mom when I was in your area
and made you [ __ ] hide? Was I hiding
behind my mom when I was in Liverpool
and all of you shut your mouth? Stop
embarrassing yourself, bro. Please. It's
getting boring now. The only people that
get bullied is yourselves every day of
my life for being so ugly and
disabled. Please, Fruit King. It's boring
now. You're not about that life. None of
you northerners are about that life.
Please stop it, bro. None of you are
about that life. It's okay to not be
about that life, you know,
bro. It's okay to not be about that
life. It's okay to not be about that
life, bro. It's
okay. Yeah, it's okay to not be about
that life, buddy.
You're not about that life. You're not
life. So why did you come out when I
went to Liverpool and me and London
Taylor went to
Liverpool? You and Kevin Murphy was
nowhere to be
seen. But you but you said you bully
people. Oh, let's you don't bully no one, mate.
Your life is in the pits. the
pittance. It really, really
is. Your lives are [ __ ] Trust me, bro.
And if I'm wrong, get off YouTube like
I'm doing. If I'm wrong, yeah, get off
of YouTube like I'm
doing. Yeah. You can't do that cuz
YouTube's your life. [Music]
Ah, that's nice, bro. That's
nice. You know what is the madest thing
about it is I was I can go to Birmingham
and knock him out, but there's no point
cuz you're all grasses. You know, I was
going to go meet a woman in Birmingham
who I met in London about two weeks ago
and I was just going to call all of them
out and just tell them to suck their
mom, but there's no point cuz you wore
glasses. So, I just I just like just
went against it.
Yeah, the guy caught me off guard. Yeah,
in the story, bro. I can go to his
actual city and bully him out of it, but
there's no point because you're all
grasses, so there's no point fighting on
a grassing shitty
community like Yeah. So, that's why I
just said there's really no point. He's
not the only one either. I would have
called that um what's his name out? That
um Provident Loans out. I would I would
have called that provident loans out and
that prime. I would have told them to go
and suck them murder and I'm not scared
of any of them. But there's no point
because they would just people here just
call the police.
So I would say I'm in your city and what
I was going to do is I was going to take
a big [ __ ] in
city being like basically I'm in your
actual [ __ ] shitty brother. [Music]
But there's no point, mate, cuz they're
all they're all police informants. None
of you are this community is about
[ __ ] Trust me. I'm not one of you. [Music]
Yeah. Never I would never fight anyone
on here, bro. Unless they come on my
door. or something cuz they're all
grasses. So why I fight someone in a
public place when we know the grassing
that goes on in this
community. Nah, I'm good,
bro. Don't care how big or small they are.
Nope. Nah, bro. You might as well
[ __ ] rob a [ __ ] bank. You might as
well just rob a [ __ ] bank. Any luck
with the girls? I've literally told you
about a million times that I've given up
with women. But again, you people must
be disabled because you ask me the same
thing over and over and over and over
again. I said 6 weeks minimum. We're on our fourth
week. So, and I said that was a minimum.
I was deadly serious with this women [ __ ] I
I want to break my nose. I despise
them. You know what I'm saying? I
actually despise every single woman on
this planet. I was dead serious when I
said I gave up, bro. You didn't believe
me, but I'm I'm being
serious. I will never ever try
again. I actually went to KFC earlier
and I saw some people out and about.
Nah, I'm good, bro. I don't want to
associate with people that can only reply to
negativity. They're they're [ __ ]
[ __ ] Why would you want to
associate with people that can only
reply back to negative comments,
negative messages? No thank you. They can [ __ ] themselves. So
yeah, that's how I feel about it anyway. So
yeah, I can't stand
him. Genuinely can't,
bro. I [ __ ] despise
them. That's the right [ __ ] word to use.
Yeah, that's the right [ __ ] word to use.
I said to that [ __ ] in America, [ __ ]
Lo, last week I said, "Listen, [ __ ] I
want to come to America next week. Are
you uh are you available Thursday,
Friday? Give me the day so I can battle
you up in front of your dad and battle
you up in front of your [ __ ]
boyfriend and we'll see who the keyboard
warrior is." [ __ ] shut her mouth.
Keyboard warrior. Everyone knows who the
keyboard warrior is
now. Everybody knows who the keyboard
warrior is now. It's you. You and your
family, [ __ ] mug. Yeah, because
obviously I haven't been going out, so I
saved all that money. Could easily go, bro. Easily
go. But uh yeah, they shut their mouth anyways.
So yeah, [ __ ] [ __ ] I can't stand
them, mate. Honestly, I can't stand
bro. They're actually worse than
roulette. I'm not even joking, bro. They're actually
That's all scumbags like really really
are. I do know what somebody said to me.
There's like all women question mark. I
said yeah [ __ ] all women of all
[ __ ] ages, of all races. They're all
the [ __ ] same. [ __ ] them, bro. This
Yeah. Sometimes my friend we talk about
that. I said I just don't want to talk
about it anymore to be honest. So
yeah, we don't try not to bring them up
anymore. They're not nice people in
general. Clearly, they're all [ __ ] They're all
NPCs, time wasters, you name it.
So, keep lagging it off. I'm going to go
out. I never end up doing it.
So I'm backwards.
I [ __ ] know this, bro.
Oh my god, I got sniffles, man.
zero. So yeah, I tell you one thing and
then you ask me the same question. [Music]
It's like roulette. I played roulette.
Yeah. Thinking, oh, it's going to be different.
That's the [ __ ] clue that is [ __ ] weather change, mate.
So, just because of
um Yeah, that was no different either. That roulette. Oh, [ __ ] [Music]
me. [ __ ] hell.
It's hot as well. I'm
about Here they are.