Get up there, [Music] [Applause]
sir. How about the run now? I'm going to pry
boy. Oh, two numbers. Two numbers out of
three approaches, mate. I'm telling you,
the track suit works charms, bro.
Telling you. I'm telling
you. It's working like a
charm. Working. Perfect.
Hey, the trap's just working like a
charm. I got two. I got two numbers,
three approaches. So, you know how I say
women only like [ __ ] Joe? You know
how K say about how women only like
[ __ ] And I'm thinking like as the
old saying goes, if you can't beat them,
join them. So I thought, you know what?
Yeah. Go out, wear a trackuit. A B
trackuit. Yeah. And then I'll show you
I'll show you the track. I'll throw the bottoms on.
Right. Yeah. There you go, mate. There
you go. Wait. There you go, mate. Just
straight up track him. That's all you
got to wear. You don't get I've got a
boyfriend when you wear the trackies,
mate. When you act like a head. I've
done three approaches. I I ain't got
one. I got a boyfriend, mate. I got two
numbers out of three approaches. I
actually recorded two of them, too.
Yeah. Hey, it's the tracks the way forward, bro. Oh,
[ __ ] It's a fake. I smell Somalian, bro.
There's a Somalian smell and it's
following me. And obviously it's not me
because I'm not Somalian, but it's quite
interesting. But it smells very Somalian. Yeah, mate.
I'm I thought Lord J was talking [ __ ] I
don't care about them people, bro.
They're just self projectors. I'm not
even going to give them my time, bro.
They're just self projectors. That's all they are.
Yeah, bro. They're just self
projectors. Like all them people on Lord
Day's channel. Yeah. I'm not even
responding to them. Like it's pointless.
They're self They're just self
reflectors. They ain't got a
life, mate. They're just self
projectors. There's no point even even
entertaining them. I've got the jeans
and bag just in case there's um
some issues. Maybe there's no one here
yet. There's no one here yet. Well,
there's people here, but not like
Yeah, them people are self projectors on
LJ's channel. They're self
projectors. Talking about 28, bro. These
people are [ __ ] 58. They can't get a
YouTube. I laugh at these people that
first and go. I'm on the rum. I said I
was going to stick to beer. Yeah, but the
rum the rum is half price. So, I thought
I can still spend my 50 budget. I got
I've got a budget of £50. Well, I'm
probably going to get an escalator, but
in terms of drinking, the budget is £50.
And I think we're not going to we're not
going to exceed it. Where's Kate? [ __ ] it out.
I saw some guy in the Weather Spoon as
well. I see some guy in the Weather
Spoons I met a couple of months ago.
Yeah. Yeah. We know each other straight away. 250 m. Bargain
bargain. I'll regret this the next day.
Next day I'm going to regret this mate
when I'm [ __ ] hung over for two, three days.
But well, I say 50. I actually bought
food as well.
I bought with a weather spoon. A burger mill. Sorry.
Yeah. Get busier so we can spend it again.
But this gets
you get you. Get Yeah, boy.
Why Joe? That Morgan never imagined a message.
I said, "Let me come to America next
week, Thursday or Friday." You didn't
reply. She knows she'll get [ __ ] up.
Just like her [ __ ] boyfriend. They
know. They know better for
themselves. They know better for
themselves. Yeah, they do.
No, just last week I said listen I've
saved a lot of money but I was put
injury for a month. Obviously I wasn't
able to go out drinking cuz I couldn't
walk. So I say listen let me come next
week. Come on. I want to show you who
the keyboard warrior
is. I said I want to show you who the
keyboard warrior is. My dad keeps
saying, "You know, your dad's talking
about keyboard warriors is let me show
you who the keyboard warrior is, [ __ ]
You're not about nothing, mate." And you
know what? Yeah. Let me tell you
something. You know what? This
guy, bro, listen. This guy, brother,
listen. This [ __ ] guy, bro, been a
Weather Spoon. I think I said something
to him. I think I said he was a B man or
something. He was trying to wake me up.
Yeah, we're talking normally in it. He
knows he can't go there, bro. He'll get
[ __ ] up. He knows. Yeah. I think he
was trying to like weigh me up on that
in it. And he thought, "Oh, I'll just
allow it, bro. He knows you'll get
[ __ ] up." Like, that's what I'm
saying, bro. You know, you'll get [ __ ]
up. That's what I'm saying. Like, he
knows. He was trying to wake me up. No,
no. He was all right. Yeah. But he was
sort of being like, "D like he was two
months ago." And I showed him, bro, I
ain't scared of you. I'm not scared of
no one in my body language. And then he
backed off in it. All right, that's it,
bro. He's a [ __ ] bro. Yeah, he might
go to the gym or whatever. I'm not
scared of no [ __ ] Doesn't matter how
many of them is. And I think I said
something to him like, "Your friend's a
[ __ ] idiot or something." I said
something not not too bad. And it was
kind of awkward cuz we saw each other
again. He knows he he will get [ __ ]
up, bro. Like, he will. He He honestly
Yeah. He honestly will. And it doesn't
matter about new boyfriend. I don't care
if you got a new boyfriend, man. You
call me a keyboard warrior. I want to
show you how much of a keyboard warrior I
am. You're not about nothing. You are
your father. Yeah. So, if you don't
care, future, stop calling people
[ __ ] keyboard warriors. Cuz you're
not a keyboard cuz you are the keyboard
warrior. No, I lost 3000 pound on
roulette the past couple of
days. No, I lost some money on roulette,
mate. No, I lost some money on roulette,
man. Uh, in the past four days, I lost
300 pound, but I didn't go out for a
month, so I was like, "Okay, well,
yeah." Nah, bro. I play that [ __ ] no
more. I don't really gamble. I was just
kind of bored over the bank holiday, so
I thought I'd play some roulette. I
actually show you one of my spins if you want.
fins. Yeah. Well, I would have spent
about £700 really.
So, there we go. I'll show you my spin
if you want. It was 80 quid. They
weren't having none of it.
W having none of it, mate.
I won't be live for long cuz I got to do
these approaches and go home, mate. One piece. So
yeah. Yeah, I got to be a bit uh Yeah,
I'm [ __ ] mate. I'm [ __ ] I'm
actually [ __ ] I'm no joke. So yeah,
hang over tomorrow from Strong. Better
believe, boy. Better believe.
So can't turn down rumbly. [ __ ]
me. You're talking about yourself. No,
you're talking about yourself. Smog
time. Mate, listen. Whatever you say
doesn't bother me cuz you're talking about
yourself. One sec. That's not allowed,
mate. You're talking about yourself
literally, mate. I went to castle three
times and you never said nothing to my
face. So all of them things that you're
writing is about yourself, mate. I've
got more money than you would ever have,
mate. You're not even worth reacting to
because at the end of the day, right,
all of the people from L J's channel,
you're just self projectors. You're
irrelevant. You're not even worth
arguing with. At the end of the day,
bro, when I was in
Newcastle, you was not saying nothing to
anyone. So, shut up. And I remember
calling you out, bro. It's minor. You
can be a keyboard warrior all you want.
No one cares. It's boring now. You
know, like all them things that you
listed is about yourself.
Congratulations. You described yourself,
man. Um, yeah, bro. Look, it's funny,
bro. It's funny.
My hair is looking a bit greasy. Well,
mate, if that's the only thing I got to
watch out, then hey, I'm beating you by
a [ __ ] long shot.
I need to go in a minute. Got some stuff
to do. Some people got a
life like these
bongos. Is that right,
Cory? Hair looks a bit greasy, bro.
You're fat. Stop judging my looks when
you're the one sat there scared to show
your face. No one cares. Boring. Boring. Now, boring.
Boring. When one of you people scooting
for cuz you showing face. I've got the
balls to show your face. Come back to
me. You can never do that. Like I said
on my video earlier, you're all kind and
ugly. though it's a
minor talking about yourself every day know
but I recorded I've already recorded two
approaches one where I got a number but
um I'm going to post on my main
channel you don't
know it's getting busy
It's going to almost be time to sign, my man.
Yeah, mate. They're all self objectives.
None of these people bother me. No
matter what they say, they don't bother
me cuz they're talking about themselves.
Think about it, bro. I'm out here
drinking. I'm about to meet a friend.
I'm out here living life. They're sat on
YouTube. No life at home, bro. They can
say what they want. Nothing they say
bothers anyone. It's boring
now. And they can't show their face either, you know. Yeah.
Have you noticed as well? None of these
people show their
face. Have you noticed that none of them
show their face? Why is
that? Why do none of these people show
face? Why do none of them show their face? Tell
us. I can tell you, but I ain't saying
none of us. Yes.
They got nothing in life for self protective.
That one over there require for a whirl.
Go. Give it a [ __ ] whirl,
man. I'm going in the old
chuckies. Three approaches. Two numbers.
No, I got a boyfriend. That's
good. No, I've got a boyfriend yet. It's
got to be the satsu. It's got to be the Ammani satsu.
But good then give it a
whirl. Trying to I'm trying to support
it to go. It's all about the tips. You
see it's all about the booby. If their
booby does not understand this can't go
over, mate. It's just going to be a
complete waste of
time. Where the is this [ __ ] He was
supposed to be here two hours ago.
Oh, I'm in London. I'm in
London. You need to see about the tits,
guys. See, Morgan ain't got no tits. It's all
fat. It's all saggy. They're all
saggy. You ain't got none.
Yeah. Oh, mate. Yeah. If you don't like
Sh, you're gay. You [ __ ] copycat. You
know what? Yeah. As soon
as mate, you know
what? So soon as I heard that, all I was
thinking is you copycat. You [ __ ]
insecure little hobo. That's bro. As
soon as I heard that, that's exactly
what I thought. That's not even funny,
bro. That's copying. Copycat.
Copycat. She's not even looking. And yet
a certain person says that if you don't
find her attractive that you're gay. He's a
copycat. He's a copycat,
mate. He's a [ __ ]
cop. He's got no
originality. That's why he's still a [ __ ]
virgin. That's what I got, mate. Don't
need to bring up my Don't need to bring
my out anymore. Got my
provisional. Yeah. what my provisional bay
eat. I'm I'm seeing what fish is
about. Hopefully I don't get I've got a
boyfriend today, mate. I haven't had it
so far. Three approaches, two numbers,
one sober, two sober, one drunk. So hopefully we
spott hopefully get [Music]
Yeah, that was a roulette spin. £80. 80
quid. We weren't having none of it,
mate. For topping. We weren't having it for
topping. We weren't having none of it,
man. Thailand in five weeks. 4 and 1/2
weeks. 4 and 1/2 weeks. Four. Four and a
half. Four and a
half. Four and a half weeks. That's four
Both come. Don't stop me, mate. Mate,
there's no cold project yet. I'm
waiting, mate. I'm picking my moment.
Chill, bro. I'm picking my
moment. I'm a
watchdog. I'm a little watchdog. Leave
me alone. I've only got two numbers,
bro. I'm a little
watchdog. I'm a watchdog, mate. Give me
a minute. [ __ ] It's only [ __ ]
7:00. There's not anyone about.
I'm a little
watch. Trust me. I'm
watch Trust me. I'll send it, bro.
Wait. There's not really There's a lot
of people, but they're all in groups at
the minute. Wait, bro. Chill.
I have a drink. It's
almost full price.
Yeah. Morgan's got saggy tits,
bro. She's got saggy ass tits.
Yeah, she's got saggy tits.
I'm going to have to get involved in a
minute. Jo, there's a card. Can I get
his name again,
please? I'm going to have to get
involved again, mate. In a
minute. 50 bargain there. Good.
This is the perks of not being on,
thousand pound a month. You can do what
you want, mate.
This is the perk of not being on £1,000 a month.
This is the perks, mate. Not being on £1,000 a
month like some virgins.
Yeah, they're all in groups at the minute. Wait.
They're all with guys at the minute.
Wait, it's only 7:00. It's early.
Wait, it's early,
bro. Yeah, Morgan's got saggy
tin. She's got saggy ass tits.
Hey, they're [ __ ] saggy as [ __ ]
Thank you, Austin. [Applause]
I need to go when he goes 50%. I literally need
to see no opportunities so far. I'm
trying to look
There's none so far.
It's funny though. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm looking at that one over
there, but I'm looking at the
boos. Oh, J. That's him.
Hey, let's see if that's the real name.
Oh, listen. Hey, listen. Here's another
thing, man. I'm in the old track suit.
Who says that you can't go? Who says
that? You don't know. You don't know
where I am, mate.
Listen, right, club? You don't know what
club I'm in. Another thing is, listen,
you little [ __ ]
Right. I've got the suit on, mate. The
track going, you don't mate. Listen.
Next time you come here, come to London.
Come to London. I will give you my
address. You know where I live. I don't
live with my mom anymore. Yeah. Come on
my door, please. I'm recording it like
you done with Tibby. You're not about
nothing, mate. You're a gingerree.
You're not about nothing. You will never
be about nothing. You're just some obese
diabetic little [ __ ]
Yeah. Hey, I will pay for your flights
to come next week and you're never going
to come for me, boy. Never. Just like
three years ago when you ran away, you
little [ __ ] Said learn.
Anyways, I'm on 50%. I'm out of here. I
might be live a bit
later. Getting a bit louder.
Listen. Right. I'll be later. I'll
definitely be later, but I'm still in
the club. I'm back at home. So, yeah.
50% now. I leave. Bye-bye.