Y I wanted to talk about uh these
disabled people on YouTube.
Ah, bit skin there.
[ __ ] Me and Tom today. Yeah, man. I
just wanted to
like talk about these little spackers,
these little self projectors in their
40s. They want to talk about people that
are [ __ ] God knows my [ __ ] age.
Yeah. And these people are sat there on
YouTube every day, year in year out, day
in day out. Can't take one day off of
YouTube. I'm going to [ __ ] start
talking about these spastics, bro. When
enough people join 100%. Yeah,
bro. Yeah, man. Not as weird as you
people. You're in your 40s and you're on
YouTube every day and you can't get off
it. That's [ __ ] weird. That's [ __ ]
weird. You know, listen, I didn't do a
video about this yesterday. Yeah.
Because I was out and then, you know,
enjoying myself. Mate, you people, you
know why I don't even respond to anyone
on LJ's thing anymore? Because you're
all projectors. Like, you're not even
worth talking to or about. Like, look at
your own lives for a second. Yeah. You
people are in your 40s. You ain't got no
money. You ain't got no life. You're sat
on [ __ ] YouTube every day. You can't
even leave your house. And you think
you've got room Yeah. to actually Yeah.
[ __ ] um talk about other people. I'm
speaking to that Muslim woman, by the
way, Cactus. She replied,
"Mad, yeah, I did." Well, obviously I
went out by myself. I did do it by
myself. Got some strange looks, but you
know, we overcame
them. The guy was like, "Oh, uh, you and
who else?" I said, "Just me." Yep.
Tell her about my love for
pork. Ah, she replied back straight away
with texting. It's going quite good,
LJ. No, I wasn't hiding my
niece. No, I wasn't. I was by myself.
You see, I was by myself. I [ __ ]
walked into JD by my [ __ ] self. I went by
myself. Yes, I [ __ ] did. What niece?
One's a [ __ ] baby and the other one I
don't even see. What
niece? I only have one [ __ ] niece and
she doesn't like Pepper Pig and the
other one's a [ __ ]
baby for [ __ ] sake. So, no, I did go
myself. No lying on my channel, matey. [Applause]
Yeah. No, I like Peppa Pig. It's lust,
mate. The [ __ ] cinema was packed out,
man. But hey, I'm not going to The
police come on the door today. I had to
report this, bro. I'm not going to be on
this community for much longer anyways,
bro. It's It's weird as [ __ ] Did you see yesterday
cactus just going for a drink? Yeah,
just just going for a drink triggers
these people. It it goes to show they
ain't got a life. They're anxiety
ridden. They can't even leave the house.
These people, bro, can't even leave the
house. They're actually
anxietyridden. They're actual spastics,
bro. It's an actual [ __ ] community. I
swear. I swear to God, bro. They're [ __ ]
weirdos. They're like in their 40s, bro,
on YouTube every day. How [ __ ] up is that?
That is [ __ ]
weird. Hey, that is [ __ ] weird, bro.
It's all weird. This community is weird, bro. Yeah. But
yeah. Yeah. Mentally deficient. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah. Yeah. We had to get to that. We
had to get there. Um, LJ before them
[ __ ] Stitch and Lola [ __ ] There was
a lot of them about them Stitch [ __ ]
Yeah, I got some funny looks. But, you
know, that's all part of the game. You
know, how else could it be explained the
same reason people still love
Spongebob? You know, if you've grown up
watching Peppa Pig, you like Peppa Pig.
It doesn't leave you. you you watch it
as a child and you still have love for
it in your heart, you know, like Tom and
Jerry, you know, that's how it can be explained very
easily. Yeah, man. Oh [ __ ] Yeah,
man. What's What are you saying? Listen
more. These adults that like
Spongebob. But yeah, this Muslim is
definitely interested. I went to an
school yesterday. I had the best [ __ ]
ever. She said, "You almost choked me to
death." I rammed it down her [ __ ] throat,
bro. Oh, she just replied, "Oh, bro, I'm
definitely meeting this Muslim
again." Definitely, definitely.
Definitely, definitely meeting her
again, bro. She texting back and forth,
back and forth. Bagged it, bro. My
friend even said as well, "Yeah, I think
you have this um Muslim
one." I [ __ ] rammed it down her
throat, bro. Rammed it down her throat
yesterday, bro. I was choking a bit,
Yeah. Yeah. You like my trainers? Thank
you. It took a while to find a pair that
I liked. And I'm going to wear the
tracksuit on Thursday. I'm going out
with my mates tomorrow, LJ. But I won't
be wearing the tracksuit. Yeah,
man. But what if she says, "Oh, you need
to convert. You need to convert to
Muslim." I wouldn't convert to Muslim,
man. I'm not [ __ ] converting to
[ __ ] Muslim. She wants to meet today,
but I'm not I'm not meeting. Well, she's
she's telling me where she is, but I
ain't going there. [ __ ] that, bro. I'm
tired. I'm not going to come out the [ __ ]
shower. I'm not converted to no
[ __ ] mate. Listen, do you not
understand why I got a money? Cuz it
attracts the [ __ ] It's not whether I
like it or not. It's it's it's what gets
the [ __ ] It's what gets the [ __ ]
I used to get boss, but now I just wear
money. Nah, bro. Not today. I'm
tired. Yeah, I'm skinn. I just spent
£500 and I spent money yesterday, but
I'm skinn. Yeah. Yeah, I'm very
Yeah. Yeah, I'm proper skinned, man. How
do you know? Yeah, I'm proper skinned,
mate. I'm going to be starving
today. Do you like my little tracksuit,
Cactus? You wear true religion, you
[ __ ] [ __ ] You want to talk about
[ __ ] Ammani, you wear true religion,
you absolute [ __ ] mate. Only [ __ ] tramps wear
that, mate. The
tracksuit, the tracksuit was over £200,
you [ __ ] stupid idiot. Yeah.
Yeah, I am done with the UK, but I just
wanted to go out and drink yesterday and
I'm going out tomorrow to meet my friend.
So, yeah, I am done with it, bro. I'm
going to Thailand in [ __ ] four weeks.
Yeah, I am done with it. But I like to
still go out and drink. I'm going out
tomorrow. My friend keeps saying, "Oh,
let's go out. Let's go out. [ __ ] it."
You know what I mean? When you're when
you're not on a grand a month, you don't
need to worry about these things, LJ.
And you're not on a grand a
month. So, yeah. When you're not on a
grand a month, you can do these things,
you know? Well, I [ __ ]
did. So, yeah. Oh, you're trying to
figure out how much things cost, bro.
You're a [ __ ] s bastard, man. You
don't know how much my stuff costs. I
thought you said I was skint as well.
Ah, you're an idiot, mate. You don't
know nothing. And it made me laugh uh
last uh yesterday when you was like, I
got my big money. I get my big money.
What's my big money? Wait. What's my big
money? You [ __ ] You don't know how
people get money. You don't know. You
know, it's actually entertaining how
stupid you really
are. You know what I mean? Yeah. Yeah.
When I got benefits. Oh, I've got a bit
of bum change here actually, if you want
to see. Yeah, I got some money lying
around there, actually, if you want to
see it. This is a bit of bum change I
didn't even take with me. Yeah, man. It's all
benefits. Yeah, I got a bit of bum change
here. It was just left on the side, man.
left. Could be deposited, could be not.
I'm skinn as hell, man. Like, I'm I'm
I'm I'm broke, man. I'm [ __ ] broke.
I'm broke as [ __ ]
I'm broke, mate. I might need to start
selling my ass on the street. Know what I'm
saying? I I might need to start selling
my ass crack on the street, bro. This is
just some money for the caller shop, you know,
mate. Yeah, I don't I don't show money,
but it was just here, so I thought, [ __ ]
it, is it? Yeah, that's over 500.
Ah, yeah. My benefits. Yeah. How much
his benefits pay? So, I lost Okay, I
spent £500 today. I lost 300 in roulette
a few days ago. I've just shown you over
£200 there. How much does these benefits
pay, bro? I need to get in on it. I need
to get in on it,
bro. No, I didn't watch it. So,
yeah. Very hard to buy things you like
nowadays. I went to Reese. I saw some
stuff and there was no point buying it
cuz I got loads of stuff in my mom's saw
which I'll be wearing tomorrow. But you
wear True Religion, mate. You cannot pay
me. You cannot [ __ ] pay me to to wear
True Religion. That is the most
trampiest [ __ ] That's the most
trampiest [ __ ] thing you could wear.
True religion. True
religion. True [ __ ]
religion. That is trampy, bro. It's so
trampy that it started becoming like £50
per thing. Back in the day, the jeans
was like £300, mate. That's what tramps
were. True religion is the most trampiest thing ever. So
yeah, before they even So what, bro? You
wore Ammani 20 years ago. Okay. Tom and
Jerry's 100 years old. People still
watch it. Okay. And your point
is Yeah, man. And your point is what,
bro? [ __ ] true religion, man. [ __ ]
off, bro. But yeah, there's some nice re
stuff, but I have loads of re stuff at
my mom's. I just wanted to wear another
tracksuit because I'm I like the
attention that I've been getting lately.
Cactus with the uh with the tracksuit, you know.
Yeah. Yeah, bro. It doesn't matter what
you call it, it gets the [ __ ] [ __ ]
in. I didn't get I got a boyfriend
once. So, there you
go. I didn't get it once, mate. Even in
the spoons, I didn't get it. And the
only one that said she was married was
35. and she approached me and she still
kissed me and all the guys at the back,
the black guys weren't getting no
attention. I was like, "Fuck me. I need
to I need to get I need to be wearing
this more often, mate. Cuz whenever I go
out with a cliff, the nice jeans and
that, you just get I've got a
boyfriend, you know." Yeah, my benefits.
Yeah. Yeah, my benefits. Okay.
Well, no. Not a fake girlfriend. Not a
fake boyfriend, nothing. Even in the Weather
Spoons. Even got a Muslim that's
interested and wants to meet again.
[ __ ] hell. Yeah, tracksuit is for me.
Well, tomorrow I'm not wearing a
tracksuit cuz I'm going clubbing until
late with my friends. But Thursday, I'll
be I'll be out
again, mate. I feel like I'm already in
Thailand, you know?
Yeah. And the Escort gave me the best
blow Well, the best [ __ ] I ever had
was actually from an American in the
alleyway. But that was a second one. Oh my [ __ ]
god. But let me tell you something. Good
things about Muslims. Do you want to
know good things about Muslims? And how
I know this cuz I've actually got Muslim
friends and not the ones that were born
here. Do you know what? Do you know
what? Uh, I tell you what's good about
Muslims is they all stick together. And
when you need money, they just give
money. They just give money. See, you
you you know, you can be very um
arrogant, but when you actually learn
the religion, you'd actually wish
English people was more like
it. Yeah, I did meet him at the end. Yes, I
did. So, better than being in your 40s
on YouTube alone speaking to people that
scared to leave the house like you, LJ,
you know. So, uh, yeah, you know, you're
ignorant about the religion and stuff,
but when you actually learn it, you
would actually wish English people was
more like that, you know, close
community. You if you had kids, you if
you have kids and you're Muslim, they
will just you can go to any relative's
house, anyone's house, and they'll take
you in. It doesn't work like that in
England, you know, with English people, you know.
I used to be ignorant about it. You know
what I'm saying? But uh trust me, bro.
They're a lot better than English
people. I'm not Muslim. How can I be
caught a Muslim when I eat pork? Nah, I
I I eat pork. How can I How am I caught
a Muslim? There's no such thing as
caught a Muslim. You're either Muslim or you're
not, mate. Being on YouTube in your 40s
is [ __ ] embarrassing, mate. Yeah.
Yeah. Uh, and no, I'm caught Turkish,
but I'm not Muslim. How can I be Muslim
when I drink and I eat
pork? And Turkish is not the same as
Pakistan either. I know these things, trust me.
Um, so yeah. Yes. But it's not the same.
Um, what's the
word? Yeah. Yeah. Story of your life,
Matty. You know what's so mad about
these people? They're talking about
people being alone, but they're alone
all their life. Like without YouTube,
these people would die. Like they can't
take one day off of YouTube. So all they
do is project. They just talk about
themselves. That's why it doesn't bother
me because all they do is literally talk
about themselves, their own lives, but
they're just a lot older and a lot
uglier and a lot fatter. So they just
talk about themselves. That's why we
would just laugh at them, you know, on
on YouTube in your 40s alone in your
yard, no friends, no [ __ ] nothing.
You got nothing, mate. You know what I'm
saying? I never talk to anyone. Yeah, bro. Projecting
again. Projected again. You're talking about
yourself. That's good, bro.
You thought going to the cinema alone
was bad. Why? Why is going to the cinema alone
bad? You know, but again, you're by
yourself all the time. So, you're
self-rejecting. Going to the cinema
alone is bad. Bro, you people need to
look at your own lives. You talk about
people being alone a lot. You're alone
every single day of your life, sat on
YouTube. I'd rather [ __ ] go to the
cinema by myself than be sat on [ __ ]
YouTube scared to leave my house like
you people. And you know it's the truth.
Yeah. You'll send Chica around. Oh,
really? Oh, we're back to this
again. Oh, we're back to this again.
You're boring, mate. Are we back to this
repeating again? It must be your
autism. You people would know all about
loneliness. You're lonely every day of your [ __ ] lives. [ __ ] So
yeah, uh stay alive and let's see. Oh my
god, you're boring. You don't give
anyone anxiety. Listen, a matter of
fact, yeah, why don't you you know have
you gone for Timmy three times? I will
literally pay for your flights to come
on my door and we'll see what you're
about. I will literally pay for your flights, man.
I will pay for your flights. 60 70 80
however much it is £300. I will pay for your
flights. Please come on my door again.
Please do. Please. You've done it with
Timmy. You've done it with Timmy and
he's a known grass. Please, mate. I
would put you in the back of a [ __ ] van,
mate. Chico is a mad [ __ ] bro. I'm not
scared of anybody, so there's no point
even saying that to me. I tell you no
matter what fact. Yeah. True
story. There was this guy I seen Weather
Spoons yesterday who I met before um
months ago, the one that I ditched and I
think I did say something to him. I
can't remember exactly what I said. I
said something and he was trying to he
was trying to weigh me up and that in
it. But he knew that I wasn't scared.
Like I can't explain it. Like he was
watching my body language and he knew he
couldn't even try and move to me, bro.
And he he was bigger than me as well.
Like so we just left it as yeah I'm
going out. Bye. So he knows bro he can't
do anything. People judge by body
language. You understand? Like L J he
only goes for Timmy because he knows
Timmy won't fight back. But he runs away
from me. He's run away from London
Taylor. You know what I'm saying, bro?
So like L J would lost a day in London.
That's why he has to come unannounced.
He has to run back to bro. This LJ is a
proper [ __ ] He's a proper [ __ ] Look,
look how many times you've gone to [ __ ]
Birmingham. You know, anyways, why don't
you come on my
door? Hey, bro, why don't you come on my
door? You're welcome
anytime. You're welcome anytime. But we
all know what your game is,
LJ. It's the boys in blue. That's what
you always turn to. The boys in blue. I
won't call the police on you. There's
only one person I'm calling the police
on and I'm going to keep continuously do
it. I The police was around today
actually and I'm going to continuously
call the police and I will not stop
until they get nicked.
So yeah, see how I handle Chico. Bro,
this guy doesn't even
exist. You're boring, bro. You're
boring. You don't scare anyone. Stop it,
man. You've said this a million times before.
Like you're [ __ ] boring,
lad. Why did I hang up the phone? Who
hung up the
phone? Cuz um I basically had an
argument with the police officer, so I
had to report the whole thing all over
again. That's why they come on my
door. Yeah, I was telling her like,
"What the [ __ ] man?" But there's only
one person I'm reporting on this
community. Hey, do you know another
thing, Cactus? Let me tell you about
this. Yeah, this is how you know these
people are proper losers because it's
not that they grasp and they call the
police. They have to constantly follow
it up. Like they have to constantly
harass the police and make out like
they're affected before the police even
does anything. That's how you know
they're losers. I was like, "Bro, I
can't even be asked with this, bro,
anymore." Like keeping doing this
reports and reports and reports. It's
not like you report it once and bam,
they're on your door. No, no, no. You
need to pursue it and pursue it and
pursue it. Why? Why do you think it took
6 months? I was like, [ __ ] bro. Like, I
can't even be bothered. I don't want to
[ __ ] keep going to the police every
[ __ ] week. I don't want them a part
of my life, bro. I don't even want them
on my door, to be honest. But I I had to because of
like I'm sick of them people on here
calling the police on
me. You know what I mean? No, I'm not
back gambling, but
Yeah. Yeah. They have to constantly
pursue them. So, here's the thing,
Cactus. People come on YouTube starting
beef and then they then they go running
to the police every week for two months.
Losers. [ __ ] losers, mate. They don't
even do it once or twice because I know
cuz I've had to follow up
stuff. And you have to literally [ __ ]
give them headaches and all sorts before
they even do anything. That's what I'm saying,
bro. Like, that's what I'm saying. like
they have to
actively they have to actively pursue
like the police. What a
loser. Like imagine being that much of a
loser. Like but again there's no there's
no point saying it cuz they don't care
what what they are. They don't care what
you call them. But that is that is that
is loser behavior,
bro. That is loser behavior. Like they
don't even do it once like for a bit of
entertainment. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no. They they continuously do it. Which
another reason why I'm leaving here as
well. And I'm thinking, "Oh, this [ __ ]
is all over [ __ ] YouTube, is it, mate? [ __ ]
this." PJ, do you not Do you understand
why people think it's weird to watch
Peppa Pig in the cinema
alone? Yeah, but I still like Peppa Pig, you
know? Yeah. He's going to come through
my door. Yeah, probably it wouldn't
never happen cuz a guy don't even
exist and he doesn't live anywhere near
me. Yeah, man. [ __ ]
off. You do realize when you're saying
these things, it's not scary cuz you
don't scare me one little bit.
Yeah. Oh, 9 minutes. Okay. Oh, really?
So, it's not 10 minutes now, bro. Come
on. It's boring now. I'm the last person
to try to give somebody anxiety.
Anyways, bro, I don't need to set anyone
on anyone, mate. No one is coming on my door. Anyways,
listen. Listen. Uh,
Cactus. Uh, do you like the track?
Moving on from LJ's boring [ __ ]
Do you know what, LJ? You've actually
got autism. You do realize that you you
you actually have
autism. You don't process things. No,
no, no, no. But you actually do have
autism. Nah, you definitely are you are
disabled. Like, I'm not even joking. You
are actually you're act you're actually
disabled, bro. Like, I'm not even
joking. Like, you are [ __ ] you are
disabled, bro. Like you're you're not
much different than Timmy, but you just
can spell a bit more. You're actually
It's like you don't process things. Like it honestly
is. Virgin boy was right about you.
Virgin boy was right about you, mate.
Like you you literally don't process
things. Leo, you ask the same thing over
[ __ ] and over
again. Why don't you process things?
It's like you don't fully get it, you know? Oh
man. Yeah, it's bad,
eh? But yeah, the only one that said
they were they approached me and I think
they generally was. They were quite old
cuz he was giving me more attention than the black
lads behind me. So yeah, I know what to
do now. Anyways, [ __ ]
me. I know what to do, man.
I didn't get a hangover, you know. No,
obviously cuz I went to the
cinema. I had three white ramen Cokes
and the rest was beer. But I had loads
of food when I before I went to sleep. I
had a chicken ticker curry cooked for me practice.
Yeah. Yeah. It was cooked for
me in their 60s. [ __ ] that. Someone in
60s. 35 37 is the [ __ ] limit, bro.
You mad. In their 60s.
Yeah. There. Someone I'm speaking to,
they live near Blackpool. I said, "Oh, I
can come up there and we can have a baby
in it." Cuz she's a single mom in it.
So, I was like, "Oh, well, I known her
from 10 years ago." So, I said, "We can have a
baby." Oh, what a lovely sight.
What a lovely sight, mate. Oh, my little
feet. They finally got a rest now.
Cactus. Do you remember when I was
limping? [ __ ] hell, bro. I was
limping, mate. [ __ ]
limping. People thought I was a
spacker. Had the foot in it. That was
weird, bro. Nah, that was weird, bro.
What the [ __ ]
What the [ __ ] bro? That was weird,
eh? Waking up 4 in the morning, your
foot is [ __ ] throbbing. Your your
foot is waking you up. Your foot of all [ __ ] things,
bro. It's gone
now, mate. I was limping wherever I was
going. I had to limp to go on that
[ __ ] date, bro. I couldn't walk
properly in it. Yeah, my feet was going
to take me to Blackpool last week. You
just never know with me. I could end up
in Manchester. Could end up in Wales.
You never know. You never
know. But I'm not a fan of tracksuits.
It's either the the bottoms with the
jeans or the t-shirt with the bottoms.
But if I'm getting this much attention,
then I'm not going to [ __ ] moan, you
know? [ __ ] it. And to be fair, they are comfortable.
Huh? Yeah. What would a certain person
do if they knew I was about to meet a woman cactus?
Huh? What do you think they would do? [Music]
What should I eat today? I think I am
losing the weight kind of now a little
bit. Well, I done a lot of walking, didn't I?
So, obviously I didn't walk for a month
as I was just eating cookie dough. Uh,
what can I eat? KS. I shouldn't really
be eating that. Um [Music]
um she was she's asking me questions,
bro. Yeah, she's
uh she's asking me questions. But what
if she said, "I'll get with you, but you have to
convert." Nah, that means no more
piggies. No, if I was
like I think the only thing you would
struggle with is the drinking.
No, you can live without [ __ ] pork.
No, no, no, no, no. It No, because you'd
only be able to eat things that are
halal. And trust me, it makes it
difficult. If you can only eat halal
things, it makes life very, very
difficult. I have Muslim friends and we
have to go to like um certain places, it
makes life hard. And in certain uh
that's the thing that I think is the
most I think is that you can only eat halal
things. And yeah, you I mean there's ways around
it, you know, but no, [ __ ] that,
bro. But she seems all right.
We need to get to scrap before them fish
head [ __ ] I said to her I went cinema
but obviously I didn't tell her I watch Peppa
Pig trainers. Uh one
sec. I need to start earning money soon
bro with this thing cuz I'm spending and
I'm not [ __ ] I wish this [ __ ] in
America called my bluff. Bro, I would
have went there this week and bad her
up. I swear down I would have I would
have I would have made RJ proud. Okay,
you want to see the gone bag? Yeah. Okay,
Daz. Yeah, this Escort man was the way
she sucked my [ __ ] dick, man. Was
madness. Wait, where's the camera? Oh,
here. She was choking on that, bro.
Okay. You want to see the gums again?
Yeah. Oh, these trainers. It took me
ages to find a pair I liked.
But yeah, we spent some dough
today. Yeah, I got some wipes as
well. I'll be needing this soon anyways
if I'm meeting this wooden again.
I need the gums. What the [ __ ]
Yeah, but you're you're a snake,
man. I spent about £400. Yeah,
400. Got some white socks. Got some
crepe ride wipes. You need them crep wipes, bro.
Trust me, they're
lovely. My vape the bats are [ __ ] on
him and oh, might as well treat myself,
mate. Save load of savings. So, why
not? Yeah, [ __ ]
it. Oh, that
escort. Nah, I'm skinn,
mate. I'm skin,
mate. Nah, be honest. I get about 30 grand a
month. I get about 30k a month. It's
okay, but not the best.
No, I'm joking. I wish I wish I got 30k
a month. I get I get three grand a
month, but um I need to start making
money soon. So
£700 a [ __ ] month, mate. I was
getting that when I
was [ __ ] 21, 22, man. And I was
living with my [ __ ] mom and it was
[ __ ] then as well. Yeah, £700 a month is
[ __ ] Um, I remember earning that,
getting that the money would just go
away, bro. I remember having to gamble
and it was [ __ ]
bro. It was [ __ ] Try
more. No, I don't get 30 grand. I [ __ ]
wish. No, not 30k, mate.
Oh, I'm going to be tempted to go back
to the [ __ ] escort again, bro. I bet
I I bet she sucks dick more than any
better [ __ ] than any other [ __ ] woman would.
Yeah. Yeah. 300 power a month be [ __ ]
Even 700 pound a month is [ __ ] Brazilian.
Brazilian. But I almost choked her in my dick,
bro. Yeah, Brazilian. They're easier to get as
well. I said to her, "Yeah, next time."
This what I said to her. Yeah. Colombian
Brazilian. Yeah. I said, "Next time I
think we'll have sex so you can get some
pleasure, too." Cuz they don't. They
think, "Oh, do you want sex and that?"
cuz you know they get money and they're
getting sex. So, but when they're just
sucking dick, they're not getting no
pleasure out of it, is it?
Yeah, I'm definitely keeping that one.
100% mate. [ __ ] hell.
Nah, bro. She's so dick good,
man. [ __ ] it.
Yeah. What's with me and [ __ ] I
need to start having sex
again. Yeah. Colombian Brazilians. Yeah,
they're all the same. They're They're
easier to get. Even people that aren't
escorts. The West is just dead. It's
just [ __ ] in this country. Dating
anywhere that's westernized, America, they're all
[ __ ] So, I'm
saying I was thinking, bro, when she
gave me that [ __ ] I was like, "Fuck,
why am I even going out and wasting time
and money when I can just get a woman
that can just do that for [ __ ] next to nothing?
Like, do you know what I'm
saying? You know what I mean, bro? Like,
you might as well just keep [ __ ]
going to her once you find a good one,
bro. Like, that's You might as well just do
that. Oh, that one's back soon as well.
The the Chinese one. She looks She licks
my ass. You might as well just stick to
escorts, bro. You might as well just
stick to [ __ ] prostitutes.
Honestly, I think it's the best way,
bro. I actually think it's the best
way. Yeah, I remember one month I spent
about £500 on them and back when I had
old J, I used to always call into my
room. I've done it lots of times, but
you'll never regret having too much
[ __ ] [ __ ] on your deathbed. Remember
that. You will never regret having too
much [ __ ] on your
deathbed, you know? Never. Never. So,
yeah, I've done it [ __ ] It's got to
be like a 100 times. It's got to
be It's got to
be about 100
times. Yeah, it's got to be 100 times I've done
it. But yeah, just get one to give you a
[ __ ] There's no there's no there's
nothing wrong with that. Just a [ __ ] you
know. But the best [ __ ] I had gripped
on was from an American in the
alleyway. Just kept coming onto me, onto
me, onto me, onto me. And
uh yeah, she says she's going to be at
this place. I'm not meeting her today. I
can't be bothered by
her. Let's see if she reaches out and is
telling me to come. She's replying back
and that, you know, but yeah. So,
um yeah, it was some American in the
alleyway, bro. Oh my [ __ ] god.
My whole body went [ __ ]
numb. Literally, it literally all went [ __ ]
numb. It's a
madness. It was good, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
Yeah. Charlie, how are you, bro? I
always pick you up, man.
Yeah. Charlie, do you know what? Yeah. I
always pick you up, bro. I say that
everyone on here is a snake, but you. I
actually, bro, like I always talk good
about you, Charlie, man. Even though
we've met like briefly and that, man,
but we still met and [ __ ] It's just a
shame you was on a [ __ ] detox when we did
meet. Yeah, you're Bro, I think like
you're the only one on here that's
actually not a snake,
bro. Literally, bro, I feel like you're
the only one that ain't a snake. Monty's
a snake. some accounts on here. They'll
talk [ __ ] behind your back. Like, yeah, you're cool,
man. We need to meet again, bro. I'll
come to Nottingham at some point, bro.
We'll definitely meet
again. We need to meet again, bro. 100%.
Sorry. Last time, bro, I was with a
woman, so I couldn't meet you. I was in
a hotel, but not even ain't that far.
Anyways, bro, we'll go casino and that
in it. Um, I was with this woman in a
hotel. So, I literally couldn't even
come to you, bro, cuz I was in a hotel
and the first night I was with Ant-Man.
So, so I couldn't obviously leave him.
So, but next time I come by myself, bro. Maybe two
weeks. We were on a proper session,
bro. But I feel like I'm a bit too old
for Nottingham Charlie, bro.
Yeah, but there's a pri Yeah, but
Charlie, there's a I'm banned as well,
but there's a private casino. It's
called Aloe. It's a private casino, and
they don't uh check your [ __ ] and that.
So, but yeah, I feel like I'm a bit too
old for Nottingham, bro. Cuz Rock City
is my favorite
club. Always used to get [ __ ] there,
but now they will know like you're 27,
bro. I mean, like, um, is it Elio? Which
one is it? I don't know what is some of
that. Yeah, it's a private casino.
There's one in Scotland,
too. But [ __ ] gambling, bro. We don't
need gambling anyways, bro. We'll just
go out on a session.
Uh yeah, not too Well, I don't think
it's that far
cuz you know, it's only the Midlands, but
uh you have to go certain places, bro,
cuz like I said, I'm a bit old.
Yeah, it's a private
casino. When I went with
Ant-Man, when I went with Ant-Man,
bro. Um, when I went with Ant-Man, they
let me in, but when I tried taking the
money out, they were being [ __ ] They
paid in the end. I think it was only £350 from
100. But maybe it's different now.
Maybe. Who knows? But we could probably
find a we Yeah.
Yeah. No, I don't know what it is,
bro. Yeah, maybe I'll come up in two
weeks or something. Maybe next month. Whatever,
bro. Chill, bro.
Yeah, be fun, man. We'll have a nice piss
up. But yeah, I do like Rock City, but I
got a feeling I'm a bit too old to
[ __ ] go in there
now. Yeah, I got a [ __ ] last time I went to
Nottingham. Couldn't [ __ ] though cuz she
was on her
period. Yeah, it was fun,
bro. The Rock City is [ __ ] a banger
though, bro. So easy to get women there.
money works as well. See, with London, I
don't know what the [ __ ] happened
yesterday. I got lucky. But London,
they're all like stuck up and they've
all got money and that. Whereas
Nottingham, there's a lot of people that
don't. There's obviously people have
money there, but there's obviously a lot
of people that don't have money there.
So, it's not like London. Like, you
could go to Rock City, brother, and
you'll get approached. It ain't
happening in [ __ ] London, mate.
Like and again there's people under
there ain't that got no money but yeah
it's less well let's just well it's cuz
it's less competition Nottingham so it's
competition so they can't be picky when
there's less competition can
they some sort of difference
bro some sort of
difference but we can still go to like
mojo and [ __ ]
Anyways, I'm going. Yeah, I'll be back
later for sure, bro. In a visual.