I'm done after today, bro. I'm done with YouTube after
today. It's [ __ ]
Oh yeah, I'm done with YouTube after today, bro.
100. Yeah, it's [ __ ] boring, bro.
It's [ __ ] [ __ ] is it? Yes,
community. Uh, I'm busy all day tomorrow as
well. This woman wanted to meet today. I couldn't be bothered.
Yeah. Yeah, bro. [ __ ]
hell. Yeah, this community is weird,
Brit Bong. It's just a bunch of [ __ ]
middle-aged self projectors, man. It's
proper weird, man. Like, you see how
they act when you go out for a
drink. It was good. It was a It was a
movie. That just goes to show how they
ain't got a life, bro. How Why do they
react like that when just normal people
going out for a [ __ ]
drink? We should enjoy the summer, bro.
This is [ __ ] bro. What the [ __ ]
Let them have their shitty YouTube, man.
[ __ ] sat on YouTube every day and got
a life, bro.
[ __ ] Do you like my little gums, Brit
Bong? I hope you like him,
bro. One second.
Yeah, I'm a bacon. [ __ ]
off. Bacon. I've never heard that word
in my life. I didn't even know that that
I didn't even know that. [ __ ]
That even meant
nons. Is it worth? Nah, it's
not. It's not.
No. You like the tracksuit? Yeah.
Yeah. Not worth seeing,
bro. That [ __ ] [ __ ] I got
yesterday was [ __ ] amazing.
Oh my [ __ ]
god. I could just start I could just I
could just keep me in this escort. It
just makes more so much sense just to
keep It's just a It's just Peppa Pig
meeting the baby. I'm so tired, man.
It's just Peppa Pig seeing the baby,
bro. £80, but I get I got to come in her
mouth about what £80 a week. You might
as well just do that, bro. Just pay £80
a [ __ ] week and then just
leave. Like, it makes sense. You got a
perfect person now, you know? Like, I
didn't get I got a boyfriend yesterday
and that, but that was rare. Like,
tomorrow I'm going out tomorrow. You're
going to get
it. Yeah, you're not going to get that
anyways in this day and
age. Yeah, she did. Yeah, but you're not
going to get that anyways in this day and
age. a [ __ ] housewife and and
uh yeah, you're not going to get that in
this day and age, mate. So, you [ __ ]
get what you [ __ ]
can and you can make an escort that if
you gave her enough
money. Yeah, but it's just easier. You
You might as well just do that, bro.
Really? I think that's good. I think
like I think that's good,
mate. I think that's a good uh thing. I
got some numbers reply
back. Uh believe it or not, Brit Bong, I
actually don't, mate. Women have got unrealistic
standards. Trust me, you actually
don't. You really don't. It doesn't
really matter how you look like. Trust
me, it's England's hard to find people.
I should be meeting this woman tomorrow,
but this is a oneoff. It's hard as
[ __ ] because yeah, I didn't get I got
boyfriends yesterday, but I've got a
number that's no longer replying. Maybe
she's asleep. Who knows? But I I The
thing is I just said this to Ant-Man.
Yeah. I just said that to Ant-Man,
right? I just said that to Ant I just
said this to Ant-Man. Yeah. like you're
like you shouldn't expect anything but
at the same time it's hypocritical cuz
really you should expect something with
the effort that you're putting in you
should be expecting something that's
like saying you go to the gym right go
to the gym and then you shouldn't expect
anything obviously no you should expect
something because you're obviously
putting effort into it so to put effort
into something and then not expect
anything back it doesn't make any sense
like anyone would expect anything back
so that Doesn't even make sense even
saying that. So, Peppa Pig was all right.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm always confident,
mate. Not certain
days, but um cuz you need like effort
and sometimes you got to force yourself
to do it. And so really with the effort
that people put in, they should be expecting
something. They should be It's not about
whether someone owes you or anything.
No, no, you should be expecting something.
Um, why wouldn't you? If you put effort in, you
know, cuz they might, this one might not
reply back. The Muslim one will meet me,
but the other one might not ever reply
back. And this is what dating is like in
this country. This is what I'm saying.
This is the [ __ ] you got to deal with.
So, I think it's just easier just using escorts, man.
No, I'm still confident. No, I'm still
confident. I'm just being real. You got
to be real at the same
time. No, it's it's just talking facts.
It agrees. It's just talking facts. I'll
be out again tomorrow. Yeah, but it's
not about I'm being confident, but I'm
real. You need to be real at the same
time. Do you know what I'm saying,
Grezy? I know deep down this country is
a waste of [ __ ] time. Even if I get
to Even if I get to meet someone. But I was
bored. You know, it's what it is, man.
It's England for you. England's hard to find
someone. No world of repeating down
there. No, I'm not repeating. No, I'm
not repeating at
all. No, I'm not repeating at all,
man. Yeah. Guess what? And women in this
day and age won't give you love either.
They will only want your money. just
escorts are honest about
it. But it doesn't matter anyways, bro.
We shouldn't be talking about this,
bro. Nah, they're virgins, mate. They're
[ __ ] virgins. They are. Timmy, bomb
[ __ ] Timmy. They're [ __ ] virgins,
mate. They're [ __ ] virgins, bro. [ __ ]
me. They're They're worse than
anyone. They're [ __ ] worse than
anyone, mate. [ __ ]
me. [ __ ] They're [ __ ] stinking,
man. They're [ __ ] virgins as
well. Yeah, I got some weird looks today
at the cinema. Greavves. I think people
thought I was a pedophile or something. Yep.
There was loads of Stits fans about
Grezy. I might play The Simpsons and run
on this projector. I've got a projector in this
room. Yeah, got a projector in this room,
lad. Could play on the big [Music]
screen. You know what, Grezy? There's a
new it coming out. And I said to my mom,
"No, there can't be." He was defeated in 1990. in
1990. Why are they Why is he
back? No, they can't be right. Grezy, he
was defeated in 1990. I remember
watching it. Not Not in 1990, but that's
when it was made. No, no, them kids defeated
him. There's no way he's back, you know. It's
back. There's no
way. Griezy, how how is that possible?
We they they killed
him and he keeps coming
back. Yeah. There's a new it coming
out. Good old it, man. Good old it. Eh,
I got some approaches to put on my main
channel. Yeah, they're completely sober as well,
Guzzy. They're completely sober approaches.
before I started drinking. I'm
knackered. I am
greasy. Long day,
eh? Yep. So did
I. But no, that [ __ ] I got from that
escort, mate. [ __ ]
hell. It was a good day yesterday. All in
all, no I've got a boyfriend and all
that [ __ ] It was good in
it. And the one that said she was
married still kissed me.
So there you go. And that's why I bought
tracksuit. That's why I bought a [ __ ]
trackuit. Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Yeah. Oh, do you know what she said?
Greasy. She said she almost choked to
death. It made me think of you. Women
are put on earth to satisfy Peter Belly's
needs. She said, "I almost choked to
death." It was funny.
Yeah, I was hot,
bro. That was
hot. I should have recorded it. Greasy.
Oh, do you like my little clothes,
Greasy? I think they're quite nice.
Me. Nice bit of clobber to go approaching
him. I'm so tired, bro. What the
[ __ ] I got sleep.
You're not If you're not a fan of
tracksuit and jeans, what do you wear?
Just shorts. Not a fan of it, bro. But
it stops me hearing I've got a
boyfriend. It stops me hearing I've got
a boyfriend, mate. So I don't mind
spending [ __ ] a couple hundred pound
if we mean stop hearing that [ __ ]
[ __ ] which I think is a good investment.
Yeah. So if you don't wear tracksuits
and you don't wear jeans, what the [ __ ]
do you wear? Shorts.
button up shirts. So, you don't wear t-shirts?
Yeah, bro. I don't really wear
tracksuits, but yeah, if it's going to
stop me here and I've got a boyfriend,
then I've got I'm wearing some nice
stuff tomorrow. Uh, greavves. I'm going
to wear some nice cargo shorts and a
nice Reese top, the sip restop. So, I'll
be looking smart tomorrow. Then it's
back to being a [ __ ] on Thursday. Yeah.
Yeah. You don't wear t-shirts. I like
t-shirts and basketball
shorts. Basketball shorts are the one,
bro. basketball shorts. [ __ ] Len,
bro. No, I've heard loads of stories
about it, but I've never
been. I know people that have. Yeah, I
know about it, but I've just never been. Yeah. Yeah, I've
heard. She said I almost choked to death. [ __ ]
hell. I finally found somebody that can
give really good
[ __ ] Jesus Christ. I want to kind
of go back there
now. Remember, you're never going to
regret getting too much [ __ ] on your deathbed.
Always remember that. You'll never
you'll never regret that on your deathbed,
mate. Oh, I told you I was going to see
Peppa Pig Greensy. Just like I told you
I was going to go to America [ __ ]
this week if the [ __ ] [ __ ] call my blood.
Yeah, [ __ ] pair of
[ __ ] That's what her and her dad is.
We pair of [ __ ] Oh, [ __ ]
me. Oh, I'm in an estic.
Squeezy. No, I've only ever shagged one
and it was a Somalian.
Yeah. What about me? Uh, it's got to be
a horror film called Weapon.
The cinema was packed today, Grezy. It
was packed. And it's all because of that
Stitch. It's him, bro. That he is.
That's why the cinema is so
packed. It's cuz of [ __ ]
Stitch. I'm telling you, bro. Yeah,
there was people watching Peppa Pig, but
it was mostly obviously Stitch. Is it [ __ ] Stitch?
Yeah. No, I've only had one morning before. That's
it. It's cute, isn't it,
Grezy? Yeah. But what about the it
clown? How was he back? He got defeated.
Do you know what makes me laugh with
that it clown?
Grezy, you will like it down here, son.
You'll never have to grow up. Uh, oh,
bro, that kills me. Do you remember that
bit where he pretends to be the guy's
dead dad and he said, "You'll like it
down here. You'll never have to grow
up." And And then he starts
laughing. [ __ ] hell. I was thinking
about that earlier,
mate. Oh, do you know what they should?
They need to make another
ring. They need to make another ring.
Greasy, they need to make a a new ring.
Defo, you'll never have to grow
up. But we they he killed him in 1990.
Why is he
back? It's like Chucky. They'd kill him,
but he keeps coming
back. Nope. I'm not saying where I went.
I'm not saying which one I
went. He got
stalkered. But yeah, that took balls
today going to watch Peppa
Pig. Trust me, it [ __ ] did, mate. Yeah.
No, you have too many [ __ ] stalkers
on there, bro. Not saying it. Saying
it. This Muslim woman likes um horror films, too. So,
yeah. You'll never have to grow
up. You'll like it down here, son.
You'll never have to grow
up. No. No. Oh, I didn't get thrown out of any
uh I [ __ ] am, mate. Cuz I only like
[ __ ] cuz [ __ ] feel better than
sex. Nah, mate. [ __ ] are better than sex. Trust
me, they are better than
sex. Trust me, they are better than sex.
You must have had a good [ __ ] mate.
They're better than
six. No, trust me. You don't have a
[ __ ] fetish. That's why you're saying
that. Just cuz you don't have a [ __ ]
fetish doesn't mean I
don't. Where's my mama,
cactus? Where's my mama?
Yeah, you have to wear a condom with
sex. You literally have to. They won't
[ __ ] you without So I just get a [ __ ]
without a condom. It's good enough for me.
Yeah. Where's my mama
cactus? Sig's not Peter Belly's mama.
He said, "Do you remember Sig's not
Peter Belly's mama?" Oh, do you remember that?
Um, Sig's not Peter Bell's mama.
No, you'll never have to grow
up. [ __ ] hell.
But this is my last live stream, bro,
for a long time
cuz I can't be bothered, man. When I
went out yesterday, these people were
just hating and
[ __ ] Same spastics every day. Remember,
cactus, it's the same spastics every
day. They got a
life. They want to look in the [ __ ] mirror, mate.
Honestly, that's what they need to do. Yeah.
If you don't find chevel co attractive, you're
gay. Nah, that's just copying,
mate. That's copying. You go on any any
sort of forum,
uh, Cactus, you will see that anywhere,
bro. Yeah, that's just copying,
bro. That's what copycats
say. People that copy each other. No originality
whatsoever. Yeah, that's copy
him. She's nowhere near as attractive as
people make out. Nowhere near. It's the
[ __ ] name, mate. It's the [ __ ] name. [ __ ] copycat, in it. Copying.
Copying. Ain't it Cactus? Just copying,
lad. [ __ ] is bang average. Yeah.
Oh, I'd have to find a new mama,
cactus. I have to find a new mama. [Music] Yeah. I'm sorry. Oh, bro.
Where is it? What? Yeah. Heat.
I think Figgy watches my YouTube as
well. I'm deleting my
videos. Delete. Delete. [Music]
I know it's you. I'm not even getting [ __ ] you. [Laughter]
Yeah, one thing is
I love that, dude. I love
that. [ __ ] I swear to God, I'm going to
[ __ ] you. Goosy really [Laughter]
hot. I find out that it's you watch. [Laughter] [Music]
Crazy. My friend said, "Yeah, somebody
was [ __ ] with my fridge." My fridge.
My friend said if we we if we find out
who it is, we're going to [ __ ]
him. He says, "I'm not gay." Yeah. But
he says we're going to [ __ ] him. Yeah.
He says if they find out what
[ __ ] is doing it, they're going
to [ __ ] Yeah.
I think he means [ __ ] them up, not
[ __ ] [ __ ] them. Do you know what I
mean? [ __ ] hell, bro. Oh, I'm dead. I'm [ __ ]
dead. I'm so [ __ ] dead.
If I find out you've been talking [ __ ]
behind my back grooms, I'm going to [ __ ]
you. I'm going to come all the way out
up north. I'm going to [ __ ] you hard. I
swear down. Yeah, I'm not even gay, but
still [ __ ] it in it. Yeah, I'm [ __ ] you off. [Laughter]
I'm always laughing, aren't I? Greasy,
you never watch Cliffing the Big Red
Wiff. The Big Red
Whiffter. He's cute, isn't he?
Easy. He's cute.
Eh, crazy. You can never forget this,
can you? Look how cute this
is. Oh my god.
Crazy. Look how cute that is. Oh, Tom and little
cracker. Oh, Tom and little cracker. Little Oh, so
cute. That is so cute. Isn't it
greasy? That's so [ __ ]
cute. So cute.
Oh, that's my mama. He
said that's so cute.
Yeah. What other cartoon do you like, Grezy?
Uh yeah. Oh, that is so funny. Tom
laughing, bro. [ __ ]
me. Do you ever remember code name kids
next door? Greasy.
Really? Oh, Greasy. Bless you. Me and
you are still kids in a way, aren't we?
Yeah. I ain't got autism, mate. Not
me. I don't have autism, buddy.
Virgin boy does, but not
me. Virgin boy does, but not me. Greasy. All right, sir.
Yeah, had Chinese today, Grezy. But now
I'm getting McDonald's
cravings. I'm getting a cravings for McDonald's.
I spent £11 today on food.
Bad. Now I want a McDonald's. [ __ ]
you. [ __ ] your McDonald's, man.
I'm going to go in a minute.
Greasy. McDonald's or no McDonald's?
McDonald's are not
crazy. I'm not
crazy. He's a cool
[ __ ] I tell you what's lush though, the
[ __ ] KFC burgers, Greasy. They are
lush. I'm going to have a Ben & Jerry's
today. I was going to get a Ben &
Jerry's today, bro. But [ __ ] I need
to stay away from that [ __ ] bro, cuz
it'll make me fat. Like, just you got to
[ __ ] around with that, bro. Trust me.
Once a week maximum I can have it
now. Yeah. McDonald's
nuggets. So even if I spend £25 today on
food altogether, it's okay, isn't it,
Grezy? So what? That's okay.
Yeah. What's the most you've spent on
food in a day, Grezy?
What's the most you've spent?
Yeah, I've spent about 14 a day
before. Yeah. Have you ever got take away twice?
live a [ __ ] one.
Yeah. Would you rather a [ __ ] grieves
your 20 chicken nuggets?
What would you prefer? [ __ ] or chicken nuggets. Huh? Really?
I'm going to order some nuggets, bro.
You're a bad influence. I'm going to I'm
going to get really
fat. I'm going to get really fat,
bro. Oh, by the way, guess who uh emailed me?
Jane. [ __ ] off. Let's go
back. Let's come back,
mate. I'm going to order some
nuggets. Oh, by the way, Grezy, you need
a Mc spicy burger.
You know what? It goes up and up and up
every time I see,
bro. Every time I see this goes up and
up and up and up and up.
But KFC is better than McDonald's in it,
Greasy. But the thing is with KFC, you
have to go in and pick your pieces. So
you can't even order it cuz it tastes like [ __ ]
just ordering it
now. Get a free
McFlurry. I get a free cheeseburger or a
free Biscoff McFlurry.
Um, oh, do you know what? I used to take
King to McDonald's every day, Greasy,
and I used to give him a burger. He used
to wait so patiently.
Um, I guess I'll just get a
cheeseburger. Customize it cuz I don't
want the other [ __ ] on the burger.
No, I'm not going to use it cuz it's not
letting me customize the
burger. I'll just go for the nuggets. I
can I can't be bothered, bro.
No, I can't be bothered.
Actually, I fancy some nuggets. I can't be
bothered. I can't believe you love
King. No, I don't need to [ __ ] on the takeaways,
bro. I'm exercising and [ __ ] I'm good,
bro. I'm all good. Plenty chicken
nuggets. I'll probably walk about three miles
tomorrow. But you need to stop this uh
comfy eating greasy lad. You'll end up
like the bomb, mate. Fat and ugly. Like
most of the people on
here. Fat and ugly, mate. You know your
metabolism slows down. Well, I was
getting weight because I didn't go out
for a month because on the foot and that
I wasn't able to walk, so
obviously all the ice cream and
that and I have people cook me food and
[ __ ] you know. I had a banging chicken
curry yesterday, but when I come back,
oh my god, it was so nice. I didn't even
get a hangover the next
day. I didn't even get a hangover.
That's how nice the food was, but it was mad.
Okay. No, I need to
start. No, I'm going to start the gyms. All right. One second.
McDonald's. Yeah. Coming
now. [ __ ] 12 quid.
124. It's amazing how much money you
save when you don't really damn bloody well in
it. It's amazing how much money you
save. You never know when you fall in
BS. You never know when you're falling
balls deep. Greasy, let's have a look.
Uh, I'm off of YouTube from uh from
after this, bro. I have some stuff to do
in my life,
so I can't be on here [ __ ]
entertaining weirdos. You
see, you know what I'm saying,
boss. I shouldn't even be on here after
all this [ __ ] that's happened as well,
but I was thinking about this earlier. You
know, I don't even gaming videos anymore.
Yeah, I swear if I find out who's done
this, I'm going to [ __ ] them. I
swear I'll [ __ ] them all but once. Yeah. Yeah.
[ __ ] right down.
Yeah. Come on. How long have Nuggets? 17
minutes. Yeah. 17
minutes. Lovely jobly.
Yeah, he doesn't care about
women. He doesn't care about women, does he? Nah.
I think I'm becoming obsessed again,
bro. I'm not going to
lie. I think I'm
obsessed. I think they all need to bow
down to my needs.
Weezy. Oh, now it's come back. Now it's
come to 21 minutes. Yeah. [ __ ]
sake. USA got a Tesco value version of me. Greasy.
Yeah. You need a goal in life, Greavesy.
You need a goal, bro. I I have a goal in
my life. This is why I'm quitting
YouTube. I'm [ __ ] 27, bro. I don't
want to get to 30 and look back at that,
bro. That's why I need to come off this [ __ ]
Lad, why don't you go and get
laid? You're probably still a
virgin. Yeah, you're still a
virgin. Yeah, Greavves. Anyways, you
should listen to what I'm saying to you,
bro. You don't want to end up like these
people. It's a serious thing I'm telling
you, mate. And I know I've just ordered
20 nuggets, but like I said, this that
might end up like you in 10 years. Bitter, fat,
ugly, no money. All right, that's
plastic. Like, you don't you don't want
to end up like these spackers,
Grezy. You know, I'm saying this stuff
cuz I care about
you. You know what I'm saying, bro?
You know, come down to London sometime.
Me, you, and King can go for a walk,
Greasy. You know, get off of
YouTube. You don't want to be like these
people, Grezy. No life but YouTube. Did
I? Come on, Grezy. Speak to me
here. I'm trying to help you.
I miss King, you
know. Thinking of King. I miss that little
whiff how he used to come up
and check if I was okay. Greavvesy.
Yeah. Used to come every morning.
Grezy scratching the little door with his little
claws. Yeah. So cute. [Music]
Right now it's gone back to 22 minutes.
Grezy, what the [ __ ] is going on with these [ __ ]
nuggets? What's going on with these
hunting nuggets, man? Come
back. I want King
back. I see loads of Frenchies out and
about and they look like King. You've
always love King, ain't it,
Greasy? Yeah, King's cute.
Yeah, ballistic bringing everyone to the
cinema. That's cute, isn't it?
Ah, you like the one I said about the
Simpsons though, is it? HTON J. Simpson,
don't make me call you by your full
name. Sit down and be good and leave
Bart Simpson alone. Done nothing to
you. Hamilton J.
Simpson. Oh, that made me laugh, but I
think it was
funny. I'm watching J
Simpson. You watch Family Guy,
Grezy? You watch Family Guy, don't you,
Yeah. Someone said to the guy that made
Family Guy, "Do did you make The
Simpsons?" He was like, "I [ __ ]
wish." He obviously said that because of
the money, in
it. Yeah. He He obviously said he's
saying that because of the money in it. Honestly, uh,
obviously I think it's genius how they
make cartoons. Greasy, what's your
opinion? Like Peppa Pig. I think that's
good how they made Peppa Pig. Where do
they even think of these things, man? Crazy. Crazy. Yeah.
I'm going to [ __ ] them hard.
Yeah, that's what I was going to do to
[ __ ] Morgan and her dad. I was going
to [ __ ] them
hard. I'll [ __ ] [ __ ] them hard. I'm I'm
not gay. Yeah. I'm not gay, but I'll
[ __ ] them hard. Trust
me. 13 minutes. Yay. 13 minutes.
I will [ __ ] them
hard. I am gay, bro. I'm
still That's so
funny. Why is it taking so long for these nuggets?
Greasy. Who's bringing them? Ronald McDonald.
Oh, [ __ ] you. Yeah. Heat.
10 minutes now. Grezy
9 minutes. Greasy, you still there, boss?
Yep. It's coming. 9
minutes. I used to love these nuggets
when I was a child as well. Greasy.
Yeah. Timmy gets 700 pound a month. Gregsy like you. Yeah.
You can adjust to that amount, but
[ __ ] £300 a
month. I spent [ __ ] god knows how
much today. Barely gets £300 a month.
Greasy. £300 a
month. That is
mad. That is crazy.
300 pound a [ __ ] month. Clem Imagine
that. Funny enough though, you probably
can still live off that a
month as hard as it might be.
You never worry about money, do you,
Grebsy? You're just a happy golucky chap.
6 minutes. Yay. Come on,
chicken. Check it out again.
Yay. Take it away,
Elf. Do you remember that,
Grezy? Grey, do you remember that? Take
it away, elf.
3 minutes. 3 minutes. 3 minutes.
Right. It's here. Right. We are back.
Oh, I got the nuggets. I got the
nuggets. Oh, they're tasty. M. [Music]
M imagine that grooy there I'm in court
and you come to the court
hearing and it's all over the same
website you can watch Stitch
on the same website you can you can
watch Stitch on and
Scooby how [ __ ] isn't that
cool like you can lose your
and your kids on the same website you
can watch Stitch on. Isn't that cool? [Music]
That better not be [ __ ]
dam. Isn't that
cool? Kind of tastes like diet coke to me.
Really? Do you remember the
tweenies? You remember the tweenies?
You might not remember that.
Yeah, I used to sit in front of the TV
all day watching Spongebob here.
Just all day I used to watch Spongebob on the
Colonium. It was lush,
mate. I love Spongebob,
bro. If they if they put a new Sponge
out, I'd watch it. [Music] was I
Spongebob. Do you remember Grezy the
Spongebob? Yeah. When Squidward, he
tried to he tried to go to a new home.
Yeah. To get away from Bob to get away
from um [ __ ] Spongebob and [ __ ]
Patrick. Yeah. And [ __ ] um They
followed him. They found him. He went to like a
[ __ ] He went to a squid home. Yeah.
He went to a [ __ ] squid home thinking
he was going to get away from Spongebob
to get a bit of peace, but they found
him. You remember that one? If you ever watch
Spongebob, I don't know if you remember that one. Remember
You never watch [Music]
Spongebob. You never watch him, did you? Trust me,
bro. Don't underestimate Peppa Pig. It's
got to become famous,
bro. It's already worldwide.
I think they done good for an English
cartoon since most of them are American
and nothing good comes from England. But
I think with Peppa Pig, yeah, you have
to give credit when credit is due. It's
English and it's pretty well known.
Would you agree, Grezy? You go on
YouTube, it's got about 22 [ __ ] million
views. It's uh quite popular. See, when
I was younger, there was no Peppa Pig.
It come out in 2004.
But I weren't aware of it back then. It
was [ __ ] Spongebob and [ __ ] Now
people don't know about less people know
about Spongebob and Looney Tunes now
because it doesn't come on the TV
because the TV subscriptions are the TV
subscriptions are so expensive.
Greasy. So that's why they know about
like Peppa Pig and [ __ ] because it comes
on Nickelodeon and obviously unless you
got a TV subscription. The only way kids
nowadays know about Spongebob and [ __ ] is through
YouTube cuz obviously how expensive is
to get a TV sub.
So that's how
um I didn't know about Peppa Pig when I was
younger. I didn't know about Peppa Pig.
That come out 2004, but I never knew
about it until my [ __ ] um niece kept
going on about it. You right, Cory? Yeah, very
skin. Having some chicken nuggets.
Nah, bro. He never came back.
Nut. Still about, bro. Still about. Sure
about do you remember Isabelle Richie? M
remember Isabelle Grezy me and Isabelle
holding hands and kissing and
stuff. USA is a m as
well. He's a proper
m. Look at me call me. I get all the ladies.
I got all the
ladies. I saw an old photo or
anything. Yeah. The chips in it. She
like, "Can I have some chips?" I said,
"No, Isabelle. I'm not buying you any
more drinks or anyone or anyone
chips." "No, Isabelle." I put I put my
foot down. I said, "No,
Isabelle." You know, and then she threw a tantrum.
music. Yeah. She she then threw a
[ __ ] tantrum. This Coke is dodgy,
man. It tastes like [ __ ] Diet Coke,
Grezy. It's [ __ ] stinking,
man. Can't stand. I think I might have
some Coke downstairs. Do I? That is dodgy,
man. You can taste the difference as
well. It tastes like [ __ ] I'm normal
Coke and It tastes like [ __ ] diet
coke. Tastes like [ __ ] diet
[ __ ] I can't be bothered to go
downstairs, but I'm going to Oh,
lovely. Got some proper folk now.
Oh, yeah. I got some proper folk now, lad. [ __ ] hell.
I got three nuggets left. Four nuggets
left and I'm [ __ ] stuffed. Greasy,
you're trying to get me
fat. I know what your game is. You're
trying to get me fat, boozy. Yeah.
Whoa. I'm stuffed, mama. One second,
bro. Yeah, I've got two nuggets
left. So, did Monty lose his kids over YouTube?
Oh, that's madness,
bro. How can you lose your kids over the same
website used to watch [ __ ] That's
mad. That's [ __ ] mad. Yeah, but I
almost got killed.
If I was in that day, London Taylor
come, I might not be here
now. When I told my sister about that, I
was laughing. She said, "It's not even
funny." I like there would have been a
murder, bro. We would have actually been
a murder, mate. Like the whole house
would have like been boarded up. It's
quite scary. Yeah.
But what makes me laugh
is that Tom and Jerry will still be on
YouTube. Stitch will still be on
YouTube. All of these things will still be on
YouTube. So even when I get killed over
YouTube, they'll still be on it.
Yeah. And they'll never get off YouTube,
mate. Anyways, I need to go. Yeah. Bye.