You'll like it down here, son. You'll
never have to grow
up. You'll like it down here,
son. Oh my god. Who's doing that then? Jesus
Christ. Going for a lot of wonder, haven't [Music]
we? Through a lot of uh
thing, a lot of Wonger,
matey. I've gone through a lot of Wonger
the past [ __ ] week. Jesus Christ.
maybe a thousand I think. [ __ ] hell,
bro. Yeah. So, basically that woman is
basically saying how uh yeah, I have to
be Muslim. I'm not [ __ ] converting to
no [ __ ] Muslim. But I ain't even that
mad, bro. Like I had nothing better to do
yesterday. Just typical England for you
in it. Time wasting people. So people
making making up they got boyfriends.
Just nothing will ever change it really.
So, nothing will ever change. I don't
expect it to in this [ __ ]
country. What nice socks,
eh? I need to go get some Don't know
what to eat
today. Maybe some pork chops, maybe. Uh,
[ __ ] I gone through that kind of
[ __ ] money, bro.
Yeah. Going through quite a lot of money, mate.
Uh should still have around 2k left.
So still went through a
lot. Yeah, bro. [ __ ] the two numbers
from [ __ ] Saturday didn't reply back.
Oh [ __ ] man. When is it ever going to
end, man? Honestly, when is when is this
[ __ ] ever really going to end? I can
never see it happening,
bro. Ah, it's always going to be the
[ __ ] S here.
It always going to be just
over. I'll be out on Saturday again cuz
I didn't get my haircut done for no reason.
So, I kind of have to go out every week.
I kind of have to go out every week cuz
once you had your hair
done it last, you know, for like three
weeks. So, you can't really stay in for
3 weeks, can
you? Yeah. Went Nando yesterday, walked to the
park. But even if they said straight up,
you have to convert. I'm not converting
to Muslim cuz why would I convert in a
to a religion that I
don't believe in? So, doesn't make
sense. They're not the only woman in the
world. So, it's kind of [ __ ] up,
though. It is. It's like a catch of 22.
I was saying this to my friend
yesterday. It's like you either meet
someone that's from a third world
country and they're not [ __ ] and
they don't pretend they got boyfriends,
but obviously they won't get with you
unless you're [ __ ] Muslim. Or you get
with somebody that's westernized, even
if they've got Muslim heritage and
they're just [ __ ] and pretend they
got boyfriends. So, either way, you
can't win. And you can't get with Indian
women because they're too hard to get. So
yeah, it's [ __ ] is it? It's a [ __ ] up
um [ __ ] up world we live in, mate.
Then you're having to pay 1520 to get
into [ __ ] clubs and even do that. But
[ __ ] rinse a load of money anyways.
It's a [ __ ] life here in England, matey.
It is truly a [ __ ] life
here and it will never never change.
It will never change in this country,
matey. They're [ __ ] mad, bro. Mad, lad. Um,
yeah. [ __ ] Let's go to the bank, get some
food. A bless you. In the West
Indies, you're nothing but a bomber clot.
You You're a bomber clot.
Yeah, I was on a date yesterday. Oh,
yeah. What I was saying to uh LG is
about the walking before you rudely hung
up. That was quite a fishish thing to
do. Is that LJ says that he walks? But
does the guy walk? Because I walked
about 10 miles yesterday. I walked all around
[ __ ] I walked all around [ __ ] um Hide
Park. Yeah, it was Hide Park. I walked
all around central London, went to
Nandos with this [ __ ] woman and it was Bro,
listen. You understand me? Yeah. That's
that's walking, bro. I don't think you
understand the definition of actually
walking. I've been walking the past three days,
bro. Nonstop. [ __ ] nonstop. I'm Wednesday. [ __ ] me.
Yeah. Yeah, man. Do you like my little
tracksuit as well,
LT? I seem to get more luck in the
tracksuit. So, I just wear the tracksuit
now to do these approaches, even though
it's baking hot outside. That was me
yesterday in Hide
Park. Yep. I went to see the little ducks.
LT, I went to see the little ducks. Yeah, man. [ __ ]
hell. Still trying to figure out what to eat today. [Music]
Um, don't know if I fancy pork
chops. Don't fancy steak. I don't fancy
red meat. Um,
bro. [ __ ] hell, man. I'm stayed up,
bro. I'm still quite tired. I'm still
[ __ ] tired from the past three days.
Tired of these [ __ ] Tired of [ __ ]
walking. kind of [ __ ] everything.
It's so boring, bro. Honestly, it's so
boring. Life is [ __ ] bro. Same repetitive thing,
man. It's honestly the same repetitive
[ __ ] thing, bro. Every [ __ ] I go
out every week, bro, cuz there's nothing
else to do on Saturdays. And I only I
only stick to the beer now as well. I
know what you said about the thing.
Yeah. I still stick to beer, bro, cuz I
don't get the hangovers. The only time I
switch the rum is when I go to the club
and I only have about
two. Well, it makes sense. I don't get
the hangovers with the beer. So, and you
save [ __ ] tons of money as
well. Cuz if I go out on Saturdays, I spend
like450. So, why not go out on a
Saturday and spend 4050 when you've had
your haircut anyways? It just doesn't
make no sense. You might as well. I'll
be out Saturday or Friday or Saturday,
one of the two.
So yeah, if you didn't go out every
Saturday, bro, you'd have nothing to
look forward to.
Honestly, you really would have nothing
to look forward to, bro. If you didn't
go out once a
week, even when you used to be able to
do your football bets, anything like
that, bro. You can spend 70 80 pound in
a week, bro. Doesn't cost that much,
lad. Yeah, it makes your beer guts, bro. But like
it's Guinness doesn't Guinness doesn't.
So nah, water doesn't work, bro. Water
doesn't. I'll try it, but you save money
and it doesn't get you [ __ ] It
doesn't get you [ __ ] the next
day. Guinness don't give you a beer
belly, bro. I don't have a beer belly. I
drink Guinness. I've got a bit of a
belly. But yeah, cactus. This [ __ ]
woman wants me to [ __ ] convert. I'm
not [ __ ] converting to [ __ ] Muslim,
bro. Ah, [ __ ] that, bro. I've got Muslim
friends. It's a catch 22, bro. You
either meet someone that's westernized
and they're all [ __ ] right?
Pretend they got boyfriends, the same
[ __ ] that they are, right?
Um, like it doesn't matter where they're
from, India, Pakistan, if they're
westernized, they're westernized, just
the same as Americans. They're no good.
And then if you meet somebody that's
like actually from the place
um they they want you to convert. So you
either way you can't or something like
that. So you can't win. And everyone's
thinking ah so maybe Indian but Indians
won't go with you.
So so it's not going to work. No matter
what you do it ain't going to work mate.
Like trust me I've been I've been at
this [ __ ] for years bro. This the same
old. But I I weren't that pissed off
about it yesterday cuz I had nothing
better to do.
So, and I left it on good terms, but
it's well, I did have something better
to do. I was [ __ ] tired, bro. So, but
yeah, just another one to add to the
[ __ ] collection, I
guess. Just another one to add to the [ __ ] collection,
LT, you have to laugh about it.
Uh, it's like when other people complain
about the boyfriend [ __ ] It's funny
them complaining about it. It is funny,
but I don't I don't even like hearing
it. I don't like hearing it happen to
other people. It just bors me. I don't
like actually seeing it happen. It's
funny when people complain about it, but
I don't like seeing it happen to anyone.
It's boring. It's just boring, bro. You
know, it is proper boring. It
is proper proper boring, bro.
So, I just managed to get into one
club. Yeah. You chat women just for them
to say they got boyfriends or just for
them to [ __ ] ghost you. It's [ __ ]
madness, isn't it,
bro? That's why there's a That's why I
thought a plan B, is
it? I was speaking to this American.
She's just a [ __ ] on [ __ ] Friday. It was. Yeah.
[ __ ] proper [ __ ] Her whole attitude
like I just don't like I just don't like
American people. [ __ ]
them. Don't like any westernized woman.
Any westernized woman at all? I don't
think I don't like them.
Me. Yeah, you should just stick to these
Brazilian escorts. I got an escort the
other day, Gains. He almost choked on my [ __ ] dick.
Yeah, she almost choked on my dick. I
was like, bro, so it's So, how much time
and money are you going to spend, bro?
Trying to [ __ ] find these people,
bro. You know what I'm
saying? You might as well just [ __ ]
pay for it, bro. If you win money, I I
see it. I see it as that now. You know,
I actually see it as that, bro. Bit like
being like [ __ ] Thailand, cuz you
can't even date in this country. It's
not about sex. You can't even date in
this country. Well, like if you're start
if you're someone like me or like or
anyone starting from this position, you
can't even date, bro. [ __ ] the sex. You
can't even date. So, don't talk about
sex. You can't even date,
bro. And man said they're not interested
in this country. That's the end of it.
That's it, bro. Is what it
is. They won't, bro. They weren't, bro,
cuz I only get
[ __ ] And that's the end of it.
This is the truth in it, bro. Cuz I was
looking fresh on Saturday as well, bro.
Nice shorts, nice top. Um, nice
[ __ ] nice um just nice hair. I curled
my hair up. It's madness, isn't it,
bro? You can look [ __ ] You can look
[ __ ] good, bro, and you still won't
get anything in this country.
Yeah. Ah, you need to It's like looking like Timmy
Eldridge. It's like looking like Timmy Eldridge,
bro. I think with it in London, I think
that they they just think they've got
more money. I just think they think
they're better than people in
it. What is it? What is it with this
London, bro? Like, you should just be
able to go out and just meet someone.
Why is it so
difficult? It should be piss easy, bro,
to just go meet someone, just go go on a
date, see how it goes.
But it's mad. And then even if you get a
date, it's pointless even going on a
date cuz they're just time wasters. It's [ __ ] isn't it?
Yeah. Yeah. I don't even [ __ ] bro. I
just get low jobs to be honest. But
yeah, but I say that when I went out two
days doing these approaches, I only got
I got a boyfriend
once. I thought I got more I got more
success approaching in a tracksuit than
not wear not wearing a tracksuit.
Yeah. Yeah. The boyfriend [ __ ] is
boring, bro. Oh, it is proper boring,
bro. I don't even know how anyone can laugh at
it. Boyfriends, boyfriends,
boyfriends. 70% of men are single. 75%
of men are single. But yet these women have
boyfriends. Yet it doesn't add up. The
maths doesn't add up. And people are
clubbing to 3 4 5:00 in the morning, but
yet they've got boyfriends. So their
boyfriends are at home what? Watching TV
by themselves. Just come on, man. We
need to be real about this. Like we've
even got 40 year olds now saying they
got boyfriends. And people in their 40s
are not classed as [ __ ] boyfriends.
They're classed as partners or husbands
fiances. They don't call them
boyfriends. That's not what the old
folks call each other. So you even got
them saying it now cuz I watched the
video. It's just I swear to God if
somebody says it to me one more time,
I'm going to actually strangle someone,
bro. I'm not even
joking. One step, but
I've got to do
uh No, when I
say no, but I'm saying this people are
clubbing till 3 4. They don't have
boyfriends, bro. They know their
boyfriends. It's [ __ ] You know, I
went out on Friday. No, Friday, Thursday
with a track suit and I didn't get I've
got a boyfriend once. I didn't get it
once. I had someone say they were
married, but they approached me and they
still kissed me. So then I was a
believer in the
tracksuit LT. So that's why I went to
JD, bought a tracksuit. I don't even
really like tracksuits, but I mean, if
it gets you better success, then who am
I to say no to, you know? And obviously
got a pair of trainers as well. So I'm
thinking, you know, if it's uh seems to
be working better, then just rock the tracksuit, bro.
I can't believe I didn't get once on
Friday and Thursday. Sorry, not Friday.
Thursday. I was like, [ __ ] am I in Thailand
already? [ __ ] hell. If you don't hear
you've got a boyfriend in the whole
[ __ ] day, mate. Jesus. Something is
seriously seriously up, you
know. No, I don't go to the clubs in No.
No. What I done was I went with a
tracksuit, went in early, but I had
jeans in my bag. So, obviously, if they
said you need to wear jeans, I would
have just changed into jeans, which is
probably what I'm going to do again on
um Saturday. I'm going to go out with a
tracksuit and put jeans in my bag in
case like worst comes to worst. But I
get in the clubs early and I just stay them.
Um but obviously I'll just bring the bag
as well. I was wearing a bag as well.
They don't let you in with tracksuits,
bro. They don't let you in. That's why
you have to go early without before the bounces come.
Yeah, but I'm going to get it again on
Saturday, more than
likely. Yeah, I've got this 47y old on
Reddit saying I'm this, saying I'm that,
saying I'm this, but apparently she's
too old for me. 47 and 27 is not too
old. That's why I could never ever get a
old woman fetish because they're just
going to use their age as an
excuse. Bit like them saying they got a
boyfriend. You know, there's there's
there's but there's no point having an
older woman fetish. I don't know how
people get them because all they're
going to say is if only I was younger.
It's boring, bro. You come across old
people in clubs quite a lot of the [ __ ]
time. I'm fed up, bro. I'm fed up today,
bro. I haven't caught up on sleep
properly. But at least I done a lot of
walking yesterday. That's a good thing, isn't
it? I'll be out Saturday again. Maybe Friday, maybe
Saturday. I done so much this week. I
don't know. It's already Monday and I
started from Thursday. I started on
Thursday and it's already Monday. [ __ ] hell,
bro. Yep. And I got two numbers on
Saturday, so I have to start all over
again. All over again,
bro. Yeah, I think that's the best thing
did. We'll see. Peppa Pig had an
American waste my time as well a couple
of months ago. They're all time wasted,
bro. Even if you meet them, they're just time
wasters. They're just complete. And I
think they've got some mental disorder
where they like wasting your time and
their time. I think they've actually got
a mental disorder,
bro. Because like you get a man say, why
would they waste their time? But they
do. I can give you a million and one
examples of how they've wasted their
time and my
time. You know what I'm saying? They
have. They literally
have. Yeah, I hate Americans. I
approached one the other day. Yeah. And
uh I didn't know she was from America
and she was just a proper stuckup [ __ ]
Even though she was from Ohio, like she
spoke back and that, but I just I just
don't like their attitude. I don't like
them. So, if I know if I know if I knew
someone was American, I wouldn't even
bother. They're the worst kind of
people. cuz they think their country is bad and
everyone's, you know, I just I just
don't like them, bro. I just don't like
them. Especially the women. They're just
[ __ ] They just think the whole world
revolves around their country, man. You
used to get with them on [ __ ]
PlayStation. And Canadian women are
[ __ ] as well, but you don't really come
across them as much. They're all bad.
Any Western country, they're all bad,
man. England, Canada, [ __ ]
America. They're all westernized.
They're all [ __ ] You know what I'm saying? That's
it. So, I would have happily got with
this person yesterday that I met, but
I'm not converting to Muslim. So, I'll
give her to my friend. You
know, that means no pork, no
drinking, I have to get circumcised. I'm
not [ __ ] doing that,
bro. I'm not doing
that. Yeah. And you know what she asked
me? She asked me yesterday, "Well, what
kind of people do you go for? Do you
have a specific um type? Do you have a
specific um person you go for?" Cuz I
said, "Oh, what what's your preference?"
And I said, "To me, it's about attitude.
It's not even so much. If I if I meet
somebody that's not a western like these
westernized [ __ ] that's enough for me.
You know what I'm saying? If they're not
like with me, it's attitude is a big
thing cuz where you deal with such these
westernized [ __ ] that think they're
better than people, you know? It's like
it's that's a big thing. That's a that's
like 75% of it,
bro. They've got bad attitude in London,
bro. Bad attitude.
Uh, it was pissing me off. Um, Saturday
was pissing me off, but then I was like,
I've got to meet this person on Sunday.
So, yeah, it was pissing me off on
Saturday. It was pissing me off properly
on on um on uh on Saturday. It
was cuz if you can't go into clubs
without paying an arm and a
leg then you know where does that leave you in
it? So you got to pay money to get into
clubs for people just to say they got a
boyfriend. It's [ __ ] bad. [ __ ] man.
Yeah, bro. You know what? Even these old
women nowadays have got more options
than the [ __ ] average
guy. [ __ ] me, bro. Sucks dick,
bro. Skin mark [ __ ] Samson, mate. I
need to go in a minute, man. I need to
go and find something to eat today. I
might get some lamb beef. I don't know,
mate. Maybe some lamb
chops. I don't [ __ ] know what I'm
having, bro. I don't fancy pork, lad.
I'll be out again Saturday. At least I'm
telling you I'm going to be out Saturday.
But nothing to lose, you know, spending450.
But if I hear you'll find someone one
more time, bro, I think I'm actually
going to go outside and strangle
someone. I'm not even
joking, bro. Mate, when are you going to
find someone when you're 47 and you're
too old to get a [ __ ] erection, bro?
You should be finding people now, bro.
You put in more effort than [ __ ] most
of these [ __ ] people. You're decent
looking. You got money, mate. Now is the perfect time.
You know, at the end of the day, I'm I'm
almost out of my [ __ ] prime, bro.
This is the age where you're going to
start like gaining weight and then I
need to be doing stuff before I'm 30,
bro. This is the the actual time. You
know, your sex drive goes down when
you're when you're in your
30s. [ __ ] hell. Yeah. You'll be on
your deathbed, bro. You would have
finally found someone
um when you're too old to even get a [ __ ] erection.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Come on,
man. They must have deactivated their
account. How's your girl Morgan
Games? Oh, bro, I wrote [ __ ] on her
[ __ ] Facebook, man. On
uh it was like a week ago, 3:00 in the
morning. I said, "Listen, you you and
your dad are a keyboard warrior, mate.
I'll come to you next Thursday, Friday.
I'm there, man. Just say the day cuz I
save money not going out for a month in it." So,
uh, I couldn't walk for like a month.
So, yeah, it went quiet. Just Yeah. In
future, don't call people a keyboard
warrior, man. Don't don't call people a
keyboard warrior when you don't know
them. You know what I'm saying? Because
you people are legitimately the keyboard
warrior because you keep going on about
[ __ ] ling people. Lawing people, man.
[ __ ] you Americans. That's what I said
to them. Said none of us are about nothing,
mate. Listen, I wrote at like 3:00 in
the morning. It was like a week ago.
Bro, it reminded me of you LT, is it?
Cuz you you got involved, didn't you?
You got involved, but I was I was behind
it all in it. I was behind you. Yep. Yeah,
bro. It reminded me of you, man. It
reminded me of you, lad.
[ __ ] them, bro. I just wrote it cuz it
was funny to write in it, you know. Oh, man.
See, I might have to start working soon,
LT. That's [ __ ] is
it? [ __ ] working soon. Oh, please
don't depress me, bro. [ __ ]
hell. Working. That's pretty
[ __ ] That's pretty [ __ ] Working, is
it? I haven't worked for [ __ ] years,
man. Yeah, but it is [ __ ] Working is
though. Like, it's nice to be a free
man, you know, to do what you want when
you want to. No responsibilities. [ __ ] me,
bro. Working is just [ __ ] I know people
have to do it. I get it. Like, it's a
good thing to do. It's a good thing to
do. Obviously, you have to work. People
got to work. But when you haven't
worked, if you had money, bro, like
coming in, you know what I'm saying,
bro? You don't want to work. You're not used to
working. Do you know what I'm saying, bro? One second,
bro. Post is coming. Yeah. Yeah. But
there's other things to do to help your
mental health, bro. Yeah. You can go to
the gym. You can go to new places, man. Nos
yesterday if you was if you was get if
you was getting 3k a month bro not
working you you wouldn't want to stop
you wouldn't want to start working and
all of that money's disposed osable. You
wouldn't want to start working,
bro. I'm No, probably what I'm doing is
I'm just going to save up. I I've got a
goal, bro. I want I want to save up.
Yeah. And open a Chinese restaurant in
in Chinatown, knowing that it's
expensive. I know it's not as easy as
that, but you had something like that,
bro. You be making bank, bro. I know
some guy that where he works here. They
made over the bank holiday £18,000 in one restaurant.
But obviously you need to work to save
up for that. Obviously I know people
have to work but but ideally you want to
be having your own business you know
when like you know after like a few
years. Do you know what I'm saying
bro? I'm not used to being told what to
do bro. Do you understand? I don't like
being told what to
do. You don't understand what I mean
bro. like you're used to working. Most
people work, but you know what I'm
saying? I don't like being told what to do. But
yeah, but yeah, you know, if you made a
restaurant, obviously risk, businesses
are risks. We know that like you can put
money into it and obviously nothing can
come out of it. But definitely, mate, if
you opened a Chinese restaurant in
Chinatown, you would 100% make money.
You would have to with all them tourists
bringing all that money in you. You'd
have to, man. You would have to make
money. You would have to. But obviously
you need thousands and thousands to start
it. You should think of doing something like that. LT. Yep.
Yeah, imagine that, bro. 3k a month for
three years, not having to
work. And then you got people on here
talking about [ __ ] a grand a month.
[ __ ] grand a month. Well, 3K a month
doesn't seem a lot to you. But
obviously, if you don't have any
outgoings, it's quite a lot, is
it? It's quite a lot. It is quite a
lot. Well, from skin in it, but
still [ __ ] grand a month, mate. You
[ __ ] I think I've spent about a grand
in about a week,
matey. Must been about a week.
Yeah, but you'd adjust. We got a grand a
month. You'd adjust. She had no outgoings,
but it be a bit
[ __ ] mate. To be honest with you, even
when I was getting 3K a month, I could
have done with more
money cuz you don't realize any money
you get, you just get
adjusted. You don't understand. You you
adjust to it. Any money you get, whether
it's a,000, 3,000, 5,000, when you earn
more, you spend
more. Do you understand? So, it doesn't
matter what money you
get. You know, even if you got £800 a
month, you would survive. You'd adjust
to it. Trust me, bro. Any money you get,
you adjust to
it. cuz I was thinking like 3k a month
is is not um is not enough which is
insane because you don't pay [ __ ]
rent. You've got like two outgoings
which is £100. It should be more than
enough. But you get used to the same
amount of money and your lifestyle. You
your taste change. You see when you get,
you know, you understand what I'm
saying? You adjust to any amount of
money that you
get. So say you was getting 40 grand a
month, you be like, "Oh, I'm traveling
the world now. Oh, I could deal with I
could do with an extra 20k a month." You
see? So it doesn't matter. Whatever
money you get, you would just adjust to
it. So, why is this even talking about
it? But I remember back when I used to
meet Izzy and stuff, I used to run low on
money. Used to get 700 pound a month.
So, yeah. [ __ ]
man. It's proper [ __ ]
Yeah, that's the
thing. Yeah, but do you know why he's
not satisfied being a
billionaire? Here's the thing, and I'll
explain I'll explain that to you. I'll
explain to you why. Because, right, part
of the fun things in life, right, is
stressing over money. Money is hard to
come by. So when you win money or you
come across money, it's like, oh, part
of the fun in life is is that little bit
of stress. Oh, I'm earning a bit more
money now. No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. Like, when you're a billionaire,
you never have to think about money ever
again. So, when someone's a billionaire,
it makes sense what I'm saying that it's
that, oh, well, money is nothing. Yeah,
they can do all of these nice things,
but eventually they'll get bored of it.
Whereas when you're not a billionaire,
the whole part of life and that
adrenaline is is about getting more
money. When you're a billionaire, you
don't have to worry about that. That's
why he's not satisfied. Do you
understand? He's a billionaire, bro.
Just like Cristiano Ronaldo. It makes
sense. Just, you know, people can be
billionaires and still be depressed,
bro. People, you know what I'm
saying? That's why he's not satisfied.
You could be a billionaire and still be [ __ ] single,
man. Housebound. Like, it's, you know
what I'm saying, bro? Like, that's why
billionaires or or they never have to
worry about money ever
again. Yeah, these guys, they're sad,
bro. Believe it or not, LT, I actually
have a life. I do have a life.
Yeah. Do you know before I went out?
Yeah. Um, on Saturday I went on LJ's
been popped up, he was sat on YouTube
drinking, [ __ ] talking to a bunch of
[ __ ] losers. But he's a loser
himself, but you know what I mean? Who's
never ever ever going to meet him. Like
they're never ever going to meet him.
But he's sat on YouTube. But bro, this
is the same guy that tells people they
ain't got no
friends. And you know the man, do you
know and and the thing, this is what I
was saying the other day, man. It's like
they're too old now as well. They can't
even change it. Why do you think they
come on here saying, "Oh, you're skin,
you're a virgin, you're this." It's
because it's themselves they're talking
about. Think of it, bro. Like sat there
on YouTube. All day he was on YouTube
because when I come back Yeah.
Um, he was still on there. I was out I
was out [ __ ] clubbing with my [ __ ]
friends, bro. But apparently I don't
have no friends compared to according to
some guy that sits on YouTube all day
talking to people that's never ever
going to meet him. You see the maddest
thing is bro, I'd actually rate it.
Yeah. If you actually done videos
meeting these people, like actual
videos, going to a beer garden, going to
club t, but he's sat on YouTube. None of
them leave the [ __ ] house. How can
they tell anyone they ain't got friends,
bro? Like, just use your use your head.
How can they tell anyone that they don't [ __ ]
madness? This a proper madness, lad.
I invited everyone to a [ __ ] barbecue,
right? No one come out. No one come. And
it was a serious invite and everyone
knew where I was. So, I mean, that tells
you that you need to know about them.
So, I'm [ __ ] bored as well. I need to
go out and get some food. I'm just about
to put my trainers on. Just another [ __ ]
week. It's already Tuesday tomorrow,
then it's Wednesday will be Saturday
before we um before we know it
again. I'll be hearing about more Make
believe Boyfriends on Saturday, bro. I can't
wait. I can't wait,
mate. It's going to be fun, isn't it?
No, it's not fun, mate. It's [ __ ]
boring. Yeah, I'm going to I'm going to
cook some food
today. Yeah, this Muslim woman was nice.
She She's a nice person, but it's I'm
not converting, bro. I'm not converting, mate. Nah.
LT salamakum. That's how I'm going to
start talking to you now, bro.
Salam. That's what I'm going to start doing,
mate. Saying I'm probably just going to
go to Hal Butchers in a minute to be fair.
Yeah. Yeah. I paid this Jamaican guy to
sort out the garden.
LT. Yeah. We g I gave him some money. He
cleaned up the garden and stuff. So, I
was able to do the barbecue. You see, it
was a It was a right tip. It was a white
kathuffle. It was a right kathuffle.
But you got dad in the
end. Uh yeah. Okay, I'm going to
go. Need to put some money away and uh
go figure out what I'm
eating. Well, another experience to add
to the [ __ ] connection. [ __ ] connection.
I'll be out with a um tracksuit and the
um bag Saturday. Stay tuned. Yeah,
man. I might wash the tracks, too.
Actually, what's the weather saying now?
Is it hot?
Maybe I'll wear the tracksuit. No, I'm
not wearing the tracksuit now cuz
um No, I'm not wearing the the tracksuit
cuz uh it's too hot. I'm going to wear
it Saturday and I'm I'm I'm not wearing
the new trainers. You see?
Yeah, Saturday will be
fun. I could probably make some money
before I go out to be fair.
make the money for Saturday. But
yeah, if my hair was growing back, then
I wouldn't go out for a month. But like
I said, I get my hair done every 3
weeks. So once I get it done, I'll just
go out every week. And then when it
finally goes back, then I might not go
out for a month.
So [ __ ] dead, man. Yeah.
relationships in this country, mate. No,
I'm not gambling. I lost 300 pound on
roulette last week. Not doing it again.
I barely gamble anymore. Nope. Not
playing that [ __ ] And if I was to
gamble, wouldn't be on Frankie. Nope.
Need to start saving money now,
matey. Nah, I'm good, bro.
Yeah, I went on this date yesterday,
Slim. I was out for like 5 hours, man.
Walked around Hide Park, went to
Nandos, and she said basically like,
"Uh, you won't get with me cuz I'm not Muslim.
So, just another one to add to this [ __ ]
collection. No, I'm not playing that
[ __ ] I'm not
gambling. Maybe next month I'll
gamble, but not this
month. I could technically do it if I
wanted to. Have I still got my online
account? No, I can't cuz I got my friend
to um change the password for me.
Yeah, I got him to change the password for me.
Yeah. Yeah. I got to change the password for me, lad.
Bye-bye. My funds are never low, mate. Never
low. Nope. Cuz it's a long process. And
then when she sees my dick, she's going
to know that I haven't actually
converted because she's going to see
your dick and then she's going to
realize you're not
circumcised. So, no, it's not going to
work. Once it gets into the
bedroom, it's not going to work. So,
we're basically back to square
one. You know what that means, LT? I got
two numbers Saturday. I didn't reply.
Well, I'll be dealing with plenty more
stuck up [ __ ] um on
Saturday. Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
Not they waste people's time on
purpose. People like to think that they
Well, not this one. I think this one was
a misunderstanding, but they they you
know when I say they waste their time,
waste people's time on purpose, they actually do,
bro. They actually do.
cuz there's so many examples I could
give you of where like none of it has
made no sense, but people on Reddit
don't seem to think that they would
waste their time on purpose because it
don't make sense. Like, yeah, it don't
make sense. We're we're we're aware that
it doesn't make sense, but they still do
it. Technically, they do still do it. So, so
yeah, that's that.
But no, I'm not low on funds. I just
don't want to gamble my money
away. What's that got to do with being low on
puns? Nah, bro. I already lost 300 for
the month. I'm not using anymore. So
yeah, get money again in two weeks. I
should have like 2K, but it's fine.
That will last you two weeks, mate,
won't it? 2K.
Yeah, that will last you. Yeah, I've got
one phone bill which is £18 coming out
and an internet bill which is 50. And
then the money's all [Music]
mine. Then the money's all mine. E
Two weeks is nothing,
mate. Hollywood is the second.
You're already the
second. Anyways, I'll be back later.
Yeah. in a bizzle.