Yeah. Yeah. GJ uh six is coming
out. Oh wow. It only took him 13 [ __ ]
years. 13 [ __ ] years.
13 [ __ ] years it took. What? [Laughter]
Yo, GTA 6 is um coming out next May. So,
I'm going to start saving 20 a week until May.
So, buy a massive TV and console and the
game cuz we think the game's going to be about
£120. But it's okay. I'll
wait. I'll just sit there and I'll wait
for it to be released. I don't even have
a Well, I've got Xbox, but I don't even
like consoles, bro. I don't even bother
to buy a new TV, but when that comes
out, I'm going to do it all over again.
saving for a game, a console, and a TV.
And the game doesn't come out till next
year. So, you know, they gave me a heads
up. It's a game, the console be like £1,400, maybe
1,400. Good idea, man. Start saving now.
But it doesn't seem like it's much when
it comes, you know.
Obviously, if I come out next month, I
just get it next month or the month
after, but it doesn't come out for
another [ __ ] year.
So, yeah. Makes perfect sense, isn't
it? Cuz when the time comes when it does
get released, it's like
nothing. Yeah. I was getting really bad
mood swings yesterday, bro, over these
this women [ __ ] bro. Really bad mood
swings. I was going to go out and I felt
like hurting someone, bro. I'm not even
joking. I felt like actually going out
and hurting someone,
bro. Yeah, bro. Saturday pissed me off,
man. Them trying to charge me to get
into clubs hearing that I haven't got a
boyfriend, bro. It's so
boring, bro. It's so boring, bro.
Honestly, it's so [ __ ] boring
now. And you have people on Reddit, man,
trying to give you [ __ ] advice. They don't know
anything. You know what I'm saying?
[ __ ] can't stand him, Brick Wrong.
Can't [ __ ] stand him,
mate. I can't stand him, bro. Really?
It's not even the person I met on
Sunday. It was the one before that. I
hate him, bro. I actually
do. Why stop for a month? It's the same
[ __ ] [ __ ] boring, mate. [ __ ] bors me. Yeah. [ __ ] It proper
sh country will never change, mate. We
stuck our [ __ ] in it. Never.
Yeah, bro. They are the problem. These
westernized pings are a [ __ ] problem,
mate. No one
else. Oh, I got another Saturday. None
of them replied. I wonder why that is.
Nope. I'm watching a clown clown and
cornfield. Yes. Um, on Friday, I'm
saving up for the new GTA coming out
next next year cuz it's coming out next
year. So, it gives you time to save. I
don't need to save, but it's just better
if you did save. 20 a week because when
it comes out, you can just buy
everything with what you save. Makes more sense,
right? Just save 20 pound a week.
Yeah, 20 pound a
week around that a
year about a th000 probably save about a
th000 that time save 20 pound a week.
Yeah. Yeah. We're still [ __ ] Joe
forever and always
mate. Forever and always.
I was so tempted yesterday to just go
outside and doing madness, bro. But I
don't want to go to prison, bro. That's
the thing. [ __ ] that. No one's worth
going to [ __ ] prison
for. Uh 4 weeks, just under
now. Get away from this [ __ ] I haven't
got a boyfriend. [ __ ] hell. I don't
know how man used to do it every week.
It's not the money side of it. It's
fine. You're spending 50 60 pound, but
it's boring, man. You know, here and
I've got a boyfriend. I've got a
boyfriend. I've got I don't know how the
[ __ ] people do it every week. [ __ ]
boring. Bors the [ __ ] out of me. It's the same
old same old [ __ ] mate. I went out
Saturday with some friends and they were
trying to charge us
1520 to get into a club. And I'm
thinking, [ __ ] so what? Dating apps
don't [ __ ] work. And to even get into
a club, you've got to spend 15, 20
pound. [ __ ] disgusting this country.
I hate women. I generally generally
[ __ ] do, but I hate them. Hate the
ground they walk on. Wouldn't say it, didn't believe
it. You know, people can say they're
different all they like, but I see I
believe it when I see it. That's that's
that's the way you got you got to look
at it really. People can say anything, you
know. They're just not interested in
this country, plain and
simple. But again, people don't tell you
on the internet because they seem to
think they're better than everyone. But
no one tells you that on the internet.
They say, "Oh, it's about confidence.
Oh, it's about this." When it's them
being stuck up, picky, snobby little
[ __ ] No one ever tells you that. No.
No. No one tells you that until you
actually go out and you experience it
yourself. You see, no one tells you
these things. They sell you a lie.
That's what they do. They're liars, bro.
We're [ __ ] absolute
idiots. Somebody was like, "Oh yeah,
yeah, maybe if someone's not for you in
this country, maybe somewhere like
Canada, Asia, Japan, and Russia." So he
listed three countries that would make
sense. But the first one, Canada. Oh
yeah, another westernized
country where they're all [ __ ]
[ __ ] Oh, another westernized country. Westernized country.
Wow. All the same in Canada as well.
What I've seen. All the same.
Westernized. [ __ ] me. Unless it's South
America or it's [ __ ] Asia, it's the same
[ __ ] Unless it's South America or Asia,
it's the same old will never change. You
know, I was trying to explain to these
people on Reddit, it's about moving
forward. It's not about the past or or
hating or not hating. that the the
future is quite scary cuz if this is
what it's going to be like forever then
what hope does somebody have when they
come back to this country. That's the
that's the main problem. It's not about really
um what has happened or what how you
think about it. It's about the future is
very scary. If this is your your your
um is this going to be your future life
in this country then man I'm not liking
it. I'm not going to lie to you but I am
not liking it. Not one little bit. I must
say I must say bro.
This is your future day. This is your
life. Yeah. Saturday is [ __ ] charging
you a bomb to get into clubs. Could even
[ __ ] get into any It [ __ ] sucks,
man. What about not getting out of bed
today, bro? It put you in this mood
again. And so And so it [ __ ] should.
So it [ __ ]
should put anyone in this [ __ ] mood.
You know what I'm saying?
[ __ ] after [ __ ] after [ __ ] after [ __ ] [ __ ] you
know. People like to blame the man
because it sounds good. You understand?
It sounds good. It just sounds good just
to blame the man. It sounds good, you know?
Yeah, but it's £20 a [ __ ] week.
They're not going
to spend that. You know what I'm
saying? It makes sense to save 20 pound
a week because it doesn't come out for a
year. So if they don't come out for a
year, it's the same thing with phones
really. If you bought a new phone, you
should be saving about 1020 a week for
when a new one gets released because
it's not going to be released for a
year. So you can just save little
amounts, even£10 even if you save half
of it, you
know? Yeah, you might gamble. I don't
really gamble anymore. No slots, no
[ __ ] roulette, no nothing.
Don't do any of that
really over here.
to go out Saturday, but I don't think I
can hack it. I don't think I can hear
I've got a boyfriend again for a very long time,
bro. Yeah, cuz you're an addict,
fella. You an addict, fella. Could you
see Did you see uh Timmy showing 300
pound yesterday? I was going to go to
the bank and withdraw some money and put
these people to shame again, but there's
no point cuz they just talk about
themselves. So no matter what you show
them, they're just going to call you
skin anyways because they're [ __ ] disabled. So
yeah. Yeah. When I lost 300 lb on
roulette over the past two days, like
last week didn't piss me off that
much. Not to how it used to before. Don't really care. Okay.
Yeah, I think that's me done for the
month for these women to be honest with
you. I think that's me done for the
month for these women. I can't lie. It's
just always the same
[ __ ] trying to charge me 1520 they
charge to me try to charge me and my little
mates to hear what I've got a boyfriend.
Who's going to [ __ ] pay 1520 to get
into a club to hear I've got a boyfriend?
You know what I'm saying? Who's who's
really going to play
that? Why would anyone pay
that? Stupid, huh?
It's just easier to blame the man
because it sounds good. It sounds good,
Joe. It sounds good. You see, sounds
good to blame the man.
Yeah. See the numbers on Saturday. No reply. Wower.
Wower. The future's quite scary. I'm not
liking the future. It kind of scares me.
I could forget about the past if I knew
it was going to be if the future was
going to be different. If I knew the
future here was going to be different,
then I could leave the past. But it's
very relevant because it's still going to
happen, you know, and it's an indication
of what your future's going to be like in this
country. I don't need a job, mate. I'm
not talking about my personal life and
my financial life on this community with pulling these grasses. Simple. So pointless. Well,
yeah. But yeah, the future scary. Very
scary. If you have to pay a bomb to get
into clubs, if you can't stop hearing
I've got a
boyfriend or other
stuff. Well, other it wasn't that bad
last week, but other stuff. Ghosting,
[ __ ] with you. If if that's never
going to change, then what is that what
what is that telling you that it's going
to keep being like in this country if you keep
trying? It's [ __ ] scary, man. It
scares the [ __ ] out of me, you know? It
took me till like 4:00 in the [ __ ]
morning to sleep yesterday. I was thinking about
it. It's so scary, you
know. And then this Muslim was like, she
wouldn't date me cuz I'm not Muslim,
which that I didn't care about. It was
that what happened the night
before, you know? Yeah.
It's always going to be [ __ ] experience
after [ __ ] experience after [ __ ]
experience in this country. That's
always what it's going to be. You know,
it's always what it's going to be. And
here's the thing that these women don't
understand, Joe. You know how they were
saying about how they've had um negative
dates and they've had this and they've
had that and they've had this. And do
you know why it doesn't affect these
people? Because they don't have to put
any effort into getting anything. That's
the difference. For you to get a date,
for you to get anything, you need to go
out and approach a [ __ ] million
people, right? He you need to go out and
you need to approach a million people.
They don't have to do anything. So,
whenever they get a date that they don't
click with, that's irrelevant because
they then they just go on to the next
person. Whereas you, you have to keep
approaching, you have to get a number,
try to get them to meet you again, and
do it all over again.
They never have to put effort into
anything in their life. And then mom was
trying to tell me, "Oh, well, yeah,
well, I put effort into my appearance."
I was like, "Well, you should be doing
that anyways. Everyone should be putting
effort into their appearance. But do you
actively have to pursue men to get a
date?" No, you do not. And that's the big
difference. That's the big big big
difference. We have to, you understand?
We have to waste money, waste time, keep
pursuing people, [ __ ] waste our
energy just to get the same [ __ ] in the end
anyways. So that's the big
difference. You wouldn't lost a quarter
of a mile in a man's shoes, mate. Trust
me. [ __ ] hate it. I do, bro. Hate it. You
know, cuz then you could just go on to
the next person, the next person, next
person. You can't just go on to the next
person. You got to do all over again. I
didn't have a date up until April. I
didn't have a whole date this year until April.
So, I [ __ ] can't stand it, mate. I
really do need to give up, mate. I I
need to like get involved with this uh
whole GTA thing again and and take my
mind somewhere cuz I'm just going to end
up doing something I regret. I'm not
even joking, bro. I'll just end up going
prison and it's it's just not worth it.
You know, it's not worth it, man. You
know, could you actually imagine them
having to approach a man? Could you
imagine them have Could you imagine it
the other way around where they would
have to pursue men? Imagine that for one
second in your mind. They would have to
go out and pursue men for dates. They
would have to go out and pursue men for
potential relationships. It would kill
them. One of them would actually kill
them. You know what I'm
saying? It's like I was pissed off
Saturday, but then I was, "Oh, I've got
somebody to meet the next day." That's
what they have every time. You
know, [ __ ] idiots.
They don't approach, man. You know what?
I've only been approached about four
times in my whole
life. In my whole career. And then you
got this guy saying, "I've been rejected
a 100 times." You've been rejected a 100
times, mate. I probably get rejected a
100 times each time I go
out. You think a hundred times is a lot?
[ __ ] these people, man. I wish Yeah.
Do you know what, right? I wish they you could
like translate your experiences to them
somehow. You could put a cable in your
[ __ ] brain into their [ __ ] brain
and then they would know your I would
love for them to to walk a mile in your
shoe for one day and see if they'd be
saying the same
stuff. See if they'd be saying the same
stuff. And it's not even like you you go
out and then you approach and then you
even get whatever it is you whatever it
is people want. No, no, no, no, no. It doesn't end
there. You know what I'm saying? It doesn't end
there. I can't [ __ ] stand them. I
wish there was a way, like I just said,
where they could actually
um just have a day in your shoes, bro.
It' be nice. Then we'll see what advice
they we'll see what advice they they can give. So
yeah, I really why people turn
into Makes makes sense, doesn't it?
makes makes perfect sense if you if you
actually see the bigger picture. Women
have dating life on easy mode to the in
the fact that they don't have to put
effort into anything to even get a date.
They don't need to put any effort into
getting a date dates and all of the
flaws that they moan about on miners.
Oh, men only want me for sex. Oh, no,
no, no, no, no. They're all they're all
little miners that can be overlapped.
They don't have to put effort into finding
anyone. That's the
difference. So, I think that the problem
is it's it's you know now what's going
to happen if you try again. You have to
put effort in and then go through it all
over again. It's like stop it's like
completing a a game of Grand Theft Auto
and then having to do it all over
again for no reason. That's literally,
bro, I swear now, that's literally what
it's like. At least that's what it actually feels like. Yeah.
So yeah, bro. That's that's the point
I'm trying to basically make is that
they don't have to put effort into anything. So
Saturday. Do not go out Saturday cuz
we've got the hair done. I don't want to
start hearing about I've got
boyfriends, you know. It's [ __ ]
boring. Bors the [ __ ] out of me, you
know. So maybe this week I probably will get it.
And the only people I do want to meet
you are people that offended on you. So what the
[ __ ] No point recording any approaches
anymore. There's no point recording any
dates anymore cuz it's always going to
be the same. The same. The same. The
same. The same. Why the [ __ ] did I have
to get into this [ __ ]
again? This [ __ ] all over again, you
know. I wish I never, man. I wish I
[ __ ] never. I'm not even joking. I wish I
never You know what I want to do? I just
want to sleep and not wake up for like a
year. You know what I want to do? I just
want to sleep until May 26th, until
Grand Theft Auto comes out. Then I can
start gaming again. You
know, it's scary, bro. It's very very very scary.
Very very very very scary,
bro. We could forget the past if there
was a different future. That's what I'm
saying, bro. Then we could
actually I think I'm going to go to the
cinema. If I go out on Saturday, I think
I'm going to go to the cinema on maybe
Monday instead. So then I have something
to look forward to. You know, if I do it
before I go out, then I'm just going to be pissed
off. Know what I'm
saying? Monday, even though it comes out
Friday, do the next day. Actually, I
just stick to beer.
When the day
tomorrow, let's count down the days to
I've got a boyfriend day. Counting down
the days, mate. Counting down the [ __ ]
days. [ __ ] boring,
eh? Very boring. ESPs. Yeah.
What are you doing? What was Timmy going
on about yesterday?
What do you mean? Them stupid videos.
He's telling you he wants me to jump on
buses. I don't know where the [ __ ] he
wants me to go on the bus. He didn't
give me a location to go on a bus. He
just told me to get on a bus. Oh, you
know GTA 6 is coming out.
Yeah, I don't play consoles no more.
PGA. No, no, I I I don't. But when that
comes out, I'm going to buy a new
console, new TV, and I'm going to buy
the game, bro. [ __ ] it. Is it? Yeah. I'm
not even bothering with it, mate. I'm
not even bothering. How did you know
about GTA 6? I've known about GTA 6 for
for a long time, PJ. It's been coming
It's been saying it was coming out about
four year ago. Yeah, but that was
rumors, though. There's actual There's
an actual trailer now. That's what I
mean. Yeah. Yeah. No, no, I'd seen the
trailer. It's It's a woman on it. It's a
woman. It's a female on it. Yeah. I
don't I don't bother with consoles.
Yeah, I can't be asking them anymore.
They're [ __ ] boring to [ __ ] Did you
see Did you see um Timmy showing £300?
£300. Oh my days, man. What's £300 going
to do? Yeah, that's a lot of money to you.
That's not a lot of money to me.
There it is. 300 quid is not a lot of
money to me. PG yet. Well, 800 is
800 is not even a lot of money. Well, it
is to you.
Well, think about it. This is a lot of
money to me. If I come out with
750 twice out of both of my money,
disability and pip, how much money do I
come out with? 1,500.
That's how much you come up with.
Yeah. Is that enough though? Nah.
Yeah, that's enough. I'm not greedy. [Laughter]
You are greedy.
I'm not greedy. 2700s and 50 in a bull. That's
basically not bad. That lad.
No. So, how much do you have now? 6,000. No, you
don't mate on Baro. What? Completely
all [ __ ] free weed. So, how the [ __ ]
are you? You must be spending all your
[ __ ] money on [ __ ] weed. You [ __ ]
No, [ __ ] weed. Fork. [ __ ]
um Yeah. Beer [ __ ] prostitutes.
No, I don't do prostitutes. Pedia,
you must do for your money to be going
like that. Did you hear Rice? Did you
hear what Rice does? No, I don't watch
him, man. No [ __ ] because he can't
because he can't get a woman and that no
woman will go with him. He [ __ ] he
got a prostitute.
Monty Monty, you know, on Saturday.
Yeah. I went out with my friends to go
drinking. But these people say that I've
got no friends. But I do. Yeah. It
doesn't matter. PJ, these are these are
the people who haven't got friends.
Huh? These are the people who haven't
got no friends. PJ
people. It is. Like you've seen it. They
they'd say no friends. And I was like,
"Man, you're just describing yourself.
Like, just leave it out now." Yeah, they
do. Yeah. Yeah. They do describe
themselves every day when they call
people skin their skin. Yeah. Yeah. They
still do on your channel.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Really?
Yeah. I don't go I don't watch your live
um all the time, bro. See, I I just work
out now, me, I just work out. I just do
press ups, my dumbbells.
I litally just blast at my workouts now.
That's what I do. Yeah. I do my pups for
my chest. I do my situps for my um six
pack and I do my weights for my arms and
my neck and all that my
back. How it Do you think it's strange
how it took them 13 years? Yeah. to
bring out a new Grand Theft Auto. A long time though.
No, not exactly. Cuz think how long it
took him to bring out GTA 5.
Yeah. How long ago? Yeah, that was like
16 years, was it? It took him years to
bring out GTA 5. Yeah. So, 20 years is it?
And when they did bring out GTA 5, you
couldn't even play online straight away.
Yeah. You couldn't even go online. could
only play multiplayer for ages. That's
it until online. What's your favorite GTA?
I like them all to be honest with you. I
San My San Andreas.
I do like Grand RP. Gr's RP is good.
PGA, which what the Grand RP?
What's that? Gr's RP. Um, it's GTA 5 but
real life where you can work as a
mechanic. You can work as a police
officer, fireman, ambulance driver,
taxi, you can be a tax man. It's more
realistic. You got to actual be a gas
man, electric man to fix stuff. And it's cheap. Yeah.
You get police chases and you get
arrested, you get put in prison and all that lot.
It's more real life. I I play San
Andreas every day. San Andreas,
huh? [ __ ] off PGM, man. Now we're bomb
when they [ __ ] Nintendo 64. Come out, you prick.
Yeah, I remember you used to play
Scooby-Doo as well.
Scooby-Doo [ __ ] Scooby video on PlayStation.
I've never played Scooby-Doo on
PlayStation. Yeah, but you listen, bro.
You don't you you never played a Game
Boy, did you? Yeah, I play game boys. I
used to have a [ __ ] PlayStation the thingy one.
How old do you think I am?
P. Jesus Christ.
I play the Nintendo 64.
What? Go on.
Oh, PJ's connections got a little bit. I
said Vice City was good, wasn't it?
Yeah, Vice City was all right. Yeah, it
weren't that bad. Yeah.
You play Minecraft? You noob?
Never played it in my life.
Yeah, I haven't. I used to love I used
to love Runescape, but I doubt you know
what it is. What? I used to love
Runescape, but I doubt you know what it is. Runescape? Yeah.
Yeah. It's where you got to escape from
rooms and that like panic rooms. You're
You're a [ __ ] idiot, man. Hammer.
Have you never heard of So, what is it,
man? No. Go on. Explain to it. It's
imposs it's impossible to even explain
the game unless you've played it. You
can't It's one of them when you can't
even explain it.
What do you mean? It's too hard to
explain it. Explain a little bit if you
can. Oh, it's like you you start off
Yeah. You have to do quests and you have
to like get skill levels to 99 and you
fight other players and stuff and it's
you'd have to literally play like play
it yourself to actually understand it.
That make sense? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So it's a bit like it's a fireball games
and stuff like that really. Yeah.
Whatever. But it's it's it's not like a
little bit like it's a little bit like
Yeah. You never complete it. That's the
thing. you never um you can never
complete it if that makes sense.
So it's a little bit like Arc Yeah.
where you got a [ __ ] where you got a
survival game kind of thing where you can't Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. It's a good game though.
[ __ ] And what's good about it is it's
hard and there's no cheats and and you
know it's hard bro you know takes time.
Well it's hard is it? Never heard of it. No.
Yeah. What are you doing today?
Uh, can't say much, but we're going out.
Yeah. Don't tell these people anything,
can it? Yeah. Nah. Nah, man. I know. It
end up like cosmic kitty and John West stalking.
Yeah. You reckon Timmy will ever go for YouTube?
No, no. His brain is [ __ ] too much of
a [ __ ] treatment. Let him off
YouTube. This community is [ __ ] It
Yeah, that's why Nat don't come on
anymore. She only makes like a cooking
videos and stuff like that. That's only
what she does. She don't even She can't
be asked with it anymore cuz you're
[ __ ] an idiot. Yeah, I don't I don't
go on um I don't go on Lord J.
[ __ ] off, man. You're always on your You
always texting me. Look, it's the same
people every day. Send your screenshots.
Yeah. Same people, same comments, same remarks.
But it is the same pictures as well.
Yeah. And the same pictures every day.
Yeah. It's just the same shape of this
community. There's nothing new with
them. There's nothing new. What do they
do? or they braid dead or something.
Only what I can think is that they got
bullied in school so they come online
and bully. That's only what I can think
of. Yeah, that's what I that's what I
thought of as well. Or or they could be
gay or something. No, no, no, no. The
way I see it is that these people are
[ __ ] what? Some of these are all
pensioners in the 60s. So, some of them
are in their 50s, 40s.
And because we're younger than them, it
could be that down to Chelsea and all
that lot. Yeah, we got more money than
them as well.
No, not all of his cuz he's got money.
[ __ ] Hilly Billy. He's a young man.
He's got money.
We're better looking than it. Oh,
they've all so he ain't got the
montanity what we've got. Yeah.
Like like that's why they y like calling
everybody [ __ ] pedos or [ __ ] I've
been off of YouTube before for a week.
Share and these people can't take one
day off of YouTube. No, they can't. They
can't. And they call you They call you
for it. But they the ones who ain't got
no live. Yeah. Truth, man.
You remember money when they asked
people to show 20 pound? I say, "Why
don't you show 20 pound?"
Yeah. And they couldn't even show 20
pound. I don't They're so obsessed with
money as well.
I don't know why cuz everybody gets
money. Some people get more, some people
get less. It's a part of life. Some
people are poor and others. It's a shame
that I'm not poor. It's a shame that I'm
in between poor and
poor. Not exactly poor. Not exactly. You
are you you're quite poor.
I am poor. Yeah, of course. Of course
I'm poor. I'm not exactly rich. I don't
have I don't have [ __ ] billions and
billions in my bank.
No, money doesn't make you happy
anyways. And money does not make you
happy anyways. Ask every celebrity out
there who's got money. If they're happy,
they got money. Ask them because most of
the celebrities don't even spend the
money. Most of these celebrities You
know why? You know why? Somebody some
London Taylor said yesterday. Yeah, I
think it was London Taylor. He said
about Oh, uh, even billionaires are not
happy. And I'll explain to you why
billionaires are not happy because they
don't have that stress for money. Part
of life yet, it's you appreciate money,
right? Because obviously it's hard to
get. No, no, no, no, no. So if you win
it, if you're a billionaire, you have
all the money you can have. So that part
of your life, it's not exciting. You
understand? No, it's not. It's not. It's
not big. But do you get my point though?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Show me when
we're ready and we
go. I'm ready anyways, babes. I'm already dressed.
Yeah. It is to do with money. Once you
like you just said, once you got
money, you're not happy with it cuz
you've got it. You can just spend it.
Well, like I still have money
basically. But there's a lot more to it
than that. Yeah.
Like look at the old celebrities now.
Yeah. They don't live in a posh big
house or anything like that. They live
in a normal house. Like course they go
to [ __ ] charity shops and all that. Look. Yeah. Okay.
And they're happy because they they're
not spending their money [ __ ] on
expensive gear like you go boss like
brand clothes and stuff like that. They
don't pay for brand clothes. Most of
these celebrities a lot of them do. You
don't buy Hugo Boss anymore.
Yeah, I know. I don't I don't get it no more.
I used to like your little clothes.
What? I used to like your little clothes.
What? You like liked my clothes are worn. Yeah,
I can get some more. You go, boss. But I
just told me ass with it anymore. It's
[ __ ] It's a [ __ ] m. It's expensive,
isn't it? It's not too expensive. No, is
it? [ __ ] I bought some trainers the
other day. Um, I bought some trainers
and a tracksuit. What? Mate,
a Marty and a night trainers.
Okay. What? You paid 150 or 180? What?
Uh, all together it was like 400.
400 quid. Not too bad then.
No, I got some wipes as well to wipe the
traders, you know.
See, if I was a millionaire. Yeah. If I
had all the money in the world, you know
what I would do? What?
I I give some to the homeless shelters
and stuff like that. What would you give them burgers?
No, give them the
money. That's what I would do if I were
rich. Homeless shelters. I helped the poor out.
I bet you're going to have I bet you're
going to eat macadox today, aren't you?
What I would do is buy a big lot of land
out, get burines on that site, and then
put every single homeless person on
there. Are you going to with those today.
Macadox McDonald's. Yeah, you do it.
No, we don't.
No, we're going into the city. It's
[ __ ] It's not nice. It's [ __ ] It
don't fill you up, man. Oh, Grey. Have
you heard the new GTA 6 is coming out?
So, I'm going to be saving 20 pound a
year until next May when it's released.
And I'm going to buy a TV, the
PlayStation, and the game to play all
the little characters on it.
Yeah. Yeah. [ __ ]
Yeah. But are we ready?
I think we're ready. Yeah.
I'll catch you in a bit. Yeah, PJ. In a bit,
fella. So, yeah, bro. Yeah. I don't know
why you going TJ's been coming out for a
long time. PJ, no, but they were just
they were just rumors.
No, they Well, I'm No, they released it
ago. I've got to go. Yeah. Okay. It's
not full. It's not fun. Right. I'll
catch you in a bit, DJ. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Greasy. So, um, it makes sense to
save 20 a week and then by the time it
releases, you'll have the money to just
buy it outright. You know what I
mean? And it wouldn't see much. So yeah,
new Samson telled, new PlayStation, new
game. What a lovely site. Me lying down
with King playing some Grand Theft Auto
Grezy. What a lovely
site. What a lovely site.
E I woke up at 10:00 today, but I was depressed.
I was uh think 4:00 in the morning, bro.
I was thinking about the dating game in
this country, how it's rigged against
men, how there's nothing you can do to
change it. And I was like, "Oh, I hope I
don't wake up today." And I woke up. So,
yeah, it's it's not about the uh past,
it's about the future. The future is
scary in this country. If you can't
approach people without hearing, I've
got a boyfriend or you can't get into
clubs without paying
1520. It's scary,
bro. How did Monty pull that and still
with her? Um, because she's a skank that
would get with anybody who's even tried getting with
me. Is that supposed to be a valid
argument or a valid
point? cuz she's a scag that would get with
anybody. You know how is it every time
you've done normal approaches, you get
I've got a boyfriend. So yeah, that's
what it is, Greg. It's more about the
future. We could forget the past if the
if the future cuz the future is the part
the past is the future, you
know. No, I can't find one. They've all got
boyfriends apparently, so they say. So
yeah, Greavvesy, the past is pretty much
the future. When the past is uh when the
past will follow your future, it's still very much
relevant cuz it's going to be the same
old [ __ ] That's why if I go out
Saturday, I'm going to go to the the
cinema the next day straight after. So
something to look forward to because if
I don't have anything to look forward
to, I'm not going out because it's just
going to be the same old. You know what I'm saying?
So, yep. Hey, guess what, Simony? Right.
Did Did I had this woman on Reddit say,
"Oh, I've been on negative dates. I've
been on this. I've been on that. I've
been on this." And do you know what I
said? I said, "Yeah, but you don't have
to actively pursue men. Men have to
actively pursue women in order to get a
relationship or to get dates. You just
have to lie around doing nothing and you
get men coming out your ass. coming out
your ass crack. So you if they if these
women Simony walked a day a mile in your
shoes for a day, it would kill them. It
would actually kill them. They have no
clue about anything. They really have
not a clue. You know, they live life on
easy mode. Yeah, they might get weirdos
messaging them. They might get people
that catfish them. These are minor
things. You don't have to actively go
out and pursue women and men to get
dates, you know. You don't have to
actively pursue men to get dates. And
when you do, then come back to me. Then
then when you can when you have to do
that, then come back to me, man. [ __ ]
off. I've been approached four times in
my whole life. And I've probably
approached four million
times. I can't stand him, mate. I really
can't stand him.
So, and then they and they tell you to
go to bars and clubs. Oh, yeah. What?
Cuz you can go to a bar and a club and
get hit on. Because you can go to a bar
and club and get hit on. That means it's
going to work for men. Oh my god. This
is funny, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Bars and
clubs, the things that cost 15, 20 pound
to get into where they miraculously
don't say they have
boyfriends. Yeah. You go to a nightclub,
bro. Miraculously, they're not going to have boyfriends.
Miraculously. Yeah. Yeah. They're going
to suddenly stop saying that. Even
though you're in the same country, in
the same [ __ ]
city, I know I don't get attached to
people. How can I get attached to e evil
people? I went on what I thought was a
date on Sunday. She said she won't date
me because I'm not Muslim. Don't
care. I was getting to like her. Now I
don't care. It is what it is, bro. It's the same [ __ ] So
So it's just the same old mate. But
yeah, you need to stop. They're not all
foreigners though, and they're not all
tourists. They're people that live here.
Some of them are English. Mate, you've
got no chance of anything serious with a
British person. They're the worst.
They're even more stuck up than these
tourists. Why do you think you only get
numbers when you go to central London?
Because they're from It goes by the the
um country that they're from. It goes by
the country that they that that that
that these women are from. All of the
countries that they're from determines
how they are. You know, mate, you got
nothing serious with a British. They're
the worst. They're the worst. Stuck up
their own ass. They're worse than
anybody. That's why whenever you go
central London, the numbers you get is
from a foreigner because they are
literally the [ __ ] worst. You
know, I met this [ __ ] this woman from Pakistan.
Um and um she wasn't obviously born here
and the attitude between her and someone
that's born here is completely different
even if they're from
Pakistan. Do you understand? So you know and that's
it and that's
it. Um if they're from Pakistan and
they're born there, they're westernized.
They're no good. So that's what it is, you
know. Yeah, that's what it is. Because
it's not cuz I'm ugly. That is literally
what it is. That actually is what it is.
It has to be that because there's people
that are on on the same look range as
me, looks range as me. You know, there's
nothing wrong with me. There's nothing,
you know, it obviously is that. Of
course, it's that because what else
could it be? You know, you're not ugly.
You dress good. You're not [ __ ] shy.
So, it it has to be that. There's
nothing else it can
be, you know? There's nothing else it
can be. Cuz my friend in the army, he's
like the same looks range as me and he's
got tattoos and he looks like a prop. He
looks like, you know how them Australian
men look, tan but white. And I'm
thinking, well, that doesn't make any
sense because I'm not getting [ __ ]
anything. And, you know, I'm not [ __ ]
ugly either. So, it has to be that.
There's nothing else it can be. You're
either black or you're white. But rest
be assured, it's not the it's not the
worst race to be. The worst race to be
is uh well, Indian or
Chinese. You know, Chinese, I think it
is Chinese and uh Chinese and Indian is
the worst. Oh my god. If you're one of
them, just leave. Simple.
cuz it doesn't make any sense because
you know you're decent looking. I'm
decent looking. You dress good. You got
money. So there's not really anything
that but your race. There's there's
nothing else it can be which
is it's [ __ ] up but there's nothing
else it can be.
You know, if you go central London, you
get one number in about six on the
street, and they'll either be from
Russia, France, Latvia, or Brazil. It
will never be someone from England. It
So, and people and even the tourists
pretend they got boyfriends as well. So,
I mean, yeah, it's everywhere.
Well, I'm going to I'll be going out
Saturday anyway. So, I I'll just go to
the cinema on
Sunday. So, at least I've got that to look forward
to. So, that's that is what it has to be
that it has to be that. So, that just
goes to show they're [ __ ]
racist. See, I'm not racist, you I I
know a lot about the culture of Muslim
people and people from Pakistan, you
know, having friends and even meeting
that woman. And she said to me, "Oh,
what what what uh what do you find
attractive about someone?" And I said,
"It's very much to do with people's
attitude." You know, I said, "I don't
like westernized people." I didn't say
it in that way, but I said it in a
roundabout way. To me, it's about
attitude and how people literally like,
"Oh, that's a big big big big thing."
And, you know, unless they're from a
third world country, they're always just
going to be [ __ ] You know, I I I
was speaking to this American on
Saturday. Yeah. She looked okay in a bar,
right? Know what I'm saying? and
uh she looks she looks
okay. Um but her whole attitude just
ruin it. Yeah, I'm from Ohio. And it's
just that whole attitude like I can't
explain it. Like it's just the the way
they speak, bro. I know this stuff. I
know. Then it's just like, "Oh, I'm
going home on Sunday." And it's like I
just just walked away. But no, they
should. Yeah, it is racist, man. I'm a
decent looking fella when I've had a
haircut. So it is it is racism. Of
course it's racism,
bro. Just cuz you got a [ __ ] black
beard. Of course it's [ __ ]
racism. I like all kind all races of
women but Chinese. But I'd probably get
with a Chinese and I have been with a
Chinese. I've been with every race
woman. So it is racism. Indian, Brazil,
white, Pakistan. I remember that with somebody from
Pakistan. So they are It is It is It is
racism. What's [ __ ] racism, bro? What the
[ __ ] And the Chinese I would a guy I
already have as well. I said I didn't
really like them, but I would and I
have. So there's not really any way to
like justify it unless the person is
butt ugly. And you're not butt ugly.
No, no, my beard. Don't make me look
like I've just got out of a boat. Just
got from out of a boat. From the boat
because I I go to the
barbers. No, because I go to the
barbers, mate. So, no, it doesn't
because I go to the
barbers. So, that actually show you me
the other day what I was wearing. I look sick, bro. Sit as
[ __ ] Yeah, but my skin's not brown
though. This was me in the Ammani
tracksuit. Oh [ __ ] One
sec. I don't trust you, bro. There's no
there's not one person that's come out
of a [ __ ] boat looking like that.
Come from a boat looking like that,
mate. You know? So, and my skin ain't
even brown. It's just slightly tanned. So, try
again. That's me
anyways. I put [ __ ] on my main channel. So,
yeah. But either way is that.
So, I'd never get rid of my beard again,
bro. Yeah. Okay, bro.
Whatever. Whatever you
say. But it doesn't matter, bro. It's
just the same [ __ ] So, why does Adman
get that? I've got a boyfriend. I've got
a boyfriend. I've got a
boyfriend. Cuz I'm putting it down for
me. It's got to be race. Also, M's
obviously. That's [ __ ] One
sec. I give you
uh No. But Grezy, what do you think
about the new GTA with the little characters?
Grezy. Yeah, but but guess what? He's
not the only one though, is it? There's
certain people on here that's confirmed
answers. not mention any names, but no
one seems to go for
them. So, you can't, you know, there's
loads of people like that even still on
this community, but no one says anything about
them. What's this? An extra £750 payment
from benefits? Nah, can't be. Yeah.
No, Grezy, you've got to get in on the action,
Greavves. You've got to get in on the action,
lad. My foot's hurting again. See my walking. So, yeah. Yeah.
But either way, like they women never
have to pursue men. I might do a I might
do a video about this, you know, dating
video. They never have to pursue men,
but they they try to relate to the
struggles. It's crazy, isn't it,
Grezy? Nope. I'm not shaving my
beard. So, that's that. I like my beard.
Enough of. So, uh, yeah, I'm not saving
it, but yeah, I like how they tried to relate to,
um, relate to the
struggles. No, my beard's fine. It looks
good with my
haircut. We're not going about my looks anyways.
Um, yeah, they tried to relate, but they can't
relate because they they literally have
everything given to them.
So, don't complain why you don't get
many women. I can complain because it's
nothing to do with my beard. And I've
had women again. Um, I've had women and
I can complain because it's not about my
beard. Me shaving is not going to make
me look any more white. So, yes, I can
complain and I [ __ ] will complain
considering I've I've tried more than
anybody in in the whole country. And
it's and I'm complaining about moving
forward. That's what I'm complaining
about. I'm complaining about actually the future now, you
know. Okay, bro. You keep telling
yourself that. Anyways, moving on. Um,
just another like all of this stuff,
right? This whole you've got a beard.
It's just another excuse. The race thing
is true, but the beard thing is an
excuse. You remember when people used to
say, "Oh, you live with your mom." Moved
out from my mom's still having the same
problems. Oh, you have no money. You got
money. Still having the same problems.
It's just another excuse. It's why we
don't we don't take what anything people
say. But the race thing is definitely
the truth. That has got to be it. That's
100% got to be it because there's
nothing else it can
be. So, but no, it's not just a beard
though. It's the whole thing. It's not just a
beard. So what? You think that if I
shave my beard, I'm suddenly going to
stop getting I've got a
boyfriend? I don't think so, bro. I
could try it one day, but I'm very very
I very much doubt it. I very very much
doubt that you're going to stop getting
I've got a boyfriend, but we'll try it, you know.
could have got more women. Uh with a
foreigner, my dad's white whiter than
you. Well, he was white. He's dead now.
Uh my dad's whiter than you and my mom
is actually from England. So, try again
[ __ ] So, uh try again you [ __ ]
[ __ ] My dad was whiter and English
than you would ever be. Try again, which
is why I'm no religion, you [ __ ] ugly
Anyways, yeah. All right. So, if I get
rid of the beard, so if I get rid of the
beard, all of a sudden I'm going to stop
getting I've got a
boyfriend. You sure about that, Joe?
Really? I'm not so sure, man. No, I'm
sure. I'm not so
sure. You will never stop getting I've
got a boyfriend ever. Especially in London.
Never. I've got a pretty good idea.
Yeah. Yeah, I've got a good
idea. Yep. I've got I've got one in
mind. I think I've got an idea that will
solve all of it. I think I've got just
the thing. Give up and leave this
country, which is what I'm doing in 3
years. Try a different Try a different
hairstyle. Already tried a different
hairstyle. Curled my hair. Slick my hair
back. Try again. Who's the foreigner? No one's a
foreigner. And we're not talking about
this, bro. We've just established that
race is the problem. We don't need to
start talking about who's [ __ ]
foreign and who's not. We've already
established this. So, yeah, that's the
that's the that's the idea, Joe. You
give up and you leave the country.
That's that's that's the idea. That's
the idea I've
got. No, I'm going to
Thailand. Nope. Haven't gambled since
when I last spoke to you.
Oh yeah. Yeah. I don't listen to
anything. You also told me to leave my
mom's house and I also know that you
also told me to uh if I moved out my
mom's and I moved out my mom's and nothing changed. Yeah.
Yeah, you're get talking about yourself.
You're getting fat going bored. That's
your life already. You little self
projector. I'm not one% bored, mate.
I've got coals coming out my [ __ ]
eyeballs. Stop talking about yourself.
You're already bored and you're [ __ ]
obese. Stop talking about yourself,
mate. You're getting yourself confused
with me again. You're already bored and
you're already fat. Bye-bye. Now go
self-reflect on another channel. Right.
Little self-reflector. [ __ ] I've got so
many people messaging me at once.
Yeah. But yeah. Oh, there's nothing
wrong with living with my mom. I wish
you told me this a [ __ ] year ago cuz
people were saying to me, "Oh, you need
to move out. your mom's a woman's not
going to go for some dead. These are
just excuses. Everything is an excuse
with these people like your beard, not
having a job or you live with your
mom. It's just another excuse, bro.
You know, it's just the same. Yeah.
Going out pulling girls. Yeah. Going out
here and I've got a boyfriend. Like, you
mean going out here and I've got a
boyfriend? Yeah. You mean going out here
and I've got a boyfriend? That's what
normally happens. Yeah. Going out here
and I got a
boyfriend. No. No. It's literally an
excuse. No, it's literally an excuse. I
got told you live with your mom. No, I
don't live with my mom now. That you
have no money, got money, t and it still
makes no difference. You're still going
to hear I've got a boyfriend. This is
what separates online advice and real
life experience. What you hear on
Reddit, what you hear on YouTube, it doesn't
um you know, a clean shaven look with
less. No, no, no. I got better luck with
the sports clothes. I got be I got uh
No, they don't have boyfriends. No, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no. The whole point
is that they don't have boyfriends. And
I'm not going to get into this again. I
know they don't have boyfriends. I'm not
going to explain to you again how I know
they don't have boyfriends. Right?
That's it. Like, I'm not I'm not getting
into this debate again. Boring. Agree to
disagree. And also, I I got better when
I used to wear
tracksuits, you know. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. You do way better in
sports clothes. Way better. You do way
better in sports clothes than you do
dressing smart. And I know this. Uhuh.
I'm not getting into this, bro. I'm not
getting into this conversation
again. And I think Joe knows why. Uh,
how do I know they don't? Bro, I'm not
going to answer you. I'm not going to
get into this
again because no matter how many times I
explain it, you still ask the same
question. So, there's no point. Yeah.
Agree to disagree.
Nope. I done way better way better with
wearing tracksuits. Way better with
trainers. When you go out dressing
smart, you just get I've got a boyfriend
like multiple times. I know, mate. Trust
me. I've been up and down the
country. Okay. Anyways, moving on now. Moving
on. Yeah, I'm a foreigner in a track
with a beard. Why you can't pull west
guys? Anyways, moving on now. So,
yeah, there's no point explaining the
boyfriend thing, Joe, because no matter
how many times um you explain it. Do you
want me to explain it again, Joe? The
boyfriend thing? Should we have the same boring conversation
again? Yeah, you need to find courses as
well, bro. Speak for yourself. You're
still a virgin. I'm just not scared to
say what I think. But you're still a
virgin. But I I'm not scared to say what
I want, what I know and what I think.
Even though I've been with women, I'm
not scared to say what I think. I'm not
a virgin like you. So maybe apply that
to yourself. Explain it to you. Okay.
You've been married. Of course you have.
Is it mad how the married the the the
marriage um rate has gone down, but
everyone on YouTube is married. Of
course you are. Lewisville Slugger.
Lewisville Slugger. It's this little
[ __ ] again. It's that Lewisville
Slugger. It's the same [ __ ] that's
been doing this on YouTube for years.
Okay, I'll explain this. It's that
spacker again in mommy's basement. Oh, I
just clocked. He's gave himself away
again. There we go. Lewis Phil Snugger,
when are you going to come off of
YouTube and [ __ ] leave your mama's
basement and finally get laid and stop
doing this [ __ ] year in year out? So,
you want me to explain it to you? Okay,
I'll explain it to you. So you got 75
80% of men that are struggling to date
and a lot of single people out there
that people are not even people that are
not even struggling to date but they're
just single. We got a huge high
population of single people you come
across you meet yet 95% of women are
claiming that they've got boyfriends.
That adds the the maths does not add up
that. And where are their boyfriends
when they're clubbing until 3 4 5:00 in
the morning? At home by themsel eating
popcorn. I don't know about you, Joe,
but that's not looking right to me. So
what? Jack the lad has come from work on
a Friday, Saturday night, sat home all
by himself watching the telly while his
girlfriend is clubbing until 600 7:00 in
the morning. The boyfriend that she's
never with. I'm sorry. I ain't [ __ ]
buying it. You know, you go all over
Facebook, right? You see the amount of
single people, single people, single
people, single people, single people.
You know, you got feminists nowadays,
women that don't even bother with men,
but yet all these women claim they've
got boyfriends. It's not looking
right. As a as a as a as a fella would
say, it's just it's just it's facts, you
know. You know, you got you got people
you got people that come from another I
had one Joe. She come from New Zealand.
She said she was working here, but
apparently she has a boyfriend. And you
didn't come with your boyfriend. So, you
love your boyfriend so much. You come
from the other side of the world. You
come from the other side of the world,
right? But your boyfriend is not with
you. Wow. Could have loved him that
much, could you? If you didn't bring him
along with you. That's if he ever That's
if he actually
existed. But yeah, anyways, I'm not
going to get into it. I know they're
bullshitting about the boyfriend thing,
bro. It's not a debate. I have my
opinion. You have yours, you
know, and they don't have boyfriends.
Um, and they don't have boyfriends.
There's no way their boyfriend is never
with them. Their boyfriends are never
ever with them. People that actually
have boyfriends or with them in the
clubs, they don't have boyfriends. It's
a boring conversation. It's a boring topic.
You know, stop [ __ ] talking [ __ ] No
one is letting their girlfriend club
until 3, four, 5:00 in the [ __ ]
morning while they're in bed by themsel.
It doesn't even make sense, you
know? [ __ ] boyfriend. Come on, man.
It's boring now.
No, it's not about right or wrong. I
have you. You have your opinion. I have
my opinion. That's it. I've just told
you logically how they don't have
boyfriends and and you're still arguing
with me. So, I have my opinion and you
have yours. Simple. I know they don't.
I'm leaving this country. End of.
Simple. So, it's not about only doing
the things I did. I I did.
No one's clubbing to [ __ ] fight, bro.
I'm not even talking about this no more,
bro. End of. You're not You're always
going to think women are right, right?
Like, there's no point me arguing with
you, bro, cuz you're just going to argue
with anything I say. I just told you a
good statistic and and and and a logical
thing, and you're still arguing with me,
okay? Every woman in the country that
says she has a boyfriend has a
boyfriend. Okay? They've all got
boyfriends. Even though they're [ __ ]
slagging it about to 5, 6:00 in the
morning and their boyfriend's never with
them and they travel abroad by
themselves and they're here for months,
but apparently they've got a boyfriend
back home. Okay, these women have all
got boyfriends. Are you happy? Like, I
don't know what you actually expect. We
get into a debate, we disagree with each
other, and then you're still trying to
convince me when I know this [ __ ]
because I've not had to work for years.
So, I know how these women are. I've had
to deal with these women. I know the
[ __ ] that they do. I know the [ __ ] that
say. Do you know what I'm
saying? She said she was married. When
When was that? There's been a few
times. Yes. Which is what I'm trying to
explain. They don't have boyfriends.
[ __ ] Dimwit. Which is what But then
they will moan that they can't find a
normal decent guy. They're [ __ ]
Anyways, I'm not going to talk about
them anymore. I don't I want to stop
talking about them. It's just negative.
So, I just want to stop talking about
them now. So, that's
it. But yeah, you've traveled all the
way from New Zealand to to come here for
work, but yet you got a boyfriend back
home. Bit far, is it? But anyways, we'll
keep our opinions to
oursel. Anyways, moving on now. I'm not
talking about this anymore. So, yeah.
I'm not talking about this anymore
because we're go we're going back and
forth, back and forth, back and forth.
We're having the same argument. We're
having the same argument over and over
and over again. And and in my opinion, I
would know. I would know. Well, you know
why you don't I don't sound like anyone
I know? Because I'm I'm nowhere near 28
and I'm nowhere near 30. That's why I
don't sound like anyone, you know,
because I'm not their [Laughter]
ages, mate. All of this, right? Let me
let me tell you something. I love your
name, by the way, on YouTube. All of
this, you're nearly 30. It's just you
trying to make yourself feel better
about the fact that you're in your 40s.
All of this like, oh, you're almost 30.
No, no, no, no, no. It's to try to
escape the fact that you are already in
your 40s, literally, and you're trying
to make yourself feel better. It's like
when you gain a bit of weight, you know,
whatever, and they're like, "Oh, you're
you're you're gaining weight because you
you want you need validation that
somebody is almost becoming like you,
fat, ugly, old." Bro, think about it,
bro. How old are you? Tell everybody how
old you are. No, 27 is nowhere near 30.
They're three years apart. No, it's
nowhere near 30. How old are you
anyways? Let's Let's hear about your age.
Let's hear about your age. Come on.
age. You're 31. No, you're not. You're
no 31. I'm going to hang out right now
and prove that you're 31. You're nowhere
near 31. Hell to the [ __ ] know you're
31. You are not no [ __ ] 31. No
[ __ ] way with the way that you are
typing, mate. You're in your [ __ ]
probably late 30s, [ __ ] 40s and
you're trying to tell somebody that
they're almost 30. See you later, buddy.
Go seek attention on another channel. So
yeah, bye-bye. You are not [ __ ] 0
[ __ ] 31. Jesus Christ. No way. Are
you Leville Slugger?
You know, that's that's got to be one of
the most annoying things is how do you
know they know that boyfriends? How do
you know they know that boyfriends? God,
it's so annoying having to explain the
same thing over and over and over and
again. You know what I'm
saying? How do you know they don't have boyfriends?
to my friend. But I just like to go
outside and [ __ ] hurt someone,
bro. Just go outside and hurt someone.
Yeah. And that's
that. Yeah. Well, you've got no
experience, so bye-bye now. Yeah, that's
good. But you don't have no experience,
so because think about it, right? You
need to you need to look at this. These
people don't have no life experience
with money, with women, with work. I'm
literally out meeting people all the
time. So, I would know more than
anybody. I would know more than anyone.
I've not had to work in [ __ ] 3, four
years. I would know more than
anybody. I would know more than anybody
how these things work. I think I'm a
good candidate to to know how these
things work and how these women work.
You know what I'm saying? I know. I know
these things cuz yeah, I've I've gone
out and and all of these people that
claim they've got life experience, I
have met way more women than they have.
Way more women than they would ever have
because I've been doing it for
years whilst they've been at home or
they've been at work. So, I I I know
more than these people 100%. 100
million%. 100 million%. Remember how
many people I have approached? [ __ ]
Yeah, there we go.
Saturday. No doubt.
Yeah, these people really no life
experience. It's actually quite
sad. These people are [ __ ] major, bro. Major self [Music]
projectors. No. Anyways, I'm gone. I'll
be back later.