Yeah, this Donald and go to sleep. I
think that's my day sorted.
That's my day sorted. Reckon back to the
old depressive ways. Where's thingy
on to the old depressive ways? Eh,
nothing ever changes. Not long term
anyways. I start switching on people
when I get like this in one of these
episodes. Yeah, I
do. I really really really really
do. You don't understand, mate. I know
my [ __ ] temper. You know what I'm saying? Yeah. coming
anyways and I probably won't even eat
again today. Lost my
appetite this whole approach and [ __ ] I
know it gets you in
it. But people go on like it's so innocent
and you know what I'm saying?
Yeah. Yeah. That's what they call back.
Yep. Life will never change, man. Long
term. What? Long term, mate.
Half an hour for [ __ ] McDonald's.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm getting these mood swings
again. I'm starting to fall out with
people again. All because of these this
approach and [ __ ] and these [ __ ] women.
Well, I'm going to end up going out and
hurting someone. But I swear to God, I'm
going to end up going out and hurting
someone. I'm not even joking. I'm going
to really end up going out and hurting
someone. get myself in some serious
trouble. You know, I can't be dealing
with this [ __ ] anymore, bro. What the
[ __ ] Year in, year out, year in, year
out, year in, year out, year in, year
out. You know what I'm saying, bro? What the actual [ __ ] You
know, it's like torment and torture. I'm
going to eat this McDonald's. I'm going
to go sleep. Hope I don't wake up. Or
maybe I don't wake up for like a whole
year. Maybe that'll be a good thing if
you don't wake up for like a whole
year. Yeah, when GTA is
out. God can't stab being awake. I'm
like this. You know, sometimes when I
get into these moods, these episodes, I
don't even like being awake. That's why
I sleep. You
know what else is there to do? Greasy.
It's the truth. All you're ever going to
keep hearing about is Blake Mill
boyfriends. You're going to have the
same experiences. A negative future
awaits you. What's there to look forward
to? Nothing is ever positive. It's
always the same old. I'm trying to
explain this to Antman and he thinks
it's funny. I don't think he thinks I'm
being serious. I'm being serious. I actually
am. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
I don't want to eat this McDonald's and
go to sleep and not wake up. I don't
wake up for a year. At least a
year. That would be [ __ ]
amazing. I have to hear about make
boyfriends again. I have to deal with
[ __ ] Oh, I'll be in heaven.
Yeah. One second. Someone sent me something.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] evil, man. I just ordered some
McDonald's. I just ordered some
Yeah, they blocked you on Reddit as
well. They tried to dig, oh, answer my
questions. Answer my questions. Yeah,
you're the one that's [ __ ] ignoring
me. Oh, wow. That's block
me. Well, I'm going to have this
McDonald's and go sleep when it comes
and hope you don't wake
up. That'll be the ideal thing. [ __ ]
this [ __ ] every week in this [ __ ]
country. It's why I gave up to get away
from it. It's why I stopped for a month
to get away from it. Practice to get
away from this
[ __ ] to get away from it
all. It's boring as
[ __ ] So boring. So so so boring. If
only you knew how boring it [ __ ] is.
You know what I'm saying? Like
jeez. And it's never going to change as
well. That's the thing. It will never
change in this country. Just it will
never change. That's the main thing is
it will never change. Never ever ever
change. Same train, same
weather, same country, same weather,
same atmosphere, same make believe
boyfriends. Hey, let me ask you this
question, Cactus. People always ask me,
how do you know they don't have
boyfriends? How would you answer that? I
answer it as 70 80% of men are single.
And why would someone's boyfriend let
them out, let their girlfriend out till
4 or 5:00 in the morning
dubbing? I think that pretty much sums
it up. Really, they ain't got [ __ ]
boyfriends. They ain't got [ __ ]
boyfriends at all. Not a chance, mate.
Half these women are [ __ ] femist.
Feminists, but they all got
boyfriends. No, I don't think
so. No, I don't think
so. Well, [ __ ]
Yeah. All that [ __ ] Absolute
[ __ ] I don't know how you would
explain it, but that's how I explain it. That's my
logic that they're never with them. 75
80% of men are
single. They're never with
them. It just doesn't seem to make a lot of
sense, you know? for when somebody
traveled from New Zealand and they're
here working and then claiming that they
got a boyfriend back at home. So, you
love your boyfriend so much you left
them all the way New Zealand. I mean,
the examples can go on and on and on and
on and on and on and on. You
know, I was getting some dark thoughts
yesterday, bro. some really really dark
thoughts to just go out and do a
madness. Just to go out and do a [ __ ]
madness, mate. And you'll have seen me
on the [ __ ] news. I've had enough of
it. Really had enough of it. Like proper
it. You know what I mean? bad, you
know. Yeah. Then they've got this and
then you got these people on Reddit that defend
them. Oh, you're still
young. No, no, no, no, no. [ __ ] off,
man. Suck my [ __ ] dick, son. [ __ ]
off. You know what I'm saying?
sick of [ __ ] hearing
that. [ __ ] off,
man. It's so scary. Cact is what the
future's like. The future's scaring me.
I'm thinking, [ __ ] if we can't get into
a club without spending 20 pound and we
can't stop hearing about make
believe, we're destined for a very
lonely future, aren't
we? Yep. We're destined for a very very
lonely future if every woman is stuck up
in evil up their own asses pretend they
got boyfriends [ __ ] club [ __ ]
charging god knows how much to get in.
It doesn't look good does it? It's quite
scary. I'm kind of scared. Yep.
That's it. I'll be going to sleep after this. Um, just
McDonald's. We're in self harming mode
now, aren't we? Self harming mode.
Yeah, because of social
media. Oh, Cactus. I had this uh this
woman tried to say, "Oh, I've been on
bad dates. I've been on bad dates."
Yeah, but have you had to actively
pursue men? Have you had to go around
the street approaching men? Have you had
to approach men in nightclubs? Thought
not. really didn't think so. Yeah,
exactly. Do not try to [ __ ] even try
to relate to me. Don't even try to
me. Do not even [ __ ] try to relate to
me. You know, I take I take offense to
that. [ __ ] off, silly little [ __ ] And
then they and then they'll start naming
some minor flaws. Oh, well, we have to
deal with creeps or people that only
want sex or catfishes. Okay. And your
point is, do you have to go up and down
the country to approach the men? No, you
do not. Shut up then, you stupid little
[ __ ] Yeah. How is anything that they
say the same? Huh? [ __ ]
idiots. But it was the other way around.
E. But the maddest thing is even though
it's it's I it's rigged against men, right?
Even though it's rigged against men,
um, which it is rigged against men, even
though it's rigged against men, you
still don't get what you want even when
you put the effort in. That's the [ __ ]
up thing about it. It's not that it's
like it's rigged against men and then,
oh well, whoever wants a relationship,
they have to go out and get it cuz you
still get the same [ __ ] You will still
get the same [ __ ] even when it's
harder. So, it's tries to [ __ ] you in
the ass, is it?
No, I wouldn't, Cactus. Nah, I would
have met somebody when I least expect
it. You know, I'm still young, so they
say. They said that when I was 15 as
well, you're still young. Nah, I would
have been a kiss this date this
virgin. Nah. Nah, you meet people when
you least expect it. You meet people
through friends. Other guys did it.
Yeah. Do you know what I So, I I was in
the Weather Spoons,
right? Uh the other day, and it was one
that I go to a lot, so I didn't want to
get banned for it. I was about to jump
on the [ __ ] table, Bob, and be like,
"At man, other guys do it." Cuz he kept
cuz he kept going on about other guys,
other guys. When he used to get drunk, I
said, "Other guys do it today." And I
was going to just shout the whole
[ __ ] pub down the street, bro. I
swear to God. Yeah. If I was in a
different pub, I would have done it. I
swear to God.
[ __ ] madness, bro. [ __ ] other
people that are never [ __ ] you, eh?
They are completely different to [ __ ]
you. [ __ ] other
people. Such a lame attempt to try to
make a valid argument. Oh, well, it's so
lazy as well, Cactus. Very
lazy. What do you think? Very, very,
very lazy. It's so lazy as
well. Have you noticed it? It's so
[ __ ] lazy. You know, oh, other people
do it, do they? You know what I'm
saying? Other people do it. You know
what I'm saying? So, it's like it's just
lazy. Grievy. Very
lazy. Nope. Nope. Only once from a
dating app. Uh, maybe two. Well, I met
two from a dating app. One was crazy and
one was Yeah. That just goes to show you
that it doesn't matter about other
people. It does not matter about other
people, you know,
cuz Yeah. You go from my
experiences, you know, it's always been
from approaching. So that tells me that
I'm going to do a video about this
dating games rigged against
men. Yeah. I'm going to I'm going to do
another video on this. I'm going to let
the whole of [ __ ] Reddit
though. This is why I gave up,
Cactus. This is exactly why I gave up
for a month cuz I didn't want to get
into this again. This is exactly why I gave
up. This is exactly why I gave up
because of this [ __ ] Because of this
[ __ ] you know? I'd rather just be
by myself than have these migrings. You
know what I'm saying? you know.
Yeah. Yeah. It's crazy, is
it? No. USA.
Yeah. There's another one as well.
You're missing two
people. I wish I I wish I just stayed
giving up, bro. I wish I just stayed
giving up. Honestly, was I just stay giving up,
bro. This is the problems it was going
to cause again. You
know, having to go out and do it all over
again. All over
again. Dude, a lot again.
It will never change. This country will
change. Never, never, never, never,
never. Been there, done it, won a t-shirt.
Yep. Where the [ __ ] is my McDonald's?
I'm [ __ ] starving. And I want to have
my boss in McDonald's
wheezy. Yeah. And you know the maddest
thing is it's never going to change. I
could forget the past if there was a
positive future, but your past dictates
your future. When it comes to this,
right, you know how they say, "Oh, you
never know um what the future holds." I
do because it's the same thing every
week. I do because it's a replica of every
week, you know? So I know because it's
been happening for years. It's been
happening for weeks, weeks, years,
months. It will never ever ever ever
ever change. Your past dictates your
future. Do you
understand? It's so scary, bro. You
know? Um, no, I haven't tried it. And
it's not even that one that I met on
Sunday. that weren't even that bad to be
honest cuz I had nothing better to do.
Went for a walk, went for some food with
someone. I didn't really lose anything.
But it's the whole Saturday. What
happened Saturday as well, you know,
numbers, not replying, same old [ __ ]
same old make believe friends. Boring,
boring, boring, boring, boring,
boring, you know.
Yeah, never will
change. I think I'm not going to go out
this week, bro, for my own sake. I think
Yeah, you would have thought by now this
would have all ended,
Greasy. You would have thought this all
would have just ended by
now. We've been through this before. We
got the mood swings. We tried again. And
then we This should be
finished. Daylight robbery. You think
buying two pairs of night shields £70 is
daylight robbery? I bought a tracksuit
and trainers cost me
£400. This should have stopped by now.
Why are we still dealing with this? You
know, if women are really as different
as people say, when is all of this going
to end? That's my question. You know, we
heard a certain virgin say, "You don't
know all women when I know [ __ ] more
than him." Right? [ __ ] virgin. So,
when is this all going to end?
Because we we we've grown up with this
now. Yeah. We've been going through this
for a very very long time. Stuck up
people pretending they got boyfriends.
It's boring now. You
know, you know, it's not doing the same
thing over and over again. It's doing
the It's doing the only thing you can
do. Isn't that right, Cactus? It's not
It's not doing the same thing over and
over and over and over and over again.
It's doing the same It's doing all you
can do over again. It's doing all that you can
do. Unless you want to go on dating apps
and get trolled and get nowhere. Unless
you want to try to make friends and
maybe meet somebody through a friend,
which is never going to happen. It's
literally all you can
do. You know, you're doing all you
actually could have done and all you're
getting is to say make
believe. Real life advice. Um, online
advice don't match real life experiences.
Yeah, it will never change. Never [ __ ] change,
mate. Never ever ever change. I was
doing all right, you know, the past couple of
weeks, you know, just like when they say
you meet people through friends.
[ __ ] Absolute [ __ ] They make
this tactus. They make it sound like
it's so easy. This whole dating thing.
Yeah, I told him I was going to block
him, you know. You know, the only reason
I'm not blocking him is because um he's
going to Thailand um tomorrow, so he's
not going to be talking about it
anymore. I said, "Bro, I'm going to
block you. Stop talking to me about
other people. How other people do this,
other people do that."
Yeah. But he's going to Thailand
tomorrow and he's not coming back. So I
said, "I will end up blocking you. I
swear to God." Yeah. They make dating
sound like it's way easier than it is.
You understand, Cactus? They make it
seem like it's so much more easy than it
actually is. Like you're not going to go
out and deal with make
believe. Yeah, of course he does.
Obviously he does. But it's more like a windup
thing. Yeah, but it's just a
windup. But it doesn't make me suffer.
How can that make me
suffer? He's the one that's happened to
go to Thailand before me.
Who said that man
skin? I never said that man
skin. Need to stop using that word as
well, buddy. Oh, we got six minutes. At
least we get to munch on some McDonald's
and get really fat in it,
Greasy. No, I don't think I can go out
next week, bro.
Yeah, you need to stop coming on my
channel and trying to
troll cuz you're bad at it. You need to
stop coming on YouTube trying to troll
people. I'm not Timmy or I'm not Timmy
or Monty Man. I've said this about a
million times. I'm not Timmy and I'm not Monty
Man. Remember that before you keep
coming on my
channel. Yep. Got a nice um cheese steak burger.
No, I'll never go a beast,
mate. Yep. Right. I can't even bother to
move, mate. I'm going to end up like
agobic, man. I can't even move.
Yep. I wish I could go out next week,
but I don't think I can hack it, bro.
This week. Next week. This week.
What is it? What's the
code? The [ __ ] are these [ __ ] One
second. Where is
he? Where the [ __ ] are these [ __ ]
That's what I was saying in the [ __ ]
pub yesterday. Uh, the other day, bro, I
was waiting for my friend
Reevesy. Here we go. The 30 thing again.
Boring. Change the
subject. The The 30 thing is getting
boring now. You're getting close to 30. It's
boring. Sending me to
sleep. One second, mate.
You need to leave this country before
you [ __ ] What's the
code? That's a stupid code. Malarkey, man. 0003. [ __ ] lost. [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah. So, I'm going to be saving up for
this. Please don't be told. Please don't
Almost always come as [ __ ]
cold. Well, this [ __ ] Yes.
I don't give a [ __ ] bro. I'm done with my
life. I don't give a
[ __ ] I don't care if I gain weight. I
don't care. I'm going to need to heat
this up somehow, won't
it? Cuz I can't eat it like this, bro.
[ __ ] cold ass [ __ ] One second. Let me warm up
somehow. I didn't give a [ __ ] but I
don't give a [ __ ] about
living. You know what I'm saying? I don't
care. I just eat like this. I can't be bothered. Mad
downstairs. I don't give a [ __ ] about
life. That's how I get
you. I was way better a couple of weeks
ago and I gave up. Yeah.
Bro, you need to stop going out the 30
thing. It's getting boring as
well. You're almost 30. You're almost
30, bro. It's getting boring now. Stop
it. I went downstairs, bro. It's getting
boring now. Respectfully, it's getting
really, really, really boring. What? [Music]
I'm going to get so
fat that people are going to want to
hold um people going to have to carry me
to to to leave the house.
They're going to have to carry me to
actually leave the house cuz I'll be that fat.
Mhm. That's not bad.
Yeah. I love McDonald's coast. It's like taking
crack. Don't know what crack taste
tastes like, but it's nice. Nice
macadox. Imagine that. Nice TV. Nice PlayStation. Nice.
Um nice um McDonald's.
M king eating
McDonald's. Nice brand new telly. Nice
PlayStation. Nice grand
filter. That is what you call a lovely site, mate.
I don't even have king anymore. If I had
king, he'd cheer me
up. He would just be lying next to me.
No. It It ain't it, but it is what it
is. Why is that leing like that?
Yeah, it's not the one, but unfortunately it is. Mhm.
Yep. Nothing you can do about
it. I I just think it's so scary, bro.
It's just so scary.
Honestly, it's so scary. But I'm scared of the
future. Some people say that
like you don't know what the future
holds and stuff, but with women, you
do. You do know what the future holds
because it's the same every
week. It's always the same with them.
So, you do know what it holds because
something's not going to miraculously
happen now. This has been going on for years. Yeah.
It's not going to miraculously just
change now after 3 years or four years
whatever cuz if you see over the years
things have changed like your financial
circumstances loads of things seem to
have changed Grezy but this stays the
same you know I have a boyfriend I can't
be with it you No, you
can't. Cuz my friend from Italy, he
says, "Oh, that's why he doesn't anymore
because he can't be bothered. I can't I
can't be bothered with I've got a
boyfriend." That's the same as me.
That's the same as me. I laughed when he
said it, but it's not funny when it
happens even to other people. I don't
even like watching it. I don't even like
watching the videos. That's why I don't
watch the videos no more cuz it's just
boring. It's It's
repetitive. You're always going to get
I've got a boyfriend. No.
Always always, mate.
Always. I just got some milk and [ __ ]
It's always the
same. Yeah. How much longer do you have
to keep trying? Yeah. I know you're
mocking me, right? But I don't mind when
you're doing it blatantly. I just don't like people
like Lewis Phil Snugger that thinks he's
smart when he's just a spatnic. That's
the people I don't like when you have
people like him go on like a million one
accounts cuz he ain't got a life and
he's got no friends. Um and he tries to do it discreetly
discreetly. Um that's the [ __ ] I was
like, "Bro, I'm not Monty Man or Timmy.
Please, you're not in control. Get off
of YouTube and get a life.
You know what I'm saying? Get off of
YouTube and get a
life. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
[ __ ] is [ __ ] expired.
What would happen if I went out on Saturday?
Cus was an Indonesian
fella. Right. That was the Indonesian fella. Indonesian
fell. The girls are waiting for
you. Remember that, bro. The girls are
waiting for you.
Yeah. Waiting for them to say they got boyfriends. Maybe. Yeah,
maybe. But that's about
it. That's about it, lad. Yeah.
What will happen if I do some approaches Saturday,
lad? Bro, I'd rather have no sex than
have sex with [ __ ]
her. No, he wouldn't have a girlfriend
if he was in Thailand because he's not
white. The only people that are
cherished in Thailand is white
westernized men. So, actually, he
wouldn't he would actually struggle in Thailand.
I'd rather have no sex than have sex with
her. So, what did USA do then, Cactus?
Yeah, I was thinking of doing madnesses,
but I don't want to go to prison. That's the
thing. That's the thing,
matey. And man's gone to prison.
Yeah, but didn't she say she was going
to show me
around? English women are [ __ ]
stinking. What are you talking about?
Them throwing women. Throwing women are
way better than English women. English
women are [ __ ]
mutters. There's way better [ __ ]
women out there than English women.
They're [ __ ] m English women are
munters. Are you [ __ ] mad? They're mters, mate.
Yeah, but what did she say? Um, Cactus,
that she told me to come to America, Cactus, or what? You know,
[ __ ] yeah, Thai women are not
attractive. [ __ ] every [ __ ] race
is better than [ __ ] English. Indian, Pakistan,
Spanish, [ __ ] anything is better than
English. Anything is be anything is
better than English, bro. Um is better
English. My favorite is Indian, but
they're just too hard to
get, you know? Well, it's better than
[ __ ] staying here and here and I've
got a [ __ ] boyfriend, isn't it? If I
pick I' I'd pick Indian me any day any
day of the week. Indian for sure.
They're too hard. [ __ ] English ones
are not the one, bro. You
mad. But you won't get with one of them. Nah. Nah,
mate. But they're all evil. Deep down
they're all evil. 27 years in counting
cactus. A fella once said to me when I
was 17, "You don't know all women. You
don't know all women." So, I was like,
"Maybe you're right." So, I've gone out,
I've lived life, and
yep, same uh same old women are still
all the same. Yet to be proven
wrong. Yep. I'm yet to be proven
wrong. Yep. 27 years in
counting. 27 years in
counting. I know all women. I know more
[ __ ] women than [ __ ] you. You [ __ ] virgin
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying? Cactus.
I know more women than you. You [ __ ]
virgin. My voice is [ __ ] strong, is
it? Yeah, [ __ ] virgin
Yeah, it's the truth though, is it? I do
know more [ __ ] women than that
virgin. Been with more women, had more
women, spoke to more women, and they
literally are all the same. But
yeah, I'm just done with it all now,
bro. Really am. Yeah,
man. Got some macaroni to choose for
later. I can just put in the microwave. So,
How did he manage to do that? Go and ask him,
mate. Yeah, go and ask him. I'm going to
have a bath here, I
think. Why the [ __ ] is this leaking, bro?
Yep. Yeah. I'm going to run myself a bath anyways
and get it. Yeah.
Where was that leaking from, bro? Where
the [ __ ] is that leaking
from? I'll be about later.