That is
smooth. Person in [ __ ] Canada, man.
Defending women. [ __ ] [ __ ]
pathetic making up to excuses and
defending women. I never thought it. I
never I didn't expect it from this
person. I really didn't, bro.
Nobody has anything to say
there. Oh man.
[ __ ] hell. Any excuse to defend
women? I expected it [ __ ] I expected
different from this person. Wow. Same on
you, man. defending
women [ __ ] making up
stuff. Making up excuses [ __ ]
pathetic. Honestly, it
is. I think she didn't like the fact
that I was calling it women from Canada
saying westernized [ __ ] It's the truth
though. I was watching some reals before
I fell asleep on Instagram. I was
watching some approaching video or some
of them just come up and who the [ __ ] do
these [ __ ] think they are? I was
listening to some of them from
America. So [ __ ] rude, man. I was
scrolling through these videos. Who the
[ __ ] do they think they are, mate? You know,
really using someone's reaction as the
cause. Well, but she never said anything
about women, which is strange.
I don't even know what what what I said
that was so
wrong. I said I'm getting nasty mooings
because of them.
And she was like, "Funny how when women
try to rel I said, "Funny when women try
to relate when they've had everything
given to them their whole life on easy
mode. I don't think I said anything
wrong. It's the truth." And then she
starts making excuses up for women
again. Coming up with the most ridiculous
things. They was like, "No woman does.
The girls aren't coming up with excuses.
They are they are meeting you finding
your horrible personality to be
offputting which doesn't make any sense
because they don't know me or my
personality before they give me attitude
and then they say they can tell that you
hate women so why on earth would they
want to spend time with you? Uh no you
hate women after you've had bad
experiences with women which is the the
only way around that would make sense.
You hate them because of how they are towards
you not for no reason. So again, trying
to defend women and make excuses for
them and then just just back to
defending women as usual as what most
people do. So that's why you can't ever
really get advice, man, because they just defend
women. So So you wake up one day. I said
to her, "Shame on you, man. I feel I
felt better for you." You know, I was
like, "Man, I actually expected better
from you. You know, we've been speaking for
years." You know what I'm saying?
Wow. And you're just defending women. So
you wake up one day and you decide to
hate women for no
reason. Or you decide to hate men for no
reason. That makes sense, doesn't it?
Yeah. So you wake up one day and think,
I'm going to hate on men today. I'm
going to hate on women today. Just think
about how ridiculous that sounds for one second.
No, you hate them because of your
experience. Because of your experiences
with them, which is the only thing that
would make sense. You know what I'm saying,
bro? No. Some women in
Canada. Yeah. some woman in
Canada trying to say trying to make up
excuses as my p same old [ __ ] when they
try to say it's your personality and
when it's ridiculous because I've got
approaching videos where I've not said
more than one or two words and they
pretended they got boyfriends. I've got
conversations where they have said
they're going to meet and then all of a
sudden they disappear. So this whole
personality thing is getting old now.
You know, we all know they don't go for
personality and it's just a madeup thing
that somebody on the internet came up
with. They just make excuses for them every
time. Sad it.
So yeah, bro, they just defend them in
any way they possibly
can. You never hear about them being
stuck up. You never about about hear
about them being time wasters. You never
hear about this stuff when in reality
that is what they are. You know, they
just sit there and defend them and
defend them and defend them.
Yeah. All they do is defend
them. I was like, "Shame on you, man.
We've been speaking for about 3 years
and you go back to defending these westernized
women." Wow. None of them because they
don't know my name. Nice try.
Okay. None of them because they don't know my
name. They don't know my name. They
don't know my full
name. And I was with a woman on Sunday.
So yeah, she's just makes excuses for um
women. I was like, I actually I expected
more from you,
man. They don't know my full
name. So, and they don't even know my
first name. So, try
again. Nope. It's I'm not linked to
Instagram or or
Snapchat. So, none of
them. Yeah, none of them. Cuz I've had
people meet me. I was thinking that at
first, but then I've had people meet me.
So, it can't be
that. It can't be that because I've had people meet
me. Obviously, they've met me and then
they've stayed in contact. So,
obviously, it can't be that. It would
make no sense.
No, it's not like that,
matey. And that's why most them reject
you in person. They don't even know
looked your name up. I can't stand
women. I expected more from this [ __ ]
one in Canada.
Yeah, it is what it is though, man.
Yeah. But yeah, it ain't that
anyways. Yeah, she defends
women. Yeah, she they just defend women
no matter what evidence you show them.
So there's just no point. She's like,
"But nobody would hate women for no
reason." That's what I'm trying to say.
Nobody would hate anyone for no reason.
It's them and their attitude and their
time wasting which makes people hate
them. But she doesn't understand it.
They're [ __ ] rude as [ __ ] I was
watching these approaching videos. I
weren't even looking for approaching
videos. They come up on Instagram when you scroll.
If any of them spoke to me that I would
have gave them a [ __ ] thick hair,
mate. I'm telling you that [ __ ] now.
Yeah. Yeah. They just make excuses for women.
Uh, mate, there's been loads of
examples. There have been loads of
examples, bro. What do you mean there
was an example? There's been plenty of
examples. There's not just been one
example. This has been happening for
years. This [ __ ] has been happening for
[ __ ] years. Am I lying?
No. Yep. Yeah. They m they all do
this. So it's they all reply to
negativity. They all they all um reply
to uh negative messages, bro. They all
do this every
time. I hate him, bro. [ __ ] hate him.
with a [ __ ] passion. With a class A
passion. I hate them, bro. I hate
them. You really don't
understand how much I hate them. The
whole dating game, everything about
them. That's why I gave up. That's why I
gave up, bro. This is the real real This
is the real reason I gave up because of
them. Then they'll make up excuses like
they can sense your personality when
they don't know your personality. They
don't know anything about you. They just
pretend they got boyfriend straight
away. They do they will do anything to defend a
woman, mate. A woman could [ __ ]
murder a newborn baby and they'd say,
"Nah, mate. The baby done it. You're
wasting your [ __ ] time arguing." But
I didn't expect it from her to be honest. You
know, obviously is these women, bro.
It's the only thing it can be is
them. Yeah, I remember. Yeah, I had
messages that was ignoring,
right? I had messages that was ignoring
and as soon as I said women are evil,
they all reply back. Well, 90% of them
reply back. I said the women are evil
and they all started replying back. One
that ignored me from months ago. They
all replied back to that trying to victimize
themselves. They all replied back to
that. It was they were to be seen then,
but normal nice messages they get
ignored. And yeah, when I actually done
that experiment, I was like, "Shit,
we're actually dealing with scum here."
Like, we're not It's not two or three
that's replied, it's 90%. It's quite a
lot. You know, that's how I knew like
you're dealing with proper
scum because a normal person wouldn't
wouldn't reply to that. They just block
you. They were like, "Oh, what the [ __ ]
You're writing stuff about women. We're
just going to block this person or continuously
ignore." But they just reply back straight away. [ __ ]
up. They're just [ __ ] Just proper
[ __ ] Evil [ __ ] That's what they are. Yep.
If I could do something right to a woman
and get away with it, I would do it. Not
[ __ ] not rape. [ __ ] that. I wouldn't
do that. But I'd give them a good
[ __ ] hiding, bro. I just go out on
the street right now and just give one a
good old ass whapon. If I knew I could
get away with it and not go to jail,
bro, I sure would do
it. I'd give them a good old ass weapon.
would. Yeah. They reply back to negative
comments. They reply to negativity, but they ignore positivity. Strange.
They're [ __ ] evil
scumbags. I might even go outside to be
honest. You get sick of it very quickly.
know, I do anyways.
Yeah. Yeah. [ __ ]
It these women in this country.
Yeah. And we got somebody in Canada
[ __ ] defending them.
Badness. You can stop hating anyone.
Men, women. You can always stop hating
anyone. You just need better
experiences. Blame your [ __ ] selves. you
know, threatening women. They they also
believe that they don't waste people's
time intentionally because it makes no
sense for them to do
that. You go and ask, bro, they don't
believe that they can they can waste
people's time when they can. And they
literally do because they literally have
done it. Your time and their time.
Yes the [ __ ] they do and yes the [ __ ]
they have but they seem to not believe
that. They don't seem to believe they
they can do that. Nah n they're not
wasting your time man. It's what is the
guy's personality bics?
Yeah, exactly. You know the drill.
I think I've just woke
up. Yeah. Not long. Woke
Yeah. And the same thing will be on
Saturday as well. You choose to go out
Saturday, Friday, whatever, it will be
the same thing that week as well. It
will be exactly the same
thing. Yeah. There there's a woman uh
from Canada, Grezy. She's defending
women again, making up stuff, saying,
"Oh, well, um they do all of this
because they know that you hate them." I
was like, "You hate them because you've
had bad experiences with them. It's
because of them. It's it's why you feel
the way you do. You understand?
So, anything to defend [ __ ] women.
You hate them because of your
experiences with them. Which can only which makes
sense. And I said to her, "Shame on you.
I don't I didn't expect that from you,
man. Defending women for no reason, you
know, making up stuff. Wow. I didn't
expect it from you. You know, I expected
it from these Reddit nerds, but I didn't
expect it from you. Wow.
And I was like, "Oh, was that what it
was?" I said to her, "Oh, I know now."
So, when you approach someone and you
don't even get to say one or two words
and they say they got a boyfriend or
they give their attitude, give you
attitude, that's because of your personality. Oh
[ __ ] Is that what it was? Oh wow. I was
I didn't know that, Grezy. Oh, right.
So they assume all these things about
you after one word. Really? I mean,
Jesus. Was that what it was all all
these years? Oh, okay. So, you've
decided to wake up one day and just hate
women for no reason. Well, well, at
least at least I know what the answer is
now, is what I said to her. I said, "Oh,
that's what that was." Oh. being sarcastic
obviously which you should understand
that yeah I woke up my foot's hurting a
little bit as well with that walking eh
Yeah. Look at us a macaroni cheese
today. Greasy. I had McDonald's earlier,
did I? So
Oh yeah, sorry about that. I just made a
cup of tea. Uh uh.
Yep. Yeah. Women are [ __ ] e women are
[ __ ] evil, man. [ __ ] [ __ ] evil
I need to send some money.
Someone just send some
money. [ __ ] evil [ __ ]
Sorry about that, man. I was sending
someone money. So,
yeah. Yeah, man. They're [ __ ] evil, Greasy.
I wish people would understand truly how evil they
are. Really, really, really evil people in
general. That can
only that can only reply back to
negativity. That can only reply back to
negativity. Okay. What's the fun in that?
That people that can only reply back to
negativity. What's the fun in
that? Yeah. GTA uh 6 is coming out next
um year. Steven Howard May. So, we're
saving 20 pound a week until
then. Um, we're going to buy a new
telly, new PlayStation, new game, whatever.
Yeah. Yeah. To be fair, I probably won't
even be out this week.
I'd like to, but I just don't want to
hear about boyfriend. Grey got boyfriends. [ __ ]
perfect. Yeah, it's pathetic, man.
Yeah, I just said to Ant-Man like he was
in the Weather Spoons before the the
second time he went to
um before second time he went to um
Thailand. I said, "How's it going, man?
Keep me updated in it." Cuz we used to
take it in terms I go out, he stays in,
he says, I go out. He's like, "How's it
going?" They've all got
boyfriends. They've all got imaginary Grezy imaginary
boyfriends. Yeah, they like to say that
around Oxford Circus as well. They're
[ __ ] [ __ ] mate. I'd love to just
throttle one of them, mate. I would love
to just throttle one of them. You know
what Bart You know what what Homer does
to Bart Simpson? Yeah. Yeah.
You know what Homer does to Bart and his
little eyes pops out. That's what I want
to do to one of
them. I know the other Izzy um she still
wants to meet and stuff but she just
can't date me cuz I'm not a Muslim.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I should have
um Yeah, I was in Hide Park. Don't know
why I said Victoria Park, but yeah, she
said she can't date me cuz I'm not a
Muslim in Grezy. Well, bro, just another
one to add to the [ __ ] collection, is
it? Just another one to add to the [ __ ]
I can't pretend I'm a
Muslim cuz then when it comes to getting
in the bedroom, you will see that I'm not circumcised.
Just another one to add to the [ __ ]
collection. Like a like pile of
DVDs again on Reddit. I'm being stalked
again on Reddit by these people. Never
mind. I'll just stop posting publicly.
You know, every time you post, right,
whoever is doing this on YouTube, I'm
just going to stop posting on the
subreddit. So, I'm just going to start private messaging
people. Yeah, that's fine, bro. Because
I'm just going to stop posting
publicly. Yep, no problem. I'm just
going to literally make a new Reddit.
Takes two seconds. And I'm just not
going to post publicly now. No skin off my
nose. No skin on my nose, Greasy. No
skin off my nose.
No skin off my nose. It's always an
excuse. It's always an
excuse that they've got a a dis
um they've got a mental thing where they
just love wasting people's
time. That's what it is. They just love
wasting people's time that and their own
time as well. They love wasting their
time and your
time. They're [ __ ] evil they are. I
hate them. I
do. I [ __ ] hate them [ __ ] I do. I
don't think I'm going to bother Saturday
to be honest. Another month off I think.
Well, it's getting longer and longer and
longer and longer and longer.
out my [ __ ] head. I hadn't been out
for a month. Yeah. [Music]
Yeah. Um, yeah. Obviously, she knew I
was I wasn't Muslim cuz I don't because
I was drinking.
would always be
evil. Yeah, because I want them for
their bodies, bro. You saying I always
Wait, wait, hold on. I still go out and
try and always fail. That was the first
time I was out for [ __ ] 5 weeks, you
[ __ ] clown. cuz I was [ __ ] bored
about I still go out and try and always
fail. Well, guess what? I pulled more
women than you and I don't try. I tried
what? Four weeks after cuz I was bored
and I was going for a drink anyways. [ __ ] off,
mate. Didn't spend anything
really. Yeah, no one can fail more than
you, mate. and stop stalking me on
Reddit as well cuz I'm just going to I'm
just going to stop posting on the
subreddit now. So, you're just wasting
your time now stalking me cuz I'm just
going to stop posting on it. I'll just
stop PMing people,
lad. You know, doesn't matter about how
many times I've had a W. I do hate
them. Of course, I [ __ ] hate
them. Why do you think I don't go out
every week? Why do you think I don't
approach every day or every other day? I
do hate them like most people do. Of
course, I [ __ ] hate them. And the
only time I try with them is I'm only
trying to get in their knickers, their
Nicknocks. Yeah, man. And they hate you as
well. Yeah. They hate me. They hate you.
We hate them.
Yeah. Yeah. They hate you as
well. That's why you're probably still a
virgin. Yeah. On YouTube. You made three
different accounts, man. You s bastard.
Yeah, this person in Canada, man. I
expected more from them to be honest. I
them and I probably won't even be out
this week. Yeah, but they hate
you. But they hate
you. I don't know, man. Just another one
of my stalkers. He was on two different accounts
earlier. Probably. Probably Lewisville
Slugger. Probably. Yeah, that sad little
bastard. Probably is to be honest. He
ain't got a life s on YouTube behind a
million accounts. Sad
bastard. Do you know the only reason I'm thinking of
um You know, the only reason I'm
thinking of going out um Terry is cuz I
had my haircut last week and it still looks
good, you know.
And that's and that's what it
is. Um, but I don't think I'm going to
bother this week, bro. I'm done again
for another six weeks. Gets longer every time
now. I hate the truth. You don't know
the what? What's the bro? The truth. You don't know
anything. You know, you don't know. You
don't know the truth cuz you don't know
anything. You know what I'm saying? So,
what what what's the truth? No, I
blocked you cuz you're a repeater. The
truth about what? You don't know anything about
anything? You know what I'm
saying? But yeah,
Greasy, the only thing you can hope is
that you get murdered, you die, and then
maybe women are different in the
afterlife. Grezy, cuz they're no
different here, mate. in these
westernized countries. You don't know
the amount of reason I was watching yes
um earlier on Instagram with these
Americans being rude to these people,
bro. Like what the [ __ ] You know, wow,
bro. You But bro, you are single. But
bro, you are single and you are alone
and you've got no friends. So, you're
talking about yourself. You know what I
was saying about earlier, bro? You're
the truth is that you're older than me.
You're uglier than me. And you you're
single. So you're talking about
yourself. There's no truth in talking about
yourself. You're talking about your own
life. Look look at you, bro. Yeah.
You've been blocked on three accounts.
You're single. You're ugly. You're older
than me. Prove me wrong. If if it's not
the truth, prove me wrong, bro. You're
talking about yourself every day. Just
like when these people like Timmy. Yeah.
when he showed £300. Yeah. Yeah. 300.
Yeah. I was so tempted to go to the bank
and just and put these people out their
misery again. But it's pointless, man.
Because it's just self-reflecting. All
of this your skin, your this. It's it's
about their own reality, their own
YouTube dependent lives. So, there's no
point. There's literally no point,
bro, because it's just self-reflectant.
That's why nothing you say bothers
anyone. Like, think of it, bro. You're
single. You're probably still a [ __ ]
virgin. You probably can't even leave
your house. You're probably in your 40s.
You are way worse, right? Yeah. You are
way worse than anybody you call anyone
else. You're single, alone, and a
virgin. That's the truth. I don't need
to [ __ ] block anyone. You know what
I'm saying? You're single. You're alone.
You're Billy No mates. Is it any wonder
you come on YouTube every day, year in
year out, Billy No mates? Like [ __ ]
how many times would you go on? Okay,
listen listen. How comes every single
time you go on Lord Day's channel, it's
the same Billy Nomates? Let's let's
let's talk about this, right? It's the
same people, Billy Omates, that can't
get off of YouTube, that can't get off
the YouTubes. YouTube is all they
[ __ ] have. You know how many times?
Yeah. I come off of YouTube for weeks
and weeks and weeks and I come back and
it's the same people Billy know mates
alone on YouTube, mate. So, anything you
say doesn't get you blocked because
you're just a
self-reflector. No one cares about it,
man. You're alone. You're ugly. You got
no woman. You're skint. I mean, [ __ ] me.
How many Let's use this as an example.
How many times have you lost the money game?
How many times have you lost a [ __ ] money
game? How many times have you lost a
money game? About 30
times. Stop it, man. It's it's it's
boring now. You know, it's really
boring. It's it's about time that you
grow up. I've been seen with more women
than everyone on here. More money than
everyone on here. More friends with
everyone on than anyone on here. More
life experience than anybody on here.
Like I have been seen with more than you
would ever have. That's facts.
Everyone's seen it, man. Everyone's seen
it. You know, we use No, no, no, no, no.
You watch YouTube because YouTube is all
you have. It's all you have. Listen,
listen, listen. Even when I'm not on
YouTube, right, you still come on. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no. Listen, listen,
listen. YouTube is all you have. It's
not to watch sad people. It's It's your
life. Think about it. If your life was
so good, you wouldn't be on here. If you
It doesn't matter about who's sad. No,
no, no, no, no, no. If your life was
that good, you wouldn't be on here. So,
every time you're on here, it's like,
"Oh, you're on YouTube again. Oh, you're
on YouTube again. Oh, you're on YouTube
again. If your life was that good, you
wouldn't be on
here every day. Sorry. You would not be
on here every day and not be able to
take a day off of YouTube. There you go.
It doesn't matter who's sad, who's got a
[ __ ] life. It says that it's all it's
literally all you have. You can't take
one day off of YouTube. You literally
can't take one day off of
YouTube. Okay, let me let me ask this
question, Grezy. Right.
If I come off of YouTube for two, three
weeks again and then in them two, three
weeks I come back and I come on and I
and I and I go back every day, right?
The amount of times I've been off, will
it be the same people on YouTube? I'm
I'm willing to do it again. I'm willing
to do this again, right? Yeah. Yeah. But
you're not sat here with your friends
because you won't be on YouTube. That's
what I'm saying. No, bro. Listen, if you
had friends or anything, you wouldn't be
on YouTube every day.
You can't be because you're on YouTube.
You're on a on a [ __ ] hole community if
you had friends. No, no, no, no, no. You
would not be on here. That's what I'm
saying. You know what I'm saying? Who am
I sitting with? Bro, you're sitting by
yourself right now alone. Mr. Lonely, I
was out with my [ __ ] friends on
Saturday. Mr. Lonely on YouTube that
can't get off it. Didn't you get blocked
off of two accounts and then you made
another account? Mr.
Lonely. Mr. Lonely like bomb. Yeah.
Didn't you get blocked off two accounts
and you came back back? Mate, you're not
set sat with no one. Mr. Lonely, who's
got a worse life than me? Yeah. And you
would not be sat on YouTube with your
friends, Mr. Lonely. Because I was on
YouTube on um sorry, I was with my
friends on Saturday and I was not on
YouTube once. I was not on YouTube once,
Mr. Lonely. So stop talking [ __ ]
[ __ ] Yeah, stop talking [ __ ]
man. Stop talking [ __ ] Mr.
Lonely. These people have been on here
for years doing this. Years doing this.
We sit, smoke, and laugh. Mate, listen.
You laugh at yourself. You sit in your
house lonely. Mr. Lonely, no friends.
You You laugh at yourself. You literally
laugh at your own [ __ ] life. You can't
get off of YouTube.
You laugh at yourselves, you spastics.
How many years have you been on here
doing this? You spastics can't come off
of YouTube. You sit on YouTube because
it's all you have. You got no money, no
friends. That's why you're on here
typing to me, you [ __ ] dumb nut. And
it is the [ __ ] truth. You sit on
YouTube because you can't even leave
your house due to anxiety, mate.
Anyways, I'm blocking you now. Bye-bye, [ __ ]
And another thing is all communities
come to an end. Griezy, you can't say
that, oh, it's a community. What a
community that's been going for 15 years
full of the same people, the same
repeating people. Bro, it's not even a
community. Wait, wait, wait, hold on,
hold on. Firstly, communities come to an
end. B, people that are in communities
don't come online every day
self-projecting. So, no, it's actually
not even a community. You actually know
what a community is. The community is
where people play [ __ ] Call of Duty
no and they and they're actual gamers.
Yeah. They're actual gamers that actual
do that actually do stuff. They don't
sit on YouTube every day calling people
what they are themselves every day for
15 [ __ ] years. You
understand? No. No one [ __ ] does
that, bro. What the [ __ ] That's not a
community. That's just [ __ ] weird on this
[ __ ] Oh, [ __ ] headache, man. Yeah. Yeah.
So yeah, anyways your block buddy.
Bye. You agree women are evil.
Um I I I I definitely think they
are. Yeah, I think I'm going to stay in
the Well, I've got cinemas to go
to. Yeah, I I don't think I'll be going
out this week somehow, man. It's a
shame. I really wanted to, bro, but I
don't think I can do I can deal with it
anymore. Make believe. Well, they are
evil, Greavvesy. Because if they wasn't
evil, they wouldn't do what they do.
Waste people's time on purpose. Ghost
people on purpose. They wouldn't do what
they do. Ghost people without
explanation. They of course they're
[ __ ] evil. Evil. Stuck up.
Devious. Yeah, I get bullied daily.
Yeah, good for you. Um, yeah, bro. Like, stuck up, devious,
like, bro, the only people that get
bullied is you people. You haters. The
only people that get bullied is you
people. That's why you're on YouTube
every day, cuz you get bullied in real
life. That's why you come on YouTube
hating every day, cuz you get bullied
all your life. You've been bullied, bro.
You don't bully no one, man. Turn on
now, bro. Come on. It's embarrassing. you bully
yourselves. So if they weren't evil,
Greavvesy, they wouldn't do these
things. If they I generally believe they
are all evil. I generally generally
believe they are. Otherwise, I wouldn't say
it. I would not say if I didn't if I
truly didn't believe it. And I went out
last week. Yeah. Cuz I hadn't been out
for a month. So I thought, "Fuck it.
I generally believe they are all evil
scum. And how I've come to that
conclusion is that in years it would
have changed by
now. You know, you you if uh in years it
would have changed. It would have
changed. Like financial situations
change, you change, people change. This
would not still be happening for years.
If they were truly as different as
people say they were, this would not
still be happening for years. The same
the same [ __ ] the same boyfriend [ __ ]
the same [ __ ] that they do. Even when
they say this would not still be
happening. Yeah. I want to use them for
their bodies. Yeah. Cuz that's all
they're good for, their bodies because
evil, you know. Yeah. You You use them
You want them for their bodies. Yeah.
Because they're evil. You don't want
them as people. You don't want to
associate with evil.
I don't agree with any of it, mate.
Maybe I might be the only one in the
world, but I know what I'm saying is
right. Otherwise, I wouldn't be saying
it and I wouldn't be leaving the country
in 4 weeks. You know, I hate them, bro.
I generally hate
them. Generally hate
them. I gave up for four weeks. Yep.
Just like that. USA is she should have
told me a day to come next week, but I
would have gave her a good [ __ ]
hiding in front of her boyfriend, in
front of her dad. I would have showed
her who the keyboard warrior was. You
want to start calling people keyboard
warrior? I'll show you who the [ __ ]
keyboard warrior is. You little scag
[ __ ] Shut her mouth though, didn't she?
Stupid slaggy little [ __ ] [ __ ] them,
bro. All of them.
Yeah. Well, we got two
days. No, we got three days until this
thing comes out in the
cinema. Well, Adman's going to Thailand tomorrow. So,
yeah. That's right. What's up with it?
Yep. [ __ ] headache. I
do. Yeah, she was all right.
Yeah. Have I ever considered becoming a Turkish
barber? No. What kind of question is that, man?
I want to open a Chinese restaurant with
Grezy. Me, Grezy, and King in a nice Chinese restaurant.
Yeah. Me, Grezy, and King. Nice Chinese
restaurant. Playing GTA 6 in the back.
Ah, what a lovely site. E, what a lovely
site. Yeah, I know I'm not Chinese. I
don't have to be
Chinese. I don't have to be Chinese, mate. Yeah,
exactly. Just [ __ ] hate women. I do.
I was thinking to go out today and just
go and attack one, go and beat one up,
but I don't want to go prison cuz then
they win even
more. Why don't I have the same energy
towards men when I'm confronted? Do you
want me to answer it? How about you give
I give you my address and you can come
today and I will I will give you the
same energy. I will personally give you
the same energy. How about that one? No
[ __ ] bro. I will give you my
address. Oh, you already have my
address. I don't need to give you my
address. You already have my address.
And I'll have the same energy towards
you. How's about that one? That's that's
a good one, isn't it? Right. I will have the same
um I will have the same energy towards
you. Talking about LT and Prime, I've
already explained this, but bro, I'd
have the same energy towards you if you
want. I'm talking about you. I'm talking
about you. Come [ __ ] round today.
Come round today and I'll show you how
much energy I have towards a man.
Yeah. Stupid little [ __ ] Yeah. And I
did have an energy towards a man because
when I was in Weather Spoons, Yeah. the
other day, I saw somebody that I um that
I cursed and he knew not to [ __ ] around
with me. And he goes to the gym and he
goes to the gym as well and he was
trying to weigh me up, but the guy knew
he would have [ __ ] got [ __ ] up.
That's why he backed off. That's why I
can't remember what I said to him, but I
said something and I ditched him as well
and he saw me. He knew, bro. He knew he
couldn't go there. I'm not scared of
anyone, mate. So just because someone
says something to a [ __ ] woman,
right? Just because someone says
something to a woman, it doesn't mean
they can't handle men. I met more people
than [ __ ] anyone on
here. You know what I'm
saying? So that's an answer. That was
actually the other day. First uh
Thursday it was. Yeah, we just went out the track. So
yeah, stop repeating yourself. No one
cares about prime and LT, man. Stop
repeating [ __ ] from years ago. You
know, I literally said to that USA, "You
can bring your boyfriend and bring your
dad and I will literally [ __ ] you up in
front of both of them." I mean, I said
both of them. You know what I'm saying?
Grezy. I said both of them. I did say
it. I hate men that defend women, bro.
Yeah. You saw what happened about two
and a half years ago when I was when I
was caught off guard. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We when I was caught
off guard. Yeah. When I was caught off
guard. Yeah. You saw me when I was
caught off guard. Yeah. About two and a
half years ago. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, man. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Good for you, bro. Two and a half
years ago when I was caught off guard.
Yeah. Yeah. I know, bro. Everyone saw
it. Yeah. But no one cares, bro, cuz
this was years ago.
Yeah. You know what I'm
saying? You know, if any man grab me,
come to my Okay. Come to my address
today and I'll grab you. Off God. Come
to my address today and I'll grab you. I
will wait all day for you, big man.
Yeah. And I will grab you up and see
what you do. Okay. Okay. Do you want to
come to the address today then? Yeah. I
will grab you up and see what you do to
me. Yeah. How about that one? How about
that one? I'm a man and I'll grab you up
and I'll put a camera in your face and
let's see what you're about today then.
Yeah. Come on, [ __ ] Yeah, it's a
fight. I will grab you up and I
guarantee you you're not going to be
fighting me. Oh, I bet you any money
you're not going to be fighting me.
Yeah, you've come on here. You've
started something. Listen, you've
started something. Listen to me, bro. I
will grab you up, put a camera in your
face, and see if you try fighting me.
Bro, bro. Bro, listen. I I will wait for
you. I will generally generally
generally wait. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no. You people are the grass, right? You
people are the ones that go to the
police over and over and over and over
and over and over and over again. You
have been grassing. Yeah. I only report
one person on this community because
they kept running to the police on me.
Yeah. You people have been grassing all
your life when you've been on here,
mate. So, don't try to say I didn't run
off anywhere, mate. He's the one that
ran off. So you're not coming today
then, [ __ ] boy. So you're not coming
today, scaredy cat. Yeah, your mom gets
fingered for a packet of biscuits. Go
suck up your mom and you know where I
live and you're not going to do nothing.
W go suck up your mom and you're not
going to cover my door cuz you're shook.
Bro, I swear to God I'm not going to
call the police on you. I am not going
to call the peace on you and go suck up
your mom. Let's see what you're really
about. Yeah. I'm telling you to go suck
your mother and you're not going to come
on my door. Go and suck your mom and
you're not going to do nothing. Yeah.
Your mom gets fingered for a packet of
biscuits. Let's see what Let's see how
much of a man you are. Let's see how
much of a man you are. Go suck up your
mom, you silly little [ __ ] You little
[ __ ] [ __ ] Don't [ __ ] suck up your
mom. And I'm saying that as well. And
you know my address, but [ __ ] boy won't
do nothing about it. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
Come on. my door. My mom hates
me. Yeah, my mom hates me. I see I talk
to my mom every day. You're a [ __ ] I
just told you to suck up your mom and
you're not coming. Go suck up your mom.
Let's see how much of a man you are.
Come on, big man. Come on, big man. Go
and suck up your mom. Are you letting me
talk to you like that? Yeah. Yeah. Let's
see. I'm not bad at you. Come on, [ __ ]
You just said that no one's going to
grab you, bro. I will grab you and I'll
mock you. Yeah, I will grab you and I'll
mock you, you [ __ ] idiot. Yeah, come
round, [ __ ] boy. Come round, [ __ ] boy.
boy. Please, bro. Come round.
Yeah. I'll have the same energy towards
you any day of the week. You little
[ __ ] boy. [ __ ] off, man. Coming on here
trying to call me a grass, mate. You
people have been grassing. All the you
are grasses. [ __ ] off, man. You don't
scare me one little bit. Come around
anytime you want. I'm not scared of you.
Yeah, you [ __ ] idiot. [ __ ] off, man.
Sad. Yeah, you're not scaring no one,
bro. I've come. You said you're going to
come, so come,
[ __ ] You know, [ __ ] idiot, bro.
Making reports. Yes. Of one person, you
[ __ ] idiot. Anyways, I'm blocking you
now. You're not about anything. Bye.
Bye-bye, [ __ ] Bye-bye. You know where
I live and you're not going to come on
my door, [ __ ] boy. Yeah, listen. You
know where I live and you're not going
to come on my door. If we don't hear you
on my door or we don't hear that you've
done something to my door and you've
done a video telling me to meet you,
you're a [ __ ] Yeah, it's all in your
hands. Everything is in your hands now.
You know where I live. You know exactly
where I live. Let's see what you're
about, [ __ ] boy. And you can't use
anyone's mom as an excuse anymore.
Exactly. You're not about that life, you
[ __ ] idiot, mate. Listen, do you know
what? A man would never grab you because
you can't even leave your house. You
wouldn't even be able to leave your
house. That's why a man would never grab
you. A man possibly can't grab someone
that don't leave their [ __ ] house,
[ __ ] You understand? Bye-bye. Stop
being a keyboard warrior. Stop typing.
You got my address. Yeah. You know, I
don't live with my mom, so stop. Yeah,
it. [ __ ] these people in this
community are [ __ ] They're shitous,
bro. Honestly, they're all
shitouses. Absolute shitouses. [ __ ] off,
man. Stupid little
idiot. Stupid idiot, bro.
Yeah. Yep. I need to go shopping in a
minute. Get some um
Coca-Cola. Listen, bro. You've got my
address. Tick tock. Tick tock. Tick
tock. Stop repeating and commonly
address. Tick tock, tick tock, tick
tock. Hurry up. What are you waiting for? Come
on. You repeating little
bastard. You repeating little bastard,
man. I'm just going to have some
macaroni cheese. I already had
McDonald's earlier, so I'm just going to
have some macaroni cheese and have some microwave food.
Yeah. [ __ ] pounding headache I
have boom boom boom
boom. Probably the fan to be fair.
Yeah. Yeah. I can't be bothered to eat anything else,
bro. I basically been in bed all day to
be fair. I told Laney to get
lost. That's what happens when I have
these episodes and mood swings. I start switching on
people. Grievy. I start switching on
people. When I get these mood swings
over these women, I start switching on
people. I know what I'm like. You know
what I'm saying? I know what I'm like, bro.
Yeah. I know what I'm like, matey.
Yep. Yep. You're calling yourself a
[ __ ] mate. You're calling yourself a
[ __ ] Yeah, like I said, you got my
address and you've got anything to say?
Knock. Come knocking on the
door. No, it's just it's not it's just
bad. It's just enough bad experiences,
Grezy. It's just bad experiences with
women. If you had enough bad experiences
that I've had, you you would feel the
same or anybody would, you know. Well,
women wouldn't because they have life on
easy mode. No, no, no, no. It's when you
deal with enough [ __ ] from these people
time and time and time and time and time
and time again. That's how you end up.
That's how you end up. It's because of
them. It's because of them. You know, if
you have got, you know, enough bad
experiences with these women, that's
what's giving you these mood swings, you
know. And no one's dealt with it like I
have. You know, even Ant-Man will tell
you this as well. time and time, year in
year out, year in year out. It's like
what Ant-Man said, it's not been going
on for weeks or months. It's been going
on for years. You know what I'm saying?
This has been going on for years. You
know, people on the internet try to give
people advice that shitty advice don't work. You
know, and it makes people just not want
to get out of bed. It makes people not
want to do anything cuz you feel like
the game is rigged against well the game
is rigged against you. It's in their
favor and rigged against us. So that
just makes people not want to do
anything. You know what I'm saying? I
tried ignoring it, shutting up and
getting on with it, you know, time and
time and time and time and time and time
and time and time and time again,
lad. You know? Yeah. And guess what,
bro? And you're a [ __ ] two-faced
bastard. Guess what? And you're saying
that man's a full-on creep. No wonder
women hate him. Let me tell you
something. I was watching loads of
Instagram approaches before I went to
sleep. And women's attitude are
disgusting. How you try to blame me and
not these women. You're a full-on s,
mate. I was watching these approaches
and these women, some of these women's
attitudes are is disgusting. And they
want to try and talk about men. They
want to talk about men. It's these
women. It's 100% women. 1 million% it is
these females. I swear to God, bro, I
would bet my life on it. It is these
westernized women. You know, it is
women. They are the problem. Otherwise,
I wouldn't say it. If if I genuinely
didn't believe it, I wouldn't say it. I
would have gave up for four weeks and
then only went out of a bom. If I did
not think that the problem was them, I
wouldn't. I wouldn't, bro. Cuz I'd be
[ __ ] lying to
myself. You know, it's like you Ricky
about the problem is me. The problem is
these [ __ ] women. I've got evidence.
I know what I [ __ ] experienced and
what I have experienced and and I know
what I'm going to continuously
experience if I keep trying in this
country. I know exactly what's going to
keep happening. I know exactly what's
going to keep happening. It is these
[ __ ] women. If you actually left your
house and you stopped sitting in all
day, you would understand instead of
being being too faced on [ __ ] YouTube
every day. Yeah. Instead of being
two-faced on [ __ ] YouTube every day.
It's like I said to you before, you
little prick. If you got something to
say, say it to my face. Don't go on
[ __ ] Red Star's channel or some
Traile channel talking absolute [ __ ]
[ __ ] Yeah. If you got something to say,
say it on my channel and say it to my
face. Simple. But you will never do
that, man. You're a little
wimp. You're a little [ __ ] wimp that
just offends women just like the rest of
them. You're pathetic. Pathetic, mate. Pathetic.
Bye-bye. I don't even know who the [ __ ]
that is. Yeah. Like, who would know more
about women, Ricky? Me or you? Somebody
that's been doing this for years and
dealing with people
and or you? Who would know more about
women? Me or you? Come on, man. It's
embarrassing. Of course, these women are
the [ __ ] problem. They're
westernized. They're westernized. You
see it as well when other people start
talking to them that, you know, they got
the same attitude. The same
attitude. London, America, Canada, New
Zealand, same westernized [ __ ]
No. Come on, man.
I see your stupid little comments, mate.
I've seen your little um I've seen your
little comments as well, Ricky. Why
don't you have anything to say when
you're on here? Huh?
No, no, nothing. I don't even do any of
that anymore cuz I just feel like it's just pointless.
No, I just feel like it's
pointless. It's pointless doing all that
extra [ __ ] you
know? Yeah. It's pointless.
Yeah. Yeah. The little two-faced [ __ ]
trying to say, "Oh, how it's not women,
it's me." No, it is definitely
definitely definitely definitely women.
It's definitely definitely women, mate.
I would know out of all people because
I've dealt with them. I know exactly how
is. You know what I'm saying? I know
exactly how they are, mate. Cuz I've
been putting it up. I've been putting up
with it for years. Not weeks, not months, [ __ ]
years, you know.
Yeah. What do you mean don't try for
anyone, Cherry? What do you
mean? You mean don't approach anymore? I
won't be approaching
anymore. Nah. No, I'm not going out this
week. I don't think so, bro.
Nah. Oh, look. I just typed women or
evil and lo and behold, they're typing straight
away. Look at this Snapchat I got,
though. They're not going to reply, are
they? You know. Wait, hold on. Hold on one
second. No, but she's not going to she's
not going to reply. Surely, she ain't
going to reply to negativity, you know.
Clearly not. But the thing is though,
it's not just this country though, is
it? But the thing is, it's not just this
country. It's America as well. It's
America, England. It's it's literally
any westernized country,
bro. Yep. She typed, replied, and then
deleted me. There always somewhere to be
seen when there's negative comments
running um going about. I've noticed that, you know.
Yeah. I'm gonna have to do a video on
this, bro. I think
Yeah. It's the women in England,
America, Canada, Australia, New Zealand,
anywhere. That's the West. They're all
like that. Same [ __ ] same attitude. Yep.
And do you know why they say it's not
women, Chevy? It's because they don't go
out and deal with women. So they don't
know what they're
like. They don't know what these women
are like because they don't deal with
them. So they just make up stuff and
say, "Oh, it's personality or whatever
it is they're saying because they don't
they don't deal with them. They have no
life experience." So that's why they
just say these things like, bro, if I go
out on Saturday, I can tell you exactly
what's going to happen. I can predict
it. I can go to William Hill right now.
I can go to William Hill right now and I
could bet money on the market and tell
you exactly what's going to happen and I
and I and I will triple my money. That's
how bad it is. So if they're not all the
same, how could I predict such a thing?
You know what I'm having? I'm having macaroni
cheese. No, it's annoying,
bro. It's not about it being worth it. No, it's
annoying. Nah, I'm just going to get
some macaroni cheese and that's it. Nah,
I'm annoyed, bro. [ __ ] that,
bro. But they're stuck up everywhere
though, Cherry. And even the people that
come to London from America that they're
all stuck up. Everyone that's in London
is stuck up. Anyone that's in central
London is stuck up.
I'm just having a microwave macaroni
cheese cuz I can't be bothered to cook.
I had some food earlier. Anyone that
comes to London is stuck up. America,
[ __ ] Doesn't matter where the [ __ ] they come
from, you know? They're all stuck up.
All they're just all the same. All the
same westernized, you know? No
good. Yeah. Yeah, I just got gave myself a [ __ ] headache.
[ __ ] No, you won't do it, Grezy,
because you know that I'll be right. And
you don't want to say that. You don't
want to say You don't want to admit that
I told you so. That's what it
is. It's because you know I'm
right. It's cuz you know that I'm right
and you're going to start experiencing
things that I'm
experiencing. That's what it is deep
down. That's exactly what it is.
Otherwise, you would have been doing it
by now. If I'm so wrong and women are
not all evil and no, go and date them.
Go and speak to them. Go and date them.
Go and open dating apps and prove me
wrong. But you can't do it. You
know, you know what I'm saying? Like that's it.
I'm my skin. Did you not listen to me,
you [ __ ] idiot? I literally said I
had McDonald's earlier. I'm not wasting
money on another takeaway. Why would I
be skinned when I get £3,000 a month?
Why would I be the any bit
skint? Me skint in the same sentence? I
don't think so,
bro. I already got to
McDonald's. I don't want to waste any
more money. I had a McDonald's earlier.
Why would I be skinned?
I'm fed up. I just want to microwave
macaroni cheese with more cheese on it.
It tastes fine. I don't
care. Why would I be skint? How can I be
skint? That doesn't even make sense, you know?
Yeah. I don't want to cook today or
anything, bro. I'm fed
up. I'm fed up. So
yeah, telling lady to get lost. Um,
Grezy telling lady to get lost,
eh? [ __ ] funny. Is it? Yeah.
Move it all [ __ ] evil. I want you to,
bro. I want you to
um Yeah, I want you to
uh I want you to try again,
bro. I want you to try again, lad. See
what we see what happens. Yeah.
these nasty [ __ ] mood swings, mate.
And they and they stop you sleeping as
well. They stop you sleeping as well.
You can't go to bed till like 2:00 3:00
in the morning. So, you don't even get like proper
sleep. Yeah. You don't even get that
proper sleep, Grezy, because you're up
thinking about it all. The bad
experiences, how the future is very
scary and it's never going to change.
The future is so
scary. If this is a taste of what my
dating life will be forever in this
country, I do not like it. It's scary,
man. It's very
scary. You can't even speak to people
without saying they got bloody
boyfriends. [ __ ] hell. And I think
how long it's been going on for as well.
It's been going on for a very very long
time, you know. It's not like a month,
two months, then we can say, "Oh, well,
these things take time, you know. You
know, even even six months. It's been
going on for [ __ ] years, Greasy. It's
been going on for bloody years with these [ __ ] you
know?" No, not 10 years. About four
Well, when I used to meet up with that
virgin, he used to try and tell me, "Oh,
you don't know all women." Cuz I don't
know why I used to say it, but I used to
say, "All women are [ __ ] All women are
this. All women are that." I don't know
why exactly I used to say it. And this
little virgin used to tell me griezy,
"Oh, you don't know all women. You don't
know all women." And then tried calling
me gay. I was like, "Okay, whatever."
And then I grew up and then I dealt with
more experiences and more women. And I
can tell you that they literally are
exactly the same.
Even at 27 years of age
now it's been going on for solidly about
four years. About four years.
Yeah. Yeah. I don't want a woman. I'm
just telling you what it is. They're
evil. I'm telling you that that they're
evil. It's not about them sucking. They
they [ __ ] are evil. That's what it
is. They're evil. Generally
are, you know. I think over the years I
just tried to give people the benefit of
doubt. Oh yeah, that was Yeah, but
that's not the best. That's just
copying. If you don't find Shelco
attractive, you're gay. No, that's just
copying. No, that's copying. That's not
even somebody that I would code
approach. No, that's just
copying. No, that's not even funny. That's just
copying. And how you know it's copying?
Because in in in years to in years,
right, people have had different tastes
of women and no one has ever been called
gay for not finding a certain woman
attractive. But if the person's name is
Cheryl Cole, they start calling you
gay. Like that's just copying. That's
not even funny. That's just copying. You
know, you've never heard anyone say,
"Oh, if you don't like this person,
you're gay." It's the name, mate. It's
nothing to do with what they look like.
It's literally the name. It's literally copy
them. It's literally copy them because
it's it's like lit. Maybe they're like a
5.5 out of 10. They're literally nothing
special. But to call someone gay really? [ __ ] hell,
bro. Jesus Christ. That's That's
madness. It's not even somebody that you
would approach on the street. Yeah,
that's copying. If you go on the student
room form, they used to say they used to copy each
other. They even used to know the
reactions in before the person says that
you're gay. Yeah, it's copying, bro.
It's a little
trend. Little trend that they picked up. [ __ ] copycats. Yeah, [ __ ]
copycats. Yeah, that's what they are.
That is copying.
That is literally
copying. That is literally copying. Oh
my god, mate. That is literally copying. Literally
Copying. I'm under the legal system,
mate. I can leave the country whenever I
want. I can do whatever I want. There's
not even going to be no court in in in 3
years. But yeah. Yeah. And you you pe
you you think by grassing that's
winning. That just makes you a loser. I
know these other people don't don't tell
you this, but you know all of this
grassing stuff, it just makes you look
like a loser. And the only reason people
don't say anything is because people
don't like me. That's just loser
behavior. That's not even winning. Even
if you had somebody [ __ ] over with the
legal system, that's just being a dirty
little grass. That's not winning. That's
far from winning. That's losing cuz you
had to cross. [ __ ] hell. Isn't that right,
Dy? [ __ ] I would feel I would feel so
much of a loser, right? If I literally
had to come online every day, starting
beef, and then go running crying to the
police every week for 6 months. I would
feel like such a [ __ ] loser. I
wouldn't even come on social media
again. But people people in here don't
have shame. So there's no point saying
this. But I I'd feel like a loser. I
literally would literally I'd probably
hang myself to be honest with you. I
would probably probably hang
myself. And I know how how much it takes
to pursue these police now cuz I had to
do it. Court advised the solicitor advised.
Um, you know, it's it's not like they
call the police once and No, no, no, no.
Like, they literally have to keep
pursuing them. Yeah. That's what losers
do. That's not winning. That's not
beating anyone. Even if they had a
million and one bell conditions, that's
just what losers do. Losers that can
give it but can't take it cuz you own
them in every aspect of life. Just
grassing. That's not winning. [ __ ] loser
[ __ ] But again, these people got no
shame, eh? Oh, nothing, man. Nothing. Nothing, bro.
Nothing. Nothing at all. Anyways,
I have to start PMing people on Reddit now.
No one's got me No one's got me [ __ ]
up by the legal
system. Not one little bit. Leaving the
country in less than four weeks. No, not
me, mate. Got the wrong
person. Definitely. Definitely. Definitely not
me. You must go to the wrong person. Bye-bye
now. Uh, bye-bye
now. Anyways, moving
on. These people can't help themselves.
I say one thing about Chev Cole and
people copy him and they're on me like a [ __ ] bonnet,
mate. [ __ ] grasses.
They have got no shame as well. They've
literally got no shame. [ __ ] hell,
man. No shame at all. This community is so
spasticated. If you'd even call it a community, that
is. Well, bro, it's in [ __ ] It's in
less than four
weeks. So, not right now, but I will be doing
Yeah, I can't believe how much these people defend
women. How much they defend
women. But it is scary though how long
it's been going on for. It is proper
scary. It is proper proper proper scary, bro.
And it's like you know before you go out
it's never going to
change skin. No. So talking about
yourself but you need to come up with
some better comebacks. That's boring now
man. We all know that I'm better looking
than anyone on this community that's
shown their face. You need to stop this
whole balding skin nose mate when you're
already bald skin and you're [ __ ]
ugly. You need to stop this [ __ ] now.
It's it's getting boring. you
know. Yep. We'll do, man. You need to
stop this [ __ ] now, man. It's getting
boring now. The only people that are
bored in skinned and ugly is yourselves.
And you're just a lot older. Stop
talking about yourselves every day. It's
not healthy. Please. It's not nice to
see it. It's not nice to see these
people talk about themselves every day on
YouTube. It's really not nice, man.
People are [ __ ] old age
pensioners. It should pop up maybe. Maybe, bro.
Maybe I need to get some painkillers, bro.
Yeah. Anyways, I'm going. And I'll be back later.