[ __ ] hell, man. [Music]
[ __ ] you bastard, man. Oh yeah,
man. Just chilling today.
Yeah, nothing to do today. [ __ ] b up
my [ __ ] head. Probably just sleep to be honest. Must be bored. Oh, good.
This country is so [ __ ] in
it. Yeah, it's [ __ ] [ __ ]
man. The women in it. The weather is
[ __ ] in it. It's a [ __ ] country to be
in. [ __ ] England. [ __ ] Old
England. [ __ ] [ __ ] everywhere as
well. Bad, isn't it? Bad, bad,
bad. Can't even speak to people without
pretending they got
boyfriends. What a world we live in.
What a depressing world we live in. And
the madest thing is, you know, I was
speaking to my friend about yesterday is
how long it's been going on. It's not
like it's 3 weeks, 6 weeks, 6 months.
It's been going on for years. This has
been going on for [ __ ] years. You
know what I'm saying? Absolutely years
and it ain't about to change because if
something would have changed, it would
have changed by
now. People don't [ __ ] try to pass
their driving test [ __ ] four years.
You know what I'm saying? It will never
ever ever change. And the and and the
only people that say it will change is
people that don't even leave the
house, don't have any life experience at
all. Think you forgot to [ __ ] reply,
mate. Yep. You'll never
change. Never ever
ever. It's going to be fed up today, I think. as
usual. Have to go out and get more
numbers and hear more. I've got
boyfriends. Oh, wow. Really looking
forward to that. Yeah. Really, really
looking forward to
that. Doing the same [ __ ] every day. Same
bar. The same [ __ ] bar. or [ __ ] that
never changes because it's been four
years. Yeah. Four [ __ ] years. [ __ ]
Well, it's been longer than four years,
but I mean the approaching's been four
years. Yep. 27 and counting. They
haven't been shown any
different. Wow. It's not
that people can say what they like until
the cows come home, but until you see
different, then you won't know any
different. can't take people's word for
it. You know, it's not how things would
work in in a court. You
know, you need to be shown different
that people don't ignore, that people
don't time waste, that people don't only
reply to negativity. We need to be shown
this. People making games of me, bro,
these people have always been
obsessed. Are you surprised? Making
games of me, bro. These people have been
obsessed for years, bro.
[ __ ] is that? Like, are are you
surprised? They've got nothing to do.
They're just fat ugly people that don't
even leave the house and got a life.
What better do they have to do, man,
than to sit on YouTube all day and got a
life? Yeah, I'm just chilling today. Yeah, man. Yeah.
So until I find somebody that's not a
ghostaster that doesn't only reply to
negativity, then I'll just keep saying they're the
same. How long was it going to take to
find these different people? Greasy. It's been
years. It's been absolutely
years. You know, I had to argue with
that old friend in Canada. Um and she blocked
me, you know, cuz I was being I was being sarcastic.
You know how long how many more years? 10, 20
years. If they were truly different, you
would have met someone that's different
by now. Don't only reply to negativity.
Don't be an ignoring [ __ ] Don't be a
ghost. Don't be a liar. But they're all
the same. You ain't going to find
someone that doesn't fit into this
category. So, that must mean they're all
the same. Every single and last one of
them. From where I'm lying. Well, as
long as it's standing, I'm actually lying down.
Boring. You know what? I might go out on
Thursday and Saturday as long as I can
fit the budget into about 150 for them
two days cuz I don't want to spend more
than 150. And we'll see in them two days
if there's anyone different like people keep
saying. Isn't that right? Like they keep
saying, I've got nothing better to do in
them two days. So, we'll see. Let's
really really see how different these
people are. And I'll probably make about
50 what? I'll probably make about 50
approaches in two days. Let's really see
how different these people are.
Yeah, I might just do Thursday and Saturday. [ __ ]
it. Going to do today. My foot hurts and
Wednesdays are [ __ ] So yeah, I'm going
to do um I'm going to do Thursday. I'm
going to do Thursday and
Saturday. Yeah. Hopefully I get proven
wrong. And by Sunday, Grievy, I'll be
coming and telling you about all about
it about how I was wrong and no no and
how it took four years and no
no. I'll be back. Well, I'm I'm not
going to be on tomorrow cuz I'm going to
do it all day. Then I'll be out all day
Saturday and you'll see me Sunday maybe
with a nice roast
dinner and I can tell you all about
it. Okay with you, boss.
Is that okay with you,
boss? You know, I think that's okay with you, boss.
Yeah. Is that okay with you,
boss? Be good to walk for a long time as
well. I haven't got nothing better to
do. And if I can fit into the budget,
then uh not cuz I'm scared cuz I need to
save money for other things, you know? I
have other things to think of, travel
plans to think of. I can't afford to be
[ __ ] wasting money in this country. I
shouldn't even be wasting time to be
honest, but I got nothing better to do
for 3 weeks. So, we'll see. Eh, we'll
see if these different people really
exist. Can't see happening. I can't see
it happening, Greasy, because of how long it's
been. It's [ __ ] four years. Three,
four years is a long time to have not
had many stuff out of it. It's quite a long time,
bro. I was just saying to uh Gregy that
I'll be going out Thursday sending it. I
don't think I'll be drinking and I'll be
out Saturday as long as I can fit the
budget into about £100 to £150. And I'll
be back Sunday telling them all about
it. how they're not all the same and I
don't know all women even though this
has been going on for years and I'm just
going to come on YouTube and tell you
all about it. So, you won't see me
Thursday. Uh you won't see me till
Sunday after today. So, yeah, we'll see
how different they really really are.
Let's see these people that don't
pretend they've got boyfriends. Let's
see these people that don't only reply
to negativity. Let's see these people
that don't ignore. Let's see these
people that don't randomly ghost. I'm
sure we'll see it Thursday and Saturday
if there are these people that aren't
aren't all the same. [ __ ] aren't all
the [ __ ] same. Yeah, right. We'll see
in it. I'm going to do two days. [ __ ]
it. I'm going to try and fit the budget
into £100, which I think I can do it if
I if I just drink beer. Well, 150 I can
spend 150 is fine, but not [ __ ] over
that when you're trying to save. So, we'll
see. We will see.
But see these people that aren't all the same,
eh? Aren't all the same. My [ __ ] ass.
They're all the [ __ ] same. Everyone
last one of them. At least I'll get the exercise
in. Might even do Sunday as well. Nah,
I'll just do Thursday and Saturday. The best
days. Yep. And And the only worrying
thing, Grez, is I'm getting um getting
old. Nowhere near 30. I'm nowhere near
30. These people say I'm near 30 because
they're the ones that are in their 40s.
But, you know, kind of getting old,
Grezy. You know, you you need to really
start doing this. You know, traveling
now, you know, 3 years. Uh, need to do a
lot in 3 years. We need to do the lot in
We need to do a lot in 3 years,
bro. Like, we don't want to just take 35
before we start doing this stuff. I was
only going to do one day, but I thought,
"Fuck it. I've got nothing to lose by
doing two days. I don't have to work or
anything, so [ __ ] it. You
can't Well, the reason Well, I I can
explain to you why I can't enjoy enjoy a
day without um women one time is because
you've got to pay 20 to get into
clubs. Yeah, I done my traveling [ __ ]
two years ago, but I'm going to start some more.
It will always be the same, Cherry. It
will always be the same. But at least I
get some exercise
in. It will always be the
same. We will never change in this
country. Never. And like I said, it's
how long it's been going on for as well.
It's not like it's 6 weeks, 6 months.
It's been going on for years. You know,
that's that's that's another thing. me
and Antman, you know, we we said that
it's how long has actually been going on
for and he's actually done something
about it cuz I am in 3 weeks, you know,
but like you should learn from his
mistakes or other people's mistakes. You
know, you're young enough to know now.
You don't need to be 33. You already
know what it's
like. But obviously, I ain't got nothing
to do in them two days.
So, there's literally I have nothing to
do, no responsibilities, no nothing to
look after. I have the money to spend.
So I don't mind, bro. [ __ ]
it. But it will always be the
same. Doesn't matter what day, what year, it's
they're not interested in this country.
End of. So shouldn't take you. And and
the thing Adman was saying, he's like,
"Oh, you've been up and down the country
as well." So it's like, he said, "If I
was you, I would only do one day a week,
but I'm stubborn. I'm a stubborn [ __ ]
That's why I won't just do one day a
week." Well, I should be doing one one
day a week, but well, you shouldn't even
be doing any days a week because you
know what it's like. You've been up and
down the [ __ ] country more than most people.
So, you know, you've been up and down
the country. Nothing changes ever.
There's no there's no major difference.
Even though London is the worst for it,
cuz they're just all stuck up. So like
but there's no major differences in in the different cities. Um
yeah, maybe I might just do one day. Who
knows? All right, that's recording for
the year. What's the news? Just fed up.
Fed up with this country. We've ped up
trying to date in this country. I'll be
gone in just less than four weeks now.
Anyways, it'll be Grezy's problem. It
will be Greavves country to deal with.
It won't be mine anymore. It will be Greavves
country. I put the fresh gums on and the
trainers and send it for two days and
then I'm done, bro.
Yeah. Hopefully we don't get get I've
got a boyfriend. Who's going to get it,
man? You in England. All you ever get
same old, same old, same
old. I think that woman ghosted as well, by the
way. I never said I was done with new
outfits, but you fought wrong. I never
said I was done with new
outfits. No, not me. So,
yeah. Yeah, this has been going on for [ __ ]
years. And the only thing that's going
to stop this is having a plan B, which
is what I've got. You can't stick to
plan A because you'll go insane. You
need a plan B. You need to get out of
here. Oh, thought you done well with new
outfits. Yeah. Yeah. I'm [ __ ] half
asleep. Yeah, I did do well, but they
started being [ __ ] again.
I did do well, but then they started
being [ __ ] again. I just I'm leaving
the country. End of that's that's it.
I'm leaving in in just less than four
weeks. I'm sick of having the same
conversation, the same [ __ ] for four
years. [ __ ] four, three, four [ __ ]
years. This has been going on, you know?
Years and years and years. Imagine
somebody harassing you for [ __ ] four
years. Imagine that. But imagine someone
harassing you for four years. Think
about it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I went on a
date and then she said that she couldn't
date me cuz I'm not
Muslim and now and then she said she'd still meet
again. Uh meet again. Yeah, LJ, it's all
about personality and mindset. That's
why you've never had a woman. That's why
you have to simp overex. I know, bro.
Because you know all about women, yet
you're the one that has to s over absolute
muners. You're the one sing over mters, not me.
Why are you always by yourself on
Saturdays? No friends, no woman, no
life, sat on YouTube talking to a bunch
of people that don't even leave the
house. Bro, you are Billy no mates. You
are Billy no mates. We have never seen
you with a woman or any friends. Bro, I
was at my mom's on Saturday. Yeah,
literally. Yeah. I went out to with with
my friends. Yeah. I I looked right. You
was on YouTube. I don't know how it
popped up. I come back. You was on
YouTube all by yourself. You're a loner.
You're a complete and utter loner, mate.
You think I'm going to waste my energy
talking to a [ __ ] talking to a
[ __ ] 40 odd that don't even have a
driving license, that's barely travel,
that's never been seen with a friend,
and that's never been seen with a woman.
Are you [ __ ] mad? You are like the
lowest of the [ __ ] low, you know?
You're like, bro, you're in you're in
your 40s and you have nothing but
YouTube. You're a clown, mate. Honestly.
Yeah. Go have a
timeout. Yeah. I'm not going to buy. You
can have a timeout. Go listen to what I
said. This guy's never been seen with
He's got no friends either. Have you
noticed he's got no friends. He's sat on
YouTube all day. All day. And you know
this whole blaming women thing. He's a
s. You've seen how he s over
beex. Yeah. You've seen how he s over
beex. Bro, this guy doesn't have a clue
about women. You know, all of these
people like Ricky Milling. Oh, you're
blaming women, bro. They don't know what
women are like cuz they got no life
experience. They just sit in all day
just like Lord
J. And yeah, you can blame women because
it literally is women that are causing
you these problems. So, who else are you
going to blame but them? We're not
blaming our car crashing on women. We're
not blaming us falling down the stairs
on women. We're blaming women for acting
like [ __ ] which is obviously it's
women. We're not [ __ ] blaming women
that [ __ ] Jesus Christ was [ __ ] born. You
understand? Oh, he let belly get, bro.
He's a [ __ ] He's He's nothing but a
[ __ ] I even said that time when you
was he was in England. Come on my door.
I don't live with my mom anymore. He's a [ __ ]
bro. He's a fat little nerd. Little
[ __ ] No friends, never been seen with
a woman, bro. He's a loser. Everyone on
his channel is a loser. I don't even go
on his channel
anymore. It's [ __ ]
weird. Weird spasticated
community. I don't [ __ ] go on it, but
for some reason when my mom went on it,
it popped up. I didn't even go on the
chat. I literally didn't even read the
chat. I just looked. I was like, "Oh,
he's on YouTube again on a Saturday
drinking, talking to himself."
Oh, I don't know, man. Don't
know. Maybe another
month. Women can get the women. Yeah.
Yeah, he can get the women. He can get
women that will [ __ ] anyone. He will get
a woman that would literally shag the
whole of YouTube. And that's been with
Money Mike. Yeah, he can get those
women. Yeah. Yeah, he Yeah, he can get
those women. Yeah. Women that have no
money, that live in a hostel, that's
achieved nothing in their [ __ ] in in
in in in their 30s. Yeah. That does
cocaine. Yeah. He can get them women.
Yeah. So, good for him, bro. I'm happy
anyone. Wouldn't get with her if you paid me.
wouldn't get with her if you pay
me. And if I keep wasting time in this
country and money in this country, I
won't be able to do other things. At the
end of the day, it's been going on for
3, four years. That's a long
time. But he's not getting regular sex
for free though, is he? Because he's
happened to buy alcohol. He's happened
to buy weed. So, he's not getting
regular sex for free. Not many people do
get regular sex for
free. But yeah, this person anyways has
has has stopped reply replying this
Muslim. So just typical England, is it? Typical England
experience. If we're lucky, next week
we'll get a date that waste our time
again. That would be
great. Yeah. Typical England experience.
I don't expect anything
less than [ __ ] I think that's
that's the that's the work way to put it now.
converting? Um, no. No, I [ __ ]
haven't. To answer your question, no,
I'm not converting to no Muslim. And
I've got Muslim friends as well.
Are they actual Muslims?
No. Then I won't be able to eat
piggies. I won't be able to eat piggies
if I done that. [ __ ]
converting. She ghosted anyway. So
yeah. So I want to go to William. I want
to do a gamble. Um, Joe, I want to put
£1,500 on on the Thursday and Saturday.
I'm going to get I've got a boyfriend.
I'm not looking for anyone. Numbers that
don't reply. Numbers that reply then
stop replying. And maybe a date that
then ghost you after. I want to I want
to ask William Hill if they'll put a bet
market on that. Then I'll start gambling
again. I could just earn money betting
betting on the dating game in this
country. I'd never have to work
again, you know? That's what I might do,
you know, just start um they need to do
a a a market for the dating game. I'd be
a [ __ ] billionaire because I can
predict everything. I could even predict
what's going to happen, what time it's
going to happen, how it's going to
happen. I'm an expert in this. You know
how people are experts in dogs and
horses and [ __ ] race cars and [ __ ]
I'm an expert in the dating game, so I'd
easily make a lot of money doing
it. Yep. So, they should let me bet on
it. I'm an
expert. Oh, yeah. He's a s. That L is a
proper proper proper proper s.
He has no clue how life
works. Blaming women. Well, who else
would you blame? It's them that are
giving you shitty experiences. You
[ __ ] you [ __ ] idiot. Who? They're
the ones that are giving you shitty
experiences in life. No one
else. But no, I wouldn't convert to
Muslim because then you Well, I asked
this question yesterday. I said, "Well,
if you convert to Muslim, would you then
have to still get
circumcised?" But I mean, even if I was
a [ __ ] Muslim, he'd say she would
then turn around and say, "Oh, well, I'm
not looking for anyone." But either way,
it's just even if it's a legitimate
reason, after the legitimate reason
reason is solved, it would then be
another excuse. It will always be the
same in this country, you know, like it
will always be. It's been going on for
years, you know, like that's it. Years
and years and years and years and years
and years and years. And at one point,
do you say to yourself like enough is enough? You
know, everyone's advice is wrong. You
proved you've proved everyone's advice
wrong as well by how they say that
you've met you meet people through
friends. You've never met anyone through
Um, yeah. That's because they're not
proper Muslims. That's because they're
born in this country. Yeah. That real
Muslims don't do it. People that are
only Muslims by name do. Yes. Muslims in
this country that are not proper Muslims
drink and maybe aren't circumcised, but
actual Muslims don't drink, don't eat
pork, and are
circumcised. There's a big big difference.
Yeah, I've cooked pork before when my
friends been watching and his face was
in disgust. They hate pork. They don't
like drinking and they only eat things
that hala. Trust me, I know these
things. And the Muslims that you are
talking about are [ __ ] of Pakistan
heritage that are born here, not ones that come
over. They would never drink, mate.
Trust me. Trust me. Spend a lot of time,
you know, with with this.
So they don't even drink in a in a pub
because a juice that's been in the same
glass as alcohol, they wouldn't drink it. You
know, we're not talking about these westernized
ones that were born here because they're
not proper, you know what I'm saying?
They're not proper Muslims. So
What's the point in there? There's a big
point in being Muslim, man. You
know, you can eat
halal. Muslim is not the worst thing to
be, bro. The worst thing to be is a
vegetarian and vegan. You can live a life being
Muslim. You know, technically you could.
It's not that hard.
Nah, no. It's not going to be the same
result. Sherry, women are not all
different. They're not all different, mate.
Nah, it's not going to be the same, bro.
What makes you say
that? What makes you say it's going to
be the same? Of course it ain't, bro.
Come on. It's not It's not been
happening for three or four years,
Cherry. Now, the only thing you can do
really honest honestly the best thing
you can do is go to your gym, give up,
and just leave this country. That's
literally the only positive thing I can
think of. There's there's nothing else.
There's nothing else. Make you, you
know, go to your gym and just leave this
country. That's all you can do, man.
Seriously, if anything was going to
change, it would have changed. Like, you
you don't understand in 3 years how much
[ __ ] has changed. You get more money,
you get less money, more less money.
This has happened, that has happened.
Like so much has happened over the
months. This stays the same. You meet
the same women, you meet the same
people, you know, like your life will
change a lot in three, four, in three,
four years, you know, even if you're not
doing anything like things come up. No,
no, no, no. This is exactly the
same, you know. It's exactly the same.
It's the same
story, you know. You should have had
about a million relationships by
now. So, yeah, just they're just it's
just going to always be the same thing in this
country. I was speaking to an American
on Saturday. She was from Ohio. Yeah,
Ohio. And she just wasn't asking me any
questions. And then I was like, "Oh,
when when do you go back?" She said
Sunday. And she's from America. I said,
"Where in America?" in Ohio that she was
going back Sunday, 10 hours on a plane.
The fact she wasn't asking me any
questions back, I just aborted. You
know, it's a red flag when they don't
ask you anything. When they don't ask
anything, they just just you just need to walk
away. I need to find one and keep her.
Ah. Uh, what do you think I've been
doing for the past 3, four
years? Okay. I need to find one. Uh,
what do you think I've been trying to do
for the past three or four years?
Spending all this
money? How many years is this going to
keep going on for? Find an eight and
keep her. Oh, okay.
Right. I've not tried doing that for the
past 3, four years, have I? I've just
been sat in. Oh, right. Okay. One
second. Yeah, it doesn't matter. She's
got someone else now.
it doesn't matter. She's got someone
else now. And it and I didn't like her
anyways, you know, her whole
attitude and um the games and [ __ ] like
it was best that she just went away to
be honest. The entitledment. I think
you're best off sticking to escorts.
[ __ ] man. That Brazilian escort sucked
my dick so good last week. Bro, you're
best off just sticking to
escorts and going Thailand. I actually
believe it, bro. I actually believe it.
you're so best off just doing that or
joining the porn industry. I think so
because you're never going to find
anyone here. Whether it's for sex,
whether it's for a relationship,
whatever it is, even a friendship, you
can't It makes me laugh when people say,
"Oh, you need women friends. You You
can't make friends if you don't have any
women friends. You won't be able to make them."
Because that's why I kept talking to
this person cuz she said, "Oh, she don't
mind being friends." I said, "Okay,
well, I can try with her friends." Now, she stopped
responding. It doesn't matter what
you're looking for or who what are you
looking for, friends uh that are women,
relationships or sex, you're not going
to get it. You're not going to get it.
It doesn't matter what you you're
looking for, it's not going to happen.
Even if it's not sex you're looking for.
You could just be somebody, right, that
wants a relationship and you're still
not going to find it. Because as soon as
you approach, you're still going to get
the same I've got a boyfriend. I've got
a boyfriend. I've got a
boyfriend. Same with like trying to join
a friend group. It's not going to happen.
So yeah, it sucks, man. Only thing now
to do is
leave. You might as I don't want something easy.
I I can't be bothered with anything
long. Yeah. That's why I've been
traveling up and down the country for
about four years. Yeah. Because that's
so easy, isn't it? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Like going to
Manchester 10 times, going out on a
session, going all over the country.
Yeah. Cuz that wasn't long at all. No.
No. No. That was easy, man. Especially
when I used to wake up like 8:00 in the
morning. It was so easy, you know,
traveling up and down the country.
Didn't cost any money. Yeah. Yeah.
Nothing long about that, is it? No. I
want something easy. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Something easy. Like I've not approached
a million people. Like I've not gone up
and down the country a million times.
Like I like I didn't go to Wales in two
weeks the same two times in a week.
Yeah. Yeah. Nothing's long about that.
Know what I'm saying? Easy. I want
everything easy. Easy.
Yeah. Do you know what I'm
saying? Uh I've had chances with women.
Uh no I haven't. I've had chances with about two
people. Maybe two two or three people
maximum. Maximum. Let me think. Two or
three people. Yeah. Maximum. And the
rest of it is and and it doesn't matter,
mate. Even if you've had chances with
three people, you should have had
chances with three million people. With
the effort that you have put in, you
should have had more op you should be
having options now. You should be lying
in bed next to someone. Okay. So what if
you had chances with three people? What
in in three or four [ __ ] years? Come
on, man. That's one person a whole year
for your effort. No, bro. That that
doesn't even count. It's been years.
Years. Not 6 months. It's been
years. You know what I'm saying?
It doesn't matter if it only takes one.
So what what what so what's someone got
to do to find this one? Someone that's
not me. Go out and keep approaching on
the street, keep dealing with the, "Oh,
I've got a boyfriend. I've got a
boyfriend." No one should have to keep
dealing with that. Women don't have to
deal with it. Women don't have to put
themselves on the line. So why should
we? You know what I'm saying? you know,
so they don't have to work. They don't
even have to put their neck on the line.
I I rephrase what I say that they can
get any man they want. I think that was
a bit silly and a bit childish, but they
can get dates whenever they want and if
if something goes wrong, they can just
find someone else. We prove that with an
evil person in America. We prove that
with an evil person in America. and
other people that are not evil, if they
get bad dates, they can just go and find
another person. We can't just find
another person. We got to start all over
again. I have to start all over again
from Thursday. You have to start all over
again. All over
again. You have to start all over
again. You have to do the lot again.
You know, I wouldn't mind if you had if
you had to put effort in and then you'd
actually get something out of it. Then
I'd be like, "Oh, well, it's just the
way society works. It's just the way the
world is." But the [ __ ] up thing about
it is even when you put effort in, you
get nothing out of
it. Even when you put effort into it,
you still get nothing out of it. So,
it's not that women have it
easier and, oh, you put a little bit of
work in, then you get whatever it is
you're looking for. You have to put the
work in and you still don't get anything.
You still get the [ __ ] I've got
boyfriends and [ __ ] all sorts of
stupid [ __ ] that they do and say,
bro. Yeah, it's bad.
So yeah, how long does someone have to
keep doing it
for? And you don't know how many people
I've met. You know, I have had way worse
dates than [ __ ] good
dates. I've not had loads of chances at
all at all at all at all at all. You
know, and you should be getting dates
every week. Every time you go out and
you try, you should get dates whether
they go anywhere or not. You, with the
amount of effort that I've tried, you
should be getting dates every day. Every
other day. At least every other day.
Just like women have dates every
day. Lined up for every day.
Yeah. Okay. Let's listen. One second.
charges with the only one I can think of
is the the Sig the Sig and the one from
Nottingham. Well, we say we've got
chances with them, but they could just
flip at any time. So, nothing is
guaranteed with them at all. So, yeah.
And anyway, so you think that's worth
three or four years of
effort? You think that's worth three or
four years of
effort? Do you think Morgan had to go on
the street every other day approaching
men? Let's let's let's use somebody as
an example, right? Do you think this
[ __ ] had to go on the street
approaching men to get a relationship or
sex? Do you think she had to do that for
four years going up and down America? Or
do you think [ __ ] Anybody had to do
that for three, four [ __ ]
years. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. One
second. One second. The one that I
kicked off with probably Okay, okay,
listen. The one that I kicked off with
would have ghosted me
100%. 100 million%. Yeah. The only two
that you got right there. The only The
only one that you The only two that you
got right there is Sig and the
Portuguese. They're the only two
guaranteed. And maybe the one from
Nottingham. That's the only one
guaranteed, mate. You know, the one that
you're talking about that I was having a
go at the park. Okay. Okay. I can I can
answer that question. I met this person
on Sunday. We went to the same park. We
walked bought them Nandos. Not cuz I
expected anything, because I just wanted
to eat and I was bored. So, I done
everything right. And guess what? And
guess what? And guess what? She says how
she wants to be friends because I'm not
a Muslim. Then I said, "Okay, that's
okay." And she said she would meet again
100%. I've asked her how her day was
going. No reply. The one two months ago
when I done everything right and she
claimed she can't feel the vibe, you
know. Let's start talking about these
ones where where people didn't have a go
at people. Exactly. You know, [ __ ]
And a Portuguese one was from a [ __ ] dating
app. That one in a park would have
ghosted 100%. 1
million%. They would have 1 million
trillion gillion% ghosted. 100%
mate. Sig the Portuguese. Maybe the one from
Nottingham. No, no, no. we can't focus
on the positives because the negatives outweigh the
positives. So I said, "Oh, I'll just be
her friend." And then I was happy just
being friends. If she said she just
wants to be friends because the way I
see it is it's hard enough to even make
[ __ ] friends with a [ __ ] woman and
I can still stay with her friends. So to
me it wasn't all a loss. I was like,
"Okay, [ __ ] it. I'll just try with her
[ __ ] friends." Now she's gone quiet.
What the [ __ ] You
know, [ __ ] annoying, mate.
You know what I'm saying,
bro? You shouldn't have had this. Why
should you have this to put this much
effort into finding someone as well? That's another
thing. It's [ __ ]
mad. It's [ __ ] madness. The negatives outweigh the
positives. And when a woman tries to
relate, oh, I've been on negative dates.
I've been on negative dates. Wow. Why
don't you go around the street, start
approm Imagine women had to do what men
did. That would be hilarious, bro. Could
you imagine they had to go on the street
approaching men? It'd [ __ ] kill them.
It would kill them after one day and
then they tried to relate to you. They
tried to relate to you about
dating. [ __ ] off. [ __ ] off, mate. You
know what I'm saying? And then they say,
"Oh, yeah, but we've got to deal with
creeps." Yeah, I'd rather deal with
creeps. I have to be careful when I go
out and because somebody might go and
steal my phone. Wow.
Wow. I don't get nose bleeds,
mate. I don't get nose
bleeds. So, yeah. Yeah, you've only
really had three. But what actually
proved from these this years is
everyone's advice is [ __ ] Joe. You
meet people through friends, [ __ ]
You meet people through dating apps. Uh,
[ __ ] Since it's not happened since
I came back from Belgium. You meet
people when you least expect it.
[ __ ] All the people that you've met
is from approaching. So surely that says
that their advice is wrong though.
Surely that says their advice is wrong.
Surely that must say that their advice
must be wrong then cuz if you're 27
right and that's the only method that
sort of made you mean people then they
must be wrong. They must be wrong in it says says
reality [ __ ] says reality they're wrong. So
yeah. Yep. I don't get nose
bleeds. I've not had a nose bed for
about 3 years. Try again. Try [Music]
again. But another thing is I I think
it's not it's not about the past, Joe.
It's it's more about the future.
Do you remember the your your the past dictates your
future? Like what happens nine times out
of 10 when you go out and this is the
future. Remember what I told you about I
could forget the past if the future
would be different. But the future is
not going to be different because it's
been going on for years. So it's not
even if we forget the past now and we move
forward. We know we know what what's
going to happen because it's the same
every time. It's the same boring [ __ ]
every time you go
out, you know? So that's why the past is
relevant to to to to now because it's
going to happen again. It always
happens. The same thing always
happens. It does when it's to do with
dating. It does when it's to do with
dating. 100%. When it's to do with
women, it definitely does because it's
the same thing every time you go
out. It does. Every every week is like a
replica. I've got a boyfriend. I'm not
looking for anyone. No, no, no, no.
Numbers. I don't reply. Numbers. It's a
replica of the last week. So, it it it
dictates it. It dictates what your life
is going to be like in England. If you
can't even speak to somebody without
pretending they've got a boyfriend. If
you can't even enter a nightclub without
spending 20. It doesn't look good, does
it? It really, really, really, really,
really doesn't look
good. It doesn't look good at all, you know.
So that just kind of be like, "Oh [ __ ]
this is what we're what we're dealing
with." So it actually does dictate the
future when it comes to
this cuz you should be married now. You
should be with someone now [ __ ]
messaging you every day with all the
effort that you put
in for all the money that you've wasted as well.
You take you took 1% positives out of
all of the things I done, bro. You're
really because it's like now we know
even if we get a date, they're just
going to waste our time. If we're even
lucky enough to even get a date, they're
just going to waste our
time. So, am I supposed to not think
that's going to happen
then? What would tell me that that's not going to
happen? Don't know, bro. You
know, so yeah, actually the past does
dictate the future because it's always the same.
Understand? Yo, you all right,
bro? Yeah, I'm [ __ ] fed up, bro. I
don't know what I'm doing today. My foot
hurts cuz I didn't even get a proper sleep. disturb
sleep your foot and all that
it [ __ ] it's a depressing life bro
it I'll be in Thailand and soon anyway
so not a
problem yeah it's not a problem at
Yeah, just be patient, bro. Yeah,
there's plenty of bad experiences along
the way. There's plenty of more bad
experiences along the
way. You never know till you try. Eh,
Cory, you never know till you
try. You never know till you try. That
isn't that right, Cory?
Yeah. Yeah. This country is [ __ ]
mate. He should be on his way to Thailand
now. Whilst he's left me in [ __ ] England.
[ __ ] Do you remember that, Call me when
we used to approach him that I've got a
boyfriend? Do you remember that? I've got a boyfriend.
Oh, I've got a
boyfriend. Oh, I got a boyfriend.
[ __ ] hell. I'm not looking forward to
hearing that, Joe. I'm really not
looking forward to it,
bro. No, not that again. Well, I only
got it two days. No, no, no, no. I only
got it two day. Two times in the past
two days I went out. But I will get it
again. I'm sure I'll get it again this week. imaginary
boyfriends. I'm sure I'll get it this
week. Yeah, I'm looking forward to
it. More boyfriends that were never with
them. You know, most these women are
feminists as well and they're not even
with men. That's another reason, you
know, that they're chatting [ __ ] because
a lot of women just go their own way and
don't bother with men, but then they
claim that they've they claim that they've got
boyfriends, which just doesn't make any
sense at all because most of the couples
that you see are are with each
other. They should legit put on Reddit,
bro, that they're not interested in this
country. So then people would stop like
wasting their time. I'm not talking
about me. I mean talking like generally
general people like I've been confident.
I've been not confident. I've had
different outfits. I've I've done
different haircuts. You name it. Like
they need to put anywhere that's like
America and England. Everyone should
just go to Brazil or
Thailand. That's what they literally
would say. They they need to say that go
to Brazil or go to Thailand or go to
Colombia or any kind of third world
country because it doesn't even need to
be a third world country. It could just
be anywhere in Asia. It could [ __ ] be
Japan or China, you know. It could it
could be anywhere but
here. Yeah, he's going Anman's going to
Thailand again today. He's not coming back. So yeah.
Yeah. I do you know what? I fancy a breakfast
today. Weather spoons
breakfast. Haven't had one for ages.
I think I'm a bit
late. I got some pork
chops. What? Why is my statement still
not come up? Yeah, I think I'm going to
get breakfast, man, to be fair. And I'm
going to have some pork chops later.
So, you might get a girl in Thailand.
You You might You might No, you won't
get a girl in
Thailand. No, you you don't It's not You
might get a girl. You will get a girl.
No, I still like to go out once a week,
Cherry, because it's something to look
forward to. I still like to go on the
beers, you know, once a week because
it's something to look forward to to
make the money back anyways. And if I do
two days, then I would have just fitted
it into the budget £100 maximum, which
is in a week. I spend like 80 pound a
week. I always do
it. Yeah. Saving, bro. I still save when
I do it. It's
only about 100 a week.
I'm not going to spend like400 pound 350
400 pound bro 100
maximum probably do 50 if I wanted to
for two days but I go I go out once a
week everywhere everywhere.
Yeah. Well, wouldn't you rather that
than keep hearing I've got a boyfriend,
I've got a boyfriend. I've got a
boyfriend. Yeah. Okay. It might not be
the best, but it's better than hearing
about I've got a boyfriend. I've got a here, you
know, you get Brazilian women here that
use people for their passport. They will
marry them. But I was like, that's an
exchange, you know? You you you know,
you you give them you give you marry
them, they get a British passport, they
stay here, they stay with you. It's no
different than an English woman using
you for money, using you [ __ ] resources.
And you know what I'm saying?
So, I'm going for breakfast in a minute.
Starving. Have some pork chops
later. Some nice old bill.
Oh, breakfast for a while, bro. [Music]
But yeah, I might not go out this week.
I might not. I might not to be honest.
And you know what? It's not even just
about the money, Cherry. It's just the
same old [ __ ] I've got a boyfriend.
boyfriend. Just It's just them stages
you have to go through. That's why
sometimes I don't even go out. Not the
money side of it. It's still quite cheap
drinking, you know, beer. I stick to
beer now cuz the hangover isn't
that. Yeah. It's not even about the
monetary side of it. It's just boring. It's boring, bro. Boring,
son. You know, here I've got a
boyfriend. I've got a boyfriend. It's boring, bro. Proper boring,
lad. [ __ ] gets me down. It does. Nah,
bro. Just play it. But it is boring. It is proper
boring. Proper boring. But yeah, I need
some um sausages and bacon down meat.
I need some bacon and and sausages down my throat. Yeah.
Well, I'm going to be back later.