Go. People on Reddit are [ __ ] stupid.
These people are [ __ ]
stupid. They must be stupid on
purpose. There's no way they
can no way they someone could be that stupid, but
they're being stupid on purpose. um
responsibility. I've noticed mate in
this society don't have a bad word to say about
women. Not a bad word to say about women. It's
mad. I ain't got a bad [ __ ]
word. Why am I speaking to multiple
women? Isn't women do it? speak to
multiple men on dating apps. Bit hypocritical is it? Bit
hypocritical. That's hypocritical.
Yeah. [ __ ] son of it, man. Jesus.
Yeah, this [ __ ] bogus, mate. [ __ ]
bogus. [ __ ] bogus, lad.
just on the
Reddit talking to people that ain't got no life
experience saying old. I was just
playing graph. I thought I sreas I'm
aiming to complete it within a couple of
days. I'm aiming to complete it within a
couple of days, bro.
Yeah, [ __ ] it
up. All the little
characters. All the little characters, mate.
Yeah. So why don't people tell people to
give up in this country if no one's
interested? I don't understand that
cuz firstly you say people people say
you meet someone when you least expect
it or like all this [ __ ] advice that you
get and then the next thing is that no
one's interested. So shouldn't people be
told to keep going to Shouldn't people
be told to go to Thailand or [ __ ]
Brazil or something if you know the
people in this country aren't
interested? Yeah. name Mon can't find a
normalized guy. But um I mean should
they just should they be telling people
just to give up then if that's the way
it is? So I'm just a bit confused to be
honest. Shouldn't most men be keep being
told they're going to die alone
or instead of giving people false
hope? So if they know this, why do they
give people false hope on Reddit and other forums? [Music]
And I don't understand to be honest with
you. Blows my
mind. [ __ ] blows my mind, lads.
completely. Yeah. And man on his way to Thailand out. Yep.
a place where you don't get I've got a
boyfriend. It's not my It's not quite my turn
yet. Yeah, not quite my turn, mate.
Yeah. Yeah. I normally just drive
around, but I'm doing missions now. Yeah.
had a nice
pizza. Got a fat belly now. I know.
Yeah. We live, we get bad experiences, then we
die. We live, we get bad experiences, we
get [ __ ] over by women because they're
all the same, and then we die. Yep.
Hey, not not a fun life at all. No life
for any young
person being depressed in a depression country.
Nah, [ __ ] boring, mate.
Nah, it's mad, isn't it, PC? We live, we
get bad experiences with women, we get
tormented, then we
die. [ __ ] really, is it? [ __ ] life. We
live, we get bad experiences, nothing
changes, and then we die. We gain
weight, then we
die. No, never be as fat as him.
Never. Never. Never. Never. Never.
Never. Did we die?
The shore is depressing in it, PC, and
there's nothing you can do to change it.
Unless you leave the country, of
course. Life ain't what you make it. I completely disagree,
lad. No, I won't. I'll never be as fat
as any of the people on here.
Never. I had I just had a nice pizza. I
have a t-bone steak as well. I'm not
going to eat till tomorrow.
Why? Nothing changes,
PC. Nothing ever changes, lad.
Yeah, nothing ever changes
s. So, how many people out of 10 do you
think have boyfriends that say it?
Steven Howard. I think three out of
10. I think about three out of 10. Three
10 for maximum.
Maybe three or
four. Yeah, about three or
four. What about
you? What about you, mate? Yeah.
Boyfriend. There's loads of feminists
out there. Loads of women that go their
own way and
stuff. I said I was going to go out
Saturday, but it's the boyfriend [ __ ] I
can't be hearing it, bro. It's
boring. I just can't be bothered,
bro. It's always I have a boyfriend. I
Wait, I have a boyfriend in
it. Can't be
bothered. [ __ ] B
me. Yeah, it's boring, bro. [ __ ]
boring. Why go clubbing if you have a
boyfriend? Because they don't have a
boyfriend and they're talking out [ __ ]
obviously cuz none of my sisters right
when they were in relationships even
before they had kids ever done that.
Never. And the only time that they did go
out was like once every six months. And
it was not lying out, mate. Trust
me. Trust me, bro. They do not have
boyfriends. 90% do not have
boyfriends. Yeah. Got no boyfriends.
They're just [ __ ] They're just evil
clunts. That's what they are.
All kinds of love giving people bad experiences. [Music]
I can't believe this Scottish person
said I should convert to Muslim. Yeah, he
would sat here drinking a bottle of Coke.
Water on my head. Oh
god. Yeah, I spoke to her today actually.
today I'm all right, mate.
No, I don't want to hear. I've got a
boyfriend for a while. It's boring. Bors me. That's
funny. Yeah. So, I've got a boyfriend. Yeah. Boyfriend, boyfriend,
boyfriend, mate. In Thailand, in Brazil,
you don't hear it.
Bro, they ain't interested in this country.
I know I know you're talking
about. See, this is the thing, Gregy,
right? They know that women aren't
interested in this
country, but yet they will tell men that
they need to try.
And I had this woman say to me, "Why are
you speaking to so many women?" I was
like, "That's hypocritical." Cuz women
speak to several different men. If
they're not exclusive to a man, if
they're on like a dating app or
something, they're talking to several different men.
So that's hypocritical. Unless someone's
exclusive to someone, they're talking to
[ __ ] different men as well. Several
different men. Probably why they [ __ ]
ghost you. That's hypocritical, isn't
it? Don't know who you're talking about, mate.
One second. Not about me voice. Yeah. Byebye.
Weirdo. Yeah. Greasy. Um, Antman said,
"You're going to get it wherever you go.
I've got a boyfriend and they should go
to Asia." He says they're all
NPCs. I said, "We've had it everywhere
we've gone, is it?" He said, "We have."
Yeah. They're all
NPCs. He says, "The only place you're
not going to get it is
Asia." That's what he said.
Yeah. The only place you're not going to
get I've got a boyfriend is
Asia. Is that true, Grezy?
and Brazil as well. Yeah.
You got a boyfriend, do
you? Oh, where is he then? Do you remember
that? [ __ ] some women are like
stitch. Nah, I don't want to speak to a
woman. They're all
evil. They're all evil
[ __ ] No, all evil, mate. Yeah.
I have a
boyfriend. I have a
boyfriend. And man said to me, Cherry,
the only place you're not going to get that is
uh is Thailand. Yeah, I've got a
boyfriend. Any pork chops? Nope. I've
got a T-bone
steak. I'm not going to eat it cuz I had
pizza today. I had a breakfast and pizza.
So, I probably won't eat again
today. Keo steak for
tomorrow. I've got a boyfriend. I must
have spent about 30 on food today.
Jesus. 30 on food.
going to start running out of cashew,
matey. Yeah, but you're always going to
get I've got a boyfriend
here. You're always going to get it.
That's why I probably won't even go out
this week to be honest. I said I was
going to go out in it, but I probably
won't even go out to I probably won't be
I probably can't won't be bothered, bro.
I just go
cinema cuz it's just going to be the
same. Mother got a boyfriend in it. So [ __ ]
it. Boring, bro. It's
boring. Yeah, I was just playing some GTA. Yep.
Yeah, I was playing Grand Theft
Auto. Yep. And on just under four uh
weeks. Yeah, man. See if I've got a I
get I've got a boyfriend over there. Never,
mate. It's like these Brazilian escorts,
man. They're [ __ ] hot. That's why I'm
thinking I'm just going to stick to them
when I come
back. One gave me the best [ __ ] I
ever had. I might as well just stick
with her. [ __ ] it. Cheapest chips in
it. Not for this community.
Nah, I don't put content on this
channel. I put on my other
channel. I only do piss taking videos on this
channel and just live streams. No.
Yeah, Cherry, man. I don't think I'm
going to go out Thursday or Saturday,
but I think I was trying
[ __ ] I can't be bothered,
man. Cuz if nothing's happened in 3,
four years, it's not going to happen
now, is it? I mean, you can still go out once a
week. You're not going to find the other
channel. No one on this community is getting
it. Yeah, she does swallow. No one on
this community is getting
it. I'm going to wait until she comes
back to um where I
live. I'm going to wait until she comes
back to where I live. Then I'm going to
go straight to her
again. That's how you know she gave a
good [ __ ] [ __ ] Oh my god,
bro. Um there's no point in London.
There's no point anywhere in England or America.
There's no point anywhere in England.
They're all the same NPCs like what Ant-Man
said. It's a shame about that American
last week. She seemed all right. She
seemed to look all right and stuff, but
she was just a complete
[ __ ] Just same [ __ ] Not interested. Don't ask
question. Yeah. Same [ __ ] isn't it?
same same continent.
Uh I want that Brazilian
[ __ ] Yeah, she was talking back. She
didn't say she had a boyfriend, but it was very
like just no interest, no
enthusiasm. Funny enough, French women
are not the worst in the world. They're
actually really friendly. French people.
No, no, no, no.
French people are rude, but French women
are nice. They'll give you their number,
then they'll troll you. French women are
not rude. French people are rude. Every
single time I've come across a French
woman, they've all been nice even on the
street, but then they [ __ ] you in the
ass when you get the number. So then
they [ __ ] you over at a later date. They
will they'll be nice to you, then
they'll troll you. I've had it with a
few French people. They're the worst
trolls. Funny. They're funny trolls, but
they're they're trolls. And it's been
every single French woman I've met as
well. They're worse, but they always
reply back and they'll [ __ ] with you,
but they'll never you'll never get with
one. But if you approach one on the
street sober, she'll give you a number
and everything, then they'll literally
just troll you. Yep. I've had it about
three times with
them. But in a way, it's kind of funny.
So, but it's not funny. But, you know, but Americans are
worst American. Yeah,
Americans. This Muslim woman's still
talking to me. So, I don't mind, man. I
don't mind having her as a friend in it.
[ __ ] it. I can try and meet people
through her friends. It's not a problem in
it. She said she'll meet again. So, I'm
not converting. So
yeah, I guess it's just nice to just
have a friend in
it. Well, I've got friends anyways, but
you know what I mean? Like I went out
and made a new friend by myself, so
better than nothing. I try and meet her
meet her friends in it, I guess. But
yeah, I can't convert. I love my piggies
too much. I had sausages and bacon
today. I went for breakfast.
Yeah, man. I want that [ __ ] Brazilian
escort back, bro. [ __ ] hell. Yeah, probably.
Yeah, I don't mind just keeping her like
as figure, you know, one day she might
change her mind or whatever. Um,
and yeah, I can try and meet people
through her. So, I try, you know, better
than nothing, is
it? I might not have the same models, you know.
The best two [ __ ] I ever had was the
American in the
alleyway and then the [ __ ] Brazilian.
Oh my [ __ ] god. Oh, you can still
remember them as mad as
well. Just too mad, bro. Too mad.
Yeah, that's cool. So good,
bro. It's not even just about sex. You
can't even find relationships in this
country. Yeah, like I said,
anyways, no, she won't become Western. No
way. Come here too late for that.
The thing is Cherry is that yeah if
something was going to happen it would
have happened by
now it would have happened it would have
happened by now 3 4 years is a long time
you know you've been doing this
approaching [ __ ] for ages and you know
something was going to happen it would
have happened by
now we need to start doing other things
because we're going to waste our life on
this if we if we don't stop
now yeah I don't mind paying her bro you
pay anyways in [ __ ]
it. You uh Yeah, you might as well just stick to
[ __ ] You might as well just stick to
escorts. She's talking my balls as well.
Yeah, she's the other side of London
because they move around. She's all the
way in [ __ ] north London. I don't
really want to go north London. And
Shink Shinki is back in London as well,
but she's like 40 minutes away from me. Yeah. Yeah. Uh
You deal with it by giving up,
bro. You deal with it by giving
up. But what I understand is people on
Reddit say that you'll find someone and
stuff, Jerry. Yeah, they know that most
people in this country are not
interested. They've said it themselves,
but yet they'll still give
advice. Why do they tell people to give
up and leave? They know the country is
like what what they're like in the country,
but America, England, Canada. I fell out
with my Cadian friend cuz I told her how
I feel about women. Then she kept
[ __ ] trying to [ __ ] defend them
again. Defending, defending, defending
them like they can't do no
wrong. So they say, but I've been I've
been hearing that since I was about 15.
Yeah, I've been hearing that since I was
about [ __ ] 15 years of age, matey.
Yeah. What happened to that
19year-old? I miss her coming around and
giving me a [ __ ]
No, she's found someone else,
mate. She's found someone else,
huh? I don't have high standards. Not at all. Yeah.
When I saw her last as well, she gained weight,
too. Yeah, you can. Yeah. What's the
idea? She gained weight last time as
well, so she looked
better. She swallowed my [ __ ] Steven Howard. Yeah.
Yeah, why would I stand outside a bus
stop? What the [ __ ]
If you don't find shovel co attractive, you're
gay. And give it a [ __ ] Yeah, 100
fucking%. That's why I can only think of
her now in terms of like escorting that.
She said, "You almost choked me to death."
Oh yeah. Ow.
Yeah. Oh, really? Is it still up?
What? Which one is it? Is it He's still
alive now. Is Is that the
one? I went to Nando the other day with that Muslim.
We went to Nandos
together around my
area. I guess she said shut madnesses e. Yeah. Yeah.
That LJ is a [ __ ] loser, mate.
Imagine being 40 odd and having not a
single friend to your
name. [ __ ] that's embarrassing, bro. He
is a proper loser, mate. Yeah.
I can't believe that. That would be Ant-Man's fourth
time he's been to Thailand. That is insane,
bro. Four times. That is a madness, bro.
[ __ ] hell. That is nuts,
bro. Only if you give me a
[ __ ] I might
consider four times Thailand. That's a
long That's quite a few times, isn't it?
Jesus Christ. I would have got I got to
go in basically 3 weeks now four
times. That is a [ __ ] badness, bro.
Yeah, but look
[ __ ] How does he afford it? It just
saves up it.
But the second trip [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. It
was. He was saying that he won some
money. That's how he could do the second trip.
Yeah, but he went back straight after
cuz he won five grand on the football in
it. Yeah, that's madness to have been
four times in a [ __ ] year. [ __ ]
me. That is a madness, bro.
That is a madness.
Sorry about that,
bro. Film outside the court. Why is
anybody filming outside the
court? There's not going to be no
[ __ ] court. The
[ __ ] That's mad how he's been to
Thailand four times in a
year. That's [ __ ] mad, mate. No,
that's that's mental health, isn't it?
That's [ __ ] mental health, mate. Is
it? Uh, when you when you show me Yeah,
man. I can When you show me 12 grand,
come back to
me. Yeah, man. When you show me 12
grand, come back to me, buddy. Yeah,
man. Yeah, I haven't got five grand. Okay, bye-bye. [Music]