I just got done another
Yeah, I just don't [ __ ] um Yeah.
This guy say he's going to teach me. He
can't teach me. Tell me I'm not in
Birmingham. You're scared to come to London.
Broki, stop it, man. Prepare it, bro.
I told him you can't teach me, bro. You
can't even do it yourself. And you're
[ __ ] man. You can't come in your [ __ ]
That's why I gone away has to come to
Birmingham for you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Hey, you know what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah, he's a [ __ ] idiot. I've not
come to Birmingham for a while. I don't
need to go Birmingham, bro. I can just
stay in London. It's the same [ __ ] here.
Oh [ __ ] Put this phone on George.
Y just on another one, bro.
Upstairs. Hey, mate. I've got a feeling
this is going to be a long day, bro.
This is going to be hard, bro. Too hard. Really hard,
bro. So, I've done three in Weather
Spoons, but two of them are sober.
Oh, good. We're going to get another. We will get
sun. We will get something. [ __ ]
hell. I don't know what the [ __ ] I was
thinking. I just started that approach. Oh
man. But guess what? These same women on
Reddit will complain they can't find a
normal person. They can't find a decent
person. So, as long as I know I've tried
and I'm going cinema tomorrow, I'm
happy, bro. I'm a happy man. But I'm
made. So, that's all
good. I'm free in this weather. It ain't
even 5:00, man.
Must be [ __ ]
mad. I must be a mad boy.
Look who's on Instagram. It's funny. I just
See, I was going to I was going to do
that one behind me though, Jay. But she
reminds me a bit of my
um my [ __ ] buddy from last year. So,
yeah. Kind of ain't done it. But I've
done three in this [ __ ]
place. I've done [ __ ] three, mate. [ __ ] it.
finally dying. What the [ __ ] man?
So I'm live in a V [Music] installed.
Oh Lord J, listen to me. Lord J, listen
to me. Listen to me clearly.
Yeah, listen to me, bro. Uh, they just
aren't interested in in this country, brother. Uh,
They just ain't interested in this country,
brother. Listen to me.
Yeah. I'm telling you, man.
100%. This is hard, bro. I think it's
got the hardest country in the world to do
to uh find friendship, sex,
relationships, whatever they looking for.
I don't know why he's saying I'm a
[ __ ] [ __ ] What happened to him?
But it's got to be the hardest hardest
country in the world. It's got to
be got to be, man.
He's [ __ ] up
there. There's snow and these
people. Bit like the weather, man. You know,
anyway, he's leaving in a couple weeks anyway.
Sir, you [ __ ] love
me. There's some people over there, but
I don't know. Look at them. They look too
young. This country is so hard.
Did I go to 76? I got in the live stream.
Yeah, I'm gone, man. Let's go. Let's go, guys. Yeah.