Get out there, boy. I'm on the [ __ ]
right now. Oh
[ __ ] I'm on the [ __ ] R, mate. Forgot
it's [ __ ] You know
what? I'm just a stick on the video now.
We're on it, babe. On it, bro.
Licky. No, we're [ __ ] licky, bro.
Yeah. No. [ __ ] lick me. Yeah,
boy. That's what we're
doing on it, bro. [ __ ] me. Still ain't
got one number. [ __ ] hard,
bro. It's hard for some reason today.
It's [ __ ] hard,
bro. [ __ ] hard,
bro. The white rum on it. Got the white
rum. I'm on it,
boy. Get on the white ramen. Yes.
What? Can't be the white one. Can't be
it. It's cheaper. That's why I opted for
it. Even though I know tomorrow I'm
going to be regretting it. Eh.
Yeah, I'm going to be regretting it. I'm
it. But [ __ ] it. No regrets on this channel,
bro. I'm in it too
deep. Too deep,
bro. I ain't got one number so far.
[ __ ] not even one
number. Madness. I must have done about
[ __ ] mate. I must have done about 10
approaches. Most of them are sober.
[ __ ] none of them. None of
Just having the W and I'm going to
regret it when I wake up, but I've got
some privacy. I boo [Music] madness. Yeah,
man. I didn't got one number yet. What
the [ __ ] I've sent so many approaches,
but I'm going to do another one. One
second. Let's go get video. Trust me. Hopefully.
Hopefully. Hopefully it
does. But I [ __ ]
labor, mate. I have been saying it all
[ __ ] day, mate. With a with an A.
Yeah. Not a U. They weren't having none
of it. Got NPCs,
unenthusiastic [ __ ] boyfriends, you
name it. You name it. Same old, man.
old. It's been the same old
man. I'm thinking of doing them two, but
they're not really my
time. I might have done it by now. Not contemplating
it. Not contemplating it, bro. I'd
already done it.
What's that? What's that?
We get some pictures today,
bro. We might not got some early, but we
get some now,
bro. We didn't get any earlier, bro, but
we're getting somehow, bro. We're you keeper.
I'm drinking white rum. [Music]
She I'm trying to One
second. Bro, I'm going to [ __ ] go and sit there.
Oh, she is. Well, I'm going to send
it. She will send it,
bro. I'm [ __ ] going to send it.
want to give it a
I'm sending it one
They've all got [ __ ] boyfriends,
mate. I just don't want I just don't
want no bartender, bro. They've all got
boyfriends. They've all got [ __ ]
boyfriends, bro. Mothers,
bro. They've all got boyfriends, bro.
[ __ ] they all got boyfriends. How
about this [ __ ] I told Adler about
himself today, bro. It's my turn,
bro. They all got
boyfriends. I don't know why. Yeah,
I they share so much [ __ ] bro. Listen,
brother. I have said it all day today,
bro. Most of them were
sober NPCs, bro. MP [ __ ] C. I'm going
to [ __ ] send it today, bro. I'm
getting my free numbers, bro. Watch.
Man's getting these free numbers. Believe
that. Man's getting these free numbers.
I said, bro,
100. [ __ ] me.
Yeah, literally, brother. My phone got b.
Yeah. Oh, what kind of nick is Oh, bro.
Oh, come on. Nick is Nick and that ain't
it, mate. I ain't got one number so far.
I've been sending it all day, but I'll
get one. Don't worry, I'm getting free.
Man's getting free. Trust me. I'll lick
it. Trust me.
Yeah. Well, [ __ ] me,
man. [ __ ] Yankee over
there, mate. This country is impossible,
bro. It's [ __ ] hard, bro.
hard. I've been sending it hard, mate. [ __ ] hard, bro.
[ __ ] I just shouted out the bartender. [Music]
I said I weren't going to get rum here,
but it's cheaper. So, I thought, "Fuck
it. Let me just have the rum." You know,
I have a few Chinese. I thought, "Fuck
it. I'll have the rum in it cuz it's
cheap." I'm going to be regretting for
two days. No cinema for me.
No cinema for me tomorrow. Hey bro,
none. I'll be [ __ ] for three days, bro.
I just done [ __ ] one [ __ ]
approaching a bartender. She said she
had a boyfriend, bro. I don't about
[ __ ] about five on street. No
drinking. There's one over there, but
she ain't that. I could give it a while,
but even that fit. I mean,
hey, hey, she's not even fit.
I done so many approaches today, bro.
Most of them are sober.
I don't create a weather spoon alone,
bro. It's like what Antman said,
equality. They just ain't interested in this
country. That don't mean I'm going to
give him f I'm not going to give him
stem, but I don't even like
her. You know what I'm saying?
But don't really like her, but looking
at her right
now. I was going to do [ __ ] her over
there, but she with a [ __ ] group of people, including
us. Rest in peace tomorrow. We
[ __ ] madness, man.
I would do it if I ask I'll send it
right now live. I send it live right
now. I'll send it live right
now. Hey, you got
boyfriend? Yep. On my own, bro. Sending
it as usual.
Yeah, I'm out here sending it. But I've
done so many [Music]
sober to do one full of laws, bro. Do it.
But where's my buddies? My buddies are
coming later, mate. Where's your
buddies? Sat home on YouTube.
Yeah. Where's your buddy? Just sat at home on
YouTube. Ain't got a line. Yeah. [Music]
I don't like her though. That's the
thing. I could, but I don't like it.
I got another drink here. Yeah, boy. [ __ ]
I should be at home playing [ __ ] Grandpa
Thor. Yeah, I
am. need to go soon. But I need to send this [ __ ]
Yeah, I didn't share any
bro. Hey, notorious. I've been sending
it sober, bro. All I've been getting is
the same old, bro. I only done about
three approaches sober. I've done like
10 in total, bro. Three of them were
[ __ ] boyfriend [ __ ] Boyfriends,
mate. Mate, I've been sending it. Sober, bro. Same
old trying to find someone I like, but I can't see
anyone. Oh, [ __ ] me, bro. One second. [ __ ] you.
Well, I know about I know about [ __ ]
freeing the weather spoons. One freeing
Give it a
while. You want me to do that one,
Victoria? [ __ ] do it. You say do it,
I'll [ __ ] do it. Even though I don't
like her, I'll [ __ ] do
it. Even though I don't like her, I'll
[ __ ] do it,
bro. Hey, go away, little
S. You say do it, I'll do it. 100
Excuse me. Sorry. I just wanted to come
over and say that. I thought you
What's your name?
Hi. Where you from?
Obviously, but where?
Kingston. You know that's that's greater
London to be fair. Yeah. I've never been
there before to be fair. My friend
always says we should go out and maybe
What's your plan for today?
Your friend. Okay. I'm just drinking a
drink, waiting for my friend. Yeah. I
was going to say, can I get your number?
You're gay. Lesbian. Oh, no. Really?
Okay. Well, have a good day. Yeah. No,
no, I believe you. Yeah. At least you
didn't say you had a boyfriend, did it?
I thought you wanted me to suggest you
were lesbian, bro. What the [ __ ] is
going on, bro?
And you know, I was first when I was sober,
bro. Talking about yourself, you're
already overweight. Stop self
protecting. Stop self protecting. We
already know what you people look like.
Fat and ugly. No protector on my
channel. Uh, no. It's not a new one,
mate. It's been going on for years,
mate. I need to go piss, bro. What's
up? I'm going to
number. Yeah, I'm going to lick
number. [ __ ] now. I actually never
Same old same old I'm wearing the app. One
second. This is bad, bro. Hey,
notorious. I've been sending them all
day. Sober. Sober. Tipsy
drunk. Been sending it all day, mate.
All [ __ ] day, bro. I want to come out
with an injury tomorrow. Trust me.
Thank you, bro. Cheers,
bro. These people that are trying to
call me chubby, they're all fat and
ugly. They're self projected. We don't
have that on my channel,
bro. I'm getting free numbers. I
promised my friend at home to come out
with three numbers by myself.
Mate, I've been sending it all day,
mate. You don't know.
She was going to be into it, bro. [ __ ] me.
Yeah. Pair of [ __ ] if you ask me,
mate. [ __ ] pair of
[ __ ] Loads of people going to start
coming in, bro. Loads of people are
going to start coming in, bro. Don't
watch that. People will start coming. B, it's
London. You like the approach? Sick is
it? I got to go to the [ __ ] pictures tomorrow,
bro. I'm in a club and they're sat at home on
YouTube. Sat at home on
YouTube. You understand? Notorious. I'm
out on a in a club sending it even
though I've got no numbers so far. I
don't know how I've got the numbers, but
I've got no numbers, but I'm going to
get some numbers. They're on YouTube.
YouTube [ __ ] group. You know what I'm
saying? Told you, bro. If if Notorious
is my boy, if he says do it, I'll do it.
[ __ ] bro. Notorious is my boy,
bro. So, like, if he says go, if he says
jump, I say how high.
[ __ ] we got that love relationship, bro.
We got this love hate
relationship. Guess she's got his
provisional me. Don't need to carry
passports. I'm looking at them too. They ain't
good. Their anxiety will never allow
them. Never, bro. And bear in mind,
notorious I done about seven
sober. Seven sober, bro. I done most of
them sober. I even done two at the same time sober.
I don't want from
Scotland. You're from Scotland. Scan.
Yeah. I'm from
Scodian Scal. That's where you're
from. Mate, you're talking about
yourself. You are fat. Stop talking
about yourself. Bye-bye now.
Self projection. Listen, notorious. You
got to understand, bro. On this
community, all it comes down to is self
projection. Bro, listen to me, bro. Notorious, bro.
Listen. We have done the same content
for years. They talk about their own
lives. Like when they call people skin,
like when they call people fat, like
when they call people ugly. Bro,
brother, they're talking about
themselves. I'm wearing £400 right here.
Nothing. It's nothing to me. Everything
that they say is about their own lives,
brother. Listen to me. Yeah. These
people in their 40s, 50s, they live,
their lives are [ __ ] They know that
their lives are [ __ ] So, what they do
is they come on YouTube and self-reflect
to try to get other people to their
level. It's all about
themselves. Fat, ugly, no friends. It's
all about themselves, bro. I've got a
friend coming here today. And um I I
plan to go out by myself, but he wants
to come out. You want to come out? All
right, cool. Come out. They self-reflect
their own lives. These people are fat
and ugly. They got no hair. They got
nothing, no friends. They They're their
own lives, bro. It's their own lives.
Mothers straight out these people.
They don't even leave their house. They're self
perfectors. They're fat and ugly. Look
at some of these people, bro.
Please. They're not going to They're not
going to kill the vibe,
lad. They're not going to kill no vibe.
We're sending it today, bro. And we're
getting numbers. We're definitely
getting numbers, bro. I don't know how
we've not already got a number, but we
haven't, which is [ __ ]
on her. She a bit
big. He's a bit big.
Told my friend to come through, mate. I
told my friend to come
through. Never getting kicked out.
Monty, they don't know where I am,
lads. They don't know where I am,
bro. Hey, they don't know where I am.
I ain't got nothing today, bro. But ah,
[ __ ] hell. I've got a boyfriend. Hey,
Notorious, listen. You know, I was
thinking with Ant-Man. Yeah. It took him
31,32 finally leave. I was like, I'm
doing that at 27. I'm doing that at 27.
Like, I know, bro. These
people are are [ __ ] stuck up in this
country. I know I'm not going to get
nowhere, but I got things to do
tomorrow. But listen, bro. I'm going to
Thailand for 3 weeks. 100%, bro. I'm
doing it at 27. I'm doing it way before
I'm 30, bro.
100%. Hey, Lord J. Yeah.
Yeah. Hey, listen. L got a little [ __ ] Listen.
Yeah. I love how you you know, to be
fair, we should we shouldn't
even we shouldn't even be [ __ ] going
mad. Listen, Lord J, listen to me. Yeah.
And man's in Thailand now. This is the
fourth time fourth time he's been this
year. It's It's been It's been fourth
time he's been this year. That's a
madness. Fourth time this year. And
listen, I like how you owned the Virgin
yesterday. You know, the Virgin. I love
it, mate. I love you owning the Virgin.
You own the Virgin every day. I'm
[ __ ] there, mate. You know what I
mean? And you know what, LJ? You've
never been to I You've never been to
Asia. You've never been to Asia.
Antman's been four times. I'm going in
three weeks. What's your excuse? I'm
going in three [ __ ] I'm going in
three weeks. I've got it all booked.
It's all booked, mate. It's all [ __ ]
booked. It's all booked,
LJ. Yeah, it's all booked, mate. It
ain't taking me to no 31, bro. Taking me
to 32. [ __ ] that.
You know what I'm saying, bro? [ __ ] that.
Yeah, mate. They're repeaters, isn't
they? You can't afford the arms. Can't
afford the arms, mate. You can't afford
the arms, mate. Come
on. Yeah, you can't afford the
gums. But I'll probably be waking up
tomorrow, notorious, with a [ __ ] foot
ache. I'll be waking up with a foot
I [ __ ] put a No,
100%. I've done
so so many approaches today. RJ, it's
not even a
joke. It's not a joke, man.
Serious. Yeah, I can't afford it, mate.
400 done. Track two trainers. Bam. We're
getting some [ __ ] today, bro.
100%. We are, bro. We're getting some
[ __ ] 100%. Even if it takes all
night long, mate. We're getting one.
I hope so. Anyways, we
are getting trust.
Bro, what the [ __ ] Your choice. I've
done so many sober, bro. So many sober,
bro. I swear to
God. So many sober. Yeah. 50. Oh, is
good. Nah, Timy's just [ __ ]
Timastic. I'm drinking white
rum. White rum, buddy. Why Rob? I
already asked the bartender out.
Nah, mate. You don't know nothing.
You're just a
s. Not at all, mate. You're just a simp.
Watch how many numbers I get today.
Watch how many numbers I get today. But
I'm going to lick it, bro. Trust
me. Trust me, bro. Watch how many
numbers I get
today. Look at Bro, you can't even leave
your house. You [ __ ] Hey Monty,
listen bro. Let me tell you something.
Monty, these people don't bother me
because they're just self
projectors. They don't bother me. Do you
understand, bro? I've been on this
community longer than you. They're
self-reflected. They don't bother me,
bro. Know what I'm
saying? Self [ __ ] reflectors.
You know what I mean? They talk about
themselves every day for a living. All right.
50. I need to go shoot, bro. I need to get some
Yeah. Yeah. About a bag. What about all
the other times I wasn't wearing a bag,
[ __ ] What about all the other times
I wasn't wearing a bag? You little
[ __ ] [ __ ] off, mate. Listen,
Natalie. Mate, mate. Mate, mate, mate,
mate, mate, mate. Listen. What about all
the other times I wasn't wearing a bag?
You [ __ ] idiot. What was the excuse that
time? Yeah, I just got out of jail,
mate. It's a good thing. If I look like
I've just got out of [ __ ] jail,
that's a [ __ ] good thing then, mate.
That means people flock towards me then,
is it? If I look like I've just got out
of jail, then mate, that's a good thing. That's
aim. Yeah, man. Listen. Oh, [ __ ] you,
Natalie G. Listen, I've seen you talk
[ __ ] about me. I've seen you talk [ __ ]
about me a million times. Listen. Oh my
god. Bro, listen. Yeah. Let me tell you
something. I would love Yeah. I would
love for you and your mom smash my head
against the table like you done Money
Mike. Yeah. That ain't got no money. R.
I would love Listen, listen. I would
love to come to Birmingham. Yeah. And
you can headline dead, bro. You're
talking about yourself. Self projection.
Listen, Nelly. Listen. I would love for
you to come and smash my head against
the table. I will knock you both out,
bro, in less than 10 seconds. Dumb, bro.
Yeah. Listen. Yeah. The only L's I've
took is from a [ __ ] man, bro. Yeah.
Listen, let me tell you something,
Natalie G. The people that you've been
with, they're [ __ ] idiots, bro. Yeah,
mate. Natalie, listen. Let me tell Let
me be for real with you. Yeah, let me be
for real with you. Yeah, it's not I
don't look bad. They're just self
projecting. Natalie, listen. This is
between me and you. Yeah, listen. I
listen, Natalie. I have seen you talk
[ __ ] about me. Not my looks, not about
that. I've seen you talk [ __ ] about me.
Yeah. These people that are commenting
above you, they're self projectors. They
talk about themselves. Don't waste your
time. You know more than me. Listen,
we've been on this community now. Yeah.
How many years? Since I before I had
[ __ ] sideburn. Listen, Danny. Before
I had these sideburns, before I had
these sideburns, we was on YouTube.
These people have been doing this for
ages. Yeah. You know what I'm
saying? What I'm saying? These people
talk about themselves. You should know
about this stuff. You don't need to
reply to them, bro. They're
self-reflectives. Know what I'm saying?
Bye-bye. [ __ ] You should know this.
You are talking [ __ ] about why don't I
don't pull. Listen, I would love you to
smash my head on the table. I would [ __ ]
you and your mom [ __ ] bro. You don't
even know. Listen, you and your mom,
bro. Yeah. I would [ __ ] you up, bro.
Like, no. No different. Like, no, no,
no, no. It won't be no money mic [ __ ]
Yeah. You would get [ __ ] up real life.
Listen, you get [ __ ] up real life.
Trust me. Trust me, bro. Like stay where
you are in Birmingham thinking that
because you done this to a [ __ ]
because you done this to Tiger, but come
and do it to me, bro. It will never
happen. It will never happen, bro.
Believe that. It would never happen. You
would get [ __ ] up. You and your mom
and Roy. Believe that, bro, for sticking
your little [ __ ] on where you are. Yeah.
You know it ain't it. You know, bro, you
know. You know it, bro. Come on. Yeah,
you know it. So that's
it. That's it, Ali. Bro, you know it.
You get [ __ ] up, bro. Like I would
tell, bro. Listen, if you was in London
right now, I would tell you. Come and
smash my head on that table, bro. You
would get You will get [ __ ] up, bro. Literally like
this. No joke, bro. I swear. Listen. No,
no, no. I think it Yeah. You get [ __ ]
up real life. Trust me, you would get
[ __ ] up real life, bro. And you never
come on this YouTube knowing how you put
someone in hospital. I swear to God. I
swear to God, bro. You wouldn't. Money
Mike is a [ __ ] You don't understand.
He's a [ __ ] bro. Listen, I have met
the guy four years, bro. He was [ __ ]
it, bro. Yeah. The first time I was in
Birmingham, shut it. The second time he
come to London, shut it. He ain't about
that life. You understand, man? You need
to know this
stuff, mate. I don't care if they hear
all of this. It's the truth in
it. I'm going try to smash my head in.
You get [ __ ] up, bro. I swear to God you
would talking about yourself, self
projecting. And listen, I I don't like
you, Natalie, cuz I've seen you talk
[ __ ] about me. I've seen you talk [ __ ]
about me, Natalie. Yeah, I've seen
you. I've seen you talk [ __ ] about me.
You know what I'm saying? I've seen it.
I've seen it. You talk [ __ ] about me on
Monty's. That's it. That's why I say this
[ __ ] Hey, these people that are
commenting, they're self-reflectors. I
can't beat Tiger. Are you mad, mate? I
beat two of them, you [ __ ] mate. I
punched him and he fell on the [ __ ]
floor and a [ __ ] freedom pass went on
his back. I can't beat Tiger, mate. He
got [ __ ] chucked on the floor. If you
watch the If you watch the video
properly, you can see where he got
punched on the [ __ ] floor and a
[ __ ] freedom pass on his [ __ ]
back, mate. He got banged on the floor.
Go watch the video properly. Yeah. Don't
watch what only [ __ ] Tra puts
up. They got [ __ ] up. Trust me. And Timmy ran away. That's
it. I'm going to do something in a bit.
There's no one
here. But I would send some ball. The
freed smack him up. You know what I'm
saying? Watch the video properly. When I
was in the garden, I slipped. [ __ ] all
that. Anyways, we're not talking about But some
[ __ ] will pick up, man. Pick up. Hey,
do you want me to see that one over
there? Do you want me to see that one over there?
Hey, you want me to see that one over there,
bro? May I need the bag here, bro?
Listen, do you want me to do it? Yes or
no? Say yes or no and I'll do
it. Do you want me to do it? Yes or no?
Excuse me. Sorry. I just wanted to come
over and say that it's cute. What's your name?
Where you from?
Lebanon. You live in
London. Ah. Vacation
or Oh, you live here.
Oh, what made you move to London?
That's awesome. You sound American.
Yeah, you sound a little bit though.
Still, what's your plan for? How old am
I? Why' you ask that?
Guess you're going to say all of us.
Guess how old are you? Um 20 [Music] months 21
o 20 almost
but we're here. No I work in London but
not in a spot. I look like I'm working
as well in a trackuit.
No, I was just talking. I just bought a video. Yeah,
I'm going to go and finish my drink
anyways. But can I add WhatsApp?
I don't have Instagram. I deleted three
months ago cuz I felt like I was just unhealthy. All right.
My number. Got her number back. Got it.
I got her [Music]
number. Got her number,
mate. Sound America to me,
man. Got number, brother.
We had two more guys.
Ask me how old I
was. She asked me how old I was. Why did you
ask? My adventures turned up, mate. Got
there at the right time, mate. [ __ ] off
your virgin. [ __ ]
off. She her friend just come
out. Bro, that was a full-on send. Did you see
it? Did you see me? Go over and speak to
her. Did you see me? Go over and speak to
her. In the front on the right. On the
right. The one with the guy that's just
come. Yeah. Did you see it? I sent it in
it 100% bro. You already know man. [ __ ]
it in it. YOLO. You only live once in
a Say again your misses. You waiting for her
today. Who you meeting?
Uh how long you been with your misses?
How long you been with your misses?
Six 10 months. [ __ ] mate. You know what?
Yeah. You should always be speaking to
other people though. just in case like
they one day break up with you. You know
what I'm saying? Because bro, six, seven
months that's probation period, ain't it?
That's the thing. But when they leave,
you're [ __ ] mate. I'm single, is
it? Mate, what do you think I just done?
You just saw me [ __ ] talking to
[ __ ] two people. [ __ ] know what I mean?
Where you from, bro? What? Bush
eating? Oh, I've been eating a few times
when I used to go to
slow [ __ ] [ __ ] mate. Yeah, I'm [ __ ] I'm
I'm east other [ __ ] way.
Yeah. Yeah. Slow is dodgy, bro. It's
dodge. I know all the ways. All the
way. What's your heritage? What's your heritage? Heritage.
I was going to guess that to be fair. Yeah.
[ __ ] at least I got one number. [ __ ]
Same. I got it. I got it. [ __ ] I got
it. I've always been confident, man. Always been
confident. I am [ __ ] bro. [ __ ]
Come on. 53%.
53. Got a
number. Got a [ __ ] number, didn't I,
mate? Then I [ __ ] got a [ __ ]
number, mate. Yeah, boys. number [ __ ]
number, mate. That's [ __ ] mate. I got
one number, mate. We're getting two
numbers today, bro. Don't watch that. I
got one [ __ ] number. I have so many approaches.
So many, bro. What the [ __ ] I should
have got more than
that. What's the time,
bro? Oh, bless her. She gave me a little number
there. She gave me a little
number. Oh, clear lower deck.
Notorious. Listen. Notorious, bro. Clear lower deck. Cleo in
there, bro. I said to this B, bro,
listen to me like two, bro. I I gave I
said this Morgan, listen. I said to her
about two weeks ago at 3:00 in the
morning. Yeah. What are you free or
Friday? I said, "Are you free Thursday
or Friday?" I was going to batter her up
in front of her [ __ ] I don't know boyfriend. But
listen, listen, bro. I was going to
battle her up, bro. in front of her
boyfriend and her dad bro. I'll show you
the keyboard is bro. Shut her mouth,
bro. I was waiting for the response. I
swear to God, bro. I was waiting for the
response. You're not about n You ain't
about none of us. Yeah, you're not about
that life. I said it. Hey, I said it.
Notorious. I said
it. All right. Notorious. Who's behind
it all? Who's behind it all? this whole
Morgan USA is he thing? Who's behind it
all? Who's behind all of it? Like
obviously you you know like LT got
involved and [ __ ] but who who would you
say is behind it
all? Who would you say is behind it all,
bro? Who's behind it all? Cuz there's
always someone that's behind it all, bro.
It's me, bro. It's [ __ ] me. Yeah.
Hey, bro. I'm going to wait. I'm going
to wait. I'm going to wait. Ah, that
Hey, where is this guy,
bro? I said deleted Instagram. Deleted
Instagram. Deleted it. Deleted it. Bro,
I don't [ __ ] with Instagram, bro. I [ __ ]
with [ __ ] right now. I'm
done. My phone's always on 50%. I need
to [ __ ] turn my phone off soon,
man. I will be back. I [ __ ] will be back,
bro. I can't even pee, bro. That's how
bad. I can't even pee,
bro. Did you like that
approach? Did you like approach though, Victorious?
Oh, [ __ ] me. Did you like it? It's [ __ ] sick.
Whatever. It was sick.
Whatever. May I send it? But I'm [Music]
good. I got a number. Yeah. But hey, I
should be getting more. [Laughter]
We're going to get some dirty looks now, man.
Get some pressure.
I got a number. I got a number.
All of this sure your fat. This your self projection. Hey,
listen money. That's just self
projecting. You're fat. You're this.
You're that. That's just self
projecting, mate. This is self
projecting. This is what these people do. They self-project. They
self-reflect. You should know this, bro. Shell projectors.
Right. Listen, I'm out of here. I'll be
back later. I'll be back live later. I
need to send this [ __ ] And yeah, I'll
be back later
100%. In the middle. In the middle. In
the middle. In the middle. ABC.