Yo
yo. Oh, it's warm out nicely, mate. It's blanket. Oh.
just had my um daily KFC. Yep. My daily
KFC. Get up there lid.
daily care. I I was thinking of doing um
posters again of that virgin. What do
you think we just go around the con
again? Do posters make the come up with
YouTube again for another two three weeks? [Laughter] Why not?
Greasy. Why not? grief? Why
not? Why not
grieving? Why not,
bro? You could actually get a waiver as
well. That's the thing we you could
actually get away with
it cuz if they say they call the police
on you, right, and the police come on
your door. Well, they don't even know
where I live anyways. But say the police
come on your door, all you'd have to do
is show the police what they've been
doing for years. The harassment, the
stalking, [ __ ] trying to get people's
money stopped, you know, like you you
actually you would actually get away
with it just like last time. That's
that's the actual thing about it because
all of the evidence that you got on them
incriminating themselves every day. You
actually would, bro. That's the
thing. If you don't
um post a
virgin. Yeah, do that.
is to be bedbound.
That's pretty funny,
bro. Went out twice today. Grievy. I
don't have agriobia, do
I? I must not have agriobia then.
Uh, you're not right,
Grezy. Yeah, I could actually go out
today and send it, bro. Easy. But I just
can't be bothered, bro. tired
and do weather [ __ ] and yeah, there's just no
point. That would mean getting a haircut
and good point, bro. I'd rather stay in
for today. Well, I did do some exercise
walking today. Oh.
Oh, lovely. Oh, I'm all in the nesticles now.
Greasy. Yeah, they all have makebelieve
boyfriends, but that's not going to stop
us. Trust me, when I go out again, bro,
oh my god, it's going to be a madness.
I'm not going to stop,
bro. [ __ ] hell. I'm not going to
stop. Could actually do it today. But
the thing is is I need to get my hair
done and w my moms and [ __ ] Like, it's long, bro.
I don't know when I'll do it, but yeah,
it's a bit long waiting till next week,
but I think we're going to have to wait
till next week, bro. I'm
sorry. I'm I'm getting uh I'm getting
the taste for it, bro. Like, I actually
want to go out and send it, bro.
Yeah. Yep. I said to my mom before, I'm
going for a little walk, and I ended up
in Brighton. I said to my mom before,
I'm going for a little walk. I ended up
Manchester. That was a long little walk,
wasn't it? You just never know where
where I could actually end
up. Oh, yeah. I said I was going for a
walk. Went to
Manchester, come back the same
day. Never know with me. You never know
me. Never know where my little legs can
take me. Isn't that right, Charles? Yeah.
Yeah, Charlie, you know the drill.
It take him anywhere when he's out
walking. I love that. That's ace, bro.
Where you at? Oh, [ __ ] loud. Charlie. Oh,
mate. [ __ ] hell. Imagine nonss went
out approaching. Nah, his anxiety wouldn't allow
it. He'd scared him away with his rat
face. I think the rat face would scare
him away before they even got to
know. Oh, crazy got caught subleting.
Don't sublet. Bye-bye,
[ __ ] Bye-bye, rat
face. You will never know where I live, rat
boy. You'll never ever ever ever know where I
live and what I have. Try again. that
face. Bro, your dad's a [ __ ] nons,
mate. Your dad's a [ __ ] pedophile and
your mom [ __ ] starved you to almost
to death. You little virgin. Yeah, I
might make posters of this [ __ ] again. I
might make posters of this little virgin
again and make him [ __ ] scared to leave his
house. I actually might make posters of
this virgin again, bro. I'm not even
joking. I was thinking about it today
when I was at KFC cuz realistically,
nothing nothing would happen. Even Even
if the police come, bro, nothing would actually
happen. I I was That's what I was saying
to Grievy before this little virgin come
on, I might just pull up posters of this
little virgin and get him [ __ ] up
since he's never ever going to meet
anyone. Just do it all over again. Hand
post them. Doesn't cost much
money. That will shut the [ __ ] rat
phase virgin [ __ ] up for a couple of
weeks. That will literally shut the virgin up.
It would, bro. It would, Charlie. And
you know it, man. Yeah. Amen. Uh, bye-bye, [ __ ] Bye-bye. Bye-bye,
[ __ ] Bye-bye, Virgin. Go and sort your
autism out. Your Peter belly addiction
and obsession is getting the better of you
again. Bye-bye now. virgin.
Leave me alone. You little virgin. You
little ratfaced ugly ratfaced
bastard. You little rat face with no
teeth. You ugly [ __ ] How the [ __ ] can
that ugly [ __ ] talk about anyone's
looks? He looks like a He looks like
[ __ ] He looks like
Gollum. [ __ ] ugly
rat. Ugly little virgin. Little bully
victim. Obsessed on YouTube every day.
Get a [ __ ] grip. Bye-bye. Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
Now, is this supposed to be bullying me?
Is this supposed to be affecting
me? It's literally not bothering me one single
bit. Nope. It's not bothering me one single bit.
Are these people supposed to be like
ruining my life or
something? Because I'm all I'm seeing is
obsession. I think they're supposed to
be I think the whole point of it is
they're supposed to be psychologically
[ __ ] with my head. Well, they're
doing a very bad job of it. Cuz it's
like what I say to Joe, these people
don't bother me one little bit. They've
not had my kids took off me. They've not
stopped my money. They ain't done
nothing. They ain't done [ __ ] all. But
apparently they [ __ ] with people's
heads. Yeah, I'm trying to find out how
they actually do that. They just come on
YouTube and just repeat themselves every day.
Bro, that was a KFC there. Don't watch
that. Like they they literally do not
bother no one by coming on YouTube every
day being obsessed, you
know? Obsessed little virgins. I don't
know how how they can sit online and be
obsessed every single
day. The [ __ ] madness, bro.
Stop repeating yourself. If you're going
to come on this channel and try to bully
someone, at least come up with new content. You're
boring. You are boring. You little
ratfaced bastard. Go and suck your
disabled dad's dick. You ratfaced little
virgin little bastard. And get my sloppy
seconds out of your virgin head. You
ugly little rat. [ __ ] hell. You ugly,
no teeth, lanky little virgin ratfaced
[ __ ] with a fat ugly girlfriend. [ __ ]
off, you little
weirdo. Go and suck your disabled dad's
dick. Tell the police that I said that
as well. God, you're so
annoying. God, you're [ __ ] annoying
as [ __ ] When somebody doesn't want
anything to do with you, like Britney,
you leave them alone. Don't keep
harassing them. That's how you get in
[ __ ] problems. Now [ __ ] up and suck
your disabled dad's dick. That's your
only chance of you losing your
virginity, your little
virgin. God, I to be fair, I can't I
can't actually hate that bad, bro. I actually feel
famous to be honest with you. I actually
do feel like famous. I can't even I
can't even get mad at these people, you
know? They're little
autistic bastards repeating every day,
you know? I just don't understand how
they can come on YouTube obsessed every
day. They don't bother no one. They
don't psychologically [ __ ] with anyone.
I don't know how many times I have to
say it. Like they really really don't
affect no one. They just affect
themselves by being obsessed every
day. They literally don't bother me one
little bit. Like and and and I'm saying
this like sincerely with my heart. They
ain't got my kids took off me. They
ain't stopped my income. They ain't
[ __ ] done nothing to me. Like
honestly, they haven't. Honest to God,
haven't. They're just obsessed every day on YouTube. Literally,
bro. [ __ ] obsessed little virgin. What's
this? Some madness, bro.
sad sad autism. Ant-Man actually told me
that he uh he had
a uh he made another channel which I
weren't even aware about and he said
that none of these people found
him. I might have to really go on that channel, bro.
I don't really want to, but I mean, if
it means these people never following me
anymore, then it's a good thing. I' i've
actually got a new channel. I just need
to put all the videos on that channel,
cuz I don't think these people are ever
literally going to stop with their
autism. They're literally never ever
ever going to stop, bro. Send it today.
No thanks. No, I'm chilling today. I
think I'm going to have to go on that
main channel, bro. I'm not going to do
the other channel. I'm not even joking.
where none of these little losers can
find me. None of these little gay
lords. I think I might just have to do
it, bro. I might just have to do it. At
least none of them will find
you. I've got the channel. I've got the
I've got the channel on my device, but I
just don't have any videos on
it because this is every single time you
go live with these autistic people
coming on your channel, making posts
about you. Like, you might as well just
make go on a new channel. literally
might as well just go on a new
channel. I think that's the best
solution, bro. I think that's the most
mature thing as well. Why don't you go
out and send it? Why don't you go out
it? Yeah. Why don't you go out and send
it? Yeah. Why don't you go and do it? I
don't need to prove anything to you. You
will never know where I live. You little
ratfaced ugly bastard. You never will
ever know where I live. And it kills
you. I don't need to prove nothing to
you, mate. You don't know where I live.
And that person on Reddit wasn't even
me. So, cuz I don't post on Reddit. I
just private message people. So, keep
thinking that you know where I am. And
keep thinking that you know what's me.
You're wrong, buddy. You're absolutely [ __ ]
wrong. I'm not talking to you. I'm
talking to this little virgin. I don't
need to prove [ __ ] nothing to you,
mate. You will never know where I live.
you little virgin. And if you're
so convinced that you know where I live,
why don't you come on a Why don't you
come on the door? If you really really
think you know where someone lives, why
don't you come on the
door, bro? You're obsessed. You will
never know where I live. And that person
on Reddit was nothing to do with me.
Yeah. Was nothing to do with me. So,
keep thinking that you know things, but
you really really don't. That's what
happens when you've got a Peter belly
obsession. You think everyone is me cuz
you're obsessed. But keep thinking you
know things but you don't know anything. That's the So yeah,
man. Blocked again. How many accounts
are you going to keep making, you little
virgin? How how bad is this launcher's
legs as autism?
How bad is this autism with this [ __ ]
virgin? How bad is it, bro? How bad is
this person's obsession with me? It's
actually making me sick. You don't ruin
anyone's life either. You don't bully no
one. I don't know how many times someone
has to tell you that you what you're
doing does not affect them, but you keep
doing it. You've got severe autism.
That's why you was diagnosed with
autism. I can see the autism now. You
know, when I was younger, right, when I
was [ __ ] younger, yeah, you you don't
really understand these things, but now
I I definitely definitely definitely do understand
it. I really really do understand it.
It's bad bad autism. It's worse than
Timmy's. You know, a lot of these, well,
not a lot of them. All of these people
that are obsessed with me is severely
autistic. It's severely severely
severely autistic. I've noticed that as
well. It's autism. It's got to be autism
and jealousy. It's got to be. How many
accounts have I made? Well, um, quite a
few. But it's not to stalk one person
and get blocked again. Is to actually
speak to people and talk to them off
here. So big difference.
just [ __ ] Sean being obsessed again.
Just a Sea being an obsessed little
virgin. Why are these people so jealous
of me? Like what what do I really really
have that these people that these people
don't have? I don't understand. Like
they're so obsessed with me. It's
[ __ ] mad. Why are they so jealous of
me? I don't understand. Like every
single time I go live, I get these
little gaylords, bro. It's so mad. Why
are they so jealous of me? Why can't
they just leave me alone? Like even what
even like what Ant-Man said as well. He
said he made a new channel. I didn't
even realize he made a new channel, bro.
I didn't even know he made a new
channel. Um but he did like ages ago.
And he said none of these people found
him. I'm not even aware of the channel.
Why won't these people just leave me
alone and stop being jealous of me every
day? I don't understand. Why are they so
[ __ ] jealous of me? Is it because
they know that I'm better looking? I've
got more money than them. Like, what
what is the jealousy about every day
being obsessed on YouTube
psychologically [ __ ] with these
people's heads? Because that's what
you're doing. You're tormenting them.
Them writing paragraphs of you, which
takes a long time to write a paragraph.
You've got something they don't have.
I'm telling you, bro, at this point now,
what you've got to see, it's got to be
that they're jealous that you're better
looking at them. It's got to be
something for these people to write
paragraphs every day reacting to you,
right? Wasting their life on you. You
got something they don't have. I'm
telling you, bro. I'm telling you. I'm
Every single time, bro, I'm I'm out
walking. It was like, mate, you got
something they don't have. I'm telling
you. I'm telling you. I'm telling you.
It's got to be some form of jealousy.
And I and I hate saying it, bro. I
really really really really really hate
saying it, but that's what it's looking like to
me. You got something they don't have.
And I don't know what it is because this
has been every single day, right?
Despite whatever you do, whatever you
say, like I'm thinking of putting
posters up of this [ __ ] again. I can go,
mate. Listen, I'm thinking of putting up
posters of this [ __ ] again. I was
actually thinking of this earlier when I
was at KFC. No, they can't go to the
piece of me. No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. They can't go to the
police about me. I've got these people's
harassment for years and years and
years. Like, if I go out here and I pull
up posters, I want the police to come to
show them what these people keep doing
every day. Won't leave me alone. These
little [ __ ] autistic little virgins.
But I can I can show them it. And that's
what I'm going to be like, what? You're
going to nick someone and take them to
court when this little ratfaced ugly rat
virgin will not leave people alone.
Which is what I told him the first time
they come here. Why do you think they
didn't do anything the last time? Cuz I
said, "This little ugly virgin won't
[ __ ] leave me alone." And he said,
"Was it was it to uh was it to stop the
person?" And I said, "Yeah, because when
I done it, it stopped them for two three
weeks. is stopped them for two, three
weeks, you know, more than what these
people could do because they don't even
do their job properly. That, you know,
tell this ratfaced ugly [ __ ] and I'll
say it to the police's face and his fat
ugly girlfriend to leave me alone. And
that's and that's literally what I would
do as well. I will do it, bro. Yeah. And
I and and that's not even the first
thing I would do, bro. That's not even
the first thing I would
do. Yeah. Cuz it's not actually like I'm
at my mom's anymore. If they knock on
the door, I would say, "Move yourself
from my property." Now, if it is, if
this is from off of YouTube, I would
tell them to remind you're not coming
in. Simple, bro. Yeah.
Simple. I can't le him because he won't
meet anyone, dummy. Dummy, dumb [ __ ]
this rat face on benefits on a grand a
month will not meet anyone. This little
£1,000 a month nodd pittance will not
meet anybody. Like, we've already
established that, lad. This little
virgin who sucks his disabled dad's
dick, this ugly little virgin will not
meet anyone. So, it seems that it has to
be the posters
again. I have to do the posters on the
little rat again. Go to the pubs he
drinks in. Stop playing these silly
little games. You know that he's not
going to meet anyone. You know that he's
not going to show people where he is
when he is, you know. And stop saying,
"What do you mean you know where he
drinks when I went out, bro? I've gone
to his area several times. We're not
playing these silly little games again.
Wrong channel, bro. Bro, wrong channel.
We're not playing these silly little
games again. Oh, go to where he works.
Um, where he drinks, go to his area.
We're not playing these silly little
games again with this little ratfaced
ugly little virgin. We're not playing
these silly games again, bro. We're not
playing these silly games with this
little rat face. You understand, [ __ ]
Yeah. But he's not sneaky though, Joe.
Cuz you remember last time when I put of
him? Oh, I'm not a fire. I'm running to
the police. I'm running to the place. It
got me arrested. And guess what? It It
shut you up for three, mate. Listen. And
guess what it done? You m It shut you up
for 3 weeks, you little ma. You little
rat face. You little rat face [ __ ] You
little ugly rat with a fat ugly
girlfriend. It also shut you up for 3
weeks, didn't it? Did it not shut you up
for 3 weeks? You little rat face. You
rat face bastard with the fat ugly
girlfriend. Isn't it so mad that I can
talk about you? Your nonsad. your fat
downy looking girlfriend, the ugly
[ __ ] and you won't meet me and say
nothing to my face. And that's the
maddest. Yeah, I think that's what it's
going to have to be, is it? You [ __ ]
ratfaced ugly nons [ __ ] bastard. I can
say what I want to you,
bro. Yeah. And you remember Yeah. And
and the thing is, if they if they go,
what I'm saying is if he goes to the
police and the police come, just show
them all of your evidence of this [ __ ]
not leaving you alone. This autistic
little [ __ ] not leaving you alone. This
autistic little gaylord matfaced virgin
erectile dysfunctional [ __ ] and I'll say
it in front of the police too. Will not
leave you alone. That's it, bro. If they
come in your yard, just say that he
keeps harassing you. He will not leave
you alone. He will not leave you alone
under any circumstances. He's got major
autism. And that's all you got to do,
bro. We've got all the evidence. all the
evidence on his channel and I've got
unlisted videos as well cuz what so what
are they going to do? Put hook you in
prison. Of course they're not,
man. So I think posters will will have
to be the only thing
unfortunately. You know, you know what
I'm saying? Teach the [ __ ] rat face
[ __ ] a letter. Get him to [ __ ] himself
again. Bro, it doesn't matter, mate.
I've got all of these harassment. I've
got all of these harassment. Why do you
think the police Why do you think the
police didn't do anything that time?
Because they know about the ratfaced the
ratfaced ugly [ __ ] You You see what I'm
saying, bro? Yeah. And that's
it. Yeah. And and and the police knew
that. So the police was like, "Well, why
did you put up posters?" I was like,
"Was it to stop it?" And I said, "Yeah."
And they like, "How long did it stop
for?" And they was like, I was like,
"Two weeks." So I was like, "Two weeks.
This little ratfaced little virgin and
his autism don't know how to leave
people alone. It's like when Britney
rejected his ugly ass. A B CDE E FG,
bro. A too [ __ ]
said. A too [ __ ] said. All because
some girl in Canada rejected him. That
weren't me on them accounts. That's
because some girl didn't want him.
Didn't want nothing to do with him. You
think I've got time to make an account
from A to Zed? Verify myself. those
accounts was actually him. You know what
I'm saying? Oh, he is a virgin, mate. He
definitely definitely definitely is a
virgin. And everything he does, proves
he's a virgin. He is a million% virgin.
Guess what? I've never had a girlfriend,
but people have seen me have sex. People
have seen me be in bed with people. He
is 100% a virgin. He could be married,
right? Listen, just It doesn't matter if
he's laughing, bro. I've made him [ __ ]
himself for 3 weeks. Yeah. He's never
made me [ __ ] myself. Just laughing. He's
not laughing. I'm laughing at him on a
grand a month. Pittance ugly fat ugly
girlfriend. I'm living in his head every
day. That's me owning, bro. Me and my
sloppy seconds, right? Living his head
free every day. All because he's a
little virgin. It doesn't matter, bro.
If he he's got a girlfriend, he is a
virgin. He's going to my house. He
doesn't know where I live. Again, I'm
not playing these silly little games.
You're not going to I'm not playing
these silly little games again. I've
told you over and over and over. I can
never get a bird like Sarah. I wouldn't
want a bird like Sarah, mate. I've had
actually normal women that are not
vulnerable. You're right. I could never
get a bird like Sarah because I don't
target disabled women. Vulnerable
disabled women. You're right. I couldn't
get a bird like that because I don't
target disabled, vulnerable, ugly
girlfriends. So yeah, I couldn't You're
right about that.
LJ does turn up. He's proved that. Uh
what? Hold on. Let me read that again. I
can't be reading that. Right. To be to
be fair, LJ does turn up. He's proved
that. LJ does turn up. What? He was
supposed to come to mine last year.
Right. Bro, he doesn't know where I am.
And even if he did know where I am, I'm
going to put a hammer fully through his
skull. Simple. I will put a hammer
through his [ __ ] whole skull. Simple,
bro. Don't play these silly little games
with me cuz I'll put a hammer straight
through your skull. It's not even a
joke. Yeah. You're not coming to no
one's address cuz I will smack a hammer
through your [ __ ] head and that will
teach you to ever act like a big man on
YouTube again. Yeah. Simple. And that's
it. Here's the thing, bro. Yeah. Here's
another thing. He didn't turn up last
year, bro. And he didn't turn up this
year. He's not going on no one's door
cuz I will lick him with a hammer. Trust
me. And you will see it. [ __ ]
foureyed fat ugly [ __ ] ain't coming on
no one's [ __ ] door. You [ __ ] shack
yourself last time. You little bad back
running into central London turning your
kettle off. [ __ ] running away from me
and London Taylor. You silly little
[ __ ] How? Well, if he ever finds out
where I am. If he ever finds out where I
know you're not I'm not playing these
silly little games with you anyways. I
am not playing. No, Sean. This
19year-old did not have a carer. Yeah,
we don't go for disabled ugly girls like
you. Disabled Sarah. Disabled
Sarah. Yeah. Anyways, and to prove to
you that uh this Sha is a virgin. It
doesn't matter if he's got a girlfriend,
he is indeed a virgin. Because isn't it
funny how he can't get my sloppy seconds
out of his head and he can't get these
women I've been with out of his head. It
proves that he's a virgin. He is 100% a
virgin. Being in a relationship does not
mean anything. Yeah, that doesn't mean
anything cuz he's in one and he's still
a virgin. I've not been in a
relationship and I've had more women
than that virgin will ever have. So,
what's a relationship even [ __ ] mean,
bro? I know people that are married.
This guy said he ain't had sex in three
months and he's a married [ __ ] mad
man. You know what I'm saying,
bro? He is a married man. That little
[ __ ] virgin has never stuck that
autistic dick up, nothing. Why do you
think he's always [ __ ] chasing my sloppy
seconds and that's it, bro? And I'm not
playing these silly little games with
you. I'm not playing these silly little
games with you. Oh, I'm coming in your
door. No, no, no. I'm not playing these
autistic games with you again. End the
[ __ ] story, bro. But yeah, all jokes
aside, I think posters is the only way.
And because you've got so much of what
this little virgin has been doing, what
can the police really do? It's their
fault to begin with.
didn't you hide behind your mom last
time, bro? With these people, um, it
ends when if they either go to prison or
they die. Obviously, either when they're
in prison or they
die. Yeah. either
like I'm so glad you called him a
nonsex. I love that. I love that, mate.
If you listen listen, okay, okay, let me
answer this, right? Let me ask answer
this. If you really really was getting
sex, right? If you really really was
getting sex and you had a girlfriend who
was giving you sex, you wouldn't be
stalking my sloppy seconds every day.
You wouldn't be obsessed with the women
that I've met or even women that I
haven't met. It goes to show, yeah, he
will be on my door in less than 10
minutes. We've heard all of this before.
Yeah, we've heard all of this before.
Take it away from my channel. Simple.
And this is why I don't go live anymore.
This is one of the reasons I don't even
bother coming on because it's the same
autistic atmosphere every time you do.
You know, like this is what uh this is
what I was saying about the new channel,
Grezy, because it's just the same
idiots. It's like what Ant-Man was
saying. Yep. As usual on natural, you
know the truth. I literally cannot come
on live stream without being without
um without being harassed by these little
mongos and by the same people. I
literally can't even go live without
being harassed by these
mongos. Nope. He doesn't have a
job, you know. And this is why I don't bother no
more, you know. This is why I don't
bother no more because it's just the
same repeating atmosphere. This is
exactly what I mean, bro. Same little
mongos. Obsessed every day. Oh my god.
You know what I'm saying? It's [ __ ]
weird. That's it, lad. Over Morgan. Over
Izzy, over this person I've not even
met, but yet you want us to believe that he has
sex. How does he have so much cash? He
doesn't have cash. He's skint as [ __ ]
He doesn't have so much cash. He's a
skifflin. All he done was withdraw his
um housing benefit which he has to pay
and make it look like he's got money. He
doesn't have much cash. The guy is a skin
flint trying to act like he's got money
when he literally does not have a pot to
piss in. Look at what the [ __ ] skin
flint wears. He doesn't have cash. He's
skint. Everyone that lives by themsel,
they get um housing benefit, but they
don't pay it automatically anymore. They
pay it to you and you have to pay it.
You know what I'm saying? Like, and you
know what I'm [ __ ] saying? He does
not have cash. He is skint. Why do you
think all them months when I was an
idiot and I used to show these people
money, they never show me nothing? They
don't have money. None of these people
have money. I've got money right here.
I'm not showing you nothing. Believe it.
Don't believe it, mate. It's up to you.
You believe it or you don't believe it.
Like, that's up to you, bro. I'm not
here to convince you.
No, he does pay the rent. He puts some
money back in to pay the rent. He has
got no money, bro. Most of the people in
this community. He has No, no, no, no,
no, no, no. He doesn't have cash. That's
his housing benefit. Anyways, end the
conversation. And this is why I do not
go live anymore. So Joe, when you see me
and I don't go live anymore, this is the exact
reason. This is the exact reason. You
can see it for yourself now. They ruin
it. They ruin
everything. like a live stream. These
little autistic little virgins, they
[ __ ] ruin everything, lad. You will
be at mine in five minutes. Yeah, good
for you, man. See you in five minutes.
You don't know where I live, but yeah,
good for you, man. Yeah, good for you.
You don't worry me one little bit. You
don't scare me one little bit. So,
you're not going to be at no one's in 5
minutes. Stop the autistic keyboard
warrior games that we've been hearing
for years upon years upon years. It's
boring now. It's [ __ ] so boring now.
And this is why I don't go live anymore.
This is exactly
why. No, no, no, no. Not him. Just all
of these people. Just all of these
people, you know. No, no, no, no, no.
It's not even that
virgin. People pretending they're coming
on your door. People pretending they're
coming to England to fight you. It's the
same autistic boring thing we've been
hearing for years and years and years,
man. It's the same old boring [ __ ] It's
boring, you know? It's like watching the
same old [ __ ] film over and over and
over and over and over again with these
[ __ ] mongos in this
community. I swear to God, bro. You
know, you know, it's so boring, man.
It's the same thing with L J. Every year
I'm coming to England. I'm coming to
England. I'm coming to England. And then
for some reason, he doesn't come to
England. know I'm coming at your door
and then he doesn't come at anyone's
door. It's boring, man. It's [ __ ]
boring. It's so boring, man. Like, how
about you just change up the community?
Like, you know what I'm saying? It's so
bro. It's so boring, though. It's so
[ __ ] boring. Like, I can see why
Ant-Man like made a new channel and and
and just got away from this. I didn't
even know he had a new channel. Like, I
can actually see why, bro.
It's so boring, bro. It actually
is. And sometimes I just don't like
hearing about these people as well.
And sometimes it's so bad I don't even
like hearing about these people, you
know? Like I'll just be chilling. Right.
So say you're just chilling. Yeah. And
you're like, I say you're talking about
some football bets you
done. And these people And these people
Well, you can Yeah. The thing is the
police are not going to do nothing. I
was going to do that. I was I was going
to report I was going to I was going to
go to the police and say like this
little rat won't leave me alone and if
you don't do anything then I'm going to
put up posters. Like at least I'm
telling you this is what I'm going to
do. Like this is literally what I'm
going to do if you do not do
anything. And I I'll be prepared to get
nicked. Like I don't care, bro. It is
what it is. But yeah, he's not ruining
my life. He's ruining my life. I'm
better looking than him. I get more
money than him. I have more money than
him. I've had more women than him. He
doesn't ruin my life. No, he's just
[ __ ] annoying. Ruin my life, mate.
I've got teeth in my head. I don't look
like a rat. I get more money than him.
Ruin my life? You [ __ ] mad, son? The
only reason I'm not out I'm not going
out today is cuz I can't be bothered.
[ __ ] little virgin. Don't ruin my
life. The lanky little rat. I ruined his
[ __ ] life for 3 weeks though when he
was scared to go out his house. [ __ ]
autistic little [ __ ] rat with his fat
ugly girlfriend. Don't ever try and tell
me that little virgin ruins my
life and never ever ruined my life. Have
I got my kids took off me? Have my money
been stopped? No. He's just a [ __ ]
annoying little autistic little virgin.
That's all he is. That needs to [ __ ] up
and suck his disabled dad's dick and
then at least that way he'd be able to
[ __ ] lose his virginity, you know? Yeah. Nice,
bro. Yeah. That's why this this
community, they just ruined everything.
Like, say you was even starting to make
money on YouTube, these people, they
just ruin everything, you
know? They ruin everything, bro.
But like even if you done posted of that
little virgin, I doubt the police would
even come for
you. I don't even think the police would
even come for you,
bro. I don't even think they would
actually come for you. And if if they
did come for you, obviously you can show
them what these people have been doing.
So, I mean, it's a win-win situ because
in a way you hope they would come, you
know. God, man, how unlucky am I, man.
[ __ ] you know. Yeah, pretty much. Yeah,
these people have never owned me. I've
got more money than them. I get more
money than them. I'm better looking than
them. I've got more confidence than
them. They don't ruin my life. My life
is still better than theirs. They don't
ruin my life at all. They do not ruin my
life. Not one little
bit. Not one little bit. I don't know
how to put that into letters or words.
They don't. They They're just weird.
Everything that they do is just weird.
Like it's just weird,
bro. It doesn't bug me. It doesn't
bother me. It's just creepy. Like you're
allowed to find things creepy, you know,
and not get owned, bro. You know what I'm saying?
Like, but yeah, it's it is
weird. None of your business. I don't
put my life on YouTube. That's none of your business, mate. Unfortunately. Yep.
Gonzo. Yeah, you you've said that about
a million times, Red Star. Yeah, you've
kind of said that about a million times.
Big nose. It wasn't funny the first time
you said it. And you've also said Gonzo
a million times and that's not the first
time you said it and it's not funny. So,
is it Hold on. Is this supposed to be
bullying me or something? This This is
what I'm trying to say. Is this supposed
to be bullying me or affecting my life?
Like, is it actually supposed to be
bullying me or affecting my life? Like,
no, no, no. At some point, I would have
thought they would just give
up. But jealousy is a disease. Like my
mom said, jealousy is a disease. So, I
mean, they can't really give up, can
they? I mean, yeah. I would have thought
they would have just gave up, not learn,
but they'll never learn, bro. Autism and
jealousy is a horrible whole thing. It
ruins many, many lives.
many many many many like and you know
how you know it's jealousy as well
because Timmy does has never had this
Timmy has never had channels dedicated
to him. I've got about three four
channels dedicated to me. That's how you
know that it's jealousy no matter who it
is because bromy's been on it longer
than me. This guy reacts to everything
and he doesn't get it. That's how I know
these people want to be me. They're
jealous of me and they want to be me.
That's what it is. I know it. I know it. 100% know
it. Say what you want. You know what I
mean? So, but that's definitely
definitely what it is.
100%. And that's it. Right.
Yeah. I think he is as well to be fair,
bro. So, but that Jamie Thompson's his
own person. So, you still have a lot of
people on here that are obsessed with
you. [ __ ] weird,
man. Absolutely weird. Oh my god. [ __ ]
obsessed. I'm a bully victim. Yeah, I'm
a bully victim, aren't I? That's why you
can't show me where you are. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm I'm such a bully victim.
That's why you can't show me where you
are, you little virgin. And I had you
[ __ ] yourself for three weeks. She
wouldn't even leave your house for 3
weeks. You literally cannot show me
where you are, Red Star. That's how much
power I have over you. You don't bully
no one, mate. I bully you in your head
every single day cuz you can't shut up about me,
Virgin. Yeah, you don't bully no one,
mate. You got asked about a million
times to show where you are. You're a
little keyboard warrior. You're a
classic keyboard warrior with no
originality. You do not bully nobody.
you repeating little bastard. There
might have been a small chance
um but you just repeat yourself every
day. So yeah, it's why you don't really
see me on it much anymore. Same repeating people.
but yeah, bro. The same repeating
people. Same repeating
people. Oh, same repeating
people. Yeah, you would have thought at
some point they would have got bored,
but nah. See, with that Morgan thing,
eventually when I when I realized I made
her change her number,
um, I made her change her number. I made
her change her number and like I made
her man split up with her. I was like,
"Okay, enough is
enough." You know what I'm saying?
Like, and I was like, I just give up
now. These people never give up. That's
strong autism. That is That is strong
mate. That is strong autism. Oh my god, that is
autism. You have autism,
Greavvesy. Yeah, that's proper autism. That
is not me, mate. Not me. After seeing
what these people are like, I can
confirm that I'm not autistic. I had
doubts in my mind before, but then after
looking at that Jamie
Thompson and that virgin legs, non legs,
I can confirm that I don't have autism.
I I I I can actually say I don't
literally. No, mate. I definitely
[ __ ] don't have autism because if you
had autism, you would be obsessed with
somebody every day. you wouldn't be able to function
um in a normal environment with normal
people. I'll give you an example. All of
the women that I've been with have been
normal, right? They've never had any.
They might have been slightly mental,
but none of them's been vulnerable. None
of them's been disabled. All of the
people I hang out with are not disabled
and they're not vulnerable. So, if you
really had autism, you'd [ __ ] know
about it. Like, you wouldn't be able to
function. Well, you thought wrong
because there's nothing wrong with
me. There's nothing wrong with me at all. So,
yeah. Maybe a bit of downs. Nah, mate.
You people are the ones that are downs.
Yep. Skimp big nose. Yeah, you said that
about a million times already. It's boring.
Yeah, you said that about a million
times now. It's boring now, man. You
just say the same stuff every single
day, mate. You shouldn't be worrying
about my nose. You should be worrying
about your rat face. You ugly rat. You
ugly rodent. [ __ ] my [ __ ] nose, mate.
You need to fix your whole ugly face.
Maybe if you weren't so ugly, you might
have been able to pull the women that Peter Belly's
pulled. Nero. Yeah. Phil for And that's
where the jealousy comes from. Mero, do
you not understand where the jealousy
comes from? Well, slash with autism. You
just said it yourself. Sean's girlfriend
has the wolfism, down syndrome, autism.
Yes. Yes. Do you not see where the
jealousy comes from when I get with
these women that have none of these
things? It's not rocket science, dad.
Why do you think he's so obsessed with
Izzy and Morgan? He can't get them out
of his head. [ __ ] little virgin. And
then you have people on here trying to
tell you that, oh, he can't be a virgin
because he's in a relationship. But that
doesn't ring right because if he was
having sex like people in relationship
having sex, why are you obsessed with my sloppy
seconds? Exactly. He's never had sex.
He's a virgin. He's a typical virgin.
Like being in a relationship actually
means anything because I've never been
in one and I've had proof that I've had
sex. You know, skin, big nose. Yeah,
you've already said that, mate. Can you
come up with some new things or just the
same repeating? Mate, you're skint and
you got a rat face. I have more money
than you would ever have. The joys are
not knowing, mate. You're a [ __ ] ugly
rat. How are you talking about someone's
nose when you look like a rat? Ugly rat
face. You want to call me big rose big
nose? You're an ugly rat, you ugly little
[ __ ] Oh, loads of accounts, bro. He
doesn't stop. He doesn't stop. This is
every single time I go live. Yeah, they
don't they don't stop, bro. Yeah, they
don't stop. It's like Joe Rogan said,
"Uh, never um never read the comments."
And apparently this is supposed to be
bullying me, by the way. This is
supposed to be affecting me. Like, but it
doesn't. Obviously, it doesn't
Yeah, it goes on all day, bro. It goes
on all day. They'll never
stop. Somebody said to me before, "Yeah,
you should leave YouTube, but I think
make another account." They was like,
"They'll never leave you
alone." Which is true,
man. Obviously, because they don't leave you
alone. Look, this is they will do this
literally all day. All day. Jealousy is a horrible
disease. The few things that happened to
you in real life on here were caused by
you and not these lot and not these lot.
Yeah. Exactly. Yeah. Yeah. These people
have never affected my life. They've
tried getting my money stopped. Never
wor. They've tried ruining my life with
police. never worked. They tried getting
neighbors to bat me. Never worked.
Already had issues with a neighbor.
Nothing to do with YouTube. They've done
nothing, mate. They've not had my kids
took off me. They ain't stopped none of
my money. Like, they wish they could
ruin me in their little wet dream, you
know? They really, really will never
ruin anyone's life. I swear to God they
won't, bro. I promise you they won't.
So, I don't know why they they do it.
They bore people, but that's about all they do.
Not like they made you go on a
Yeah. Yep. Exactly. Yeah. It's cuz I
don't like that neighbor. He's a [ __ ]
But that's nothing to do with YouTube.
That's nothing to do with YouTube, mate.
Because let me tell you something. If I
live by myself and people put up posters
in my area, I'm not going nowhere. I'm
not going nowhere. There is already
history there. like these. What I said,
Nero, is that with cowards, there's only
so much you can do behind the
keyboard. There's only so much that you
can do behind the keyboard um as a
coward because obviously you're a
coward. So, you only hide behind your
keyboard and there's only about five
things you can do and everything you've
already tried and you failed. And that's
not me to like go them or try to piss
them off. It's telling them how the reality actually works.
Like, think about it. I ain't got my
kids took off
me. You're never going to know where I
live, mate. You're never known where I
live. And you know the reason why I will
never tell these people where I live is
because they want to try to control your
life. They're not going to come on your
door. They're not going to come to your
flat or wherever you are. They're just
going to try and control your
life. And that's all they are. Like they
don't need to know. Why? Why would you
tell these people where you live? You
know, they knew where you lived for
years and they never done nothing. They
literally done nothing. You don't tell
these people where you live. If they
find out where you live, then okay, you
know, then they know where you live in
it. That's it. But you wouldn't tell
these people where you live because all
they're going to do is try to cause
issues and not do anything themselves
and control your life. You know, that's
what they'll do. They'll never come at
your door. None of these people ever
will. You don't need to know the area I
live in. It's none of your
business. You don't need to know
that. I live wherever you want me to
live. Nah, man. Never. You don't need to
know the area I
live, you know. And that's it. You don't
need to know that, you know.
So, like, bro, come on. Give it up.
We've been doing this now for years.
We've been doing this back and forth
[ __ ] You know what I mean? For years
now, bro. It's
boring. It's properly properly
boring. I fancy going out today
approaching, but I'm not going to.
something Sean's anxiety would never
allow him to
do. I'm trying to think ways around
this. I mean, I can put posters up of
the [ __ ] and ruin him, make him shut his
rat face up for a few weeks, you
know? Yeah. You're never going to know
where I am. That's the That's the best
way, you know. That's the [ __ ] best way.
Who is this? Someone send me a voice
now. One sec.
Uh, what's popping? Nons being up. Nons legs being
obsessed as usual. Yeah, non legs being
obsessed with me as usual. Just the same
old. Keeps making a 100 different
accounts. Just the usual whenever Peter
Belly goes live.
Yeah, just the same
old. Why the [ __ ] is Rice calling me,
bro? [ __ ] off,
man. [ __ ] off, bro. Why the [ __ ] is this
guy calling me? [Music]
Yeah, I'm coming off live now anyways,
but I can't be [ __ ] Same old
[ __ ] Same old same old same old [ __ ]
Why do you even bother going live, man?
Well, was only live for an hour as well. [ __ ] me.