[ __ ]
hell. [ __ ] you know that, mate. Yep. Oh, that's
lovely. It's all been moved. Oh, been
moved. It's all been
moved. I love this electron. Oh
[ __ ] I woke up. Yeah, I was tired. Had
some nice food. Now I'm [ __ ] tired
again. Catches up when you done it,
mate. Back in the old nesticles. Cactus
got free numbers yesterday. Didn't
reply. I seem to do better on these
Thursdays. Only hope now is this
Australian that that lives here, the
teacher. But it's not guaranteed,
bro. Oh, I'm not going out next
week. No way. I need a break, bro. I'm
[ __ ] I need a break from it all,
man. I wrote that poem yesterday. I I
ain't seen you since, buddy. But
uh yeah, I wrote that
uh I wrote that
poem and uh I didn't get a reply back.
These [ __ ] are
heartless. [ __ ] are heartless, lad. They're
[ __ ] They're actually
[ __ ] Blankie is warming up now.
Cactus sign up Peter Belly's
mama. I'll be going somewhere the week
after. So that's it,
bro. It's not about money. It's not
about the money side of it. It's just
boring, isn't it? Every week. So you
need a break and forget all about it
again before you try again. I
think they're just not interested in this country
cactus. Oh, mate.
Yeah. No, that Jesse is just a [ __ ]
troll, mate. I knew it straight away. I
knew it straight away. She was a troll. Yeah.
What was that? I was
l same old same
old. Nothing's changed in 4 years.
Nothing's going to change in another 10
years. I mean, it's pretty self-explanatory,
really. Every week is pretty much
self-explanatory. Every every week every week's
um I say this to
man every every week is the
same every week is the same scenario you
know same scenario every
week. You cried out me,
mate. Only I can help myself. And let's
leave this country, which is what I'm
doing, which I won't do in three weeks.
So, I won't be out next week, bro. Bothered. Yeah. Oh [ __ ]
I need a [ __ ] rest, mate. That's what
I need. A good [ __ ]
rest. A good two weeks
rest. Uh, good week. West matey. O.
Yeah. One sec.
Listen guys, TV
doesn't TV doesn't come on YouTube
anymore. Doesn't uh Yeah. [Music]
They all got my
friends. Therefore, don't end up like virgin
dads. Oh, the only virgin is you, Timmy.
We've been over this many, many times.
Mate, the only virgin is you and
bomb and virgin
legs. They're the only guaranteed
virgins. I think Lord Jay is a virgin as
well. I don't even think he's got kids.
I I might I might be the first one to to
say this, but I don't even think he has
kids cuz there's there's no
way someone can have kids and be on
YouTube all day every day. I don't even
believe he's got
kids. I'm actually I might sound
delusional now, but I don't even believe
it. Cuz how can someone have kids,
right, and be on YouTube all day, every day? Nah, [Music]
man. I even think he's got kids, dad.
That's how bad it is,
bro. You think he's got kids? I don't
think he's got kids.
I don't think you got
kids. I've never been laid projecting
again. Talking about
yourself. What have I told you about
talking about yourself, man? I said this
to [ __ ] LJ earlier.
You people need to stop talking about
yourselves. Your mental health is never
going to improve if you just keep talking about
yourselves. Sat on YouTube all day.
Skin, bro. How's [ __ ]
man. Oh, bro. I told you about talking
about yourself. It's not good for your mental
health. L don't have kids. I'm at this
point now where bro, is there any proof
that he's actually got
kids? What? You hear you hear kids in the
background? Yeah, you've heard kids in
my background. I don't even believe he's got kids,
Daz. I just I just don't believe
it. Cuz of uh I don't I don't even think he's got
kids. I'll be I'm not even joking, bro.
I don't even think he's got
kids, guys. I swear to God, bro.
Oh. Oh, [ __ ] bro.
I'm [ __ ] lucky, mate.
I'm exhausted, man.
What's a day
today? [ __ ] night. Get
out. This is [ __ ] bloody, bro. That's funny,
bro. Come that Oh, [ __ ]
me. Nothing, bro. Just chilling. Just in
the nesticles. I fell asleep. Had some good
food. Now I'm just chilling.
Literally straight chilling,
bro. Yeah, just drinking some coke. I
was playing a bit of salads, but yeah,
the food made me tired,
so I'll be having a long break.
Want to pet
kangaroo. Even I would pet kangaroo
that. Yeah, pet kangaroo, man.
Uh weird box.
Yeah. Oh, I'm just [ __ ] chilling,
bro. Yeah, I won't be out next week.
Looking back on that foot thing like to
think I couldn't walk properly for
[ __ ] like six
weeks. This man it was [ __ ] stinking.
I was just saying Steven is I don't
think this L guy actually have has
kids. I don't think he actually he
actually has kids because people that
have kids would not be on YouTube all
day. Yeah, you might have heard kids in
the background. Yeah, but you've heard
kids in my background when I used to
live with my mom. He don't have kids,
bro. He's probably a virgin just like
[ __ ] Timmy if you think about
it. He probably is. He probably is a
virgin. A lot of the people on here
don't actually have lives, you know. He
ain't got no He ain't got kids, bro. No
way. Cuz you He's got more time in his
hands than I
do. More time in his hands than I do. He
ain't got kids, bro. How can you have
more time on your hands than I do? And I don't have
kids. He ain't got no one, bro. He's got
no kids. He's got no friends. He's got
no misses. He has no sex life. He has
nothing, bro. Trust me.
We were just talking about
Timmy. We've never seen him with a woman once on
here. Not once. Not [ __ ] once,
lad. Getting up there in age. You're
already up there in age,
matey. You're probably in your 40s,
matey. Mate, you're already up there in
age. You're well past your cell by date. self
projecting. Who would mate with that? Yeah, exactly. Bro,
exactly. You're 30. Well, you're older
than me then, aren't
you? Well, you're older than
me. They wouldn't mate with that thing,
bro. That's why he doesn't actually have
kids. He doesn't have kids.
Why? Why has he got all Why has he got
all them ugly tattoos as well? I don't
know why people get tattoos. They're [ __ ]
ugly. I always hated them. I
did. No, I won't be 30 in two years. Try
again. It won't be two years. Try again, buddy.
Yeah. Again, stop self projecting.
You're in your 40s,
mate. Yeah. Take a take a closer look to
home. 2 years is a long time. And no,
it's not two years cuz you don't even
have my age and you're already claiming
30. Uh, stop self projecting. You're
already in your
40s. Not even people in their 30s on this
community. Stop projecting. It's funny,
is it, Stephen? How would you get these
people that are in their 40s, 50s trying
to tell you you're close to 30 when
you're nowhere near 30 and they're in
their 40s and 50s? It's just another form of
projection. Just another form of
projection. Literally just another form of
it. Yep. They're all self projectors,
bro. [ __ ] hell. These people. These
people are self projectors, lad. Self
projectors. Cell projectors, it screenshotting
that. [ __ ] off, you virgin.
Go [ __ ] your disabled ugly girlfriend. You [ __ ]
virgin. I'm screenshotting that as well. [ __ ]
virgin. [ __ ] virgin. One second. Go
[ __ ] your ugly disabled
girlfriend. You might actually lose your
virginity. Yeah, man. One second,
bro. One second. Let me go on the police
side. Let me report this [ __ ]
again. I'm reporting this [ __ ] again to
the police. One second. This little virgin. One
second. One second. When I'm off this
live stream, I'm going to report this virgin
again. Why is it gone all in white again, man?
I'll be on their case
again before I go to sleep. It takes about 20 minutes. Yeah. But
anyways, I'm going to keep reporting it.
It's been about a week, two weeks as
well. I'm going to follow up on it and
send just [ __ ] is still harassing me and
I'm just going to keep screenshotting
everything that they do now. I've
already got like an op an ongoing
[ __ ] case and [ __ ] So, I'm just
going to keep reporting it and escalating
it. Yeah, I'm going to do it, bro. I've
been doing it anyway. It's bare, so I'm
doing it before I go to sleep. This
[ __ ] little lanky little [ __ ]
virgin rat [ __ ] is going to stop [ __ ]
harassing me with his fat ugly
girlfriend. I tell you that for [ __ ]
nothing. [ __ ] ugly [Applause]
[ __ ] I don't think that people are
going to come on my live stream when I'm
[ __ ] drunk thinking that I'm stupid.
I've noticed that they they come on here
when I'm drunk thinking I'm going to say
a load of mad
stuff. There you go.
doing it again. Thank you. Keep it
coming, man. Keep it coming. Keep it
coming for me. It just helps my case even
more. Go sort your ugly rat face out,
you rodent looking
[ __ ] Go sort that rat face out, you ugly
[ __ ] You rataced [ __ ] vermin
Anyways, that's another one for me.
Thank you. That's [ __ ] two right
there. That's literally two
right. There you go. I'm reporting all
of this before I go to sleep, so it's
fine. Not a problem,
bro. And stop trying to add me on
Snapchat as well, you
virgin. Stop trying to add me on [ __ ]
Snapchat as well.
I'm not [ __ ] accepting it, you
[ __ ] virgin. No, [ __ ] off. Stop
[ __ ] adding me on Snapchat,
weirdo. Everyone's a virgin. Not
everyone. Maybe three or four people
confirmed. Yeah, Timmy Bomb, Virgin Boy. Um, Lar 50/50.
Um, yeah, they're
confirmed. Oh, them ones are definitely definitely confirmed,
bro. Anyways, back to tattoos. Why do
Why do people get tattoos? They're so
ugly. Why do people get tattoos? They're so [ __ ]
ugly. Why do they get tattoos?
The sock has women. Pat's married. So,
uh, you're all married on here, aren't
you? You're all married on here.
Uh-huh. PJ, you never had a woman. Oh,
bro, you're talking about yourself
again. I told you about projector,
man. Yeah, I've never had a woman. Yeah.
What have I told you about talking about
yourself? What have I told you about
talking about yourself? Do you know
what's weird about these people, Steven?
They're so autistic that they get
themselves confused with uh they get
themselves confused with you. It's part
of their disability. Like, you know how
they say your skin, you're this, you're
that, you're this, you're that, you're
this, you're that. They get themselves
confused with you. It's part of their
disability. Could I've just
screenshotted a few things. I'm just
going to report it again.
going to be on their case again. Don't
forget there was a bank holiday there, weren't there?
So, there we go. Thank you. Keep it
coming. Keep it coming. Keep it coming,
please. Thank you. It just helps my
case. You're doing lot of work. Thank
you. Thank you so much. Keep it coming.
Keep it coming. Keep it coming. Please
keep making accounts. Thank
you. Have I got a disability? Not like
you people, mate. Not like you people, you
know. Not like you
people. You've got a projecting disability. you
know. Anyways, bye-bye now. Right, let
me report this thing quickly. One
second. I'll do this all over
again. We take down a
few. One second. One second, bro.
Yep. Anyways, G uh Stephen Howard, what
do you think happened with
that Australian? It's [ __ ] up, is it,
bro? I don't know what I'm doing
tomorrow. I'm just
uh I'm just on the police site now. One second.
They don't make these things easy.
E. Oh, here we
go. It's asking, "What are we reporting? Sexual
assault, stalking, or harassment." I
think that's definitely the one. I'll
follow this up about four
times. Yeah, I've got the site ready to
do it anyways. When I've ended this live stream, but um yeah,
man. I got no plans tomorrow,
bro. I've got no
plans. I won't be out next week, bro. I
need a break from it all.
It's not about the money side of it.
It's about you need a break long enough
to forget that it's just the same [ __ ] every
week. Same [ __ ] every week. And it the
only one I'm still talking to is the teacher.
But obviously that can end anywhere, you
know. They're like,
lad. Yep. Bye-bye.
I said I was going to go to the gym. I
was going to start the gym again.
Yeah. I'm going to start the gym
again. I said I was going to start the gym, didn't
I? Which is
good. Good thing to get into it.
Um, I said I was going to go to a gym,
didn't I? So, I definitely can't go out
this week. You can't go gym and then go
out the same week. You need like two weeks in
between. Like a good You can go out
every two weeks if you go to your gym,
but not every
week. So, yeah, maybe we go to the gym,
maybe. And I might do a video about
these people whilst I'm at the gym. This
is how it starts. These people don't go
to the gym. They become fat. They got no
life. So they just come on YouTube projecting every
day. Yeah, I'm going
bro. Let's go to the [ __ ] gym in
it. I'm not far from one.
So yeah. help tomorrow. If I go to gym
tomorrow, I'm going to eat like
some maybe some uh um
maybe maybe some salmon. I might get a bit of
salmon. Bit of salmon and veg. A salmon and donkeys,
mate. A bit of salmon and some chicken, maybe. Yeah.
Uh oh, mate. I used to love salmon.
And then you can just get like some
chicken breast, some steak, all of that
[ __ ] See, these people are so lazy. All
these people have to do is clean up
their diet and go gym. They don't even
need to change their diet. They just
need to clean it up a little bit.
But they'd rather just sit on YouTube
every day just projecting their [ __ ]
lives onto other
people. You know, it's not like you're
it's not like these skinny people. If
you're skinny, you need to spend
thousands before you can get muscly.
Like, you need to literally spend
thousands. But if you know, you can gain
weight like me, you know, a little bit.
You can build muscle in no
time. You know, you can build muscle in no time.
know, there's not really no excuse
really. By the time I've joined the gym,
month membership, a bit of food, what
what you talking 3040 pound, you know?
There's no there's not really any excuse
for for it, you know. And I did say I
was going to go to a gym tomorrow. So,
I'm going to go to a gym.
Yeah. Cuz just dating thing is getting
really boring, bro. So, I won't be out
this week. So, yeah. [Music]
I need to start going to sleep and
waking up at the same time every
day. I try to do it, but my routine for
some reason it just gets [ __ ] I say
this to my friend. It's like the most
important thing with your mental health
is you need to go to bed and wake up at
the same time every day or around about
the same time every day. So mine
obviously being around 10:30 and waking
up about 8:00. You need to go to bed and
wake up at the same time every day if
you can, but which obviously if you had
a routine you
can. So obviously sleep's important as
well when you're going to the to the gym
and [ __ ] It's about sleep as well. You
know what I'm saying? You sleep good,
eat good, and Yeah.
I do a lot of walking anyways,
but I'll be going back. But I'll be
going back. Don't
worry. No, I don't want to speak to you.
You're boring to me. Go self-reflect on another
channel. I need to report this little
virgin in a minute.
Anyways, and you know what's so bad is
they come on my channel when I'm drunk.
Steven Howard and thinking that I'm
going to mention them so they can get me
nicked. They're such a loser, bro. Such
a [ __ ] loser. I've never known such a
[ __ ] loser in my life. And trust me,
I've known loads of people. They
purposely went on my channel when I was
in the pub thinking I was going to bench
them so they could lobby me. What a
[ __ ] loser. I know they ain't got no
shame in that, bro, but proper proper
losers, bro. I swear down. Proper [ __ ] losers.
Yeah. No [ __ ]
uh no pet kangaroo. E Steven
Howard. No pet kangaroo.
Mic used to go to as well. So
yeah. Yeah. I know. No. I know what I'm
doing, bro. I know what I'm doing. I
know what these little virgins do. Yeah.
You don't need to tell me. I know, bro.
I might be drunk, but I know what these people are
doing. Trying to, you know, get you
nicked again cuz they're [ __ ] low life loser
virgins. Ain't got a
life. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
You don't need to tell me, bro. I'm I'm
a million steps ahead of
them. They think And that's But when you
get drunk again, you need to start
screenshotting [ __ ] This virgin keeps
doing this [ __ ] ratfaced virgin [ __ ]
So then um you know you can keep
reporting it and reporting it and
reporting it. So maybe I should get drunk more often.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm not going to stop, mate.
I'm not going to stop reporting them.
Trust me. So the police may as well just
not like long it off, bro. Like you
wanted to get yourself involved. Let's
get involved now. You know, you want to
get involved with social media. That's,
you know, whatever. Then let's get involved
then. Oh yes. More for me. I love this.
You know, now they're going to actually
have to do something now, you know,
because I've been following this up for
a month, right? This what this little
virgin's been doing, right? I'm just
going to keep reporting it and reporting
it and reporting it and reporting it and
reporting it and eventually it's all
going to get dropped. They're going to be [ __ ]
You know, they're doing God's work.
They're literally doing Lord's
work. That's four things right
now. Going to be at them. Going to be at
them again. One
second. One second. Is a time
address. I'm lucky I got jail, bro. Stop
talking about grassing on my channel,
you little weirdo. Anyone that talks
about [ __ ] grassing and that is as
good as a
grass. You know what I'm saying? Stop
talking about grass and about, oh,
you're lucky you're not in jail. Grass.
That's something a [ __ ] grass would
say. That's literally something that a grass would
say. Okay, I'm just typing my address
now. One second.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm I'm phoning Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm phoning the police. I'm not a
grass. I'm doing what you people do. I'm
not a grass. I'm I'm doing what you
people do. You've called the police on
me a million times, time and time and
time and time again. You know, there's
no point you coming on my [ __ ] calling
me a grass because it's not going to
bother me because we all know what you
people do running to the police millions
of millions millions and millions and
millions of times. Remember Steven
Howard, the Newcastle, the [ __ ] when
I used to live with my mom, the amount
of times these people have called the
police. That's fine. Yeah. Don't cry
when it happens to you. You know, I've
I've said this as well, Steven Howard.
You know, if somebody stabbed me
outside, I wouldn't tell the police. If
somebody if somebody uh if
somebody robbed my bike, I wouldn't call
the police. But when it's to do with
these people on YouTube, I'll be the
biggest grass. And I hate police. You
know how much I hate police because
you're just doing to them what they've
been doing to you over the years. You're
not even grassing. Actually, you're not
grassing. You're doing to
them. You're doing to them. You're doing
to them what they're doing to you. What
they've done to you for years and years
and years and years and years and years
and years and years and years. And yet
when you say you're calling the piece on
them, you're the one that's a grass.
Bro, you know how bad it is. LJ don't
even come in here and call me a grass
anymore because at the end of the day,
right, these people have been calling
the police for years. So like, [ __ ]
that, bro. Like you you are you can't
even tell anyone else they're in grass,
you know? Cuz you know people like
Trouble, right? Let's let's use Trouble
as example. Steven Howard, he likes to
call the police on people because it's
entertaining. Okay, fine. That's fine.
But don't cry when it happens to you
then. Don't winge and
moan. Don't winge and moan when it
happens to you. Don't cry when it
happens to you. That's what I'm saying.
It's entertaining when it happens to other people.
Um but don't cry
when when it happens to you. Hold
on. I'm I'm reporting this now. One second.
Don't cry when it happens to
you. So, yeah. One
second. I'm just reporting this. Hold on a
minute. Yo, the police might actually
uh the police might actually
um police might actually do something
actually. Yeah, they they they call the
police on people all day every day of
their lives. But then when you when you
do it, they don't call you a grass. I
think that's part of their autism,
bro. I think that's literally part of their autism.
Yeah, I think it's B autism.
Anyways, type in my name. One second.
I'm reporting this online. One second,
bro. I can start the whole ball rolling again
now. This is very stressful though.
Steven Hour. This is how you know this
little virgin don't have a life cuz you
know how I'm following up these reports
and stuff. It's very time
consuming. Um it's very time consuming.
It's boring. It's stress every week
having to keep going to the police.
That's how you know he's a virgin
because somebody would not have that
amount of time on their hands to keep
dealing with police. Nobody wants police
involved with their life. The police are
going to [ __ ] come on my door again.
I don't really want them coming on my
door again having to report something.
That's how you know he's a big virgin
because I I can literally vouch because
I've had to follow up with these reports
and you've had to go there or they come
on your door and trust me no one wants
police on their door but it has to be
done. But I'm saying that's how you know he's a
virgin because if someone somebody does
not have somebody a normal person would
not have that much time on their hands.
So, of course, it has to be done and I
am doing it, but I had to stop for like
two weeks cuz I needed a break. And this
little virgin has been doing it every
day probably for about six months.
That's how you know he's a big virgin.
You know what I'm saying, Steven Howard?
And you know how like all the things he
used to say sounds like what a virgin
would say. Of course you'd know all about
virgins being one yourself. Of course,
you'd know all about how you know all
about virgins. you are the biggest one
yourself, so you know all the telltale
signs. But Stephen Albert, I'm doing
this because I need to do this. I'm
doing this to protect myself. And even I
had to stop for like two weeks because
it's like, bro, like just following this
[ __ ] up every week. You know, when
people come out of prison, they don't
want to be involved with police the rest
of their life. That's how you know he's
virgin. Mentally obsessed virgin. And I
can I can tell you I can tell you it
because I've done it myself.
I can tell you it because I've done it
myself. No one wants to be involved with
police. People don't want police coming
on their [ __ ] door. You know what I'm
saying? Even if they are a victim, it's
not [ __ ] They're just not The only
thing I'd say that's good about the
police is they're coming um they're
coming down hard on phone snatchers. I
was in central London and they had like police mo
motorbikes. That's what they should be
[ __ ] doing. going down hard on
[ __ ] phone snatchers, not people that
saying mean things online. I was like,
"Oh, they're finally cracking down on
these [ __ ] now. That's a good thing." You
know, I hate phone snatchers. They're cowards,
mate. Nah, this takes ages. Bye-bye,
Jamie Thompson. You fat weirdo. Hey, I'm
going to the gym tomorrow. You should
try it, Jamie. I'll be starting the gym
again tomorrow. You should try it, mate.
You might lose some weight. Lose some of them
chins. You weirdo. But uh yeah, I don't
like I don't Oh, you don't need to worry
about people bullying me. You people
can't bully no one. You bully
yourselves. You people bully yourselves,
mate. You've been bullied since the day
you come out your mom's [ __ ] You people
don't bully no one, lad. You bully
yourselves from the time you come out
your mum's [ __ ]
You people bully nothing, mate. You
ain't got a life. You probably don't
even walk to the corner shop because you
probably get bullied when you try to leave your
house, mate. You people don't bully no
one. You bully yourselves every day on
YouTube. Isn't that right? Um Steven
Howard. Yeah, these people can never
bully me, mate. These people have had my
These people know where I live, you
know. Stephen Howard, we should mention
this. These people actually know where I
live. Yeah, you people don't bully no
one. You bully
yourselves. I don't like phone statues. They're very
cowardly. Have I got autism? I don't
have autism, but you do. Self
projector. So many self- projectors.
[ __ ] hell. Why do these people keep
talking about themselves? It's not good
for their mental health,
man. Uh, one second. Are you
under? No. Sorry. I'm trying to fill
this out at the same time, lad.
Yep. You know what this little virgin's
doing? They know that the whole thing's
getting dropped, so they're trying to
target me when I'm drunk, so then they
can get me nicked again. And they're a
loser, bro. They're a proper life
loser. Like they know that the whole
thing is is probably already dropped. So
they're trying to get you to say things
so they can get you nicked again cuz
they're just mentally obsessed virgins.
It's not going to
work. You can say what you want, do what
you want. Say you stop people saying
things. Yeah. If that makes you feel
better about yourself, that's good. You
know, we're not falling for your trap, bro.
Yeah, bro. [ __ ] off.
Anyways, yeah, one second. Hold
on. So, I'm trying to fill this out. Hold on.
Is there anything personal we need to
know about? I'm going to tell them that
I suffer from crippling anxiety. Autism.
I can't leave my
house. Autism. Crippling
anxiety. Autism. Crippling
anxiety. Yeah. One second.
Yeah. And like I said, they do it when
you're drunk as
well, cuz they think you're going to
[ __ ] up. Never in a million
years. These virgins need to get a
hobby. These little virgins need to get
a hobby and then get a
life. Seriously, bro.
Oh [ __ ] that's my other number now. Oh
[ __ ] I need to get my other phone out.
One second. It takes a piece like Yeah, cuz a
second. Why is the color bright? It's
gone [ __ ] Hold
on, hold on, hold on, hold on. Let me just concentrate
now. Display and
brightness. Where's the
display? Hold on a
minute. No, I'm skint as well,
mate. I can't send you nothing, mate. I'm
skin. I'm skin
myself. Okay, let me fill this thing
out. If we if we need to Yeah. contact
me on my phone. I'll put my SIM on my other
phone. I'll just use this as a
tablet. Get another phone just in case of what
exactly? Another phone for
what? What am I getting another phone
for? I've already got two
phones. I got
two. There we go. We got
two. Why do I need another phone, bro? I
already have two phones.
Yeah, I've already got screenshots, bro.
I've got screenshots on this phone. I've
got everything. I've got a whole
harassment folder. One second. Let me
finish off. Let me finish this
report. I had to buy this £400 phone,
bro. There was a reason for
it. Something to do with some job that
I'm doing. So, not getting into it. Just
I don't need to sort out my personal
life. But yeah. Esta
visa. It's quite good. This £400 phone.
I quite like
it. Yeah, I've got everything. One
second. Let me finish off reporting
this. I should have on this phone as well.
One second. Please second. Hold
on. Right. Telephone
number. Okay. Well, give me two seconds.
I'm going to come back live. Let me just
report this. Hold on. I'm going to come
back here. Just give me give me about 10
minutes. And I need to concentrate and I
can't concentrate with you [ __ ] So
yeah, just to report this virgin. So
yeah, give me give me about 15 minutes.