Yeah, I knew they were going to call me.
They they call me at this
uh they call you at that
time and I have to switch my SIM on my
other phone. So yeah.
Yep. That's the way it
goes. That's the way it
be. Yeah. Sorry about that. I was on the
phone to the old bell subway
surfer. Yeah, I told you I was serious, man.
100%. Sorry, mate. I was just on the
phone to the old
bill. Sorry about
that. Oh, the old
Bill. Yeah, I'm bored. Timmy, do you
want the link?
Timmy. Hey, Timmy. I need to talk to you, man.
judging by 1 million%. Do you know what?
I'll probably sign up to it now to be
fair, right? Let me
see. We're [ __ ] that good. One second,
bro. I should be able to get the early
hours to be
fair plus of
peak. So, it's going to be about 40 odd
pound. Don't need to buy the meat. We
get like some protein
shakes. But it's worth it in it, I think. [Music]
So that be alltogether like what? 40
quid. Yeah, I'm joining this gym, bro. I
told you I was dead serious about it.
Serious serious gains, bro. And I'll go
later. And then I was just on the phone to the
police. I told you they were going to
call me. That sounds like a good
combination. Getting the police
involved, going to the
gym. What a lovely
site. I don't think you could you could
want a better site than that. You know
what I'm saying? I [ __ ] couldn't. No.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to a gym tomorrow, think.
Defo. And And it's good cuz we can we
can kind of get like a decent body for
next month, which is July, cuz obviously
the weather's kind of [ __ ] So
yeah, I'll probably start with a big breakfast tomorrow
then go then salmon then chicken breast.
So it's going to it's going to be a lot
of money but be worth it. I
think something to do, you know, keeps
uh keeps you active.
Yeah, that's what I'm doing anyways. Nice.
Yeah. Probably save [ __ ] tons as well to be fair. Yeah. [Music]
Mhm. What do you think, Brick B? It's a
It's a lovely site, lad. Is it? Lovely sight. Hey, Timmy. Hello.
Hello. Can't hear
you. Kimmy. All right, PJ. How you doing?
One second. Let me rejoin my It's my
side. One second. No, it might be my
side. [ __ ] me. They were lush over
[ __ ] Skittles. Get the [ __ ] in
there. [ __ ] taste of the rainbow.
Delit. Where the bloody hell's he gone?
There he is. Can you hear me now? Can
I can't hear you. I'll come back. I need
to reset this. I can't even hear you.
One second. Let me reset the live
stream. I can't even hear you, man.
Phone's [ __ ] One sec.