Sorry. One sec.
I can't even hear this [ __ ]
mate. Yeah, I just had a police on the
phone. I just done another
report. You know, Timmy is a [ __ ]
idiot, mate. You can't come on in the
internet every day calling the police on [Music]
people and then when somebody does it
back to you, you say that they're a
grass. Like the world does not work like
that. Like you you you can't be a grass
and then when someone
reports you, you then call them a grass.
Like it's like what I said, you wanted
to call the police on people cuz it's
entertaining. It's it's funny getting
people arrested. Okay, whatever. But
just don't cry when it happens to you
then. Don't stop moaning and winging
when it happens to you. It's the same
thing with that traumad. If I had a
chance to get that trauma nicked, I
would do it because he's called the
police many, many times on people. So
yeah, you can't call people what you are
what you've been doing yourself for
years. [ __ ] off, mate. There's no point
even putting it on my channel. No one
listen remember Brit Bong. I never got I
never got the police involved to start
with. I never wanted to to to deal with
police. But then these people kept
getting police involved. So [ __ ] them.
Is it? If you can't beat him, join them.
Simple. It's my whole [ __ ] thing.
Anyways, how you doing PJ? So, I'm
smoking my vape de lad. Look, PJ, right?
I'm all right. I'm going to I'm I'm
going to be honest to you, mate. Oh, if
you want to I'm not going to argue. If
you want to call me a virgin, if it
makes you feel happy, PJ, you can call
me a virgin. Right, PJ? Look, you coming
on here saying [ __ ] about women, put
that aside a minute, but I'm talking
about you saying you're going to burn
the police back and all this and all
that. You're giving the trolls absolute
nine clar gold content. PJ, it took me
last week to learn this. And this is why
I've removed myself from the situation. PJ,
you can't be grasses and then call other
people grass. For PJ, no one PJ, I don't
grass. I wind them up. You don't get it.
I am a wind up merchant. PJ, do you
think I go to the police over this
YouTube [ __ ] The police can't even
[ __ ] get nons off the street, let
alone [ __ ] internet trolls. PJ. Well,
I've been nicked over it many times. But
PJ, you to be honest with you, PJ, you
have said some [ __ ] mate, which is
going to get you nicked over it. You've
been nicked [ __ ] half a dozen times
more than me. And all I speak about is
like Islam being an evil religion, and I
get nicked for that. And [ __ ] me, you
know? I mean, that's the only thing I've
actually been nicked for, you know, on
this website about Islam. Yeah, I've
been prison. You haven't? So PJ, if
you've been to prison, what prison did
you go to?
I've been to prison. Which one? There's
many of them in London. Why do you want
to know what prison I've been to? Cuz
you haven't been, have you? Of course.
Why would I say I haven't? I haven't.
PJ, I haven't been to prison. I've been
close, but I haven't been to prison. PJ,
you don't want to go to prison, PJ. You
wouldn't survive. Even I wouldn't want
to go to prison. So, okay then, PJ, what
time is me schedule? Wait, what do you
mean you you've been close? You've never
been to court? Yes, I have, PJ. Okay.
And what did they give you then? They
gave me Sorry, let me start again, PJ.
Cuz I did with all my words then. I was
lucky, PJ. I didn't have any evidence on
me, so I got a caution.
They took it to So you've never been
Yes, I Yes, I have. But it went out the
window. The people who took me to court lost.
Really? Yes, PJ. Really, PJ? Really?
They lost. And I got all my solister
funds back and all my money back.
So, how many convictions do you have?
None. Cuz like I said, I always win. PJ,
I am the winner.
Yeah, LJ says he has six convictions.
That's [ __ ] Oh, Lord Jay hasn't
been arrested. Don't listen to that
[ __ ] He's trying to be the new
[ __ ] Timmy Aldridge for [ __ ] sake.
We all know that now. It don't take a
rocket science to work that one out. PJ,
don't believe everything that guy tells
you. He hasn't. I don't I don't even
believe I don't even believe he's got
kids. He has got kids. He's not lying on
that. I'll say lit because you know
people how can you have kids if you're
on YouTube all day every day P PJ I will
say one thing Bangu is not a virgin
right I mean I don't like I'm not saying
I'm saying I don't think he's got kids
but PJ I don't like a lot of people on
here myself and there's a lot of people
who got a lot more money than me PJ but
I can't go around calling them skin PJ
when they've got do you know what I mean
every it doesn't some trolls PJ they
might have no lives and I totally agree
with you that 100% right but they're not
all [ __ ] [ __ ] virgins and poor. But I
mean, more than anything, PJ, a troll is
loaded cuz they don't leave the [ __ ]
house. What like Mr. B?
I'm not going to stag Mr. B off cuz I
like Mr. B. But like, you know, Mr. B if
that's his life going to the arcade and
backs the house and he wins consensually
because you can win on some people are
born to win on them machines, PJ, and
some people are born to die skint on
them. And unfortunately, I'm one of them
ones. How How much money do you have
right now, PJ? I've got on me probably.
right now 80 quid and I've got about
I'll be honest with you 250 to the end
of the week in the bank.
That's my personal account. PJ I had a
bad loss this week myself. But the thing
is PJ I don't talk about it on the
internet and I'll explain why PJ because
you're giving trolls. It's not like the
old days I don't really gamble anymore.
No, let me let me let me tell you
something. Yeah. So, I lost 300 I lost
300 pound on online roulette about two
weeks ago, and yesterday I lost 20 pound
in the pub slot, but I don't do it
seriously anymore, you know. No, I don't
PJ. I mean, it was the first time I had
a [ __ ] bad time on the 500s, PJ. I
win and lose, PJ, but when I have a bad
loss like I done last week, I won't be
on it now for a good month, PJ. I have
that That's what I'm saying. That's what
I'm saying. Exactly. That's what I'm
saying. When I win, PJ, I ain't going to
lie, I'll carry on and carry on and
carry on cuz I love gambling. But if I
lose PJ, I have to hold back because you
know what it was? I found a site that
lets you gamble with pounds. You know,
most of it's euros nowadays, but I found
one with pounds. It's addictive, man.
Roulette, PJ, PJ, all roulette is
addictive. PJ, why do you think PJ if I
didn't do roulette, I'd be very, very
successful and loaded now. You can even
ask money Mike. I know what I'm doing on
the fruit machines. But when it comes to
[ __ ] random games, sort of roulette
or where the house edge wins PJ, you're
never going to beat him. The only way
you still play fishing frenzy in it? Not
anymore. [ __ ] hate that game. Have
you seen Bookit's video where he can't
even get the hundred on it anymore on
the pub version? They've they've lo the
APRs on them, PJ. You can't win on them
like you used to. Some people, like I
said, like Mr. B are born to win. Some
people waiting for the football again. I
think the [ __ ] worst gambler out
there in my view, and he's the most
unluckiest gambler is probably Lord Jay.
I I do you know that Saturdays don't
feel the same without football betting
is in it. Yeah. Well, I do a little bit
myself here and then PJ, but to be
honest to you, PJ, I try to keep away
from gambling if I can. PJ, I'm like
you. I've gone back down the gym. I've
been at the gym all weekend. PJ, I can't
be bothered with the gambling anymore.
It's [ __ ] is it? Well, the industry's
gone now, PJ. The industry just you
can't win big anymore. I mean, PJ
PJ, I won in 2023 about about 30 grand
through the year. No word of a lie.
2024, I lost it all. This year, I'm
probably about 30 grand down because I
don't gamble. You remember that time I
went in the casino with 150 and I hit 11
mult cash? PJ, PJ, we've all done it.
We've all bumped big. But you got to ask
yourself the question, and I said this
to Money Mike in the week, it doesn't
matter how big you win. It's the fact is
how far do you want to [ __ ] fall?
Because in the end, PJ, you'll end up
flat on your [ __ ] face. You always
lose, in it, in the end. Yeah. Yes, you
do. Unless if you know what you're doing
on the fruit machines or the football
because there is pro gamblers out there,
PJ, and there is some very successful
gamblers, but you know, you need the
only the only good, you know, like, you
know, like a double both teams just go
on the football. That's good, isn't it?
Well, yeah. I've done that a few times
and I've won a couple hundred. But it
never lasts forever, PJ. I mean, like,
if you do football bets like Lord Jay,
you're only going to win one a [ __ ]
year. You know, the odds of winning the
odds of winning. I don't do that. I just
do double both teams to score. I mean,
look at 50% chance. But look at Seaside
Mark PJ. Look at Seaside Mark. He's only
won three grand once and he's the worst
gambler. I say Lord Jay is the second
unlucky. I say Mark's the unluckiest
gambler out there. Who would you say?
Who would you say is the worst gambler
on here? Like like the worst one ever?
Probably Mark and [ __ ] Lord Jay. The
others had too bad. What about us? Nah.
Well PJ, you have won some big amounts.
I mean, when it comes to the roulette,
you're like me. I have seen you sit
there and you do watch. But the thing
is, PJ, you can't expect to win. You
can't expect to win at all. And the
thing is, PJ, I you know, you haven't
take this personally. You haven't got
many people on your side. You've pissed
off a lot of people on the internet. You
said some [ __ ] things about women and
kids. And I'm not here to have a go at
you, PJ, cuz I'm in a chilled mood
tonight. And you got to take some
responsibility somewhere down the line.
PJ, I'm not an angel online. I'm a bad
troll. I tell people I don't hide it,
PJ. And I'm not on here to impress PJ to
impress people, PJ. People don't like
me, PJ. I don't give a [ __ ] But there's
a difference between you and me, PJ. I'm
built a lot more stronger than you.
Yeah, but Timmy, you don't put gambling
videos up anymore. But what what do you
want me to do, PJ? I hate this
community. It's like you said, how many
threats is Done? 10 [ __ ] million.
Done [ __ ] nothing. V 25 million
threats. Nothing. Banger says he's going
to kill me and I close his channel down.
A mother bottle job. PJ, I haven't got
time to entertain [ __ ] babies. PJ, a
whole new channel away from this
community. Do you hear? PJ, I do speak
to the communities, but I'm not saying
on here. Yes. Yeah. know, but I've got I
I I upload content on another community
that these people don't know about.
That's what I mean. Yeah. But the thing
is, PJ, the more you tell people this
sort of thing, the more they find it,
PJ, at the end of the day, I think
you're just a [ __ ] up kid. Don't take
this personally with bad autism like me.
And don't say you haven't got to me. So,
what you got then cuz you are on pip. If
you haven't got autism, what you got?
So, what you got then? You've got
something wrong with you. It doesn't
matter what I have, bro. Does it? So
yeah, you've got some sort of something
wrong. I'm not interested. I don't
really give a [ __ ] anyway. PJ, I don't.
It doesn't matter really, does it? But
PJ, you got to ask yourself the question.
But Timmy, you said you get £800 a
month, isn't it? That's cuz I get pip.
If I didn't get pip, I'd be on the same
as [ __ ] Tiger. £43 a month. How you
can't even live off that, is it PJ? I
don't think anyone I I struggle to live
off 800, PJ. Let alone [ __ ] 403. And
I and my food shop's about 100 quid a
week. Would you would you struggle to
live off a thousand? Yeah. Do you know
my lifestyle, PJ? Do you know how much I
need per month? And I'm not going to
[ __ ] to you. Two grand a month plus.
I get free. Well, I don't know how the
[ __ ] you get three grand, but I wouldn't
I mean, there's these rumors going
around that you've been subleting. I
wouldn't do that. PJ PJ, don't sublet.
You will go You'll get [ __ ] years for
that. And I mean yours. No, not not me. It's not
It's If if you want to make easy money,
PJ, don't sublet. I I don't I don't do
illegal stuff. Well, you don't get three
grand a month off pit, PJ. Put it that
way. So, you must be you must be caring
for maybe I'll work to be Well, I don't
know what you [ __ ] do. I don't really
care, PJ. To be honest to you. Maybe
I'll work, huh? I'm not one of these
people who gives a [ __ ] about people's
lives on there, PJ. To be honest to you.
I mean, it's so hard to make money on
YouTube nowadays. PJ, it's hard to make
money anywhere. I mean, I make my money
some way, but again, it's my secrets.
Yeah, exactly. You know, at the end of
the day, PJ, all I'm saying to you is
One second, Timmy. Hold on. Hold on a
minute, bro. One sec. You're talking
about us this accountable behind the
scenes. Why don't you join the hangouts?
PJ, I wouldn't bring trolls in here,
mate, cuz you you you know, be you know,
but PJ, I'm not I'm not trying to bully
you. I'm trying to help you here. You
coming on YouTube every day talking
about women, talking about this. You're
not helping yourself, bro. You're not
helping yourself one bit. If you need
help with women, there's organizations
out there that will help you with women. Organizations.
PJ, I didn't lose my virginity till I
was 19. I was I was crap with women at
school. I own it. I had a few
girlfriends at school, but I was see me,
man. PJ, I had a I have had a
relationship for 20 years. PJ, everybody
on YouTube knows that. They've seen my [ __ ] misses.
You can't be a virgin, sit there and
stay stand at the same woman for 20
years, PJ. Unless look at this. One
second. Has got 1200 a month and
everything buys catalog. Look at this
little projector. Hey, Monty. Sorry, not
Monty. Um Timmy, you don't realize most
of these people here are just self
projectors. You realize, PJ, you self
project. I self project. We all [ __ ]
do it on here. We're all trolls
back with them because they're just self
projectors. But you do it as well, PJ.
And I don't think you realize where you
do it. We all do it, PJ. The h the whole
human race self- projects. I don't self
project. These people are big self projectors.
But P, but seriously, PJ, what do you
want to do in your life? Do you want to
stand on here moaning for the rest of
your life or do you want to go out there
and do something? Look at this, bro. I'm
the only one on here that actually has a
life um to me. Yeah, but moaning about
riming an hour a night is not a life,
Peter. You need to do something. Okay.
So, I don't go out then. I don't go out.
It's not about going out PJ. I go out
PJ, but coming back on a Sunday evening
at [ __ ] you know, 1:49 in the
morning on YouTube, PJ and having a
life. The only reason why I'm watching
tonight is cuz I can't sleep. And the
reason why I can't sleep, PJs, is
because it's [ __ ] you know, quite
warm tonight. I I don't sleep a lot, PJ.
I only need four hours a night and I'm up.
Yeah, I can't sleep cuz I had a nap. You
know when you have a nap and you can't
go back to sleep? Yeah, if you have a
nap, mate, you're [ __ ] That's what
I'm saying. Yeah. Thing thing is thing
is PJ, my sleeping's weird. One day I
can be in bed 1 till 5 at night. One day
I can be in bed 1 in the afternoon to
11:00 at night. I've got I I've got in
zombie PJ. So my sleeping ain't perfect.
But if I get I've got my voluntary job
starting tomorrow, PJ. So I've got to be
there by 10:00. So I got Are you still
going on holiday? [ __ ] two. Damn
[ __ ] right. I am I need one mate
after the [ __ ] strain of [ __ ] year
I've had on here with spastics. When are you going?
PM, when are you going? Me? I'm going in July.
Yeah, I'm not I'm not saying what day
here, but I'm going at the end of July.
What? Um, are you going to put some
videos up? I might do when I come back.
Yeah. Yeah, might as well. But don't
forget, PJ, I've hid my account to the
end of August. I'm having a break. I've
only come on here tonight, PJ, cuz I'm
[ __ ] extremely bored and I'm
scratching the back of my head out and I
don't want to go to Murka because I
can't afford to lose any more [ __ ]
money. You should come to London.
What? Right now, PJ. [ __ ] hell. It
cost me about Not right now, but like
maybe next week.
I might be, PJ. You don't know. We can
have some Guinness.
PJ, I don't want Guinness. I'm [ __ ]
summertime. I drink cider in the summer
or laga. Well, you don't like Yeah, but
not in the summertime. It's a winter's
drink for me. Really? Yep. I drink that
in the winter. But I bet you've never
had Corona. Yes, I have. I don't mind
Corona. I've had it many. I don't know
why I stick to cheaper, Tim. I stick to
beer cuz it's cheaper and you get no hangovers.
Well, yeah. At your age, you shouldn't
get hangovers on beer. I do cuz I'm
older. But but when you when I drink
spirits, I get hangover for like two
days. It's bad. That's why I try not to
drink spirits anymore. Bob, spirits are
not good for you. Unless you drink
vodka, cuz vodka doesn't give me a
hangover. It's a clear alcohol. Any
other spirit like whiskey and that makes
me ill for days.
Yeah. But the thing is PJ, right what do
you do this? Can I ask you a question?
You [ __ ] know. How does Hyperlinks
have all this money? Oh, I can ask you
that he went into crypto and he got very
successful. Cuz he been to He's been to
Vegas quite a few times. And he Yeah,
but PJ Vegas ain't that dear. I could go
twice a year if I didn't gamble in the
UK. Really? Yeah. Really?
I only Sorry, Timmy. Did you used to
speak to Ant-Man? No, I've never Don't
even know who he is.
Well, how do you know what have you
heard of him? I've heard of him many
times, PJ, but I don't know who he is.
I've never physically met him like you
like in the past and I don't know. I
don't know much about him. No, he used
to watch Seaside Mark. Everybody's seen
Seaside Mark. That's how the [ __ ] PS
community come over here through Seaside
Mark. But serious question, PJ. Serious.
What do you get out of this YouTube? Cuz
I get absolutely [ __ ] all out of it.
That's why I'm having a break. I don't
really come on much anymore to me. So
why you here, man? talking about women,
the same [ __ ] letting the trolls
[ __ ] get to you. Now, at the end of
the day, PJ, you do get some decent
people in here, you know. But PJ, I
troll you and I'll own it while I troll
you cuz the [ __ ] you said about women
and [ __ ] kids is disgusting and
that's why I troll you. I couldn't hit
you, PJ. [ __ ] You should come and do
something about it. But PJ, you don't
understand. I'll kill you. I'm [ __ ]
massive. If I punch you once, you could
even beat me with tiger. You PJ, if you
want to sign a contract so when I
[ __ ] put you six foot under, you
can't do me for murder. I'm very happy
to do running up the road. PJ, I ran
towards you. You ran. You were the
backwards man. You were the backwards
man. Ran up the road and left. PJ, PJ,
PJ, we're having a nice conversation
here. Let's not ruin it [ __ ] over
stupid. You could even beat me twoon-one
for [ __ ] sake. PJ, if you want to sign
PJ, if you want to sign a contract, I am
that confident in a boxing ring. You
won't get up. I've been PJ, I've been
learning to box myself in the past
couple of years. I'm not brilliant at
it, but I'm getting there and I'm going
back more fulltime.
Okay, put it this way. I could beat
[ __ ] three Mongols up [ __ ] piece
of piss. But the thing is, PJ, I'm not a
fighter. I don't go out there to hurt
people, PJ. I'm a I'm a lover, but I
only hurt someone PJ. Somebody pushed me
to the [ __ ] limits. And I mean, push
me to the limit. Timmy Monty beat you.
Monty didn't do anything. PJ again. I
would have killed him. Even Mark Taylor
said that on the stream. If Timmy would
have put full strength in, Mongol would
have been [ __ ] six foot under. M.
you. I don't The reason why I've never
fully gone into people on this website
made you taste a filthy mattress. Uh, no
he didn't. I slipped. Get it right. So
like at the end of the day, the only one
who knows what I'm about on here is
Money Mike. He's the only one who knows
I've got a short [ __ ] temper. Yeah,
but Money to be fair, he's a [ __ ] No,
he's not. He had to take money was
trying to Okay. Okay. You You weren't
there. You weren't You weren't there the
other day when Money Mike had to take a
baseball bat and carve me to the [ __ ]
floor cuz I was fuming with someone. I'm
not going to say it, but I was fuming
with somebody on YouTube and I was going
to go and do the windows in PJ money to
stop me. PJ, I have got a short temper.
You just don't I just don't show it on
here. You might see me a bit triggered,
but if any of you saw my temper, I don't
think you know what to do.
I think you're trolling me, Timmy. I'm
not trolling you, PJ. I'm being deadly
[ __ ] serious. What do you want out of
life, Timmy? I've already got everything
I want out of life, PJ. A good family
and that. And that's why I don't come on
here talking about women, talking about
the same [ __ ] PJ, and I troll. Because
if you want, why don't you why don't you
move to Australia? PJ, I might in time.
You know, start a new life. But PJ, can
I ask you a question? Why did you [ __ ]
yourself when Prime hit you by the
[ __ ] neck? If that was me, I'd just
laugh. Cuz you cuz you cuz you caught me
off guard. If that you went running up
the road, you idiot. What are you
talking about, PJ? PJ, I got caught off
guard by Welsh. He punched me to the
floor. And if you look at the video, I
said, "Is that the best you got?" And I
was running up the street when Tiger come.
It wasn't my fight, PJ. It was between
you called Tiger a [ __ ] He was running
up the road because I was running up the
road. PJ, I was running up the road cuz
it wasn't my fight. It was between you
and PJ. It was your fight because No, it
wasn't PJ. Yes, you did. You did, PJ. I
think you've got a very short memory.
You called him a [ __ ] and and he came
out and [ __ ] battered you. No, it
wasn't. It wasn't our fight. You're the
one that got him to fight me. No, PJ, I
didn't. He's got his own mind, PJ. And
even he can confirm that fight. One
second. One second. Let me kick Timmy a
second. He said that it was my fight and
he's got his own mind. I never argued
with Tiger ever. Never argued with
Tiger. Never had beef with Tiger. So,
no. You got Tiger to fight your battles
and then you ran away. So, yeah. Anyway,
stop repeating yourself. Your boy
now. Not you, Timmy. Sorry. had to block this
account. Yeah. Stop repeating yourself.
Yeah. Never had beef with Tiger ever.
Never had a problem with
Tiger. But yeah, somehow he
come and fight and fight me. What's Yeah.
One second, bro. Awesome.
Sorry about that,
bro. Turn the fan on and have a little
snooze. I paid all my bills for the month. Asberger. Yep.
paid all my bills for the month,
lad. Yeah. All of them. Electric, phone,
internet. You proud of me?
Anyways, I'm out of here. See you later.