Oh, [ __ ] took ages,
man. They want to meet. So, we'll see. We will
Uh, just clean the kitchen, man. Just
chilling. Going gym tomorrow. Not today.
I'm going tomorrow. I said every other
day in it. But just had some steak.
H good old
steak. Good old
shaky. Oh, is it? No one cares, bro. The
only one he violates is himself. I've
told him many times, he can come to
London. And he keep keeps making
excuses. And I said, once you prove you
book the flights, I'll pay. I don't care
about these retards, bro. Stop
um stop bringing it on my channel. The
guy knows where I am. I've offered him
to come millions of times. Don't bring
that [ __ ] on my channel or any
[ __ ] that's associated with him.
Yeah. I went to the gym yesterday. I'm
going again tomorrow.
He violates himself. Dispastic. I don't
want to hear about it. Weirdo,
man. Chilling here with a cup of
[ __ ] He doesn't violate no one,
mate. Yeah, there's no time for it cuz
he doesn't violate no one. He's been
asked several times to come to London
without LT getting involved and he shits
it every time now. Yeah. He doesn't
violate no one but himself. That's the
only one that he's got time for.
Yeah. You think some diabetic [ __ ]
tattooed ugly freak who's never who's
not even well traveled in his 40s can
can violate someone like me, bro? It's
not even it's not even making sense.
That's not even making sense,
bro. Oh, did that say
anything? Anyways, moving on
now. Anyways, moving on now.
Boring. Um, so yeah, I like my medium. Well
done. Yeah. Anyways, moving on now.
Boring. Anyways, moving on. I'm not even
going to block this account. I'm just
going to ignore
it. Get a life. Go for
YouTube. Get a life. No one has ever
violated me ever.
Anyone that's come to my door, I've
literally come out every time, mate. The
guy come to England and he done
nothing. He came to England and he done
nothing. Literally nothing. He argued
with me at my front doorstep and I told
him to [ __ ] off and I was standing in
front of my mom. You think I would ever
go on someone's door just to argue with
them? No, bro. That that might be out of
order to you in your [ __ ] world, but
not not in real life. That that is
nothing. He's just wasting his time.
Really, if he was actually basically to
tell the truth like, "Come on, bro. You
done nothing." He had several chances to
hit me. I was standing in front of my
mom. Try again, bro. That's [ __ ] [ __ ]
Hear about nothing. Anyone can jump on a
20-minute plane and go on someone's door
and have a panic attack. Anyone can do
that. It's boring. You would never leave
YouTube. You would never leave YouTube.
I've seen you on here for years.
I've seen you on YouTube for years, man.
You will never leave
YouTube. Yeah. Yeah. You will never leave YouTube,
man. I've seen you on here for years.
That Yeah, that John Street account. You
will never leave YouTube. Little
self-reflector. Oh, that's cute, isn't it?
Yeah. You will never leave YouTube
either. You can't take a day off of YouTube. So yeah.
Yeah. Yes, I've tried lobster before.
Right. Who put a thumbs up to that? One
second. What needs to be done about
that, bro? My hands smell like [ __ ] bleach now. Yep.
So, when are you people going to come
off of YouTube
anyways? When will you people come off
YouTube? Come off of YouTube.
Nope. No plans. Plans to go to Thailand in 3 weeks.
Nope. Why do I smell Lewisville
Slugger? I can smell Louisville Slugger
again. I'm getting them vibes again.
H maybe I'm maybe my smelling is not
um as it's supposed to be but I smell a looseful slugger.
won't mention any names, but
yeah, if it's been your dream for years,
why aren't you
um why haven't you
gone? Why haven't you gone? If it's been
your uh dream for
years, money or what?
[ __ ] man. I don't know why I'm so
tired. Yeah, it was
okay. I'm going to much prefer Thailand.
What do you mean you never got around to
it? How can you not get around to it,
mate? We got a date on Thursday.
Hopefully she don't flake. Yay.
Oh [ __ ] These [ __ ] are mad. This is
one of the reasons why I'm going to
Thailand, man. To get away from it all.
Yeah. Boston. Long
story. Yeah. Boston is a long story. So
yeah, so obviously I'll be drinking on
Thursday cuz I need to meet this woman.
So no, I'm not doing that one. [ __ ] that, bro.
No, I went to get um the main purpose
was getting revenge on some
[ __ ] Yeah. Getting some getting
revenge on some nasty [ __ ] Didn't come
out. Of course. Cuz them Americans are
all yappy yappy yappy. You know what I'm saying,
bro? They're all yap yap yap yap yap yap
yap. They all talk but no action, you know.
So, yeah, just hitting the gym.
Obviously, this person wants to meet on Thursday,
so I'll meet them. If they didn't want
to meet, then I wouldn't be going out
until next week. So, yeah.
Yep. Yeah, I did. Got a key. Yeah, man.
Cuz obviously you can't go German and
drink the [ __ ] same wheat, bro. It
defeats the object. You know what I'm
saying? It completely defeats the [ __ ] object.
What? It's out. Sorry.
Sorry. Well, I went to a lot of places, bro.
I went to some bars,
clubs. Am I drinking this week? Did you
not listen to what I just said? Have you
got brain damage? Respectfully, did you
not listen to what I just
said? I just said if this person wants
to meet me, which they said they are, then I
will. But if not, then
no. I'm going I'm at the gym in it, so
I'm not going to drink the next day.
I'm upset. I'm not upset at all. I'm
fine. Not upset at all,
matey. Yeah. I was going to drink. Yeah.
Yeah. Drink spirits. It's neat. Less
calories. Yeah, man. And then you wake
up the next day with a hangover for two
days and you got paranoia and anxiety.
Yeah. That's better, isn't
it? Yeah. And then you get paran. I was
going to drink spirits to be
honest. Yeah, don't call me Bella, man.
You never say to my face, so don't say on here. So,
yeah. No. Yeah, I probably will drink
the spirits, but spirits is worse. It's the worst
thing. Is my anxiety crippling? Yeah.
Yeah. I'm bedbound, mate. I'm
bedbound. Yeah. Bed bound. I can't leave
the house. I'm bedbound.
Yeah. Didn't you
know? Yeah. I got bad anxiety in
me. Proper bad, man. Can't leave the house. Nothing.
No. No. Bad anxiety. I've got Yeah. I'm
bedbound. Bit like you people on YouTube
every day with cripping anxiety, isn't
it? Yeah. It's almost as bad as yours on
YouTube every day. I can't leave the
house. Yeah. It's almost as bad as your anxiety.
I'm a funny [ __ ] Is it? You know what?
I think I should I should be a comedian.
It's almost as bad as yours. And Lord
Jay's I'm an absolute victim. Yeah.
Okay, bro. You're a keyboard warrior. My
life is embarrassing. My life is better
than yours. Bye-bye. Bye-bye, keyboard
warrior. Oh, you're at work. Oh, right. You're at
work. Yeah, mate. The only victim is you
people on YouTube. You've been bullied
your whole life. That's why you come on
YouTube every day because you're absolute bully
victims. No, it was real. Obviously, it
was real, bro. What the [ __ ] Yeah, the
police called me cuz I reported um
Virgin Boy, which I told you I was doing
anyways. Mate, the only victims is you
people. You little bully victims. That's
why you come on YouTube every day, cuz
you ain't got a life. You've been
bullied your whole life. The only
victims is you people. Proper proper victims.
Sorry, Jo. I was just cleaning the
kitchen, mate. So, yeah, it was it was
long. Just doing some cleaning up. Yeah, it was
real. Yeah, they called me at like
11:00, man. So, they called me and I
spoke to them. Yeah, I told you I'm
doing this reporting [ __ ] when it comes
to this virgin. I told I told you that
like [ __ ] four weeks
ago. That's a criminal event events. I
don't give a [ __ ] bro. You're talking
to somebody that that don't care. And I
didn't lie about anything. And even if I
did, I don't care. I'm not scared of the
police. Like, you shouldn't be saying it
to somebody like me. I literally don't
care. Like, I don't even like the
police. So, I don't care if I was to lie
to them. I literally don't
care. Like, one little bit. I don't like
them. Never have, never will. So,
so yeah, I literally don't care about
them. I hate them. They're they're
probably on the same rave length as
probably pedophiles. That's how much I
despise them. I don't like police. Never
have, never will, especially in this
country. So, I wouldn't give two shits
about lying to
them. And then your next question is
going to be why do you call them then if
you don't like them? Am I I'm guessing
Why do you call the police if you don't like
them? I can't call the police that.
Well, I can because I just just did. So,
I can call them that because I just did.
They were saying,
"Jo, I can because I literally just did." So,
yeah. One second, bro.
Um, you don't you you don't want to know
what I was saying to them when they come
down there. I was calling them piglets,
piggies, everything. I don't give a
[ __ ] I don't like the police. They're
bent as [ __ ] Corrupt.
Corrupt. Yeah. People, mate, listen. You
people on YouTube every day, you know
all about getting bullied.
Bye-bye. You know all about getting
bullied. You're on YouTube every
day. Nah, it's not madness, bro. I have
to do it. I have I had to call them. I
have to keep following it up and calling
them as well. And to be honest, they
love coming to the house, so why not?
You know, it's a big thing for the
police. So, in a way, I'm actually helping
them. So, yeah. So yeah,
man. These people are such self
projectors, man. These people definitely
been bullied in life on this community. Definitely bully
victims. The only people that get
bullied. Yeah. Just like when you kept
ringing them up saying that I was
bullying you. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Just
like when you people have called the
police on me a million times saying that
I was bullying you. And I've had them at
my [ __ ] door. See, the thing is with
these people, Joe, they don't like it
when it's on the other foot. Like, they
don't mind. Like, they call the police,
right? Because it's entertaining to
them. It's funny to them, and it's all
well and good, but then as soon as you
do it back, they don't like it. Have you
noticed that with these little [ __ ]
virgins on this community? These little
weirdos, they don't like it when you do
it back to them. They'll call you out
all the names under the sun like,
"You're a grass." And [ __ ] off, mate.
Like, they do this madness. Yeah. And
then when you do it back to them, they don't like
it. It's so
weird. It's such It's so weird, bro. Like
really. Exactly, bro. Like I I will
listen. They have done it millions of
times. Millions. Millions. Millions of
times. So you can't cry when it happens
to you, you know, like I know a few
times right when they done it, I was
like, "Okay, whatever. They're just
doing it to like muck around and they
haven't really done it." And I was like,
"If you can't beat them, join it. [ __ ]
it. I'll do the same thing, you know."
And LT knows knows now and and that
Tramino, if I had a chance to do it to
him, I'd do it to him. Okay. It's funny.
It's funny you doing it to people, but
then when it happens to you, don't start
crying. That's what I'm saying. Don't
start moaning and
winging, you know?
So you know you who's the one that
started calling police from this
community you know several different
people you know so don't you wanted to
get the police involved they wanted to
get involved so let's get them involved
that's my whole that's my whole that's
my whole outlook on
it so you know and it's same with
Tramodo if I ever found out Trador
um you know I'll do the same thing to
him you know same thing to him. And to
be honest with you, if I found out about
LJ J, I would do the same thing to him
because he's called places up trying to
get me banned. And in my eyes, that's
grassing. In my in my eyes, that's
grassing. So if he does
that, if I have a chance to [ __ ] him
with the police, I'll [ __ ] him with the
police. Simple. Like it's, you know what
I'm saying? Cuz in a
way, I'm not going over it again, bro.
They told me to come back in three and a
half years. I'm done talking about this. You
know, it's boring now, man. Just don't
cry if it happens to you. I'm following
this [ __ ] up every
week and that's it. And then eventually
they're going to get
nicked. Trust me, it took them six
months to [ __ ] nick me. So yeah, you
can't beat them. Join them. And the
courts told me to do that as well. And
the solicitor told me to do that as well. So
yeah, you wanted to start getting police
involved on this community for whatever
reason. So they're involved now in it.
So that's it. I don't mind. So,
uh, just don't contact the [ __ ] which
is which is a good thing really. I'm I'm
glad, you know,
like this seems crazy to have to do
this. Well, I'm going to be doing No,
not three years. It's not going to be
three years. Probably about like a
month, six months. But I don't care, bro.
They just said, "Don't contact the C."
That's the only thing I've got. So, I'm
happy. Really, the court's done me a
favor. Who wants to contact that [ __ ]
virgin? That silly little coward virgin.
So, anyways, moving
on. So, yeah, when somebody plays you at
your own game, don't start moaning and winging and
crying, you know? That's it, bro. I
don't mind. You know, I've been lit.
Fine, whatever. But don't m Don't moan
when it happens to
you. Laughing at what? I've basically
got away with it. It's going to be
dropped in three and a half years.
There's nothing to be laughing at. You
know, they have to be careful what they
do now as well.
So, they have to be careful what they do
now as well because obviously they know
I'm I'm I'm reporting every week. And
I'm going to come back on here when I'm
drunk cuz that's when they seem to come
on here when I'm drunk because they
think I'm going to slip up. Why do you
think they come on here when I'm
drinking? Because they think I'm going
to start mentioning them and they can
run to the police again. So I know when
I'm drunk to come back on here and
screenshot the lot and then just go back
to the police with all the other things
you've got and it will make everything
relevant. Why do you think they don't
come on here anymore really? And
everything that they do do they delete?
Because they know, is it? They [ __ ]
man. So that's it.
Nope. Why would I be on probation, you
[ __ ] idiot? I didn't even get found
guilty. So why'd I be on probation, you
fool? Probation? How can I be in
probation when they told me to come back
in three and a half years? That doesn't
even make sense. But
um but yeah, anyways, it'll get sorted out anyways.
So, it'll get sorted. Don't worry, man.
These things take
time. But it's very stressful to keep
doing it every week. That's how you know he's a
virgin. That's how you know he's a
proper virgin. And the thing is, Joe,
yeah, you you always try and say, "Oh,
they're not a virgin because they've got
a girlfriend." You never back me up.
I've been laid more times than him
clearly cuz he's still a [ __ ] virgin.
But I never see you back me up. And
we've actually seen me have sex. That
guy is a proper proper virgin. Trust me,
mate. For somebody to put themsel
through that, you must be a proper
virgin. And And you can't you can't copy
and paste it either. You can't copy and
paste the [ __ ] Nah. No. That that's a
that's a proper virgin, bro. Especially
if you're in a relationship as well cuz
it's stress on yourself. It's actually
it's stress on yourself doing that every
week. It's stress on me doing it every
week. I stopped for like two weeks. I
was like [ __ ] hell having police come
on your door and call you. It's [ __ ]
man. Mate, that [ __ ] has never had sex
ever. Why do you think he knows all the
telltale signs about virgins? He's the
biggest one himself. So why do you think
he goes on about virgins? cuz he's he's
the walking virgin. The walking talking
one. Trust me, mate. There's no way,
mate. You can have a sex life if you're
reporting crime every week, mate. He's
never had it. Literally. Literally never
had it. It don't go in. I'm telling
you. And you're saying that you're not
asked? Well, you're clearly asked
because every time I've said it, you
keep defending the [ __ ] So, obviously,
you are asked. He's a walking talking
[ __ ] virgin, mate. walking talking
one the biggest one going known to
mankind if there was one so uh yeah that's
it and you're saying that I shouldn't lie to
police please. Yeah, there's not going
to be no court date. There's not going
to be no court date. I've got all the
evidence that I'm bringing with me. Just
I said just send me everything that
you've got and I've got pages and videos
and pages. Good luck. Good luck. Good luck, Virgin
boy. Yeah, you're not going to come to no [ __ ]
court. You're going to go to court and
lose. That would be just
embarrassing. [ __ ] hell,
man. Yeah, I don't like the police,
lad. There is people that are in
relationships that don't have sex. There
there is literally people that are in
relationships that don't have
sex. Literally there there literally is
How can you have sex with a special
needs a special needs woman? How can you
have sex with a special needs woman?
That doesn't even make any sense. You
know why do you think he goes on about
[ __ ] Morgan and all of these people?
It's because he's a
virgin. Cuz he's the biggest virgin
going. the biggest
one. It's so nice that he doesn't know
any about about any of these new women.
Imagine you knew about the Australian
the Thai Australian. Oh, [ __ ] me, mate.
Could you imagine? Eh,
uh, Joe, stop it. It's boring now,
buddy. It's boring. Stop it. You're not
going to put fear into me. You're not
going to put anxiety into me. Stop it.
Remember what I told you about me not
being Monty and
Timmy? Please, bro. It's embarrassing. Stop
it. I wouldn't take it per I wouldn't
you wouldn't take the risk when I've
literally got all the evidence of this
[ __ ] harassing me for 10 years. Well,
you must be a damn fool because guess
what, bro? If there even was a chance of
me going to prison, I would take that
chance any day of the week. If they said
to me right
now, right? If they said to me right
now, um, you know, you can go to prison
for 6 months in three and a half years
or you can plead guilty. I'd be like,
take me to prison. Simple. Like that.
That's what I'm like. I would say take
me to prison because at the end of the
day, the amount of evidence that I've got,
um, you'd be a damn fool to plead
guilty. So like, yeah. So I even if that was the
case, it's never going to happen. You're
never going to go to prison for that.
I'd rather go prison. So that's that's
that that's that's my whole thing on it. So So
yeah, but anyways, mate, are you stupid?
How can you go to prison for that? No
one goes to prison for that. You don't
even get community service for that.
So you don't even get community service for
that. I need to report. I'm going to
call the police again, maybe on Friday,
maybe. Yeah, exactly. No, no, not clever
at all. I've got all the evidence. Nope.
Nope. Nope. Not clever at all, mate. Not
clever in the slightest. It's only a
case of me having to keep going back to
the police. Um, and keep doing it and
doing it and doing it. It's not them
being clever. They're not clever at all.
They're thick as pig [ __ ] But it's me
having to keep going back and back and
back and back and back. Mate, trust me,
I've got everything and it's going to
make all of this stuff relevant. Not not
clever in the
slightest. So, it's not in my record,
mate. I've got no convictions.
I've got no convictions. I've got no
convictions whatsoever. And even when
you get convicted, it lasts about it
goes away after some some some for like
filtering and stuff. But trust me, Joe,
it's not going to happen. But
yeah, mate, it's not even going to go to
court in three and a half years. We
shouldn't even be talking about this.
It's not even going to court. Why are we
still talking about this boring [ __ ]
bro? It's boring, man. What the [ __ ]
still going on about
this [ __ ] This is boring, bro. Three
and a half [ __ ] years. I might be dead by
then. Anyways, moving on, man. [ __ ] hell. So,
yeah. I do feel sorry for the courts
though, the police having to [ __ ]
waste taxpayers money on somebody that
started it himself. It's sad cuz there's
actual people out there getting robbed,
getting their phone snatched, people
being [ __ ] murdered and [ __ ] and
then you got somebody that start [ __ ]
themselves on the internet and then
plays victim. It's pretty It's pretty
[ __ ] up, is it really? I saw somebody
get their phone robbed the other day and
uh they got um they were
crying. Yeah, it's not going to happen
anyways. We're moving on from this now.
Anyways, I don't want to talk about it
anymore, but they are cracking down on
phone snatches, which is what they
should be doing, man. They shouldn't be
catching people saying [ __ ] mean
things on the internet. They should be
catching phone snatches, man. The amount
of misery they cause to people's lives,
you know that they should be catching
them. That's why they've got police on
motorbikes now in Oxford Circus. And so
they [ __ ] should. They should. They
need to start cracking down hard on them [ __ ]
um Yeah, bro. I don't care. You're not
going to scare me. I don't give a [ __ ]
Good for them. I'm not asked. I'm not
talking about this no more. It's boring.
I'm not talking about it no more. I
don't ever bring this up. The police
called me. I answered the [ __ ]
phone. I don't give a [ __ ] I'm not
talking about this [ __ ] in three and a
half [ __ ] years, almost four years.
It's boring, bro. Get a
grip. Yeah, bro. You're not scaring me,
bro. Just stop going on about it. I don't
care. I literally don't give a
[ __ ] I'm not going getting into this.
It's boring, bro. I don't even like
having to go to the [ __ ] police every
[ __ ] week, but I've got
to. So, at the end of the day, like,
let's just stop talking about it now,
bro. It's boring.
We're talking about you people not
having [ __ ] lives, man. What the
[ __ ] bro? Listen, Joe, let me let me
try to explain this to you one more
time. Yeah. I don't care about the
police. I I
I don't like the police. Do Do you not
understand how how many times do I have
to tell you this? Yeah. That time that
they come on my door the other day, they
were lucky they didn't get a good
[ __ ] hiding. And it was only good
that, you know, I was saying stuff with
my mouth. I was saying stuff with my
mouth and it was words and not actions.
Bro, do you know the amount of [ __ ] I
was telling I was saying to them when
they were here. I say the other day, two
months ago, whatever. I don't care about
them. They do not scare me. I don't
care. I do not like them. Simple. That's
it, bro. It's they're corrupt as [ __ ]
And that's it. And that that's it. And
I'll say it to the face. I don't like them. Simple.
So So I don't care about the the the
police. I don't like the
police. I really do not like them. I
don't respect them one little bit. I
think they've got their favorites. I
think they're corrupt. I think the
system's [ __ ] And I don't like them. Simple.
So in this country anyways I don't know
about how how other countries work
but this country I do not like
them who I'm what am I lying about? What
about? What the [ __ ] am I lying about?
Yeah. Anyways, we're not talking about
this anymore, bro. I'm not talking about
police and [ __ ] anymore, bro. What the
[ __ ] Stop bringing up the police, bro. What the [ __ ] God,
man. I keep [ __ ] calling the police.
I tell you what's going to get thrown
out in court in three and a half years.
If it makes the three and a half years,
the amount of evidence that I've got,
that's what's going to be getting thrown
out. That's what's been going to that's
going to be getting what that's what's
going to be getting thrown
out. You know what I'm
saying? That's what's going to be
getting thrown out.
I'll tell you that. I tell you that's
what's going to be getting thrown
out. So yeah, and I'm not talking about this anymore.
Anyways, we're not talking about this
anymore. Police and [ __ ] courts and [ __ ] you know.
So yeah, I'm not talking about anymore. Moving on.
Yeah, it's boring, bro. Really, really,
boring. Okay, we're not talking about
this anymore, bro. I'm done. You're talking to
yourself. You're talking to yourself now,
bro. Yeah, I'm not talking about this no
more. Anyone that keeps bringing up, I'm
going to block them. I don't want to
talk about it anymore. So, stop bringing
it up. It's annoying. You know, they're
going to get [ __ ] in the end. Trust
me. However smart you think they
are. Yeah. Oh, listen Ricky. You know
how you know about autism? Because
you've got it yourself. It's not your
brother. I I read your comment on uh
someone's whose was it? Someone's
channel, bro. It's not your brother
that's got autism. It's It's yourself.
You've got autism. That's how you know
all the telltale signs about the cinema
and because you you've got autism and
anxiety. It's yourself, not your
brother. It's yourself, you autistic [ __ ]
You know, keep talking [ __ ] behind
people's back, bro. You will never say
anything to anyone's face. You
anxietyridden little s. You don't ever
leave your house, bro. Ever. You anxiety
Mr. Autistic. It's you, not your
brother. Go suck your mom, you silly
[ __ ] And you know where I live and
you're not going to do a damn thing
about it. Bro, listen. How about this
right here, right now? Yeah. I'll prove
everyone how much of an autistic,
anxietyridden [ __ ] you are right now.
You got my address. Why don't you come
to my address? Why don't you tell us
where you live? You [ __ ] keyboard
warrior. Anxietyridden [ __ ]
Can't leave his house. You [ __ ]
autistic s [ __ ] who can't leave
his house. Go and suck up your mom.
Ricky, go suck up your mom. I You have
my address. I don't have yours. You
[ __ ] stupid little
[ __ ] You [ __ ] anxietyridden piece of
[ __ ] Will never come on my door. Never.
And you know where I live as well.
Everyone knows where I live. So there you go, bro.
Yeah. You [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] You live
in hole. Pro do a video showing that you
live in hole, bro. Yeah. Do a video
showing you living in hole and I'll come
on Saturday. You live in hole. Yeah.
Okay. Do a video showing that you live
in hole on your account and I'm coming
on Saturday, bro. You're the only one
with autism, bro. You silly little [ __ ]
That's why you defend women because
you're a virgin. You don't know anything
about [ __ ] women. You [ __ ]
anxietyridden little northerner. You're
all the [ __ ] same. You little northern anxietyridden
bastards. You little [ __ ] northerner.
Anxietyridden bastards. How many times
have I come up your gaff and violated
you many times and none of you come out?
How many times has this anxiety ridden
autistic person come and embarrass you
to the point where you can't even leave
your house? You little [ __ ] Yeah, you
talk [ __ ] behind people's back, but in
real life, you're just a northern little
[ __ ] You're just a little [ __ ]
And you know you are as
well. You have 200 women and you [ __ ]
your mom 200 times, mate. That's the
only women that you've had. You [ __ ]
anxietyridden bastard northerner. Little
[ __ ] Oh, don't cry, bro. Cuz I've
caught you talking [ __ ] behind my back.
But you never say to my face. Never.
Only behind your little account because
of your anxiety.
only behind your little gay account. And
you know better as well. You know better
as well, bro. You know better as well.
Like how many times have I had Yeah, he
was skinny lad. Whatever, bro. Listen,
all you do is talk [ __ ] behind people's
back behind your little gay account.
Like enough of it now, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. I apologize to LJ, bro. The
guy caught me off guard. Yeah, the guy
caught me off guard. But guess what?
You've known where I've lived for years
and you ain't done nothing. You autistic
anxiety [ __ ] And don't don't make out
that you got a brother. You've got
autism yourself. You autistic [ __ ]
That's why you know about autism because
you got it yourself. You [ __ ]
autistic disabled [ __ ] That's how you
know about it, bro. That's how you know
about it, bro. Cuz you're an autistic
disabled [ __ ] yourself. You know all the telltale
signs. Do you know what I'm saying, bro?
Why don't you get a job, you [ __ ]
disabled [ __ ] Why don't you get a job,
you [ __ ] disabled [ __ ] You can't
even leave your house because of
anxiety. You [ __ ] anxietyridden
disabled [ __ ] on benefits. Don't [ __ ]
come on here trying to talk about me
with your autistic anxiety disabled self
behind your little account, bro. Man up.
Man up and stop hiding behind a fake
account, you [ __ ] northern disabled
[ __ ] Yeah. Don't [ __ ] stop [ __ ]
hiding behind a fake account with your
[ __ ] autism and your [ __ ] anxiety.
Too scared to leave your [ __ ] gaff
and so you have to talk [ __ ] behind
people's back, bro. [ __ ] off, man. You're an
idiot. You know all about autism, mate.
You've got the condition yourself.
You're living it. It's a daily struggle,
mate. It's a [ __ ] daily struggle with
your autism. That's how you know all
about it. It's a daily struggle in your life.
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] off. I'm going go
suck your mom. Go suck your mother.
Yeah. You still not doing that video,
are you? You're a [ __ ] idiot,
bro. And you want to talk about me, bro?
You're You're in your [ __ ] me, bro.
You're in your late 30s to earliest, and
you've never been seen with a woman.
Isn't it funny how I'm the only one on
here that's been seen with money, women,
friends? It's not that I'm trying to
shut off and say, "Oh, I'm better than
everyone. Oh, I'm better than everyone.
I'm better than everyone." Not that I'm
trying to do that at all at all. But why
am I the only one that's been seen with
women and money on this
community? That's a bit odd, isn't it?
Cuz I mean this community and don't say
because you don't put your life on it.
You're on YouTube every [ __ ] day, son.
So you're on YouTube every [ __ ]
day taking the piss out of conditions
that you suffer with. I can go to the
shopping center right now. I can go to
central London right
now. Huh? You can't. You [ __ ]
can't. Taking a piss out of [ __ ]
conditions that you suffer
with. It's [ __ ] madness.
Mate, we've all seen you people fat,
ugly. That's why you That's why Let's
Bro, it's why, like I keep saying, it's
why you people on here every day, cuz
you ain't got a lie. YouTube is your
life. You don't even leave your [ __ ] house. It's
embarrassing. Really embarrassing,
mate. Oh, yeah. I've never paid mate.
You've never had sex. You've never paid
a woman. You've never had sex. You're a little
sado. You're a little You do it every
week. You don't do nothing. You little
keyboard warrior. Shut up. You don't do
anything. You little sad bastard. You
just sit on your little stupid account
talking [ __ ] behind people's back. And
then when people ask you to say to their
face, you have a history fit. You don't
do nothing every week, you little sad
bastard. Come and join the link right
now and show us what you look like. I
bet you're just some fat, ugly bastard.
Fat, ugly, just like the bomb. Fat,
ugly, anxietyridden. shaken just like
the bomb. Isn't it funny how all you
people Yeah. when you get exposed, you
all look the same. All fat, all ugly,
all got anxiety. Isn't it the same
pattern with these people and their
looks and their age? The same fat, ugly
people. Isn't it madness? It's cuz they
get bullied every day in life, so they
have to come on here. That's what it is.
They're the people that come on here
every day and they get bullied. That's
that's why they're coming here telling
that telling people that they have what
they have themselves cuz they're bully
victims. Absolute bully victims. They
don't fit into society,
mate. Look at you, bro. Yeah, you're
telling me that you live in Hull, which
you probably don't even live in hole.
That's [ __ ] mate. A povertyridden
area where nothing goes down. Your life
is at the pits. I'm in my 20s. I live in
London. I've got more money than you.
I've had more [ __ ] than you. I got
more friends than you. I don't live in
no povertyridden area where every other
house is [ __ ] boarded up. You absolute [ __ ]
idiot. It's embarrassing,
man. Really is
embarrassing. You need to get a grip.
Anyways, I got a date on Thursday. So, yay. [Applause]
Yay. Mate, you don't know where I live.
You don't know what I pay. Yeah. And
mate, even if that was the case, so I'm
living in London, rent free. I'm still
beating y'all. Is it? I'm still beating y'all. So yeah.
Yeah. I was thinking of going to the
mall today and doing some approaches,
but can't be
asked. Nah, can't be asked, mate. Let's
see. You don't know where I live,
mate. You don't know what I pay, what I
don't pay. You know, you you people are
[ __ ] pathetic, man. For real. Yeah.
What? Establishing a
You know what I'm saying, bro? Yeah. So,
what if I lived in a in in a cat's house
with my rent paid for? What's that got
to do with you? It's still a better life
than you. You see, people you people
ain't got no life. That's why you bounce
off other people's lives, cuz you ain't
got a life. Ask yourself this question,
right? What would you do if
YouTube? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Guess what, though? I've
shown my face and I've met people,
Ricky, you can only talk behind. You can
only say stuff behind a fake account. It
doesn't matter, mate, who I've said
sorry to. I've defeated people in this
community. You only talk [ __ ] behind a fake
account. So yeah, shut the [ __ ] up. You
are a [ __ ] and you know where I live
and your mom's a [ __ ] And I've asked
you to show me where you live and you
still can't do it. You
know, do you know what I'm saying?
You're asking me like, "Bro, you don't
even leave your house. You're a sad
little keyboard warrior. How old are
you? Why don't you tell everyone how old
you are? Let me guess. Late 30s, 40s. Definitely.
Yeah. You're talking about what men do,
mate. You're talking [ __ ] behind a fake
account, mate. You're talking [ __ ]
behind a fake account. Do a video
showing where you live and I will come
on Saturday. That's a good chance. Yeah.
Come in the hangouts. Show us where you
live. And you have my word, I will come
on Saturday and show everybody how of
much of a man you are. Oh, are you going
to run away again? One
second. He's some [ __ ] idiot that
talks [ __ ] behind people's back on different
channels. Yeah, he's a [ __ ] bipolar
little [ __ ] mong. Anyways, one
sec. Yeah, he's a bipolar mong, bro. One sec. Hold
up. Uh, where are we?
Anyways, go spend your rest life on
YouTube and single. You're talking about
yourself again, buddy. Oh, what? You running
away? Oh, you're running away, [ __ ]
boy. Why are you running away, [ __ ]
boy? You've got so much to say, right,
on other people's channel. One second.
And I'm just getting a link for you,
bro. Why Why are you running
away? Why are you running away, you little [ __ ]
boy? You know you are single. You ain't
got no sex. You sad skinned little
virgin. Bro, listen. Listen, listen.
Join the hangouts and show us where you
live and I will come Saturday. Come on,
you little wimp. Come on, you little
[ __ ] You said that you live in Hull.
Okay, come and join the hangouts and
show us it on the way to the gym. You're
not going to be a wimp, are you? Anxiety
boy. Mr. Anxiety, you're not running
away, are you? You [ __ ] stupid Northern
[ __ ] You [ __ ] Northern [ __ ] I'm
saying these things to you. Come on. Are
you going to join or not? You little
wimp. Wimp boy who's got anxiety. [ __ ]
boy with autism. Are you going to join
or not? Are you going to continue being
a little [ __ ] who sucks his mom? Come
on. You You said that I've got anxiety.
I want to come on
Saturday. Come on. Why are you running
away? You've got all this [ __ ] to say
behind your little autistic anxiety
account. You probably can't even join
the [ __ ] gym without taking your
medication. Your autistic medication.
Autism boy. Mr. Autism with anxiety. Are
you coming or not? You just said that
people have got anxiety. Okay. I've got
the biggest anxiety ever. I can't even
leave my house. But I'll come to hole
and tell you to [ __ ] your mom and she
gets fingered for a packet of biscuits.
The [ __ ] northern [ __ ] Come on. Come
on. Anxiety boy. Why are you running?
You got so much [ __ ] to say on
Travodal's channel. You little virgin
[ __ ] And I know that you like to sip
women all day long. You've got a lot to
say behind an account. Come and say it
to my face. Come and say it to my face,
you little snaky [ __ ] And I'll show you
how we deal with snakes down here. You
snaky little [ __ ] You [ __ ] autistic
[ __ ] virgin riddled with anxiety.
Come on. What are you waiting for?
What are you [ __ ] waiting for?
Join. Show us where you are. Come on.
Prove your living hole. Show us some
[ __ ] street that you don't live in.
Look, I'll look it up. I'm coming
Saturday. I've never been before. I know
all about it, though. You're another
[ __ ] bomb, mate. You're a
[ __ ] You're a [ __ ] [ __ ] mate. You
got nothing to say to no one's face. You
got nothing nothing to say to anyone's
face. You're embarrassing, mate. Don't
ever [ __ ] try to call yourself a man.
You little weasel. You little [ __ ]
weasel. When you never had a woman in
your life, mate. Yeah. That's why you
talk about women. Because at the end of
the day, bro, you ain't got no life
experience. Well, we don't even really
talk about women anymore. You ain't got
no like if you got something to say, I
will I'm I'm prepared to come to you.
You know, I've started a gym now. You
probably been going longer than me.
[ __ ] idiot, mate. You couldn't even
pay a woman for sex. You're that
Butters. Yeah, you never had
sex. You've never been in a relationship
and you're older than me. You've never
even had sex. You've never even had sex,
you little [ __ ] And you're talking
about somebody half your age. Look at
you in your 40s. Can't show where he is.
has to hide behind a fake account. Let's
look at you. You know, you talk about
other people. Yeah. Let's talk about
you. You know, [ __ ]
idiot. He's a weasel, mate. A [ __ ] weasel.
They all talk mate. They are all
talk. They are all [ __ ] talking
now. Football's playing again. Uh when's it?
August. Is it August? They start
again. I think so.
Zippy. I think it's August, isn't it?
Yep. Anyone can say they live anywhere.
I just put the link up. You haven't
joined. You're [ __ ] idiot. It's just
another bomb. Another bomb. Another one
that's [ __ ] double your age. Another
one that's fat. Another one that's ugly.
Another one that ain't got no life.
Which is why they can't take one day off
YouTube. You know, you talk [ __ ] behind
my back, right? So, I'm saying come and
say it to my face. I don't like people
that talk [ __ ] behind people's back. If
you say it on this channel, you don't
get blocked. You understand?
If anyone if someone comes on here and
talks [ __ ] then they talk [ __ ] But if
I find them doing it on another channel,
that's what pisses me off. You
know, you lick my ass. Yeah. You're
licking my ass on here. And then I find
you talking [ __ ] about me on another
one. And then you're saying that you
live in a hole. So prove you live in a
hole and then you've gone and apparently
off to the
gym. Yeah, bro. It's not even
believable, man. Get a [ __ ] grip. Hello.
Yeah. Literally, bro, look at me,
bro. I'm better looking than [ __ ]
99% of these people, bro. And I ain't
even had a haircut. Look,
99% and I've got a date on Thursday.
Yeah, they are all bored, all obese, all
ain't got no life experience. You know,
they got no life
experience. The way they talk about
women, the way they talk about all of
these things, bro, you could just tell
they got no life experience.
It Yep. And not not to mention I got
more money than them as well.
It's like what Ronald Pump said, better
looking, more money, better life, and
they and it kills them. I think that's
the truth. That
is even though I'm looking a bit
homeless now. You talk about my nose.
You know, all I got to worry about is my
nose, bro. With you, you've got your
whole [ __ ] your whole face. You're
bald. You got [ __ ] you got double
[ __ ] chins. You know what I'm saying,
bro? Yeah. It's everything with these
people, mate. It's not just a [ __ ]
It's not just one thing like a [ __ ]
nose. Look, they can talk about my nose
all day long, bro. Do Do they make me
insecure? Not one little
bit. You know what I'm saying? Look
right here, right now. This is me. Yeah. You
understand? I'd rather [ __ ] I ain't
even a haircut, bro. I'm looking a bit
homeless. I'd rather look like this than
[ __ ] look like these [ __ ] rats,
bro. These rat faces, bro. I'd rather
have that than have a [ __ ] rat face.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah,
bro. Wish I could go to the gym today,
but I'm aching from yesterday cuz I
haven't been for so
long. When do I need to eat again? 6. I
think I need to eat again at 6, I
think. Is it 6? Yeah, I think it is 6. It's 6:00, lad.
6:00. I look better now cuz I eat
vegetables. So, I don't look as tired as I did
before. But I I could work on my legs
today, but I never do leg day.
Watch when I look Max in a couple next
week I look even better but I'm going to
sick. So Joe, you don't think it was
normal to be upset to be upset about that
Australian? Look at those cute little
eyes. Let me tell you something, K Joe.
This is a fun fact.
What do you think got um into Morgan's
knick-knacks? The eyeballs. It's the
cute little eyes. What do you think got
into Sig's Nick knickknocks? It's the
into the one in Nottingham's
knickknacks? The cute little eyes, you know.
Yeah. I got into their knick-knocks, baby.
knickknocks. Their knickknocks,
mate. Oh, [ __ ] h. So, two. What am I
eating? Six. I got chicken at
six. Yeah, I got
chicken. Oh, sorry. The beard. The beard
and the eyes. The beard and the eyes.
I've got a date on Saturday.
I got a date on Saturday. Yeah,
man. It's like this red story. He tries
to say that I'm bored. He wishes I was
bored, bro. He wishes I was almost 30
because it makes himself not feel as
much as a loser.
Yeah. Everything that they say is is
about themselves, bro. Is about their
own lives. They bother no one, bro. Not
one little bit. They don't. Here's the
thing. Yeah. They try to chat [ __ ] about
you all they want.
Yeah. No, I just going to get on the
spirits. I don't take [ __ ] for Nandos
now, bro. You should know the drill.
They don't deserve it. They talk about people's uh looks.
Um but they're the ones that don't show
their face. And even when they speak
[ __ ] about your looks, you still show your face.
Yeah, they they talk [ __ ] about your
looks, but you're the one that still
shows your face. These people can't show
their face. That's the difference. So,
what did you think happened with that
little Australian Joe? She done the
dirty on me, didn't she? I was sold the
dream. Oh, I had nap before Monty
though. That's the difference. I had nap before Monty.
Yeah, I had Natalie before
Monty. Would you think it was funny that Australian Joe? Nah.
Oh, I'll tell I'll ask Monty about this.
Hey, Monty. Yo, go for it.
Can you hear me? Yeah. Yeah, I can hear
you. I can hear you a little bit. Yeah.
Did there's this guy? Yeah. I said to
him, I've caught him talking [ __ ] about
me. I said, if you've got anything to
say, say it to my face. He says I've got
autism and anxiety. He's talking about himself, Monty.
Yeah. Ask them to come on camera and
show themselves if they think they're
better. Yeah, but they if they think
they're better, tell them to come on
camera. I have, but they run away. Thanks,
babes. Monty. What?
Go on. Why do they call Monty? Why do
they call me autistic? I'm not autistic.
PG. Half of this community is [ __ ]
autistic. For [ __ ] sake.
I'm not autistic, buddy. But they keep
calling me it.
Yeah. Don't ask them to come on camera
to show theirelves
because that's that's it.
It's because No, it's because most
it's because most of these in the
probably the not public the Yeah. most
from in the 40s to 50s.
That's not [ __ ] The hate Monty the
haters, aren't they? Yeah. They were
always there. They were always there.
The sexy bastards in this community and that's lush.
Go. I'm jumping off. I'm jumping off.
Yeah. No, the ugly people. Yeah. The
ugly the ugly people on here. Yeah. They
all look like B. They all look like
[ __ ] Yeah. You all look like Shagger.
They all look They all look like Pat
mustard. They all look like [ __ ]
um belly for sweat. You look like
Parise. That's what these people look like. Yeah.
Go on. Yeah, I'm going to jump off.
Yeah. See you.
Hey, Joe. Do you think I could go to the
mall today and approach or do you think
I'd be scared? I could do it if I really wanted
to, but would I?
Um, no. I could do it if I wanted to,
but I can't be
bothered. What do you think to that?
Nah, I can't be bothered,
mate. I can't be sp I could do it if I wanted
to. But did you do you think I could do
it or do you think I'd be scared? I could do
it. What do you mean don't waste my
time? What would they say, Joe?
say? You don't even know what they would
say though, do you?
Is it something like I've got a
boyfriend? They've all got boyfriends. Yeah.
No, they say they have uh they say they have boyfriends.
Joe, why do you play my silly
games? So, is that normal? Was it normal
though, Joe, to feel sad about that,
Australian? It made me sad for a couple of
days. I felt like
crying cuz I can't believe people could
just sell you a dream and then do a
runner. They'll be in Spain tomorrow.
They said they're going to Spain and
they're going back to Australia in July.
I just hate that, you know, being sold a
dream. It's not cool. It's not clever.
It's actually really
sad, you know, to be sold a dream. I
hate being sold a
dream. Why would people sell me a dream?
Oh, was that normal to be sad about,
Joe? Be honest. Is that Was that normal
to be sad about? I think it
was. Why is that? Why have I got
emotional and abandoned attachment
issues? I thought we were going to be
friends to the end.
But it's not with everyone that I've met.
Joe, it's not with everyone that I
met. It was this little Thai Australian.
I thought he was going to be friends to
the end, you know.
Nope. But I had a really good
childhood. Really, really good
childhood. So what? You don't think it's
normal to be sad about that Australian?
But my friend gave me some good advice. He
said, he said to me,
uh, let out of your mind feel like you
don't care of anything or anyone. And I
thought that that's good
advice. That's the advice I
needed. Yeah, I think that's good advice
to be fair.
Yeah. So, you're telling me you would
have been sad about that
Australian? Would you be sad or
no? Would have you been
sad? It's so weird though. Like, Joe,
it's so weird. I literally wrote, "Yeah,
hi. It was nice meeting you last night
and chatting with you. How's your day
going?" And then she put another heart
and then she said, "Hey, it's quite good
hung over dough. How about you?" Then I
wrote, "Stay, but I just came back from
the cinema." And obviously she's going back to
Australia. Oh, going back going out the
country on Wednesday. So I was like, "I
was thinking we could meet up either
tomorrow, Sunday before you leave." And
then I got blocked never to be spoken to again.
I went to Antman. I said, "You told me
these Australians was different." And he
said, "Nope. You know this. You know
they're westernized. You know they're
all the same American English." I said,
"I didn't know that." I said, "I've been
sold a dream
here." He says, "You know, you know what they're like. know.
Yeah. Being sold a [ __ ] dream.
Oh, why do these
people don't come on WhatsApp anymore?
Just hopefully this person actually
meets on Thursday,
man. Well, it's a good thing and a bad
thing because I have to start I'll have
to drink on Saturday on Thursday and if not
then Oh god, Jim.
Yeah. Yeah. I was just texting these
numbers I had. Oh, they want to go out
Thursday. They want to have Thursday.
And one came forward.
So, one came forward.
It's [ __ ] exhausting, eh? Oh, it's quite
exhausting. Need to get a haircut, man. Wait, who's
that? Who the [ __ ] is
Tam? No, that can't be that
uh Scottish guy. No
way. I deleted his number.
There's no way we found our daddy.
What? We might have found our daddy here.
Joe, that can't be. That can't
be that one from Glasgow. No
way. I'm No. Let's go. No. No
way. Nah. No way. You remember that?
Um, you remember that
tab from Glasgow that I was trying to
find from last year? Well, his number
pops up on here. That can't be the real
him. Let me call this number and see who it
is. Oh [ __ ] he's been calling me. One
second. Let me try.
Okay. Do it all. Well, I would 301
947 ID is not available via 141.
07301. But I don't have this Tam's number
saved. Trying to think if I've met
anyone else called
Tam. No, it's got to be him, is it? [Music] Hello.
No. Who the [ __ ] is
that? No, that's definitely not him.
That's definitely not a Scottish
accent. Who the [ __ ] is that, bro? I
must have said someone's number is the
same name as him.
No, that's definitely not him.
Right. No, it's definitely
not. Who the [ __ ] is
that? I don't know who that is,
man. Who do you think it
is? I can't be bothered talking, bro. That's long.
You know, one of them may just [ __ ]
long anyways. [ __ ]
them. Should we do some calls? We can
actually do some calls.
We could do some calls, you know, some prank
calls. Should we do some prank
calls? Could do some phone
calls. Let's call USA. Izzy USA changed her
number. Let me call this
Canadian. Should I call this
Canadian? Oh, I
can't I numbers on here. What am I doing?
This number has called control. To get
through, please press four.
Sorry, I can't come to the phone right now.
How do I leave a message?
Oi, answer your
phone or I'll come to Canada and beat you [Laughter]
up. All right.
Um, I'm trying to think of who we can
call. Aussie. Who the [ __ ] is Aussie?
So this wrote, "Is this Tam from
Glasgow?" I don't think it is, but I
don't know who else I'd have as Tam. I
don't know. No
Tam, so I'll just text up.
So, prank calls would be fun.
Yeah, I like this new phone. It's pretty cool, isn't
it? That's got to be
him. I think it is him,
mate. Oh, it is him. Oh [ __ ]
We found our
daddy. No way. What? There's no way I found my
dada. Oh no,
Tammy. Tammy, I found you, Tammy. And I
wasn't even looking for you. You've been
found. Oh, Tammy.
Wait, let me let me let me let me do
this WhatsApp. Let me do this WhatsApp.
Let me let
me No, it can't
be. But I don't really want to have this
number on on the same number as what I
call. They don't know my number because
of WhatsApp. No, there's no way that's
Tammy. Oh no, Tammy.
No, it can't be Tammy,
mate. One second. I need to find my
phone. I'm going to have WhatsApp on
this phone. I'm just number
two. Now, we're going to see all the
numbers that have blocked me. Oh, don't
that this is the most depressing thing I
think is seeing all the numbers that
block you cuz you got a new number. Oh, mate.
Okay, this is the depressing
thing. This is really the depressing
thing. So depressing. I don't want to
see how many people block me. Oh, mate. [ __ ]
me. So many people. You can see the
amount of people that's blocked
you. I'm deleting this
after because it's just so
depressing. So many of them have
made too many. I'm deleting it after so
many have blocked me, bro.
So many mate. I'm deleting it after
though. I'm deleting the number
after. I don't know why they give their
numbers and they block you. It's [ __ ]
up. So many. Obviously, they don't have my
number. Obviously, that Australian
blocked me as well.
This is when I used to
like do this whole Morgan [ __ ] but
obviously she changed her
number. I don't like seeing it, bro.
There's so many of them. Oh,
mate. So many of them
have not a lot a lot, but enough.
Let me message USA. Is
he just switch sims or something?
Nah, that number's gone,
mate. I hate this. I really hate
this. But to be fair, they're not too
It's not too too bad. It's enough. It is
enough. That Australian definitely
blocked me. Oh, do you want to see what
that Australian looked like as well? Do
you want to see what she looked like?
I need to tell that 19year-old as well.
I said, "I'm not getting with you ever
again. You blocked me." Yeah, that's it.
That's the end. I'm not I'm not dealing
with you again. You blocked me. [ __ ] you
it. Oh, it is
her. O, you little [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
Didn't you get my message on [ __ ]
Facebook, you little [ __ ] Yeah, I
told you a couple of weeks ago. Let me
come up. Yeah, to where you're at at
[ __ ] Thursday, Saturday, Thursday or
Friday. You're not about nothing, mate.
You are your dad. And you know you and
your dad will never be about nothing,
mate. Yeah. You're not about that
[ __ ] life ever. Yeah. All you can do
is make up stories about people, but in
real life, you know you're not about
nothing. And you're banned from London
as well. Yeah. Never ever ever ever
ever Yeah. do I want to [ __ ] know
that you're here again. Let me tell you
that. You're not about nothing, mate.
You and your [ __ ] stupid boyfriend
with these stupid tattoos. I even said,
"Yeah, I'll do it in front of your
boyfriend and your [ __ ] dad." And
then you're talking about how you're
going to call the police on people.
You're a [ __ ] [ __ ] That's what you
are, Morgan. You're a [ __ ]
mate. Oh, she must got the number back.
He must have the number back cuz it's
two ticks. I had a feeling that would
happened to be honest. I think man got blocked straight
away. Bro, listen. I don't think it was
a good idea me getting this new phone,
you know. I actually don't think this is a good [Laughter]
idea. Oh, I don't think this is a [Music]
This weren't a good
idea. Oh, this weren't a good idea, man.
How have I got three more than I do
here? Oh, you got owned, mate. You got
Oh, yeah. She's definitely back on that
number. [ __ ] [ __ ] Cuz it's It went
two ticks. And do you know what? I had a
feeling it was going to do that.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. To be fair, not many not that many
people got me to be honest. [Music]
Yeah. Oh, that's that New Zealand
though, is it? Yeah, I remember that
one. That's that New
Zealander. Yeah, look what I wrote, man.
Oh, you little [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
Didn't you get my message on [ __ ]
Facebook, you little [ __ ] Yeah, I
told you a couple of weeks ago. Let me
come up. Yeah, where you're at at
[ __ ] Thursday, Saturday. Thursday or
Friday. You're not about nothing, mate.
But yeah, do you know what? I had a
feeling that number would have went back
on to be honest. I did have a feeling. I
knew that was the
thing. Yeah, I knew it, mate. [ __ ]
me. I knew it.
Yeah, that is [ __ ] up, bro. [Applause] Oh,
no. I just thought I'd put O in it.
[ __ ] No one cares about you. We've got
a new Izzy. Anyways,
uh where are
we? A lot of them is like block
then just the same [ __ ]
Yeah, I didn't I didn't realize that she
Yeah, I knew she was back on that
number. Do you know she's done the
little [ __ ] She took her [ __ ] SIM
out and then she put it back
on. Oh, mate. But she couldn't have
blocked me that fast. How she There's no
way she blocked me that
fast. What? In two minutes. No way. What the
[ __ ] That is so weird.
Oh, that's that Yankee
[ __ ] So, she's must she must still be
under that same number. Oh.
That is odd, bro. I need to start deleting these
numbers. Yeah, I'm going to end up
messaging that [ __ ] um Australian
Lizzy. I need to get off this [ __ ] bro.
I need to I just need to delete WhatsApp
off this phone because I'm just going to
end up contacting her, mate. Trust
me. This is why I don't like this these phones, bro.
I get too deep in
it. But I think that definitely is the
TAM, but his picture doesn't come up.
But yeah, I think that is the one
from So, we've found out she has not
actually changed her
number and she's not
uh Yeah, she's still under that same
number now. She must have put the SIM back
in. This may really
is devious. E
She is [ __ ] devious, bro. Oh,
mate. Yeah, that's her, mate. That's definitely her.
really getting involved with this [ __ ]
again. There's not even my picture, so
she doesn't even know my
picture. Oh man, I'm making a cup of
[ __ ] bro. We've discovered some things
today on this
phone. See, that's how they were
discovered. You see on that phone,
that's how it was dis that's how they were
discovered. You understand? That's how
they were actually discovered.
Um, I'm a born legend. That's what I am.
What? Yeah, a few block me. Not not all of
them. I'm deleting this WhatsApp later.
I don't want it on on this phone. But
again, I'm going to have to start doing
on this phone because it's the only one
I can call out on and
stuff. Um, it's just about dating
and gambling and [ __ ] to be
fair. Just bollocks, mate. Load of old bollocks.
We just go I just go we just go live
talking about gambling and women and [Music]
[ __ ] Nah, we just talk about how [ __ ]
dating is in this country.
Oh, this is some Scottish girl that I kissed.
Yeah. Oh, mate. Yeah. So, she hasn't
deleted her number. She hasn't changed
her number, Joe. She must have took the
SIM out and put it back in cuz I've
texted USA Izzy and it's two ticks and
then I sent the voice note and then it's one tick.
Yeah, she's still on she's still on that number,
mate. She's definitely still on that
number. She probably just switched for a
while until it till the coast was clear
cuz I done it before when that Jamie
Thompson kept [ __ ] You know what I'm saying,
lad? Yeah, dating's hard in these
westernized countries for
sure. Do you want to see Australian? Uh,
Izzy, I'll show you her if you want.
I'll show you if you
want. She's quite the Chinese
look. She quite She has the Chinese
Yep. No eyelashes or
nothing. No eyelashes, mate. And we
found our data.
And we found our daddy mate.
Nah. Can't believe you left
me. I'm saying that to Tam. I just said
to Tam. I can't believe you left me,
man. I can't I can't believe he left me.
Oh my god. I wish I never got this
phone, Joe. But I need it for something.
I wish I didn't get this phone because what I've
discovered is quite bad, isn't it? What I've
discovered. I I sound kind of weird.
Thank you, ma'am. You, too. Oh, no.
No. They were They're discovered. I'm deleting
WhatsApp. I'm deleting it, bro. [ __ ]
this. One second.
I don't even know. You don't know me, matey.
Right. Yeah. I need to delete
this. Unhealthy bar.
I do content on another
channel. Who the [ __ ] is this?
Yeah. Yeah. I'm deleting this, bro.
soon. Yeah, I'm deleting it at some point.
Yeah, thank you, man.
Damn. Talking about yourself. What
about like boobs and roulette wheels? I
don't like I don't like roulette.
Yeah, that [ __ ] caught another [ __ ]
She's still under that number,
mate. What do you think of that, Joe?
She's still under that [ __ ] number. Hello.
Yes, sir. It's me. Who's
this? Where you from,
man? Oh, sorry. I got the wrong person,
man. Sorry about
that. No, it's not Tammy.
Oh, so why did you say you're from
[ __ ] Glasgow? No, we didn't find
Tammy. But we know that [ __ ] is still
under that same number. Not for long, though.
Oh, I hope that's not someone I know,
mate, cuz they're going to think I'm [ __ ]
weird. If that is someone I know, hold
on. Probably is something I know to be
fair. But why did I save him as Tam?
That don't make
sense. Drug dealer
maybe. I'm just going to tell this
19year-old one thing.
Yeah. Okay. Listen. So, I had to get a
new phone, right? And uh yeah, so
obviously you've come up because I've
had to get on my WhatsApp. I'm going to
delete my account to you. Anyways,
listen. Don't bother unblocking me like
on my old number because I'm not going
to be talking to you again. So you can't
block me then unblock me then block me
then unblock me. Like I don't care. Like
so if you unblock me again I'm not
speaking to you ever again. So yeah cuz
you seem to have bipolar. You seem to
block and unblock and block and unblock.
So I'm deleting my WhatsApp on this
number now anyways. So
yeah. Grievy we found out that USA Izzy
in fact didn't delete her number. She
didn't change her number. So, she's under another
number. Sorry, she's under the same
number. Sorry. So, I put oi. It's got two
ticks. And so, I thought, "Oh, [ __ ] it.
Let me just send another voice message."
And I and I and I'll let you listen to
the voice message. Grezy,
you little [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah. Didn't
you get my message on [ __ ] Facebook,
you little [ __ ] That's That's me.
Yeah. I told you a couple of weeks ago.
Let me come up. Yeah. to where you're at
at [ __ ] Thursday, Saturday, Thursday
or Friday. You're not about nothing,
mate. You are your dad. And you know,
you and your dad will never be about
nothing, mate. Yeah. You're not about
that in [ __ ] life. I could help
myself. All you can do is make up
stories about people in real life. You
know, you're not about nothing. And
you're banned from London as well. Yeah.
Never ever ever ever
Yeah. do I want to [ __ ] know that
you're here again. Let me tell you that.
You're not about nothing, mate. You and
your [ __ ] stupid boyfriend with these
stupid tattoos. I even said, "Yeah, I'll
do it in front of your boyfriend
and you're talking about how you're
going to call the police on people."
You're a [ __ ] [ __ ] That's what you a [ __ ] mate.
Crazy. Do you want to see um Australian
Izzy? She's really
pretty. Obviously, I got a new phone and
my number my other number. So, all of
the ones that block me are unblocked.
This is uh Australian
Izzy. She's quite cute, isn't it? She has no
eyelashes. But uh yeah, it's quite It's quite sweet
looking, if I must say so
myself. I need to I need to delete this
bloody I need to I need to I need to
delete this WhatsApp I need to delete
this WhatsApp account, Grezy, before I
get myself in trouble.
before I get myself in trouble, [Laughter]
mate. You know what I'm saying? Grezy.
Yeah. Before I get myself in serious
trouble, mate. This is why I don't want
to use this phone cuz I'll just end up
drinking and saying to Aussie, "Why
didn't you love me? Why did you leave
me? Why did you sell me a dream?"
See what I'm saying? So,
uh, you do all of these nasty things,
you know, like when I've had a little
guzzle. Oh, I need to cook my dinner at
600. 6, I think. Is it 6?
Yeah. Chicken and veg. So, I like I
said, I eat at set times. [ __ ]
She's like, "My little voice, Grezy.
That's how I discovered them." You see,
this phone has unlocked like a few
things. You know what I'm
saying? That's how That's how they were
discovered. You know what I'm saying?
Music. That's how they were
discovered. Yeah. That's how they That's
how they weren't
discovered. You know what I mean? Like
when someone gets discovered.
Yeah. Bless you. Oh, greedy. Bless you.
We're going to get into lots of trouble
with that phone. There's lots of fun to
be had, in
it. Oh. She's quite a cute in Aussie, is
he? Well, like I said, I'm going to go
to the gym. I'm going to make I'm going
to have some dreadlocks. I'm going to go grow some
dreadlocks. Then I'm going to message
her and then maybe she'll accept me in
like a year or so when I'm more bumped
up. When I'm more
up, you know. Yeah.
They know exactly who I am, mate.
Not so [ __ ] big now, though, are you?
When I'm [ __ ] texting you on
WhatsApp, are you? [ __ ] pair of
[ __ ] [ __ ] excuse
me. You know what I mean? [ __ ] [Laughter]
Well, they come in and [ __ ] the kitchen up
again. They come in and [ __ ] the kitchen up
again. I can't stop laughing, bro.
Captain, a black guy told my daughter
the other day, Grey, and he said,
"You're right, Captain." I was howling
for about 10 minutes, right,
Captain? I find these things so funny. I
don't know where Mommy Fight got me
from, to be fair. I really don't know.
Um, some chicken and
vegetables. Some chicken and vegetables,
mate. I had some steak earlier. I had to
clean the [ __ ] kitchen, mate. [ __ ]
me. I'm supposed to be having a break
today. I'm still sore from my workout yesterday. So,
yeah, Peter belly.
Yeah. You all right,
Captain? I don't know why that made me
laugh. You right,
Captain? What do you think of Aussie?
Izzy, do you think she's sweet looking? Huh?
He thinks he's sweet
looking. Thinks she's a pretty good
c. That's right. You seem like a
cat. I think we'll get on just
fine. Is she Is she your type,
Boozy? She looks a bit young, but you
know, Adman says he likes them younger.
He says, "You know me, I like them a bit younger.
Um, I think she's 20 20 years of age, [Laughter]
actually. I think she's 20 years of age. You like
her? I said, if you don't love me, I'm
going to come to Australia and beat you
up. What do you think about that,
Grizzly? I'm going to kind of beat you
up. Yeah. So, USA Izzy must have been
using another SIM for a bit and then
went back to that one, didn't she? Ah,
crafty [ __ ] is it? But you know what? I
had a feeling once I once I texted
again, it was going to uh that was going
to happen. [ __ ] crafty [ __ ] didn't
she? Yeah, she's a crafty [ __ ] now.
Yeah, man. Bit of PE. Yeah. Obviously,
I'm going to go to the gym, make some
gains, work on myself a little
bit. Then maybe
uh what do you think,
stupid? And then
uh hopefully she will accept me once
I've improved myself. That's the plan.
Anyways, she's 20 though. She's a bit
young. I think something
just Yeah, which is a bit too young for
me really. But it's 22 young for me.
Greasy. I think it's [ __ ] stupid.
Sending someone a [ __ ] me and [ __ ] it
up. That's what I think.
Can What do you think is stupid? What?
like USA is and the number and
that she's stuck with me for life,
didn't she? No, I don't care about her.
I just thought I couldn't help
myself. A pet
kangaroo. Grey, you can't say that we
wouldn't be a good
couple with our little pet
kangaroo. Come on,
Greavvesy. with a little pet
kangaroo. You want a mate? Come
on. It's a pet. Bless
you. No, I'm going to go there and beat
her up if she doesn't love me. I'm going
to come next year.
Yeah. No, I'm joking, bro. She's She's
20, bro. That's too young for me. 20 is
too young for me. It's is 22 young for Griezy
anyways. Yeah. I don't I told this 19year-old [ __ ]
off. Don't come
back because if you do it I'm I'm delete like if
you was a joke, bro. It was a joke.
Jesus Christ. It's a joke,
mate. No, I'm only joking, bro.
But if I met someone in the future when
they're 20, it's too young, is it?
Yeah. Like in the future.
Yeah. I need to delete this account soon,
mate. I need to delete this WhatsApp account, bro.
Seriously, it's mad. I got so many
women's women that block me. It makes
you wonder why they give their number if
they're just going to block you. It's so
weird. They give you their number, they
reply, then they block you. If you look
at this [ __ ] bro, you can see how many
times. Yeah. So, she's too young for me
anyways. Yeah, she looks young, bro.
still weird like randomly blocking,
replying and loving a message and randomly
blocking. That is weird. That is very
weird. Where was that picture in
Australia? Looks like it. Is
it? It looks like Australia to me.
Matey, you still like my little phone,
don't you know, Greavves? I think it's
cool. Would that would that be good
enough for you, Grezy? This phone
or all you can see is USA. Is
he? That's That's good enough, isn't
it? I think it's fast enough.
No, it's fast
enough. I think it's fast enough.
Yeah. We say now we got this. We can
actually do some prank
calls. Know what I'm saying,
bro? We order at some
point. It's a lovely little
phone. Oh, you even said that. You even
think she looks good as well, don't you? Australian Izzy.
You even think Australian is he looks
good then don't you?
Yeah. Bless you
then. Oh, bless you then. Even if you
think she looks good. That's cute. [ __ ] up
later. That Muslim one's gone quiet.
Grievesy, you know what, Grey? I've had
enough. Just add enough. You know,
sometimes you just think to
yourself, just add
enough. You know, you can get like that,
can't you, Grezy? Sometimes, just add
enough. You ever think to yourself that
sometimes, Grezy? Add enough. Just add
enough. Turn it off, mate.
just I don't know, you
know, just had enough of it all. Yeah,
that Muslim one. I messaged
her. Are you at quart 6 yesterday? No reply. No
reply. Even though we was together for
four hours, we went for a little
Nando. Oh man, what the
heck? It's a madness, isn't it, lad?
No. What do you think of Oussie? Izzy.
Do you think she looks good?
Go. Would you give her what? Would you
give her a
ride? Would you give her a ride
downtown? Why have I got three more
contacts on that phone than the other
one? That don't make
sense. Would you give her a little ride?
Okay. Second. Let me get my
mobile. Is that cute? Let me get my
We Yeah, I messaged USA Izzy. She's
still under the same number. She was off
of it and I messaged her and it went two
ticks. Then I sent another another
message and then uh it went it went, bro. Look,
my message on [ __ ] Facebook, you
little [ __ ] Yeah, I told you a
couple of weeks ago. Let me come up.
Yeah, I sent her a voice
note. I sent her a little voice note.
This is why I don't like getting new
phones and stuff. I just start [ __ ] with
people. There she is. She looks all right, don't
she? Would you give her a go?
Joe, you want to give her a go?
Don't tell me you wouldn't give that a go. That's the
one. Yeah, she's 20 years of
age. Do you like when I say that grieves
you of age? 20 years of
age. Yeah. Well, you want to give it a
go? Yeah, but you know me, Joe. I like
them younger. my ad man. I like them a bit
younger. That's my preference, is
it? That's my preference, is it? I just
like them a bit younger.
Me? Yeah, I like him a bit younger. [Laughter]
But you have to No, no, you got you got
a big ad man up though. Like he's been
Asia four times in a year and LJ's never been to
Asia. And LJ's never been to Asia ever.
Imagine that. He's never been to Asia.
Never. Because he's not well traveled, you know.
Would you [ __ ] that Australian is
he? Would you [ __ ] that Australian? Izzy, um,
Reezy, I don't even think I would, bro. To be
honest, I just liked having someone to
speak to, but it was special then, but
it's over now. Why is this USA back on this number
then? Why is she back on this number?
She blocked me in two minutes. There's
no way she knew it was me in 2
minutes. Yeah, that is definitely her,
mate. She's a coward, mate. She can't
even speak to me, man. She's a proper
coward. Do you think me going with a 20y
old is wrong? How about me going with a
20-y old? Do you think that's wrong?
Yeah, that is. He's 20.
So, no, I can't date a 20-y old that
looks that young,
bro. I can show you a lot of numbers.
I've got what they look like.
Yeah, there's this French one I got, but
she didn't reply, which is strange.
Yeah, she she was all right, but she
didn't reply. She seemed nice face to
face, but she never
replied. I got so many women's numbers,
mate. Just gallivanting around trying to
find a candidate for baby Peter Grezy, you know. them old
days. You'll like it down here, son.
You'll never have to grow
up. Oh, I'm going to play [Music]
it. I should have been on my phone.
Yeah, but that was just for sex. One second. [Music] Daddy,
that's my home now, son.
Want a balloon, man?
Come here, Scott. I love
this. I love that old cloud. [Laughter]
that. Go down here with me.
He's a lovely little clown. He's a
clown. Yeah, I just Well, I never used
to have sex. She used to just give me a
[ __ ] She was 18 at one point. I
don't give a [ __ ]
mate. Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah, but I think Australian is too young for
me. Oh, you know, you know, this is a
very funny picture. This is I can't stop
laughing like this. Like, look, these
are all the GTA and then you got six
over there. It just looks so out of
place. What is it doing there? It took
you [ __ ] 13 [ __ ] years and it
thinks it can just be added now. Greavesy,
look. And now it thinks it could just be
[ __ ] added. Look, that's a madness.
Then it thinks all of a sudden it could
just be added again. [ __ ] idiot,
man. Yeah. Yeah. But you know, I like
him a bit young, Joe. Yeah,
man. Yeah, you know, like I'm a bit young,
mate. At least the phone's good. I might
I'm tempted to use this phone to go out now, but nah.
What's her way? I wait for USA to
reply. I don't know why she doesn't
doesn't reply. Joe, why did she say he
don't want to
reply? You was big enough when you was
making people cry. Isn't that right,
Greasy? You was big enough when you was
[ __ ] with people's heads and then
when somebody stands up to you, you run away.
that doesn't even make any sense. Madness,
bro. I'm going to call this number,
bro. Rest in peace,
Pville. Cool ended. How could it be
coolended? I don't make sense. There you
go. What's going on?
Your call has been forwarded to an
automated voice messaging
system. 7 7 4 9 2 2 3 8 8 6 is not
available. The mailbox is full and
cannot accept any messages at this time. Goodbye.
What? I'm not happy again.
ated voice messaging
system. 7 7 4 9 2 I'm going to send a
little voice message.
8 6 is not
available. The mailbot is full and
cannot accept any messages at this time. Goodbye. [ __ ]
sake. Wanted to give her a little call.
See if we got anyone
else. So is that Muslim ignoring me
then? Grezy, I messaged her at quart 6
yesterday and no reply.
Yeah, that's definitely ignoring, isn't it?
Obviously. Yeah, it's definitely
ignoring. There's no way someone's busy until that
time. No way.
What do you think,
Greasy? Want to play some
sippy. My brand new track, Two Times
Together with Steve Aoki, is available
now on Tik Tok. And I can't wait to see
all the amazing creations you guys are
gonna come up with.
Make you idle
bastard. Get your [ __ ] [ __ ] What
time? What time is it? Oh yeah. And you lit [ __ ]
A nice way to talk, isn't it? [Music]
You [ __ ] I hope you don't have to [ __ ]
that [ __ ] bed again.
All right, I'll show you one. I've got a
balance with you. I'll show you a funny one, Grezy.
You found my right dungeon, you [ __ ] [Music] [Laughter]
Oh, I love
words now. You're going to celebrate my
[ __ ] day. You got that was in cover, boy. I'll
[ __ ] go dark and [ __ ] it again. Yeah,
listen here. Devil,
mate, I tell you what. I love
Al. Oh, bro.
I'm good. You excited about tonight?
Yeah, I'm very excited, mate. For you? I
bet now a lot of things that you have a
rape dungeon. A rape what? A rape? Oh,
yeah. Yeah. Yeah. The bloody rape
dungeon, mate. Yeah. [ __ ] off about
it. They're really liking the idea of
the rape dungeon, you know. Um the kids
in the dungeon don't seem to like it as
much, but you know, who does like to be
raped and tortured anyway? But who
cares? It's all just a bit of fun. All
right, listen. Yeah, I'm typing it, but
Um, do you know what this reminds me of?
Do you remember Mick Jonathan Robinson
when he went to Australia to um escape
to try to escape his horrific crimes
against children? Do you remember Virgin Boy's
dad, Mick Jonathan Robinson? That's his
real name. If you look it up, you'll
actually uh get
it. I'm going to look on it now. One sec.
That reminds you of Mick Jonathan Robinson.
Whoa, I'm not signing in.
Welcome to Lobby Land's busy international
airport. Excitement today as we await
the arrival of the most basic
What the [ __ ] [Laughter]
No, I like I like that man. Hey, do you
know this video of Ant-Man makes me laugh.
Yeah, I love it. One sec.
sec. One second. One sec.
You never guess what happened tonight.
Yeah, I was on the piss on
that. I went into Admirals and won money
back. So, I've got I've got 100 quid.
So, I've only spent 20 quid all day and
I've got my bike
out. Listen to this [ __ ] I went into
William Mills and I was 50 quid in the
machine. 50 quid. I lost 50 quid in the
machine. I thought, "Fuck this." So, I
went up to the guy behind the counter.
He was on his own. I went I looked I
went to I went, "Are you?" I said, "I'm
not supposed to be in it." I said,
"You're letting me in. I've just spent
[ __ ] 50 quid on the machine.
And he was like, he was like, "Oh,
[ __ ] hell." He went, "I didn't know."
He And I said, "Yeah, well, you do
[ __ ] said, um, I said, I had a
dream." Yeah. I said, "Fuck, I might I
had a drink." I I went
to Well, give me 50 quid back and I
won't show it to anyone cuz you
shouldn't have been let me in anyway.
You know what he did? He gave me the 50
quid back. I couldn't [ __ ] believe
it. You give me the money back. The guy
in William Owens gave me my 50 quid back
what I put on the machine.
See, he was really skint, you know, like
when he was my age. Yeah, he was my age.
He was around about my age then. He was
way worse off than me. Like he was
eating like cold beans and [ __ ] You
know what I mean? Like I got it a lot
easier than what he had it. saying,
"We had like nothing." Like the most he
had was like £100. Like he at 26 27 was
me at like 20
21. He was eating cold beans. Like he
literally had nothing. I'm a lot luckier
than him now. So there's not really no
excuse for me to wait until his age to
go to Thailand. You know he's 31, 32, you
know. I'm having chicken breast,
bro. Yo, [ __ ] off. You're trying You're
making me [ __ ] fancy a takeaway now, you
[ __ ] You're making me fancy a [ __ ]
takeaway, you bastard. I'm not going to
have a takeaway until I finish all that
food in the
fridge. I could have salmon or
chicken and I think that's it. I have
nothing left after that.
Go gym tomorrow.
Oh, have a piece with
jalapenos. Oh, have a have a piece with
jalapenos, lad. Have you had um Dave's
chicken, Grezy? They might not have it
where you are, but it's quite nice. It's called Dave's
Chicken. Yeah. [ __ ] hot though, so
make sure you get medium.
There was only actually one to be
honest. Maybe there was only
one. Hopefully I can meet this woman on
Thursday and have a baby in it,
Greavvesy. I really want a baby pet kangaroo
though. Yeah. Get Get pizza with beef,
jalapenos, and tandoori chicken. Oh,
mate. You're making me fancy one
now. You're making me [ __ ] fancy one.
I mean, I could technically have one and
still and still like be be fit, still be
like in shape and that,
but yeah, I could eat I could order a pizza
myself and I'll still be all right.
But probably. Yeah.
How much are you going to pay for it though,
Greasy? Don't know where I'd get it from
though. I don't really like Domino's or
pizza and that. I think they're [ __ ] [Music]
Um, what do you think we
see going on with the
internet or I
think I fancy a [ __ ] pizza, man. [ __ ] you, you
[ __ ] But my friend might cook for me.
So obviously my friend cooks for me,
then I won't get a pizza.
Obviously, you're making me fancy a
pizza now, bro. What the [ __ ]
bro? Where you going to get it
from? Where you going to get it from?
Yeah, the big chains are [ __ ] though,
aren't they? The big chains are [ __ ]
Let me see what Papa John's is
saying. Let me see if there's any. Papa
John's is all right. Is Papa John's is the best
one. [ __ ] you, G. You're going to get me fat, mate.
You're actually going to get me fat. You can't
£10 off £30. So if you spend £30, it will be
20. Uh only two sides, two medium pizzas,
£30. Any XXL pizza, a classic side and a premium side.
So if you spend £30, you get for 20. So
that's not too bad. Then obviously you
can get a nice pizza. But I don't want
to get really fat, Greasy. I think if I
eat a pizza, I'm going to get really fat
now. What if I get really
fat? What if I eat and I get really fat?
Nah. Oh, so you work out? Yeah, you
actually do work
out. I might get a pizza and I can just
have the chicken for breakfast. I could
have the pizza now and then have the
chicken. Then I could have the chicken and
uh and salmon tomorrow.
Yeah. Oh, you're going to get me fat. You
are. I'm going to create my own pizza.
Yeah. I'll just have the salmon and
chicken tomorrow. I need to go jump
tomorrow. So yeah, go tomorrow.
So [ __ ] you with
this on a nice stuffed crust
pizza. Okay with you, boss.
£24. How is it £24 already without even adding
toppings? That is so
expensive. £24 with stuffed crust and I
haven't even added [ __ ] toppings on it
yet. Oh my [ __ ] god, man. One second.
Topping. Hold on. Let me add it.
£31. So, it's going to be
£21. That's not that much, is it? I've
got steak, Philly beef, onion, onion,
mushroom, and jalapenos. What do you
think to that, Grezy? Yeah, that's
that's good. No, £31, but obviously
it'll be £21 cuz you get £10
off. So, it's not too bad, is it? Today,
Tuesday, it's not that bad, is it? No.
Okay, now it's saying £24 cuz it's two
pound delivery fee. What the [ __ ]
Unless I got a medium one, but that's
eight slices. Eight slices. One, two. I
can do eight I can have eight slices,
can't I? Wait, how many slices is the
one that you're getting? Mine's eight.
Yeah, eight slices. One second. That's
expensive, bro. One sec. Let me go back
on this. Let me go back on this. One
second. This can't be
right. I'd have to get a medium one.
That's too expensive,
bro. What do you think? I think 10
slices. I think it is. It's £24. What do you think?
£24. [ __ ] it. Let me just get it. £24.
is a bit expensive,
but uh so be it. E so be it. Can't take
it with you when you can't take it with
you when you die. E.
So I'll give it a while. Yeah, why not?
Got my meal sorted for tomorrow anyways.
So Oh, I'm going to be a fat bastard
soon. I'm going to show you it when it
comes as well.
I don't want to I don't want to donate
to charity. Why on God's earth would I
want to donate to
charity? Are you having your pizza now on Grezy? Complete details. Peter Peter 07393939966
email. It's going to say that we already
have your email.
That's what it's going to
say. Pay by
bank. Debit card. I'm going to pay by
debit card. So, what do you think,
Greaves? You get it? Yeah, I would give
it a whirl, would it? [ __ ] it. I'd give
while. Yeah, I'll just wait a while.
Yeah. Yeah, I think I might just Yeah,
I'm going to give it a whirl. [ __ ] it.
Why not in it? I would. Give it a whirl.
I can get you in trouble. Mie.
4462. I didn't know you worked out.
Greasy. Is that to stop getting big and
fat? Bless you. Is that to stop getting
uh Yeah, I'm going to work out tomorrow
and eat the salmon and the
chicken. So, you're not going to get fat
in a [ __ ] day, are you?
So, I don't want to look like [ __ ]
[ __ ] nons legs his [ __ ] dad. Fat [ __ ] Fat
[ __ ] Fat [ __ ] mate. Fat [ __ ]
Yeah, same as me, bro.
Yeah. Oh, it better not ask me to
verify. Oh, I can't verify it. It's
asking me to verify and I can't do it.
No, I can't do I have to wait until I
get my money later in my other account.
It's asked me to verify and I can't
verify on this one cuz it's a different
number. So, I have to do on my other bank account.
Uh what for? No, I can do it in 15
minutes. Hold on. I get money in 15
minutes. So, I should be able to do it in 15
minutes. PM. Yes. I'll have to wait cuz
I can't verify in that
account cuz I it's I don't have the same number.
So, I have to do the [ __ ] lot
again. Greavvesy, I've got to do the
[ __ ] lot again. Have you ever had to
do that before,
Grezy? Have you ever had to do that the lot again?
Yeah, the [ __ ] lot again.
Yeah. Bless you.
You like USA? So I get my um See, I get
my I get my protein and stuff now from
chicken and steak. I used to get it from USA's
boobies, but I don't I I don't get it
from there anymore. I used to get it
from her boobies, but yeah, I don't get
it from there
anymore. But to be honest with you, it
would save a lot of
money. It would save a lot of money.
Okay. A lot of
money. Oh, should I get Nando Greavesy
H? I've not for a while, but that's too
expensive. Um, that's too
expensive. Do you know what? Yeah, I
might just get I might just buy
something and make make a curry, bro.
£24 is a lot of money, isn't
it? Yeah, it's a lot of money, bro. Is
it? It's quite a
lot. I just got to Chinese or something.
Maybe I'll just go get some hot wings or
something cuz that is still like
somewhat healthy. Maybe maybe I'll get
the pizza from the up the road shop.
Maybe I'll just walk and go and get it.
I'll just walk up the road and find a pizza
shop. How's that, Grezy? I think that's
better. Yeah, just go walk up the road and get
um get a
pizza. I think that's a better idea,
mate. Save some Wonga. What do you
think, Greasy? Boss, is that okay with you,
boss? They knew it here. One second. Let me see. [Music]
barbecue. They should have pizza in this
place. Let me walk and I'll just get the
pizza. I'll bring the pizza back. It
can't be that
expensive, mate. My where my little legs
have took me before. They've took me to
Manchester. They've took me to Brighton.
They've took me everywhere. My little legs.
Yeah. I ended up Yeah. Yeah.
Greensy. So you you wouldn't have sex
with Australian Izzy. No. You would you
wouldn't have you wouldn't have sex with
her, would you? You would you wouldn't
have sex with
her if she said, "Oh, let's have sex.
You would then turn around and think,
"No, we're not having
sex. Let me see what this cunt's
doing." Then I don't know what I'm
doing. See if they're cooking or not. If
he says yeah,
then I should just buy the pizza to be honest. [Music]
What's the place called you get from
Grimsy? Wait. Oh, I didn't even read
that. I have to celebrate getting USA is
number. Why do I have to celebrate
that? Why do I need to celebrate that?
Grezy, he's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
I didn't see what kind of person she
was. She just came onto me.
Greavvesy. She came on to me and then I
felt something in my
toodger. Then I felt something in my toddy. So
yeah. Yeah. I've had a number for ages,
bro. Do you want my number?
You remember that,
Grezy? Do you remember that? Do you want my
number? Yeah, I
do. I do, please. Thank
you. Someone's having a
barbecue. I was supposed to have what to
say about never. Oh, someone's having a
barbecue. Someone's having a barbecue.
Someone's having a barbecue. Someone's
Someone's having someone's having a
barbecue this evening.
Roomsy bar this evening.
Well, I'm going to get this pizza. I'll
do a video when I um when I come back
with a pizza. Okay, Grezy. I'll show you
a little uh do a little pizza update.