They move. [Laughter] Get mix. [Music]
I'm getting a Corona again.
I'm wait for 50.
It's getting shot block, mate. It's
getting block in here.
100%, man. 100
working for me.
Bro, dad, I can't be wrong with this
community anymore. It's the same [ __ ]
every day. Creepy, bro. I don't come
there no more. It's so creepy, bro. So
creepy. I can't be wrong with that.
I can't bother so
I'm good. I'm good.
I'm out here drinking. So creepy. [Laughter] I can't. [Music]
Mine is an Italian. Is he now? Steven
Howard. Oh [ __ ] My [ __ ] card is
I [ __ ] Nice [Applause] front. Yes. Amen.
I'm out here.
I'm [ __ ] out here, boy.
I'm out here, boy. How about
I'm going to sit here. I'm going to sit What's that? Hear
me? Can you hear me?
Look at all that heavy man. [Music]
Hello. Can you hear me? Hello. [Music]
Hey, can you hear me?
Hey, they won't touch.
I got I got Go there. I know.
You hear me? Hey, [Music] where
I don't care no more. I don't care no [Music]
Oh, you want me to go to the spirit?
You want me to go to the spirit? Thanks. That is
that is an Italian Izzy Steven Howard Andre. Yeah.
No hand over me. No hand over for me. No.
No hand over for me, buddy.
I got bait. I got bait as well. No. Up.
I was in my [ __ ] bro, on Thursday.
That picture I was in with my [ __ ] face. Yeah,
bro. I b eight [ __ ] quit treat.
If I need to kill the spirits, I [ __ ] will. But man, no.
today. Well, it's one last try. We're
giving it one last try.
They giving it a little
giving a little sh
Oh bro, I was on a date on Thursday. She
was [ __ ] sexy. [Music] My [ __ ]
up the blue. Oh.
a little bit
on that [ __ ] light on fire. I got some
I'm on YouTube.
It's so creepy. It's [ __ ] weird. It's
creepy. I don't come on the bus.
I don't come on the bus anymore. So creepy. Creepy, bro. [Music]
That's all day, mate. Sto,
yeah, bro, I can spend £3,000
a month for pit. Yeah, get up. You keep
telling yourself that, buddy.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that, boys.
Keep yourself up.
Yeah. Story of your life. You are
stinking. Stop self projected.
Don't talk about yourself.
Story of your life.
Talking about yourself.
It's not for the mental health.
He's sitting here.
What's up? I'm going to sit here.
Hey, you're the only one on pitch. Stop
talking about yourself. Is there Sit down. Open it.
Slide over. No, you can pull it. Pull
it. Over. Over here.
Pull it. Pull it. Sound [Music]
good. Chill in. Chill in. [Music]
Stop talking about yourself. Looks like
Oh, there he is. All right.
I've never been there before.
So, I'm going to leave it now. up. [Laughter] I'm actually [ __ ]
people next to me. 17%
I'm screenshotting all of this.
I'm screenshotting all of this. Don't worry about
20% claim. These
people talk about himself every day. Yeah. Uh baby,
come back. Okay. What about the [ __ ]
I told you? Cyber bro,
huh? British. Am I British? Yeah. Honestly,
it's your country, bro. It's easy for
you think it's not easy for me. It's a
westernized country. What the [ __ ] Why
is it easy? You know, you have a king.
I come from a different country. Yeah. Listen.
He's going to pass. Hey, listen.
Listen, listen. Go and speak to them in
front of her in front of me. Go.
Trust me. I saw what you see. How many of the name go to
your [ __ ] I have to get drunk
me like two bottles down
to me. I don't I don't [ __ ] ser [Music]
my name is bro. Yeah.
Yeah. If you need drink, anything I
need. I don't eat [ __ ] I got my
bait. I got
there. Go now. It's a long night. It's a
long night. It's a long It's a long [Music]
Man, she's looking at you. She wants
you, man. She keeps looking at you,
babe. Keep looking at you, bro.
She is looking at you.
She wants your dick.
Yeah. Yeah. Too much for my
I'm going to say good stuff. [Music] upstairs.
What are you drinking? What are you
drinking? What are you drinking?
Vodka. How many drinking beer? Only
beer. Beer. Beer. And no more drink.
This is only beer.
How about that? I was [ __ ] over there. This is
I don't I only drink beer cuz I can't
deal with this. It's too much and it's too expensive. [ __ ]
them two over there. [ __ ] you actually.
I don't know any [Music] sushi.
Muslims can eat sushi. But Muslims can
eat allow. Yeah. Yeah. I know. I don't
like pushing. I haven't tried but there
are some things I'm not afraid to try.
You should try the best.
You're missing out on so many things. Hey, thank you. Good news. [Music] Come back.
I don't know the [ __ ] you going about
I don't know what the [ __ ] you was going on about [Music]
talking about [ __ ] [ __ ] up here
How about get her old man.
What the [ __ ]
Talking about yourself, buddy. Go self [Music]
effect on another channel.
What you call [ __ ] [Music]
Well, why the [ __ ] that blow up?
He [ __ ] it, man.
What the [ __ ] man? Buddy
on another channel.
A million times.
They [ __ ] took the [ __ ] toilet out, [ __ ]
They took the toilet out with piss. They
cooked on a pitch. [ __ ] cooking.
They shook the [ __ ] toilet with piss. [Music]
What the [ __ ] [Laughter]
Don't worry about the lights.
[ __ ] you, man. Oh [ __ ] [Music]
Where are you from? Oh, nice. here. Huh? My friend,
maybe I'll probably ask you
on the way. Yeah. Give me a couple of
lines of coke and maybe I'll be on the a
couple of nights of co. Yeah. the girls
like in the [ __ ] knock.
But I mean if you have a cute appreciate
you. Can you get a happy ending? Hey [Music]
[ __ ] y'all. The people [Applause] 100%. [Music]
It's all [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah. At least I [ __ ] up.
Uh 28. 28.
old getting old like [ __ ] like I
know. [ __ ] me. They're only like 2000.
I need to start
You don't want
in your 40s. You never been lazy,
mate. You're in your 40s and you and
you've never been laid. Stop talking about
you got a girlfriend as well. [Music]
I've got a
when it gets when I You're talking about
yourself. You're in your 40s, 50s.
You've never You've never had You've
never had sex. That's why YouTube every
day. You ain't got a life.
Listen, Stephen Howard.
These people come on YouTube every day
cuz they ain't got a life. Their lives
are ruined. They're old men. Bitter old
men. Virgin got a lie. That's why they
sat on YouTube all day. It's the truth. Well,
it's the truth. They ain't got a life. That's
on YouTube. They ain't got a life.
40 50 yards.
Yeah, they ain't got no life, babe. They
ain't got no lives.
And now the YouTube life.
Talk about yourself. Go away.
Yeah, that's okay. [Applause]
I'm waiting. I'm waiting.
I'm going to [ __ ] send it.
I'm going to I'm already fire. 65.
Ah, I never expect
I never drink once.
No, I got it two times. Four years.
It makes you [ __ ]
just makes you [ __ ] horny.
Who are you? Ben, why are you turning
up? This guy acknowledged me when I went
to the bathroom.
You're a crazy
listen Howard. All of these people that
are saying you're this or that sat on
YouTube in their 40s, 50s, ain't got no
money, ain't got no life. Remember that. Listen, even
all of these people
that I'm talking on here hating,
they're all in their 40s, 50s, ain't going 100.
They're all in their 40s, 50. They don't know, nobody.
That's why they're on YouTube every day.
I know the one every day, bro. They are. Oh [ __ ] [Music]
I don't know who he is. This man
I'm getting some food for me as well.
I'm getting some food for me too, mate.
Oh, Mr. B, I'm getting some nice be cool.
I guess somebody [ __ ] L [Music] [Applause] [ __ ] laugh.
Don't hang over [ __ ]
Don't hang over me.
Bro, I'm beating that woman again in my throat.
My throat. I'm beating her again.
I'm [ __ ] beating her again, mate. All
right, I'll be here again. [Music]
I've been picking my moment. I've been sat here
I've been bleeding. I've been now.
She's not a lawyer, bro. But I'm meeting
her again. She's not a lawyer. Hey [Music] [Applause] Stop it.
Check your picture. Listen [ __ ] I
[ __ ] [ __ ] it.
I'm like [ __ ] I should have [ __ ] said it.
My friend was supposed to come with me
today, but he never by myself. He's a [ __ ] absolute I'm
I'm going to go central approaches.
I've got central approaches. I'm clear.