God, this [ __ ] burger is so
stupid. God, he's so ugly as well. I'm
I'm making posters, by the way.
Definitely reopen the case. What is this
[ __ ] stupid rat face? For real,
they're going to open a case, mate. All
someone's got to do is show the police
your channel of your autism every single
day. You don't have no case. You and
your fat ugly girlfriend. And this is
what I say to you all the time because I
always have to bring the person up in
it. You and your fat ugly girlfriend do not have
no [ __ ] case. What? Please get me
open, mate. All someone's got to do is
show the police your YouTube channel.
I've got all your evidence, all of your
golden you and your ugly rat face
walking around telling people to [ __ ]
meet you. You [ __ ] diagnosed autistic
[ __ ] That's all I've got to do, bro. Just
simple. Yeah. You and your ugly [ __ ]
rat face and your fat ugly girlfriend.
That's you with me. When I when I start
[ __ ] I don't stop. You know what I
mean? I'm I'm a crazy guy.
You lost it,
bro. [ __ ] hell. You're still
repeating the same
stories. [ __ ] autistic little [ __ ]
Oh my god, he is obsessed. All tents to
the maximum. [ __ ] one of you got
[ __ ] diagos with [ __ ] learning
difficulties. You [ __ ] little ber.
[ __ ] hell. I'm doing posters on this
[ __ ] Trust me, bro. I'm gonna make some
posters tomorrow, bro. I actually
already made him to be fair. I put him
on the [ __ ] photo editor. I'm going
to make this [ __ ] be scared to leave his
[ __ ] house again. Just like he was
for three weeks. Hey, Zippy. Yeah, I'll
[ __ ] with this little [ __ ] bro. There's
literally nothing this little virgin can do.
There's literally nothing this rat
virgin with his fat ugly girlfriend can
do about it. Literally
nothing. You think you really think
Mexican makes the police of it anyway?
Who who do you really think, bro, is is
actually scared of the police? Like, oh
my god, him and his [ __ ] special
needs with that rat face. Who does he
It's actually a madness. Like, [ __ ]
hell, bro. 9 minutes. 9 minutes. [ __ ]
obsessed. This is why you don't meet
people with autism. Diagnosed autism. [ __ ] hell. Diagnosed
autism. [ __ ] hell, bro. [ __ ] hell. Matter.
up some of your local restaurants, by
the way. Trying to find your [ __ ]
address. Trying to find your [ __ ]
address. By the way, does Matson ring a
bell? Does the Indian cuisine ring a
bell? That's the actual names of the
places. Yeah, I was s
find this rap place. I was trying to
find his [ __ ] address, you know,
because when you when you call the same
in um place and you give your name,
sometimes you can find people's addresses that
way. That's what Virgin trying to get
the [ __ ] cunt's address.
Oh, mate. I'd have a field time with your [ __ ]
neighbors. I'd have a
feel. An absolute feel time, de lad. Awesome. [Music]
You have no matches right now.
Oh my god, he's so obsessed. Stephen
Howard, how we doing, bro? He's [ __ ]
obsessed. That little rat face. Oh my
god, his autism is so
bad. [ __ ] replying to his own [ __ ]
videos and [ __ ] God, he is
obsessed. And you know what? The only
maddest thing about it is no one likes
this little virgin either, you know?
They they just they just pretend to like
literally nobody likes that little
ratfaced virgin. He's so ugly as well. I
don't actually realize he he knows how
ugly he actually is. He's such an ugly [ __ ]
Like, bro, I had this [ __ ] walking
around for 13 minutes doing autistic
faces because of
me. Imagine that. Someone on
YouTube just repeating the same [ __ ]
making the same autistic faces. Oh my
god, he is so [ __ ] Bro, he is so
ugly. Isn't he so ugly? Like, oh my
[ __ ] god, he looks like a rat.
God, he is so
ugly. He is such an ugly bastard. Like
honestly, man, if I if I had a face like
that, I swear now my approaching days would be
done. Same old repeating madeup stories
by the same virgin. Yeah. And he's fat
girlfriend. And it's a madness, isn't it?
Some madness, brother. [Music]
No, I know. He He's proper proper ugly.
Proper proper proper ugly. You know when
he say do you know the uh video when he
said O M. It's good because he is the M.
When he was looking at himself saying
that it's actually good because he
actually is the
M. He actually is the alltime M. And he
doesn't even realize that he is really
really ugly. Like really really an ugly
[ __ ] Look at all of the women that I've
been with and look at who he's been
with. Come on, bro. It speaks volume. It actually speaks
volume. Look, he's with a [ __ ] DeWolf
with special needs. Have I ever had to resort to
that? God. God, he is
ugly, mate. He his whole face is
[ __ ] He He talks about my nose. Has
he seen his whole
face? [ __ ] can't even go any facial
hair. [ __ ] virgin. Utter complete and utter
virgin. Madness, isn't
it? Special needs as well. Steven
Howard, he he's really really really got
special needs as well. It's actually
mad. Like this little loser thinks that
he can get the police
involved, mate. He can get the police
involved. How, bro? All I'd have to do
is show the police all of the evidence
that I've got for you and that's it.
You're not a victim, Virgin boy. Get out
of your head. Well, you are a victim on
YouTube. You're bully victim. But um I
never fingered a woman. Sorry, I have to
ban these retards. Um, but yeah, and he
tries to say that I'm balding, bro. I've
got more head than he will ever
have. Everything he says, he projects
balding, ugly. He is ugly. Oh my god, he is ugly,
bro. He [ __ ] And he's balding as
well. Like you said, he's [ __ ]
balding. I noticed that as well. [ __ ]
[ __ ] wants to talk about my [ __ ]
hairline as you see in his own [ __ ]
balding [ __ ] And his hair spinning as
well. [ __ ] balding ugly rat.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah. Yeah. [ __ ] virgin. Um
Yeah, I'm about nothing. Owning me. He
doesn't owe me though, does he? Because
he won't meet me and not say and he
won't say anything to my face. And mate,
I had him running around for 9 minutes
shouting about me. I think I'm the one
that's owning. He doesn't owe no one.
He's just a little keyboard warrior with
his little autistic face. He doesn't own
anybody, mate. I get more money than
him. I'm better looking than him. I've
had normal women. He hasn't. He's the
one who's on £1,000 a month. Not
me. [ __ ] [ __ ] Don't owe no one. You
really think somebody could owe me when
I've had them running to the police
screaming how he's not a fighter? Take
that out, [ __ ] Yeah, he's got a
disabled girlfriend that don't give him
sex. I give him that. He does. He's got
a disabled girlfriend that don't give
him no sex and he's jealous of all the
women that I've been with. So, let that
speak volume again. He's got a
girlfriend. She doesn't [ __ ] him. She's
disabled, but he's still obsessed with
all my women. Yeah, I give you that. I'm
not in denial on this channel. Yes, I
don't have a special needs disabled
girlfriend like he does. And I actually
have teeth in my mouth unlike he does.
And I don't look like a rat. And I'm not
on a,000 pound a month poverty. So,
yeah. I guess Peter Benny's the one
who's winning. Do you think anybody
Steven Howard could could come to my
area? Bro, just just check this for a
second, bro, and have me screaming how
I'm not a fighter and run into the
police. Do you think any anybody could
do that to me? No, bro. I don't think
so. Don't you remember it, bro? Do you
not remember that two years ago? Like,
you know what I'm saying? Do you
remember that like two years ago with
his little rat face? I'm not a
fighter. I'm not a fighter. I'm running
to that place. I'm running to that
place. I'm not a
fighter. But on YouTube, he's some kind
of big man with his little rat
face running around his area for 9
minutes with his [ __ ] autistic face.
With his little disabled face. Yeah, he
owns me, bro. Get used to it. Yeah, but
here's the thing. I can say I can say to
his fate. I can say to him I can say I
love it. And do you know what I love?
That I get thousands of pounds a month
and I've got more than you. Do you know
what I love? That I always have more money than
you. I've got an evil little that's what
kills these people that I got more money
than them and they know it deep down as
well. Thousands and thousands more than
them. You know, that's what I love that
you're on benefits and you're a little
keyboard warrior. Get yourself gone,
buddy. Little virgin. But yeah, bro. So,
here's the thing. Who can actually say
who to someone's face, bro? Like, that's
it. Yeah. If you owe me so much, come
and meet me. You walking around with
your little disabled rat face for 9
minutes having an autistic [ __ ]
handsome is not owning someone. Like,
have you actually seen how ugly you
really really are? Which is also part of
the reason why he's obsessed with all of
my ex sloppy seconds, cuz he's too ugly
to get anything to himself. Look at it,
bro. He's landed himself in a
relationship with the wolf. The wolf's
[ __ ] that A can't even talk and B
doesn't give him no sex. But I'm the
ugly one. I'm the ugly one. But I'm the
ugly one apparently. H Steven. Yeah.
Coming from somebody that looks like a
rat. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Yeah. We've heard it all before, Red
Star. We've heard it all before, mate.
Yeah. You already had And guess what? I
got more money than you now. And I get
thousands more than you a month. How
about that one? Yeah, that's it. Yeah,
of course he does. He's a keyboard
warrior. He doesn't own anybody with his
little disabled rat face. My [ __ ]
niece broke a car on YouTube [ __ ]
being a keyboard warrior and she's
[ __ ] six years of age. Him running
around Kent with his little disabled rat
face. Yeah. Every single time you go to
his area. I'm not a fighter. I'm not a
fighter. I'm not a fighter. But
apparently he owns me because you can
walk around with his little disabled
face telling the same stories over and
over and over again.
Huh? Yeah. If you showed me 12 grand,
I've been waiting for somebody to show
me 12 grand for a very, very, very long
time, bro. Yeah, I've been waiting for
it, bro. Yeah, go show me 12 grand.
Sorry about that, Stephen Howard. Just say little self-reflectors.
Yeah. Do you know what? I can play the
money game with these people right now,
Stephen Hour, but I won't. You know why
I won't? Because I don't entertain these
little bongos. If they show me 12 grand,
that's a different story. I'm not
showing these little mongos, nothing.
Oh, tomorrow. Okay, get your 12 grand
out tomorrow, bro. We'll play the money
game. Yeah, like I said, bro, anyone
that shows me 12 grand, bro. These You
do realize these people are like the
same three people that's been doing this
for years. Like you just said, the same
old mugs. It is. It is the same old
mugs, bro. It's the same
three. I'd say three people maximum. All
autistic, all skinned, all on benefits,
all lonely, and they come on here and
self-reflect their life every
day. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Show me 12 grand
cash. Yeah. Yeah. Go do that. Anyways,
bye-bye. Now, it's the same three
people, bro. It's like the same three
people, Max. It's not even loads and
loads of people. It's the same spastics
that's been doing it for years. Yeah,
bro. [ __ ] Little Virgin doesn't own
me. If you owe somebody so much, why
don't you meet them and say what you got
to say on YouTube to their face because
you know you'd get [ __ ] up. You owe
me. How do you owe me? Have I got my
kids to cop me? Have I lost my money cuz
of you? Have I been hurt? Have I been
killed? No. You just embarrassed
yourself every day on YouTube and you
look obsessed. None of these people have
ever owned me, bro. They've never ever
affected my life. I'm telling you, they
haven't. 100%, bro. They never have.
They've been a pain in the ass, you
know, sometimes. But think about it,
bro. All of this stuff that happened, it
wasn't because of
YouTube. The thing with the neighbor is
cuz when I used to gamble, I used to go
mad and had arguments with the neighbor.
I had like fights with the neighbors and
[ __ ] That wasn't because of YouTuber
and I wasn't living by myself. Do these
people think what they've done has
affected your life? But it hasn't. These
people will never affect my
life. And I don't know how many times
you have to say that until they get it.
They really don't affect no one to be
honest. I know, but have you seen him?
He's so ugly, Charlie. He's so [ __ ]
ugly. This is what I don't understand.
He is such an ugly [ __ ] which is why
he's so obsessed with all of the women
that I've been with. Well, I said on the
video. I did say that on the
video. And then he says that he's going
to get the police involved if I put up
posters of him, mate. All you've got to
do is show the police his channel.
All he does is self project. He has got
the face of a rat. He is balding. Look,
bro. If you look at his hairline, he's
balding. He's ugly. His face looks like
someone's just thrown a load of acid on
it. Nah, it's not five months, bro. It's
it's free. It's free. It's free max. It
looks like someone's chucked acid on his
face. He is so
ugly, you know. And that's that's where
the jealousy comes from. He knows deep
down that I'm a million times better
looking than he would ever be. That's
why I've been with these women that he
can't get out of his head and it kills
him. It hurts him. That's why he says
that I've got a big nose coming from
him. The rat face ugly bastard on the
ground and my Yeah. Okay,
bro. Okay, bro. Yeah, it's funny though, ain't
it? We should call him a,000 pound a
month boy. That's what we should call
him, Charlie. A,000 pound a month boy.
You know, the grind a
month. Yeah, I'd say the same five mugs,
bro. Yeah, I'd say
so. It's free, bro. Honestly, I'm
telling you, it's free. It's free
people. I'm telling you,
bro. I've got all of his [ __ ] bro. I've
got everything. I've got everything.
I've even got unlisted videos as well.
So I I would say say that the police
actually came. Yeah. He doesn't get
rejected. He does get rejected. That's
why he's with the wolf. Ugly
[ __ ] Yeah. He does get rejected
though, doesn't he? Yeah. Yeah. Listen,
he does get rejected. That's why he
can't get my sloppy seconds out of his
head. Now go self-reflect on another
channel, you fat disabled [ __ ] Bye-bye
now. You fat disabled 40-year-old Ma. Bye-bye now.
So yeah like anyways I was really
ups for example all you got to do is
show the police he channel
that guess what she said had a boyfriend
um all you got to do is show the police
all of what he's been doing for years he
would be [ __ ] bro especially even now
like he couldn't even get the police
involved and I wouldn't care even if he
did cuz I Stick it on the [ __ ]
police. I would stick it on the police,
bro. I don't give a [ __ ] about police in
this country, bro. They're [ __ ] soft
as [ __ ] You think police in this
country or anything, bro? I stuck it on
them last time. You know, they were
lucky that I was living with my mom at
that time as well. Trust me, bro. Cuz I
would have boyed them off even more.
Swear to God. Yeah. She said she had a
boyfriend. Yeah. What was you expecting
her to say, bro? Come on. It's England.
I had a woman say to me that she was too
young for me today and she's 21. I'm
27. It doesn't matter about him playing
a [ __ ] card. Bro, listen. They've put me
up on the system as [ __ ] disabled
because what they [ __ ] told him. It
doesn't matter. I would say I would tell
the police. Tell this [ __ ] ugly rat
to [ __ ] stop doing videos of me on
YouTube. Tell this [ __ ] ugly rat [ __ ]
to stop coming on YouTube every [ __ ]
day trying to annoy
people. Yeah, cuz that's what he's been
doing. You [ __ ] tell this ugly [ __ ]
rap. I'll say I'll say I'll say out the
[ __ ] window as well if I have
to. No, they don't have partners. One
second. My phone's about to die. One sec.
Yeah, no more Plow and Harrow. You
remember when I put up posters last
time, bro? That [ __ ] got scared for like
3 weeks. Three weeks. He wouldn't go to
the Plow and Harrow for two months. And
all he done was waiting until it died
down before he started his [ __ ] again.
He was [ __ ] scared. He was running to
the police with his rat face. Remember? Yeah. Yeah,
bro. It was actually a
madness. Do you remember or do you not
remember? You know, he's [ __ ] ugly rat
face. Is the lawyer looking at that ugly
face every day as well?
Yeah. Yeah. He doesn't go on a Sunday
night. He goes on different Listen,
listen. Listen. All of this, right? You
know where I am. You know where I drink,
it's all a load of old bollocks. Do you
want to know how you know it's a load of
albolics? Because when somebody is in
the virgin's area, as you have seen,
what happens? So, he tries to meet you
in all of these places apparently. Okay.
When you are in his area for over an
hour talking about his dad, talking
about his disabled girlfriend, where is
this [ __ ] all of a sudden? all of this
like you know where he drinks. It's all
autistic little games, bro.
Yeah. It's it's it's it's autistic
little games, bro. That's
it. Yeah. Exactly, bro. Exactly. Yeah. Do
you Well, a 9 minute video on pe autism.
Autism. You're so ugly. And he's balding
as well. He is literally balding. Oh my god.
I'm the one who's boarding, mate. I've
got more head than you will ever
have. [ __ ] I'm balding. I'm bored,
mate. Look in the mirror, please. Just
look in the mirror. You look like a [ __ ] rat.
He generally generally looks like a [ __ ]
rat. See the bad as well. He's actually
balding. He says that I'm balding.
[ __ ] not 1% balding. That's him
balding. Have you seen his hairline? It's [ __ ]
backwards. That [ __ ] is definitely
balding. Balding. Ugly rat. No
teeth. What could get worse, bro? What
could get worse? Yeah, man. [Music]
Oh n sorry I don't meet people off
YouTube so I don't know. Sorry about
that. Been there on that one the
t-shirt. I'm saying that you're bold as
a as a cult as a coping mechanism. No,
Sean, you literally are bored. You
literally are bored. Why would I need to
use it as a coping mechanism? You're the
one that uses it as an insult every day
because you are the one who's bored and
you are the one that's a manta. Look at
your face. You look like a
rat. And everybody
agrees. But people that hate
me cuz they're jealous of Pete belly.
They can't be Pete Belly. [ __ ]
ugly. You use my nose being big when
it's a normal size
to hide the fact that you're an ugly
[ __ ] that can't get normal
women. You know, that's that's why you
say that I've got a big nose to to hide
the fact that you know that you are
literally the ugly
[ __ ] Watch my back. Oh,
bye-bye. One of three
people. Yeah, man. Like you you talking
about my nose every day. You're obsessed
with my nose. Is that supposed to make
me insecure, mate? You look like a rat.
You creepy little non. A rat with no
facial hair. Rat, no facial hair.
Balding [ __ ] rat ears. He looks
inbred as well. He looks like one of
them. He looks like he's
someone on his face. He's so ugly. [ __ ] ugly,
[ __ ] [ __ ] ugly, [ __ ]
And then you got uh Triple H, right?
Saying that he owns me. What do you know
what's common with Triple H? I What's
the What's the same? What's the What's the sim
sim simulity between Triple H
and what's the
simulity? They both sharp and you go to
the area three times.
Of course he would say
that to say mate he doesn't come out cuz
I tried meeting him three times. Is it
mad? They're all They're both cowards.
They've got that in common, don't they?
They've got in common that they're both
cowards. I love
that. Yeah, they have that uh sim
similarity. I don't think I've ever said
that word before. My first time saying it. Yeah.
Yeah. No, he is [ __ ] ugly. He is a
really That's why he thinks by trying
with these women that I've already been
with, they're going to give him a
chance, but he's too ugly. That's why he
talks about my nose. He talks about my
nose and it's something like a
2-year-old would say like I'm I'm saying
is that supposed to make me
insecure? A a toothless little rat that
looks like a downy with autism is is
saying I've got a big nose. Am I
supposed to cut my nose off
something? Mate, if if my nose is all
I've got to [ __ ] worry about, mate,
that's a lot better than you. He all
these whole facial features look
downy. Like his whole actual
face is it's just ugly. It's just
ugly. You know, you know what I'm
saying? face is [ __ ] stinking, bro.
Stinking. Look at all of the women that
I've been with and look at all of the
women that he's been with. But he says
that I'm the ugly one, Steven Howard.
How does that make
sense? Whether I met them once, twice,
three times, four times. Look at all of the
women that I've been with. And then look
at all of the women that he's been with.
But I'm the ugly one. Remember I'm the
ugly one. Just remember that, bro.
Yeah. I'm saying just just remember that,
bro. And then look at who he is
with. Isn't that something?
that isn't that something Steven Howard?
Wow. Oh, [ __ ]
hell. We love that [ __ ] bro.
It's a madness, isn't
it? I've got people obsessed with me, Steven
Howard. People that are [ __ ] obsessed with me,
eh? That is so [Music]
weird. I know. He's [ __ ] himself
again. I will teach him from being a
little keyboard warrior. He needs to
learn to leave people
alone. He needs to learn enough is
enough and he needs to leave people
alone on on the
interwebs, you know. Yeah. He will be
worried. I'm going, bro. I'm doing these
posters. I swear to God I'm doing these
posters. Shut the [ __ ] up again for another month.
Yeah. Yeah. Simple.
See, the thing is this is this is a prime example
of the system in this country being
[ __ ] up because he's autism. He
shouldn't be allowed on the street with
his autism. He needs to be in prison. He
needs to be dead with his autism and his
obsession. He literally needs to not
even be put he needs sectioned, but yet
he's on the street. And for
example, if I call the police, the
police are not going to do anything. So
this is it's actually the system's fault
why why this little ratfaced autistic
little bastard is roaming the streets
with his [ __ ] autism every day. So
Peter Belly will have to be the one to
stop him yet
again. And if the police come, bro, I'd
love them to come. I'll be a bit cheeky
at first, but I'd love them to come. I'm
not scared of the
police, you know, especially over a
topic like I know that I'd win with, you
know, and that's it, bro. That's
it. You know, cuz all you got to say to
the police, okay, so it's all right for
this [ __ ] to come on YouTube every day
making videos upon videos upon videos
trying to get people's money stopped,
which you know, you know, just mention
all these things and there's no way in
hell that's legal for somebody to keep
doing this every day. So, it is it is their
fault. So, you know, all you have to say
to the police is like what they've done,
you know, like they won't get away with
it, but trust me.
Say you've had the benefit people call
you two times because of this kind of
harassing me. I've got proof of that. He
won't leave people loaded on YouTube
every day. What? The police is going to
say that's legal. Yeah. No, it ain't
[ __ ] legal. And it ain't legal. And
you know what? Yeah. If the police try
and say to me, "Block him." I'll say,
"Fuck off. Why don't he block me?" Yeah.
I'll say it works both ways then,
doesn't it? That's all I've got to say.
But I would be doing the posters again,
bro. Trust me 100%. I'll be doing the
posters again. That will shut the [ __ ]
up. And in that plow and harrow as well,
I'm going to say if you see I'm going to
say right, if you see this little virgin
[ __ ] you let me [ __ ] know. Yeah. And
I'd even offer money. You call me as
soon as you see this little virgin [ __ ]
even walk into this premises. And if I
walk past and he's in there and I don't
see you, I'm smashing your whole pub up.
I will smash your whole [ __ ] pub up,
bro. I don't care if I get if I get done
for criminal damage. This [ __ ] is going
to learn, mate.
you know, whether it's the right way or
whether it's the wrong
way. And that's it. And that is exactly
what I do. And you know, also what I'm
going to do, Stephen Howard, I'm going
to post posters up where he doesn't
know. So he'll be walking in somewhere
and some [ __ ] just kicks the [ __ ] out of
him. Yeah. That's what he needs. A good
old fashioned [ __ ] idol. Need [ __ ]
autism be out of him, bro. You know what
I'm saying? That's what I'm going to
do, you know?
And then you just say to the police as
well, like, and I'll say to the police
as well, I'll keep doing it until you
stop. I'll keep doing it. So, you know,
that's it. This little virgin needs to
[ __ ] learn, mate. This little virgin
needs to [ __ ] learn. And there's
actually a law for it as well. The
police actually said to me, "Oh, so what
did you do the posters for? Was it to
stop him?" And I said, "Yeah." And
that's the only thing that worked. But
there is an actual law in it as well
because they don't do their job
properly. So that's
it. But this [ __ ] needs to be
incarcerated, bro. I'm not even joking.
He needs to be incarcerated. It's the
worst autism I've ever come across in my
27 years of
life. It's It's really bad. Really,
really bad autism. He's obsess obsessed
with me. He's obsessed with all the
women I've banged. women have not
banged. He can't get my sloppy seconds
out of his head. You know, people come
on my channel and they're like, "Oh,
well, he can't be a virgin if he has a
girlfriend." Well, he can. And well, he
is because if he wasn't, why does he sit
around all day stalking my sloppy
seconds? If you're in in a relationship
getting sex, right, let's let's let's
listen to your logic. If you're in a
relationship getting sex, why are you
obsessed with my sloppy seconds every day?
obsessed with my sloppy seconds because
you don't get nothing yourself. You're a little
virgin. You're a typical little virgin.
That's what you are. So, somebody that's
um and he makes it his whole goal to get
these people to slate you off cuz he's
an insecure little virgin. That's part
of autism by the way. You know, he can't
accept the fact that you've shag normal
women. So he tells himself that you
haven't every single day to make himself feel
better because he's a little [ __ ]
virgin with autism. The Chev Cole thing,
that's autism. But that's more of like a
trend. If you don't find Chevil Cole
attractive, you're gay. Yeah, he was
just trying to fit in there. Just trying
to fit in. There's no there the there's
no fun when someone's just trying to fit
in. If you don't find shovel co
attractive, you're gay. [ __ ] hell,
mate. I must be [ __ ] gay then cuz
that [ __ ] is [ __ ] stinking,
son. I didn't know I was gay, bro. Oh,
really? I didn't even know
that. [ __ ] stinking. Cheers. He's a little
copycat. That's what he is. He's a little copycat.
Um, why do you think Chase doesn't meet
him anymore? Why do you think Kenzie
don't meet him no
more? You know, he even started he he
even started ignoring
Chase. You know, why do you think I told
Chase here to try and meet him and I was
going to smash him up. You know that. I
think he caught on to it. Benji doesn't
meet him anymore. Chase don't meet him.
Yeah, Chase was trying to get him to go
somewhere. I was going to smash him up
on camera, bro. I put it on YouTube, but
the [ __ ] on or maybe they just fell out.
But yeah, I said to Chase, "Yeah, I'll
get him to meet me, you and I'll turn up
and smash the [ __ ] in." That's what I
was going to do. Yeah. And I was going
to make the little [ __ ] say sorry about
100 times and I was going to spit down
his throat as
well, you know? I'll make that fine
thing look like nah, bro. Trust me. Yeah.
You know how it is, isn't
it? He's got bed, but he's tired.
Yeah. No one meets that little virgin no more.
But I don't actually understand what the
police would actually do because even if
they got a restraining order on this
little virgin, he would just make new
accounts. He literally needs to be put
in prison or or or dead. Like I I I
don't know the any other
options. It's either they drop dead or
they go in prison. That's that's it.
I feel sorry for his dad. Imagine, even
though his dad's a nons, but imagine
that, like you you you you know, you had
a kid that's got the worst autism in the
world. Imagine that. The worst autism in
the in in the whole wide
world. You gave, you know, you you
brought life to somebody that's a
greeneyed monster, a greeneyed autistic
little monster. That's some madness
going. No wonder his mom starved him. No
wonder his mom disowned him. His mommy
mama. His mama disowned
him. You know what I'm
saying? Yeah. It's [ __ ] funny, bro. [Applause]
I sure am happen to do posters again. I
sure am, buddy. Of this little [ __ ] lanky little virgin.
[ __ ] I didn't care. Yeah. And I and I'm
not listening because at the way the way
I see it, mate, is if the police come
back for me, I'm just going to show them
his channel of him harassing me every
day. So, it's all good, man. Yeah. I got
warned, but I'm not listening. I said,
"You do something about this, cunt."
Yeah. Before you [ __ ] start coming on
my [ __ ] door making videos of me
every single day on [ __ ] YouTube. Um,
I won't let him in. Like me, I live by
myself now. Like, I don't live with my
mom. So, I'll tell them like I say,
"Okay, what you uh" they like, "Oh,
we're looking for Peter." I'll be like,
"It's me speaking. What do you want?"
And then they're going to be like, "Oh,
uh, they're obviously going to tell me
cuz I'm the person." I will tell them to
[ __ ] off and come back um with a warrant
and come back when you do something
about this little [ __ ] And I will and I
will not let them in. You know, if they
get a warrant and they want to break in,
they can break in all they want. You
know, the results going to the results
going to be the same, bro. You know,
I'll say, "You do something about this
cunt." You know what I'll say to them?
I'll say to them,
"Listen, yeah, you come back with a
warrant. I'm going to go to the police
station and I'm going to report this
[ __ ] When something's done about this
[ __ ] then come back to me, then come
back to my yard about warn about it.
Bro, I'll show them his whole channel of
he's harassing. It's already on the
system every day with this little
[ __ ] virgin and his fat ugly
girlfriend. What are they going to do,
bro? What? Take me to court. It's not
possible, you know? It's not [ __ ]
possible. It's their fault to begin
with. It's the police's fault to be and
the system's fault
really. And and the police kind of got
it last time. I was like, well, this is
the only thing that stopped it. You never stopped
it. You know, this is the only thing
that stopped it. That's another thing
you need to make and make them aware of
as well that it actually stops it for
like two, three
weeks, you know.
So, you know, how can I be wrong then if
it stops it? He is going to stop, mate.
When I do these posters, he is going to
[ __ ] stop. Trust me, he is going to
[ __ ] stop. When I do these posters,
lad, he will be stopping. And he won't
be going to that plow and harrow anymore
as well, cuz I'm going to be going there
tomorrow. I'll be getting a bus there
tomorrow, mate. and I'll be having a word with
him. So, he won't be he won't he will be
stopping, mate. And he won't be going there
anymore. Dude, I'm going to speak to all
the workers. I'm going to go all to I'm
going to go around the local restaurants
as well. I'm going to show videos of
him. Doesn't matter if he goes to the I
want him to go to the police. I want him
to go to the police. Yeah. Yeah, bro. I
want him to go to the police so I can
show them what he's been doing for
years. Him and that Red account. I want
them to go to the police. I want them
to. I love it. I don't care about the
police. Call them. You You make it easy
for me when you call them. You know, you
can go to the police all you [ __ ]
want. I'll tell them to [ __ ] off.
Simple. But they don't know where I live
anyways. So, good luck with that, you
know. But even if they do come, it's
better for me cuz then I can show them
what this little virgin has been doing
for years. That's good, bro. At least it
will finally come to an end, you
know. So that's
it. That's it,
bro. Um, and I'm going to go to the plow
and harrow as well.
I say I'm going to go to the local
restaurants as well and I'm going to say
um I'm going to offer to pay um for the
address cuz obviously it's in a village
in it. So you know what Asian people are
like. They'll probably will give you his
address. I tried to get his address
earlier. I I was calling up pretending to be
him. I was
uh um I was calling up pretending to be
him as well saying, "Oh, uh yeah, this
is Sean. My address should be on the
system. Trust me, I will find his
address. Trust me, when I go around that
village, I will find that come to
address and the neighbors are going to
know everything. I'll make it so bad he
won't live there
anymore. If and when I get this address,
posters will be going out regardless if
I have if I get the address or not. He
he ain't living there no more. Trust me.
Yeah. So, all you got to do is it's a
village. Yeah. Go to some of them
takeaways saying that this guy keeps
harassing your little sister. Offer them
a little bit of money. 150 maybe they'll
give you that address mate. You know
what Asians are like with money. Chinese
people in the I said give me this little
[ __ ] faggot's address this little rat
face and you will get a prize and just
act like a concerned brother or
something. And as soon as you got that address lovely
mate to the one in stone. Yeah. The plow and hammer. Yeah. But
yeah, surprised I not caught him. I'm
not surprised I don't c I didn't c I
haven't caught him because I don't live
anywhere near Lone and I haven't for like two
years and he goes live for like 2
minutes and then runs back to the train
station. Why would I catch him? He's
nowhere near my area and he goes live
when he's just about to jump on the
train back home again. Silly little
games which we'll not get into. That's
how I'm not called the little virgin
because he doesn't actually tell you
when and where he's going and that he
actually stays live and I don't live in
that area no more. So,
um it's how is it mad because I go to
central London? No, it's not mad. Why
would it be mad? He doesn't live
anywhere near me. All of the places that
he goes to is nowhere near
me. He doesn't go out every weekend. He
goes to that [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
place which is nowhere near [ __ ]
central London. But anyways, you should
be able to get his address that way.
Definitely should be able to get his
address that way, I
reckon. Yeah, bro. It's off about
150 quid. They'll give you the address.
I have to pop. Oh, mate. I will post.
Oh, mate. I'll put posters
everywhere, you know. I'll do it the
non-coward way and I'll do it the coward
way. You know, I'll be a coward and I'll
also not be a coward. So, just to be a
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
And I'll do posters, but I will do
posters every week. Every week. I swear
to God, I'll send the I'll send the
ladies posters every week, bro. I'll
hand post them. You know, like last
time. You remember the hand posted on one, Charlie? Yeah. So
yeah. So yeah, that's what I'll be
doing, bro. It's all good, is it? They
get the police. [ __ ] it. Just show the
police the channel, the YouTube
channel. Unlisted videos. I've got
unlisted videos as well where he's
trying to go people.
Um, and I said to the police woman, if
he's such a victim, why is he telling
people to go to the club to fight him
when he obviously he's pretending to try
and meet people? So that's why they
didn't do anything to me because they
know that what he's been doing for years, you
know. Yep. Wherever I see fit. Wherever
I see fit. No, I'm not doing these
little thing. Going to them [ __ ]
clubs. No, I'm not playing little gigs.
I'm going to go out. I'm going to put
posters out and I'm going to find the
cub's address. Hopefully, I should be
able to with one of the takeaways. It's
only a small
village. I'm going to try and find his
barber as well. I remember him saying
his barber with
Welsh. Yep. He won't be going to no barber
shop. H no shop at all, bro.
Yeah. And then obviously they call the
police. Show the police what they've
been doing to you for years. You
know what can I don't even think the
police would come anymore, bro. They're
so fed up of coming for me. You know,
coming for me. They're fed up. I've been
nicked about six times over YouTube. I
think they're generally fed up with me, you know. Yeah. [Music]
handing it out wherever I see
fit. He runs straight to the police coward. [ __ ]
virgin. I [ __ ] hate that [ __ ] I hope
he gets cancer. Him and his fat ugly
girlfriend. I know it's bad to say, but I actually
do. Yeah, I know, bro. I know. I know.
Like you said, dead or in prison. Dead
or uh dead or in prison.
dead isn't that I hope he gets I hope
him and his girlfriend get cancelled and
die said that as well. Yeah, it's lush.
Yeah, it's mad talk. I hate him. He's a
[ __ ] ugly little rat that won't leave
people alone. I hate him. I hope he dies
of cancer. At least if you actually done
that, bro, like you'd actually be left.
Um, when I mean leave me alone, um, I
mean like you being a annoying,
harassing little rat. Not as in you
bully no one because you don't bully no
one. You bully yourself every day when
you come on YouTube. Write paragraphs about Peter
Betty. That's what I mean by um like
leaving people alone. I mean like stop
going on about them, you
know, cuz you don't know what m I could
I could literally beat that [ __ ] with my
little finger. That's how bad it is. But
then he comes on YouTube like he's some
kind of big
man. No, he would never have a kid,
mate. No, he can't come. How can he have
a How can How can he have a kid? He's got erectile
dysfunction. He's mate, he's got
erectile dysfunction. He's never having no
kid. You can't get it up. Silly little virgin.
Have I heard from the American? No. Why
would I hear from the American, bro?
Have you got brain damage or
something? We hate each other. So why
would I hear from
her? Uh, it it it's called autism.
Steven Albert, it's called
autism. That's what that's why. Because
it's it's autism.
Why would you ask about that? Why you
asking stupid questions? You knew it was
finished [ __ ] two [ __ ] three years
ago. Why would I hear from them? What?
They just going to randomly message me
and be like, "Oh, yeah. Come to America.
Come on, bro. Get real." I basically
interfered with their
life. You know, I kind of interfere with
their life. Oh, I got some pictures of
her as well. She's [ __ ] stinking. She
is. She's turned really, really ugly.
I'll put a picture up,
man. Now you're going to accuse me like
[ __ ] sure now. She a really badly,
man. God, she [ __ ] aged
badly. Yeah, I was talking about it for
months, but what I'm saying is why would
I hear from them? It doesn't make any sense, you know. Yep.
You aged terribly, man. What the [ __ ] happened to you?
Jeez. That is one very, very ugly face.
Almost as ugly as Sean.
Yeah. [ __ ] Stinking. CS.
No, no, I don't
care. No, I've already forgotten,
mate. I've actually forgotten. I don't
care about it no more, Charlie. The
reason I don't care about it is because
I made a [ __ ] change her number. Her
boyfriend split up with her. She went to
the police on me five times. I went to
America. She didn't come out. I done
what I had to
do. Like I don't need to do anything
more, bro. It's the end
it. Imagine you bumped into her in
London again. Stop being stupid. That
would never happen. And I wouldn't care.
I don't have autism like Sean. That's
the thing. I can let people
go. You know, people that I've been
intimate with. I just didn't like the
fact that they they done something and
they thought they got away with it.
That's what was annoying
me. with this little virgin. Sure. This
was [ __ ] like 10 years ago and he's still
obsessed. Still obsessed after 10
years. Still obsessed. Imagine
that. Now, would I say anything now? Probably not.
No. But before I would have whipped her
ass, but she's a fat ugly [ __ ] and I
got my own back anyway.
So, yeah. No, before I would have
whooped her ass. But I would have
whooped her ass. I'm not going to lie to
you, but now I don't really
care. I thought I found a new mama,
Charlie. My mama from
Manchester. I thought I found a new
mama. How cute was that though, Charlie?
But you see that one in Manchester? That
pissed me off for two days. I don't
care. Guess what? Sean's still going on about it.
Sean's still going on about it. I got
over it in two days. [ __ ] pissing me off,
bro. Yeah, I know. But Sean's still
obsessed. See, that's
autism. That's why he was diagnosed with
autism. You see, her name was actually Alicia.
Yeah. He's obsessed with all of my
um ex flings, the women I'm in contact
with. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. He's a he's he gets jealous
when I meet new women cuz it reminds him
of what he would ever have and he
obsesses over there and and he his whole
goal is to try to make he makes it his
whole goal to find out if you've slept
with him or not. That's how we know he's
a virgin. He done the same thing with
Izzy. He done the same thing with Izzy.
Morgan. Why did she block me? I don't
know why she blocked
me. It's not important though, is it?
She blocked me, so there's no point
going on about
it. Same thing with
Izzy. Same thing with all of them, bro.
He He makes it his whole goal. That's
another form of
autism. That's how you know he's still a
virgin and he's not in a secure relationship.
He's in a relationship with a dwarf that
could give him sex. That's why he's still a
virgin. But yeah, don't know why she
blocked me. Probably cuz she was
trolling me. Who cares, bro? I haven't
even met the person. Could you imagine I
actually met them,
Charlie? Yeah. No woman
knows. No, no one on here knows women
that have actually met in person and
they haven't done for two
years. He is so
upset. He's so obsessed. Do you remember
when he was messaging
Sigma? He hates the fact that I'm better
looking than him and I've had better women
um better women than him. But yeah, he
calls me ugly. It doesn't make
sense. Doesn't make any sense. Maybe.
Yeah, she had big boobs as well,
Charlie. So maybe. I don't
know. I was kind of looking forward to
meeting them, but they just [ __ ] me around.
So don't know why they blocked. Everything was
fine. He's not a fighter. He better want
to [ __ ] hope he's a fighter, mate. if
he ever sees me. That's what I say when
people say that he's not a fighter.
Charlie, do you know what I say? I say
you better [ __ ] one of OP [ __ ] is
what he's saying when he sees
me. Yeah. He keeps saying that big no
stuff and it's really boring. It's It's
not bullying. It's just really really
boring because he's in denial. He knows
that I am much better looking than he would ever
be. That's mad. She ghosted you for no
reason. Uh I wouldn't say that's mad. I
would say that's
England. That's England for
you. That's England for you, isn't it,
Charlie? Hey, Charlie.
Yeah. Yeah. So, basically, no, no. Okay,
I'll explain it to you quickly again.
Right. I messaged them on
Instagram thinking, "Oh, this person's
never going to reply." So, then they
replied. Um, I said, "Oh, I'll take you
to get your nails done, ret." She said,
"I'll be up for that. We can meet up."
And then she gave me a
number and then we was like talking for
like two three
days, right? Um just normal chat, our
hobbies, what we're into. We was the
same age which was good. And we're
talking I went out the Friday drinking
and I spoke to her again the Saturday
and then we're talking and that we
arranged to meet. I said, "Oh, let me
let's meet next week instead of the 28th
cuz it's quick." And then I noticed that
she blocked me on Instagram even though
we were speaking on WhatsApp. He was
only speaking on
WhatsApp. Uh that we was mainly speaking
on WhatsApp after I was like, "Um, why
did you block me on WhatsApp on
Instagram? Is everything
okay?" And then she turned around and
said, "Oh, I didn't um you know, I had
loads of requests from like random
people that." And then he was doing my
head in ter
um I was like, "Well, you have blocked
me cuz I'm next to my friend and he's
typed your name in." And then she
blocked me on
WhatsApp and I didn't say anything
wrong. Didn't talk about sex. Didn't
talk about no weirdness. See, and it
weren't even easy for me as well cuz I
still had to go Manchester as well. So
it wasn't an easy ride even if they did want
me. So yeah, it pissed me off, bro. So I
wasted time like two, three days sending
we was sending voice notes, talking for
reason. For absolutely no reason, bro.
just for them to go to the
end. Yeah, it's pissing me off, bro.
They piss me off. These women in this
country, they piss me off,
bro. That's why I don't really bother
anymore. I said to her, "Oh, let's meet
outside the hotel, like the hotel
reception." And she said, "Yeah, that's
fine. I know where that is." And then
she just turned in weird. What do you
want me to say, man? You
know, but she probably had that plan all
along cuz she said that she the reason
she couldn't meet this Saturday was she
had a friend's wedding. I don't believe
her. Friends wedding, she said. No, I don't believe
her. I don't know why, but I don't
believe she had a friend's wedding on
Saturday. So, yeah. I don't even know
why she even gave me her number if she
was just going to do that, to be honest. Hey,
Charlie. What's the point of even giving
your [ __ ] number,
bro? It was good as well cuz we're the
same age. Same age. Like the same [ __ ] But
nah, when something's good too good to
be true, Charlie, it probably is.
She's become very
stinking. Why have you become very
stinking? This is what Sean is jealous
over, by the way, people.
Maybe she is [ __ ] stinking, bro. Yeah.
[ __ ] hell. It's crazy,
lad. I can't remember what she looked
like when I met her. She didn't look
that bad. Not as bad as that, but I
remember she looked kind of
bad. Yeah, Sean got jealous over that as
well. Sean got jealous over that. Do you
remember the approach? It killed him,
Charlie. Oh my god. Peter Benny Paul's an
American. Peter belly Paul's an
He got [ __ ] so jealous, bro. Do you
remember? He was like,
"Oh, what did he say again?" He was
like, he made a community post about it
when she offered me her [Music]
number. Charles has found Charles has
got new misses.
is didn't take him long to move on.
Easy. See, she doesn't even look like
she's a bad person. But she is a bad
person. Cuz if she wasn't a bad person,
she would have done what she done.
Simple. You You are a bad person, man.
I watch like mom's videos and stuff
where it's all of them and the kids and
whatnot, but of course you're a bad person, you
know. Yeah, he's
obsessed. He is obsessed. Obsessed. M proper
obsessment. He's pretty much stalking
you at this point. You think? I didn't know that. Yeah.
And she did sleep with me as well. She
only said she never slept with me
because she was cheating on her
boyfriend. Nice pride on
legs. Yeah. Yeah. Hope he does. Hope she
Yeah, he does.
Bro, I'm not answering them questions,
bro. She never said that because that
weren't even her. That was V1. And I'm
not talking about this anymore anyways,
bro. This is old school. I just thought
I'd show you her pictures cuz she's [ __ ] ugly.
But yeah, she missed out, bro. She
missed out on more stakes and more
wine. Yeah, I think half of it was as well. Yeah.
Do I feel bad? Nah, not really. I think
they deserved everything they
got. I went to the cinema the other day.
Did I think of
them? Not really. Nah, because I know
I've got revenge. That's the whole thing
about it was it was like getting that
revenge. It's like when I got that
revenge on Isabelle, I was fine after a
few months. It's all about getting
revenge. And once you got
revenge and they don't never to [ __ ]
with you ever again, you know, you you
feel happy, bro. You know what I mean?
You changing your number, your man
splitting up with
you. How would be a war, bro? We're not
going over this again, bro. It's boring.
We're not talking about this again.
It's boring as [ __ ]
lad. You remember the tenants that
almost died, Charlie? You remember the
tenants that almost got
killed? Imagine that. Yeah. Moving into
a house thinking that you're safe.
You're just renting a house. You're
renting a room and you almost lose your life. That's
mad. All right. There's actually a
madness. That's actually quite scary to be
honest. That's actually quite scary, isn't
it? People getting chased out the
[ __ ] door and that madness. This
Yeah. So, what do you give USA? Is he
out of 10
now? Yeah, man.
Yeah. Do you want my
number? Do you want my number?
I woke up the other day, Charlie.
Yeah. And there was these people making
noise. I think it was from next door.
And it was all night
long. It was all night long. Swear down,
bro. I thought somebody was whispering
whispering in my
ear. I thought somebody was whispering
in my ear, bro. cuz I woke up at like 5
in the morning. I was like, "No,
something's not right." I don't wake up
at 5 in the
morning. I don't wake up at 5 in the
morning. I wake up at like 7 7:30. I
don't have any
plans. No drinking, no sending for a while,
bro. Yeah. I thought [ __ ] someone was
whispering in my [ __ ]
ear. Yeah, it's mad, bro.
It was all night
long. It was all night long sleeping
out. I think they were drinking or
something. Yeah. I think they were drinking.
Yeah. Yeah. I think they were drinking.
Bro, I got no plans tomorrow. I don't
make plans. But no, it was all night
long, mate. It was all night long. I
swear to God, bro. It was all night long.
Yeah. Wonder if that guy ever got his bike back. Nah. Never.
No. What? Was like [ __ ] It was like
from 2:00 in the morning, bro. I said,
"Did you hear
that?" He said, "Yeah, I was with my
friend and he was like he he woke him up
as well." I like you hear that [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah, bro. I'll never forget.
Yeah. Few months ago, bro. I swear to
God, it was when that whole Twitter
thing was going on where they put me on
Twitter. I swear down, bro. I woke up at
like 2 3:00 in the morning. No [ __ ] 2
3:00 in the morning. I woke up, bro.
And I swear to God, somebody was
climbing up the [ __ ] window like next
door. He was on some ninja
[ __ ] you know?
Like [ __ ] it was somebody climbing up
the [ __ ] house next to our neighbor,
bro. I was like I thought I was seeing
things. I thought I thought they might
and man's like they might have got the wrong
house. No, I didn't get scared. I just
thought, what the [ __ ] am I seeing, bro?
He was on some ninja
[ __ ] He was on some ninja [ __ ] man.
Yeah. And I was like, am I am I got the wrong
house? I don't know. That made me laugh.
Climbing up windows and [ __ ]
Yeah. That was all night long. Hours all
Yeah. Do you remember when I started on my mom's
neighbor? Yeah. Yeah, I lost money
gambling and I remembered the night
before I couldn't let it lie. I was
like, "Come on then, big man." And then
he started coming on the door.
Remember? Yep. I lost money gambling. I
was in my little resh. I was like, "Come
on then, big
man." Do you
remember? I know cuz it's where my mom
lives in it. But I didn't even that's
that's the whole reason I didn't do that
in Bers cuz it's where my mom lives.
That's the only reason it felt cuz I was
scared. I swear that I swear to God
because it would have ended there.
Trust these things work. That's why I just
like start drinking as well. Bro, don't
forget what I used to do is when I used
to go to central London, I used to come
back to my mom's area and drink in the pub
um before going home. So, I used to get
really drunk in
it. Proper [ __ ] I used to get proper
[ __ ] and and I play online roulette in
it. I was playing on the bus. I remember
I was playing it, bro. I used to play
that online roulette, man, bro. I swear
to God. I was playing on the bus. I was
doing like 300 pound
spins. [ __ ] crazy,
bro. I was drunk somewhere, man.
Yeah. They used to make so much noise in that
house. It's not really fair. Is it? I
used to make a lot of noise,
bro. It worked the whole street
up. Hey, Charlie, you still didn't
answer me. What happened to my
mama? Charlie, what happened to my mama?
I thought that one in Manchester was
going to be my mommy. She had big
boobs, but she left me all by
myself. Well, I'm now because I already have years.
Wow. Yeah. She's in peace now.
Yeah. I used to scare the dog as well. I
used to scare King the dog. He used to
give me jokes. the dog. Yeah,
man. I haven't seen my sisters for ages,
bro. I speak to my sisters, but I just
ain't seen them. I just keep myself to
myself. I just It over YouTube. I just
don't like see them.
Don't know why for ages, bro. I still occasionally.
Yeah. Could be an independent adult.
She's going to sleep in a minute, mate. I'm
[ __ ] I was actually thinking I was
going to go see that woman in Manchester
and move to Manchester. Bro, I was
having all of these mad
plans. keep her to live there, have a
baby. Peter, I was thinking of mad things now
cuz I don't really see my role anymore.
So, I was just going to move on with my life in
it. Even if it meant going to another
city, just seeing how it would work out, you
know? You know what I'm
saying? No, I'm being serious,
bro. cuz the rent would have been
cheaper. Split the rent, have a kid,
free housing. What was your
uncle? I'm not joking, bro. I was being serious,
man. Thought this could be the one.
Charlie, I actually thought it could
have been the one because they were
messaging back and forth, back and
forth, and I was saying all the right
things and [ __ ] So,
but no, bro. It's bad that it's bad that,
bro. No, I don't think so.
could have made some babies with
her. Apparently, she's got mental health
and PTSD apparently.
So the Virgin says, So Virgin Sea
says, "Well, bro, um,
how I was I was waiting for a long time
to meet someone.
I don't know,
bro. Do you remember that one Steven
Howard taking a baby away from its mama?
taking the baby away from its
mama. I don't know why where I even come
out with that from,
bro. Taking the baby away from it mama.
I don't know. I just felt like I got
took away from my mama in it. Attachment
issues. Who knows? I don't I don't [ __ ]
know my mom.
And like every time, yeah, I see a baby
face here, I just it reminds me of it.
Like a baby that's like with its dad
taking the baby away from it
mama. Yeah, you little [ __ ] mock me in
it with what I [ __ ] say, don't you? You [ __ ]
Women were put on this earth to fetch food
apparently. Well, women was put on this
earth to satisfy Peter B's
needs. Is that right, Charlie? Yeah.
Or when I see a horror film that's American.
Yeah. Or a horror film that's American.
Mhm. Yeah. She left and I got revenge.
So that's all good. [Applause]
You remember Elephant in Castle? Castle. [ __ ]
off. Got haunted for a while, man. Do
you remember when I was crying on the
train? On the train,
Charlie? I was crying on the train and
that was a crazy back
there. Crying on the [ __ ] train, eh?
Crying on the train. Train a
be. That's a
madness. Crying on the [ __ ] train,
lad. Yeah. I wanted them to explain why they're not
interested. Yeah. I spoke to Chinese
Izzy today actually. She said that we
can't she doesn't want to text no more
because I never go up and see her. I was
like, "You live up north. You live a bit
far." I said, "I'll come to you. I will
come." But she said, "We we live too far
to text." I keep saying I'm going to go
up there, but I don't. Yeah.
Uh, Antman said they're just not
interested in this
country because that's the truth of it.
But it sounds so mad.
Like it actually sounds so mad, but it's
so true. Like they're not interested in this
country. That's the actual truth of it,
which is mad. It's just mad saying it
like that, you
know. They're just not interested in this
country. Do it, Charlie. Yeah.
Mhm. Yeah, bro. Of course. Sometime in
March. Sometime in March. Yeah,
definitely. But I can't be bothered with women anymore,
mate. I just can't be bothered with him,
lad. You get like that as you get older.
You just can't be bothered in it. Not a
cup. That's what Natalie G
said. Not my cuppper.
So, how come a chron couldn't go to
these places like Amsterdam and
Manchester and stuff,
Charlie? Because he ain't got the money.
He ain't got the
funds. You know, maybe he's little skin flint,
mate. 30 and he's never been out the
country. Never been on an
airplane. It's cuz he's skinn. That's
why. Skinner than a [ __ ] skin.
He's very skinny. He is very
skinny. Hey, Grezy. No, that's USA. Is
he? Yeah, she's gone
downhill. Yeah, she's gone downhill. She
has I wish I was black, Charlie. I wish
I was a black
man. If I was a black man, they'd come to me.
I wish I was black sometimes,
but I say that I see black guys get rejected.
Rejected. They get what they want back.
I wonder how she come to England all by
herself. That's crazy, bro. That's how
you know she's not normal. She came to England by
herself. She came to England all by
herself. What the [ __ ] bro?
That is [ __ ]
crazy. I remember when I travel, we used
to travel by
myself. I wonder if Grezy could go to Amsterdam by
himself. Greasy would [ __ ] his
pants. That's actually mad. But if you
come to England all by
yourself, that's crazy,
bro. by your [ __ ] self. What the
bro? I went to [ __ ] I went a few
countries by myself and when you come
back, it takes some uh
adjusting. I went to Amsterdam by
myself. [ __ ] the escorts. Oh my god,
I was a crazy
[ __ ] I was crazy, bro. Do you remember that, Charlie?
I remember me and LT was beefing at the
time and he was like, "I'm going to come
on your door. Pat Mustard, you and Pat
Mustard's winding me up. I'm going to
come on your door." I was like, "Mate,
good. Good luck with that cuz I'm not
even in the
country." I said, "I'm not even in the country, mate."
So, yeah, I went on the ferry all by
myself. Charlie, I thought I'd treat
myself to a little
holiday. And I met some people in the
hostel who I still talk to to this day. So,
Yeah, that's mad doing that by yourself though. [ __ ]
hell. Why do you need someone with you,
Grezy? I don't know about myself, buddy.
I've seen the fairy power [ __ ] 100 times as
well. I can't believe I actually don't
know about myself, though. That's mad, is
it? You need some balls to do that, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Um still waiting for his pip decision. Yeah.
Someone's got a really bad phobia of
heights and he's got a phobia of
dogs. He's He's actually got a phobia of
dogs because of Tilly the
Dalmatian. You scared of You're scared
dogs? No, man.
Nothing. You scared of dogs, Sean?
Are you scared of
ducks? Ducks. Ducks.
Ducks. Scared of
ducks. You scared of ducks. kill.
Yeah. Why would you go by yourself? Grezy, you
scared? I [ __ ] done it, bro. I done
Belgium by myself. None of them spoke [ __ ]
English. That was a crazy back then.
Yeah, I remember when I used to go
uh I remember I used to go Manchester
like sometimes I'd wake up Charlie one
day and I'd be like where's my little
legs going to take me
today? Maybe Wales, maybe
Manchester. You just
never just never knew where my little
legs could take me, you know.
Sometimes I'd wake up one day be like,
"Let me go to Manchester. Let me go to
Liverpool. My legs take me everywhere,
man." That's why they're so
toned. I never I'll never forget when I
said that to him. I'm just going for a
walk and I ended up in
Brian. [ __ ] hell, bro. [Music]
We have good times,
right? Yeah. My little legs,
mate. That time I went to the beach by myself, Charlie.
Yeah, that was good, bro. That was
good. I've only been up some once.
I was there for 3
days. I remember I was smoking weed and
drinking wine. I had a panic attack,
bro. I had a mad panic
attack. You like that woman that said
she wouldn't suck a dick for a million
pound. I think she's over exaggerating.
I think she would definitely suck a dick
for a million pound.
for a million pound. Don't be stupid. Of
course you would,
mate. I'd lick [ __ ] for [ __ ] a
million pound. And I don't eat [ __ ] I
hate I hate
that. Of course you would for a million
pound. Why you do it anyways, don't
you? You give it to Black Flynn for
free, you know. So why wouldn't you for
a million pound?
If he was a black guy, they'd do it
freezy. So, I mean, [ __ ] a million
pounds. I'm actually starting to want to become black
again. Like, I actually want to be black.
Yeah, just not my dick.
Yeah, maybe USA is not sucked
dick. Maybe she's never sucked dick in it,
Charlie. Well, Damon told me that he she
sucked his dick. That's what Damon told
me. That's what they Yeah, that's what Damon told
me. He asked me how his dick tasted cuz
I said, "Oh, I got some of your uh I got
you some of your women that you was with. Yeah,
man. They give it to them for free,
man. Free of
charge. Yeah, but they might not be
virgins. They might just not suck
dick. Steve never sucked my dick. She
said, "Oh, I will only suck your dick if
you eat my pussy." I was I'm not eating
your [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] out of here.
Eat my [ __ ] Are you [ __ ]
mad? Get out of here with that
[ __ ] I don't do that, bro. It's disgusting.
I had someone on Instagram, but
yeah, you know, I don't know when I'll
be approaching again, bro. I just can't
be bothered with it all
anymore. It's cold as well. Uh because I
don't I don't like doing
it. I dominate. I don't get
dominated. Nah, I'm good.
Sorry, this woman's um pissed off with me on
Instagram. One second. Let me
reply. One second. One second. One
second. Second. Hold. Let me reply to
this. Two seconds. So
yeah, put Charles up. I've actually got a picture. Oh yeah. [Music]
So, do you reckon if I was a black guy would
help? You actually reckon if I was a
black guy would help,
Charlie? I think it
would. But I see loads of black guys get
rejected. But I think
being being a black guy would give you
advantage. What do you
think? I said that for like two years
and I was like, "Oh, you're just being silly." What? No.
Maybe black guys are just more superior.
I don't know, bro.
But they get what they want,
mate. This [ __ ] has got bipolar, lads.
I said to her, "Oh, I've got a video of
me getting a [ __ ] Do you want to see
it?" She said, "That's weird. If that's
how you speak to other women, I see how
they block you." I said, "Well, you've
seen how I speak to other women. So, why
are you making excuses for them? You've
literally seen every single message that
I have sent someone. You've seen my approaches.
So when you're when you're arguing with someone
that's always going to defend women,
it's just a waste of your time, waste of
my time, you know,
like [ __ ] man. [ __ ] him.
Anyways, this is what I want. She's on
Instagram, bro. She's [ __ ]
sexy, but she's impossible to
get. Well, she not sexy, but she's all right in
it. But you can never get anyone like
that due to simps.
due to simps,
lad. All of this [ __ ] approaching
[ __ ] that's making me tired,
bro. Instagram user.
I need to go shoot
now kind of a bit. Yeah. Imagine
I've actually been with women that have boobs like
that. Maybe not as
big. Well, no, I think I have
actually. Sig, USA, Izzy, the Albanian had big
tits. Other people, I'm sure they've had
big tits. There was someone in the night
club before I was squeezing their tits.
Those were big as well. bit like
that. They were put on earth to satisfy
my needs. Grezy to satisfy Peter Benny's
needs. I'll never forget when you typed
that. I know he was taking a piss, but
it was funny.
Why are you saying what the
[ __ ] Yeah, she's got big
tits. There's like 500 Instagram followers. Yeah.
Yeah, imagine that,
mate. It needs to be glued to
her. I've actually seen her tits, by the
way. I've seen her nudes. She's actually
got nudes. She's from America.
Yeah, I've actually seen her tits. She
got like videos and
that. I don't think I I don't think I've
been with anyone that's had as big tits
as that to be
fair. I've been with people that's had
really big tits, but
not maybe they were just as big, but
just I don't know. That's quite rare, is it? Yeah. of
food. Yeah, bro. I don't
know. I got blocked for saying that.
Uh, I got a video of me getting a
[ __ ] I still got that video of me
getting a [ __ ] It was funny. It made
nons rage. He put it on his channel and
then he got his whole channel
banned. All cuz Peter Benny got a
[ __ ] You remember
that? The whole central channel got
banned and you had to start fresh again.
You had to start talking channel and be fresh again.
Oh, it's funny,
bro. That was a ladder. I want to piss.
I need to piss. I'm going to piss and think.
Yeah, might be only fans. Who knows?
Anyway, I need to go to bed. I'm [ __ ] knacking,
lad. I'm pissing the bath,
mate. Every morning when I wake up, I
piss in the
bath. Piss in the bath, mate. It's the
habit. Anyways, I need to go to bed. I'm
[ __ ] knackered. All right, catch.