Oh [ __ ] Oh man,
I'm getting tired, bro.
[ __ ] sausage, man.
No, I don't care.
Nope. And I don't care either. Oh.
Oh, I don't know how I want to go today.
I'm so tired. Tired me. Yeah.
Get some lamb, bro.
What's your opinion on dates, Brick
Borg? Do you think they're a waste of time? pretty much.
Do you think they are? Yeah. Well, obviously
I want a detox now anyways. So, I'm just
going to be going to the gym.
I'll just be going to the gym. uh
they are waste of time even if you are single
cuz you know you remember I told you
about life experience and you shouldn't
believe what you read on the internet
now you remember when you read things on
the internet yeah
and they say oh
you know if you go out and
you chat women up it works and but what
happens when you actually go out and you
chat with women, they pretend they got boyfriends.
What do you hear on internet about
dates? Oh, people go on dates. But do
you really know?
Huh? Do you really know why? Why do
women go on dates?
They do it to pass time.
Again, you need to learn from your own
experiences, bro. You can't read stuff
on the internet.
They go on dates to waste time and to
maybe to use you or to pass time,
not to get in a relationship with you.
Again, this is something you learn from life experience.
See, what you read on the internet is incorrect.
What you read on the internet is completely incorrect.
You know, they they tell so many lies online.
You only you only know stuff. Um
when you actually go out and do it, you
know, you do it yourself. I got free
numbers yesterday. No, they reply back.
They never reply back on [ __ ] Saturdays.
Yep, I did. So your experiences are all bad.
Yeah. But a lot No, but a lot of other
people have had bad experiences too
because my friends come back and say similar things
like it don't end with a date. Dates are [ __ ] up.
Because the problem with dates is you'll
never win with dates because with dates they're
it's one or the other.
You're normal, you get friend-zoned,
you're assertive, you creep them out. So
there's there's there's literally no way
to even win dates, I guess, unless you flirted prior.
Uh cuz I am, bro.
You don't need to worry why I'm worried.
Yeah, you won't have a good experience.
You need to leave the country. I'm gone
in two weeks.
Millions of people have relationships.
Good for them. There's millions of
people that are also single as well. But
that's what you need to do, bro. Nah,
not billions. There's loads of single
people out there. There is many, many,
many single people out there. Most of
the people I meet are single.
So, no, no, there there are more single
people than people in relationships. But
anyways, the thing is
the problem is with it is that that's
what it is anyways. So
yeah, you're not you're not going to get
good experiences, bro. If you've not had
good experiences in four years,
two weeks. Yeah. Two weeks. If you
haven't had if you ain't had if you
ain't had good experiences in [ __ ]
three, four [ __ ] years, you're not
going to get And this is the thing you
need to understand as well, practice.
It's been going on for years. It's not
been six months. It's been going on for years. Um,
that's quite worrying.
You know what I'm saying? So that's
that's that's what made me actually book
the whole thing. It's not what was
happening. It's how long it's been happening for.
And the problem is that comes with it.
So that's what it is, lad. So it doesn't
matter how I'm getting there, bro. What
route I'm getting there, but just know
I'm going to be there in it. So
yeah, it would never change this. This
will never change, bro.
Trust me, we live we live in the most
[ __ ] global city, too. So,
it will never change. Nah,
I'm all pissed off about it. I just
don't understand why people on the
internet made up stuff.
Nope. I will be no doing no live streams there.
I don't come on this community much
anymore, bro. I can't be bothered with
the creepiness of it all.
One second. But hold on. Someone send me
a voice now.
There are people going there.
That's him, matey. Yeah, that's the Indonesian fella.
That man's like, "Oh, no one would ever
give up in this country." You would.
I've got friends that have already given
up and they've not even they've not even
done it like 5% as me of me. So there's some people,
mate, I'm [ __ ] above others looking
and even I can't find anyone.
Got money, dress good, smell good. Yeah,
mate. I went out with two of my friends
yesterday and we all got nothing. Well,
I got numbers, they got nothing.
But I got nothing with the numbers. We
all look different. I'm not going to
show my other friend, but yeah, we all
went out and he we literally none of us
we got all the same [ __ ] They just
didn't get any numbers.
No, he's improved himself a lot, man.
I've not seen him for a very long time. So, uh
don't have a gay fellow. Don't have a gay friend.
That's how you know it's them because
you got three different people with
three different personalities and three different looks.
It doesn't really matter who's I'm I
need to go to the butchers. I'm [ __ ]
exhausted, bro. What the [ __ ] I don't
even bother to walk anywhere.
So scary. I hate this now cuz now I get
attached now. Cactus. I couldn't get
attached for two years.
I got attached to Australian easy for
about two days then.
But not now, you know. Yeah.
But what I mean is I mean
I mean no give up in your country.
That's yeah you'd give up in your
country. That's what I mean. You
wouldn't give up period. You just go to
other countries. But in terms of the a
westernized country, you would give up cuz obviously
but it's hard to when you live in London
and you can go out and you got the money
to go out. So
today trying to date Zippy
trying to date in this country. Zippy,
what the hell's bells? Yeah,
none of them members reply. [ __ ] me. Really? Damn.
None of them members replied. What the
[ __ ] bro? They never reply on Saturdays.
I think people make it seem a lot easier
than it actually is.
There's nothing easy about dating in
this country, mate. There's not one bit
of it that's easy.
Do you know what I find so mad is like
you get you go around Oxford Circus
and they're all stuck up. Like you can
see from their face, they've all got the
same attitude. They're all stuck up.
Do you think people from Reddit actually
leave the house?
You can't do right for doing wrong. I
don't even think I don't even think I'd
actually even go on a date again to be
honest with you. I don't even know
what's the point of me approaching cuz
I'm not going to even go on a date
anymore. So, what's the [ __ ] point?
I think dates are just stupid, bro. Cuz
they're not actual dates. They're not
they're not what they used to be. 198
1980s, you know, the 1980s. They're not actual dates.
They're not they're not what you would
think a date actually is.
Have I ever lost a phone? Nope. I got a
phone stolen though.
Yeah, is is a bit [ __ ] But maybe one
of them will reply later. Yeah.
You would have thought so, mate.
So, yeah, they're actual dates in the 80s, bro.
No, she done a [ __ ] on me. And this is
how you know it's not you as well
because if you notice right with dates
right you will do different things with
different people but the outcome is
still the same.
I gave her to my uh other Muslim friend.
Yeah. That's it. That's what I'm saying.
I know I wish I know you're mocking me.
I know you're taking a piss, but that's
the way it is. You know what I'm saying?
Like that is the way it is. Um,
says obviously I know you're taking a
piss on that, but I just gave her to my
Muslim friend, so you know, good to me.
She's I'm not Muslim and I'm not about
to be Muslim, so
uh I'm a pool clubber. Yeah, that's
literally what it is.
Australian, Albanian, Brazilian, even
people that you kiss. It's It's so mad
that you can even kiss someone and they
will still ghost you. that that's how
you know it is it is them because
you can do different things with
different people and the outcome would
always be the same
cuz the thing is you know that you're
and it can [ __ ] with your head as well.
That's the thing with this whole dating
thing. It can [ __ ] with your head
thinking oh what if I done this but then
even if you done that they still would
have wasted your time.
So, it's like you've never just think
about all the dates you've been on.
Like, I've been on four this year, but
one of them was me, obviously, cuz she
had no money and I weren't going to keep
buying her [ __ ]
And then you got somebody that travels
an hour away to see you yet says they
don't feel the vibe even though you're
above average looking. Makes sense,
isn't it? But, uh, just just with them
experiences, bro. I'm going to have to
stay in now until I get really bored
again. It is [ __ ] boring, bro.
You can't even be And you know what
makes me laugh is that I even accepted
friendship with this Muslim woman. Like
I actually accepted friendship.
Um obviously I could have tried to meet
her friends and I didn't do anything
wrong. Wasn't creepy and then they stole
reply back for a bit and then never
heard from them again. So, it's like
don't ever think it's you're doing this
wrong or you're doing this right. It
will always it will always end the same.
Doesn't matter what what you do or how
you do it.
You know what I'm saying? So,
yeah. And so, it makes me laugh when you
get people on Reddit that say, "Oh, you
should you just get female friends. You
mate, you can't even barely get a
conversation out of someone nowadays."
That's That's literally how bad it is.
You can barely get a conversation out
someone, let alone a [ __ ] friendship,
let alone a [ __ ] relationship, let
alone [ __ ] sex. How the [ __ ] are you
going to get that if you can't even get
a conversation out of someone at the
best of times? So,
I don't know, man. You think people on
Reddit are trolling when they give
dating advice, cactus, cuz we know that
America's got to be the worst place for it. America's
And they're all American.
This woman was 100 times better than
USA. Is he, bro? Oh my god. 100 times
better. You always get with these other
women and you think back and thinking,
"What the [ __ ] was you thinking?"
But then again, it shows you that even a
[ __ ] two out of [ __ ] 10 thinks
they're [ __ ] better than you.
But yeah, it is one date and that's it.
Cuz I can tell you, bro, I've been on
perfect dates before.
Perfect dates like casino and
everything. And then
I think they've got unrealistic expectations, bro.
Yeah, ball off, bro. You're boring.
And I think they've got really
unre unrealistic expectations.
This is someone I went on a date with. Uh,
who's holding hands, walking
across Lester Square?
Yeah, she's sexy, man. Look in real life as well.
Virgin boy couldn't get that. Virgin boy
couldn't get that. Cactus. Virgin boy
Oh, [ __ ] me.
What am I saying?
Yeah, things are the same in India.
I was just talking to someone from
India. It's the same here, bro. Even
with these Indian women,
it's hard this country, bro.
You can't even go out Saturdays. There's
point just going out Saturdays, bro. I
just stick to Thursdays. I I don't even
Bro, the [ __ ]
was it? Was it okay? Not really.
I went out with two of my friends, but I
started off alone.
Do you want me to do the video? Do you
want me to put a video up where I'm
showing me alone? Um,
Cactus, I'll do it just for you.
Um, no. It wasn't okay, bro.
Cuz my card stopped working. That put me
into stress and then I couldn't
uh they then they they said they had a
boyfriend. These women said they had a
Yeah, they all said they have boyfriends. So,
it's not the best, is it?
Yeah, you must do, bro. You must do. I
have a lot of people that fancy me.
Oh, that's nice. Yeah.
Go to Go to the butchers.
Going to the butchers.
Oh well, cactus. Just another one to add
to this [ __ ] connection. All right.
40y old self projector. Oh well,
another one to add to the [ __ ] collection. Oh.
Yeah, I need to go back to the gym and
give up for a few weeks, bro. This is [ __ ] up.
Yeah, I just had McDonald's. Yeah. See,
I think that's got to be the best like
looking person I've ever had a date
with, you know.
I actually couldn't believe it. So, I'm
I'm expecting them to look like they did
in their WhatsApp picture. I was like,
"Oh my god, what the [ __ ]
They're actually [ __ ]
They're actually penguing
to think. Is there anyone else? Nah,
bro. All of my dates never really looked
good to be honest. I just got 20 nuggets.
I'm trying to think of any other ones on. No,
the Brazilian one was okay, but nowhere
near as good as her.
Nowhere near as good as her, bro.
I don't approach at the gym.
Nope. Not Muslim.
So having this vape here. Yeah,
I was vaping in Oxford Circus.
Might put a video up for RJ. Yeah.
Oh, she's paying, bro. Nope.
Do I tell my dates about YouTube? Yeah,
all of them. Yeah,
I tell all of my dates about YouTube.
Yeah, all the time, bro. Yeah,
this is wrong. Hold on.
Why you need breaks from this stuff,
bro? Cuz it'll give you a mental breakdown.
I don't really come on YouTube much anymore. Cuz uh yeah,
I was giving you a stupid answer because
you was asking me a stupid question. Why
are you asking me if I ask my dates about YouTube?
Man, that's the most stupid thing to
ask. Obviously, I would never tell
anyone about YouTube. You got like brain
damage or something?
I drunk a lot of beer yesterday. Yeah, I
drunk beer. Only stick to beer now cuz I
don't I don't get the hangover as well as much. Yeah.
Yeah. Sorry. I don't really come on much
any ignore you. I just don't really come
on anymore. No, there's no point coming
on. You just just hear repeaters right
now. It's just it's just it's just
creepy. Like it's it's creepy, bro. So
creepy. No, it is. It is. It is creepy.
It is. It is. It is creepy as [ __ ]
I still I still get your notifications and stuff.
I only go live
as I can't even be asked to be honest.
Yeah, it's boring, isn't it? It is
boring. I'll probably go live in a bit
or something. But are you still are you
still working out?
Yeah, I'm still working out. Yeah. No, I
got a vape. It was 8 quid.
So, you're fing though, are you?
Yeah. Quite fun. You can't even handle it.
I bought it when I was on a date, Monty.
I bought the vape when I was on a date.
From Australia. Yeah.
From Australia. What? No.
We're always from Australia. Yeah.
I care to [ __ ] off.
What about you? [ __ ] 100.
Why you used to like her even back in
the day, Monty?
Okay. Yeah, I know I did.
Why do I say [ __ ]
on the toilet?
Why do I say [ __ ] me? Because I think
it's funny. Got a problem with that.
You're funky. You peed yet? No, you're
You're [ __ ] funky, man. No, you are.
You don't know what a fun [ __ ] means.
Money, if you don't stop, I'm going to
come over there. I'm not gay yet, but
I'm going to come and [ __ ] you, man. If
you keep talking [ __ ]
you can't even [ __ ] your way out of a [ __ ] woman.
Come and [ __ ] you. You keep pissing me
off. Yeah. Yeah.
What do you mean I'm pissing you off?
Huh? What do you mean I'm pissing you off?
I'm joking, man. Well, I get my watch,
bro. Who is Why did you let that guy in
your paddle, bro? That paddle. Your
paddle, bro. Do you know that guy? That
one from London. Which one?
The one from London. I can't remember.
They all come up when they're on my
panel for some reason. I don't know why
they It's just me on my own. Nobody
comes up. Only one person. That's fish, man. Yeah.
Up on my panel. They all [ __ ] fly up
on my panel for some reason.
He's a [ __ ] bro. I told him to
and he said, "Oh, I'll see you when I
see you." You're not going to see me
when you see me. Do you know how big
London is? You wouldn't even bump into
the same person, bro. Unless you're like
around the same area. I said go square.
Wait, hold on, hold on, hold on a
minute, buddy. Hold on a minute, buddy.
This person said, "Didn't you say you
was off YouTube now? Can't stay away,
can you?" But hold on. Why are you on
YouTube then? Same same question goes to them, though,
hang on. YouTube's everybody's
platforms. So, you people don't on it. Yeah.
So, use on YouTube. Same same goes to
you. So, why use on YouTube?
Don't talk about questions. We need the
same as you.
Yeah, someone said Monty shut your
mouth. Someone said Monty shut your
mouth. They're weirdos, isn't it?
My mouth's always open to you, you little clown.
I've just been busy, man. I don't know
what to mean. What?
Yeah, I just don't come here much anymore.
Faked. I can't be asked with it.
It's [ __ ] creepy. The darkest secret
you've got, PJ. The darkest secret
you've ever got.
When you used to groom me on the PlayStation, you sick.
You sick bastard. You That's You told me
that was our little secret.
No, you proper sick bastard. You Yeah,
they Yeah, they did. Yeah, they did.
They did think that.
What did you say, Money?
Yeah, proper shaking. Hey, buddy. Listen
to this, Monty. You absolute bacon.
You are [ __ ] bacon.
[ __ ] you [ __ ] edge like a [ __ ]
flying [ __ ] sauce, your dick. You
[ __ ] up. Yeah.
Yep. You got a [ __ ] egg brain, man. talking.
Hey Monty, you even used to say on
PlayStation that I'm your favorite.
You'll never be my favorite.
No, I was you
that that TJ Hooker had eyes for you,
mate. Is it? No, he had eyes for you,
not me. He never likes me. He likes you in it.
He punched you, not me.
Buddy, buddy, you used to laugh at the
thingy, didn't you? Um, the bungle thing. What bungalippy
the zippy thing? No.
Yeah, you did. Monty never laughs, you know. I
You see Monty? Monty never laughs. Monty
never laughs, man. Yeah, PG.
Why do you never laugh?
What do you mean?
Have I got any mates in real life? Yeah,
I've got mates in real life. I'll show
you me and my friend if you want. Yeah,
he's mate in real life. If I tell you he
has he has not and he uses it every day
on his norm when he's talking himself
off. Why these people obsessed Why are
these people obsessed with people having no friends?
Cuz they ain't got no friends.
It's the same [ __ ] every day. So which one?
Put the picture back up. Put the picture
back up. Okay.
So, which one sock stick first? The one
on the right or the one on the left?
When I only do it after you uh
um uh after you have a sword fight with
Hey, Monty, you know you know when these
people listen listen Monty, you know
when these people project you, I don't
think they're even doing it on purpose.
Not in reject. No. Yeah, but I'm saying
I'm saying I'm saying that they they I
think their disabilities confuse
themselves with you.
What among you? Yeah. No, their No,
their disability like it makes them
confuse themselves with you. So, they're
actually talking about themselves. You
get it? No, they do that every day. They
do that every day. That's why you're on
YouTube for [ __ ] 20 years.
Yeah. They're saying that have I spent
my pip. Yeah, my pip. I didn't know that
PJ if you go to shorts. Yeah. Yeah. On
your videos. So if you go to shorts and
then if you go to [ __ ] there's
something like a little bar thing next
to writing. If you click onto that bar
thing, you can scroll down and then you
can see how old these people are.
I've seen it. Some of these accounts are
like 15 years old. Monty. Yeah. Some of
the these people like in the 50s to 60s, my lad. Yeah.
Mine [ __ ] on that. It's only a couple of
young ones in here like ourselves. Me,
you, Matt, at that age anyways.
Yeah. Obviously, I'm not saying that I'm
young cuz I'm [ __ ] middle age now.
You're a crafty [ __ ]
What a car do when it comes to it. Huh?
Can you pick your ear? PJ. Yeah.
Just noticing it.
Yeah. Go on. Do you think Do you think
these people cold approach?
Only what these can catch is [ __ ] cold. Really, buddy?
Yeah, really. That's all these
concussions are called. Do you remember
you always ask me, buddy? Why did you
get me into this shitty community in it?
Yeah, but why did you get me into the [ __ ] community?
Did I thought it was going to change?
What? You thought it was going to change?
Yeah. Five years later, same repeaters. [Laughter]
Why has not been 5 years though?
It has been 5 years. That's the [ __ ]
thing. It's been six years coming now.
Co was around about this time a year.
16. It's been six [ __ ] years already. Sing fears.