Wow.
That r is still rigged. That was the
first time in like 3 weeks. Still
rigged. Still avoiding every number.
I still seeking out that loser. [ __ ]
hell. I would have thought it would have
changed by now, bro. Shees Christ. [ __ ] dead.
Yeah, it never changes, bro.
Same old [ __ ] that people blame the
house for. And it's nothing to do with that [ __ ]
There's some centipedes in this [ __ ]
It's nothing to do with house edge. I'm
surprised that [ __ ] always gets a blame
for it. Now you know house edge. No way
in a million years. Have you seen that
in five spins you never hit a tier
number? No. Don't force it. It's fixed. Yeah.
Bro, this guy is trying to get my lot my
[ __ ] loss. I swear to God
with it. Same been ping with it. They
say that it's gambling, but they can't
be gambling because any gambler would
win. Anyone that gamles even every month
eventually anyone that puts money in will win.
You can't lose that many times.
Bad luck comes to an end. Good luck
Nothing lasts forever. Have you ever
heard that saying nothing lasts forever,
right? Just calm down.
Just gambling. So they say
so secular slot says with his fake money.
Oh [ __ ] One second.
That is that okay?
So secular not says with his fake money
with his old casino buns.
Yeah, that guy uses fake money.
Oh [ __ ] But yeah, I got definitely use this money. [ __ ] this.
You don't even get a fair game of it. [Music]
just went through the [ __ ] eyeballs
through the blood eyeballs cuz Tier is a
section on the wall on the on the wheel.
Don't forget about it. Don't forget
about Tiier, buddy.
But somehow when you put your money on
the table, it seems to play so different
every single time. It makes you wonder,
doesn't it? This is why we don't do this [ __ ] anymore.
anymore because this exact reason.
because it's just rigged. Why would you
put some money into something that's
[ __ ] rigged? A little bit pissed off
today, so I fancy doing it. But
you don't even get a fair game.
Literally, you don't even get a fair
[ __ ] game. It's as [ __ ]
You thought you go and fix.
That's what I say.
But I talk about this gambling stuff,
bro. People should know about it.
They should know how rigged it is.
Well, you can't even get mad at it
anymore to be honest. It's just funny.
You really think you can actually get
mad at this [ __ ] anymore? You know,
you can't even get mad at anyone.
How can you get mad at something that's just rigged?
But what do you actually want to do?
Just smash the [ __ ] house up or
something? Bro, you're [ __ ] crazy.
I try that instead of going out cuz I'm
going out for two weeks.
Seems to love that zero section. It
seems to love that zero section.
[ __ ] loves it like a [ __ ]
Jesus Christ. It seems to love that zero
section that roulette. I just put 250 on
it. Oh, I'm just eating some curry.
Yeah, I just put some 250 on the roulette.
Same old, same old.
But secular slop says that it's a form
of entertainment. So he says yeah, you
do realize there's other there's other
areas on the real Grezy, but it seems to
keep attacking that left side of zero.
It seems to love that area when I put my
money on the table. It seems to love it
like a pedo. Like it literally literally
seems to love it like a dirty nons. You
never see any other numbers. Never see
any other numbers by that zero section.
What a load of old bollocks considering
there you do five [ __ ] spins.
You know, sometimes we do silly things, eh? Well,
it's all just a bit of fun. Hey [Music]
chooses fake money telling me bro he does
he shows no emotion he seems to think it's entertaining
entertaining I think it's quite
depressing me I don't know about you
greensy but is that supposed to be entertaining
so what did you lose £250 okay
um am I supposed to be entertained
I'm not very entertained. I'm more
entertained about this.
Got my bills paid, check electric, check.
My money, check. Damn responsibility.
Uh, yeah. Check. Oh,
what's going on, Kevin?
What's going on, Kevin?
That's these questions that need to be
asked. Is it crazy?
No, I just find that session, but I felt
like doing something dafted. 250. Guess
what numbers come out again? The pedo section.
Pedo pattern. That's new section. Oh, it never changes.
Yeah, never change, bro. remember
the Pedo Patterson area and they didn't
let me uh it didn't let me rebet as well
when they went to that area.
You think it's so mad how that area
don't come out once.
Have you noticed how whenever you put
money on the table you don't get one T
number? Have you noticed that?
Second slot says it's a form of
entertainment. A form of entertainment
says, but I don't really see what's so
entertaining to play something that's
rigged, which is why we hardly do it
anymore. Last time was a month ago. Yeah.
Yep. It goes in hiding. It's [ __ ]
ripped as [ __ ] If you look at a normal
wheel, Yeah. You remember what that
scoop used to say? Oh, they don't need
to cheat. They got the house. Well, they
[ __ ] do, mate. Whether they need to
or not, they [ __ ] well do because if
you go on a normal roulette table,
right, where people are not placing
bets, you see it's so random. Tier 00
tier, you you see a uh a pattern and as
soon as you put money on the table,
completely different. Have you noticed that
it is rigged? 100% it is rigged.
I'm probably playing higher than
probably a lot of people to be fair. But
yeah, that's definitely rigged. 100%
that's rigged, man. Don't need to be a
loser over 250. It's facts. If you like
the truth, grow the [ __ ] up. area. Hey, me. Very dark. Yeah.
Oh well. You win some, you lose some. So
they say seven, eight months counting.
Nope. I'm done, bro. You're not going to
get me gambling. That's my monthly [ __ ]
done. I'm not doing it no more.
One of above minimum.
No, I'm good, buddy. I'm all right.
I only done that because I'm not going
out for a couple of weeks. So, where's
the date? 15. Yeah, I'm not going out
for a bit. So, no.
[ __ ] weak as [ __ ]
He can keep calling all he wants, mate.
I'm not doing it.
I'm done. No,
but you never know till you try.
I'm just just going to be in the gym now.
Maybe, maybe not. I'm not talking about
my life on here.
I'm just talking about gambling.
I'm not even going to be on here
tomorrow anyways. Sy you spastics.
This community creeps me the [ __ ] out. I
don't really come here anymore. It's
just I've got nothing better to do today.
Nah, it's creepy. This community creep
gy is very very It's not a community. We
need to stop calling it a community cuz
it's not a community. It's a place for
the spastics. It's not even It's not
even big enough to be a community. It's
not a community, bro. communities are
big and they and they've actually got a
point to prove.
Yeah. Anyways, I'm not talking about her. Anyways,
and I didn't let the others disappear.
They disappeared on their own will. So,
get your facts right.
They disappeared. They disappeared on
their own will.
Yes. Don't say to me, "Don't let her
disappear like the rest." They
disappeared on their own will, mate. No
one made them disappear.
I probably won't be here again, to be
honest. Oh, well, it doesn't matter now, does it?
No, none of them. I saw USA put up a new picture. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Guess what? I can get somebody better
than her [ __ ] ugly boyfriend with
ugly tattoos. I'm better than her and
her boyfriend. [ __ ] a lot of them. You
know what I'm saying? Music. I'm better
than her and her boyfriend. I've got
more money than her and her boyfriend.
How's about that? Yeah.
I just purch 100%. Yeah,
this one's perfect, but I don't think
I'll be meeting her again.
But yeah, she's [ __ ] perfect,
mate. You ain't got no choice. If they
don't want to meet you again, they're
not going to meet you again. So you
[ __ ] will let her go cuz it's not
[ __ ] up to you. If they don't want to
meet you again,
I'm not explaining it again.
I can't explain it again. I've already
told you why people go on dates. The
past time. I'm not getting into it
again. Once you get yourself some life
experience, buddy, you'll understand.
[ __ ] I'm vegetable for a couple of
weeks. So, that's 250 out. 250 save. So, So yeah,
you want to [ __ ]
Oh, what the [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm not going out for a couple of
weeks anyways now. I need to get into
this gym [ __ ] So yeah,
but yeah, if she says she doesn't want
to meet again, she doesn't want to meet
again if if she does turn around and say
that. So you have to let her go. She's
[ __ ] perfect as well, man. [ __ ] hell.
And you got USA Easy who's like a
[ __ ] two out of 10. What the [ __ ] was
I thinking, mate? A [ __ ] two out of
10 thinking they're [ __ ] better than
me. Are you mad?
But I won't be out now for two weeks. So
I get that all again to be honest. So [Music]
way over that be
I mean all dating is a waste of time in
this country in it. stop. So yeah,
boy must have been so jealous, bro.
You know what I'm saying?
Virgin boy must have been so jealous.
He must have been [ __ ] hitting you
know who, mate. Yeah, [ __ ] me.
I'm just fed up, me
to be fed up, is it? Nope.
It's not nice to be fed up, is it? [ __ ] up.
I think when he finally loses his
virginity, I I'll give him a hug and say
congratulations. You buy them and pop
it. You buy me pop that cherry in. I've
noticed that with this community, right?
They can give it, but they can't take
it. Have you noticed that? They can give
but they can't take
when he gets a big mark for them. It's
the boys in blue, man.
Boys in blue.
Yeah, the boys.
Yeah. I want to give up. I don't find
anyone on her phone then. Yep.
It's pain, bro.
You look so different than like
the best day I've ever been on. That's
that's for sure. But
just another one to uh
just another one to add to the [ __ ]
collection as I would say.
She kind of looks like one of the hot escorts.
I'm fed up now.
I just wanted a little adrenaline rush.
Do some bed. Yeah.
Let me message this person. Yeah.
You imagine that?
I'm fed up, mate. I'm [ __ ] fed up.
See, now all I can think about is that
250. You see, this is how you know it's
not a form of entertainment.
You know what that [ __ ] Scottish
pricks is from Glasgow. Ain't a form of
entertainment, bro. I just gave you a
prime example. Food have any bills paid,
borrowed enough money, you know?
So, what does that mean? It shouldn't
bother you then. So, you've done all
that. Okay. So, what is it supposed to
just not bother you now then?
It doesn't get me angry anymore cuz I'm
used to it. But
I think we got bigger problems going on
in the world now.
Much bigger problems, bro. Yep.
It don't bother me anymore like it used
to. I don't really do it anymore.
Oh, she is sexy, bro.
Oh my [ __ ] god.
She is hot, bro.
I'm so glad people can't get their hands
on this one, you know. Yeah,
the Indonesian fell.
You know what? I like him, man. Because
he spent he spent the day with me on my birthday.
What do you mean you didn't get email?
Bro, I just emailed you. You [ __ ]
Yep. They weren't big big, but
they were big enough.
Yeah, I don't think I'll be there again
though. But yeah,
I've never been on.
I'm shocked she actually met me to be
honest cuz I met her in the weather spoons.
I just sent it in. I thought [ __ ] it.
I don't think she wants to meet again,
you [ __ ] idiot.
Obviously, if I don't meet her again,
it's not going to be me. It's going to
be her. Is it
BB? That says B.
Yeah, obviously it wouldn't be me, would
it? Bad laughing. Yeah. So,
yeah. Actually, the thing is when you go
on so many bad dates, you expect the
dates to be bad and you do things to
ensure they're not wasting your time,
which can come which which can come
across as weird.
But then we all know if you act normal
on dates, they just waste your time
anyways. So, you can't do right for
doing wrong because you're either normal
and they just waste your time anyways,
like the Pakist.
So there's there's literally like no
there's literally like no in the middle.
Yeah, there's literally like no in the middle.
So I'll be going to the gym straight for
two weeks anyways. Two weeks. Three week
two weeks. Three weeks. Um
two weeks, three weeks.
Get that money back. So yeah,
went on with that Ukrainian cactus.
Do you remember that? Do you remember
that while I went on with that Ukrainian
with the casino?
uh the money and [ __ ] Do you remember
that? I remember that time. There was no
kissing. There was no flirting.
There was nothing but good vibes and
they still wasted your time. So it's like,
do you understand? Look at that
Pakistani girl. [ __ ] went quiet after 5
hours. The [ __ ] bro? So
again, unless you go on dates or you've
been on a lot of dates, you you
literally just won't understand. I was
speaking to a guy about this. So,
so yeah, remember that one? The Ukrainian one?
That's a Gore.
So even if you do like everything right,
yeah, they'll still make up some excuse
not to not to see you again. You understand?
And then when it happens, enough enough
then you'll be like, "Oh, it's just
another day. It's just another you know what?
Yeah, that that exactly the Indian that
was an excuse. That was just that was
just going on dates to pastime.
Yeah, that was just going on dates to
pass time. The Indians listen that's
that's one that's that's one to pastime.
There's been a few of them that beat past time.
So yeah, the Ukrainian
cuz I'm thinking of dates where I've
been completely normal on
and they've still wasted your time.
They've still wasted just they've still
wasted your time.
You understand me? Do you understand me, bro?
Oh, they've still done some madness.
But yeah, I won't be going out for a
couple of weeks anyway. So,
just save my money. I think I spent a
lot anyway. So,
you don't get into a relationship.
Now, you got to understand from my point
of view, I'm doing things to ensure that
I'm not wasting my time. So, she was
like, "Oh, yeah, you was asking this and
you was asking that, but I'm asking this
stuff so I don't think I'm wasting my
time again. You don't understand when
you've been on so many dates that just
waste your time." You have it ingrained
that, oh, let's ensure
we don't waste our time again.
I don't care, bro. No one cares about
him. Stop bringing it on my channel.
stop bringing creepy weird drama on my
channel. So anyways, cactus, that's
basically what it is. So like um yeah,
and it's not even that. I mean, I guess
they could meet you again, but the thing
is even if they meet you again, it wouldn't progress
cuz there's Do you remember the Albanian
one that I kissed? There's been people
I've actually kissed and made out with
and then they've just ghosted, which
doesn't make any sense. They were sat
there snogging you for like an hour. So
this person might have been genuine, but
it's fairly unlikely that all of the
people that you've been on date with
this. So this person so happens to be
someone that's genuine. And I said
basically, you know, if we lose this
person that we are [ __ ] we are
actually [ __ ] now because we have to
do this all again. And I'm not doing
Yeah. I'm going away soon. So that's it.
So yeah, sorry.
How can you not find it again?
Sorry. What did you say? Work up. You
should try something else. There is nothing else.
Approaching is literally the only way.
So I wonder what would have happened. So
if she kept meeting, it probably would
have just progressed into nothing, I'm guessing.
Well, no, it would have progressed into nothing.
It's not the 1980s. Again, what you see
online and what you experience, they're
two different things.
That's the whole point of a life
experience. You see, I'm sorry.
I need to get a lecture today about what
I've done either. So
yeah, two numbers replied but then they stopped.
I can't be bothered anymore. I'm only
going to make some money on my days off
to be fair. But
along I don't even want to go back to it
after that, bro. I feel like if this
person doesn't meet again, I don't want
to go back to it. I don't want to go
back to this. I think you made your
point in this country. You made your
point more than enough [ __ ] times.
You know what I'm saying? But it's like
I've made my point more than enough times.
What is that? Is that the [ __ ] internet?
One second, please.
I am trying something else. I'm leaving the country.
M these [ __ ] are [ __ ] me around
today. I just emailed them [ __ ] two times.
It would have been too easy, mate. Is it?
So if I stay with that person now,
that'll be too easy, mate.
I've learned I've actually got a lot of patience. Yep.
Just need a break, mate. That's what I need.
What's your opinion, Cactus?
I just said to him, "Oh, we should meet
again for this." Right. I had to like
actually I had to kind of play victim.
So, it's all backwards. It's all It's
all [ __ ] But what what I got from it
is you just don't just don't take advice
online when it comes to dating.
Like, if I could give anyone advice
right now, I'd be like, "Well, you want
to date in this country, you play at
your own risk. Dating apps rigged
against men. Approach women. Don't
pretend they got boyfriend. You have to
deal with all this madness before you
even find anyone. Dates, most people go
on dates to pass time. But if you read
up on this stuff, Cactus, you never see
it. No one ever says this stuff. You You
learn it for yourself. So So
yeah, I don't get attached anymore. So
remember Aussie is he
shouldn't feel bad though. They've done
this [ __ ] load of times. But
I [ __ ] [ __ ] made out with
people and squeeze their [ __ ] boobs
and then they've done the same [ __ ] and
they were touching me at the same time. So
yeah, one minute, buddy. I need to do something.
I'm trying to close this account down. Anyways,
I won't be on again. I won't be on again
after today. It's just that it was Sunday.
You haven't restricted my account, you [ __ ]
Why are you saying you have?
They have not restricted my accounts.
One second. I'm not talking about
YouTube money. One second, bro.
One second, brother.
Yeah, they blocked me access.
That's good. I don't want to play your
stupid freak games again.
Yeah. So, if she doesn't if she doesn't
meet again, then I'm [ __ ]
Basically, I am actually [ __ ]
She's [ __ ] sexy as well, man. It's
the bad thing about it.
Here's what it is, mate.
Had enough, mate. It's [ __ ] had enough.
So, what you're trying to tell me now,
I'm going to find someone that's better
looking. No way, bro. No way.
It's actually just completely [ __ ]
with my head. This whole dating thing.
You know what? Right. This is actually
the first time in a long time I've
actually had a break. I don't get a
I want to do some uh security work soon, buddy. Right.
Let me try again to see if they've
definitely closed it.
I wanted to make some babies, man.
wanted to raise some babies.
Yeah, that neighbor tried starting on
the um cactus.
This neighbor tried starting on me
kind of the other day when I went to my
mom's. It was proper awkward
just walk past him, ignored him.
Yeah, that's proper orphan, mate.
My mom wasn't picking up her phone, so I
thought she was dead. So, I went around
at 6:00 in the morning and uh Yeah, it's
proper dodge, man.
I said I ain't coming around here anymore. It's weird. It's creepy.
Yeah. One second, buddy. Just one second.
You know what? I can't be bothered with
it, Cactus. Do you know what it is, bro?
Like, I'm not scared of anyone. Believe
in me. I'm not scared of anyone. I even
had a woman give me a dirty look. But I
just ignored it. It's not even about
that. It's I've got nothing to prove. I
ain't got no point to prove, bro.
He saying, "Oh, come and say something
to me now." I was like, "You I saying
like he's the one that was saying
stuff." So I just walked past him. Like
you are literally the one that was
running your mouth. Yeah. And we've seen
what you wrote on YouTube. So I just
walked past him.
But I and my mom lives there and [ __ ]
so I just ignore it, bro. I'm too old
for all of this [ __ ] mate. I just want
a peaceful life.
Know what I'm saying?
So yeah, if I don't uh if I can't meet
her again, I'm [ __ ] basically.
You know, I'm too old to start fighting
people in neighborhoods, mate. [ __ ] that.
It's just ridiculous.
What I understand is like this was eight
months ago. So why the [ __ ] is are these
people still salty?
Like this woman Uh,
this woman broke her neck to look at me, mate.
She broke her neck to look at me, bro.
She saw the look she gave me. What the [ __ ] bro?
After 8 months and you're still salty.
Does these people have nothing going on, mate?
Then I'm out here. I get my [ __ ] heart broken.
You don't be [ __ ] quiet, mate.
I don't know. [ __ ] hell.
But we always get led to this [ __ ] don't we? Cactus.
Yeah, it's crazy, bro.
Oh, that Somalian one was messaging me earlier. Cactus,
just [ __ ] off. [ __ ] the lottery, mate.
It's absolutely [ __ ] the lot here.
Let me try and deposit £10. See if it
Where's my card?
Oh, I left it downstairs.
That's what I'm saying now, bro. [ __ ]
the lot of you, mate.
Going to go to the gym for a couple of
weeks and just say, you know what? [ __ ] the lawyer.
You know, I should have done that a long
time ago, mate. Should
have done that a long time ago.
After USA is he in it, Cactus? Yeah.
Well, she had No, only today she
started. [ __ ] off. I just want to be
left alone. I just need to be left alone
for like a month.
I just want to be left alone, bro. You
know what I mean?
Why is it letting me log in?
Yeah, I'm not interested. No, what
happened was she tried coming back, but
I said, "I can't deal with your mood
swings." So, I just blocked her.
So, I just blocked her. I said, "Don't
bother unblocking me again." If you
block me, cuz I'm not beating you again.
[ __ ] all of them in it.
Yeah. I mean, this was actually like the last draw.
No, but obviously I'm giving up now for
a long time. So, um
I won't get the mood swings cuz I'm just
going to be going gym and [ __ ]
I hate it, bro.
Just another one to add to the [ __ ] collection.
What do you think?
Yeah, I got two numbers that reply back. Well,
yep. I've had to deal with her as well, mate.
I messaged some of these women anyways,
so if they want to come out next week,
we can go out. If not, then I'm I'm I'm
done with it, mate. But
maybe I need to go to the gym and get really muscularly
then people start taking me back.
You know what I'm saying?
Do you want to see USA Izzy's new picture?
I need to do me for a little bit now,
bro. I've got stuff to do, man. Yeah,
now fun. We've had more. We've had more
than enough fun now. [ __ ]
Instagram pictures because the last one
was stinking sad. No,
it's not about the money, you know. I
can go out every week. It's about you
need a break from it because it can it
just can it can just get too much, you know.
Oh, USA Isabelle. What?
Look at USA Isabelle.
She still got her boobies, don't she? Cactus.
Ah, USA is about [Music] Nuts. Yeah.
Say good man. Yeah.
Actually 12 days. Yeah.
What a life.
I got these [ __ ] from YouTube
trying to [ __ ] follow me on Instagram, mate.
Trying to [ __ ] follow me.
Yeah. If anyone wants to be fed up about
it, it' be me, man.
I might go out make some money tomorrow. Yeah.
Go and make some money.
Don't even close your account. What the [ __ ]
Reck on purpose as well. [Music]
89 pound a week.
Yeah, I would have to do something
tomorrow, bro. Thank you.
We could probably a day.
I'll probably just come off social
media, I think, for a little bit.
This is not good, bro. This is not good.
Going to go gym at 8:00 in the morning
tomorrow. What about eight?
Yeah, try and get it for about eight. I think
I need to keep myself like really
occupied cuz I'm going to go mad if I don't Fire. [Music] Okay.
Let me see what is said. [Music]