Here
we go. The next workout. I need to go
[ __ ] gym today and I can't be [ __ ]
Damn, this country sure is depressing.
But I'll be out soon anyways, so that's
a good thing. I won't have to deal with
this [ __ ] ever again.
That's the thing.
Remember I told you about ending up.
These are all self-reflectors on YouTubes.
These are all self-reflected [ __ ]
That's the first That's the first start,
bro. It's the first step.
I'm [ __ ] exhausted. Oh my god, I'm
knackered. What the [ __ ]
Even though I'm surprised that it
started snowing again.
Oh, this country sure is depressing.
Well, I'm going to have this tea in
Belgium, I think. Yeah,
with some salmon salmon and some
milkshake and [ __ ]
cuz it's going to be very hard to get
back into if you don't go now. I said
fresh start Monday. So, yeah.
Yeah, it's going to show is depressing,
man. Show is depressing.
told you about that detox now as well. So,
how was you?
It's just a cycle. I'm just saying I'm
mad about this. It's a big cycle, isn't it? Big cycle.
I won't be out for the longest time
possible to be honest when I even come back.
It's the same [ __ ] every week. That's
why people need to take breaks from it
cuz it's the same [ __ ] every week. You
know what I mean? It's not It's not even
It's not even financial.
It's not even It's not even to do with
finances. It's not even that.
It's just [ __ ] boring. I'm saying
it's the same [ __ ] every week. [ __ ] me,
bro. What the hell?
It's [ __ ] boring. I like hearing
about it. I said to my friend as well, I
don't want to hear about this anymore.
You know, he told me on approach on the
train. I was like, bro, I don't want to
hear it anymore. I don't want to hear
it. Simple. It just pisses me off
listening about it, but I don't even
like hearing about it, you know.
That's funny. That roulette yesterday.
Zero section. Zero section. Zero
section. Well, at least they closed my
account down anyways.
I don't even have the motiv I don't even
have motivation to go to gym now, bro.
To be honest with you,
I'm going to do it, but I got no
motivation to lie.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] [ __ ] the country, bro. Boring. [ __ ] boring.
Just till you leave.
That's what I said. You know, you know,
[ __ ] bustles are probably going to stop now.
Yeah. Where are we now? Monday this
week. [ __ ] that.
Going out to experience the same thing,
to hear the same [ __ ] They get the same
numbers that reply. Stop replying. You
suggest meeting up. No thanks. I'm good.
It's the same old in this country. And
to be honest with you, people shouldn't
even be encouraging you to try here
anymore. You waste enough time and
enough [ __ ] money. It will never change.
cuz I look I was having a conversation
with this guy on Instagram last night
and it was it's like bro it doesn't matter
what the [ __ ] it is a dance class a
[ __ ] gym a [ __ ] bar they're the
same [ __ ] everywhere you know I'm
saying I was saying this to this woman
in [ __ ] New Zealand as well
you call people that go to Thailand
losers back home you know who I think
are the real losers people that sit
there and disrespect themselves dealing
with these entitled women day in and day
out. They're the real losers to have
that to have that tolerance level. To be
honest, they're the [ __ ] real losers.
They're the real ultra losers for them
to put themselves through that every
[ __ ] day or every week, how however
when people go out.
I can't even be bothered to go to the
[ __ ] gym, bro.
I can't be [ __ ] Listen,
so tired tired of all this [ __ ] Not not
literally, you know. So,
just fed up. Fed up my life. Uh, same
old, same old. I need to go to the gym
today, but I'll probably be [ __ ] but
I have to otherwise I won't be able to
get into it.
Lost 250 yesterday on roulette, but hey,
it's just gambling. E, so they say.
So, a young man from Glasgow says by the
name of Kevin,
he's just gambling.
Gamble responsibly. That's what he says.
And even when you gamble responsibly,
it's just the same old [ __ ] Anyways,
you can only guess what numbers come
out. You can only guess what numbers
come out yesterday. It was the same old
numbers. It's the same old numbers,
mate. You know, same old Pedo Patterson
numbers. I don't gamble anymore. I just
fancied it cuz I just pissed off with the women.
I was just pissed off with the women.
So, I thought, "Fuck it." Before I
closed my account, let me try a quick
250. Same old [ __ ] How people say that
ain't rigged is beyond me. Well, it was
a month since I last done it. They That
is beyond me. How people can try and say
that ain't [ __ ] rigged. They are.
They They've got something wrong with
their head, bro. That is 100% rigged.
Look, there's no there's not one tier
number that comes out the whole spins
that I done. All it is is 297. They're
the only numbers that come out. It's f
of course it's [ __ ] rigged, man.
Don't be so naive. You know,
there's somebody I went on a date with.
Probably won't be going on another date with them.
But yeah, it's the same old [ __ ] I went
out Saturday. It was the same old.
Yeah. Thailand's in calling, bro. two weeks.
I think I won't even try again when I
come back to be honest. It's boring,
mate. It is [ __ ] boring. It is. Oh my
god. Having to go out in that [ __ ] heat.
And you know, you get like people that
scoop that say it's the house edge. It
ain't no [ __ ] house edge. You can't
miss that many times. And I'm not
talking about it anymore cuz it's
boring. But I'm just saying it ain't no
house edge. It's [ __ ] And I don't
do it anymore.
I don't do it anymore. That was the
first time in a month. I don't do it anymore.
So, for that exact reason, cuz it's the
same old [ __ ] It's [ __ ] boring. It's
rigged. Just like with women, it's the
same old [ __ ] Same old boring. Same old
boring. That's never going to change.
And you know what makes me laugh, right?
When people say, "Take a break." Now,
that advice doesn't really make any
sense, though, because when you go back
into it, it's just going to be the same
[ __ ] Oh [ __ ] man. My fault.
It's not going to change. When you go
back in, when you take a break and you
go back, it will be exactly the same old
again. It's the same like a drug addict.
It's the same like a drug addict going
back to drugs after 3 months. It's ridiculous.
There's no like you take a break from
dating. There's you literally have to
leave the country. There's no there's
nothing else, you know? There's no such
thing as a break.
A break is
is not to go back to the same old that
has no chance of [ __ ] changing. That
doesn't even make sense.
So, I won't be out this week. Simple.
Um, I'm not deal with this [ __ ] anymore.
It's boring. It's [ __ ] boring, man.
[ __ ] I think we done every week for a
long time as well, to be honest.
So, there's no there's no taking breaks.
You need to leave. That's it. So,
it's never going to change. Even if you
go on dates, it's just going to be a
waste of time. It's never going to change here.
I probably sleep all day to be honest.
Once I go to the gym, I'm just going to
come back and sleep all day. It's just [ __ ] depressing.
You know what? I've got another channel.
Yeah. Where I put some cold approaches
up. You know what? I might actually do a
video about dating on that channel and
just advise people to just ignore
everyone that posts on Reddit, ignore
everyone that posts on YouTube, ignores
any [ __ ] dating coach cuz they're
full of [ __ ] They're absolutely so full
I'll tell them that if you go and
approach, they're going to pretend they
got boyfriends. If they if you if they
give you their number, they're going to
not reply. You're going to meet the same
people with the same attitude. I'm going
to tell him that, you know. I'm going to
tell these people everything
so they don't make make the same
mistakes and wasting their time. You know,
I was on Reddit yesterday scrolling
through, oh, women like confidence.
Women don't give a [ __ ] about
confidence. How many approaches we
[ __ ] done last week?
Well, yeah, last week was last Saturday.
So if it's not changed in four years,
you need to convince me on how it's
going to change in another four years. I
need convincing here because to me it
doesn't seem good. I mean, it only took
me losing gambling 6 months in a row to
then then quit, which I have quit. Once
a month is basically quitting and it's
not even once a month. I don't even do
it most of the time. So I mean if
something's been going on and that was 6 months
you know even though people told me you
know gambling is random you can win
after 6 months I put my middle finger up
to them and thought [ __ ] you no way you
can lose that many times in 6 months and
then so we stopped that but I mean this
has been going on a little longer longer
than 6 months. So when so do you have to
do it for another four years then? Do we
have to waste more time and another and
and and more money for another four
years, you know,
and somehow it's going to miraculously
be different. Yeah, bro. And I ain't got
a hole in my ass.
I ain't got a [ __ ] hole in my ass. If
if if if in another four years all of a
sudden this thing is going to change,
but it ain't going to change. You know,
I was getting some nasty dirty [ __ ]
mood swings yesterday, bro. You don't
even know. You really really don't even
want to know, bro. And I won't even
discuss that with you, you know. It's
boring, mate. It's boring. Give it a
break, you know.
No, I'm not getting dates, you idiot.
I'm not getting dates. I had one date.
No, I'm not getting dates. I had one
date in the past seven, eight weeks. So,
no, I'm not getting dates.
And you And even if I'm getting dates,
you want to know why the dates aren't
working? I've explained it to you about
a million times
and I'll have to explain it again to
you. What is a date? A date is not what
a date was in the 1980s. Dates are these
women go on dates to pass time and or
use you. That's a date to them. That's
not what a date is to us. So, and it
doesn't even matter, mate. I haven't had
a date for like seven weeks before the
other day, mate. It doesn't even [ __ ]
matter, you know? So
where? I don't have a date next week. I
don't have a date. You need to leave
this country. We need to stop. We We
We're leaving, bro. That's That's what
we're doing now. I'm not doing this no
more. I'm not doing this [ __ ] no more. You know,
I'm not doing this [ __ ] no more. Trying
to figure out this and me getting blamed
and people giving [ __ ] advice. I'm not
doing this no more. We're done with
this, bro. We're done with this chapter.
It's boring. I think we've already
wasted enough time and money in this country.
You will not win on a date because if
you're normal and slow, they're going to
they're just going to ghost you anyways
and flake you anyways. If you're if
you're uh assertive, they're going to
think you're creepy. There's literally
no in between. Look at what that Muslim
girl done, and that was just a
friendship. Look at what that Muslim
woman done, and that was just a [ __ ]
friendship. And she started going weird.
It's them. They're weirdos. They're not
interested in this country. End of. I'm
not trying to I'm not trying to figure
it out no more.
I'm not trying to figure this out no
more. Simple as that. So,
it's just another way to try to [ __ ]
with your head and victimize themselves. So,
yeah. I need to go I need to somehow go
to the gym today, Grey. My eyes are
hanging out my [ __ ] head. You know,
then my eyes are hanging out my [ __ ]
head, bro. I'm so tired. I'm just fed up
with all of this. I'm surprised I woke
up at like the the time I woke up.
I thought I wasn't going to wake up, lad.
No, I thought I was going to wake up
till like 11:00 where I woke up early.
It will never ever ever change.
But and now there's not even no point
going on a date, Joe, because it will
always be the same old. No matter how
you act, it will always be the same old.
And you know what I say, right? Let's
just say, for example, you are wrong on
every single date, which how many dates
have we been on this year? Four dates.
Let's what was it? Four, three or four.
So we've been trying since February
and we are now June. We are now mid
June. So, you've gone out pretty much
every single week. So, say you're wrong
on every single date, hypothetically.
Okay. What about all the ones that never
went on dates with you? What about all
the ones that pretend they got
boyfriends? Imaginary boyfriends? What
about the ones that give their number
and then don't reply? I mean, [ __ ] me,
bro. If you're doing If you're only
wrong on four [ __ ] dates, then Jesus
Christ. What about all the ones that
never went on a date with you? Exactly.
Four dates, bro, is is is shocking.
That's not even That's not even four
date. That's not even one date in a
month, you know. That's not even one
date in a [ __ ] month, lad.
You know, I said to my friend, "Don't
talk to me about it no more, bro.
I went to my mom's the other day, yo. I
had to deal with these shitty [ __ ]
neighbors. I had a good mind. I had a
good mind um yesterday to [ __ ] go
back there, bro. You see, I had a good
[ __ ] mind, bro. You know, I only
didn't do anything because of her and
she lives there. And you know, things
were looking good. So, I thought, I
don't want to get into problems with
people no more, no matter who they are,
cuz I just want an easy life. But, bro,
I had a good mind, bro, to go back
there. You don't understand?
And it ain't any ain't anywhere near
where I live and it's caused madness,
you know? Like, you don't understand,
bro. Cuz when you get to a certain age
and you have like certain things going
on, you think things are looking up, you
be like, "Ah, [ __ ] them." Let them have
their ego. If this old woman wants to
give me a dirty look, let her give me a
dirty look. If someone wants to try that
bad on the road, let them try that bad.
Do you know what I'm saying? That's what
what what happens, you know? You know,
when people have have things going on in
their life, but then, bro, like nothing.
I got nothing to lose, bro.
You know what I'm saying? I had nothing.
I swear down. So
yeah, literally have nothing to lose
now, bro. You know,
so I guess we can never believe things
that we hear about gambling. We can't
believe things that we can ever hear
about women. We can't even believe
anything that we're told.
It's like the scoop guy was saying for years.
Oh. Oh. Oh. Go away slang you weirdo.
Oh. Oh. It's house edge. Ooh. House
edge. Go. But it ain't a house edge,
bro. I literally done 50 spins
yesterday. 250. I didn't hit one number.
Why is no tier number coming out, bro?
When I'm putting money on the table. It
loves that zero section every time.
Every single time. That zero section.
What is it with it? Because it's
obviously rigged. We already know this.
Art. We already know this.
It made me laugh. And Scoop used to come
on and say they don't need to cheat.
Well, they [ __ ] well do.
You know, it's actually sickening to say
that this shit's been going on for months.
And then you got these women that are
wasting your time.
Why not back it? Um because if I started
backing it then it's going to go on
tier. The whole point of what I'm saying
is it's going on numbers that I'm not
betting to avoid my numbers that I am
betting. So it's pretty self-explanatory.
But yeah, I let them have that little
ego trip. Like when I was at my mom's
the other day, I I thought she was dead.
So I went to do a little welfare check.
And the amount of [ __ ] I had to deal
with with the with with with these
people, I just ignored it. I was like,
"Oh, just allow it." You know,
you know, I got some numbers. If they
want to be salty about this stuff, let
them, you know, they're their children.
But they don't know the real side of me,
bro. They don't. They really, really,
really, really don't.
It's rigged against people that bet on
it. Yes. Lewis Phil Slugger.
Lewis Phil Slugger. I can smell you a
mile off, but I don't what I don't care
about that, bro. There's no point. It's
like that's why I come for [ __ ]
YouTube. Um, when Monty man was pissing
me off, when was it last week when I
joined these hangouts and then these
people would continuously come on and
piss me off. I swear to God, bro, I was
going to go to Birmingham and knock that
prime out. That's why I had to That's
why I had to take a step back. I was
like, "Oh, these people are not worth
it." No, these people do this stuff on
YouTube cuz they're jealous. They know
there's no point wasting money and time
on these people, you know? That's why I
just come off of it. I couldn't be
[ __ ] with it. And anyone that starts
drama on my YouTube, I just block them now. So yeah,
I was getting really dark thoughts
yesterday, bro. If I'm not going to lie to you.
That's why I just come off of it cuz
none of these people are worth it, you
know. And I like people to think I'm
scared of them, but I'm really, really,
really not. So what am I scared of an
old woman breaking her neck to look at
me? I was walking up the road up the
hill to my mom's yard and you got this
old woman. I was going to say to her,
"What? What the [ __ ] are you looking
at?" But I didn't. So I must be scared
of an old woman then. I'm scared of no
one around that [ __ ] area, bro.
People allow it because it's for a
peaceful life. You don't understand.
You don't [ __ ] where you live or you
don't [ __ ] where other people live.
If it was my if it was my house,
I would stop madness and I'll just try
and get rehoused.
But not when someone else is living
there with your family. You know what
I'm saying? That general stuff. You
know, where I live, people don't cause
problems. We don't have problems. We
just get on with our own [ __ ]
We don't start problems. You know what I'm saying?
trying to say or say something to me
now. I was like, "You're the one on
YouTube saying this, that, and the
other." I just walked past him, bro. I
just walked past. [ __ ] all that, bro.
That's all long [ __ ] bro. And when I
thought things were actually looking
good and that, I was like, "Let just let
them just have their little ego trip for
a little longer. I can't be asked with
them, bro." You know what I'm saying?
If somebody physically puts their hands
on you or
or gets in your face, then obviously
then it's a different story. You know
what I mean?
It's like this prime. I can't be
bothered with him. You know,
same with the other guy in London. I
can't be bothered with him. They're all
fat lossers. They got a life. They got
nothing going for themselves. I don't
need to [ __ ] waste my time with them.
I'm going to go to the gym today, even
if it takes a little longer. Just give
me a while, bro. I'm [ __ ]
Can't be asked with it.
So, you should you should be on a date
next uh this week. We got four numbers,
didn't we? Last week, last Saturday.
Oh, I done an approach in my area, Joe.
The other day got the number by the caller shop.
got the number. This guy on the balcony
started clapping. He said, "Oh, well
done." I said, "It's the norm."
But they're just not interested in this
country. You should have learned from
last week and and sorry, last week, the
last year and the year before that and [ __ ]
You're putting all your eggs into one
basket to get nothing out out of it.
It's never going to change ever. Like,
you know that time when I went on that
date, right? I was like, "Oh, it's just
going to be a bad one. It's just going
to be a negative one. I I thought that
because you have to think these things
because it's realistic. It's not you
being delusional. It's you being a realist
and and not having high expectations,
which I like. Wait, so wait, that
logically doesn't make any sense. So why
are we approaching when we know that
even if we go on a date, it's just going
to be the same old? That logically
doesn't even make any sense because it
will always be the same old forever and always. Sir.
Okay. Okay. I I think sometimes you
don't focus on the positive. You're
getting numbers and dates, but it
doesn't go further. I've just explained
to you why it doesn't go further.
I've literally, bro, I've literally just
explained to you why it doesn't go further.
I gave you two examples. And I gave you
an example of of a Muslim woman as well.
I literally just explained that already.
I know you get a date one in a million
attempts. Get it right. When you're
saying stuff, you need to rephrase it.
Okay. I'm getting dates. Okay. Okay.
Okay. So, do I have a date this week?
No, I don't. And the reason I'm asking
you that is because of all the amount of
numbers I've got in the past. Am I
getting a date this week? Am I on a date
this week? Mate, if you was getting
dates every week or every two weeks,
you'd actually have a you'd actually
have some kind of a point. But you don't
because they were every four and few
between. So, you can't even use that as
an argument. What you got three, four
dates in this whole year with amount of
approaching that you've done. It just
proves my point, you know,
and a lot of people will just go on
dates to waste time
and then they'll just come out with some
[ __ ] anyways or like, "Oh, I'm
Muslim." Or, "Oh, well, I don't feel the
connection." Or, "Oh, well, it's always
going to be something. It's always going
to be something." And you don't even go
on that many dates anyway. So, it's not
even It's not even a valid argument.
I just can't. It's just the dating the
dating game in this country is depressing.
Which is why I actually gambled on
yesterday. I only gambled 250.
Uh it's just the whole dating [ __ ]
You just feel like you're going around
and around and around and around and
around in circles. This is why I booked
these flights to leave.
It's depressing, bro. It's It's actually
really really really really depressing.
I don't know if I don't know if anyone's
um been into this whole dating thing.
The whole ghosting, the whole this, the
whole that. No, I'm not a different
person. I don't drink. I was happy the
past couple of days to be honest. Even
when I was at my mom's. No, no, no, no,
no. I was good for a couple of days
going to the gym and [ __ ] but then when
you realize, oh [ __ ] like it's not
going to change. They're always going to
pretend they got boyfriends. They're
always going to go on dates to waste
your time. It gives you a reality check.
It gives you the the reality check that
you need to leave.
No, I was fine the past couple of days.
happy. Why do you think I ignored that
neighbor? And I ignored all the [ __ ] I
dealt with when I went to my mom's area
cuz I couldn't be bothered with them. I
was like, they've obviously got
something going on in their life to
still be salty after 8 months. [ __ ]
them. I'm living my life, you know. But
then, you know, when you have people
wasting your time again and hearing the
make boyfriends again and hearing the
numbers stop replying again, boring.
And that's when you need to take a break
from it again. You don't need to take a
break. You need to leave. Sorry. You
don't need to take a break. You need to
leave this country. That's the break you
need is getting out of here. It will
never ever ever ever ever change. 4
years don't lie. 4 years is a long [ __ ] time.
4 years is a long time for this [ __ ] to
have still been going on for
you know need to put up with even
[ __ ] 10% of what I have and he's
already left. So what excuse do you
really have? None. You know and that's it.
So that's it.
I'm not going to tell you what happened
on this day anyways. It's just another
little victimizing excuse. They they
don't they don't make sense, right? They
go on deep dates with people. I remember
this this [ __ ] used to happen with busy
before, right? Oh, they should you
should make a move. Oh, you should take
things slow. Oh, r. And what happens
when you do that? You get friend-zoned.
So, it's like even no matter what way
you you look at this, it will never
change. I don't know if I can go to the
gym today, but I'm just too tired and depressed.
I don't think I can I don't think I can
actually physically go out today, you know,
and it will never change as well. That's
You can't win on these dates. Even when
you get the dates, you can't even
[ __ ] hardly get one.
Look, I messaged some people on sat um
Saturday and the number I got Wednesday.
Nothing. Not a sausage.
Not a bloody sausage.
So, what do I have to go out another
month and try again to get another day
and hope it's better? I'm not doing it.
I'm not doing it. I am not doing it.
I'm not doing this. No way.
So, yeah, that date on Thursday pissed
me off as well. You know, if if you just
went out simply and got the I've got a
boyfriend [ __ ] I I would just said,
"Okay, well, it's just another week of
[ __ ] We'll try again next week." But
this is what you're going to be dealing
with time and time and time and time and
time and time again.
I've had it loads of times.
You know, you can't win.
You can't win. You're either too fast
and you're creepy or you're normal and
they just waste time. So, there's no
there's literally no in between. So,
but somehow people seem to think it's
going to change. Like when I was saying
to this person on Reddit, they like,
"Oh, you need to take months off. You
can't even take months off. It's
impossible to take months off. And even
if you took months off, you you're still
going back into the same [ __ ] You're
literally still going back into it again, you know?
So, it doesn't matter if you got it, you
know. It doesn't matter. I was fine
before this whole [ __ ] again, you
know, and and I only stuck to the beer
on Saturday as well.
Stock up people everywhere you go. Do
you know how boring that gets, Grezy?
Everywhere you go, just stuck up people.
You're walking around Oxford Circus and
people are walking like their [ __ ] don't
stink coming out their [ __ ] ass. It's [ __ ] boring.
Have you seen it? I don't know if
anyone's ever been to Oxford Circus.
They all walk around with the same attitude.
Droids from [ __ ] Star Wars. [ __ ] NPCs.
But yeah, most people just go on dates
to waste your time. Anyways,
I'm surprised I've not had alcohol
poisoning. The amount of the times I've
gone out drinking thinking that it was
going to change. Um, the amount of times
I've been sick cuz I'm eating properly.
I'm surprised I haven't had [ __ ]
alcohol poisoned. I'm sure I've drunk
more than my [ __ ] father [ __ ] did.
All cuz of these women.
I'm sure I must have. I'm sure I have
drunk more. Not every day. I haven't
drunk every day, but must have dr. I
must be. I know I've drunk more than my
sisters. 100%. I know I have.
They don't drink. I know. I must have I
must have drugged a lot of people, bro. Trust me. Just here. Boyfriend.
Rey. They've all got boyfriends. [ __ ] off.
I'm saying. Yeah.
So you saw a fresh start today. Hey, Grey.
I had to [ __ ] live to a [ __ ] date
only for them to 20 minutes say after
they don't feel the vibe. Time waster,
which doesn't even make any sense. So I
I will have none of this in 2 weeks.
I'll have none of these time wasted
because I was going to go out and
seriously hurt somebody yesterday.
Like I I shouldn't even be saying this,
but I I really was tempted
to just go out and do something.
You know how you keep saying, "Oh, come random com."
I go [ __ ] do some cutting. Yeah.
Yeah. It's pissing me off. It is still
pissing me off. You have to wake up
thinking of this [ __ ] Is it about time
you get some positive experiences,
Grezy? Ain't it about time you got some
positive experiences? Come on now, man.
We wasting more time, more money than anyone.
When is this going to end?
People on Reddit say it's going to end,
but doesn't look like it. It's been
going on for years.
I was so good the past couple of days as
well, bro. So good. I went to ladies,
had a nice rest.
But it will never change. It will never change. Never.
Well, you know, hopefully maybe you'll
get another date in another month. Well,
we won't be here in a month and they
were going out this week. So,
you know, I wouldn't mind if you was
getting dates every Fortnite and he was
[ __ ] them up. I I wouldn't mind.
There'd be there'd be nothing to
complain about, but it's just so boring.
I don't even want to hear about it
anymore, you know? It's just so [ __ ] up.
Just feel like going outside and [ __ ]
doing something in, bro. I swear.
I'm really lucky. But I don't even get
to go to the [ __ ] cinema. There's
nothing on. I'm just going to stay here,
be tired, think about the bad
experiences. I just want to go and just
just hurt some of them. I swear to God. Yeah.
Yeah. I just want to go and just [ __ ]
hurt some [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
It will never change, Greavves. Never change.
It's been this way for years.
This will never change the country.
No, I'm just fed up with the women. Not
even I don't have a I don't have a
hangover. I stick to beer now, so I
don't have a hangover.
It's just a bad experiences with women.
It's draining. [ __ ] draining. It is.
Absolutely [ __ ] draining.
If only I could explain to you, Grevy.
But so, but you know, you should listen
to people on Reddit. Grievy. You know,
you're still young.
Even though this has been going on for
years and you've been drinking every
week, you know, it's you're still young.
It's not even the spirits cuz I don't
even drink spirits. So, it's not even
that. That's it's these women that are
make are driving me like this again.
This whole dating the dating game in
this country is getting me mad again.
I drink Corona. I drink Guinness.
I drink all that good little stuff. The
Corona. The Guinness, you know.
I might try to get some cocoonable back
up for the doctors when I had that foot
injury. They gave me concalable even
though I don't need it. I I wanted to
just go just go to the gym and then sleep
to forget about all of these.
I don't worry.
Just forget about all these bad
experiences, Grezy. That will never change.
Look, some coke has just been spilled there.
Yep. Some coke has just been spilled there, man.
That you are. Huh?
Go away. Hey little Welsh weirdo. We
don't allow keyboard warriors on my channel, buddy.
We don't allow keyboard warriors on my
channel. Ball off, mate.
B off. You little keyboard. I know
exactly who you are.
You b Yeah.
Oh man, I just spilled coke everywhere.
This life never changes, does it?
Never ever changes in this depressing country. What?
I just [ __ ] spilled coke everywhere, mate. Boring. One second.
Bro, you're boring. Go away, you little
whales keyboard warrior. You're boring.
If you've got anything to say, you can
come and say to my face. Chop chop. You
got my address.
Straight to Lizzy line from Paddington. Chop chop.
Go away. You little Welsh keyboard
warrior. Chop chop. You in your 30s,
40s, mate. If you ain't got nothing to
say to my face, I'm not interested. I'll
give you the same advice I give to many others.
You ain't got some anything to say to my
face, bugger off. It's that simple.
That's it. You little Welsh weirdo.
Simp. I ain't got life. What the [ __ ]
would you know about problem people
being a problem? You don't even leave
your house, you little keyboard lawyer.
You got one about, oh, people are scared
of me. People scared of you. Mate, come
to my address today. Stop making
excuses. You have all of this time to be
on YouTube time and time and time and
time and time again with the kitty, the
caliban, and the cheaper.
Come today and stop making excuses. I
will wait for you literally all day. All
day. I don't want to see no more little
shitty little comments. Come to my
address today and you'll know what time
it is. Simple.
That's it. Stop making excuses in the
valleys. You trying to tell people how
they're [ __ ] they're scared to come
to [ __ ] Wales and I see your comments
all the time. Stop making excuses. I'll
wait all day for you, mate. Even if I've
got to stay live for 3 hours, I'll stay
live for 3 hours. And if you're not
willing to do that, stop being a keyboard warrior.
Like what Morgan's dad says, stop being
a keyboard warrior.
Stop being a keyboard warrior. You know
you're boring little sheep shagger down
in the valleys.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] man. [ __ ] off
keyboard here, bro. It's embarrassing. [ __ ] me.
And no, I don't think I'm the problem. I
don't think other people are the
problem. I think these stuck up [ __ ]
are the problem in this country, which
is why I'm leaving. Which is literally
why I'm leaving. Think of think of
Ant-Man for example. Somebody that was
swore he'd never fly again. He was [ __ ]
scared of flying. He f he swore he'd
never fly again. And he's been to
Thailand four times in a year. Jesus
Christ. That's [ __ ] Mantto. So that
that means he's been on a plate a plane
eight times. How bad is that? Eh, that's
what they drive you to do. They do drive
you to do things like that.
They do drive you to that, mate. Yeah,
that's how they get you. [ __ ] me. That's
pretty extreme, though, isn't it, Greasy?
That is That is insane, bro.
That is insane, isn't it, bro?
But all of these little things you're
typing, Silver Surf, if only you have
these problems all the time. You're not
even getting a reaction. I've seen your
keyboard warrior [ __ ] for years now,
buddy. You know where my address is.
Stop making excuses.
And if you're not coming, I'm not
entertaining you. Simple. I'm not like
Monty. I don't let little Mongs on my channel, right?
I don't let little Mongs on my [ __ ]
channel chatting [ __ ] [ __ ]
you know? chatting [ __ ] time and time
and time again
to start [ __ ] that they can't finish. I
don't let people do that, bro. I don't
let people like that on my channel.
Anyways, I'm out of here in two weeks. So, that's it.
It sure was a depressing life in England.
I was thinking that as soon as I
[ __ ] woke up,
oh no, not this [ __ ] life in England again.
Reason I want to go to the gym. Yeah. Is
like cuz I've already started it, you
see? and I paid for it. So,
I think I might need somebody to carry
me to the gym. Grey,
I would just sleep all day. Me,
I would just sleep all day. I don't want
to be around people. You see, when I'm
like this, I don't want to be around anyone.
You know, it isolates you. These bad
experiences isolate you. You really don't understand.
You know, man, I wish there was a way
like even there's not even no hope. Even
next week ain't going to change. If you
went out if you went out this week, it
wouldn't change. Nothing will ever
change in this country. Never.
Yep. It's from these women and these
women have caused it. Well, the
gathering was a bit [ __ ] as well. Um,
but yeah, it's the women that's caused
it. It's the bad experiences.
Anyone that's had the experiences I
have, they would feel exactly the same way.
I thought, okay, we finally have to we
can finally stop in this country now.
But never. It will never ever ever ever change.
Never, ever, ever, ever, ever.
And I've accepted that now. So, yeah.
But stop talking about yourself
again. Monty, listen to me. This is what
you need to do, bro.
You need to uh block these people, these
little [ __ ] 40-year-olds, and don't
let them come on your channel that that
start [ __ ] they can't finish.
You see like take a leaf out of my book.
I don't let these people talk about
themselves on my channel. I just block
them. You spastics. These little
victims. You know what I'm saying? So
yeah. And they're the ones that have
caused this depression. It's literally
them. I was fine a couple of days ago
even when I wasn't drinking.
I had the gambling as well. And I
gambled responsibly as well. Again,
secular slot says as long as you gamble
responsibly. I don't I can't even do it.
Scott accent. It's all well and good.
You got your bills paid. It's never
good. It's still I didn't get angry
yesterday or smash things or anything
cuz I'm just used to it now. But for him
to try to say that, oh, as long as
you've got all your bills paid and
you've got food, it doesn't make an
ounce of difference. It will still
affect you the same way. You know, the
reason I don't get mad about it anymore
is I don't have the energy. I can't be
bothered. You know what I'm saying?
But uh I wasn't very entertained. Not
like when I come out the the the cinema
and this guy's and this guy's betting
big amounts of money. That's how you
know it's fake money what he's using.
That's how you know it's fake money what he's using. So yeah.
So yeah, there's no hope now in this
country. So it'll be gone in two weeks. Bro,
like I said, I'm surprised I've not had
alcohol poison to be honest. I'm
surprised I'm not [ __ ] obese.
I really want to go to this gym, but I
don't think I can do it today, bro. To be honest,
you are Welsh and you have my address.
Everyone has my address.
Everybody has my address. Listen, I'm
not answering your questions about how
you know I'm Welsh. Come to my address.
Everyone has it. Or shut the [ __ ] up.
Simple. I've been seeing your comments
now for ages. Yeah. I've been seeing
your comments now for years. Yeah. I'm
not answering your questions. Put up or
shut up. End of. Let me know when you're
on your way. Simple. Yeah.
Trying to say how trying to turn it into
a conversation where you don't mate.
Mate, listen. This is not a Monty man
channel or a Timmy channel. Trying to
turn it into a [ __ ] conversation.
Trying to turn it into a [ __ ]
conversation so you don't meet me. [ __ ] off, man.
But I I actually think Yeah. If anyone
went through the [ __ ] I went through, I
think they would have just killed
someone by now. Or they definitely would
have gave up. But but people tell me
I've got no patience. This is what makes
me laugh. They say that you got no
patience. But mate, you have to have
patience because been doing this for
years with these shitty women in this
country. You must have some sort of
patience. I mean, I've been I've been
putting this up. I've been put up with
this the longest for the longest time
now. Longer than anybody. Longer than
anybody. Any PUA artist that you see,
I've been dealing with this the longest.
And believe you me, it don't change. It
doesn't matter what people on Reddit
say. It doesn't matter what people
online say. The stays the same. The [ __ ]
up people stay where they are.
It's the same old and it never changes,
you know. It's the same old and it and
it never changes. And they want to blame
everyone but the women. It's never
changes, bro. This has been going on for
years now. Boring as [ __ ]
And then you get these people trying to
be [ __ ] as well.
just [ __ ] people. Is that really what
your life has to offer dealing with
[ __ ] disinterested people? There's got
to be more to life than that, bro.
There's got to be more to life than that.
Dealing with stuck up westernized rude
people. There's got to be, bro.
There's got to be more to life than that
somewhere. Even if it's just around the
[ __ ] corner, you know?
And it [ __ ] with your head badly as
well. That's the thing people don't
understand. It [ __ ] with your head badly.
Year in year out. Year in year out. Year
in year out. Year in year out. Year in
Does it ever [ __ ] end?
Does it ever ever [ __ ] end?
You know, I was saying to this woman in
New Zealand, I got £650 in one account.
She Oh, is that all? I was like, mate, listen. £650.
If someone had £650 savings, they got no
outgoings. It's actually pretty decent.
Like, what are you talking about? London
is more expensive than New Zealand. You
This is why I hate these westernized
women. I [ __ ] hate them. Who the [ __ ]
do they think they are? Like, bro,
London is more expensive than [ __ ]
New Zealand. You [ __ ] idiot. Way more
expensive than [ __ ] New Zealand.
So don't [ __ ] try that like you're
[ __ ] better than me cuz you [ __ ] ain't.
You know what I'm saying?
It will never change. Never change this country ever.
I spent about £200 on Thursday for
nothing. No reason.
For no reason. Now I spent some money
Saturday too for literally no reason.
I think I'm just going to go back to
sleep, I reckon.
Boring, is it? Boring.
I've got a vape next to me as well. I
feel some [ __ ] fat belly, bro.
Wish people done [ __ ] welfare checks
on me, mate.
Hopefully, we can go sleep and
nope. I've got money. Nope. Money is not
the issue. It's these women that are the
issue. I don't care about I don't care
about money. Money comes and goes. We
can't take it with us when we die. And I
get paid as well in a couple of days.
So, why why would money be the issue?
Nah, I'm just sick of women. bad
experiences with women. It's never about
money. We adjust to any amount of money
that we get. Money is not the issue at
all. I could go out this week if I
wanted to. Go out next week. Well, not
next week cuz we're tired. But I could
literally not even go on that plane and
still continue to go out here. I ain't
got nobody problems.
Not at all. And have it for years.
Nobody's not the issue at all.
I spent quite a bit. I used to do it all the time.
Nah, money ain't the issue at all.
So yeah, but £650
in one account. Is she trying to say is
that all? Is that all? Mate, listen. I
don't think you really know what the
definition of skin is, which I never
used to know the definition of skin to
be honest. But think about it like this. Yeah,
think about it like this. You you you
would know when you're skinned when
you're eating [ __ ] cold beans from a
[ __ ] tin or without an eight [ __ ]
tin. If you want to know the definition
of skin, it's what Ant-Man used to be
when he was my age. So he had nothing.
He used to have to go to the food bank
and everything. But when you got some
little [ __ ] in New Zealand, some little
westernizer trying to [ __ ] try and
tell you about how he's when I said this
in literally one account is that mate.
Listen, these people don't know the
definition of skin,
you know, is is is in insane.
You know what I'm saying?
[ __ ] stupid westernized [ __ ]
mate. you. I know people that have to
live off 80 pound for a month. It's not
even a joke. You don't understand. I
have friends. I know different cultures.
I know people's different way of living.
I know this stuff. So, I would say if
somebody had £650 in their account,
they're doing quite good if they don't
have to work. Obviously, they're doing quite good. So,
you know what I'm saying?
But I know see she says that she's well
traveled. Well, if you was well
traveled, you would know the culture
difference. Well, people, there's people
out there that literally have nothing
for the whole month. Literally nothing.
Like you, as long as you got £400 in
your [ __ ] account, mate, you're laughing.
You try to show off that you're well
traveled all the time, but yet you don't
understand the culture difference.
Stupid [ __ ] Westernized [ __ ] woman. Yeah.
Saying westernized [ __ ] Hate him. I
do. [ __ ] hate him. [ __ ] hate them, bro.
I [ __ ] hate him more than anyone.
Even more than that, man. You really don't understand.
So, no, money is not the issue. Why
would money be the issue when I get
frequent money, bro? Come on now. Stop
trying to blame everything else.
is not the issue at all.
I would have spent £200 on Thursday if I
didn't have it, would I?
I don't care about money, mate.
These little bongs on here that's
obsessed with money.
[ __ ] obsessed with money, aren't they?
I ain't dealing with that behavior.
[ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ]
I hope she gets you no [ __ ] what. I'm
not saying it.
I hope she gets you know [ __ ] what? I
ain't saying it, mate. I don't want my
channel to get banned.
Oh, really? Yeah. Yeah. Just like when
you approach and they pretend they got
boyfriends. Yeah. They they they they
just assume you're broke in it, Joe. Yeah.
M just like when you approach them and
they pretend they got boyfriends. Yeah.
They they probably just assume you're
broke or something, can it? Yeah. Yeah.
What about all them times?
Yeah. When they're not interested. Yeah.
Yeah. Good for you, man. I'm just lying
in bed too depressed to even leave the house.
I was supposed to go to the gym today,
but I literally can't even be bothered.
I physically can't even move
these dating these negative dating
experiences. Sure. Take it out on you.
Again, I'm blocking these spasticated
people. I'm not giving them the time a day.
If you got a brain cell, listen. Yeah.
With these people, you block them. You
don't entertain them. They want to make
up stuff. They want to try and get a
conversation out of you. Try and get an
argument out of you. These people that
have always been bullied their whole
life. You just block them and ignore
them. They're spackers.
They're [ __ ] 40y old losers. You
don't even entertain them, man. What you
should be doing, bro. What the [ __ ]
They're not even worth responding to
and arguing with. These people have been
bullied their whole life. Let them take
that L, bro. Let them write their [ __ ]
on the internet, you know. But yeah,
he calls people skinned, but yet he
wears Primark socks and he wears True
Religion. But yeah, I am very very
skinned. Very very very skinned that I
wear True Religion and Primark socks.
Mate, the day I'd have to go to Primark
and and buy socks is the day I literally
think, "What is my life, bro? [ __ ] hell.
That is embarrassing, bro. [ __ ] pry box socks. Yeah.
Yeah. I can't even be bothe to go to the
gym today, but I can't even bother to go
out. I probably won't even play Grand
Theft Auto. Going to play Grand Theft
Auto with my friend. I don't even have the energy.
He doesn't have no properties. He's
[ __ ] skinn as [ __ ] If he has
properties, he wouldn't be begging for
money on the internet. Mate mate mate
mate mate mate mate mate mate mate
listen to me right here right now. If he
had properties he wouldn't be on YouTube
begging for money.
Yeah. You don't see me on YouTube
begging for money, do you? So he doesn't
have no properties. He's literally skint
than a skin flint.
Literally he has nothing. I don't know
what this guy has told you but what has
he actually shown you? Somebody that
comes on the internet begging for money
does not own no properties.
I don't know what this guy has been
telling you, bro. Listen, I get free
bags a month and you wouldn't be able to
pay me to beg for money.
You wouldn't need to You would You could
even beg me, bro. Yeah.
Because I've got something called pride
and I'm not skint. So me having to ask
other people for money is I would never do it.
He's skinned at a skin flint. [ __ ] me,
bro. Jesus Christ, lad. Yeah.
Anyways, we're not talking about that
[ __ ] Anyways, listen. This is what
these people want. Attention. But yeah,
I'm not going to the gym today, I don't
think. I'll probably just go back to sleep.
Hope I wake up a different person. Hopefully.
Hopefully wake up and just uh
completely different person. That'll be
good. Is it
be alive? it.
I don't even like to be in public when
I'm like this. This is why I'm just
going to stay in bed. Yeah.
Yeah. I got you depressed. Well, try
being me, mate.
And you're banned. Bye-bye, weirdo.
Um, so yeah, I'm getting you depressed.
think I [ __ ] feel I'm going to waste
my time and money on these [ __ ] to be
told that I'm still young and stuff's
going to change. Joe, you're still
young. Things are going to change. One
word of advice, never take any advice
from people on the internet or even real life either.
They will never tell you the truth.
They'll never tell you about, you know,
if you go on dates, they're going to
waste your time. They're never going to
tell you about how people are not
interested in this country. No one's
going to tell you this [ __ ] until you
figure out yourself.
They're just going to lie to you and
sell you dreams
because they're simps and they do
anything to defend women.
Yeah, that's another one as well. It
happened. You least expect it. Heard
that one before.
Been hearing that one for about 10
years. Nothing changes.
Literally nothing changes.
I'm not getting out of bed today.
It's just depressing.
It is so [ __ ] depressing, isn't it?
Well, we could be like Lord Jay, fat
bald, four eyes, no money, and got ugly
kids. It could be like him
with a disabled [ __ ] with four eyes, no
money, and he's got [ __ ] disabled
[ __ ] inbredad kids. Really? We could
could be worse.
That's scared of his own shadow. So, it
could be worse. Yeah.
Could be worse, is it? Oh yeah. Yeah.
Could be like that anxiety with him belt.
Oh, really? Any Hey, hey, hey. Come to
my address. I don't want to keep hearing
you typing, man. Good for you. Are you
coming or not?
Oh, nice for you, man. Are you coming or
not? I'm waiting for you. We're going to
block you now. Anyways, come back when
you can come with my address. I've been
seeing your keyboard warrior [ __ ] now
for a very long time. Yeah.
See, I just said all of that mad stuff
about LJ's kids, and he's never going to
come and do anything to me. He's not
going to even do He's not even going to
give me a second chance like he gave
Timmy a second chance. Nope.
Cuz he's a [ __ ]
He is a [ __ ] anxietyridden [ __ ] Do
not listen to anything this [ __ ] says.
He is He is a melt. A [ __ ] melt. I
even offered to pay for the flights.
He's He's not about that life, man. He
ain't about that life, please.
Anyways, enough about these weirdos. No,
seriously though, enough about these plastics. Right. That's Yeah,
I can't believe I can't even go to the
gym today. [ __ ] hell.
Even go to the [ __ ] gym today.
That's [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's depressing that
The sooner I leave, the better though,
to be honest. I think once we're out of
here, it'll be good. It'll be a good
life once we're out of here.
No more [ __ ] No more No more make
believe boyfriends. No more [ __ ] mind
in it, Joe.
Right here. One more time. I've got a
boyfriend. I'm going to break someone's
neck like they did in Family Guy. I'm so
glad I'm leaving. Yeah.
Yeah. The only people that are skinned
are these people. That's why they go
about money every day cuz they are skin.
They know all about that skin life.
Well, I'm staying in bed. I'm too
depressed to do anything else.
It's so depressing. This whole dating
scene is so so depressing. If you could
only expl If you could only make someone understand
needs to go work anyways. Yeah.
Not that hot.
I need to buy some food anyways. So, yeah. Yeah.
are going on dates to pass time.
I'm going on dates to pass time, which
is why people go, "What the [ __ ]
Are people going on dates to waste of time?" Fast time. Yeah.
So yeah, I can't even get out of bed
today, but it's so depressing
knowing that it would never change in
it. It would never change till we're out of here. Yeah,
they sure do. Yeah.
Yeah. They don't do it because they're
trying to date you. They don't do it
because they want a relationship with
you. They literally do it just to pass
time or to use you. One of the two.
Yeah, you need to get some more life
experience, bro. People like people like
you and Reddit, you need to start doing
this [ __ ] bro. You you you'll figure it
out for yourself.
It's like, does anyone on Reddit tell
you that when you approach, you hear
about boyfriends? No. No one ever tells
you this until you actually go out and
do it yourself.
You ever tell you that it's going to be
the same [ __ ] for years? Nope. You have
to figure that out yourself.
I had to figure out myself.
It's so depressing, bro.
Yeah. They would never change.
The only positive is leaving this country.
That's the only positive is leaving
here. Leaving this country. That's the
only thing I can think of now. Nothing
else springs to mind.
Cuz all these people that try to say
women aren't the problem. It's because
they don't go out and deal with women.
You know what I'm saying? Like look at
all of the stuff that people on Reddit
say and the stuff that's in inaccurate,
you know. So,
well, my friend's living there now. My
friend, he's living there.
So, yeah. And if you go Philippines,
they actually want a relationship. If
you go to the Philippines, they actually
want a relationship.
That's another thing. in the
Philippines, they actually want a relationship. So,
uh, and Thailand is for the [ __ ] So,
cuz I went to Philippines
and they actually want relationships.
They actually want to be with you as
well. That's the thing. Whereas here,
they just go on dates to waste time and
to waste your time and to waste their
time. As illogical as it sounds, that's
exactly why they go on dates.
as illogical as it sounds. I'm aware it
does sound illogical, but trust me, that
is the that is what they do. So, yeah,
but no, you'll come back and then you'll
just eventually move out there.
I can't believe the state I went on
Thursday, bro. Oh my god, that pissed me off.
[ __ ] hell, I'm not even going to even
see them ever again. They were literally
like a nine out of 10 as well. Just
another one to add to the [ __ ]
collection. E, I got a load of [ __ ] collections.
[ __ ] hell. It's piling up and piling
up and piling up.
It's going to like I'm not going to have
no more room left. That's why I need a
new taper because it's it's building up
and up and up and up and up and up and
up and up and up and up. This [ __ ] connection
piles up and up and up and up and up and
up and up and up and up.
Not going to tell you what went wrong,
but just went wrong in it. Simple.
Said I was too um
too uh forward.
But these people don't understand that
when you had your time wasted a million.
It's just another excuse that you have
to be that way to to prevent your time
getting wasted. So
yeah, to prevent your time getting
wasted, you have to be like that. But
it's just another excuse.
Remember I told you about being normal
and then being assertive? Do you
remember when I told you about that?
Because I think back on it, I'm
thinking, okay, well, let's just say
they're right with this one. Okay. Okay.
So, what happened with this Muslim woman
that ghosted you that supposed to be
your friend? That wasn't even a day.
Okay. What happened there? Cuz they
replied. They replied, they will meet again. no
nope. Never asked for sex. Not at all.
Not interested in sex. Didn't ask her at
all for sex. We was holding a hand and I
was trying to escalate things and no, it
wasn't sex. So, you got that wrong. So,
then then Okay. So, she's right. Okay.
Then what about that Muslim one that
messaged you saying how they're going to
meet again and then they stop replying?
H. What about that one? What about the
one that met you? Nope. Not a [ __ ]
either. Try again.
We're just trying to kiss basically,
which is normal to me. So, it's just another excuse.
No, I was saying to him every hour and a
half like, "Oh, oh, when should we meet
again?" Because I've had my time wasted
a million times. So, you would do this
[ __ ] It's only natural to [ __ ] do this [ __ ]
So again, it's another way of
victimizing themsel even though we all
know that they were going to waste our
time anyways. They have to use it and
they have to be a victim. Do you
understand? They literally have to be a
victim. It's the same thing as how that
Morgan did it as well.
She wasted uh you know, she has to be a victim.
It can't be, oh, she's a stuck up
westernized [ __ ] that just wanted to use
someone. No, no, she has to be a victim,
you know. Otherwise, there there it has
to be that way, bro.
She has to be a victim, you see.
I did ask for a [ __ ] bro. Or sex.
What the [ __ ] bro? Are you [ __ ] mad?
No, I was just holding hands. We was
together forever for like 4 hours. So, I
was like, "Oh." I say, "Where do you
want to see each other again?
Um, and she he seems to think that's
forward, but what else are you supposed
to do? Get your time wasted again. So,
it's just weird. Just done with it all. Anyways,
I am fing done with it all.
I thought it was actually going to be
good, man. you know, but and I said,
"Oh, like I'm out the other day. Sorry."
And that and then I said, "We should
meet up again, you know, go for some
food and that."
Yeah. And if you didn't do that, she
would have just wasted your time
anyways. So, Yep. cuz I can preach
because I've been on other dates where
they've been completely opposite
and if you didn't, she would have just
wasted your time anyways. time and I
just gave you an example of that as
well. The Muslim girl
and that wasn't even a date. They would
have just wasted your time anyways.
It's a form of victimizing.
And that's not too fast, too soon.
Kissing and asking stuff after 4 hours.
Nah, that's not too soon at all. That's
called progressing. That's called trying to progress.
So, what would have happened if they
would have just wasted your time
anyways. It would have been another
excuse why they're not interested.
100% 100% mate because I've even been on
dates where I've kissed people and they've ghosted.
So, they can't even get their way out.
It's just they're the problem. It's a
waste of time. We're leaving this
country. End of. We're done trying to
we have to be done trying to figure this
stuff out. Simple. It would have been
another excuse cuz I I've I've been on
previous dates where none of this stuff
has happened and they will still make
excuses or they will still [ __ ] you
over. So, I've got dating experience.
If I didn't, then I'd think, okay, well,
it's me. But I know with other dates
where these things have not happened,
I can give you a million and one different examples.
I can give you a a million and one
different examples like right here,
right now in different ways with
different people. The way it escalated
and they they've still done it. They've
still done the same thing.
Oh my god. Did you not listen to what I
just said? I've just told you that I
have took it slow with other people
before and they've done the same thing.
Case in point, that Muslim girl. Case in point, [ __ ]
loads of other people. All that happens
is it doesn't progress if you take it
slower and they ghost you. Anyways,
there's nothing to learn from. You
didn't you didn't do anything wrong. You
was being cautious to not get your time
wasted. If anything, that was a good
thing that you done cuz all that's going
to happen is they're just going to beat
you and waste your time. There's there's
nothing to learn from. It's like I was
telling my Indonesian friend, it's
nothing to learn from. They would have
done it anyways cuz I've got experiences
with different different um different
people that I've done different things with.
Oh, you'll be mine at 11:00 a.m. Oh,
okay, buddy. You keep telling yourself that, right? Uh,
nah, they're all the [ __ ] same. Other
girls are different. No, mate. All all
women are the [ __ ] same. I can tell
you how many dates that I have been on
and they are literally all the same. And
I've done and I've done different things
as well. No, they're all the [ __ ]
same, man. Stop being ridiculous. Stop
it. Stop being silly. You know, what
about all them other people that you
kissed that ghosted? What about all them
other people that you didn't kiss and
you took it slow? What What was the
excuse that time?
You know, it's just another excuse.
That's the way it is. It's just another excuse.
What do you want me to do? Get a [ __ ]
friend zone or something? It's not too
much too soon at all. Nothing to learn from.
There's nothing to learn from. The only
thing that I learned from is doing this
to prevent getting my time wasted like
all the other times. That's what I
learned. You know, I learned that it's a
waste of time. Going on these dates are
a waste of time. Which is why I want I
done what I did because I learned from that.
Yes. The common demonita is me. No other
guy struggles. Yep. Yep. Yep. It's
boring now, bro. We've heard all of this
before. Yes. Yes. Yes. Women don't
pretend they've got boyfriends. Women
don't go on dates to waste people's
time. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. It's all
me. I'm the big fat ugly problem. Bar
it. Poor me. Cry me a river. Bro, is
that what you want to hear? Cuz I can
tell you things that you want to hear if
you want. Women don't go on dates to
waste time. Women don't pretend they've
got boyfriends. I've not been on a 100
million one dates and not acted creepy.
No, I'm a 27year-old that's got no life
experience. I don't know anything. I
don't know what you want to hear.
They're westernized [ __ ] women. You
[ __ ] idiot. Do you not know? They're
westernized women. They're [ __ ] For
[ __ ] sake, I I I don't know what what
more you want. They are definitely the
problem. If I did not think they were
the problem, I would not be going on a
plane for 12 hours. If I had Germany,
right, I' I'd stay kut. I would
literally stay kut. They are the
problem. So bad that I'm leaving because
of it. That Ant-Man's left because of
it. That's how sure we are that they are
the problem. that I'm not having no
other argument about this anymore.
It is them. They are weirdos. It is
You know, I know it's easy to blame the
man and not look into the bigger P. It's
easy. It sounds good. It's like what I
was saying the other day. It sounds good
to blame the man. It's easy. It sounds
good. But if you actually look into the
bigger picture of what they do, you
know, but you won't. You'll just offend
women. So, there's no point, lad.
If I if I if I if I if I would stay I
could stay kaput right here right now
and go out every week make money and go
out every week but I don't want to cuz I
know they are the problem. So I'd rather
just leave. That's what I'm saying. I'd
rather just leave. I could go out today
if I wanted to. I could go out tomorrow
if I wanted to. I can go out Saturday if
I wanted to. But why do I want to deal
with people that are all the same that
are no different? They literally are
NPCs. Like you go into the same clubs,
they say the same [ __ ] I've got a
boyfriend. I've got a boyfriend. I've
got a boyfriend. So mate, you can say
they're all different till the cows come
home, but I'm leaving and you're staying
here. So that's it. 100%.
And you know what? Maybe maybe this
person was genuine and maybe I am wrong,
but I can't imagine how all these other
dates have done exactly the same thing
in different scenarios and this one
would so happen to be different. I can't
imagine it. I think what would have
happened is they would have just ghosted
you or they would have met you and it
would have progressed. That's what would
have happened. I.e. you would have got
friendly owned. That's exactly what
would have happened
if you took things slow. That is exactly
what would have happened
cuz it can't even [ __ ] with your head
that much because look at all the other
ones. You've had people that's
[ __ ] kissed you that's got met
you again. How they going to pull a way
out of that one? Did I
Yeah, there's been people I've actually
kissed and they've done the same thing.
So, how how do you get out of that one?
How So, how would they get out of that one then?
It sounds good. Laming a man, it sounds
good. It's an easy way out. It sounds
good. It [ __ ] sounds good. And what
about all these people that pretend they
got boyfriends anyways? Like, okay.
Okay. Like, this is what I'm saying.
Like, I if I Let's just say that I am
wrong on every single date I've been on,
which I'm not. Okay, fair enough. But
what about all of these people that keep
pretending they got [ __ ] boyfriends?
Well, what what about them then?
You're talking about very small
percentage of people. Small percentage of people, you know?
So, there's nothing there's nothing to
learn from. Like, you might think I'm
being awkward and I'm being difficult,
but I'm not.
There's nothing to learn from. The only
thing you need to learn is to leave this country.
That's the only thing you need to learn.
But then again, it's kind of just
pointless explaining to people that have
got no life experience with these
westernized women. So, I mean, it's just
kind of a waste of time, isn't it?
That's why I don't really do this
anymore, bro. Cuz you're sat here
explaining to people that don't even
understand. So, what the [ __ ] is the point?
like they I mean they don't understand
that much that they actually think women
go on dates with you because they want
to be with you. I mean that's what
people are under the impression. People
think that you can go to bars and clubs
and not here. I've got a boyfriend. So
I'm just kind of wasting my time
explaining it to these people. Yeah.
Yeah. Sometimes I fall asleep listening
to incel stuff. Yeah.
Stop asking stupid questions.
That's my answer to you.
Does that does that did that answer did
that answer your question? I think
that's a good question. I answered this person, Grezy.
Stop asking stupid questions.
That's a good answer. And that's to this
one. Stop asking stupid questions.
Stop trying to make excuses for these
women. If you had any brain cell, you
would leave like I'm doing.
[ __ ] hell. They they see they this is
this is their lack of exper life life
experience Grezy you know I'm going to
mention your your name lad they have no life experience
listen do you think right if I come on
here now starting fresh that people
would have told me oh if you went out
they're going to tell you they got a
boyfriend do you think anyone would have
told me that if I went on now saying
that oh uh yeah I give out many red
flags yep yep yep yep Yep. Maybe this,
maybe that, maybe this, maybe that. We
can speculate to accumulate. Maybe this,
maybe that, maybe this, maybe that. Yep.
Yeah, man. Maybe I do. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. Like when that one met me uh
last month when she traveled an hour to
see me for 20 minutes. Yeah. I gave up I
gave so many red flags. Told her I
gambled. Told her I was broke. Ate with
my mouth full. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yeah. I've
done all of that. Yeah. Did you know?
Did you know that's what happens when I
go on these dates? I uh I eat with my
mouth full. Um I tell them that I'm a
gambling addict and I've got no money.
Did you know this stuff? Yeah. Yeah. Oh.
And I tell them that um I tell them that
I just want to use them for their body.
Yeah. Did you know that? Yeah. Yeah. We
we we should say that stuff to make make
you feel better. Well, I'm I'm I'm just
telling you this stuff to make you feel
better cuz you're always going to defend
women, so I might as well just I might
as well just go along with it. Yep. I
insult them. I beat them up. I eat with
my mouthful. Yeah. Did you know these
things? I make funny noises.
Yep. Did you know all of these things? Yeah.
Did you know these things? This is what
I do, man. I tell them all about my
YouTube channel. Oh, is it any wonder
why they run off? Oh, dear do me.
You know, if that's what makes you happy
and makes you feel better, bro, I got
along with it. Yeah,
I hate them. I do. I actually hate them.
I actually hate them, bro. You don't
understand. You don't know the thoughts
I was getting yesterday, bro. You really
don't know the thoughts I was getting yesterday.
Sick of people wasting my time. Oh my
god. We don't have much time in this in
this world. You know we
know what I'm saying. It's like Reddit.
They got no life experience. So they
just blame men. But we all know these
people don't even leave the house on
Reddit. You know,
so they just love blaming men for some
reason cuz they seem to think men women
are serious. They seem to think women go on dates.
So yeah, I go out and I tell women that
I'm addicted to gambling. I show them my
YouTube channel. I make funny noises. I
insult them. I beat them up. Yeah, I do
all of that stuff. Did you hear that? Yeah.
No, they're time wasters. They're time
That's what they are. They're time wasters.
Nothing wrong with a first date. Nothing
wrong with flirting on the first date.
Nothing wrong with it at all.
Do you know what? I wouldn't even go on
a date now. You know, I wouldn't even go
on a date unless I was speaking to the
person for 30 minutes. I know I kissed
them. I don't even think I would. You
know, that Thursday I went out grieves.
I was like, "Oh, no. Not another one.
another one to add to the [ __ ]
collection. Before I even met them,
before I had even met them, I was like,
"Oh no, this is going to be a waste of
time, man." I just knew it. I just had
it in my head like, "It's going to be a
waste of time.
This is just going to be a waste of my
time." I knew it. I knew it before I
even went on it, you know? I come down
with a flu that day as well. I was like,
"I can't be bothered doing this. This is boring."
You know, cuz I'm so used to it now.
To be honest, I don't even think I would
go on another date. Even if I had a
chance, to be honest with you,
I don't think I would, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Crippling anxiety. Yeah.
Never suffered with anxiety in my life.
So you must be talking about yourself
there, buddy. I mean, I leave my house.
You people don't. So, who's the one
that's really got anxiety?
Yeah. Anxiety, bro. You know all about
it. You're the main culprit for the
suffering. Isn't that right, Grezy? you
know all about the condition that you're
suffering. It's like you know this whole
L J and stuff, right? You know this when
he says that you've got anxiety, it's
it's just cuz he's got anxiety. They
want to make themselves feel better that
they're the ones that suffer with the condition.
They suffer with it themselves. So they
tell other people that they suffer with it.
So it's just to make themselves feel
better. The fact that they're the ones
that suffer with the condition. You know
what I'm saying?
Why do I lie to the police? I don't lie
to the police. I'm disabled, mate.
The only one that's got anxiety is you people.
That's got anxiety is you people.
[ __ ] hell. Yeah.
I do have I do have crippling anxiety,
mate. Actually, I do have crippling anxiety. Yeah,
I do have crippling anxiety, mate. I do actually. Yeah.
USAD put a new picture up, by the way.
Man, I should have that date should have
wasted my time, bro. That would have
really got back at that [ __ ]
That that would have really got back of that [ __ ] Yeah,
should have gave up from then. Really?
Do you know I should have gave up about
No, realistically, I should have gave up
3 years ago to be honest. I should have
gave up 3 years ago. I think that's good. Uh,
yes I have. Yes, I [ __ ] have. You
know this [ __ ] thing I You know this
date I went on on [ __ ] Thursday? She
was like a [ __ ] nine, bro. Yes, I
[ __ ] have. 100% I have. Bro, you mad?
Why do you think I'm [ __ ] pissed off
about this these two dates, bro? Huh?
Yeah. So, what I was saying is she's uh
that day I went was like a [ __ ] 8.59
to be fair. That [ __ ] is like a [ __ ]
three. Are you [ __ ] mad, bro? She's
like a [ __ ] three, bro.
Literally a [ __ ] three.
Do you like a [ __ ] three, man? What
the [ __ ] A three out of 10? Are you
mad, bro? [ __ ]
Too bad they're not interested in this country.
That would have shown the [ __ ] [ __ ]
hell. That would have showed the [ __ ] Yeah, 100%.
Yeah, I don't think I could ever do like
a a normal job. I get too many mood
swings. So, I wouldn't be able to just
like go out when they call me. You know,
some people get random shifts. I
couldn't do it. I get too many mood swings.
I get too many mood swings, bro. I don't
think I can actually do it. I don't like
being told what to do and stuff.
I don't like being told what to do.
Life's hard enough and then you have to
deal with these [ __ ] women.
It's a [ __ ] life, ain't it, man?
You got a fling.
Why do you tell people to uh give up on
dating? You have a fling, don't you?
Yeah. They can get sex whenever they want.
Can get sex whenever they want.
I might go KFC today.
Wait. Oh, someone said they got a Burger King voucher.
Let me see.
Ask me if I can use a barbecue fer.
You can ask him if I can use his Burger King voucher.
He writes a burger king in it. So I just text him. Yeah,
it's a [ __ ] country to be in, is it?
I'm so cheeky asking if I could use his voucher. Uh,
that's why you need to be self-employed, mate.
Not interested in 80% of men. They're
not No. No. They're not interested in
80% of men.
So, yeah. No. No. They're not interested
in 80% of men. Get it right. Me and 80%
of men. Yeah.
The fact that more people struggle than
don't struggle says a lot about them.
It says a lot about them.
Wow. See, this this woman from New
Zealand is [ __ ] delusional. Absolute
delusional. £650 doesn't cover rent.
Don't pay rent. Barely covers a nice
dinner at a good restaurant. I was like,
are you delusional, mate? London is way
more expensive than New Zealand.
London is way more expensive is way more
expensive than New Zealand.
Like, have I been to a nice restaurant?
Yeah, bro. I've been to many, many nice restaurants.
And there's not many that come to about 650
unless you unless you go to the [ __ ]
shard. She is delusional. Even if you go
to the shard yet in London Bridge, it's
about 150. It's about, let's say, it's
about two. It's about 2 250 maximum.
She's [ __ ] delusional, mate. And she
lived in [ __ ] New Zealand as well. Yeah. Heat. [Music]
Oh, bam me again. Bad me again. Bam me
again. Bam me again. What is it? Just
read it. Always banning people.
Always [ __ ] banning people. This [ __ ] Reddit.
Go [ __ ] Five.
So I have to make a new Reddit account.
stuck to it.
Yeah, I'm depressed, mate. I can't even
get out of [ __ ] bed. I'm going to ask
this guy if I can use his Burger King vouchers.
Yeah, I'm depressed, but I was supposed
to go to the gym today, but I can't even
get out of bed. Imagine you having to go
to [ __ ] work and you can't work. Imagine
having to uh imagine has to go you
having to go work when you got mood swings, you know.
Imagine you happen to uh imagine you
happen to go to work but you got mood
swings and you get these like random
shifts. I tell them to [ __ ] off me.
That's why I can never work. You see,
cuz the mood swings and [ __ ] I don't
like being in public when I get these
nasty mood swings. I just want to stay
alone, you know?
Well, hopefully we die in our sleep.
I can't wait, bro.
I can't wait until the day I finally
die, bro. Be out of this life. Never
have to think about this again,
you know? I'll never have to think about
this again. You know, there's this
woman. She said, "Oh, you should give up
the dating for a few months. It's easy
for her to." Have you noticed the women
that always say this are always ones
that in relationships and get sex? Have
you noticed that, Cactus? They're always
the women that get relationships and sex.
Have you noticed that? Have you noticed
Like this stupid little [ __ ] here.
like this stupid little sid
doing something today, bro. I swear to God,
I don't love her. She's a [ __ ] ugly
[ __ ] ugly [ __ ] she is.
I just want to die in my sleep, man. I
just want all of this [ __ ] to end. It's
boring now. It's been going on for years.
It's been going on for [ __ ] years
now, bro. It needs to stop. You know
what I'm saying? It's been going on for
[ __ ] donkeyy's years, you know.
It's been going on for [ __ ] years,
Cactus. It never changes.
She kept saying to me that £650
doesn't even cover a nice meal.
Delusional. London is more expensive
than New Zealand and there's very few
restaurants that come up to £650.
She's [ __ ] delusional. If you go to
the shard, right, you might be spending
250300, but £650 it's not even a heard
of for two people. I wouldn't even spend
£300 for a [ __ ] meal. Are you mad? Delusional.
Anyone would think that I'm saying six pound like£650
bro it's not as as little as you're
making it out like they make it out like
they're just delusional entitled [ __ ]
and I'm thinking for somebody that's
wellraveled yeah you seem to be very
very ignorant you claim that you're and
she said how does that have a
correlation it does have a correlation
cuz if you're well traveled you would
see how people that are actually skinn
live people that are skinn actually if
like what the [ __ ]
you know, I've got 40k in savings. I was
like, good for you, man.
Like, what the [ __ ]
It's nowhere near as little as you're
[ __ ] making it out, mate. It's not
lots and lots and lots of lots of money,
but it's nowhere near as little as
you're [ __ ] making it out.
It's nowhere near as little as you're
making it out.
That's how entitled they are. Yep.
I can't even get out of bed today, bro.
Can't even go to the gym. I was supposed
to go to the gym. I can't even go to the
Do you remember the neighbor, Cactus?
Got lots of fle as well. Do you remember the neighbor?
Do you remember the neighbor, bro?
Yeah. Weird, isn't it? Well, hopefully I
die in my sleep today, matey. That'll be
a better life, isn't it?
Yeah, I saw him the other day. He said,
"Oh, what you say now?" No, no, no, no,
no, no, no. I just walk past him. Just
straight walk past just like I walked
past the old woman giving me a dirty
look. I can't be I can't be bothered,
bro, cuz I thought like there's no point
cuz things are going to change in that
is it? Like things are going to change,
you know? things were looking up and
stuff in it. So, I thought I just let
them have their little [ __ ] five
minutes of fame in it. And then that's
why I just ignored it cuz I couldn't be bothered, lad.
So, it's like some old woman was giving
me a dirty look at it. It was so awkward. But yeah. Yeah.
So many [ __ ] in that area. You
don't get [ __ ] here, mate. No.
So yeah, I thought cuz things were
looking up a like things were looking
up, you see. So I thought, oh, there's
no point retaliating to low lives, you
know, cuz things were looking good. I
was like I was meeting this person, but
nope. Just the same old negative
experiences with women.
And it ain't about to change either.
It ain't about to change.
People say it does change, but it
doesn't cuz it's just the same old.
I wasn't taking it too fast on the day
as well. I just wanted to ensure I
wasn't wasting my time.
But don't feel bad, man. And they would
have wasted your time anyways. Look at
all these other people that's wasted your time.
All right. No, don't you worry about
that. They would have just wasted your time anyways.
I think that's the thing that gets me is
the time wasted dates and the ghosters.
That's what really gets me.
Oh, just on Thursday in it, they said
that I was asking a lot of questions. I
just said every hour and a half like,
"All right, when do you want to meet
again?" and stuff because I just didn't
want to feel like I was wasting my time again.
And we was holding hands and they said,
"Oh yeah, you tried kissing a few times
and stuff." I was like, "Yeah, it's normal kissing."
But if you didn't do that, you would
have just got your time wasted. So I I uh
the one in the picture. So what was I
supposed to do? Just waste my time.
So, I don't even really want to talk
about it anymore. It's just depressing,
bro. It's really depressing.
I'm surprised people don't talk about
this enough. You know, dating being
depressing. They talk about gambling.
They talk about eating shitty food. They
talk about drugs, but we never hear about dating.
So, but I you shouldn't let it play on
your mind too much. It's just another
way of them [ __ ] with your head cuz
we all know that we've been on normal
dates and we've been normal on dates and
then they just waste your time after and
that one would have been the same. So, it's like
yeah, you have to kind of do that. I
won't be going on any more dates anyways.
Yeah, they're all [ __ ] in this country,
mate. They were all entitled West [ __ ]
but she would have just met and it would
have just progressed. I know these
things cuz I've been on dates. I won't
even go on another date now. Like, it's
that bad. I won't even go on another
date unless I've spoke to them for like
half an hour and know we've kissed. I
won't even go on another date. That's
how bad it is. Like, that is literally
how bad it is. I won't even go on
another one cuz that Thursday, yeah, I
was like, "Oh, uh, I can't be bothered,
man. I'm [ __ ] I've got a flu and that
I couldn't be asked and I knew it was
just going to be the same old [ __ ] So yeah,
that's why I couldn't be bothered, you
see. But I'd still done it anyways cuz
what other choice did I have? So I just
wanted to stay. So So yeah,
it will never change in this country sadly.
Got hungry out as well.
I know. I know. I was getting some sick
thoughts yesterday, bro. Like going to
my mom's and doing [ __ ] and that. I was
getting some really sick thoughts, bro. But uh
there was no there's there's I just
don't want to go prison. That's the
thing. Cuz then they win even more if
you get put in prison. You know what I'm
saying? Like that's what it is.
Yeah. Cuz that's what it is. It's not
that I've got a boyfriend. It's not even
the numbers that don't reply. We can
just say, "Oh, that's England. We'll do
it again next week." We go out for a
drink anyways. We go out for a drink
next. We we go out for a drink next
week. Oh, it's going to be the same
anyways. We expect it. It's the dates
that get in your head because they make
it seem like there's something wrong
with you, but there's nothing wrong with
you. There's nothing wrong with the way
that you look. There's no Cuz obviously
with a boyfriend [ __ ] you could say
that, but everyone gets it. Oh, I've got
a boyfriend. It's the same [ __ ]
Most people deal with it. But when you
go on these dates, you feel like you're
alone in it. But obviously, there is
other I'm sure it happens to other
people as well. and then you feel like
there's something wrong with you when
there's nothing wrong with you and then
it [ __ ] with your head. That's the
that's the part that [ __ ] me up is the
ghosting and the the dates. That's what
gets me that's what gets me going, bro.
That's why I don't even really want to
do it ever again, bro.
Cuz it's not even like you're you're
this fat ugly.
Uh cuz then you can be like, "Oh, well,
it makes sense. Oh, we have to keep
trying. We know our we know our place,
isn't it?" But when you're not fat,
ugly, and you're kind of like, you know,
like a normal person, it thinks like,
well, it actually is hopeless, isn't it?
It's got to be hopeless in this country.
If you look like Timmy Aldridge and you
got these dates and it was happening,
then you'll be like, "Okay, well, maybe
it's time to move to spastics cuz we're
we're we're cuz we're really pushing and
we're really punching above." But when
you're not right and you're actually
normal and these things are happening,
it's like what the [ __ ] It lowers your
confidence even more. Well, it lowers
your confidence. Not even more. It
lowers your confidence. You understand?
There's nothing wrong with you and other
people that try um stuff, you know. So,
It will never change ever.
Um, I'm trying to think where else to walk today.
I don't know.
So, that's it. But
it's the dates that [ __ ] me up.
Yeah. It's the dates that get on my nerves.
Wait, this is another time waster, is
it? Just another time waster.
Just like all of the women time wasters.
That's all it is. Nothing more, nothing less.
People on Reddit said I'd be married now, cactus.
They say I'd be married now. [ __ ] liars.
It'll never change.
Cuz most the dates I've been on, I've
kissed on the first date. Most of them I have.
Pretty much most of the dates I've been
on, I've actually kissed them.
But you're just meeting mental [ __ ]
people. Do you understand?
[ __ ] starving. I am
Yeah, I just need to just Yeah. give up forever. That's it.
I'm so hungry, bro.
I was thinking that yeah,
I was go I was going good, you know,
doing good going to the gym and stuff,
but I just I'm just too depressed to go, you know,
it will never change.
Breaks only make sense if things would
change. But the this will never change.
So taking breaks doesn't even make any
sense because it will never change. You
will always be the same old
[ __ ] behavior, [ __ ] attitude, [ __ ]
people. It will never change.
Yep. And I sent it to this New Zealand
woman. She said, "No, they're just not
interested in you in this country." I
said, "Correction. They're not
interested in me and 80% of people in
this country." Correction.
She says, "Do a poll." Okay, I will do a poll. Simple. You know,
cuz if it's not them, why is it more
people struggle than don't struggle in
this in this modern day and age, right?
In this in this modern society, right?
Answer me this. Why is it that most
people struggle and don't struggle then?
If it ain't them, like if I was if I was
watching these people, bro, and they
weren't getting the same [ __ ] as me, I
would really start thinking like there's
something wrong with me, but they all
get the same [ __ ] as well. I've got a
boyfriend. I've got a boyfriend. I've
got a boyfriend. And it's like, well,
hold on. This is happening to so many
other people. How can it be me? Do you understand?
And there's not really a lot of them in
London, to be fair. No, I don't. I don't
meet a lot of New Zealanders or
Australians. I meet more American people.
No, you don't really meet a lot of them,
but there were just seven of them at the train
uh on Thursday. Was it Thursday,
Saturday? Sorry. Yeah. They were just
waiting there and it just reminded me of
Mick Jonathan Robinson
cuz one of them had like the the
mustache. He went all the way to
Australia to try and
escape his his crimes.
escape his crimes
to try and escape the fact of what he done. Yeah.
Yeah. To a very young age because of it.
Literally. Yeah. I'll tell you what it
reminds me of. Look, it's like that
proper Australian uh
I don't know. No, it just reminded me of
Mick Jonathan Robinson
who put in care at a very young age.
Yeah. Look, if you watch these videos
with Crazy Al, it's proper Australian, isn't it? Yeah. See,
it just reminds me of the dad, isn't it?
I don't know why. It just reminds me of the dad.
[ __ ] hell. It reminds me of the [ __ ] That's
Yeah. One second, bro.
Sorry about that, bro. I'll just My Yeah, bro. KSI.
He's got 12 million followers on Instagram. Yeah.
Yeah, sorry about that.
I can't even get out of bed, mate. I'm
just going to go KFC, I think.
Yeah, I'm going to go I'm going to go KFC.
Suppressor this country greasy.
Not. Yeah, it's too early to go cuz I
only want to eat once today cuz I'm
saving some money in it. So,
saving some money.
There's 10. I can't eat now cuz I would
then I'll eat again later. So I don't
want to eat again later.
This country will never change, will it? Weezy,
what do you reckon will happen if I go
out on Saturday approaching again? Weezy,
what do you think will happen?
What do you think will happen? that
boyfriend. You like that, don't you? Yeah.
Yeah. I'm not doing it again here, mate.
I'm not doing it again here. I'm sorry,
bro. I'm not doing it again here.
Don't do that again, man. My boyfriend's
This is what makes me laugh when you got
people that say stuff like this at this
time though gym junk food is on the way.
If you don't make changes the result
never going to alter.
What the [ __ ] bro? How many changes have we made?
Like how many changes have we made in
our life? How much traveling and
approaching have we done in our life?
Creepsy. We've done it time and time and
time and time again. How many times have
we done this?
Like change change change.
Like how many times?
Stupid advice, isn't it? [Music]
I'll be depressed as long as I continue
to stay here. I think in this country. Yes. [Music] Yeah.
Yeah. I'm going anyways.