Oh,
I just thought I'd write one of
one of man's quotes. One of
Yeah, one of Antman's quotes.
One of Antman's quotes, mate.
I know. I found it funny.
This is uninterested in this country.
That's a m. Yeah.
That's funny, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Not allowed. Why is Monty so disabled?
I had a whole chicken all to myself,
Grezy. I had a grilled chicken all to myself.
It was lovely.
Then I had a cup of [ __ ] Now I'm just
in bed now.
They just aren't interested in this
country, Grezy. Simple as that.
Well, you don't like that. Uh, Cherry,
you don't like that? No.
Why do you like Natalie Cherry?
I think she's a [ __ ] pig if you ask me
Greavvesy. I think she's a [ __ ] pig.
Oh, I missed this one. I went on a date
with man. It was so cute.
You have to admit that's cute though, is it? Grievesy.
Oh, that little picture on my YouTube is cute. Grievesy.
Well, another one bites the Another one
bites the dust.
Another one bites the dust. Another one
bites the dust. Another one bites. And
another one bites. And another one bites
the dust. Is that right, Grezy? Yep.
I'm just resting,
Gy. I'm having a little rest. I'm
talking to somebody on WhatsApp. She's replied.
Yeah. How how how hard would you say
dating is in uh England, Grimsy?
It's [ __ ] very hard, mate.
And all the clubs are full of the same
people. So it leaves me on the streets
like a homeless person.
You find the same people in clubs as
well. Same age range, same suckup
people. So you're left to the streets,
but yeah, people knock street approaches
so much. But that's where you find all
different kinds of people on the street
cuz everyone's walking on the street, you know? So
this guy said, "Oh, you might be coming
on too strong." Well, do you know what, mate?
I would love I would love somebody to
explain to me what that means one day,
Greavvesy. Coming on too strong.
It's what like USA is. He tried saying
to my friend, "I came on too strong." I
was like, "Love, you took me to your
apartment and you came on to me.
What the fuck?" And and I'm the one
that's come on too strong. I would love
one day for somebody to actually explain
that to me. What that even means
coming on too strong.
I'd love for somebody to explain that
one to me one day. Uh
yeah. So you're in America. Hold on a
minute. Right. This guy saying
So, you've done all of these approaches
and you've never got I've got a
boyfriend once. Stop talking [ __ ] So,
you live in America, right? And you've
done all of these approaches and a
woman's never told you she has a
boyfriend. You're talking [ __ ] mate.
The only people that you're the only
woman that you've approached is in your
head. There's no way. Even people that
get women, even even people that get
women, they say it too. Like if you if
you if you was approaching enough people
like me and him. So you're telling me
that you're never going to get it once?
Well, you're talking that absolute [ __ ]
Really are talking [ __ ]
complimenting them is coming on too
strong. Oh, okay. Right.
Oh, Grey. Apparently that's too strong. Oh, okay.
Right. Oh, interesting.
At least we know the answer now, is it,
Grimsy? Oh [ __ ] Is that what it was all along?
Oh [ __ ] Is that what it was? Oh Jesus.
Yeah. Do you know? No. No. Do you know
what you need to do, Gregy? You know,
when you go to a nightclub, you should
just talk about the weather. Talk about
the weather. Talk about politics.
Yeah. Then they're definitely not going
to say they've got boyfriends then, are they?
All right. Okay. So, coming on too
strong is calling them beautiful,
whatever. Okay. Fine. Okay. Well, I
didn't know that was a problem. Well,
next time I go out, I'll I I'll start
talking about politics and other things.
Then see if they then start saying
they've got a boyfriend.
Maybe maybe maybe they'll stop saying
it. May maybe it is that greasy. Yeah. Oh, interesting. Right. Okay.
There's no way it can be so different in
America. Grievy, what's your opinion?
There's no way because what people say
on Reddit, it contradicts real life experiences. Griezy,
please tell me you understand what I mean. Grieves. Yeah.
It seems to contradict uh your real life
experiences seem to contradict their
advice. Do you understand, Grezy?
You understand what I'm getting at?
You know, I'm trying too low.
There are good women everywhere.
There are good women everywhere. Well,
27 years in counting, almost 28. And
I've never met a good one.
And I've never met a good
women everywhere. He said, "Yeah, I
believe it when I see it, mate. I'll
take your word for it." 27 and counting.
Been 28 this year. Still waiting.
Still waiting, mate. Just like that guy
in the shop. I'll wait, Grezy. I'll wait.
And I'm still there, bro. I'm still in
that shop. I'll wait.
I'll wait. Yeah,
I'll just wait. Yeah.
Oh, really? There's good women
everywhere, was there?
What outer space?
What I mean by that, uh, Greavesy, is
they'll say, "Oh, you need to go out and
approach women. You need to do this. You
need to do that." But then when you do
it, they say they got boyfriends. So,
how much life experience do these people
really have? And they don't live in
Asia. They live in America, which is
just as bad, if not worse.
So, how can somebody live in America and
give this advice and then you take their
advice and their advice don't even work?
So, what do they actually leave the
house or what?
They're absolutely not all the same and
they are not absolutely evil. I said
they [ __ ] a million% are 100% a
million the same and they a million%
evil. That's what I said.
They sure are. That's what That's what I
said. They said they they're absolutely
are not all the same. They're absolutely
not all evil. I said they [ __ ] well a
million% are. Not even 110%. A million%.
They [ __ ] well are, mate. 100%. you
you might have met them.
He said 20 years counting and I've met
hundreds of good women. I told him you
might have met them in your dreams but
that's about it. You didn't you didn't
meet them in America mate and you didn't
[ __ ] meet them in England. So,
I generally can't ever say I've met
anyone that's stiff in Grezy.
And I would say that I've got some sort
of decent decent life experience now at
27 Grimsy and I've been around the
country with my little feet jumping on
and off trains and I generally can't say
I've never met anyone that's different.
You know what I'm saying, bro? I generally generally can't.
No, I generally can't even Let me try
and think. No, they're all the same literally.
N that's what I said actively in my life.
And even if what this guy is saying is
true, it can't be because there's no way
somebody can go out and approach all
them women and never hear I've got a
boyfriend once in their life. It's
literally impossible. Unless she was in
Asia or South America. There's no way.
No, I'm not disabled, but you're disabled.
I'm sure I'm not disabled, but you're disabled. Yeah.
On a night on a night, we all
I'm not disabled, but I'm sure I'm not
disabled, but I know you are.
I'm so cheeky. You know, this actually this gets
I'm arguing with this guy on Reddit.
Am I trolling, mate? I've had more women
than you. Don't worry about if I've ever
had a girlfriend or not. I've had more
women than you, mate.
Yeah. Focus on yourself. Don't worry
about what I've had and what I haven't had.
The relationship is
is with one person.
One second. I had to pay them. Yeah.
Yeah. You keep telling yourself that, buddy.
Yep. No one is.
Bro, we're actually going around in Hey,
Gregy. We're actually going around in
circles. You understand? We're actually
going round and round and round in circles.
We are literally we're actually going
around in circles now.
Yeah, we're having the same argument
over and over again. I just realized
we're actually going round and around in circles again.
Yeah. To prove my negative experiences
with them. To prove my negative
experiences with them.
Showing the world how stuck up and
ignorant they are. Showing the world how
which is why I'm which is why I'm
recording. [ __ ] stupid prick.
But yeah, we're actually going around in
circles over and over again.
Yeah, exactly, bro. There's no shame in
admitting uh you have disabilities
because you do have disabilities. Yep.
Is this you coming forward telling
people that you're disabled? We know
you're disabled. You didn't have to tell
us. Oh, is this you coming out you're
disabled? We already knew you was disabled, bro. Oh,
bro, you didn't need to come forward. We
already knew you're disabled. We already
know that you're a disabled [ __ ]
because you people have been on YouTube
for years projecting. It will free you.
And it has coming out that you are
disabled. Yes, you are. You disabled
[ __ ] You can't get off of YouTube.
Can't take one day off of it. You know,
I like Grezy. I could actually say that,
you know, one day off of it. All of you
people are disabled. Fat, ugly, lonely,
and disabled. You know all about having
disabilities. It's what you are. It's
what you suffer with.
Yeah. Funny it. Sorry. You got me got me
going a little bit there, son. Yeah. But
yeah, you have got disabilities, man. Yeah.
Don't know who the [ __ ] it is, but bye-bye.
Yeah, we were actually going around and
around in circles. I'm on Reddit and I
was and this guy was women are
absolutely not all the same and they're
absolutely not all evil. I said, they
[ __ ] well are, mate. And I've met
more than you. And I'm 20 [ __ ] seven
and I've never met a good one. 27 years and counting.
27 years and counting. We're actually
going round and round in circles now.
We are literally going round and round
in circles like naughty.
You know what I'm saying?
What the [ __ ] does coming on too strong
mean? I still haven't been answered this
question. Grieves, I've asked about two different people.
Not to be dick, but I think I'd have a
better idea of this than you. You
absolut You really don't. I've
approached more women than you and I've
met more women than you. Trust me. I'm
arguing with some [ __ ] stranger on
Reddit. But I still don't actually know
what this word actually means. Coming on too strong.
Um um I I still don't understand what
this word means to be honest. Maybe
we'll get an answer.
And then they're like, "Oh, have you
ever dated a woman? Have I had sex with
a woman?" I'm not answering any of your
questions, mate. Even if, listen,
listen, listen. Even if somebody dates a
woman, it is one woman that they're
dating. That doesn't mean that they know
about women. That does not mean that
they know about women because they would
have dated one woman woman out of
millions. Do these people think that
because they might have been in a
relationship with one person, they seem
to know all women? That doesn't even
make any [ __ ] sense. I said to him,
"Listen, I have met more women than you
would ever have. Probably more people
than most in the world. I've been on
dates. I've gone on um I've met time and
time and time and time and time and time
and time and time again. No, he's saying
that I'm coming on too strong because I
went up to these women and said, "Oh,
you was beautiful."
How is that coming on too strong?
So, they tell you that you need to be
assertive, but then when you're
assertive, you're coming on too strong.
[ __ ] logic. [ __ ] it right in the ass.
[ __ ] it right in the ass. If you don't
flirt, you're boring. You need to flirt.
And then when you flirt, no, you're
coming on too strong. [ __ ] logic right
in the ass. You can't win. It's a madness, you know.
I'm just saying to him, bye-bye, s.
Bye-bye, S. He's a [ __ ] s. Yeah.
That's [ __ ] There's not a [ __ ]
balance at all, mate.
Stop defending women. It's embarrassing.
You're asking me if I've ever had sex
with a woman. Get the [ __ ] out of here.
You know what I'm saying? If I If I have
ever had sex with a woman, bro, how
about you suck my [ __ ] dick and stop
asking stupid questions?
Stop asking stupid questions
cuz when you get when you get stupid
answers, don't stop asking stupid questions, bro.
That is a weird question. Why are you
asking people if they've had sex?
I'm going to try and get him on this panel.
[ __ ] s. Why are you asking me if I've
had sex? You weirdo.
And they seem to think Yeah. Even if
they've been in a relationship, that
doesn't mean they know any more about
women. That's one woman that they've
gone on a date with.
Even if right say say you have met women
right and you've never been in a
relationship and one person's been in a
relationship you know more about women
than them because think about it you
have met women from different countries
you've been on date like you you are
actively meeting them literally every
day at one point so how would somebody
that's been in a relationship with only
one person know more about women than you
do you know what I'm him. [Music]
Anyways, I'm going to try and get this
[ __ ] on it. Anyways,
let me try and get this [ __ ] on here.
Yep. You're talking about yourself
again, mate. Classic autism. You know
all about You know all about autism
because you suffer with it yourself. So
you know all about the condition that
you've got. Yeah. You are autistic. You
have got autism. Yes, we know. Stop
talking about yourself.
Yeah. You are the definition of autism.
When anyone goes in when anyone goes in
the dictionary, bro. Yeah. You come up.
Autism is you. It's what you suffer
with. It's the condition that you get
benefits for. Yes, you have got autism.
Stop talking about yourself. Yeah.
Anyways, bro. Anyways, if you got
something to say, you come say to my
face. You got my address. Anyways, bro,
argue with a keyboard warrior.
Yep. You are disabled. Yes, you we we
know you are disabled. Stop calling yourself disabled,
bro. Listen, if you're not going to come
on my door and say anything to my face,
everyone just knows you're talking about
yourself. Rooster disabled. Yes, we know
you're disabled. Yes, we know that
you're autistic. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Yes. We We know you are. Stop talking about yourself.
But yeah, there's no balance, Joe.
There's no balance at all. Yep. You are
special. You are special needs. Stop
talking about yourself, you little bully
victim. Bye-bye now, you little bully
You're 100% a virgin. You know what I
said to him? He said, "You need to get
therapy or something. You need to stop
approaching so many women and you just
over cool down your mindset, your
beliefs, and the way you interact with
women." My interaction is fine. He
completely ignored everything cuz he's a
s does not work. It's unhealthy. You're
going to end up hurting someone. I
really wish you would take my advice. I
said, "Haha, you're a s. You're 100% a
virgin. You have no experience." He's a
virgin. You've got no life. You've got
You've got You've got no life experience
and 100% still a virgin. 100% still a virgin. A,000%.
You have literally no life experience
and you've ignor And you've ignored
everything I've shown you as well.
They literally ignore everything you
show them and twist it to what suits
themselves. That's literally what they
do on this Reddit. They literally will
just make up things.
Yeah. And then they just
I try to, but they are stuck up [ __ ] Yeah.
I can't do that when they're all stuck
up [ __ ] I'm just going to I'm just
going to keep saying it. Stuck up
[ __ ] Stuck up [ __ ] You can't
form relationships with stuck up [ __ ]
that have got attitude problems. I'm
just I'm just going to start writing it.
You can't form
with stuck up [ __ ]
as my videos and messages as as as
my messages and videos. Yeah.
Well, if you join a hangout, I will tell
you're 100% a virgin. The way he's
defending women, bro. The way he's
defending women, the way you're
defending women, it just goes to show
you've never had it. Because the only
people that defend women are are people
that have never had women. Just go just
goes to show you've never you've never
had a woman. It just goes to show
because it's lack of when people that do
this, right? People that do this, right?
I tell you what. Yeah. People that do this,
they do this because they think they're
going to get women. And that's why they defend women,
that's why they literally do it because
they think by defending women it's going
to get them women because they've never
had a woman. So they don't know how to
act. You understand, bro? So that's why
they defend these women. It's quite sad
to be honest, mate. I mean, you get a
lot of white knights in real life as
well. There is no balance. There is no
balance, Joe, because the problem is them.
And that's what a lot of people need to
stop doing in these countries. They need
to stop thinking that it's them and
they're the problem. It's these women.
And you'll find that out when you go to
Asia. When you leave the country, you
will find out. You'll find out that
they're the problem.
Cuz you won't have these problems when
you leave the country.
I'm trying to get this guy to join the
[ __ ] Streamyard, bro. What the [ __ ]
We can actually have a uh we can
actually have a conversation, bro,
instead of [ __ ] typing.
Another one who thinks it's about a game. Ah,
you're a confirmed virgin. He's a
virgin, bro. I'm telling you is you're a
confirmed virgin. He is defending women
blaming game. You're a virgin. He is a [ __ ] virgin.
You need to get laid. You need to get
out your mom's basement, bro.
You really need to get laid. You really,
really need to get laid. Hey, bro. This
guy needs to get laid, bro. I don't even
think I'm all that attractive now. I've
never had any issues at all. Mate, you
need to get out of your dreams. You have
had issues. That's why you're defending
women. That's exact. You 100% have had
issues, which is why you resort to sing.
Watch. You've 100%
million% had had issues, which is why
you resort to sing.
You desperately need to get laid, bro.
This is dangerous.
You desperately need to get laid. 100%.
Ah, projection. I've had more women than
you, Virgin boy. Projection.
No, I'm talking about you, the S on
Reddit. I'm going to get this guy in
Hangouts now. Watch. Now I'm talking
about you, the S on Reddit. That's what
I'm saying. Now I'm talking about you.
I'm talking about the simp on [ __ ]
Reddit. Not me. I'm talking about the
[ __ ] s on [ __ ] Reddit, son.
You know what I'm saying?
Not not projecting. I'm talking about
you the simp on Reddit.
Do you love me? Yeah,
they [ __ ] all evil. You evil and stuck up.
They are all evil and [ __ ] stuck up.
Go get laid.
Go get [ __ ] laid.
Why don't you tell us what you think, Grezy?
They just defend women. Why do they do
it? Why do they do nothing but defend
women? I don't understand. They are all
[ __ ] evil, bro. Otherwise, we
wouldn't waste our time saying they're
[ __ ] evil. Of course, they're [ __ ] evil, man.
I I wrote to him. Yeah. This is what I
wrote to him. Yeah,
I said to him also sent you messages of
them wanting and wasting my time
flaking, ghosting, playing mind games,
but I guess that didn't suit you. I
guess them screenshots didn't suit you.
What do you think, Grezy? That's funny,
isn't it? But I guess that didn't suit you.
Them experiences didn't suit you.
I think that's quite uh my experiences
don't suit these people.
It don't suit you.
Do you know where I got that from? I got
that from the virgin. You know when I
used to meet him? Yeah. He used to say
to me, "It doesn't suit you to believe
it." Believe what? You're [ __ ] virgin.
What am I believing? He said, "It
doesn't suit you." Yeah. It's like these
people, "My experiences don't suit you." Yeah.
Yeah. You live in America and you've
approached all these women and none of
them's ever said they've got a boyfriend.
You must be living in fairy tale land,
bro. Cuz bro, that's happened to anyone
that's approached. Even people that get
[ __ ] Even people that get [ __ ]
He is I think he's living in La La Land.
He is literally living in La La Land.
And then he and then he reverses it by
trying to say, "Oh, because they don't
want to date you." Like he just ignores
everything that they've done, all the
wrong that they do, and then just just
twists it to himself. [ __ ] weirdo weasel. Yeah,
it's pretty [ __ ] up, isn't it?
Why don't you tell us what you think, Grezy?
All the experiences are so different to
what you hear on Reddit quality. You get
loads of people that give advice, but no
one ever tells you that people will
pretend they got boyfriends. No one ever
tells you this.
No one ever tells you that. You, you know,
But being in a relationship don't mean
anything because you're in a
relationship with one woman.
You're in a relationship with one
[ __ ] woman. That's not all these
other women. What the [ __ ] do people
think that because they've been in one
relationship, they know more about
women? That is one woman.
That is not several women. You know what
I'm saying, bro?
What the [ __ ] I've always wondered
that. You know, you know,
you don't need to be in a relationship
to to know what people are like. You
know, you can just meet them for [ __ ]
long enough. What the [ __ ] Why do you
have to hold their hand and [ __ ] help
them through their [ __ ] period to
know what they're [ __ ] like? What the
I think they just come and just read it
just to annoy people. Bro, I I actually
feel greedy. Yeah, it's coming to annoy people.
And you need to get out of this mindset
that all women are evil. It's not a
mindset. It's reality.
It's reality from experiences.
It's reality from my experiences.
My My mindset My mindset will change
when my experiences change.
I think that's fair enough.
I think that's fair enough to be honest.
My mindset will change when my experiences change. Yeah.
That's the way mindsets change, isn't it?
Mindset is shaped by your
by your life experiences. Yeah.
Normal approaches. No more messages.
Good actions. Yeah.
They're just trying to bait me. It ain't
working. It ain't going to work. Cuz all
these people are trying to do, they're
just trying to bait you.
They're just trying to bait you, bro. Listen
again. making making up stuff.
Showed you normal approaches. Normal messages.
Stop trying to bait me. It's not going to work. Yep.
One second, bro.
One second. I'm going to send you the thing. So yeah,
there you go, Monty.
So yeah, I believe it when I see
equality. They say that women aren't
evil and they're all different. I've
been hearing it for years. Never been
shown any different. I think I've met a
lot of people as well. Quality
Marty, someone's calls you dis someone's
calling you disabled.
Yeah, they must be more disabled than me
just for even mentioning disabled,
you know. Yeah. What you doing, PG? [ __ ] man. Yeah, man.
Why are you going out tonight? Are you
not at all?
Not at all. Yeah. You want about that
guy underneath the last comment, ain't you?
Yeah. Yeah. That guy's Have you seen that guy?
Yeah. I told that guy to meet me. He was
in [ __ ] thingies chat today. Told him
to meet me. He was in [ __ ]
um who name Natalie. Natalie Bible
Basher. The one who [ __ ] got squirt tits. Yeah.
Yeah. He was in there. The one from
what? The one from Nottingham.
Yeah. Yeah. The one at the one at the
bottom there with the man with a bald
head. He was in that room this morning.
He was having a wank over n he was
literally masturbating overn this
morning because I ended up on this panel
that he put him off his wank.
Yeah, completely put him off his wank. P you
what you doing anyways? I hate women. I
hate women. Me
dumb. Definitely not as dumb as you. You think [ __ ]
these self reflectors little [ __ ] PG.
Yeah, that's why they don't bother me.
They don't bother me either, man. [ __ ] guns.
No. So, what's what's your plans tonight then, PJ?
Just chilling in bed.
Chilling in bed. Yeah, I had a morning
dog this morning. Nah, that's what you
do, mate. Over your dog.
Over the diesel.
Yeah. Where's your dog, PJ? My mom's.
And what about the staff?
I don't know, mate. Well, there you go then, PJ.
Oh [ __ ] You can bring diesel up. You
want Ps. I'm just going to bring up your
dog. You can bring up Diesel.
Yeah, that's fine.
So, how's your mom keeping anyways? Good. is here. Yeah,
that's good. That's good. Why you on
YouTube, PG? I thought you quit. Why you
going to turn these spastics for?
I was nothing better to I got nothing
better to do. Yeah, but didn't you say
last night you're going to be deleting your YouTube
and not coming back on? I am.
I thought you was I thought you was
leaving as well.
I can't. I'm addicted.
I'm addicted. Me, PJ, it's like It's like crap.
YouTube's like crack, mate. I get
addicted. Yeah, man.
Yeah, I know. I leave every day. I leave
and I turn off my live stream. I'm going
to come back on it. Yeah.
You and R can have a sword fight.
No, you want a sword fight with Rise.
No, not at all. You do want a sword
fight with Rise. No, not at all, mate.
What are you doing, PGA? Cuz I have you
a sword fight if you want.
No. sword fight.
Me and you can have a sword fight. PG
one second. Hold on.
Come on. Let me back. Hold on. I'm with
this car. I'm read it. One second.
I like money, but I'm just arguing with
someone on Reddit, so I can't even.
They say women aren't the problem.
Quality polers. Quality polers. They say
women aren't the problem, but you go out
every Saturday and it seems to be pretty similar. I mean,
I mean, I actually live stream places
that I go into, but apparently they're
they're not the problem. And every all
of the things I've shown is not true.
All of my experiences are not true, and
all of my
text messages are not true.
So, they're not the problem at all. Okay,
fine. If that's what they think, then
that's that's on them, isn't it? Yeah. Okay.
They always make excuses for women.
I noticed that they always defend them, you know. [Music]
These people on Reddit, man, they're [ __ ] idiots.
I'm not being a simp to treat women like
they're human. They're not [ __ ]
human. They're [ __ ] evil.
They're not [ __ ] human. They're [ __ ] evil.
[ __ ] evil life.
Yeah, this guy's never approached.
Yeah, this guy has never approached,
lad. He's He showed me Snapchat
messages. Okay. Right. This guy's never
approached. He's just a s. Yeah,
he's a s, mate. Yep.
What do they say, Cherry? When you
approach these women, what do they say?
They just want to make excuses as to why
they're not interested in this country.
That's a westernized country. They just
want to make excuses and blame the man,
whoever the [ __ ] it is. That's what they
do. They love to blame.
Like, the truth hurts. That's what it
is. The truth hurts with these people.
You know the truth hurts with these people.
Problem is they have 100%.
I mean I don't know how many times I'm
going to keep giving people the benefit
of the doubt. you know,
you know, how many times are you going
to keep um
it literally doesn't
I think I'm just going to give up with
it all to be honest to do with evil
again. I don't know why I went out
again. I don't know. I think I went to meet someone.
Yeah, I think I'm just going to give up
completely again, bro. To be honest,
like I did last time for 3 weeks.
That's how bad it gets. It literally
gets that bad.
It literally gets that depressing.
This is another thing that people on
Reddit will tell you. Yeah.
But apparently they're not evil and I'm wrong. Okay,
women are not evil.
You keep telling yourself that
action speak louder than words. Eh,
they are all the same. They're all all
evil as well. Yep.
Why would this guy fall for? Bye-bye. Bye-bye now.
Ask me if I've ever had sex I've ever
dated. Bye-bye now. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye now. Asking stupid questions. Stupid questions.
You think if someone dates one woman
that means they all of a sudden know
everything about women? Well, so you you
need to date people to know what the
whole population is like. Okay, bro. Wow.
Yes, I have actually dated a woman and
she was also a [ __ ]
13 times if you must know. Yeah. Yes, I
have actually. And she was also an
entitled [ __ ] Next question. Yeah.
Yes, I have. And she was an entitled
[ __ ] as well.
Just like some of the one night stands
I've had. Your point is
Okay. Your point is you asked a question
10 times and I've answered it. And your
point is what?
And your point is what?
What I am doing, bro? I am doing it. I
am doing. But I just thought I'd just
give this person the beneficiary of the doubt, lad.
Yeah, they are evil. I just thought I'd
give this person the benefit of the
doubt. Cuz you know, they wanted to meet
from a couple of weeks ago. Cuz I've
gave a lot of people the benefit of the
doubt. I gave a lot of people the
benefit of the doubt. Yeah.
People just do nothing but defend women.
And they probably had less women than
you as well.
Ah, the insult insult. The insult, the
insult, insults, bro. That's how you
know you got him rattled. When they
start talking about Elliot Rogers, you
know they've got no fight left in them.
You know they've got no fight left in
him. When they start mentioning incels,
you know you've won the argument. You know,
you know you won the argument when you
start talking about Elliot [ __ ] Rogers.
[ __ ] Elliot Rogers. That's so old now.
That's boring. You know you've got them.
You've got them where it hurts. When
they start calling you an incel, when
you got no argument left in you, they
throw the incel. Woo! We got him. You
just know you've got them, bro.
And yes, I have dated and she was a [ __ ]
as well. And yes, I have had one night
stands and yes, they were a [ __ ] as
well, which has no relevance to
anything. You know, I had I didn't have
KFC. I just had a whole chicken.
You're sick. Defending women will never
get you laid. Stop defending them.
It's embarrassing. Stop [ __ ]
defending women all your life. It's
embarrassing. What do you get out of it, man?
The way I interact is completely fine. Yeah.
They are the stuck up [ __ ] not me.
But yeah, the reason I I have given up, but like
um I just thought I'd just give this
person the benefit of the doubt.
I basically have given up. You know how
many detoxes I go on? They are all the
same. They literally are all the same.
You could try again for another 10 years
and people will be saying they're not
all the same, but they are all the same
evil scum. Every single time you go out
again, you're going to meet the same
scummy women, the same attitude, the
same [ __ ] Are you remember? Are you
forgetting how long I gave up for now?
You're not going to bait me, bro. So,
just stop it. I keep saying to this guy
on Reddit, you're not going to bait me.
You're not going to draw me out.
Nah, mate. I'm not doing that. No,
I'm not paying for sex. I don't even
have sex. So,
never. And even if you offer money,
money don't even work anyways.
And I don't have um I wouldn't be doing
that because A I'm not doing that. B um
it wouldn't even work even if I was
going to do that. So yeah, I'm all right. Thanks.
I'm good, bro. Yeah,
I still got a number. She just said
she's not going to meet again.
I'm almost there, mate.
I'm going to be bored this week.
Probably going to get put off going to
the gym now.
Oh man, the sooner this life ends, the better, lad.
Yeah, she's probably down on holiday.
Nope. She lives here. Yeah.
That way you won't resort to sing.
I said to him, apply that to yourself
and then you won't resort to sing.
No, she not down on her day. She lives here. Yep.
Oh, how many times you going to give
people the benefit of the doubt?
before you realize, [ __ ] it, all women
are actually the same and we should stop
taking people's advice. Like, how many
times are we going to stop taking these
pe like give we need to stop giving
people the beneficiary doubt as Timmy
calls it? They're all the same. You saw
me in that nightclub last week.
I don't think you saw me do any
approaches, but they said it as well,
didn't they? Boyfriend, boyfriend,
boyfriend. They are literally all the same.
Nah, mate. I don't meet people off YouTube.
Yeah, I don't meet people off YouTube.
Actions speak louder than words. I
believe it when I see it.
This 40 year old woman is trying to call
me. I met her and her husband the other day.
Think you've misclicked me there, mate. Yeah.
It will get you rejected and your time wasted.
You know when they start calling you an
intel, you know that you've won.
When they start throwing around the
insel word, you know you've won, lad.
Uh, random bird. It was actually
somebody that I went on a date with for
4 hours. Jay Willow, just thought it'd
be be nice to put up.
What? Are you jealous or something? Are
you jealous that I was able to go on a
date with somebody that looks like that?
Sounds like jealousy to me, bud.
And me and you get along, bro. Like incel.
I love it when people call me an incel,
bro. Cuz you just know you've beat them.
They've got no fight left in them. It's
like an old man being being thrown to
the floor and smashed up. Yeah. And the
only thing they can say is
inel because you've beat them, bro.
Everything you said is the truth.
It's not a random bird. It's somebody
that I went on a date with for a few
hours and yeah, we was drunk. So, why not, bro?
What's What's wrong with that, bro? Why
not? Why can't I put fill it up?
She's a standard five out of 10. She's
not a five out of 10, bro.
She is She was [ __ ] sexy. Mother, you
mad? And I'm not a [ __ ] s. And most
of the women I've been on been on dates
with have been like not even all that.
She ain't a five out of 10, bro. She is
literally, bro, she is nice in real
life. And trust me, I don't need to [ __ ] simp
cuz I'm not even seeing her ever again, lad. So,
got five out of 10. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Doesn't really matter anyways, bro. It's
better than anything the virgin can get
in it day will. It's better than
anything the virgin can get.
Who the [ __ ] is Who is Miss World, lad?
I need to change that picture anyways,
bro. It was just to kind of get the virgin jealous.
just to get the virgin jealous. You know
what I mean? Jay, we're like the virgin, you know? Uh
I don't know. Yeah, it was fun. It was
cool, wasn't it, though?
It was quite cool. I like that.
Yeah, bro. Two weeks to go, I can
finally get this [ __ ] all.
They're just not interested in this
country. Simple as that. I'm not
mentioning any names, J. cuz I'm a
law-abiding citizen. But he knows who he is.
A certain person that can't afford Stone Island.
A certain person that's on a thousand
quid a month.
You know who I'm talking about. J will relay.
I'm just taking my bank card with me, buddy.
I'm going to Asia because they're just
not interested in this country. DJ were like
blocked me. What a loser.
Certain person with a special needs one. Yeah.
Yeah. A special needs one. Yeah. That's
something I've never had. A special needs girlfriend. Yeah.
Yeah. I admit it. I've never [ __ ] with
a special needs girl. I admit
I don't think she's a seven a five out
of 10. I think she's [ __ ] sexy. Me,
the one that I went out with, she looks
better in person.
Yeah. Well, she's the best date I've
been on so far anyways.
But yeah, [ __ ] her anyways. Uh Yeah. So, what?
Don't you think it's weird how I've had
all these women and I've never had to
resort to a disabled girl?
No, I've never had to resort to a
disabled girl ever. Never me.
Never in my life have I had to resort to
a disabled girl ever.
And I've been with some bad bad looking people
like this young lady here. Okay.
What the [ __ ] was I thinking when I went
with that mate? [ __ ] hell. What was I
thinking when I went with that young
lady? I must had [ __ ] in my eyes. You
know what I'm saying?
Must had [ __ ] in my [ __ ] eyes, son.
I must had [ __ ] in my eyes. J will I [Music]
but this guy has not approached women
because if he approached women even in
America you would get rejected. They're
[ __ ] in America. I see videos all the
time. And how do I know? Cuz this [ __ ]
comes from America.
Yeah. Because this cuz that [ __ ] comes
from America. If anything, they're
[ __ ] worse over there than they are
here. I hate I hate Americans.
You know what I'm saying? [ __ ] But
he's approached and he's never got I've
got a boyfriend. Yeah, bro. You wish,
man. You wish. Even the people that get
girls are, you know, even people that get girls.
That's my little friend. Yuck. Yuck.
That's not my mommy. That's my mommy.
That's my mommy. be
not my mama.
Yeah, you used to like that, didn't you?
No, my mommy's laney.
I said to this woman, I don't like you.
You're flatchested, but maybe if you got
pregnant, then maybe your boobies will get bigger.
Could you imagine? Uh,
now he's my mate, bro.
We spent my birthday together. We met
like two years ago. We've done New
Year's Eve together. He's a cool guy,
man. He's from Indonesia.
So, what I was saying is
um could you imagine USA's boobs if she
got pregnant? Grezy,
they'd be hanging to the floor.
Greasy, they'll be hanging to the floor. Imagine that.
Yeah. Imagine, bro.
Yeah. I think you fancy USA easy me.
I think you fancy her. Yeah. Heat. Yeah,
I've got this person, you know, she's
wrote to me.
Hey, I would love to, but I have I have
to leave tomorrow
for my session.
I have to leave tomorrow for my session
in Santi for two months. Maybe after
summer. Kiss emoji.
Who the [ __ ] goes to Santi for 2 months?
You're full of [ __ ] Another one not interested. Oh no.
Another one that's not interested in this country.
Who the [ __ ] goes to Greece for [ __ ] two months?
Dude, this was this one was from Saturday.
I'm just going to start flirting with her
for the lows in it. [ __ ] it. I got no
number. Got nothing to lose now, you know.
Nope. She's white.
No, she's white.
Yeah, the Italian one didn't have big
big boobs, but they were big enough.
You want to see her? Okay. One sec.
Oh, it doesn't let me. It doesn't let me
screenshot it. Oh, I can do it with my
other phone. God, I can. One second. Can
I've got lamb for tea today, Grezy. I
got lamb for tea.
That [ __ ] Australian one looks about
[ __ ] 14, bro.
It's like what Ant-Man says. He likes
them younger. I don't like them younger.
I like them around my age. I'll show you
her if you want. One sec.
One second, bro.
Want to see her? Yeah.
Okay. Got another phone. Eh,
looks all right, is it?
I mean, these are the kind this is the
kind of age group you uh surround yourself with
when you uh go to these clubs even
though you've got to be 18. This is this
is this is what was making me really
think. Yeah. Should I keep going to
these places? Greasy.
Should I keep going to these places? And
I think, you know,
I don't know
because the thing is they're all they're
all the same age group and they're all
the same [ __ ]
they've all got the same attitude and
even though obviously they're legal to
go in there and stuff, but you don't
really get many older people go there
like like 27 and stuff, you know what I mean? So
I mean you do get them but so so
I mean yeah
obviously if she says yeah I'm not going
to say no to it am I? Doesn't matter how
old she is.
Um, obviously to an extent, you know,
I'm not Antman,
but even if she's 18, I'll still [ __ ]
do it. Yeah, [ __ ] that, bro. You have to
get what you can in this country. Is
that right, Grezy? Is that right, Grecy?
Is that right?
Is that right, Grezy?
Yeah, if she's 1890, I'd still do it obviously.
Why? The neighbor called me a pedo, Joe.
Yeah, the neighbor called me a pedo. I
just walked past. Just ignored him. He's
trying to bait me out in it.
Yeah, he said I was a pedo. He's just
trying to bait me out, bro. Everybody
knows I'm not Yeah, he's trying to bait me out. Ha.
Yeah. He's just trying to bait me out.
Yeah. It's not going to work, bro. It's
not going to work.
I just walk past him, bro. Yeah, cuz
he's trying to bait me out, bro. That's
what he's trying to do, bro. I I listen,
bro. I ignored an old woman that kept
staring at me. She gave me the dirtiest
look. So why am I scared of an old
woman? Bro, I'm not scared of anyone. I
just can't be bothered with them.
And you got to understand that my mom
lives there. So,
you know, my mom lives there sort of thing.
The cops knew there was something fishy.
Yeah. Yeah. But at the end of the day,
bro, listen. The way I got to see it is
he was saying all of this [ __ ] on
YouTube. No, no, no, no, no. He saw me
there. He could have done something.
He know he done nothing. So at the end
of the day, bro, like he was the one
running up his mouth. Just walk past
him, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Cuz he wanted to try and get
me action. I just wal past him. It's the
same thing if a woman done it. It's the
same thing if someone else done it, you know.
Listen, you wouldn't do anything, Joe.
I'd come to you tomorrow and I'd call
you a pedo and you wouldn't do anything
about it. Yeah. So you want me to go and
[ __ ] him up and then my mom will have to
move house. Is that what you want? So
you want me to go there, [ __ ] him up and
then I would never be able to go there
again and then my mom will literally
have to move house even if I don't live
there. Yeah, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Yeah, cuz that's really
gonna like solve stuff, is it? Yeah. If
I'm a pedo, why don't you do something
to a pedo? You know, you they were
running up their [ __ ] mouth for god
knows how [ __ ] long. I had to hear
it. So that's it. Yeah,
I will say something next time, but I'm
not going to start hitting people. I
know what I'm going to say next time. I
was like severely hung over. I just
walked past. I'm going to say something
next time, but I'm not going to start
hitting people. I already know what I'm
going to say.
I will say something, but I'm not going
to um I'm not going to say that. I'm not
going to say that. I'm I'm just going to
do it in a smart way. But I'm not
fighting people. Obviously, unless they
put their hands on me, then obviously I'm not.
I thought of some good things anyways. So,
but nothing's going to be like
insulting. It's just going to be
cleverly just own them, both.
Yeah, I already know what I'm going to
say, but it's not going to be like, "Oh,
[ __ ] this." Or, "No, no, no, no." It's
going to be worded cryptically.
And to be honest, I'm just going to say
to him, "You can have the first punch."
That's what I'm going to say, bro. Like,
I'm going to do it very smartly,
like, but I will say something next
time. Yeah, 100%.
But I'm not fighting or like going to
try to like trigger like a thing. That's
up to them, bro. Anyone wants to put
their hands on me, they're getting it.
Simple. But that's I'm not going to
start like saying madness. I'm just
going to say everything smartly cuz now
I've had time to think of it.
And I said and I'll just say if you're
going to do something, do something.
That's it. And I think that's a good way
to put it because you're defending
yourself and you're leaving the ball in
their court. So I think that's that's a
good way to be honest. Yeah. 100%, bro.
And the mad thing is I'm not scared. I'm
not scared of anyone. Like, you should
have saw how that woman was looking at me.
Like, giving me a bro, there could be
anyone and I still would have done the
same thing. You know what I'm saying? I
still would have done exactly the same thing
because the way I saw it is, oh, I
thought things was going to go well with
this person. I kind of feel like I had a
little bit to lose. I was in a good
mood. I couldn't be bothered getting in.
I couldn't be bothered getting into it with people.
But I'm not going to lie, when I was
drinking the other day, I was messaging
my mom and I was I'm thinking of coming
out and it I'm thinking of coming now.
Like on Saturday, I'm thinking of really
coming and causing Nate.
But that's and I was in a good mood and
that in it. So I just pull it down to
oh, they've got no life. They're just
trying to bait me. [ __ ] him minute. You
know what I'm saying? Cuz I was in a
good mood. But if I was in a bad not a
bad mood or a normal mood, bro,
obviously I would have
doesn't matter who they are. So
I won't be hitting anyone. I won't be
doing anything. I'll just say something
very, very smartly
and that's it.
And it shouldn't be you're saying this,
you're saying that. It should be what
are they saying? They're the ones that
have come on YouTube. They're the ones
that are doing all of this. and they're
the ones that are doing all of that, but
they're not doing anything. You know
what I'm saying? So,
it should be what actually they're
saying, not what you're saying. You know
what I mean?
And obviously I'll say about the pedo
[ __ ] it being obviously pe to annoy
people on YouTube and [ __ ] obviously. So, yeah,
that's all you need to do. And then
after that, see with these people,
right, what they like to do is they like
to It never turns into fights though.
Here's the thing. This this this stuff
never turns into fights because when you
actually defend yourself, right, no one
ever bothers. No one ever bothers.
That's the thing. Even though you'd
probably lose or not not probably lose,
but you could lose some of them, they
won't even go there, bro. As soon as you
defend yourself, they they they wouldn't
even go there.
It never even escalates to that
cuz I done it with a neighbor before
like around here [ __ ] ages ago. Big
[ __ ] He was big [ __ ] [ __ ] he was.
And after that he just started like
licking my ass. So
but it was a different scenario. I was
living like by myself. Like my mom
wasn't living there. So like I had like but yeah
but yeah that's all you need to do. Just
need to say something but don't actually
get into like any fights and [ __ ] Yeah. [Music]
Obviously if someone grabs you and they
start trying to like knock on the door
then you have to do something 100%. Yeah.
I feel like at my age, you get too old
for it. You just want a peaceful life,
you know? That's how I see it. You just
want a peaceful, normal life. And the
fact that it was months and months and months ago,
right? So, you just think, "Well, [ __ ]
it. I can't be bothered. Doesn't matter
who they are." Do you know what I mean?
But yeah, you should have just said
something like, "Oh, well, I'm here. Why
don't you do something?"
You know? Yeah,
cuz I don't think my mom understands my
temper. Well, she does understand my
temper. I've got a big temper and I will
just like it will just cause more and
more more more more problems.
So that's why I'm not going to start
like banging on doors and causing all
mayhem. I'm not doing any of that [ __ ]
But I will say something 100%.
And if that woman looks at me again, I'm
going to say something as well.
But no, nothing like banging on doors
and smashing people up. [ __ ] all that.
You need to put the ball in their court.
Like you, all you need to do is show
that you're not scared of them and give
them a chance to to actually do
something if they really want to do
something. And then chances are they're
not going to do anything. And then you
can just Yeah. leave it.
No banging on people's door, no smashing
windows, none of none of that [ __ ] you know.
They're the ones that started it. So, at
the end of the day, you can give them a
chance to finish it. Simple.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
But I'm really not scared, matey. Too me.
But next time I'm there, I'll be back
there soon as well. Anyways, cuz I have
to do a welfare check. I will definitely
say something 100%. If I see them, I
I'll say something obviously,
but I got to go out my way to do it. But 100%. Yeah.
I want to ideally like do in front of my
mom as well so she knows like that, bro.
Trust me, I'm not scared. Like I don't
know how many times I've had to actually say that.
But yeah. Oh, he's my friend, man.
Yeah, he's my friend.
He's a good guy, eh?
I don't know why people want to start
drama and [ __ ] I just want a peaceful life, me,
I only come to do a [ __ ] welfare check.
I just want a [ __ ] peaceful life. I
don't know how people can be that age
and still be salty after all them
months. That's a madness, bro.
Jesus Christ, man. That's [ __ ] up.
That is mad, bro. That is madness.
And it's not even like you were saying
stuff about him and his kids. Then then
I could be I can understand it. Like he
just wants to show off because he thinks
people are scared of him around the area. But
what I'm going to do is I'm going to sit
when I go back there. I'm going to sit
by the window and I'm going to wait. I'm
going to wait for him to come out.
That's what I'm going to do. And I'm
going to go straight outside.
Trust me, I'll stay there 2 days if I
have to, bro.
Cuz I think you've had your ego trip now
for a little bit too long. You know what
I'm saying? You've had it for like a
little bit too long now, bro. And it
needs to be it needs to be shut down, you know?
Dude, that's all it is. It needs to be
shut down. Just like that. USA is It
needs to be shut down. Your ego needed Yeah.
She got big [ __ ] ego check, bro. Yeah.
But yeah, next time if you see any of
them again, you you you have to
cuz there's emotions, bro, in it.
There's there's obviously commotion if
you'll bump in again or whatever. So,
you basically need to say if you're
going to do something, do it.
You know, we've seen comments. We've
seen [ __ ] videos. You know what I'm saying? What?
Oh, this is good. Yeah. Yeah, that's it. Ah,
you hate that, eh?
Hate me, man.
We're going to have to cook the [ __ ]
lab today, though, bro. [ __ ]
Are you still there, though? If you give
me If you give me £300, I'll go there now.
I'll go there now and I'll stay alive.
You give me 300 pound, I'll go there now
and stay live
and I'll cause chaos,
Joe. I'll cause absolute chaos.
300 pound, bro. Stay live. I go live on
my other phone.
I'll show you some good drama, bro.
Not [ __ ] um L J knocking on people's [ __ ] door.
And then [ __ ] hiding behind the
[ __ ] gate. I was madness, bro.
No one on this side is £300. Yeah,
sounds about right.
What was what was what was the favorite
day? What was your favorite day I've
been on Grezy? You think
out of all of the women I've met, which
one was your favorite? Breezy,
but you get to that age where you just
want a peaceful life, mate.
You know, that's why I don't really come
on here much anymore, cuz I just want a peaceful life.
What? The Aussie one or the escort?
You've never seen Chinese, is he?
But you've never seen her.
Oh, what? The one that looks quite
young. We What? Why was she your
favorite? Well, because of the pet kangaroo.
What? The little pet kangaroo one.
Oh, the pet kangaroo. Isn't it? Oh, Grezy.
I've got a funny one for you. Grievy.
Me and Chinese Aussie Izzy.
Me. Me and a Chinese Izzy. Yeah.
Me and a Chinese Izzy with a pet kangaroo
and my son being Chinese Australian
watching Al Stewart having a beer and a
cat backwards. Imagine that, Grezy.
Ah, what a lovely sight.
Yeah. And then a little kangaroo having
a bottle of milk. Oh, greeny.
How cute is that?
Uh, why am I in a That Chinese man is my friend.
That Chinese man is uh my my friend. Yep.
Went down under, mate. Went down under
the little pet kangaroo with the milk bottle. Greavvesy.
That's so cute with a stone island little top.
Yeah. What's What's wrong with that?
How often do you think women have sex,
Quezy? Like single women,
how often do you think they have sex?
like normal people that are single that
are not in relationships.
Would you guess it?
Yeah, but we don't get to have sex with them.
They're made to suck dick. I don't even
I wouldn't even [ __ ] one of them again.
I would just get them to suck my dick again.
Yeah, we can't get nothing. How
depressing is that?
Yeah, we can't get nothing.
So, how do I be one of these men's um side biddy?
You can't, mate.
And man's like, "Oh, there's something
wrong with you, PJ. You know, you've
tried everything in this country.
There's nothing more to try." That's
what he said. Grezy, is he right? He
said, "There's something seriously wrong
with you. You've tried everything."
That's what he said. He's right in it, Grezy.
Obviously, he's right in it.
Yeah, he's in Thailand.
He's living in Thailand now. Greasy.
Yeah, you just have to give up.
I've got my Pekka out right now. Greasy.
Greasy. I've got my pecker out right now. Let's
give it a little stroke.
Yeah, I've got my pecker out now.
I greasy. How do you know what that
means? No, Greasy. Me, the pet baby
kangaroo, Chinese uh Australian Izzy,
and my son watching Al Stewart with his
with his Aussie accent. What?
I agree. Do you remember I said to LT,
"You wanted to get a Morgan Nick.
You always wanted to get her
knickknacks." And he's like, "Oh, you
trolled me." I was like, "Nah, you want
to get her knickers." Knicknocks.
Yeah. I love that little word. It's so
clean, didn't it? Her licks.
[ __ ] pair of [ __ ] Leave a pair of
[ __ ] pair of [ __ ] Easy. Yeah.
Why does she use so many filters?
Yeah, she she stole that same number, the [ __ ]
My little head. Nah, it's not as little
as yours, buddy.
I think Greensy fancies her.
Yeah, your other picture.
She's not lost, man. She's [ __ ]
stinking. She put another picture up,
Grezy, on her Instagram, you know, the
other day and it was [ __ ] stinking,
son. Oh, I think I got it. One second,
Oh, I deleted it. [ __ ] sake, man.
Yeah. Where is it?
No, I must have screenshotted it. I must one second.
See, when people meet me, they never see
the end of me, do they?
They never see the end of me, do they,
Greasy? Once they meet me once.
This is her without filters.
Nope. Not at all. Because I know the real her.
Now this is the real her. She's [ __ ] stinking, son. Yeah,
she's [ __ ] stinking.
Yeah, I don't I just don't like tattoos, period.
She's [ __ ] stinking, son.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. It's filters.
Here's her, bro. It's filters.
[ __ ] Are you ever going to get a a tattoo, Grezy?
I remember when I almost got killed over
YouTube. Uh Greasy,
that would have been my That would have
been my life gone over the same website
you can watch Stitch on.
The same website you can watch Stitch
on. That would have been playing at my funeral.
It's not even funny though, is it
really? Nah. Nah, that's not funny, bro.
Someone breaking into your house and
killing you over YouTube. How can you
even find that funny, bro? That's not
funny. It's not funny, Grezy. Ah.
I'm just going to start trolling these women now.
Stitch, you're back. Stitch.
Hello. Haven't watched you at the pictures yet.
I haven't watched you at the pictures yet. Stitchy,
do you love me? Stitch,
who do you love more? Me or Gresy?
Oh, do you know what? I like Grievy. I
like Buzz Light You and Woody. They're
lovely little characters. Stitch. Yeah.
I do you remember Buzz Lighty you and
Woody? No. They were lovely little characters.
They were lovely little characters. Did
you remember Woody?
I don't think you know Toy Story, do
you, Grezy? That's a banger.
Yeah, just one sec. She's going to meet me,
right? Hold on. She said she's going to
meet me. One second.
What she say? Hold on.
Yeah, she's she said that she's free.
So, let me know what your schedule is saying.
It seems to be easier to get dates in
the summer greasy, but they're just not
interested in this country. Yeah.
He can't get attached attached anymore
because he's already found his mama.
Because he's already found his mama. You
remember Grezy? I'm surprised that these
people are so naive to [ __ ] filters
now. Do you know that
because he's already found his mama?
He's already found his mama.
He's already found his mother lives. A
thing not Peter Pley's mama. I hate you
people. You mock You just mock me. All
you do is [ __ ] mock me every day. Is it?
You [ __ ] mock me every [ __ ] day,
bro. I'm sick of it because he's already
found his mama.
Who's my mama? Greasy. Sing not Peter
Belly's mama. Remember that one? Sig not
Peter Belly's mama.
Oh, this Italian woman said that her
birthday was at April April the 14th.
And that's my favorite month, March and
April. You remember my birthday, Grezy?
Do you do you remember mine?
Do you have a bad? Huh? Buzz. Buzzy. Where's Woody?
What the hell?
Where's Woody? What have you done to
You ain't killed him, have you, Buzz?
I was like, "Yeah, where's Woody?"
I'm all right.
I'm trying to find Woody.
I've been recording his phone, but he's
not been picking up for some reason.
Yeah, he's not picking up for some pizza. Clear deck.
Clear lower deck.
Clear lower deck. You can do that. Yeah.
That made me laugh, you know. Yeah,
I almost got attacked on the stream.
The lady was all right. Just to see if
lady was all right. Grieves. I almost got attacked.
That's quite scary, isn't it?
Yeah. Anyways, where's Woody gone?
I wait for myself a couple of time. 2 seconds.
Gy, it's got to be this mug.
It can't be any other mug. One second. Spiderman. Spiderman Mark.
This is Spiderman. Papa.
Hang on a minute. Ah,
you're a little character.
You can't have a bet. You can't have a
bet. A pet kangaroo.
You can't have a pet hanger.
She's a cat. Jeez,
a [ __ ] cat.
I'm a guy. Guys,
all guys out there
guys do it. Do it. Yeah. All
right, back in the course now.
I get these sexy [ __ ]
What's going on here then?
Oh my god. Yeah, it's too hot. I'm I'm
just in the little nestles. Um Grezy
having a little vape. Yeah. Yep.
What do you think of that? This is what
the pet kangaroo
the pet kangaroo would look like.
Look at that. Imagine that. A pet kangaroo. Yeah.
Yeah. That's cute. Is it?
And imagine somebody like hurt the
kangaroo. We'd have to beat them up. It grim.
That's my little kanga.
Yeah. This Italian woman said I said to
her, "What's your favorite animal?" She
said, she said elephant. I said, "I like
elephants as well.
would be the perfect couple.
What do you see? I like elephants as
well. Do you
do anything? He said he wanted to go to
[ __ ] Canada. You're going to go
[ __ ] Canada? You can't go Canada,
mate. You can't afford it. You're going
to go all the way to [ __ ] Canada Gy.
You're going to go all the way to Canada
with some of the that on you. Some of
they ain't They ain't interested in you.
It ain't interested in you, mate. That's
[ __ ] a long way to go. Is it crazy? Canada,
that's a long way to go.
[ __ ] Canada, eh?
[ __ ] pair of [ __ ]
You ask me, Greaves.
Let's have a look.
What's my second
This old woman said she met her partner
in the gym. [ __ ] paracunts,
right? I'm having a little sneeze now,
Gy. I'll be up in approximately 5 hours.
In approximately 5 hours.
Is that cute, Groovy? Ready for my
little lamb dinner.
Goozy for a little lamb dinner.
You're You're a master troll. You are
greedy. You've got a million accounts.
You got a million accounts. You doing it.
Have you ever licked a vape?
This is triple melon vape.
I don't even know why I'm smoking it to be honest.
I think it is a chargeable one though.
Oh yeah, it is. It is.
Yeah, it is the chargeable one. Yeah,
me and the Italian was was we was
vaping. We was vaping. We was vaping at
the same vape. How cute is that?
Walking around, holding hands, having a
little vape together,
talking about the future. No, what a lovely sight.
What a lovely site.
What a [ __ ] lovely site, mate.
There certain people can't handle a
curry. She had a nice curry yesterday, Greavves.
And there certain people can't it
grieves. You just can't hack a vape and
that's absolutely fine. Sorry, hack a
curry. That's absolutely fine.
Everyone's made for it. You know,
the world's take cover.
My friend said he done a he done a an
approach on the train yesterday. Grezy.
And at the end she says, "No, sorry. I
have a boyfriend."
What do you think I done, Grezy? I was
[ __ ] lying in bed. But what do you
think I done when I heard? Huh?
Yeah. What do you think I done when I heard that?
No, sorry. I have a boyfriend. Ah, boyfriend.
Ah, by my friend.
You know what I'm going to start saying
when they say I'm going to be I'm going
to say you need a new one. You need an upgrade.
What do you think, Greasy? You need an upgrade.
What do you think of that?
Yeah, you need an upgrade. I used to say
I've got a boyfriend as well. Do you
remember the old school Peter Belly
groups? I used to say I've got a
boyfriend as well. They'll be like I
used to know I used to say I've got a
boyfriend. Don't let that stop us. Give
it a little while. You never know what's
around the corner, Greasy.
Says it's not funny. You've got an
obsession with that. It's boring. He
says, "Lady, I've got a boyfriend."
[ __ ] He says it's boring.
Yeah. He says that when he went to
Spain, he got it there, too, Grezy. when
he went to Spain, he got it there as
well. I've got a boyfriend in Spain
cuz a lot of people English there isn't
it. And he said when he was on holiday,
they said they had a boyfriend.
Crazy. He said that the only place
you're not going to get that is Asia. He said
that's what he said. He said that's the
only place you're not going to get it. Yeah.
Is he right, Grezy? I think so. It
Yeah, I think so. I'm guess I guess so. Yeah.
I have a boyfriend.
He said to me that you're obsessed with
that. He said he said it's boring. It is
boring. No, it is boring. It is boring.
Cuz how many times did we hear it, Grezy? Huh?
How many times did we hear that? Huh?
Now I'll never know. Yeah. He says, "Oh,
I really wanted to approach her. I
really wanted to approach her." Right.
And uh he's like, "I should have just
done it. Now I'll never know.
Now I'll never know."
You know, that's why I done that one by
the corner shop the other day. Um,
Cactus, cuz if I didn't do it, I would
have never known.
I would have never known.
Now I do know. I got a number and she
didn't even reply.
So now I do know, don't I? Yeah, I Yeah,
now I'll never know.
And my friend was like, I'll just do it.
I don't I can't be [ __ ] But then I
done it. I went for the kill cactus.
I never know. Yeah.
Other guys do it. He doesn't He doesn't
like it though, does it? When when
somebody when somebody does it to him.
Other guys do it. He says, "Oh, you have
you have a go at me. I'm [ __ ] ill." I
says, "Mate, I used to have to listen to
your [ __ ] every Saturday.
Every Saturday I [ __ ]
Yeah, exactly, bro. Yeah.
You miss 100. Yeah.
And you also miss 100% of the shots that
you do take.
Oh, he doesn't like it though, does he?
when someone else says it's him.
Why and man said to me, "Captain is the
only place you're not going to hear why
I've got a boyfriend is uh
um is Asia." Yeah, I was going to go on
the table. I was going to jump on the
Weather Spoons table and start dancing,
bro. And I was going to start [ __ ]
dancing. Say, "H, how are you all
doing?" My friend wants to know. Yeah,
cuz I'm [ __ ] mad, bro. You hear it
time and time and time again.
Yeah. [ __ ] these are [ __ ] mega
trollers, bro. Yeah. Other guys.
Yeah. I asked him. I said, "Don't ask
me, mate. I don't [ __ ] know. You ask
them." And he said, "I'm not going to
ask them because it's weird." I said,
"Stop [ __ ] telling me about it then.
Look at that tie woman that man's with.
She's [ __ ] nice, bro. They all look
like Australian, is he? She's one of
them. Them Thai women catches. She's one of them.
Yeah. man said there's nothing funny about it.
He says there's nothing funny about
that. I've got a boyfriend. It's true
though. It's not funny. [Laughter]
He says he takes it serious. He said
it's not funny. No, it's not [ __ ]
[ __ ] It's not funny. I got boyfriend Yeah.
Nah, she just said she doesn't want to
she doesn't want to meet again and stuff
cuz apparently I was still forward.
So, I don't know how I'm going to repair
that one. I don't think I am. I think I'm [ __ ] Nope.
I just said, "Oh, we should go for a
nice meal and stuff." I said, "Oh, yeah.
I came on a bit forward because I've had
like bad experience in the past and I'm
new to this whole dating thing and
stuff." And I was trying to make them
feel sorry for me so they could meet me
again. I said, "Let's go for a nice
meal." And she says, "Oh, sorry, no, but
no hard feelings." I was like, "What a cunt." Yeah. Make love.
Make love. It's cute, isn't it? Yeah.
No, they don't care, mate.
They're horrible old [ __ ] All do you
want to see some [ __ ] Do you want to
see what filters do? Yeah. This is USA
Izzy with filters and this is USA fil
USA Izzy without the filters.
What a difference.
What a difference. She removed that
picture quite quickly because she knows
that she looks like a bit of a spacker cactus. Yeah,
that's not my [ __ ] Bubba, mate.
You remember what I used to say, Cactus?
That's my mama. Nobody else's.
That's not my mama.
Yuck. Yuck. That's not my mama.
Yuck. Yuck. That's not my mama. Yuck.
That That's not my mama.
That's my mama.
That's my mama. Cactus.
That's two heartless [ __ ] Australian
[ __ ] Izzy. And then we got this
Italian. Eh, [ __ ] hell, bro. These
[ __ ] are evil. Why do people say
they're not evil when they literally are evil?
I was thinking that maybe we can make laugh.
I mean, she hasn't blocked me, but
all I was doing is trying to kiss
Cactus. We was holding hands, rubbing
each other's hands, walking along. And
then I said, "Oh, can we kiss?"
I said, "Come on, just give me a kiss,
will you?" that this. Yeah. I just said,
"Give me a kiss, will you?"
There's not to be had.
I mean, if someone don't kiss you on the
first date, they're wasting your time, right?
I always like kisses. I like to be
kissed and huggled. Crey.
Yeah. I said, "Can we kiss after the
four after the four hours?" Yeah.
Let's let's let's have a little kiss.
And then off she went. She ran away.
She ran away. Uh Grezy,
she ran away.
Never to be seen again.
She didn't block me or anything. She
replied, but yeah. Strange, eh?
It's funny about it. I just don't
understand why these people go on dates.
I bet uh when that picture went up
though. No, she lives in London. She
lives in London. Yeah. I bet when that
picture went up though, a certain
greeneyed monster started hitting her.
You know who. The greeneyed monster come out.
You know, Cactus, the greeneyed monster
for Monsters, Inc.
Not mentioning any names at all, mate.
I'm a law abiding citizen here. But, you know, yeah,
it's not my fault. I'm badass
and I can get these sexy [ __ ] It's
the looks my mama gave me. I didn't have
a say in the matter.
Let's have a little smoochy smoochy.
Is that right, Grezy?
Hey, how you doing?
How you doing? You all right?
So, what do you reckon she would have
done? Do you reckon she would have
wasted my time? Uh, Cactus, this
Italian. Anyways, what's your honest
opinion? I think she was just going to
waste my time, I'm guessing. Am I out
partying? Nope. I'm lying in bed having
a little chill out today.
Never for these horrific crimes against children.
Who are you?
I don't know who you are.
What do you think about her? She was
just wasting my time though, Cactus.
And I wasn't approaching the weather spoons.
Yeah, it's probably just wasting my
time, is it?
Yeah. Well, I'm trying to get this other
woman to go on a date.
Then we can make love.
Yeah. She tried to say cuz I was asking
her questions, but I was asking her like,
"When should we meet again?" because I
didn't want to get my time wasted again
and I just know like can we kissing that.
So I don't think I done anything wrong.
I mean I've done things perfect before
and they've and they've still wasted my time. So
Yep. You come on too strong. There's
always an excuse in it, mate. It's
either you come on too strong or you
didn't come on strong enough in it, Cactus. Yep.
It's either you come on too strong or
you you haven't come on strong enough
and you need to flirt. That's why you
you can never win there. There is no in
the middle. You see?
And that's how you avoid the friend
zone. See at the same time cactus.
Okay. So what did you want me to do
then? Just stay with her and nothing
happened and then get friend zoned or
get her to not meet again?
So that's what would have happened. They
probably just they might have not met
you again or they would have met you and
it wouldn't have progressed into anything. So
I mean most dates I've been on I've
kissed them on the first date most dates.
But it doesn't make any sense cactus
because even when you make out with
people Yeah. Say you go on a date and
you make out with someone they'll still ghost you.
They'll still ghost you while something
will happen. You remember that Brazilian
cactus who is kissing kissing kissing
and they were supposed to meet I think
on a I can't remember the exact day they
never heard from them again. So you
can't even say that people come on too
strong because there's one you actually
have kissed and they've still done it or
ones that you haven't even tried to kiss
and they've still done it.
But that's cuz I've got like a lot of
experience with this [ __ ] So obviously
I know in it special now.
Yeah. Really? who they want that before
or after they pretend they got boyfriends.
See, none of that stuff you say makes
any sense because we all know, cactus,
when we try to approach a woman, what
happens nine times out of 10? So all of
this stuff that happens after,
right, it's irrelevant. And that's how I
know that honestly, right, I don't feel
too bad cuz I know that I've been on
dates before where I've kissed most of
them multiple times.
Well, you don't understand better than
me, mate, cuz I've I've met enough of
you [ __ ] so I know exactly what the
kind of [ __ ] you do. Yep. The Albanian
one, the Brazilian one, the Australian one.
Uh there's been other ones as well.
Australian Brazilian Australian
Australian Brazilian. There's been many
of them, bro. There's been many of them
I've kissed on the first date. Many of
them. And they've still done it.
Yeah. And Alba didn't even let me touch
her boobs as well. There's been many of
them, bro. Many of them.
Yeah, I did. Yeah,
I was squeezing her boobs. Yeah. And
then she just said that she doesn't want
to meet again because of the English.
Her English is not very good. So,
there has been other ones. I'm sure
there's been other ones I've kissed. There has.
Most dates I've been on. I've kissed the
first date. So, Brazilian,
the Albanian, the Australian.
So, they can't even get their way out of saying, "Oh,
yeah. I was squeezing her boobs. Her
moves was [ __ ] her boobs were big. So,
you know what I mean? Uh, Cactus. So,
what's your opinion on the Italian one, Cactus?
This would have wasted my time, I guess. Huh?
That's how I know they're weird. Cuz of
the Albanian one and the [ __ ] that
Brazilian one. That's how you know they're weird.
Don't know, man. Ask him.
Yeah, that Albanian one had big boobs, man.
I can show you her if you want.
And she was rubbing my little neck as well.
She has big boobs.
I don't know who you are, Molly Cat.
I'm creepy. You're creepy as well.
You're the one that's pretending to be a
man. That's pretending to be a woman
when you're a man.
That's really creepy if you ask me.
But you said USA was my mama.
You said you you said USA was my mama.
Yeah. I remember I remember squeezing
that boom really hard. Yeah.
could have been my mama.
You said USA was my mama.
Yeah. Story of your life, buddy. I've
had more women than you would ever have, [ __ ]
I've had more women than you will ever have, [ __ ]
So go apply that to yourself, [ __ ]
You're sick and twisted, [ __ ]
I'm sick and twisted for you, Tactus.
Mate, you are single. You should ask
yourself that question. Do you think you
will always be single? Mate, ask
yourself that question. You are single.
Single and alone. Stop. You need to ask
yourself that question.
So anyways, Cactus, what do you think
would have happened with that Italian? Huh?
Yeah, I think she's she has the biggest
ones that that I've ever been with to be honest. Yeah.
Yeah. You could get lots of
I don't like cats. I like dogs. Silly goose. Oh
yeah, I think she had the biggest ones
I've ever been with to be fair.
I think so. Yeah.
Yeah, she I think definitely. Yeah,
we had a little kiss in the bar, Cactus.
And that's when C and Uncle Bad Touch
come into play. But that's what I'm
saying. They're weird. Why would they
kiss you and [ __ ] Keep touching you and
whatever and then they ghost you. That's so weird.
Ask yourself that, bro. They've been
rejecting you your whole life. You've
probably never even seen a woman naked. Yeah.
You probably never even seen a woman naked.
Yeah, she did. Yeah, cheated. Yeah,
they do that then and they ghost you.
Anyways, it's weird, isn't it?
Have I ever had a second date? Nah, mate. Yeah,
I don't think that Italian one could
have been my mama. Her her boobs weren't
big enough, but she was she was cute.
But her boobs weren't big enough for me for me.
So they do that's how you know the
problem is not you cactus. Cuz all of
these people want to say oh like you
come too strong and that. Yeah. But
think about it like this bro. Yeah. What
about the ones that you never tried to
kiss? What about the ones that you
wasn't too forward with? And what about
the ones that you did kiss? They still
done the same thing. So that's how I
know from experience. It's nothing to
even sweat because the chances are
they're just going to do the same thing
again and again and again.
Nah, bro. You're talking about yourself.
Unattractive with no job, money. No,
you're just talking about yourself, bro.
They see that in you cuz you're talking
about yourself, but you're not talking
about me. They see that they see that in
you and that's why you're still a virgin.
Yeah. No, they see that in you, though.
That's why you're still a virgin.
They didn't see that in me, but they see
that in you. So, yeah.
No, they see that in you, bro. You're
just a self-reflector.
Most of you people don't even work. You
want benefits on £300 a month. Nah, bro.
Talking about yourself.
I've warned you about that as well. It's
very unhealthy, lad.
Nah, it must it must do a number on your
mental health to keep talking about
yourself every day on YouTube.
That must really do your mental health bad, bro.
Coming online talking about yourself.
That must really do a number on your
mental health, lad. Coming online every
day talking about yourself, sat there
with no money, no job, no friends. I can
say all of these things to you as well,
bro. You know, it must really [ __ ] with
your mental health. Why do you do it,
bro? How about just coming off YouTube
getting a life?
Anyways, Cactus, what do you think would
have happened with that Italian one?
Um, you need to ask yourself, how much
do you get for your Spacker benefits?
You You need to ask again. You need to
ask yourself that question. Why are you
skinn every month on YouTube?
We want to know how much money you get
with your spack of for your spack of benefits.
Yeah, we need to know how much you get,
bro. Cuz you seem to be skinned every
every time you come on here.
Oh man, you're just a self-reflector. Bye-bye.
Imagine the Albanian one and USA is he
actors. Imagine they put their boobs together.
She didn't ghost. She replied back. She
But the Albanian one did.
But uh No, she didn't ghost. She just replied back. Yeah.
Yeah. Exactly. But
yeah, you need to be you need to be
kissing on the first date anyways.
If they don't kiss you on the first
date, I don't think they're going to
kiss you on the second date.
That's my whole thing anyways. I mean
that's my logic.
What about yours?
It's a gam boy. But yeah. Yeah.
I don't know how that USA Izzy can come
on to me and then try and tell me that
I'm the one that's come on too strong
when she's the one that come on to me.
Like all of the advice you get is just
[ __ ] like you you can't take any
advice. I don't think you can take any
advice, bro. Cuz all the advice you'll
get is [ __ ]
Because they say like, give me example
practice. They say women want to be
friends first, but then then you get friend-zoned.
Then you get friend-zoned.
And then even if you try to be friends
with them, they still ghost you. As in
point, that Muslim one.
Nope. I not I'm not gambling anymore,
bro. I gambled yesterday. I'm not gambling anymore.
I'm good, bro. No, I closed my account down anyways.
No, I'm not gambling, bro. I'm not gambling. Sorry.
Yeah, I know. I'm leaving the country.
Yeah, I know. I'm leaving the country in
two weeks. That's what's going to be
working, though. I know something that's
really going to work is leaving the country.
That's what's going to work. And if I
leave the country and it still don't
work, then uh well, we can come back.
No, you need to leave the country, which
is what I'm doing in 2 weeks.
Cuz the thing is these people online,
cactus, they like to blame men because
it sounds good.
It's easy and it sounds good. Oh, just
blame the man. You know what I'm saying?
Because it sounds good. You see?
But really, it is. Excuse me. But
really, it is the women in this country.
And when I go to Thailand, you will see
that it was the women in this country
all along, you know.
Yep. He says that he's not heard it once
in Thailand. So, I don't think I'll be
hearing it either.
It's not even funny that saying is so
annoying. It gets so boring, bro.
Especially when we know they don't have boyfriends
cuz it's obvious there's a lot of
feminists out there. There's a lot of
people that don't deal with men anymore.
There's loads of single men. There's You
know what I'm saying? So
you're pulling in Philippines without
paying, mate. There's people in the
Philippines that actually want
relationships with people. Yeah.
It is definitely the women in this
country. They've got unrealistic. I
mean, I know this stuff cuz I've dealt
with them. So,
you just need to leave. End off, bro. That's it.
That's what I'm doing. I'm leaving this country. So yeah, Yep.
He gets less than me, bro. I've actually
had a one night stand when I've been out
with him. I've actually pulled when I
was out with him. Oh, you're going to
laugh at this cactus. I remember before.
Yeah, I told you this before. Me and the
two army lads, which I know one of them
is my friend. I don't know the other
one. And the Indonesian, we went into
this club in it. And uh me and the Indonesian,
we approached them two ones from Ireland
and one was kissing me. And then I was
trying to get her to get my other
friend. I was trying to get her to get
my other friend.
My friend and she was like, "No." She
was saying how she doesn't like him. She
doesn't like him. And then the other guy
from the army come and they started
kissing. But the other guy in the army,
he was already in a relationship and she
was still kissing him.
How mad is that?
No. I'm going to book it when I'm there.
It's only like£105 a day a day.
Yeah, that was a mad story. That is that
would have [ __ ] up my confidence
forever, bro. I think that would have
[ __ ] up my confidence forever, lad. I
did that, bro. What the [ __ ]
That That is [ __ ]
But I remember I done it with Ant-Man
before. I approached someone for Ant-Man
and there's like, "Who cares?" They're
like, "Who cares? You're better
looking." And then she started kissing
me. It was a madness. Then she started
kissing me. That's [ __ ] mad.
To good old Thailand.
That's where. To good old Thailand.
Poor old Indonesian fella.
That's what one woman told me before.
Oh my god, bro. What the [ __ ] is wrong
with me? Then she started kissing me.
You remember Davin?
So, flight booking. Suck my dick. You're
not going to You're not going to know
the time and the exact date I'm going.
Are you mad? So, you can ring up the airline.
[ __ ] off, mate. Suck my dick. I cactus.
Do you remember um do you remember Damon?
He says, "Oh, you got some sloppy
seconds of mine. How' my dick taste?"
What does he mean by how does his dick
taste? That's a bit gross. That's a bit gruesome.
It's got this.
I remember when LT got involved and he started uh
Yeah, but why would he say how did how
did my dick taste? What What does he
mean by that? Mm-m.
I remember when LT got involved that he
was wed and stuff, but how did all of
this [ __ ] come about? Like, who was he
who was the root cause of it? all of
this messaging and all of this chaos.
Here is the root cause.
Who was the root cause of it all?
It was [ __ ] LT.
I think it was LTV.
How was it me, bro?
How was it me? What? Cuz I asked them to just apologize.
What? Because I asked them to apologize.
All I asked him was apologize.
Do you think USA Izzy has ever gave a [ __ ] cactus?
Nah, I don't think she has. Has she?
I don't think so.
No, I don't think so. They didn't say
talk about you or
Yeah. Imagine it's a madness, isn't it?
Yeah. Baby Peter
I don't think she's ever gave a [ __ ]
Do you think, Cactus? She has.
Yeah, she gives it to the blacks.
You remember she gives it to the blacks.
Yeah, it could have ended up in death.
It could have ended up in death. Cactus
USA is ever gave a [ __ ] though. That
which is uh quite disturbing.
Do you think she's gave a lot of
[ __ ] before? Cactus. Nope. Nah. Nah, bro.
Not my matey. Yeah, really.
I said, "Can you give me a hand job?" He
said, "There's nothing in that for me." [ __ ] off.
I bet they've been for expecting me to
eat you out and that.
No, there's been a few of them.
The one night that stand in London, 19year-old,
other American one, Manchester, Nottingham. Yep.
There's been a few of them.
been a few of them, bro.
There's nothing in that for me.
I wonder this Italian want to suck the Todd Cactus.
I think it's impossible to get a [ __ ]
nowadays without paying for it. What do
you think? Yeah,
I should have kicked that one out from
Nottingham, man. I should have let her
stay the night to give me a [ __ ] in the morning,
but I just kicked her out after I was done.
After I was done, Cactus.
Yeah, I know. That was funny, is it?
I haven't been back to knots since
I've been there a few times. I don't know. Yeah.
Where have my little legs take me in it,
Cactus? There might be a new video on
Saturday. Where have my little legs take me, Cactus?
Keep your eyes peeled and your notification on.
Keep the bell on, buddy. Keep the bell
on. Wherever Peter Belly's little legs take him.
Literally, I've got to record everything. Maybe. Yeah.
Might [ __ ] off somewhere, mate. You used
to like that little series, didn't you,
Cactus? Where have my little legs take me? Yeah.
You like that? Don't you catch this?
What an A cactus shack. Yeah.
I wonder what Sig does nowadays.
Bless Sig. She got involved. She got
involved with the whole YouTube thing as
well, didn't she, Cactus?
She got involved with the whole YouTube thing.
Nah, don't go down on [ __ ]
I think that's what she was expecting.
I'm not doing that. She's had loads of
black penis in her.
I was squeezing her boobies on the couch. [Music]
Uh yeah, they can love it all they want.
I'm not doing that. [ __ ] that. [ __ ]
going down on someone. That's [ __ ] nasty.
No, I'm all right. Thanks.
She's boring though. She wanted to uh
she wanted to [ __ ] with a condom at first.
She's boring. Why would you want to [ __ ]
with a condom?
How else are you going to feel the dick
properly? How else are you going to get pregnant?
At first, you wanted a condom.
Why would you want a condom? Condoms suck,
don't they, Cactus?
Condoms suck, man.
I hate condoms.
Yeah. And then she said my ex said that as well.
Yeah. Then I started playing with them.
And then she was getting horny.
Then she says, "Do you have any condoms?" [ __ ] off.
That's why I should have said that. [ __ ]
off. Is it? Yeah.
You remember when I had to limp to go on
that date? I limped to go on that date
and I got my [ __ ] time wasted and I
had to limp to go on that date, mate. [ __ ] hell.
Oh, [ __ ] for that about you don't feel
the vibe. [ __ ] off.
You don't feel the [ __ ] vibe, eh? Yeah.
You don't feel the vibe. Are you mad?
I remember when this Australian woman
called me unhinged. She said, "Oh,
darling, you really are unhinged.
You really are unhinged."
Is that funny, Cactus?
Darling, you really are unhinged.
I love it. Is it? Yeah.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Going on dates are a
bloody waste of time.
They're a waste of time. Cactus. Yeah. Yep.
That's the one.
Should I do some prank calls?
I might do some prank calls.
I hate phone calls. I find them so
awkward. I can approach anyone on the
street sober. I just hate phone calls.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] [ __ ] mate.
So, do you think that that Italian one
would have done what she done anyways then? Cactus,
do you reckon she would have done what
she done anyways? Yeah.
And while I ask for some pork,
I ask for some pork chops.
I like pork.
Well, who's messaging me? Oh, I thought
that was a reply. I like it when I get reply back. Yeah.
What's the solution? Hey, Cactus.
You can go get some coke in a minute,
man. I'm [ __ ] dying for coke here. of Coca-Cola.
Nah, one of ages.
So, do you think that Italian would have
done what she done anyways? Cactus.
See, what's so mad is she wanted to meet
me straight away. That um USA is he
like, "Hi, do you want to meet up on
Tuesday?" She messaged me first. But if
we' done that, we'd be told, "Oh, you
can't try." What's that?
What the [ __ ] That was my phone. Um, if
we done that, like got a number and
tried to meet them straight away, all
the all the little simps would be like,
"Oh, you you you coming on too strong."
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're coming on too strong.
But when a woman wants to meet you
straight away, no problem. You see the double standards.
Bits messaging me saying, "Oh, hi. Let's
meet Tuesday straight away." But if we
done that, mate,
we get called for it. [Music] You understand?
I'll show you another woman I met.
She turned weird.
See her? She turned weird.
Yeah, I met this one in a club.
Kind of stuck up at it.
Maybe that's your type.
Yeah, maybe that's your type, bud.
I got lots of women here.
This is a French one who I called approach sober.
Got her number
sober by the train station. There's one.
That one's nice looking, but she turned
out to be a [ __ ]
He goes on and it goes on and it goes
on. These are all WhatsApp [ __ ] contacts.
They just aren't interested in this
country. I'm going to call a 19year-old.
Going to give her a little bell.
Yep. How do you think I feel? I've had
to go out and [ __ ] do it.
Pick up your ass. CL phone.
It is depressing.
It sure is depressing, mate. Who's this?
The worst is when they meet you and it [ __ ] up.
It was special then, but it's over now.
pick up your [ __ ] phone, buff. [Music]
Nah, we're still We still got time.
We're still young.
No, we're still young.
We're still young, mate.
I want to I want to try and get on the phone.
[ __ ] it. She's an overall [ __ ]
Yeah. When when least expect it. I can't
believe that that Italian one cactus. I
can't believe that Italian one.
I can't believe that Italian one.
Yes. I'm I'm trying to call you.
I'm trying to call you. Pick up your phone.
on WhatsApp. What the hell?
No, I didn't buy her food. I just bought
her two drinks. She bought her own getting a second.
Punch your [ __ ] phone.
I want to talk. Oh, mate. Right. [Laughter]
So, I got my Casper from this phone yet.
What do you reckon the green monster does?
I do say roast. I do say the roast and
they still say no.
I do. I do say roast dinner. They still say no.
I think I said to her, let's go for
roast dinner. I have tried that. I do do
I either say roast dinner or nandos and
they're just not interested in this country.
Simple as that. They're not interested
in this. They're not interested in this
country. Simple as that.
That's what man said.
Oh my god. Will you pick up your bloody
phone before I come there and beat you up? [Music]
She said, "What do you want to talk
about?" I said, "Us.
I want to talk about us."
Can we just talk
talk about us?
Well, you'll see if you pick up
No, don't start playing your silly
little games, right? You're the one
that's You're the one that blocks,
unblocks, blocks, unblocks, and I
basically just said, "If you do it
again, we can't meet up anymore. We
can't do this anymore. You know, it's a serious matter."
I said that in a voice note.
I'm going to start talking about the
Todd in a minute.
Like, I can't believe it. Like, it's
been so long. It's been like February
and you haven't come around to see me,
you know, go for a Chinese like we used
to when you used to come around to my
house. You know, I miss them days and
all of a sudden you just vanished.
What happened to the days where you used
to suck my to?
What happened to those days, man? And
you don't visit me. You don't do a
welfare check on me. You don't give me
[ __ ] anymore. What the hell is going into you?
This is really ridiculous now.
No, don't start playing your silly little games.
You're the one that's You're the one
that blocks and blocks blocks and
blocks. And I basically just said, "If
you do it again, we can't meet up
anymore. We can't do this anymore." You
know, it's a serious matter. [Laughter] Yeah.
I can't be asked to listen to that. But
I don't know why you're like messaging
me now when you literally just messaged
me being like, "Oh, I don't want to see
you anymore." Blah, blah, blah. And
stuff like that. So why are you
messaging me now? Like what what is
going on? No, that's a load of bollocks.
I'm talking. No, that's a load of
bollocks. You know where I live as well
and you don't even come and see me
anymore. What the hell?
Look, I'm not going to listen to any of
your voice messages cuz I just said I'm
on the train and I'm like with someone
right now. I can call you after if you
want, but I just wait.
No, I'm not going to wait. Answer your
phone right now
before I come there and beat you up. Uh, yeah.
These lower punts.
No, I'm not waiting. I' I've got a bone
to pick with you smelly women.
You know, one second.
I'll just wait. I want that Italian back, man.
I want to call someone. I get anxious on
phone calls, you know? I find them so
awkward, which is weird cuz I could I
could approach anyone, but
I really want to [ __ ] with someone like
in in a I mean,
yeah, I used to do these prank calls all
the time. Do you know what I need to do,
Grez? I need to play San Andreas and do
prank calls at the same time. stream San
Andreas and do prank calls at the same time.
You know what I'm saying? Cuz um
cuz Yeah, it'll be funny. You know what
streamers used to do?
I get so anxious on these prank calls, man.
Oh, one second. I've got this s. You
want me to call Chinese Izzy?
want to try these. Is he?
This person's mailbox is full. You
cannot leave a message. Goodbye.
What do you mean I can't leave a
message? That doesn't even make any sense.
Do I scream?
This is what I said to the um 90y old
look. Like I can't believe it. Like it's
been so long. This is what I said. It's
been like February and you haven't come
out to see me, you know, go for a
Chinese like you used to when you used
to come around to my house. You know, I
miss them days and all of a sudden you just vanished.
What happened to the days when you used
to suck my to?
What happened to those days, man? And
you don't visit me. You don't do a
welfare check on me. You don't give me
[ __ ] anymore. What the hell has
gotten into you?
This is really ridiculous. Now,
that's cute, isn't it? And then this is
what she sent me.
I can't be asked to listen to that. But
I don't know why you're like messaging
me now when you're literally just
messaging me like, "Oh, I don't want to
see you anymore." Blah blah blah and
stuff like that. So why are you
messaging me out? Like what what is
going on? To make love. Look, I'm not
going to listen to any of your voice
message cuz I just said I'm on the train
and I'm like to make love. Obviously,
it's like what I used to say to LJ to make love.
I think this is the only one that would
actually stay with me, bro.
And I can't stay with her cuz she's too
young for me. But I can get like
[ __ ] and [ __ ] What's the date? She
I think she's like 20. So
she not even ugly either, but still. Wait,
I can't believe that Italian one, bro.
What the [ __ ]
How many women are we going to keep
[ __ ] with, bro? Until we find someone.
Where the [ __ ] is she going, bro?
You think Virgin boy is 20 uh Dennis of
the 19year-old cactus?
She's nice. The 19year-old and and the
Italian one's nice.
They're both nice. Oh, I got a message.
No, that's a load of bollocks.
You can come and see me anymore. What the hell? Yeah.
You said I'll meet you tomorrow. But you
can't meet me tomorrow. I don't have any
money. I need to start saving now.
There's no money. I don't have money
like I used to, mate.
Oh, she said, "Do you want me to come
over tomorrow? He's
I can come over tomorrow if you want. Yeah.
The Italian is not that bad than a
19year-old. The only good thing about
the Italian is she was 25.
You know, this one's quite young, you
know. But let me give her a little bow.
[ __ ] sake, man. No. Trying
to see who I can call here. Oh.
Oh, gosh. Darn it.
You're back in Birmingham. What the
hell? How can you be back in Birmingham?
Doesn't even make any sense.
This person's mailbox is full. You
cannot What do you mean? You're back in Birmingham. [Music]
Do you know what you do you know what
she just said? Chinese is she said I
can't speak English.
What do you mean you can't speak English?
I said let's talk on the phone. She said
I can't speak English. That's [ __ ] funny.
Just the way she typed it. I can't speak English.
Oh my god. That's is funny, bro. That
just made me laugh.
Oh gosh. Darn it. [Music]
Yeah, I should I should try and call
again. You know that Conrad?
You remember a Conrad cactus?
Do you remember? One second.
Someone's calling me. Hello. Hello. Hi.
Yo, what's up? I wanted to see how you was doing.
Right. Okay. I'm good. How are you? I'm
good. I've got a bone to pick with you.
What? I've got a bone to pick with you.
Right. Why do you keep blocking and unblocking?
I don't know. I've been busy recently
and stuff. Have you found someone else?
No, just been busy. Yeah, but you went
to Wales and I didn't hear from you the
whole time you was there.
Yeah, I know. Cuz I was with my family.
I thought you I was getting kind of um
kind of worried, you know.
No, it's fine. I was just with my
family. Yeah. Yeah. Funny week that was.
It was more like It was more like two
[ __ ] It was like two months.
I don't know.
Anyway, what do you want? Cuz I'm kind
of with my friend right now as well. Um
there's there's two things I wanted to
say. Yeah. So basically I I went on this
date last Thursday and it was kind of bogus, man.
Right. Is that why you're following me?
No, but that that's one of the reasons I
just want it was just creepy, you know.
Okay. And uh what do you want to meet up tomorrow?
Potentially. Okay. Well, just let me
know anyways. Yeah. Huh?
Um, I don't know. We go for some drinks.
We go for some food. You can come
around. We get some Chinese,
you know, like like you used to.
Do you remember? Yeah. Like you used to.
So, uh, you can just come around and see
all my little friends again.
Maybe. Do you remember when you come and
you saw and you saw the girl?
When you come and you saw the girl, man.
Come downstairs. Yeah.
She moved out then. Ah, she's gone, man.
She ain't been back for [ __ ] months.
Oh, good. Well, she's still paying it,
so it's all good. Yeah. Oh,
yeah. I was just just just come around
tomorrow. You know, me and you go way back.
I mean, I'll see. I've got like no money
in my zip card or no money in general.
Like, I'm actually broke to the tea. But
we're friends to the end.
Yeah, I know. But I'm saying I couldn't
afford to get that. I literally have no money. Okay.
Well, I we'll see you tomorrow in it.
Right. Bye. But you can't One second.
One second. You can't you can't keep
blocking and unblocking though. That's
kind of mean.
Okay. Why are you talking like that? It
sounds so creepy. What? How am I How am
I talking? Oh, I don't know. Right. I'm
going. Bye. Okay. I'll talk to you
later. Yeah. Love you.
Oh, I didn't get love you back.
That's me getting my to suck tomorrow.
She says, "Why you talking like that?"
She's like, she's like, "Why?
She's like, "Why are you talking like
that?" Oh, that's funny.
And I messaged that I messaged that
Chinese Izzy. Yeah. Um, Chinese Izzy and
she does speak English. I said, "Let's
speak on the phone." She said, "I don't
speak English." I was dead.
It's just the way she wrote it. Oh, Grezy.
Why? That voice is so creepy. Oh, it's
like it's a lovely little voice.
That's me getting my todd tomorrow.
That is me getting my toes sucked tomorrow, mate. Yeah,
that is funny, bro.
Oh, I was with my family. So that means
you can keep blocking and unblocking me.
I can call her Somalian, you know. She
she's been messaging me.
I can actually call her, you know, [ __ ] with her.
I don't want her to have my new number.
That's the thing.
See that one? Yeah. [Music]
Why? Why is the fold phone faster than
this phone, Cactus? It's so much faster.
Like, this fold phone is so fast.
I think it's cuz of the flagship phone, is it?
So fast, bro.
I want to call this punt.
What the hell?
Why are you talking like that? It sounds so creepy.
I don't know.
No, you know what? I had to come off
this community for a bit. It was getting
creepy, bro. I told Monty that. I was
like, "No, it's it's actually creepy.
It's [ __ ] creepy." [Applause] Yeah. Might
try sex tomorrow. I had it for a while. Yeah.
Well, I'll be back later anyways.