We're going Morning
man. Go into this YouTube sh
Well, that was a woman messaging me about but You know,
I went on a date Thursday. Another time waster. Cory,
the country's dead, bro.
You can't find anyone in this country,
mate. It's [ __ ] dead.
in this country. Cory, lad.
Yeah, man. They've all got boyfriends, Cory.
Just a time waster.
Same as always, isn't it?
They've all got boyfriends.
I started a gym, by the way, last week.
I went two times last week. I'm going
again tomorrow, bro. I'm going again tomorrow 100%.
Sorry. I just been slacking, bro.
It's the dating [ __ ] It's depressing, isn't it? Oh,
we was holding hands and walking and
flirting and then when I said, "Oh, can
can I kiss and that?" She says, "No,
Cory says no to the kiss."
Yeah. She said I was too forward, which
I wasn't, but
Yeah. [ __ ] mate. Yeah, man.
Time race with it.
It's hard to find anyone in this country, Cory. Hard.
Yeah, I know. But I'm saying generally,
bro, I got some numbers on Saturday
and I'm just getting [ __ ] from them.
I hate them, bro.
They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
Call me. They're [ __ ] lad. Yeah.
There's one. Yeah. She said she's going
to Santi tomorrow for 2 months and she
said she'll meet me after the summer
which is Yeah,
but that doesn't make any sense. And
then I ask I message her again and then
she'll reply. This was earlier.
Pretty boring, is it?
[ __ ] bing, guys. Pause me, mate. Pause me. Yeah.
Them tic tacs and half make you [ __ ]
burp in it, bro. You know tic tacs, they
make you [ __ ] burp, don't they, bro? Yes. Yeah.
You can't see pizza. I'm going to have
some lamb later, bro.
A lot of lamb.
I had chicken earlier. I had a whole chicken.
Where's the virgin? I don't see him much anymore. Cory,
where's that [ __ ] burger?
Where's that [ __ ] Where's that
[ __ ] virgin? Sorry.
Love you, bro. Love you.
Yeah, this new Samsung phone is pretty
good. You know, the power
this phone cost me.
Where's the virgin?
Where that [ __ ] virgin from?
Where's that [ __ ] virgin?
That [ __ ] virgin can.
Where is he? Call me. Call me. Where is
[ __ ] virgin. You call me [ __ ] That
What would happen if I do some
approaches on Saturday?
Say I go out Saturday and I done some
approaching women. What do you think would happen?
Boyfriend in it.
Boyfriend in it, Cory.
We might get lucky. Yeah, pigs might fly as well.
Yeah, bro. Pigs might fly.
Pigs might fly, lad.
It's a lovely side.
Nah, you won't get lucky in this country.
You won't get lucky in this country,
mate. They're not interested.
Like what Antman said, Richie, they're
not interested in this country. Hey,
there's something good in the cinema next month.
Spain won't work. Spain's full of English people.
No, Spain is full of English people.
Spain won't work, bro. It's full of the English.
Only Only Asia works.
I told you this before, Cory. The only
place you're not going to get I've got a
boyfriend is Asia.
That's the only place you're not going
to get it.
That's what Hanland said to me.
The only place you're not going to get
at is um
Asia, I think. Is it
Richie? How many of them do you think
have boyfriends? I think three out of 10.
The ones that say they've got
boyfriends, I think three out of 10. Me
100%, bro. Yeah. Like three out of 10 maybe.
had some food earlier. I had old chicken.
Yeah. I told you the only place you're
not going to get I've got a boyfriend is
Asia Cherry. I told you this before.
That's the only place you're not going
to get it.
Yeah, I'm going to have some lamb later
cook for me.
Well, I have a boyfriend. I start.
Yeah. And she still got with me even
when she had a boyfriend. They ain't got boyfriends, bro.
in a C.
It's that [ __ ]
I'm not gullible, bro. I'm not gullible.
Like, you might think I'm gullible, but
I'm not gullible.
Yeah, it's not even funny. It's far from
It's far from funny. I have a boyfriend. Uh [ __ ] tons of
They've all got boyfriends.
Yeah, but Chloe, listen. They've all got boyfriends.
Tory cuz I said to man I said oh how's
it going he's going boyfriends
they all got boyfriends
that one coming
I'll never forget boyfriend.
That is funny, bro.
Is that man right, Cherry? That they're
just not interested in this country.
Is he right? Is he right, Cherry?
at least a commodity box.
Oh, talking about yourself there, Sogorg
on the time. Uh,
talking about yourself there, bud. Like
I said, you little self-reflectors don't
bother me cuz you're just talking about
yourselves. Anyways, uh,
one second. I need to call Monty Man and
come back. Two seconds. Yeah, you don't
bother me with your little
self-reflecting comments cuz this is
about your own life. And I actually
remember you from like two, three years
ago when I actually went to uh
Newcastle. You shut yourself then as
well and you didn't come out.
Well, you get away with yourself. You [ __ ] self-reflect.
One second. Let me call this guy.
And mate, you're sat there lonely in
your 40s. You don't even leave your
house. And you're talking about no
misses and social anxiety. Bro, look
closer to home.
You little self-reflector.
Self-reflected little [ __ ] Jordy
[ __ ] who didn't come out when I was in Newcastle.
kept his mouth shut.
We know this money. All the spastics
come from large a channel, bro. One sec box.
If you notice, bro, all the little
[ __ ] projectors, they all come from that channel.
They don't come from your channel. They
all come from that channel. Have you noticed that?
If you notice, they've all come they all
come from that channel, right?
You little creeps. Self-reflectors.
Never had social anxiety my in my life.
Never had a speech impediment in my life. Self-reflecting.
But you don't just have social anxiety.
You got crippling anxiety.
Can't leave your house. Can't do
anything. You're just talking about
yourself. What? PJ,
you all right? I'm good. Why do these
people love talking about themselves
every day? Because they're [ __ ] mongos. PG,
mate. They all come from L channel,
buddy. Yeah, they all [ __ ] weirdos.
They all are. They all saw on YouTube
day in and day out masturbating over the same sentences.
Yeah, it's weird, isn't it?
Yeah. The self reflect they can't get.
So they so they reject on other people.
It's the truth, isn't it? Of course it is.
Yeah. What you What you having for tea today?
I'm think um don't know publicly clitoris.
I remember I remember m you don't eat
beef cuz you're cuz you're Hindu in it.
Are you eating beef? You [ __ ] I'm not Hindu.
Hindu. Huh? You bloody bastard. I'm not
You even know what it is. Hindu. Muslim.
Nah, it's a different religion. It's not
Muslim. It's Hindu. Hindu. Same kind of
the bud stuff. spot in it. Hindus with
Is that with the bug bug spot? Yes. Yeah.
Have you ever been Have you Have you
ever been to a mosque?
Well, have I [ __ ] been to a mosque? I
smashed I put most windows through
before though. I smash windows.
Yeah, but I mean like just to see what
it's like, you know. I have.
You got to take your shoes off. Yeah, I
have. I went to Ramadan just to get the
free food cuz they give food.
You got to take your shoes off. Yeah, I know.
Yeah. [ __ ] that [ __ ] I'm a sho person.
I have to keep my shoes on. Really?
Yeah. Yeah. You like your feet on the
ground as well, don't you? What do you
mean? Like you like your feet on the ground.
I like my feet on the ground.
Everybody's feet on the ground.
No, I mean you don't like going on boats
and stuff. Yeah, I like going on boats.
I like going on planes. I like going in
cars. I like doing pedal pedaling bikes.
I like You got You got You got a phobia
of that, don't you?
No, I got a phobia of wanking.
A phobia of wanking.
Yeah, I got a big phobia over one kid
over that [ __ ]
I can't believe you introduced me to
that freak on PlayStation, man. Can't
believe you introduced me to this
[ __ ] community. It's so Yeah, this
community is creepy, is it? I have to
say I'm gone again, Monty. It's too
creepy for me.
[ __ ] off. You drive my ass into this
[ __ ] on here. Yeah, but you met Natalie.
Oh, yeah. I met Natalie and I'm [ __ ]
happy that I met met Natalie.
What would you do if she stopped you?
Would you be quiet?
No, I just go back into woods again and
make myself a [ __ ] house. That was six. Really?
Really? Yeah. I'll get you to move in with me.
No, money, you know, you get attached.
No, man. You've been paying [ __ ]
stick tax you, PJ. Yeah. Yeah. Money,
you get attached. Attached
to what? To women.
No, I get attached to [ __ ] people.
Yeah, but when a woman leaves you, you
cry in it. No, I don't [ __ ] cry. I laugh.
No, you I'm going to cry.
I [ __ ] you. That's the only time you see
me laugh if a woman breaks up with me. Really?
Really? That's all the time you probably
see me laugh.
I don't find any of it funny. Do you?
Yeah. When a woman breaks up to you.
Yeah. It's funny as [ __ ] Why?
It's just I don't know. It's just funny.
I just laugh. I don't know why. I just Yeah.
It's funny. It's [ __ ] funny. You
should try the golden You should try the
golden shower, Natalie.
I've already done it.
No, you haven't. Oh, [ __ ] woman
pisses on you in it. No, but you should
be the one pissing.
No, it should be Natalie. It should be
You should be the one pissing in it. No.
No. It's It's a woman. It's a woman who
pisses on a man, not a man pisses on a
woman. Well, a man pisses on a woman as well.
No, but it's more a woman's thing. It's
basically what it actually means when a
woman pieces on a man. They're basically
marking a territory basically. Really? Yeah.
Ask to spell Ask to spell helicopter now.
Why don't you spell dildo?
Why do the same [ __ ] Because it's all
in the jokes. They've got spell this, spell that.
That's only what they can say. That's
only what they can do. That's only the
jokes they've got.
Yeah. But it's just repeating, isn't it?
Yeah. That's only what the other
repeaters. They only can [ __ ] At
least this B can pull women. [Laughter]
Hey Monty, you know a certain person he
can't be trusted near schools in it.
Jimmy Eldridge. No.
No. Your mate. Your mate. Do you mean
shing on legs?
No. No mate. [ __ ] man. You went for your
I saw you argue with Timmy earlier.
What about it, Timmy? It's still going
on YouTube. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, he is. Yeah, he's just fantastic. [Laughter]
Do you remember that time in the code station
with Jimmy? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He were
kicking [ __ ] kicks at me. Yeah. [ __ ] Disabled.
There are some people in this community
they can't Monty. Ever some people in
this community, they can't be trusted around kids.
No, these people [ __ ] look like Jimmy Eldridge. Yeah.
Ask him. Ask these people how much
they'll weigh, PJ. Ask him what they'll weigh.
PJ's laugh is very cheeky. Ask Monty if
he thinks your laugh is cheeky. Do you
think my laugh is cheeky, Monty?
No. Your laugh is [ __ ] gay as [ __ ]
man. It sounds like you're sucking up a [ __ ] T.
No, it does.
is mine laugh, cheeky.
No, you never laugh.
What do you mean I never laugh? You
never laugh at anything, man. I do laugh.
Yeah. Yeah, of course I do. I laugh I
laugh at a blind person walking into a lamp post. Really?
Yeah. Why would you not laugh if you see
a blind man walking to a lamp post? No.
Why calls me a virgin?
Yeah. Yeah. He's a virgin. I don't even
believe he's in money. Yeah. I don't
even believe I don't even want to be up.
Yeah. Well, I don't even believe he has
kids cuz you wouldn't be on here if you had kids.
Yeah, he's on here 24/7, is he? Every
[ __ ] day. Yeah, that's what I mean.
Every day he's on here. No, I think I
think that he has got kids, but I think
that they separated him and his misses.
So, I think that he sees his kids like
on a weekend or
something like that.
Yeah. Yeah. So that's what I think.
I think that time I think that time.
Yeah. You was in love with that bird
from Australia. You should have just went there.
No. Australia for a bird. It's too much money, man.
Why am I going to pay so much money to
go to Australia for a bird? Did you was
in love? I wasn't in love. I was only
having a quick tug on your [ __ ]
PlayStation. [ __ ] me, man.
Yeah, but you could have got to
Australia in no time. Yeah, I got them
done. Oh, [ __ ] hell. Yeah, I got the
money for it, but I'm not doing that
[ __ ] I'm not going to Australia.
Yeah, be funny.
Well, you come Australia with me.
I can't come to Australia, money. Why?
Because I'm an illegal immigrant.
Yeah, you get sent back on a banana boat. You
right. Really? Yeah. You get sent back
to the UK on a banana boat.
I went to my mom's the other day. Yeah.
Um because I went to do a welfare check
on her and the neighbors were giving me
funny looks. Yeah, they will do because
of the community. Yeah. See what I mean,
buddy? It's [ __ ] weird as [ __ ] Yeah.
You just tell them I'm on YouTube and
it's a [ __ ] dark side of YouTube.
Yeah. You had problems with the neighbors too?
No, not really. Because soon as he had
problems with the neighbors, I told him.
Yeah, but they I swear some come at your
door. Yeah. Loads of people come at my
door, but I scared them off. Wait, what
did they come in the door saying? You
know, it was only Trixie.
Yeah. Yeah. He was a [ __ ] man. He was a
[ __ ] him. Trixie. Yeah.
We check to live in Plymouth.
Yeah, he's from London though. Is it?
Yeah, from London but lived in Plymouth.
He [ __ ] it when I turn up. We're playing
games with the man. Does Kayie still
come on YouTube? I don't see her. I
watch it. I don't I don't talk about
her. No, I don't even talk to her.
How the [ __ ] am I going to talk to that
rat for? Mate, I knew it. I knew back on
PlayStation. Yeah, that [ __ ] that
Sammy was the one for you in it. No, she
was she wanted you like Sammy. She was
the one for you, mate. It No, she was
the one for you, lad. I mean, remember
that chat room till this day with me and
you in the chat room together next Sammy
in the chat room asking you to go oneon
one with her.
Yes. He had a scout accent.
Liverpool accent that kind of accent sp
you remember money?
Yeah, of course I remember.
I don't know. Did you do anything with
her? I don't think you did. Did you?
Could could have done? No, I don't know.
Did I don't know. I think she must have
saw your neck and run off. No, that's
our little secret.
Yeah, it is in it. You used to say to me
on PlayStation, yeah, we when we used to
do stuff, you used to say, "Don't tell
anyone. It's our little secret." [ __ ]
off. I've never said that.
Secret. No. PJ PJ Hooker. Thank you, L.
Huh? PJ Hooker proper on you.
Who is this? that that that PG hooker
that gay guy
I'm from Canada
when you reading last time I met you in
these chat room
I don't know how I got into that chat
room but that's a [ __ ] you was in that chat
yeah he's weird boy
off man he fancied my ass man he wanted
my [ __ ] my ass yeah he
And you wanted to give him it. I didn't
want to give it a man. PJ, you know some
scary people, lad. You know some scary
ass people. You
What do you mean? You know some scary
people like [ __ ] Well, I'm sorry to
say, but you have met some weird ass
people like [ __ ]
Jack the Ripper. [ __ ] Johnny Long Legs.
Yeah, but you went with you went to the
bar with um Jack the Ripper. I've never
been anywhere with Chat the Ripper.
I thought you No, I've never even met
Chat the Ripper. Yeah, he puts his
American accent on even though he's from
Birmingham. He's weird. Yeah. Yeah.
He's weird, man. Yeah, he is. He is. But
I remember when he used to jump on his
bed like naked back on PlayStation roof.
Not even funny. He used to walk past the
camera naked with his dick hanging out
and everything. That man wear that man.
Sounds a [ __ ] Is it money? Sounds a
can. Well, come on. I'm sure like you
played bums on this with him. A
Who was your favorite on the
PlayStation? Like the women
the women who girl likes?
Nah, she was [ __ ] stinking, mate. girl likes
that had had his eye on her own it. She weren't stinking.
Yeah, but he had he had his eye on her own it.
Yeah, but she weren't stinking though.
She w she weren't good looking.
She was all right. She was all right. Who's this?
of the stand. [ __ ] me.
[ __ ] bastard. See you later. Who Who
the [ __ ] is that? It's the that comes in
the chats and makes all these funny
voices and [ __ ] Weirdo. Well, not even
funny. Some weird noises. He makes like
it just did then. You used to hold hands
on first aids, didn't you? I [ __ ]
actually I go first stairs, mate.
Funny. You're too funny, man.
[ __ ] [ __ ] I got a first date. I
[ __ ] leave it and [ __ ] first.
Right. Women usually do this, PJ. Yeah.
Go on a date, go back home. Go on a
date, go back home. Third day, you get
the [ __ ] Yeah. Me totally different.
Check him out today, go back home, give
him a good old with him the next day.
It's a It's all in a small m It's all in
a small dick situation. Pier. So when
you've got a small dick and like myself
like every woman lost a mom with a small dick. PJ
you used to be I remember I remember on
PlayStation. Yeah. You used to be
obsessed with [ __ ]
I've never been obsessed with blow jobs.
Yeah. On PlayStation you did. No, it was
more obsessed than wanting me, man. Back then. Yeah.
[ __ ] you. I remember I remember that fat
then used to give you [ __ ] grief,
didn't he? Never give me grief. I used
to call him [ __ ] used.
No, seriously, buddy. Yeah. I used to
pick on him fat down. I used to pick fat
down on PlayStation 3. I used to call
him Jeff. Did you do you money? You got
paid today, ain't it? No, I get paid
tomorrow. Well, tonight at 12:00.
What? A lot.
What are you treating me? How you
treating me? Yeah.
Yeah. What? You getting me a ring?
Yeah. What ring are you getting?
What ring you get me PG?
Whatever one you want.
Right. I want a diamond ring. And it's
got to be gold. Yeah.
I want a pretty diamond ring. How much
are you getting some more money? 7 and
90 or 780 something like that. All
right, ain't it? What? That's all right,
Yeah. Then my next money, my disability
money, I come out with 740.
Do you think Yeah. Do you think um
you would be able to go out drinking
every every week on benefits? No. It
even if you got my money then yeah then
yeah cuz I come out with disability and
benefits. So yeah I probably could
cuz I come out with enough money to do
that. Well like 1,500 is it? I'll come
out with 700 on each money on both of my
money. That's my disability and normal.
I'll [ __ ] tell you now. Stay there.
You [ __ ] Egyptian bastard.
Uh, once tell you, I can't. Let me go
into my online banking.
What goes in and what goes out, right?
Probably got nine. right
in. Right. Here we go. PG normal money.
Right. This is my disability. Yeah. Uh,
if I come out with my disability money 749 and 80p. Yeah,
that's my disability money. So, I come
out with 7. Yeah.
That's how much money I come up with.
How much you was breaking up? Oh, what? Paid?
Yeah. 740 and what? 749. Yes. And 88p.
Yeah. Yeah. Right. My normal money I'll
come out with that is 790.
Okay. Good, isn't it? That's good money.
Yeah. Is that that? So you get 15. You
get basically about 1,500 a month. Yeah,
basically 1,500 a month. Yeah.
It's all right. Is it? It's good money. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, so more money on these little clowns
on this community then. Yeah, that's good.
Yeah, that's skin, isn't it? Yeah. the uh
how long do you think how money how long
do you think it will take you to save to go America?
Not long cuz it's only a,000 to America.
So there's my ticket straight away next
month. Get me another,000 to pay for my
hotel. Just go. Really?
Basically, it's only cost you what? Um
it's going to cost you a thousand either
way. So there you go. probably
know it's probably a day or so. But you
also got to think about food. You also
got to think about when you get back
home. So probably longer. If I was going
to go straight away, it probably be
already I get paid my disability cuz I
get paid visibility straight after my normal payment. Yeah.
How's our little special Pete um the ma
today? Uh you're doing fine you little
ma. You are the ma with special needs.
Yeah, you're talking about yourself.
That's fine. You little m.
Why do these people keep calling
themselves a m? It's just what they do.
I feel bad for him, too. Huh? I feel bad
for him, too. It's just that they
[ __ ] ain't got no life really. Yeah.
on YouTube calling people moners
to it every day.
Yeah. PJ, do you pick your nose and eat
your bogeies? Yeah, I was doing it
earlier. Well, yeah. It's [ __ ] nice,
isn't it? I love it. I I love the
feeling when you when you pick the bogey
and you pull it.
Yeah. I like I like I like the stringy
ones, mate. Monty, can you suck my toes?
I don't like to like this to Yeah. I
like the stringy one. Yeah. It's nice
when you pull it, is it? Yeah. And it's
a big [ __ ] solid at the end of it.
Yeah. It's nice. Yeah. Yeah. I like it.
Do you know when you blow your nose
sometimes and you get a big crispy one?
Oh, they're the best. They're the best. We
eat our booies for tea, don't we?
They're the best. They have your gries. All
right, buddy. You had breakfast for
lunch. You had lunch. No, you had you
had eggs for lunch.
No, actually I didn't actually.
Yeah. Do you want to know what I had for
lunch? What? I have one guess. But I
give you three guesses. It is a takeaway.
Uh, and it's not McDonald's. And it's
not a kebab. Subway. And it's not Burger
King or KFC. Subway. Yeah, man. You got
it in one Subway. I knew it. I knew it. Yeah. Subway.
Your family called you Special Pete and
women call you the Manta. You are the
Manta. Yeah. That's why I've had more
women than you and you're sat on YouTube
all day alone. Stop calling yourself a Manta.
These people really need to stop
bullying themselves, man. I feel bad for them.
One, these people taking the piss out of
y. They can't even take a piece out of a
[ __ ] packet of a crisp. Really? Yeah. Really?
I'm going to wake up in a [ __ ] phone. I'm back.
What would you do if someone got you pregnant? What?
What you do if someone got you pregnant?
What would I do if someone gets me
pregnant? [ __ ] knows that be impossible.
Watch how super super super super get me pregnant.
What if it happened?
You can't get a man pregnant. PJ, man.
What the [ __ ]
All right, buddy. I remember. All right,
buddy. I'm going to show you something.
Yeah. And I want to see if you remember
it. Yeah. I'm going to send it to you on Facebook.
Go on then.
I'm an Yeah, I'm an emirate.
One second. Yeah, you can.
Is that nice? The top of the [ __ ] buddy.
There you go. I said it to you.
I'll send it to you.
You show me a picture of your dad.
Where from? You sent me a picture of your dad.
Yeah. What? You don't remember where
it's from? From Yeah. Shameless.
How How do you remember? Frank Gallagher.
How do you How do you remember that?
How How can you not forget Frank Gallagher?
I remember if I was talking to you,
you'd know about it. He soon shut his
mouth up then, didn't he? He soon shut
his mouth up then, didn't he?
Who did the PlayStation? Yeah.
No, that was years ago.
You know about it.
If I talking to you, you know about it. Yeah.
That were years ago now. It's true though. It
PJ, have you found your spoon yet?
Yeah, it's up your M's.
No, last time I did sport to you on
PlayStation, you lost your teaspoon.
Did you find your teaspoon?
Didn't find it. That's a country, ain't
it? Yeah. So, where's your spoon? Yes. I know.
Oh, PG lost his [ __ ] speed. Hey,
Monty, that fish man that comes on your
live is a weirdo, isn't it? No, it's all
right, P man. He don't ask me not to
[ __ ] But he calls me [ __ ] and then when
I said meet him, he didn't want to. So
why started me then? It's pointless.
Oh, [ __ ] no. [ __ ] no. It's [ __ ] It's
[ __ ] It's [ __ ] ming, isn't it?
when people do that.
It is [ __ ]
It is. Anyway, P, I'm gonna jump off
anyways here because I'm going to give
Natalie a bit of a cuddles. Yeah. All right, mate.
Yeah. All right, then. I see you in a
minute. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Let me know how your next wank does.
Yeah, I'll I'll do a video and and send
you it. No, PJ. Yeah, just let me know.
Do Monty, do the Wait, wait. Do you
remember the video of me getting a
[ __ ] Yeah, no. I don't want it
again. I don't want it again. I I bet
you went to it. I bet you I bet you went
to it, didn't you?
No. No. No. Did I [ __ ] to it? Did you
like it a little bit though? I didn't
even like it a little bit. Do you think
she was good at it? Maybe next time.
Send me a video of you [ __ ] a woman
with PJ. Not a [ __ ] That's totally
different. Yeah, but do you think it was
good? Do you think it was like good?
Don't send me no videos.
You think it was good? No, it was hanging.
Why was she giving me a [ __ ] buddy?
Because you obviously you asked her to
give you a [ __ ]
Yeah, and I came in my mouth.
You come in a mouth, did you? Yeah, I'm
getting one tomorrow as well. Someone's
coming round, my friend.
Yeah, 4:00, man. I'm all PJ, you need to
go down on a woman, man. You need to
lick a woman out, man. You can't just
make a woman give your blood. That's disgusting.
Is it [ __ ]
disgusting? You're gay. You're gay, PJ.
You've got like a [ __ ] out.
You're gay, mate. You're gay.
A woman likes a little bit of a tongue and action. Huh?
A woman likes a little bit of a tonga nephew.
Well, that could make you laugh quickly
before you go. Go on then.
That makes you laugh at it.
No, not really.
Why don't you laugh at anything, man?
What? Why don't you laugh at anything?
Because your your jokes a gay thing.
Okay. What is it? What is in the picture then?
It looked like [ __ ] rice in his mom's pouch.
No, seriously. Yeah, it look like it's
rice in his mom's pouch.
No, you don't offer anything. I don't
think you understand any of the jokes
and stuff in it. I do understand the
jokes. P. Yeah. This the jokes are lame. Really?
Here, let me show you something, DJ.
This will make you laugh.
Oh, I can. There you go.
What? Look at me. Have a PJ.
That will make you laugh.
Oh, funny. It Yeah, that's an [ __ ]
P. Yeah. And he's got his legs up in here.
That's weird. Yeah. Hey, will this make you laugh? Who's that? Beex X.
Really? She's ugly now. Yeah, that's
ugly, isn't it?
Well, let's make you laugh.
He's [ __ ] He's weird him, ain't he?
Yeah, he is a weird. He is a weird then
people used to go and he's not Is he a n
is he a n
go watch his old videos back in the day
where he mentions that he wants 11y old
to do [ __ ] to him.
Yeah, someone said that.
Yeah, go and watch his videos. your love of YouTube.
Money, what's this?
All right, see you later, PJ. [ __ ]
see you later. Bye-bye.
[ __ ] get me out of there.
Why the [ __ ] you sending me a picture of
your knob for?
I'm not. You [ __ ] just sent me a
picture with your [ __ ] black [ __ ]
pants on with your [ __ ] hand on your
[ __ ] Do I turn you on PJ? N
I think a dude turn PJ on. I'm I'm
jumping off this [ __ ] My [ __ ] No,
you don't. You don't.
Yeah, I [ __ ] do. I see you. Whoa.
This was me in central London the other day. Yeah. Are you