All right, come h is cooking.
Loving it, mate. I'm sorry. Oh [ __ ] Let's
go All right. Little baby.
Oh, just sorry, man. Uh,
yeah, agree with you. I'm really going
to try and get the fold seven next
month, but it's quite pricey, isn't it, Grevy?
[ __ ] off. Stop messaging me asking me
for money, mate. I'm never going to be
able to [ __ ] save with these [ __ ]
[ __ ] Keep asking me for money.
Greavvesy, leave me alone. [ __ ] off.
Yeah. What the f seven
What do you think, Grezy? Get the fold seven.
Why don't you tell us what you think, Grezy?
I love the speed on these phones.
They're so good. Why? What?
What's wrong with the current one? Well,
it's blocked. I can only call
outside. I can only call on Wi-Fi. I can
only text on Wi-Fi. But obviously, I've
got a new phone in it where I can do all
of that stuff on.
Nothing wrong with it.
I just love the new phone and stuff.
I don't have the money for it, bro. If I
had a lot of money, then I would. If I
had like 7k sat, then I probably would,
but I don't have that kind of money, mate.
There's no right grievy.
They're very fast though, Grezy. They
stay very fast. They never They never
slow down these phones.
They never slow down. Never.
They're so fast. Like you just bought
them. It must be why they're so
expensive, is it? They're flagship
phones. Quotation mark.
They're a lot faster than this one I
bought. 500 this [ __ ] phone cost me. Yeah,
I can smell the toy being cooked squeezy.
I'm looking forward to it, mate. [ __ ] starving.
I don't know what I should do this week.
I could chill out. I can make some
money. Greasy cuz I won't be drinking
this week. I'm going to go to a gym. I
definitely said I was going to a gym. I ain't
I was thinking of maybe going Blackpool
on Saturday. greasy to give you the
little video you've been waiting for.
Maybe make some money then go there. I don't know.
Just do something insane, you know, before leaving.
I spend more time on YouTube than Timmy.
Well, guess what? You can't even take
one day off of YouTube.
I can I took weeks off of YouTube, days.
I won't be on YouTube tomorrow.
I can leave YouTube. You people, you you
can't take one day off of it. So,
I just had nothing to do today. You say
I'm just lazy grease. I'd rather sit
down and just eat, you know? Just sit
down and eat food
like a fat [ __ ] [Music]
star. But um
I want to try and complete this GTA game
today before I go to bed. Uh,
normal women don't exist in this
country, Grezy. So, I'm to go across the
across the sea. San Andreas.
But I love I love I love driving around
Gezy. It's more fun. Yeah.
uninterested in this country. Greasy.
And Oh, you fly mastered can.
Lucy, you fly mastered can.
um discount and he works Thursdays and
Saturdays greasy. So all I'm going to do
is after I've had a drink just go into
the Burger King and [ __ ] use his
discount. £5 a meal, mate. [ __ ] get
in there, son. Obviously I'm going to
buy him something as well cuz he's
letting me use his discount. So, you
know, it's [ __ ] dirt cheap, mate. The
meals are like £1011, so I can use his
discount. And Thursdays and Saturdays
are my favorite days. So, I said, he he
said he works Thursday and Saturday, and
he has to be in to do it. I said, "Mate,
I'll give it a while. [ __ ] it." Yeah.
You can't be a nice Burger King gre
after a nice drinking session. Damn.
Yeah, this 19year-old keeps wanting
money off me. I'm not [ __ ] made of
money. Just leave me alone. I hate these vultures.
I hate vultures. Me, bro.
Don't know about you, but hate me. I'm gone.