Yo yo. Oh,
man. Oh, [ __ ]
Oh, the fox, man. yeah.
Yo, cactus. Elephant in castle.
Elephant in castle. [ __ ] hell.
No, I just slept, man. [ __ ] I've done a
lot the past couple of days,
bro. I'm [ __ ] knacking, man.
I am [ __ ]
Did I [ __ ] out?
I don't know yet.
I'm so [ __ ]
Yeah. What do you think of anything in
Castle Cactus? That's where I met my mama.
Wow. have se
I'm not sure. I lost some summon but I
might just get KFC.
If only you saw the views.
If only you saw the views. She said
she's going to come down today or
tomorrow at 19 yard.
[ __ ] hell, mate.
Now I'm just going to get the pieces to be fair. Yeah.
These women are [ __ ] in it. Cactus.
You know what you saying? Are you coming
around or not? I'm going to get some KFC
soon and it'll be a lovely site.
Me, you, and KFC. Yeah,
they're all [ __ ] Oh, [ __ ] bro. Oh, man. Oh, god.
cycling short things takes out it.
Could you imagine Virgin boy in a cycle?
Could you Could you imagine Virgin
Virgin boy in a cycle? got this [ __ ]
I love how you wait for me. You were
like, "Hello, mate." Nothing, man. I
just been doing a lot of cycling
yesterday. I cycled 20 miles.
I went all around South London, central London.
basically places I had one night stands.
It was a lovely site.
Now I'm just straight up chilling, man.
I'm chilling now. I'm [ __ ] nowadays. Fancy KFC.
I lost some fancy KFC.
No life but YouTube. Can't get off of
YouTube. That's why I come on sometime
just to say, "Oh, you you're still on
YouTube." I get such satisfaction, you
know. I do I do it to Monty Man as well.
Be like, "You're still on YouTube. Can't
get off it."
Send it on start over. I think I'm going
up for drinks.
Yeah, I was riding everywhere, mate.
Oh, [ __ ] me.
Yeah, I know. I was riding everywhere.
[ __ ] asses out today. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] me. No, bro.
Do you remember singing USA is he cactus?
They were horrible old [ __ ] weren't they?
Horrible [ __ ] They were cactus.
Yeah, Monty said he's called the police
on the Virgin and he needed my crime
reference number. I was like, "Is that
[ __ ] Virgin bothering you,
mate? Is that [ __ ] Virgin bothering
you as well?" I gave him the account. I
gave him the reference number.
I don't know that Virgin was bothering you, mate. Yeah,
USA. Easy still wanted the same number. Cactus. Uh [Music]
You still want me? You [ __ ] mad, bro.
Don't you [ __ ] don't. I don't want her.
She going to come tomorrow.
Yeah, I don't want her back.
I know, mate. I don't care about them.
I literally don't care about them. [Music]
Oh, someone in front of me. [Music]
She's going to come tomorrow. We're
going to [ __ ]
No, you still haven't left YouTube.
You're still on it.
Oh, [ __ ] off, man. Hey, you can't even
take a day off of YouTube, mate. Don't
come on my live stream telling me how I
how I still haven't left YouTube. You
can't even take a [ __ ] day off YouTube.
You don't come tomorrow. [ __ ] Oh,
no. Good. Hey,
this is [ __ ] man.
A joke, man. So tired.
Like I said, wherever my little legs
take me, Cactus.
Wherever my little legs take me.
Oh, she's she's doing something today,
but she's going to come tomorrow.
I get some punani tomorrow.
I probably won't even go out Saturday to
be honest. If she comes tomorrow and I
get to [ __ ] her, I probably won't even
go out tomorrow. I probably won't even
go out Saturday.
Point this, bro. I don't even enjoy it
anymore, man. It's just the same old [ __ ]
Steven Howard always like I've got a boyfriend cactus
but I'm not entirely sure mate because I
can't be bothered.
I might be out on Saturday but I don't
know. I can't be bothered
cuz it's always like I've got a
boyfriend. Know what I mean? Cactus.
That's what my friend said. I just copied them.
But yeah, it is boring though. It is boring.
So I would have went out today. Well, I
prefer Thursdays and Saturdays, but I'm
fixate to go out.
Exactly. Why try when you know the
result? It will never change as well.
It will never change ever. I would just
stick to beers too, you know.
No point trying. You know the result.
Yeah, it's always the same result. Even
if you get a number,
but if I go out, it's just a drink, you
know? I keep saying we should go out,
but it would just be literally to drink
and obviously I'll approach when I'm
drinking, but I'm not going to go out
just to approach.
One second. Someone's messaging me. Yeah.
Yeah. Are you trolling, Cactus?
Be honest if you're trolling me right
now. But yeah. No. Do you know what
[ __ ] up the self-esteem? It's not that
I've got a boyfriend. It's not numbers
that don't reply. It's numbers that
reply to stop replying and then dates.
Dates that where they waste your time.
That's what [ __ ] you. That's what [ __ ]
you. If I go out tomorrow and I hear,
"Oh, I've got a boyfriend. I've got a boyfriend."
Then obviously I expect this [ __ ] in it.
Nothing too awesome. I wanted to go out
for a drink anyways. But when you obviously all,
hey, listen, Stephen, I got a nice little tag. I'm cycling.
I'm cycling about. So yeah.
Oh my [ __ ] man.
Do you remember when I told that black
guy about USA is he?
And he was smiling like he already knew.
He was smil He was smiling as if he already knew.
It's a little burn.
He He He was smiling like he already knew. But
yeah, she not coming today. She's coming
tomorrow. I said, "Okay, so we're going
to [ __ ] tomorrow.
We'll [ __ ] tomorrow then. That's fine."
Yeah, I might go outside Saturday. I
don't know, mate. I just can't be bothered.
I might get KFC today, Joe.
I got some salmon, but I want to get some KFC.
I don't know. KFC, maybe.
Yeah, that's cuz you're fully white,
bro. I need to go to your gym tomorrow
as well. I want to get my muscles more
strong. again. Sorry, big man.
So, I'm going to keep going.
I'm going to keep [ __ ] going.
No, I just woke up, Jo.
I just [ __ ] woke up.
I just [ __ ] woke up, matey.
New horror film coming out. See, I wish
there was something in the cinema, man. nothing
going to go around. She says she's going
to come around tomorrow, but like I
said, if she comes around, then
I might not even go out Saturday.
I don't know. I'm getting too old for it all, mate.
You got enough women's numbers and [ __ ] So
if something was going to happen, it
would have happened by now.
Cycle to [ __ ] That's [ __ ] Oh, bro.
I'm going to do this again, you know.
I'm going to cycle again
and show the views this time.
Do you remember the neighbor cactus?
You know what I felt like doing
yesterday, bro? When I was staying at my
mom's, I had to stay in a different
room. I felt like doing this, bro. But
I'm actually I'm actually tapped to my
head, you know,
cuz like to go out on a bike. Yeah. No,
I didn't cycle to CO, but I bet that one
will [ __ ] come up.
Bro, I was saying to my bro, this whole
fight thing has got me tapped, bro.
Like, I went out again. Even after they
[ __ ] up the first time, I done it again, bro.
I don't give a [ __ ] What's up?
Yeah, bro. I'll get some mad I know. Yeah.
Yeah. I thought I did a madness yesterday, but
I was like, I'll just leave it. It's not worth it.
But my sister was there with a baby and
that in it. So,
trust me, I could I could cause some damage.
Isn't that right, Cactus? Yeah.
I can't be asked, man. that I I said to
my mom, if it was my house, like say it
was my house and you didn't live there,
I would just start on all of them and
then just say that they bullied me and
then got and then I just get me house.
That's what I would do.
I just say like I would just start
madness and then just move. That's what
I would do. Not my house though
if I'm still in it.
It's so [ __ ] up, lad.
Yeah, I saw him the other day.
No, I'd play victim to move. I'd play
victim to them move house. That's what
I'm saying. I'd play victim to them
actually have to move house. I would
play victim. I'd start on all of them.
I'd [ __ ] win and then I would just I
I would just go to the to house and play
victim and say that they bully me so I
can move. Yeah.
Trust me, bro. You don't show on your doorstep. Simple. Yeah.
Yeah. He commented on YouTube. Yeah.
I always feel like he's listening to me
as well. Like whenever I'm there,
you know what I'm saying? I always feel
like he's listening to me.
Just It's next door now, ain't it?
And it shouldn't be what I'm saying.
It's what are they saying? They saw me.
Yeah. And they done they done nothing.
He shouldn't be laughing because he done
nothing. He wrote all of this [ __ ] on
YouTube. Oh, this that, this, that,
this, that. And then when he saw me,
he'd done [ __ ] all. So really, he
shouldn't be laughing. Yeah, he run his
mouth a little bit eight months later
and I just walked past him, but I
wouldn't be laughing, mate. I would not
be laughing if I if I spent all that
time and effort, you know, and you can't
even say they grabbed you and made you
say sorry, cuz they didn't. They done nothing.
And they're the ones that actually
caused it and they kept they kept
starting as well.
You know what I'm saying? They they're
the ones that actually started it, too.
Yeah. I'm gone because I want to go, but
I'm there because I want to go. I like
it where I am.
I love where I am. I don't want to go
back. And I was there yesterday. I was
actually there for 3 days the other day.
Yeah. Good for him.
I don't want to go there. I don't like
the neighbors. I don't like the people.
I don't like the area. Simple.
So shouldn't be what I'm saying. They're
the one that started all of this madness.
And then so you know, you don't even
need to say anything. You don't even
need to do anything. That's the maddest
But you don't understand. I can go there
and easily violate
and and that's it. But I can't be asked, man.
But he started it. He actually did start
You know, it all started with roulette catches.
You know, it all started, You know, it
all started with that roulette table
when I used to play the roulette.
I was being a bit noisy.
I was being a bit noisy. And then
instead of him knocking like he could
have eased the door and said, "Oh, like
my child's trying to sleep. Can you just
be quiet?" No, no, no, no, no. Like he
was he was shouting up his mouth and
then I just retaliated. Bro,
that's how it started, bro. So, it did
start with it did start with with him.
So, that's why I just [ __ ] ignore it, bro.
Madness. See, where I live, you don't
get any of this stuff.
You don't get any of this stuff. None of
it at all. At all at all. So, Yeah.
Yeah. Might have been quiet before I
turned up. But if he had turned around
and said, "Oh, like my child's kind of
trying to see. Can you please keep your
noise down?" I think he said, "Shut the
[ __ ] up." And I said, "Who the [ __ ] are
you talking to, you cunt?" And then it
all started from there, basically. Yeah.
So yeah, bro.
Yeah, maybe. But if if they turned
around and said
like, "Oh, can you just be quiet like
you're you're disturbing me?" then I'll
be like, "Oh, okay."
So, it's not all me. Um,
but it is It's so weird. So weird.
It's just people in it. People are weird.
Oh, I'm going to have a nice Kentucky
Fried Chicken today.
If the virgin will ever get laid. I
don't think so, man.
I don't think so, mate. Yeah, I got
salmon in the fridge. I'll probably just
have that later as well. But
yeah, I would have
because where I where I used to live, I
started on a neighbor and he was a big
[ __ ] He was a big fat [ __ ] the the
gay guy that had children. I started on
him, bro, cuz he was trying to [ __ ]
film one of my friends thinking it was
me. And I I [ __ ] stood up to him, bro.
But it was where I live. and
so I could do it. And then after that
then they just they were just all right
after that. They were a big [ __ ] They
were a big [ __ ] as well. Big fat [ __ ]
He was a gay guy with two kids. He had a
dog as well. I don't give a [ __ ] mate.
Like you just come here and you think
you're going to start recording people
thinking it's me? I said go and record
me now. And I slapped the camera at your [ __ ] hand.
Yeah. And then he and then he stopped.
And then he never never done it again.
Then he was just all right. Yeah. You've
been here what, two [ __ ] months?
We've been here [ __ ] years, mate. And
you think you can start going around
thinking that you're going to start
[ __ ] recording people? I said,
"Record me, big man." That's what I said.
[ __ ] idiot, bro.
I remember it was one summer, you know.
It was summer. I remember it as well.
[ __ ] pair of [ __ ]
Jo pair of [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah,
I don't like that bite and talk. I like
to be a legal citizen, you know.
A legal citizen, matey.
Beard's getting long.
A legal [ __ ] citizen. Whatever that means.
Be vaping a lot tomorrow. Yep.
Do you like Jennifer Aniston, Joe? I
keep seeing pictures of her when she was younger.
Um, she's average
again. That was another that was another
trend as well. Jennifer Aniston, Beyonce,
um, they were all trends.
They were all all trends. Trends that
they're just trends, in it, basically.
But I remember her being one of them.
Oh, you like Sher Cole? I mean, yeah. If
you don't like Sher Cole, you're [ __ ] gay.
Even though she's the most average
looking person. Nah, you're [ __ ] gay, mate.
You're [ __ ] gay, mate.
[ __ ] gay. Don't like Chev. You're
[ __ ] gay, mate.
[ __ ] gay. I wonder how many better
looking people you see every day. Uh,
but he wouldn't call you gay for that
though, would he? Nah, cuz their name's
not Shervel Carl. [ __ ] copycat.
I literally don't even see the appeal. I
don't I don't see the I don't see the hype.
She's not even that good.
Let alone her defining your sexuality if
you don't find her attractive. What the
[ __ ] There's literally nothing special about her.
No, it just looks like a normal person.
Nothing special at all. I'm trying to
think. Trying to look. Yeah, man.
You have celebrity crushes then, Joe. I
take it. You have celebrity crushes, eh?
You have celebrity crushes, do you?
They're pointless. They're a waste of time. Yeah.
Told you I'd sleep today, bro. It's
[ __ ] that good.
All that little cycling. All that cycling about.
Oh, mate. I went over some big [ __ ]
steep [ __ ] speed bump, too.
Yeah, he just said that she cing just to
fit in. Just to fit in. I just wanted to
grab his little head and just rub it and
say, "You little copycat."
I always told him he was a Tesco Value
version of Elvis Presley.
Just a Tesco value version of Elvis Presley.
You are that one, Joe? Yeah.
Oh, mate. Why is it with this Elvis
Presley, man? He's [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, Elvis Presley, he's proper [ __ ] He is.
But at least Elvis Presley had the
looks. He had the money. I mean, Joe,
he had the looks, he had the money. So,
Nah, I don't kiss virgins. Sorry, mate.
But at least Elvis had the looks and had the money
or like a certain person. Is that right, Joe? Yeah.
He had no talent. Boo. Boo. Boo.
When he when he used to come on the
telly, I used to be like, "Boo, he sucks." Yeah,
he [ __ ] sucks, mate.
Oh, I can't stop thinking about that
whiff I saw the other day. Grievously, I
want him. He's so cute.
He's so cute. I was going to say, how
much for the dog? I want him.
He's a lovely little dog he was.
He was messaging me. Yeah. Yeah man.
So you imagine me on a little cycle breezy.
Yeah. I was like when I when I was like
by London Bridge, I was like that's
where I met my mommy. Oh, I actually was
near the bit where I met my mama cuz it
was by like the train station and there
was a pub London Bridge. There's a pub
in there. I said that's where I met my mama. Music
belly can't get attached now. He's
already found his mama.
I hate you people. You You always mock me.
You always [ __ ] mock me. Yeah. Awesome.
You copy that.
Right. Let me put my little shorts on
and head off to Colonel's Kentucky. Greavvesy.
Let me head off to the Colonel Kentucky.
Is that okay with you, boss?
I might go out on Saturday and make some
money on Sunday. What noise?
Is that okay with you, boss?
Yeah. What are you eating today?
Yeah, I know somebody that can get me
discount in Burger King Grezy. So,
basically I met some guy in the Burger
King in Leicester Square and um yeah,
basically we got talking and he said
that he can get me discount but he only
works on Thursdays and Saturdays, but
Thursdays and Saturdays are my favorite
day. So, I was like, "Mate, you
shouldn't be asking. You shouldn't be
offering me that because
you're going to get me really fat." But
I love burger. I love Burger King, so
you know you're going to get me fat.
Oh, bless you then, Grezy. Bless. To be
honest, I might get some ice cream today
as well. To be honest,
I need to start really saving money,
man. But it's hard, is it, Greasy?
Is there anywhere on sale that Ben &
Jerry's? Let me see.
sure about the gaining weight cuz
obviously I exercise a lot and stuff but
it's [ __ ] a [ __ ] to try to get on
sale now it
oh there's one here
I just love Ben and Jerry's cookie
that's just me all over bro I don't like
I don't like any other Um,
but you only live once, in it.
You only live once.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
I don't know how many calories I must
have burnt yesterday, but Oh,
my arms are feeling quite strong.
We see that's all that matters, isn't it?
Oh, that must be her.
Just come around and tuck my willie.
Yeah, I'm going to [ __ ] this time. Definitely. Yeah.
What do you reckon it would have
happened today, Greasy, if I went out? I
think I would have collapsed.
I actually think I would have collapsed,
bro. Genuinely would have collapsed,
I think I would have collapsed, matey.
What do you think? Yeah,
I think I would have eventually would
have fought with me.
But for Saturday, we'll be good.
Are you ready for Saturday, Grezy? Boyfriend,
you better [ __ ] be ready.
You better be [ __ ] ready. Boyfriend,
I'm going to go live just for you, lad.
They won't got boyfriends. Right,
I'm going KFC. I'll talk to you later. Bye.