Yeah. Yeah. Just doing a little uh
welfare check just to see just to see if
it's the same people in YouTube. I told
you I was going to start doing this
every week or so. Oh, [ __ ]
People that they're talking about themselves.
One, two, three. people. Oh yeah.
Well, that's it. Day zero.
Oh, we already got one person coming.
Oh, mate. What a [ __ ] day I had
yesterday. You still on your YouTube
cactus. What a [ __ ] day I had, mate.
I was cycling all around London. It was
taking me to [ __ ] Elephant and Castle
where I had a one night stand and then
it was taking me to Batisy where I had a
one night stand. I went all over the
place. Safe to say I'm completely [ __ ]
now. Anything in Castle is where I met
uh USA Izzy and I was like, "Oh, if only
I actually stayed around that night
and just stayed there, what would have happened?"
Now I'll never know.
No, I'll never know. When I went to
where I had a one night stand with Sig.
Oh, no. Just cycling around, man. Get some exercising.
[ __ ] long it was, mate. Oh, [ __ ] me.
And yeah, I went to your gym as well.
Now I'll never know.
Now I'll never know. There were some
sexy [ __ ] about, but I don't care
anymore. I didn't approach anyone. I
can't be asked with it anymore. Boring,
mate. I'm going soon. I'm going next
week. So, don't do it.
Yeah, I'm not talking about it. But
look, look at that tan, bro. Look at
that tan. Look at them arms. He's
telling me, "Hey, tone it up, mate. Look
at Look at the color between this
t-shirt and this arm. We brown very soon, mate."
Yeah, good for them, man. They're all
the outdressers. Good for them. Go and
approach them. Oh [ __ ] they're out in
dresses, man. That's good for them, man.
Then maybe you should start approaching
them if they're out in [ __ ] dresses.
Don't tell me about it.
Nah, I'm trying to get her to come
around today to be honest, bro. Look,
this tomorrow should be brown. That's
how much [ __ ] That's how much I was
in the sun.
Oh, but now I'll never know.
Now I'll never know, lad.
Yeah, it's too hot out there, man. I got
the fan on.
Yeah, I got the fan on.
I was really hoardy yesterday, man. I
can't go out today. I'm too [ __ ]
Look, I'm making some serious gains
again. Look, Greasy. I'm making some
serious gains, buddy.
And I'm getting a serious tan, man.
Yeah, we don't [ __ ] about, bro.
Nah, mate. I'm I'll be sending I tell
you what I'll be sending. I'll be
sending my my my head to the pillow and
going to sleep. That's what I'll be
doing. I'll be going to sleep, mate. I'm
[ __ ] knacking, mate. I cycled so much
yesterday, Gre. I must have cycled about 20 miles.
I must have cycled about 20 miles, mate.
I got some [ __ ] Look at my Look at
that pan, bro. Well, the light's
actually off, so you can't even see it. Look,
look at my look at my timeline, bro.
Well, it went red sunburn, but now it's
going to it's going to go back to um
it's going to go back to uh it's going
to go back brown. So, I cycled like 20 miles yesterday.
It was a madness. Anything at Castle,
but I was going all around London
Bridge. I was having fun in the sun.
Just like you should be doing, having
fun in the sun.
Yeah. Look, I cut my finger as well.
Some [ __ ] almost run me over the can. He
almost run me over the [ __ ] Yeah. [ __ ] hell. Oh, what?
Nah, I could be I can't be [ __ ] I was too tired.
I've done a lot the past couple of days.
I was too tired. I can't be bothered
with it. It's just the same [ __ ]
This is the same [ __ ] but then I can't be asked
after that Italian one and all of that
[ __ ] I couldn't be bothered with it.
I'm just wasting my time here. I'm gone
next week anyway. So, nah, I just
figured I'm just wasting my time here.
It's pointless. I'm wasting my time and
I'm too exhausted.
My friend wants to go out Saturday, but
I probably won't even go out to be
honest. Is this no point anymore, man?
It's always the same old.
It's pointless, mate. You get to an age
where you think I can't be [ __ ]
I did make some videos, but I'm not
putting it up.
I went to Elephant and Castle, Grezy.
It's called Elephant and Castle. It's
where I met USA Izzy. It's where we made love.
It's where I sucked on her boobies.
Greasy. Now I'll never know. Squeezy.
Now I'll [ __ ] never know, mate.
It's basically called a place. It's it's
it's just got loads of car loads of
cars. Oh, mate. I saw a cute little wifter.
Um Greavvesy. He was so cute. Oh my god.
He was like a white little wolf. I I
wanted to nick him. He was so cute.
Now, I can't even remember what the B&B
looked like, but I know it was the same area.
Get this [ __ ] round to horny, man.
Yeah. Is this a load of one second?
Oh, here it is. Look, I'll take a
screenshot of the video. Oh my god, it's
so cute. Rezy, look.
She's so cute.
I don't know what [ __ ] breed it is.
He cutey. Look.
Don't know what [ __ ] breed that dog
is, but I wanted it.
Yeah, he's cute, mate.
Don't know what [ __ ] breed he was. I
I've never seen that breed in my life.
It looks like something of a cartoon and
that and everyone went over to rub him
and stuff. He's cute.
Always wanted your phrase.
Now I'll never know, cactus. Now I'll
never know. I had that stuck in my head
yesterday, you know. Now I'll never know, Grezy.
Now I'll never know.
I'm horny, bro.
I was so horny yesterday, man.
Saying pulling in this country is too
hard, is it?
This 19year-old's a [ __ ] as well, lad. You know,
it's [ __ ] It's too bad. It's
impossible pulling in this country, is
it? But I'm sick of this 19y old man. I
just don't like her. Cuz that's what
happens when they're like when they're
like 18, 19.
[ __ ] off, you little Welsh [ __ ] If I
ever see you in London again, I'm going
to smash your [ __ ] face in. Tell the
police I said that as well. I will smash
your [ __ ] face in, you [ __ ] W
skitty in the galan.
You [ __ ] Wales [ __ ] Yeah, let me
know when you're in London again, you
little [ __ ] And actually, let me know
where you are, bro. Watch what happens
to you, you little [ __ ] snake. I'll kick
your ass right out of it and send you
back to where you come from, you silly [ __ ] Yeah,
tell the police said that as well, J.
Yeah, [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
You and that little virgin. Yeah, let me
know when you're both together.
Please do, matey. Anyways, so as I was
saying before, this [ __ ] interrupted me
is that's how they start off. You see,
they start off very naive learning about
life. So they're not as bad when they're
18, 19. You understand cactus? When
they're 18, they're not bad. But as they
get older, they just turn into [ __ ]
They just turn into westernized [ __ ]
that love Tik Tok and love Instagram. So
all the women become [ __ ] You see,
that's what happens. They just become [ __ ] So
you see what I mean? It's very rare
they're that country when they're that
age. You see?
So yeah. Yeah. That's all that's all you
can do. You're a little grass. That's
fine, bro. You're just a little grass.
You're a little [ __ ] Anyways, I've
been to Wales a few times and you kept
your mouth shut. You're a [ __ ] idiot, bro. Yeah.
Trying to act like you're some [ __ ]
kind of hard man last time. Yeah. When
you was running down the train station
when you know I was still in London. You
know you'd get [ __ ] up, you idiot. And
the only reason I didn't go to Wales is
because I couldn't go because of the co
and you was running down the stairs even
though you knew I was still in London
and that wasn't even a time of the
meeting place. You're pathetic, mate.
Yeah. Come back when you can actually
grow a beard, you [ __ ] weirdo. Bye-bye now. idiot. Anyways,
so yeah, cactus, that's basically where
we're at. So yeah,
good to cycle around. Eh,
it's quite cheap today.
I made a new friend. Cactus.
But yeah, it's hard to pull this up. Yeah,
it's hard, bro. It is hard. I was
thinking yesterday when I was lying
about you might as well just stick to
[ __ ] when you come back here, you
might as well stick to [ __ ] Brazilian escorts.
You might as well stick to Brazilian
escorts. [ __ ] it. Save time, save money.
You might as well just stick to that. Is
it? I think so.
What's a [ __ ] Dion as well, bro?
Brazilian ones. The Brazilian ones. Yeah.
Yeah. It's hard, man.
I don't know, bro. I don't know.
So, I couldn't even go out today cuz I'm
just too exhausted, lad.
No, it's not hard for me, bro. I can
just use escorts.
Them women outside are not interested. I
was in central London 3 days in a row. I
didn't even do any approaches because I
can't be bothered with it. It's the same [ __ ]
cuz it's like, okay, well, even if you
get a number, the chances of it going
anywhere is slim to none. So there's no
point even trying in this country cuz
even if you get a number, yeah, say they
don't say, "Oh, I've got a boyfriend."
The chances of it leading anywhere is is
it's is nil. And then when you realize
that the chances is nil, then
you know, it's like I'm doing it on
Saturday because I am going out
drinking. If it wasn't for drinking, I
would never do an approach ever again.
So yeah, you have given up because
you're going out after the [ __ ] few
days I've had. I was like, "Oh, I need a
drink this week." But if I wasn't
drinking, I wouldn't do any approaches
because I can't be bothered. So, you
basically I basically have given up really
cuz you're out drinking anyways and
you're going to approach because you're
drunk. So, but in terms of sober, I
wouldn't do it again, but I can't be bothered.
Not even scared. Obviously, I do them
all the time. So, I think it was the one
near my house. when I didn't reply back
in the Italian, it just put me off. It
just put me off like approaching anyone
ever again. Cuz
if it was just the I haven't got a
boyfriend [ __ ] then it wouldn't be so
bad. Same [ __ ] every week. But when you
know that this is what you're kind of
dealing with, it's very unlikely all of
a sudden now it's just going to change.
So you might as well just not even bother.
That's it just makes perfect sense. If
something was going to happen, it would
have happened by now. And them two
experiences specifically has put me off.
And now this 19year-old's being a [ __ ]
now as well. So
yeah, only fun for you, mate. Getting
choked by some random guy's [ __ ] where
they pee isn't fun. So you can see how
she's sort of turning into a [ __ ] You
can see how she's writing. She's turning
into a [ __ ]
And this is what they they turn into.
They turn into [ __ ] as they get older.
And she's obviously dead to 20 now, so
she's getting older. Then they just turn into [ __ ]
I was just saying uh I was cycling about
all around London
yesterday, Joe. I cycled about 20 miles.
Got the exercise in. Got the nice tan
going. Ready to go away. Got some nice
muscularly arms. Nice tan to go away
with. Yeah. See, I can't sit on YouTube
all day like these people. Um, so
basically, um, yeah, I was just doing
some cycling and it was a long [ __ ] 3
days. So, yeah. And she and yeah, I
didn't speak to anyone,
but she's becoming a [ __ ] now. This
19year-old's actually come to [ __ ] I
said, "Hold on a minute, mate." I was
like, I'm not your mate, firstly, and
second of all, I'm not a random guy.
Somebody I'm somebody that you've met 20
times. So, she's actually turning into a [ __ ] now.
That's what happens. They turn into
[ __ ] as soon as they start like uh
watching like Tik Tok and [ __ ] all of
that [ __ ] They just turned into [ __ ]
So, that's why I was in central London
for 3 days. Bro, do you know the amount
of women I saw? convince me to any of
them cuz unless I'm drunk, there's no
point me putting up with their [ __ ]
It's boring. It bors me. You know, I'm
exhausted and you're not going to get a different reply.
That one by the house and that Italian
one, it tells me all I need to know. So, it's pointless
and I'm so exhausted as well. So,
I'm not [ __ ] I'm not doing it, bro.
So, [ __ ] them. Yeah.
But yeah, she was all right when I first met her.
Just something to do.
Just something to do. I went to Elephant
and Castle. I went to where I had the
one night stands. Basy Sig, USA, Izzy,
Elephant and Castle. Now I'll never know
what would have happened if I stayed
around that night.
Now I'll never know.
Isn't that right, Cactus? It was
actually quite a good experience. Some
nice views to be had. You almost [ __ ]
run me over the [ __ ]
You almost run me [ __ ] over the [ __ ]
Yeah, it was a nice nice view. It was a lovely view.
Lovely lovely view. Yeah.
Went really far out. People could people
could believe it
now. I'll never know.
Nah, mate. I just wanted to go out on
the bike. Just wanted to go out. Oh,
it's [ __ ] long, mate. [ __ ] ass is
hurting. But I didn't speak to any women
because I can't be bothered with them, bro.
Cuz it's like even if you get a [ __ ]
date, we know what happens when we even
get a date. So, the whole thing is just pointless.
You know what I'm going to do with this
19year-old? I'm going to get around
again and I'm going to choke her in my
dick and then [ __ ] her off.
I'm going to choke her with my dick.
Yeah. One more time. Make her swallow my
car and I'm going to [ __ ] her off. I
don't like I don't like her her I don't
like what she's becoming.
Yeah. It felt very nostalgia. It almost
brought a tear to my eye.
You know, anyone that goes to London,
you should rent one of these bikes, man.
They're pedal bikes, but they're smooth
pedal bikes, so you don't get So you
don't get tired.
So you don't even get tired.
It It's a good experience, but a [ __ ]
tiring one at the end. I was almost
crashed into people, mate.
I was almost crashing into people. But
the bad thing with central London is
there's no [ __ ]
There's no proper bike lanes. There's no
bike lanes. There's only bike lanes when
you get out of central London. There's
like literally no bike lanes.
And the police officer said hi to me. He
must uh he must um
be encouraged by what I'm doing for the
economy and stuff, which is quite sweet.
I was on the [ __ ] road. Sometimes I
was on the pavement, but mostly I was on
the road and the cycle lanes. Just such
a good experience, man.
It was a good experience.
just to like be going all around the
areas. It's like a good view, you know.
I was like, "Elephant and Castle." Oh,
and I met some guy and I said, "Oh,
where are you from?" He said, "Elephant
and Castle." I was like, "You can't be.
You know, we got we got rid of that area.
We can't you can't be from there.
You can't be.
You can't be. We we got rid of that
person and I thought like, okay, I'm
still getting [ __ ] over here cuz I own
the whole of [ __ ] South London. I
don't think I started in East London. So
that's miles away. That see is where all
the dogs It's where it's where all the
little dogs live. Cactus.
I'm going to I'm going to choke I'm
going to choke her in my dick and I'm
going to [ __ ] her up. But I don't like her attitude.
He's becoming a westernized [ __ ]
and I don't like it.
Why are they such [ __ ] man? I swear to
God, bro. Why do they have to be such
[ __ ] Like even the way they walk, they
they walk like their [ __ ] don't stink. Yeah,
I remember that. Yeah,
I took some videos,
but not the one in London Bridge. That
was a mad view, bro.
I'm surprised I didn't get [ __ ] run
over at one point. I was so tired, bro.
It wasn't even a joke.
At one point,
I'm going to get her to come over and
I'm going to choke her in my dick. [ __ ] this. He's
just a [ __ ]
Here's a screenshot.
It wasn't an electric bike. It was a It
was a smooth pedal bike, which felt like
an electric bike. I'll show you if you want.
This is where I was.
This is some of it.
That dog is so cute, mate.
madness with my [ __ ] signal, bro.
I'm bathing. I I'll give you a little look.
Nope. You still haven't left YouTube.
The signal. Why did the signal matter?
Because I needed a signal to unlock the
bike. So when I parked it and I had no
signal, I couldn't unlock the bike and I
had to go all the way back home and then
come back again. I had to change my SIM
in the end cuz the signal kept kept
cutting out. I had to change my rider.
I put my little feet up. Look at that.
Oh, [ __ ] And that's how I got time. So, yeah, that's lovely. Yeah,
just having fun in the sun. Oh, mate.
Nah, it didn't even feel like 20 miles.
The pedal is so smooth. My feet ain't
even hurting. My feet are not even
hurting. The only thing that's hurting
them is my ass. They're pedal bikes, but
they're smooth pedal bikes. So, I can't
explain it. It's not like an actual
normal pedal bike.
I know it was [ __ ] it was long, bro.
But it's good though because at least
I'll be brown tomorrow when it finally
uh runs out. So yeah,
that's what these people need to be
doing. like this instead of coming on
YouTube every day projecting,
you know, they might find it will do him
the world of good
talking about themselves every day.
You know, I might actually [ __ ] this
[ __ ] today. You know that.
I might actually [ __ ] her. I might go to
suck my dick and just ram her one more
time and then [ __ ] her off.
We're going to make sure she swallows as well. Again,
I hate her. She's a [ __ ]
The older she's getting, the worse she's getting.
And it's going to turn me on even more
cuz she's a [ __ ] And I want to make her
just [ __ ] my dick. That's what I want to
do. I want to [ __ ] her hard as well,
bro. I ain't had sex in ages.
She has to be such a [ __ ] All these
women are all [ __ ] every time, bro. Yeah.
And I'm going and I'm just going to [ __ ]
off by watch. Yeah,
cuz she's a [ __ ] She's an actual [ __ ]
Have you noticed they're all actual
[ __ ] Like they're just [ __ ] Even
people that like you've been with
just why why is they've just turned all
of a sudden into a [ __ ]
Yeah. Don't worry though, I'm I'll make
her pay with my dick. Watch.
Yeah, just watch, bro. Watch. I'm going
to [ __ ] her so hard, bro. Watch. And I'm
just going to leave her. Random guy. And
you're calling me mate. I'm not your
[ __ ] mate. But I I'll keep going
along with it, though. I'll keep going
along with it.
She's starting to be a proper [ __ ] now.
Really hate it. I do hate it. I hate it, man.
First of all, I'm going to make her suck
my dick and I'm just going to run my
dick in her watch. That's what I'm going to do. Yeah.
And that's it.
I've had enough of it.
Generally just had enough of it.
That's why I don't speak to them
anymore, you know? I just do my own
thing. This is why I don't don't bother
with them no more. I got some numbers
Saturday. So they reply. Two replied and
stop replying. And then you got that
Italian like what the [ __ ]
this [ __ ] watch. I'll go around [ __ ] [ __ ]
I'll probably do anal with her as well.
Guys, stop being a weirdo on my channel, Joe man.
Stop being a weirdo on my channel.
I told you about this before.
Border the line sexual assault. You wish, bro.
But yeah, they've started being like [ __ ]
and I'm really really getting sick of it,
you know. Well, I don't bother with them no more.
Don't bother with them no more. Me
cuz I approached one in my area, gave me
her number, didn't reply. Italian went
on a date. She wasting my time. Now, how
long are you going to keep really
dealing with this? You know,
no, it's not saying what it sounds like.
You're taking what I've said out of
context. I said she's going to suck my
dick and I'm going to [ __ ] her hard.
How was that sexual assault?
But yeah, she's Anyway, she's becoming a
[ __ ] Anyway, they all they're all
[ __ ] I even found like the people that
I got went on dates with, they've got
this [ __ ] attitude.
And I don't think you're going to find
anyone in this country that doesn't have this attitude.
It's never going to change. Like, it
will never change ever. Like, my friend
keeps saying, "Oh, we should go out Saturday." But yeah,
I just want to get her around so I can
[ __ ] her, bro.
Watch. I'm just going to [ __ ] her, man.
I should get the bits pregnant.
That's what what I should have done with
USA. Is he? Yeah.
Yeah. You know how they they like to
trap men. We should trap them in it. Yeah.
She said she doesn't like choke sucking
dick because it makes her choke and that.
What the [ __ ]
She looks better now as well. She's
gained weight and she looks older. But
nah, I can't stay with someone that's a
[ __ ] Sorry. I don't like [ __ ] Nah.
And they've all seemed to be [ __ ]
Really? westernized Tik Tok watches.
They are literally Joe MPCs. Like I I'm
not bothered about it anymore. I'm
leaving. I don't care. But they are they
literally are all the same. Like I'm not
bothered. But I'm speaking from a
realistic point of view, right?
I went around on this bike. I saw so
many different people. I must have
cycled 20, 30 miles. I heard people on
the train and they literally are exactly
the same in London. They have the same
attitude. They have the same snobby
look. Like even if you earrop
conversation, like you can sense and and
feel fear feel the entitlement coming
from them like you can't explain it.
It's really hard to explain.
Like I can't explain it like when
they're talking. So
you can't like it wasn't a line bike. So
you can't explain it, mate. You can't
explain it. But they're all the same
like stuck up too many stuck up people.
That's what I mean. So that's why I
don't [ __ ] with them.
Yeah. I actually fancy some sex. I've
not had sex for ages. Only [ __ ]
Yeah. When I was last with the escort,
she said, "Oh, you're not going to have
sex again this time." I said, "Nope."
Yeah, they're like NPCs. You can't even
get a convo out of them, let alone get a
friend friendship out of them, let alone
get a relationship out of them. So, you
know that Pakistan girl, I gave her to
my Pakistan friend who's actually a
Muslim and she's being a [ __ ] to him. I
was like, "What?" Like, she's replying
back, but she's doing some [ __ ] [ __ ] again.
She's being a [ __ ] Like, I can't
explain it. Like, proper trolling. She's
like, "Oh, Pete is a good friend." I was
like, "Bro, is this person trolling or something?
I'm a good friend. You met me once for 5
hours and then you just stopped. You
just went ghosted." So, I just gave I
gave her to um to him because obviously
I'm not Muslim. So, I'm not converting.
Why should I have to convert? You know,
I'm not doing that. So, now you said you
only date a Muslim, so you can date my
friend then, can't you? Simple.
So, that's it. And then she's just being
a proper proper [ __ ]
It's the cuntiness with them. You know
what I'm saying? Yeah.
I wouldn't do it if I weren't drinking,
bro. I would not deal with him if I weren't drinking.
I thought this Italian one would have
actually been all right, like been the
one, but nah.
All the same time wasters entitled.
Yeah, that Italian one and the one near
my house really [ __ ] with my head,
bro. I'm not going to lie to you. It
[ __ ] with my head
cuz it just the more this stuff happens,
the more you think, okay, yeah, it is
impossible, is it? It's impossible. It's
got to be impossible in this country.
It's got to be impossible in this
country, you know, but even if you're
decent looking and you get a number, it
doesn't even go anywhere anyways. So,
oh, and you see it in the gym as well.
You see sexy women in the gym.
But there's no point talking to them
because they're just going to say they
got boyfriends. So, I just mess with
your head. So, there's no point.
Yep. The one where the guy clapped, she didn't reply.
even though I got her number stone cold
struggle right next to the house then I
done the Italian one
and then she obviously met me so it's
like there's just no point nothing good
can come out of it
n I'm not doing gym approaches nothing
good can come out of it
like Joe nothing good good can come out
of approaching like nothing good can
come out of it
once I ram this [ __ ] 19year-old I'm
going Rammer, R. Yeah, I'm going to
rammer hard. Then maybe I'll consider
putting up with it again when I come back.
But nah, I don't know. I just can't be
bothered with them.
They're just all the same, bro.
Yeah, that Italian one and the other one
were good looking, man. The other one by
the shop was as well.
See, they moan about all men being the
same, but then when they find normal
people, they then they're not
interested. So, I mean, what the [ __ ]
I don't pay for anything.
So, I'm just going to tell her to come
around and I'm just going to [ __ ] her.
That's the Italian one.
We started being weird cuz we tried
kissing after like 4 hours.
We was flirting, holding hands and [ __ ]
She's not a [ __ ] escort, you [ __ ]
idiot. Do you just listen to what I [ __ ] said?
Yeah, I'm going to do that. I'm going to
might as well. I can't be dealing with
her and seeing her when she's got this attitude.
I think she's 20 now, but yeah.
Yeah, she's Italian. And then she just
turned like I was I'm not dealing with this [ __ ]
And then I even said, "Oh, let's like
meet again. Oh, I'm new to this date and
shit." I even said, "Oh, I don't want to
[ __ ] it up." So, I tried meeting her
again. And then she just weren't having
any of it. So, so I tried. Can't say I didn't try, bro.
Sad state of affairs, eh?
Yeah, you are a loser. Stop talking
about yourself. I see you on Monty's all
the time, man.
Yeah, stop talking about yourself, bro.
It's not good for your mental health. Go
get a bike and [ __ ] cycle for like 30 miles, man.
And then come back and then look in the
mirror. Don't talk about yourself on my
chat, bro. It's no good for your mental health.
So, it's just the same old same old.
Just somebody wanted to go on a date to
waste your [ __ ] time. But I started
really liking this Italian one, man. She
was [ __ ] cute.
She looked better in real life as well.
Anyways, bye-bye. Yeah, he does. And you
don't have a bird. And you've never had
a bird. Go take it away from my channel.
And she was like, I don't know, bro. I
just did. She was She was nice looking, bro.
was holding hands, vaping, which is why
I bought the vape,
which is why I bought the vape. Oh,
look. Got some bun change here. I spent
about [ __ ] 200 [ __ ] quid the other day, mate.
Just on [ __ ] a load of old Oh, man.
What you doing?
Smudge, smudge, smudge. 200 pound on a
date. But not to worry. Got some more
bum change here.
Got some bond change here in the cooler
and a nice little vape.
Get better at it now. So, this is the
only thing I have left to remember you by, you know.
Now, I'll now I'll never know.
They're rechargeable ones, too.
Yeah, they're rechargeable ones, too.
Yeah, that's only one was nice, bro.
What the [ __ ] I'm expecting some
4.5 out of 10. Five out of 10.
What's funny is she went to the wrong
bar cuz there's a few of the bars with a
different name and had to run all the
way to where she was.
And I was like, "Oh [ __ ] is that my date?" Wow.
She's quite good-looking.
And I don't say someone's good-looking
when they're not good-looking like these simp. Well, yeah.
Yeah. I don't know.
It's [ __ ] up, isn't it? Yesterday I
was in a black track suit approaching.
But the one, like I said, the one around
my shop that the one around the shop was
also nice as well. So, but she just
didn't reply. They don't even give
people a [ __ ] chance, but then they
moan about men. It's ridiculous, man.
Fix the [ __ ] up, bro.
You know, but like I said, real life
experiences, online advice, two
different things, Joe.
They're complete two different things.
In real life, they're all NPCs and stuck
up, but what people on Reddit tell you
is something completely different.
So, you know, you can't take any advice online.
cuz it won't match with your life
experiences. It will contradict your
life experiences. You see,
when I run around the corner, she could
have at least [ __ ] met you to see how
it went. Even for like food and stuff.
See, the thing is, I don't even care
about sex. I just wanted to meet
someone. I didn't even care about the
sex. Like if they turned around and
said, "Oh, we won't have sex for a month
or whatever." I wouldn't give a [ __ ]
you know? It's just about get make
getting getting the ball rolling. And
the only thing I went for the [ __ ]
kiss for the Italian is cuz we were like
flirting and [ __ ] so I thought why not?
It wasn't like completely dead.
Nah, it's not a London thing. It's an England thing.
It's an American thing. They're like
that everywhere here.
They're like that everywhere here.
They're all [ __ ] Everyone's a [ __ ]
here. Like you open the door for someone.
It's like this northern guys. Oh, watch
where you going. I said, you [ __ ] saw
me in front of you. But to be fair, he
weren't that bad. Like for a cyclist.
Yeah. He wasn't even that rude. Like
them cyclist. Yeah. I seen one the other
day and he was like he said to the guy,
"Oh, smash your [ __ ] face." And I
said, "I wish you [ __ ] said that to
me, mate. I'd throw him off that [ __ ]
bike." But for a cyclist, he just was
basically like, "Oh, like just be a bit
more careful." But they can get really
rude them cyclists.
They can get really [ __ ] rude.
But he was all right to be fair.
They get really rude.
But I just said like I was you just saw
me. I was in front of you. You know what
I'm saying? So yeah, they get really
rude. They can
cyclists are the rudest kind of people,
but they should be cycle lanes in
central London. But I don't know why
there's no cycle lanes.
They're cycle they're getting a [ __ ]
road [ __ ] tax. You know what I'm saying? So
but no, they're not they're not fine. No
woman's fine in this country. Well,
unless they're in their 40s or 50s,
they're not fine. I can safely say I've
never ever met a decent woman in my
whole life. Wow, that speaks [ __ ]
volume. That does.
That actually speaks a lot of volume to
be sat there at 27 with all this life
experience and say, "Oh, you've never
even met one." That was actually No.
No. I generally can't even think of one.
I was going to say sig, but then maybe
it was just because she was just dumb.
But no, they're all all the same really.
Whether they pretend they got boyfriends
or whether they play mind games or
whether they're like wasting people's
time, they all seem pretty pretty the
same to me from all the ones that I've met.
Even though Virgin Boy tries to tell me
they're different, even though I've been
with more women than him, but he's
trying to say that I don't know all
women, even though I know more women
than him, but apparently I don't know all women. So yeah,
USA Izzy, complete [ __ ] Doesn't matter
if you got her or not. Just all of them.
All of them.
And then they cry like a [ __ ] when you
start messaging their family. Like I
don't get it. Like you start being a
[ __ ] Someone be a come back to you and
then you start playing victim.
And like the whole like them replying
back to negativity and being a [ __ ] had
a come from Australia last week. So they
all what they do is pretty similar
to each other.
Yeah. So that was probably cuz she was
just low IQ
and then a 19year-old just gets worse
and worse and worse and worse and worse. So yeah,
and you know it's them as well because I
was thinking like what could have you
done different on this date with this
Italian and there's nothing you could
have done because even the people that
you have kissed and you have made out
with have still ghosted you. Even the
people that you haven't tried kissing
has ghosted you. So it's like obviously
it's [ __ ] them. They're me. They're
mental, isn't it? So
this mad mad bro
they go and they to pass time simple. So
yeah I've just had enough of it mate.
That's why I didn't really speak to anyone anymore.
And they make you um they make you lose
your confidence because they make they
make you think that it's something wrong
with you even though it's there's
nothing [ __ ] wrong with you.
You know what I'm saying? So it's just
like a it's just a mind game. It's just
it's just mind [ __ ] because with the
whole I've got a boyfriend, they say
that to most people. That's just what
you're always going to get. So you can
kind of move on from it. But then when
it's like dates and stuff, you think oh
like is there something wrong with you?
Because obviously you feel like you're
alone in it because you don't see other
people's dates. You don't see how other
people's dates go, but you see people
approach and see they say they got
boyfriends, but you don't see these
things happen on dates because you don't
watch. You don't see people's dates. So
that's why you think it's you.
So, but obviously it's them because cuz
if you look at previous experiences, you
can see that it's obviously [ __ ]
them. Now, I had a breakfast today, man.
I went to Calvary. I ate seven slices of
bacon. Oh, bro. I had seven slices of
bacon, two sausages. Oh, mate. I had a
lot. I got my money's worth. I got my
£10 worth, bro. I ate six, seven slices
of bacon, two sausages, egg. Obviously,
I'm going to the gym now. So, like a
nice breakfast. I'm not going today to
the gym, though, cuz um
cuz of um I can't be [ __ ] bothered,
mate. I can't be bothered.
I want to try and get this [ __ ] pregnant, bro.
But obviously, she's not going to keep the baby, you know.
She's not going to keep baby Peter, cactus.
But yeah, I had some breakfast earlier,
bro. You want to see it? I put the video
up if you want.
[ __ ] I can't believe I ate six slices
of bacon. [ __ ] yeah.
cuz I could go to Weather Spoons, but if
you go to this one, you can pick how
much you want. So, it just made more sense.
I ate a [ __ ] lot, mate.
The [ __ ] lot. Yeah.
So, I don't know, man.
But yeah, I am [ __ ] horny, bro. So,
Don't know why people don't like sucking Willie.
This morning was the same as well.
What the [ __ ] man?
You don't know why they don't like
[ __ ] Willie, bro.
But yeah, I'm horny. I need to try and
get this [ __ ] round to there.
Should I come in her or should I come in
her mouth? I think coming in her mouth is better
to be honest. I want to get her before
she turns into a proper [ __ ] and I can't
deal with her ever again. I think in the
mouth is better because they actually
swallow your babies.
You don't know what I said to my friend yesterday,
Cactus. I said, "I'm really, really
tired. Can you come around and rub my
feet and give me huggles and and rub my
hair?" She didn't reply. Of course, she
didn't reply. Like, nothing sexual. Just
like foot rubs. Just like a massage,
mate. Like, no sexual [ __ ] Nothing, bro.
Just like a massage or something, bro. I was [ __ ]
like give me hugs and something and give
me like hugs.
Oh, it's [ __ ] mate. I was not though
in it. Yeah, I said I need some loving.
I'm [ __ ] over here.
Yeah, I'm [ __ ] over here, lad.
No, I was [ __ ] You know how tired I
was? You know what I've been doing the
past couple of [ __ ] days, mate? I was
so tired people thought I was drunk.
Man, I was [ __ ] mate. I just said to
her, "Can you just rub my Can you just
come and give me rub rubs?"
Yeah, I'm [ __ ] I'm constantly horny, bro. Constantly.
Let me try and get this [ __ ] around. Oh, man.
You remember that American that gave me
a [ __ ] in the alleyway cactus? It's
not even about sex. You can't even find
anyone. Just to
I actually wanted to like spend time
more time with this Italian and see
where it went.
I don't really I'm not really asked
about sex when it's to do with someone
that you can spend a long time with. But
it doesn't matter. Again, all the dating
advice you you get is just backwards.
All the advice you get is backwards.
It's not like real life.
Did anyone ever tell you right when you
was a kid, oh, when you approach women,
they're just going to say they got
boyfriends? No. They made it out like
how dating life would have been solved
by [ __ ] approaching.
They said, oh yeah, once you approach,
and I used to think, cactus, when I was
younger, I used to think, oh yeah, like
once you speak to women, they're going
to be like, oh, like someone's going to
give you a chance, right? You know,
you've done you did a brave thing. Cuz
dating apps are bad for your mental
health. You see, like then they're not
good. So, okay. Well, once we we we can
grow a pair of balls and speak to to
women, maybe they'll give us a chance.
Nah. No. And yeah, the friendship as
well. That Pakistan girl, we she said
that she was going to be friends
talking. Don't even hear from her
anymore. And I wasn't weird on that
date. Didn't tried to kiss her. So, I
know how I've acted with I've acted
differently with different people
and it's still the same result. So,
you can't even get a convo or friendship.
Even a friendship, even if you just
wanted some friends that were women, you
you still wouldn't be able to find it.
It's not about sex or relationship. You
can't get anything with them. They're NPCs.
That's why they all copy each other.
They have the same attitude,
the same make believe [ __ ] They say
the same [ __ ] It's just the same, bro.
So, I'll go out. Maybe I'll go out
Saturday. Can't go out today. I'm too tired.
The Italian one was my favorite. You
know, I tried so hard to get her to meet
me again. Like, she just won't have
enough none of it.
Sucks dick, bro. It does suck dick.
But I don't stay attached to people now
because I know what happens. They've
been doing this for years, mate. Years. Yeah.
You even see, you know, the mad thing
with this is even when you watch horror
films. Yeah. You can't, you see sex scenes then
and it ain't real life. Like that stuff
doesn't happen in real life. And you
still see sex scenes then.
So yeah, you still see sex scenes then, mate.
No, I just think they're [ __ ]
I just think they're just westernized
stuck up [ __ ]
That's what I think. But yeah. Yeah, man.
I liked holding that Italian one's hand
and rubbing her fingers, man. She had pink nails
lester square holding hands. Cactus, I
was going to record it, but I didn't.
Yeah, I was going to record it, but I didn't. Yeah.
And your life mission is to keep mocking me. Yeah.
And your yours is to mock me, mate.
Is it mad how I'm so ugly, but I've had
better looking women than virgin boy.
But I'm so ugly. I've got a big nose. I'm balding.
I've had more women than that virgin.
Mook women that virgin. Oh,
I don't know all women, do I? Cactus. I Yeah.
Yeah. I think with her I'm going to
I'm going to get a [ __ ] and then
probably [ __ ] her after the [ __ ]
See, you need a [ __ ] before even
[ __ ] it. Gets you in the mood, you know.
So it it even it gets you in the mood.
yeah, you can't pull nothing, mate.
That's why he's so salty. That's why
he's he's stuck on my ex. Yeah, [Music]
it's a [ __ ] position to be in though, is it?
It is a [ __ ] position to be in,
especially in the summer.
Especially in the summer.
It is [ __ ] in it.
What do you think the solution is, Cactus?
There's just no point even trying anymore.
No point even trying anymore.
Yeah. I feel like I get depressed in the
summer. Me, I feel like the best, you
know, my favorite month is March. It's
not too hot. It's not too cold.
But you just get so depressed in the summer.
I was actually thinking they're dead
people today. People that I know that
are dead. I almost just started crying
randomly whilst eating [ __ ] food. I
really get bad depression in the summer, you know.
It was weird, bro. Purple weird.
And you can't even date either.
You can't even date. That's the thing, Cactus.
It's a shame about the [ __ ] Italian, man.
It's such a shame, eh?
Sad, bro. Bro, sad.
Sad, sad, sad. Oh,
I'm not. It wasn't him, bro. I'm not
talking about it.
It's not even him. No, I wasn't. And
it's not even him. I get the bad this
bad depression in summer, bro. I don't
know what it is.
Well, it's got worse cuz I haven't had
much sleep. So, bad sleep makes it
worse. Of course, I haven't been
sleeping properly. So, I've been doing
stuff the past few days. It's the first
time I've actually just sat down.
But, no, I wasn't close to him and he
wasn't even my real brother and I don't
really care about him either.
I'll never be going to another funeral
again in my life. When I sat down, I was
thinking to myself, I will never go cuz
my uh the other day, my mom wasn't
replying. Uh, another thing, Cactus, you
can't even go out in peace. So, when I
went out last Saturday, my card stopped
working, so I had to use another card. I
never had much money on it. My [ __ ]
sister's boyfriend was trying to involve
me in their [ __ ] And then on top of
that, I didn't hear from my mom since
255, and I was like, "Oh [ __ ] I hope
she's all right." So, I went back I had
2 hours sleep and I got the first train
back. I got the first train to a house.
So I couldn't even enjoy it properly
when I was out Saturday. It's always
something. That's why I used to stop
going out cuz I used to think that every
week it would be something
and I oh like hope she's not dead. You
know the last the last message she sent
me was quite worrying
cuz if she dies I'm not going to a
funeral. I'm never going to another
funeral again. I can't do it. I don't
like funerals and I will never go to a
funeral ever again in my life. I
wouldn't expect anyone to ever go to any
of mine either. Just to mine if I die.
So when I die. So
I just don't like him.
They're just scary, mate.
And that's the thing. Yeah. They used to
do it as well. Like when I went to
Amsterdam, that's why I used to stop going out.
It's like getting a dog. That's the
thing that scares me about getting a dog
is like I don't I would want to die
before the dog or die with the dog so I
don't have to deal with a dog's death or
even like a child. Like I wouldn't I
don't want to I wouldn't want to deal
with their death. So I'd rather die with
them. You know what I'm saying?
Cuz I'm never going to a funeral ever
again, bro. seeing a coffin and seeing a
body in a coffin.
Like where I live, you see loads of like
people in coffins being walked and
stuff. And I just don't like it.
So I was like, "Oh, if she dies, I'll
have no parents left now." But luckily,
she's still alive and well. So yeah.
But I'll never go to another funeral ever again.
Used to go out every Saturday. You used
to get called back.
What a buzz kill, mate. What a [ __ ] buzz kill.
What a [ __ ] buzz kill, matey. Yeah.
Nah, I got my sisters.
I saw my sister yesterday,
but I'll be all right anyways. I'm I'm
used to being by myself anyways. I'm quite independent.
You can't even meet a woman, so you
won't have a woman.
long term because you can't even meet
one that's serious that doesn't play games. So yeah,
is she coming today or what, mate?
I need some [ __ ]
I need some I need some loving, bro. So
yeah, it's not a London thing. It's a
It's an England thing. It's an American
thing. It's a France thing. It's all Westernized things.
So why do you think no one tells you
this stuff on Reddit anyways?
Yeah, she is being a proper proper [ __ ]
but she always comes running back to Peter Belly.
She always comes running back to Peter Belly
cuz Peter Belly had loads of cash. Not
anymore, but still have money, but not
as much as I used to have. Who does?
They're still like decent, but uh
uh so when you're used to knowing that
at a young age,
I don't pay her.
I go out for drinks. I don't pay her.
I don't pay her at all. We go out for
drinks and [ __ ] and get food, but I
don't pay her. So,
but hopefully when I wake up I feel
better. Bro, I'm [ __ ] I feel like [ __ ] bro.
See, did people on Reddit say
People on Reddit say you'll meet
someone, but you never do.
And the whole dating thing just [ __ ]
with your head. See, people don't
understand it. They think it's like, "Oh, yeah.
You keep trying. You keep trying.
And it's just the same old [ __ ]
every [ __ ] time.
Sorry, bro. It's the same. It's the same
[ __ ] like every time.
It It's the same rubbish every time, bro. It's [ __ ]
Joe. When when when would it actually change, man?
Nothing ever changes.
It's It's been going on for years now,
man. Like, all jokes aside, it's been
going on for [ __ ] years.
It's like the NPC reply is, "I have a
boyfriend." So, why does no one on
Reddit say that? Like listen, you're
probably not going to meet a woman in
this country. Most are just not
interested because and so when you try,
you're trying at your own risk. Why did
no one ever tell me that
factors? Why did no one ever tell me that?
But it's not it's not the it's not even
the boyfriend [ __ ] to be honest. It's
the whole that when I went on that date
last week and then the the the the
person I approached from the by the
shop, I was like, "Shit, this really
ain't going to change, is it?"
How would they know that? Because well,
how would they know that women like
confidence and all of this [ __ ] Cuz
everything that they write is [ __ ]
So if they don't know things, why they
why are they given wrong advice?
They seem to make it, oh yeah, you work on yourself
and then you go out and then you'll find
a woman. That's any advice they will
give you is that.
So if they don't know, then why are they
giving wrong advice, you know?
I wonder who started these conspiracy
rumors. I'm so interested and like I'm You know,
Antman said, Cactus Ant-Man said, "The
only place you're not going to get I've
got a boyfriend is Asia."
Yeah. Well, that's true. Yeah. Exactly.
Yeah. Cuz if you go out in real life,
you you will see how it's really like.
It's like these people on YouTube, they
want to say, "Oh, it's you." But they
don't know anything because they don't
leave the house. And the dating game has
changed in the past 15, 20 years. So
what the [ __ ] would they know? You know
what I'm saying? Like it's it's it's
that it's that it's that [ __ ] simple. So
it's just depressing, bro.
That's all it is. It's just really depressing.
No, you go Philippines. Philippines is for relationships. Philippines?
There's relationships. But I don't know.
I'm just sick of dealing with these time wasters. Len, bro.
I approach them in a tracksuit.
No, there is no there is no how they are
successful and learn because and one
second this Italian. Yeah, I actually
approached her in a track suit. But
listen, there's no there's no successful
and learn because it's it's very much to
do with your race as well because I know
some guy who who goes he he he's in the
army, right? and we're about the same
looks right wise six seven whatever and
he's got tattoo right he seems to do
really good on these dating apps and I
can't even get matches so I'm thinking
he looks like you know how them tanned
Australian people uh live you know how
them tanned Australian people are right um
he looks very white and I'm thinking no
this isn't right how so I said to him
it's got to be a racist issue It has to
be cuz as much as people try to say you
look fully white, I don't. Fully white
is blonde, blue eyes, it it it literally
has to be that. Which is good. I'm happy
for him that he gets like all of this,
you know, matches and stuff, but I'm
thinking like we should both be getting
it, but he gets it. So, it's very much
to do with race, luck. So that's why
they can't give no advice because it's
like say an Indian person, right,
wants advice on how to get white women
and you got some [ __ ] good-looking
guy who's blonde blonde
and [ __ ] blue eyes,
right? You can't give advice cuz no
one's going to go for a [ __ ] Indian
person who's 5' [ __ ] six. So that
that's why you can't give advice. There
is no learning. And you're either lucky
or you're not. And if you're the wrong
race, then boy, you're [ __ ] So
simple. So, no, you can be decent
looking. You can wear good clothes. All
I've ever worn was good clothes, and you
still get the same [ __ ]
But it's definitely
definitely his race, even if it's 60% of it.
This guy's like scrawny as well, like
he's in the army and that. And uh but he
obviously looks fully white. So
it is [ __ ] strange, bro, how like he
seems to get these matches, but I don't
get really any matches when I used to
use them. I think it's just race.
Got to be race. It's got to be, man. Cuz
I done this I done this cuz I done this
experiment to say I done I done this
experiment before, you know, with uh
some other guy. And I'm thinking, what
the [ __ ] We're like the same looks
range, whatever it is, looks range it
is. And they seem to do a lot better
just for the simple fact they've got
blue eyes and they're [ __ ] white. But
I don't look I don't look like a
foreigner that's just come out off the
boat at all, mate. I groomed very good.
Yep. I wear Dior Savage. I was wearing
it yesterday actually when I went to my
mom's. But yeah, I wear the Savage. It
cost me £140. It doesn't make no difference.
It literally makes no difference
whatsoever what you wear, what you do.
There's just no
there there's nothing. I always wear
nice after save. I can't go out without
wear after shave. [ __ ] £140 it cost
me that after save. Ah, [ __ ]
But even still, like so that's what it
is. It it that is literally what it is
cuz I'm thinking this guy is not you know
m so it's got to be it's got to be your race
especially with dating apps cuz you're
not ugly you're decent looking. Why the
[ __ ] are you not getting any success or
very limited success? And then you need
to think of wait who are most of the
people that you went on dates with?
They were Italian. Well, I've never been
on a date with Italian before except
that one. Mexican, Italian, obviously
that 19year-old, but she was like
younger. They've all been sort of mixed
and very rarely have they not been
mixed. So, that should tell you all you
need to know as well. You've never
really been on a date with a full
English woman that's completely white
except the 19-year-old. Yeah, you had
the Australian, USA. He wasn't fully
white. the Italian, the other Italian.
So, it's got to be your race. There
there's nothing else it can lead to.
But it's not the wor It's not the worst
race. Like, we're not the worst race. If
you're like Indian or something,
but yeah, if I wear tracksuits, it makes
it better. Yeah. But the problem is
I don't want an English woman. They're
[ __ ] stinking. Why would I want to be
on a date with a [ __ ] stinky English
woman? I don't even like English women.
Are you [ __ ] mad? But yeah, I you do
better in a track suit, Stephanie. Oh,
an Albanian as well. I was on a date
with an Albanian. Yeah, but she was only
one. Most of them have been Albanian,
Italian, Syrian. Yeah, the tracksuit
makes it better. But when you don't, but
you can't get into the clubs with a
tracksuit, so you have to go in really
early. But I mean that's how I got
that's how I got there tally and I wore a tracksuit.
The black tracksuit is the black
tracksuit as well. Um but most of I
wouldn't want to be with women. Bro I
don't like English women. Are you mad?
If I could choose I would pick either
Indian, Turkish or Albanian or Italian.
I would [ __ ] English women are the
worst, bro. Their whole attitude. I
mean, they're all [ __ ] but [ __ ]
English women. I I consider myself
[ __ ] lucky. I want to [ __ ] be on a
date with an English woman. I had a I
had a I had a one night stand with an
English woman after Sig. It was the same
It was the same week I [ __ ] Sig.
So, I'd choose Indian. If I if I could
pick any, I'd [ __ ] I'd probably pick Indian B.
They never say they've got boyfriends.
Indians say they never say it. I've
approached loads of Indians, bro. They
never say it.
Then you can read between the [ __ ] lines here.
And then the French ones just [ __ ]
troll you. The French ones just troll
the [ __ ] out of you every time.
That's another thing I should have done
to start targeting my own race, which is
something I've been meaning to do, but I
just never really did it.
So, yeah, you need to go for Yeah. Indian, Albanian,
something like that. They're they're the
best ones. They're not [ __ ] English.
She wants a [ __ ] English woman. Yeah, [ __ ] that. You mad?
All [ __ ] entitled [ __ ] They're just
as bad as Americans.
So, what was the USA Izzy thinking when
I um approached her, Cactus?
She wanted a dick there and there, didn't it?
Yeah. And they're not our boyfriends. So
then they're not going to date me, are they? Yeah.
[ __ ] off, mate. [ __ ] off.
You're having a [ __ ] laugh, aren't you, mate?
You're having a laugh.
So, what would um Virgin Boy do if I had
a baby with like this Italian or something?
Yeah. And we we need to be taught at a
young at a young age not to go for them
stuck up entitled Westernized [ __ ] I
think we'll start learning how we need
to learn to stay away from them entitled
[ __ ] scumbag [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm going to start teaching little
kids this, mate. My [ __ ] nephew and
[ __ ] Yeah, I'll teach my nephew it.
Stay away from these [ __ ] westernized
English stuckup [ __ ] Yeah,
but I think uh the person on Reddit was
right. There's too many stuckup [ __ ]
in your country.
They said there's too many stuck up
[ __ ] in your weird country. Maybe.
Duh. They are [ __ ] stuck up.
They are stuck up [ __ ]
Other guys do it. Do you remember
cactus? Other guys do it. But then when
I retaliate to him, he doesn't like it.
So why start on me every Saturday when
you've had a drink if you can't take it back?
If you can't [ __ ] take it back, go in.
Other guys do it.
But he doesn't like it when people say
that to him. Is it? Yeah.
Oh, my little nestles.
Can you see? Look, my eyes look less tired now.
My beard's got really long again. Don't
know what's happening here.
Oh, man. I've got this nice tan in it.
Hello, bro. It's coming. It's coming.
Even if it takes two days, it's coming,
bro. I'm just sat in front of the fan
having a little chill out.
Having a little chill out, mate. Yeah,
I want this [ __ ] to come around, bro.
So I can ram her.
I was going to I'm going to do it. I'm
going to end up doing it. It's just I I
normally go to that web spoon. Everyone
knows me. I'm going to be like other
guys are doing it. And man, look. Yeah,
cuz he's [ __ ] pissing me off with that, bro.
other guys that are [ __ ] fully white
that have met people through [ __ ]
work that have met people through [ __ ]
other circumstances, bro. Like, [ __ ] me.
But I know he's just trolling. I know
he's just trying to He's just trying to
get a reaction. I said, "You're not
going to bait me, bro. I know what
you're trying to do.
I know what you're trying to do, mate." Yeah.
I remember one day. Yeah. Cactus. I was
staying at my friends. Yeah.
And these women were pissing me off. I
came back, bro. I smashed the mug and I
pissed all over the kitchen floor in it.
And then they wondered what happened. I
was like, "Oh, did you have an
accident?" I said, "Oh, yeah. I slipped,
pissed all over the floor, kitchen
floor, smashed the mug up and
everything. I had to get a new mug.
Other guys do it.
Oh my gosh. Yeah. Mhm.
You like that, Grezy?
Yeah. I pissed all over the [ __ ] kitchen floor.
You like that, don't you, Grezy?
That's our little secret, Grezy.
Now my favorite is he got boyfriend.
I said, "Calm down, ad man. You're going
to catch a case." You remember Greasy? I
was like, "Oh, how's it going, man?" Cuz
it used to be he would go out one week,
then I'd go out the next week and we'd
sort of take it in turns.
I said, "How's it going?" And he said,
"Ah, they've all got boyfriends."
I was laughing, bro. I was laughing. Yeah.
It bors me, mate. Bors me. This country
bors me, bro. Yeah.
Oh, did you like that?
Oh, bro, I'm so horny, man. I want to
have a wank, but I'm saving all the
sperm for her if she comes today or tomorrow.
Well, you'll be seeing it next week, mate. Yeah.
Remember, they only reply to negative messages, Joe.
They only reply to negative messages. Yeah.
I said to I said to ad man, "What if the
neighbors come on the door?" He said,
"Oh, mate." He said, "I'm not here for a
fighting that is it." Yeah.
I said, "What if the neighbors come on
the door?" A big angry mob. Imagine
that. An angry mob catch up on the door.
H. He said, "How can you even find that funny?"
I was playing with my Willie yesterday,
Joe, before I went to sleep.
I was just playing with it.
Is that cute? Yeah.
Playing with my little Willie. Yeah,
playing with my little Pekka. I was
thinking of some things. I just I don't
even watch Paul and me. I just used the Wank Bank. Nope.
I had the Italian one.
I had the uh where I fingered somebody
in a club. The one that gave me a
[ __ ] in the alleyway. Sometimes I
think of that.
Yeah. I just think of that to be honest
cuz you have to hold on to their
memories, cactus, because they never
happen again, do they? No.
That's what That's the three things I
was thinking of.
I don't even watch porn.
You remember old man porn, Cactus?
Do you remember Ogie? Old man.
Yeah, I was horny, man.
That's the best [ __ ] I ever got was
in the alleyway.
I can still remember it to this day.
Yeah, I really want you, but I don't
think you want me. Bless you.
Oh, Grezy, bless you. Yeah,
there's a new horror film coming out next month.
Sometimes I think of Sig.
Just depends, you know.
I just drank over experiences that I've had. Yeah.
I remember Antman said, "Fuck it. I
should have just [ __ ] raped her."
That's what Antman said. He said he said
I should have [ __ ] raped her instead of approaching.
Do you remember cactus? Yeah.
He was like, "Yeah, that's what he was
saying through this [ __ ] frame, sir."
It's the way he said it. It's not funny.
It's not funny, but it's the way he said it. Yep. Uh
what me and USA had USA Izzy had was special
and you remember when I kept betting on
the number 25 cactus and then it kept it
kept coming in.
Yeah. I remember my birthday I kept
betting on 25 and it kept coming in. Yeah.
Yeah. I remember being I remember me and
Adman was a naughty game. It was funny.
I don't care about the ass. I just care
about the boobs
and the mouth to give me a [ __ ]
That's all I care about. Nothing else, you know.
Yeah. It's funny, is it? cactus. Yeah. Not again. Ah, that's
Yeah. When I was on when I was with this
Pakistan girl, I felt something in my to
cuz all the people I meet, they're never
like fat and ugly like Virgin Boy, you
know? They're always like decent looking 6.57s. Yeah,
I don't think I had it with the Italian.
Maybe. I don't know.
Do you remember the sh was attractive? Cactus
copying. That is so copying.
I don't like copycats.
I don't like people that copy each other.
I try to live life, mate. I was by
cycling around the past two days,
but uh I cycled all around London, different places.
I didn't go north. It was just south.
Yeah. Literally, she's not even she's
not even good-looking.
She's not even good looking. Like I
would say that Italian one is way better than her.
Yeah. Not for much longer.
Yeah, that Italian one is uh
she's way better.
But it's like me. I wouldn't say that
you're gay if you don't find her
attractive. That's just copying. Cuz if
you go on any student room form and he's
like, "Oh, you're the one that brought
her up." Yes, I brought her up because
people kept copying each other.
And when we were friends, I I wanted to
know what your opinion on her was
or I can't remember how it come up into
conversation. You are copying. It's just
like if somebody said that this Italian
wasn't attractive, then they don't find
her attractive. Is it? Some people don't
find some of the people I've been with
attractive attractive. Literally every
single most of the people I met has been
better than her. [ __ ] copying.
What if you only like black women? What
if you only like mixed race women? Copycat.
[ __ ] copycat, mate.
See, me and my friend, we we've got
different types of women that we like.
I just like Indian ones with like big boobs and [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, also I remember it. years old.
That Brazilian escort gave me the best
[ __ ] man. I think I'm going to have
to travel to her, you know.
You said you almost choked me to death.
That's what you call living life, is it? Yeah.
That's what you call living life, matey.
It ain't happened.
No, no, no.
Escorts never block you, Joe. Never.
I got some numbers I can message in a
couple of months. See if
they want to meet up. Yeah.
I feel like I've got so many numbers. Yeah. If like
this might sound weird to you, but I was
thinking like hitting the gym and that Yeah.
just getting mad ripped and then two
months later just message them all again
and say, "Oh, do you want to meet up?"
No, no, no. And I feel like cuz you've
got so many,
right? I mean, like say about six, seven
ones you and then if they don't meet
you, I think you should just give up
forever. That's enough women right there.
And if they're not going to say yeah,
then no one's going to say yeah. I'm
kind of thinking of stuff like that, you know?
months later. You know, you know how it is.
People are weird. You know, [Music]
Yeah. I used to do that, you know.
I used to like do, do you know what I
used to do? I used to get like three
grand cash, two grand cash. I used to
say, "Look how much money I've saved not
going out in XY Z amount of time."
And it still never worked. It still
made it make it to try and make it seem
like, oh, I got loads and loads of money that
but never works. So, so yeah.
What is this coming out of my account? One second.
One second, bro. Okay. 450.
Breathe. One second.
I'll be back later. Yeah.