kind of data, man.
Give it a
good channel got
band. So I'm on this one.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] madness, bro. It's crazy as madness. Yeah,
bro. [ __ ] hell. Did you see that?
Jeez. I don't I don't know if he rigs it, but
[ __ ] he only puts up
wins. Well, he only puts up wins,
but I got two features actually. They
were both [ __ ] and I I had a fight with
a guy in the shop as well. Well, I tell
you what happened. Ah, bro, it was a
madness. I could have got killed killed
on it. And that's why people you don't
gamble cuz it ruins everything. And it's
not about the money. £200 is nothing to
me, mate. I'm going out tomorrow and I'm
sending it. Yeah, but it's the
principle. My channel, real channel,
stop and step, fake channel. Understand?
He what he probably does, he probably
records it and he does a few hundred
pounds until he actually wins. That's
probably what the [ __ ] does. He
doesn't show he doesn't show real wins.
Like, bro, it's not real. You don't
understand? So, yeah.
madness. Yeah, he never loses, eh? Even
when he goes to the arcades, which the
payout percentage is even lower there,
but he never ever loses. He never loses,
man. Isn't it? I mentioned him in my
video. I think that's about the 11th
session or 12th
session. Yeah, it was a madness, bro.
[ __ ] this guy. Yeah.
Well, it seems like the only loser is
you, buddy, because you keep making fake
accounts to get blocked. So, I guess the
only loser is you. No one else. I'm not
entertaining these weirdos. Anyways, um
uh where have I been having a life?
That's where I've been having a life.
And where have I been today? I lost 200
pound on a FOB. And this guy, I said to
him, "Oh, your machines are upsetting
me." No, no, no, no, no, no, no. And he
he said, "Oh, he's going to do this to
me. He's going to do that to And I said,
"Bro, why don't you come after work?" I
gave him my address as well. He was
being all mad and that and he comes out
with a pole. I says, "Come and hit me
with it then." I said, "Go in then, bad
man. Hit me with your pole. Hit me with
your [ __ ] pole." Yeah. I was like,
"Bro, there's cameras in everywhere. Come
literally. Bye-bye. Um, come literally
after work where there's no cameras and
you're not coming out this house."
That's what I said to him. [ __ ] [ __ ]
old man. It was a madness. And I didn't
I didn't even insult him. I didn't even
insult him. I swear to God I didn't even
swear him insult him. I was like, "Mate,
you don't scare no one." I said, "Give
me your address. If you don't come to my
address, I'm putting your windows
through." It was like It was like a I
don't know what it was like a plastic
pole. It was something. It wasn't a
hammer. It was like a plastic
pole. So yeah. And I said, "If you don't
come, give me your address. I'll put
your [ __ ] windows through." That's
what I said to him, bro.
So yeah, it was a madness. So that was
all from gambling as well. Ruined the
whole day. Yep. Can always count on
gambling to to ruin the day, I'd say.
And I could have got nicked as well. It
was on a high road. Everyone
looked luckily £200. Nothing to me in
it. It was actually Well, actually, I
lost £300 actually. I put Well, 280. I
put 80 pound on the roulette, but oh
well. It's a gambling channel. I didn't
I didn't put that. Yep. 200 pound just
like that. And I've got to get passport
sorted tomorrow. And I've got to go out
and send it. I got this Scottish woman
last week. Oh my god. I went out by
myself, bro. Was pulling all
sorts. So yeah, I'm going to go out
again tomorrow. Send it. I got to get
passport sorted. [ __ ] That's annoying.
But I'll do it. It's fine.
Yeah. Yeah. It sucks, bro.
Um the other the last 80 was on
roulette. Yep. The last 80 was on
roulette. But I don't really come on
here anymore cuz these little weirdos.
But I did put like obviously I put the
gambling videos up.
Um so people think you lost 200 pound.
200 is nothing to me you know but you
know as mad as that sounds bro.
So yeah, exactly. I said to him, bro, I
told him I said I told him then I said
to him, I gave him my address. I said,
"Why don't you come after work, big
man?" And he said, "He sees me all the
time." No. 280 down. I said, "He sees me
all the time." I said, "Come on, big
man." That's what I said. I said, "Why
don't you come Why don't you come after
work, big man, where there's no cameras
and give me your address? If you don't
come, I'm going to put your [ __ ]
windows through." Yeah. Yeah. But the
pictures are not going to give me that
address. I said, "You don't scare me.
You don't intimidate me at all,
bro. Bye-bye. You can go self-reflect on
another channel. Yeah, bro. This is for
like the genuine people that actually
want to watch G videos. All the [ __ ]
self-p projectors, I'm not going to
entertain them. So, if you see people
getting blocked, you understand what it
is. I told him, "Why don't you give me
your address, big man? Stop doing this
stuff on camera." When you know that,
bro, all you're on camera, I'm on
camera, you know?
Yeah, it's a
madness. You won't you won't be phoning
the bookies because you don't know what
bookies it is and you don't know where
it is. So, good luck with that, buddy. You little
weirdo. No, obviously it wasn't him. It was someone
else. He That's the problem. He can't
stop. He can't stop losing the
self-reflectors. Sorry, any any genuine
person who's watching this. Um, you
know, um, you do get spastics on it.
This is why nobody come on here anymore.
Um yeah, meeting that Scottish woman
last week, it makes me want to um want
to visit Scotland
again. No, it was someone else, bro. But
it's it's so mad how like if I didn't
gamble today, I wouldn't have been made
to feel like that and that never and
that would have not happened. This is all from gambling.
Yeah. I don't I don't know, bro. I don't
really care. We're not mentioning them
people on my channel and anyone that
brings weird drama on my channel is getting themselves
blocked. Yeah. So, you can't win, bro.
Like, you show the real side of gambling
and people hate on it. People hate on
it, bro. People hate on it. It's a
madness. You know, they hate on a on a
on a real gambling channel. They should
like it. It shows losses and well, wins
when you win. You know what I'm saying?
So, but they they'd rather hate on a on
on a legit gambling channel. It's [ __ ] up, you
know. You know, it is actually
mad. Yeah, I know. No, I haven't gambled
for a while. I just thought I tried £200
and then 200 turned into 80, but that is
me done for a month 100. But that's me
done forever. I need to really stop
this, bro. It's no good for your moods.
I could have got killed today or nicked.
It was mad. It was bad, bro. I was going
to let him [ __ ] intimidate me. I was
like, "You don't [ __ ] intimidate me."
You know, and I won't even cussing him.
Him, his religion, nothing. And he
started on it. And And he started
madness, bro. Like, for no reason. And
he said, "I'm going to give you my
address. Write it down. I'm going to
write it down for you, big man." Yeah. I
mean, you can come anytime you
want. So, I know. I don't understand why
they take the piss out of somebody that
puts losers up. But it's not good, bro.
It's not I was supposed to get my head
done in that today, but I just wanted to come back
home. It's sad, isn't it?
But it's the way it is,
eh? No, I'm not scared of them, bro. I
don't care if they know people. I don't
care, bro. I don't
care, you know? I don't care who the
[ __ ] they know, bro. Let them know who
they want to know. I don't give a [ __ ]
I don't care, bro. I've got a metal hammer. So,
yeah. I was going to go back with a
metal hammer, but my friends, leave it,
leave it, leave it, you know. So, the
guy he got, bro, he got owned any hit me
with a pole. Go on, go on. What are you
going to do? That's what I said. And it
was for no reason as well. I wasn't
cussing him. I wasn't insulting him. I
was telling him about these [ __ ]
machines. Uh-huh. Yeah. He's a [ __ ]
bro. He knows, right? It's one of them
bookies where there's loads of police
outside. He's a [ __ ] Oh, why do you
think he wants to do everything on
camera? I said, "Take it away from the
camera." He says, "Oh, I see you
sometimes." I said, "Do you see me? Why
don't you come and do something when you
see me again then?" Why does he want to
do stuff on camera when he knows there's
police outside so he can say, "Oh, he
was racist." Oh, that's what he wants to
do. He's a [ __ ] If he was a real man,
if he was a real gangster.
Yeah. He would literally come on your
door away from these cameras.
Yeah. It's like that uh police officer
with the whole uh Sean thing when he's
like wind your neck and I said why don't
you wind your [ __ ] neck and you pig.
You know that's what I said to him. I
said you're not going to be saying that
if you weren't wearing that silly little
uniform behind a desk where there's
loads of police. Keep your mouth shut.
Anyone that's really about anything
would actually come on someone's door
where there's no cameras and that's it.
So no one can sit on anyone, you
know? Remember him as well? He's been
saying that same [ __ ] for like 10 years,
bro. I told him about himself when I was
17 as well. I said, "You wind your
[ __ ] nick." You know, [ __ ] shitty
[ __ ] Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] if they
nicked me for it. I don't give a [ __ ]
Do you think I'm bothered? What are they
going to do? put you in prison because
you told him to whine his neck in the
[ __ ] eating [ __ ] Yeah, you're going to
get arrested and what? Go to jail for
saying that? I don't think so, man. I
don't give a
[ __ ] So, yeah. Yeah, you're not going
to get arrested for saying that. Well, I
was already arrested. I was actually
already arrested. It was actually the
sergeant. So, I mean, what they going to
do? Put you in prison for calling him a [ __ ] eatating
[ __ ] So, yeah.
But yeah, doesn't change, I think. Yeah,
I was already arrested anyways. So, I already got
arrested. And the other ones were cool
as well. He was just being a dick. He
done it 10 years ago as well. I told him
about himself 10 years ago as well.
[ __ ] [ __ ] eating
[ __ ] Cuz that's what pigs do. They eat
[ __ ] you know? They're despised by
whole [ __ ] religion, mate. It goes to
show that no one likes peace. But yeah,
that guy is a bounty, man, bro.
But you just know he would be the first
one to run to police saying, "Oh, I was
defending myself. Oh, he was racist. Oh,
you know what they're like, bro. That's
why he wants to do everything on
camera." [ __ ] [ __ ] Oh, well.
But that's the thing, man. Is
it? Um, I don't give my life away on
here, Joe. I don't give my life away on
here, lad. You're not going to see me
send it. I've actually got a video of me
with a woman um from last week. I got a
few women last week, but nah, I'm not
going to put it up, bro. I can't be [ __ ]
It's the madness though. We need to
learn from this gambling. Why does it
feel like we never learn? It's so
embarrassing. Oh my god, it is so
embarrassing. And it's not about losing
200, 280 quid, mate, cuz I'll give5600
away for no [ __ ] reason. And I
wouldn't care. I won't even be an
aggressive to that guy. And then he
thinks he's going to try and Oh, I don't
care, mate. Yeah. I don't give a [ __ ]
what you are, mate. Or who you [ __ ]
know, [ __ ] Yeah, cuz you don't know who I know
either, you know. I'm not going to let
him [ __ ] intimidate me. There's no
one that's going to intimidate me, brother. You
mad, you know? But that's all from
gambling basically cuz if you didn't
gamble, that wouldn't happen. But it's
just gambling. I was playing Deluxe
Roulette. Deluxe Roulette in the arcade.
I was 80 pound down on
that. It's so mad, isn't it? It's so
[ __ ] mad, bro. It's so mad.
We need to learn, bro.
[ __ ] Going to drive you insane. This is, you
know, but I don't really make
plans. But yeah, it's nice to see people
still obsessed with
me, you know.
I seen Monty went he left cuz they found his
address. That was kind of funny, bro.
I'm not going to
lie. Oh, 280 300 gun like that. [ __ ] hell. That's
mad. It's actually stickling,
bro. I thought I was going to get a
bonus. I actually paid
It's time like that. You wish you just
gave 200 pound to someone or£300 to someone. You
know, you really need to stop going in
them places, bro. Cuz the day could have really
escalated. What if he hit you or what if
you hit him? You know, it's
mad. And the reason why you say, "Oh,
would you feel the same if you lost one
pound or two pound?" No, you wouldn't
feel the same if you lost one pound or
two pound because it's not enough money
to get involved in. You don't
understand. You need to gamble a big enough
amount. No, it's not even what you could
have done with
not No, it's just losing. It's just lo
Not necessarily. When it was two grand,
I was like, "Oh, I can do something with
two grand, 1100 pound, but not [ __ ]
200 quid." No, but it's just like you
could have gave your mom £200. I mean, 2002
28. I mean, I wouldn't really be
thinking, "Oh, I could have done
something with that." But if it's like
£1,100 or something, then obviously,
yeah, it's a it's losing any amount.
It's annoying losing any amount. And
it's because you're constantly
losing. Yep. Lucky money is no object, John.
object, you know. But that's not the
point, bro. You could have just gave
£300. I still got to get my passport sorted as well. [ __ ] sake. Oh
Yep. It's a madness,
lad. It is a [ __ ]
madness. Oh, wow.
I have more stuff to do tomorrow as
well. It doesn't matter what it would
have done. It doesn't matter what it
would have done. I can still do it. It's
It's No, no, no, no. It's not about£300
would have got your passport. I could
still do it. I'm still going to do it.
It's just annoying losing and having a bit less
now cuz I only have a certain Well, I'm
not going to get into my financial
circumstances. Whatever. you mind how
much I get. But yeah, no, it's not that
I can still do it. Obviously, I can
still [ __ ] do
it. But it's just not nice losing.
So, stop it, bro. Please stop the stop
the lame trolling. It's you. It's really
bad, bro. It's really, really bad. I
just go back and put one if I had a
certain amount. Bro, I'm not money man
or Timmy. Remember that every time
you're coming on here trying to troll,
just keep that in mind. I'm not Money
Man and I ain't
Timmy. I'm sure Joe knows that. Stop
talking stupidness. Stop talking nonsense.
Yeah [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] sake. And I need to
go back to my send it as
well. And I need to go back to M and
send it as well. [ __ ]
hell. Imagine that. And I've got to go
out tomorrow and send it.
Yeah, you you big me uploading losses,
but you just said I'd go back into one
if I had a certain amount. Are you
stupid? Only a stupid person would come
out with something like
that. That is [ __ ]
foolishness. No. Cut your losses and
move on with your life and don't do it
again, bro. That's what you should be
saying. Cuz the thing is before you do
it, Joe, you forget the last time how it
made you feel. This is the problem with
it. Yes, it's your choice to do it.
Doesn't matter if money is no object.
I'm not wasting my money. Simple.
Listen, Joe. Yeah, you. It is true that
nobody forces you to do it. Yes. No one
is saying people force you to do it, but
it's how it makes you feel
afterwards. And the guy in the B shop
was like, "Are you on drugs or
something?" Cuz I couldn't keep still.
I'm like moving like somebody that's got
Tourette's. You can't control how it
makes you feel afterwards. I've tried,
bro. I've tried. I just said call it 200
pound loss, whatever. I wouldn't care
about the money, but it still annoys
you. It still pisses you off. So, your
only option is to not do
it. Yeah, pretty much. Yeah. I just
wanted an adrenaline
rush. I just wanted an adrenaline rush to be
fair. Such a [ __ ] waste of money, is it?
bro. It actually is, isn't
it? So, I'll be sending it tomorrow. I
got a Scottish woman last week. It was
lush, mate. [ __ ]
lush. I touched her boobies and I was
kissing her, too. Oh, bro. I met this
woman, Joe. Oh, man. She was a [ __ ]
psychopath. She wouldn't [ __ ] off. She
kept stalking me after she got my
number. Oh my god, bro. Like, she was a
weirdo. Oh, [ __ ] me. She was a weirdo,
bro. I got like four numbers. She was a [ __ ] weirdo.
Yeah, she was a weirdo. You don't want
to do You want to know the story?
and she was a [ __ ] freak. So
basically I approached her and she was
40 and she has two kids. She didn't look
40. She was really really nice and was
talking holding hands. And then she said
that she's celibate and she's not had
sex for 13 years. So she's not
interested in sex. She's not interested
in relationships. And she said she's
religious. She was westernized. Muslim
westernized and she was religious and
she's like in order for her to get with
me or anyone they have to be Muslim. But
I was like you're drinking in a club
that's forbidden against your religion.
You can't be a religion and do one bad
thing. You can't do no bad thing. She
was [ __ ] eating. Like I was like you
can't it's forbidden. I've got Muslim
friends, you know, like and they don't
do none of that stuff. Not that I know
of, you know. I've I've I've seen you do
it. Right. So if you're looking for a
man who's a religious Muslim, you're not
going to find that in a club because
it's forbidden against your
religion. No, she didn't think I was
Muslim. No, I I said I don't agree with
the religion because I don't believe in
circumcision this, that, and the other.
I don't agree with it. Because I don't
agree with it. So I'm not I'm not going
to pretend I I I don't agree with the
religion. Similar like I don't care who
is Muslim. They they are who they are,
bro. I'm not [ __ ] racist.
But with with me, I would say alcohol is
one of the worst things you can do that
is forbidden. Like even eating pork is
not as bad as drinking alcohol. Alcohol
is bad, you know, bro. Like it's bad.
Trust me. You know, especially when you
overdo it. So you're Muslim. You're a
religious Muslim, but you drink alcohol.
Doesn't make any sense. And you want to
find a man. And then she was messaging
me and she was a [ __ ] freak,
man. And I was like, I'm not play. Yeah.
Playing hard to get. And she's 40 with
two kids. Yeah, you can play with some
other [ __ ] [ __ ] 40 and two kids. 40
years of age and she's got two
kids. She was nice, but she just turned
out to be a weirdo, mate.
Um, but yeah, it was fun. It was fun
nonetheless, but it was good, man.
But this Scottish woman, it makes me I
want I kind of So I was watching some
Glasgow videos yesterday and I was
thinking of Tam. Do you remember the guy
that got away though that I met last
year and I lost his number cuz obviously
my phone got stolen and he told me that
I needed help. And it's so mad to think
that if I if I if and when I ever go to
Glasgow, I will never see him again cuz
I lost his
contact. Yeah, maybe I need to go back
to Scotland. I was actually thinking of
going back. Well, I woke up today. I was
like, "Oh, should I just go Blackpool
and then Scotland after?" Because it's
both the Northwest, isn't it? I was
thinking of going Scotland and [ __ ]
Blackpool. Blackpool and Scotland.
Blackpool and then Scotland. But I don't know,
bro. Cuz uh they're not too too far from
each other. I just thought, "Ah, I can't be
bothered." But yeah, man. A 40year-old
with two [ __ ] kids playing hard to get. [ __ ]
me. I just got out to have fun now
drinking. Can't believe that. 280 quid,
man. [ __ ] you
now. That's crazy,
bro. How do we get in these situations?
The whole street was looking, Joe. The
Yeah. It's very hard to make money
nowadays, Joe. Very hard to make money.
I was looking up some cleaning jobs yesterday.
Oh, just arguing and that is in it. Like
people's looking in. I was arguing with guy.
Yeah. I was looking at some cleaning
jobs, Joe. Yeah. It's hard to make money nowadays,
mate. Cuz everything that you think of
doing it has some kind of catch to it.
Well, I've got some ideas to make money
in the summer, which I'm not going to
disclose cuz they're my Well, because
the guy said that he was he was cussing
me in the bookies. the the man in the
bookies. I told him, "Fuck off, man."
You know, I said, "Go and hit me with
that pole. Go on, big man. You're not intimidating me,
mate." But [ __ ] him anyways,
bro. I said, "Come to my address after
work. That's mad, is it?" But yeah, it's
very hard to make money nowadays, matey.
Very hard to make money nowadays, matey.
I've got some ideas in the summer. But
yeah, that delivery was [ __ ] man. I
used my friend's account for one day. It's too
hard. It's hard to make money nowadays.
Delayed. Yeah, it is hard to make money, bro.
Yeah, it's hard. There's not like you've
seen it yourself. There's not even money
in the gambling industry anymore. But
I'd say if you lost that 280 and you
only lose that for the month, you're
laughing, mate. If you only lost 280300
for the month and you don't do it again
even for a month, you're laughing, man.
You know, you're laughing. There's not
even no money in the [ __ ] industry
anymore. Oh, I was talking to one of the
casino managers that had a vendara
against me. We saw each other again and
we spoke. I said, "You always used to
stop me coming in, didn't you?" And he
was like, "Oh, like it it's cuz I knew
you was banned." I was like, "No, it
wasn't. You missed me. You used to hate
me ringing you [ __ ] every week." Like
it was friendly and that and we was
talking and that um kind of like a
reunion, you know, years later. Um, but
he told me there's some illegal
casinos. Um, yeah, a talented a
talentless loser like yourself. That's
why you stalk me every single day, Peter
Griffin. Cuz you ain't got a life. Yeah,
a bit like yourself, fat, ugly Peter
Griffin looking [ __ ] that stalks
me every day because you wish you were me. Anyways,
um, uh, was it? Yeah, he told he told me
that there's some illegal casinos in
London. So, you buy in for 200 and they
give you 300.
There's no money in the
industry, mate. Listen, I don't even get
mad at these people. I was going to say
anymore, but I've never got mad at these
people. I mean, look, Jamie Thompson,
Peter Griffin, fat ugly [ __ ]
And then look at Peter
belly. Where does the jealousy come
from, bro? You want to be me or
something? You sit online every day
stalking me. You're a sado. I live in
your head, bro. I can't get mad at that.
Why do you why do you sit online every
day and stalk me, bro? Like, what is
that all about? Like, are you jealous of
me or something? Like, what is
it? This is what I'm trying to say.
Yeah. You go and L channels that are PJ
lost 300 pound. Bro, do you not
understand that A, this is a legit gambling
channel? This is a legit gambling
channel. So, you're not going to see
[ __ ] on this channel. And a and b,
gambling's nothing to me losing
gambling. There's nothing. So, I don't
know why you laugh. Like, just cuz you
people are skin on benefits, not
everyone is the same as you people.
I must try to help people with Gro. [Music] Yeah.
Yeah, they're obsessed with me, bro.
They're obsessed with me. These people
are obsessed with me.
Delayed. I think they want to be me,
man. They want to be me,
bro. Severely want to be me, bro. I
swear. I put gambling content on this
channel to show the losses. It's not
anything to me losing is is what I'm
trying to explain over and over and over
again. It doesn't bother me. It doesn't
affect my living. Me losing. Do you not
understand? So, you should stop trying
to take the piss out of it. You
know, but they compare your financial
circumstances to their financial
circumstances cuz these people get £300
a month. You see, these people get £400
a month maximum. So losing 300 pound to
them is obviously a lot of
money. Know what I'm
saying? I don't care about putting losses up,
bro. You think I give a [ __ ] about
lockers up, bro? [ __ ]
me. You know what I'm saying, Fred? wasn't bothering [Music]
me. [ __ ] bro.
probably be live again later to be fair.
I got some stuff to do
tomorrow. Oh, Sunday morning I got some batches. Yeah.
blood of old Bill of
Bill. Load of old Bill. What's the fun
in a load of old
Bill? After today, I'll be [ __ ] off
again for another couple of weeks, mate. Yeah.
It's mad how I've got so many stalkers.
Like they literally just sit there and
wait for me to go
live. It's crazy, bro. It is mad. All right,
boss. Yeah, bro. I was just off this
[ __ ] bro. I couldn't be bothered with
these wankers. Greasy. I thought I'd
come back for a little bit. I'm going to
come off and go live later. Probably
only to get some Chinese food I'm
staring. So, yeah. Just thought I put a
fish and frenzy video up for all of you
[ __ ] And that's me,
bro. Yeah, it's a madness,
man. It is a
madness. I'll be I got a Scottish woman
last week, Greavvesy. It made me think of you.
I was touching her boobies and kissing
her. Is that okay with you,
bossy? Is that okay with you,
boss? Yeah, I'll go live tomorrow at the
nightclub. I'll go live in the club.
Yeah, I'll go live in the old [Music]
clubby. Yeah, I'll do it for you, buddy.
Yeah, I lost £280 today
gambling. 280 [ __ ]
quid. Huh? Wow.
But yeah, same as spastics on
here. It's the same [ __ ] squeezy. I I
used a quote in uh my video today. One
of your quotes. I'll
wait. Don't know if you watched it yet,
but I was like, the machines are all full,
but it's not a problem. I'll
wait. You will wait. Yeah. until one of
the machines are
free. But I waited like 15 minutes and I
joged on. So yeah.
Yeah. So yeah, 280 down today, Greasy.
But remember, just gambling. You win
some, you lose
some. Wink wink.
You win some, you lose some. Just
gambling. Remember that when you watch
my videos, even though there's no wins,
but remember, yeah, I almost had a fight
today with the worker. He said, "Oh,
come outside with a pole and that." I
said, "Come on then, big man." That's
what I said, "Come on then." I said,
"Come on then. I'll give you my address.
You can come after
work. I'll write my address down for
him." I said, "Give me your address, and
if you don't come on my address, I'm
going to put your [ __ ] windows
through your car."
You've not left the house in 3 weeks.
You sound like a [ __ ]
mate. I'm going to send it, bro. After I
saw this passport
out. Oh, [ __ ] hell. What a life, bro. 280 down
gambling. Yeah, I've just got life,
Stephen Howard. I can't be bothered with
it anymore. This community, lad. I just
can't be bothered with it.
It's just the same old same old same
obsessed weirdos. I just thought I'd pop
my ugly face in for few hours. I'm going
to come back later. But I just can't be
bothered with it anymore, bro. It's boring, you
know. You obsess people. So
yeah, don't really need to be on there,
but I still put the gambling videos up.
Yeah, these people thought me losing 300
pound was going to affect me.
Um, it's going to affect me. Um, Harry,
losing 300 pound is going to affect me.
That's bad, is it? They actually think
that's going to affect me, in it.
Yeah, that's funny, bro. Yeah, that is really
funny. That affects me, bro. I I don't like financially. Yeah, by
me. Yep. Well, why didn't you approach her
then? You still there, Steven? We got a
Scottish Izzy now, by the way. I've been
waiting for it. A Scottish
Izzy. We got a Scottish Izzy, lad.
She wasn't a 10 out of 10. There's no
woman in this country that's a 10 out of
10. Don't be so
foolish. Don't be so
foolish. Harry, don't be so
foolish. There no [ __ ]
woman at all. Yeah, that is in this country. that
you're not seeing anyone, Harry. You're
only seeing your right [ __ ] hand.
That's who you're seeing, bro. Get out
of here with that
bollocks. At least I go get some Chinese
in a bit and then I'll be back
later. You know, you know what I find so funny,
people? What happened to the other
channel? Nons got it banned.
nonsleg got it got it
bad, you know. Not he's on a grand a
month. Grand a month
hittance grand a month. Yeah, the
[ __ ] user got it banned, bro. I have
to make another one. Yeah, I was
watching. I was
watching. How can you be on a grand a
month? A grand a
month. A grand a month.
You you you live on a grand a month,
show, how can you live off a grand a
month? Um, no. I think I said something
on my live, bro. Yeah, I said something
on my live and then uh I got banned that way.
Yeah, you're the you're the grinder
show. Never cuz that wasn't me that
posted that. Bye-bye now, [ __ ] I've
seen you on Num Legs's channel.
Yeah, I couldn't live on an
off I couldn't live on a grandma, mate.
Not my lifestyle, bro. Not my [ __ ]
lifestyle. Yeah, my friend, he lives on
400 pound a month. Uh, he lives in from
Liverpool, but he moved to New Zealand.
Now he's back in Liverpool. I could live
on a ground above
me cuz I like my out and I like my drinking.
No, I I couldn't do it, bro. I cannot
live on the ground. [ __ ] that. [ __ ] that
[ __ ] No way, bro. I [ __ ]
lost [ __ ] almost 300 lb today.
Yeah. I can live on the ground up, mate.
Nah. No, man. No. [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah. 1,200. All
right. Yeah. And I don't want to take
away the escorts. I don't want to take
away the drinking. I spent about4500 on escorts last
month. Yeah. I I spent about £400 on escorts last
month. Living the dream. Living the
dream. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Living the [ __ ] dream. I spent about
400 quid on him. I wouldn't take away I
could take away gambling because
gambling is a waste of money anyways.
But I like drinking in
escorts. Yeah, but it's a [ __ ] life
though. It's easy but it's [ __ ] It's
[ __ ] It's a [ __ ]
life, you know. It's a [ __ ] life for
grand a month. Yeah. My internet bills
now. My internet bill is £50 now. Yep.
My internet bill is 50 cuz I had to get
a re I had to get uh I had to renew the
contract. But it's a lot cheaper now.
Yeah. Yeah, but it's a [ __ ]
life cuz once you go out drinking,
you're finished, Harry. You go out
drinking once in London, you're
finished. You are literally
finished. You know, look at all of them
videos I used to do in Leeds and [ __ ]
Sheffield. You can't [ __ ] do a grand month.
Yeah. Uh, good luck with that. Wait, so
how much do you get a month from
VZ? How much do you get a month? Well,
I'm taking you get a,000 a
month. 750. [ __ ]
hell. Yeah. You would never guess how
much Peter Belly gets. That's for Peter
Belly to to know and you to never find out.
Maybe I get 300 pound a month. Who
knows? 750. How do you get
750? I mean, no, you can live off a
grand a month. You can you can and still
save, but you would have to adjust to
it. It would just make life harder.
Like, think of it. Yeah. You've got all
of these women problems. Yeah. But these
Well, not much anymore because I don't
really care about it. But think about
like this, bro. You've got these women
problems. Yeah. And the only thing you
can really do is go out and try. You go
out and you try, you're done for. You
know, you go out once, you're done for
for the month. You can't go out twice a
month on a [ __ ] grand a month. You're
done for. It just makes problems worse.
Yeah. That's it, bro. So, you can't get
more than 800 off
benefits. Yes, you can. I'm not getting
into what I get anyways, but I'm just
saying I could You can live off a grind
up. Yes. And you would adjust to it. But
if you got a high sex drive and you live
in London and stuff, it's going to be very
difficult. But you would manage. Yeah.
Cuz I mean you no matter what money you
get, you adjust to it, you know. So
no, I'm not saying how much money I get, but yeah.
Yeah, but 750. Yeah, bro. And you know
the the worst thing about it, Greg, is
it's hard to get a job now. It's hard to
job. It's hard to get a job. Um every
time it's hard to make money as well.
So, it's hard to get a job. It's hard to make money.
So, sort of um yeah, it's difficult,
bro. And everything's by the books as
well. So, I'm thinking of ways to make
money in the summer cuz I like my nice
Reese clothes. I like that lifestyle,
you know? And if I can find a way to get
make money, I work for it, bro. I don't care. You
know, when you've been spoiled for 4
years, 3 years, it's hard to go back to
a normal lifestyle. You
know, I'm used to having thousands, bro.
Going to the mall and spending you. I'm
saying, you can't do that on
benefits. Not saying that, oh, some
people are not going to get a grand a
month for [ __ ] or you're [ __ ] grezy. I'm
just saying that we have different
lifestyles, you know, but trust me, bro.
Like if only these
people well I'm not even going to
educate them how much money I get but if
they if these people really agree with
you like me I would tell you in private
you know it's it's not it's not a
problem but that's what I'm trying to
say to you doesn't matter what how I get
money or what money I get it doesn't
matter but we're talking about a grand a
month I would tell Gregy because I know
Greavves on the grass but I'm not saying
nothing bro like you've seen the does. But
yeah, but it doesn't make a difference,
bro. Gambling is [ __ ] Usually gambling
is [ __ ] you know. Hello. [Music] Bye-bye,
weirdo. Do I take my mom's benefits? Cuz
I took my mom's
benefits. Why did I take my mom's benefits?
But more stupid to say, man.
No, I've not heard, bro. Yep.
But Shell, stop acting like you don't
live on a grand sh,
mate. You're you're in a grand Stop.
And you see what I'm saying, bro? Like, yeah,
you're you want to grind them up. Maybe
you could do Uber Grezy. Nope, that
doesn't work cuz I've done it once on my
friend's account before. And you can
tell the benefits. I don't give a [ __ ]
Yes, I used delivery once and I earned
35 quid. There you go. Benefits, if
you're watching, I earned 35 quid in one
day and I stopped. Even that's [ __ ]
making money with [ __ ] [ __ ]
But I've got a good idea in the summer
anyways. I just don't want to tell anyone the
idea. I could tell you one idea, but I
would tell you the main idea. You
know, how much do you think Peter Belly
gets a month from Steven
Howard? I don't want to make these people jealous,
bro. Well, we'll be having a boogie
tomorrow anyways. How much do you think, Stephen
Howard? The problem with it is my
friend's got an electric
bike, but I need to [ __ ] get a
charger cuz he lost the charger. And I
was thinking of doing that. Like, I was
thinking of ways to like make money with
whilst I've been off this community,
bro. Like, I have my head screwed on,
but it is difficult. It is difficult.
Like, because it just is difficult, you
know? But what I'm probably going to do in the
summer Yeah. What I'm going to do in the summer, bro,
is is what I'm going to do in the summer
is I'm going to cook burgers outside a
nightclub and see if I can make money
that way. But that's not the main idea.
And that's one of them. There you go. I
just gave you an
idea. And see if you
can sort of make money that way. I don't know.
No, that's why I would never use a
motorbike. Yeah, I'm I'm scared of
crashing as well, Grezy. I would never
go on a motorbike. You're not getting me
on a motorbike. My friend's got a motor
bike as well. I can use my friend's
motorbike. He lives like 30 minutes
away. I'm not getting on a motorbike.
[ __ ] that, bro. I've seen crashes in real life, you
know? Yeah. Like I like I You're not
getting me on no motorbike, bro. It ain't
happen. I am not going on no [ __ ]
motorbike, bro. You're having a [ __ ]
rank clap. You're not getting me on no
motorbikes. Even if my life depends on
it, cuz the crashes, it's nah. Nah, no,
no, no. I've seen it, bro. I've seen it
firsthand. So, but electric bikes, yeah,
I would do it. Of course, I would. But
it's not it's not good nowadays doing
that kind of job, bro.
But yeah, so 700 plus 500 1 2 3 4 1200.
Yeah, man. Maybe I
do. But yeah, see the thing is Stephen,
how would you really think I can't go to
the ATM right now and withdraw a load of
money and show these people? I don't
need to prove myself to these [ __ ] You
know, technically I' I've showed money
today. [ __ ] you know,
um I showed money today, didn't I?
[ __ ] when I gambled that [ __ ] 200
quid even though it was £300 but
yeah you get my [ __ ] point bro.
Yeah. So the money you're on Greezy how
would you ever go to America? You wouldn't it?
H you wouldn't would you? Scottish Izzy
bought me some shots and I bought her
some drinks. Oh, I miss Scottish Izzy.
Izzy. Scottish Izzy was making Peter
Belly very hard. So the money you get,
how would you go to America? You
wouldn't in it. Unless you stay for a very long time.
Yeah, got some horror films coming out,
but not until next month. I'll be
watching it, mate. Don't you [ __ ] worry.
Yeah, but say you didn't have
savings. Yeah, but say you did have
Yeah, you got some savings.
Yeah. But what if you did have savings?
Oh, it's a Scottish
woman. I did go to the States. I showed
you the booking as well. Scottish Izzy.
Um, Scottish Izzy is some woman that I
met last Friday and we kissed and
touched. We danced together as well. Oh,
I met some crazy woman. She was Muslim.
Oh my god, she was crazy, bro. I didn't
tell you about this Stephen Howard and
and Greavves. She was [ __ ] mad, bro.
Like, she kept texting me and texting
me, texting me. I was trying to distance
my myself away from her cuz she says
that she's a religious Muslim and she's
celibate and that she would only get
with somebody that's Muslim yet she's in
a nightclub drinking alcohol. She's in a
nightclub drinking alcohol but she want
any guy that she potentially would get
with has to be has to be has to be she
has to has to be um a Muslim. But I said
but you're not I called her a fake
Muslim because you real Muslims don't
drink alcohol. So, you can't be in a
club drinking alcohol and claim you're
Muslim and then expect people to convert
to your religion because you're not a
Muslim. Because if he was, you wouldn't
be drinking. I've got Muslim friends,
mate. You know, I'm from London. I know
how these things
work. So, it's it just doesn't make any
sense. Uh, yes, my passport did have the
required days yet. Yes, it did. And
we're not getting into this anyways. I
know where I went and that's it. I know
who changed their number. I know who
shot themsself. And that's it, bro. That
is 100% it. I know all of these things.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay, bro. Anyways, bye-bye
now. Stop repeating yourself. So, yeah,
that's what happened. We anyway. So, she
turned out to be a [ __ ] weirdo. Um,
and a freak. So, yeah. I just Yeah, she
was 40 with two kids. Imagine that. 40
years of age with two kids and she was
playing hard to get. Imagine that.
That's crazy. That is crazy. And she's
playing hard to [ __ ] get. It's a
madness. That is a madness,
lad. Anyways, I'm going to go get this
Chinese and I will be
back later. Definitely be back later.
And I'm [ __ ] off again for a couple
of weeks. How old were the kids? I think
one was 12 and one was 25.
Yeah, they've always got an excuse, bro.
It It doesn't bother me anymore. It
doesn't bother me. I'm a loser, bro.
Look at what you look like. Look at your
face, mate. You only wish. Yeah. You at
at the end of the day,
you you bro, look at the state of you in
your [ __ ] ugly face. Look at that
ugly [ __ ] face, bro. No wonder you
sit there every day stalking me on
YouTube. You ugly bastard. You ugly
[ __ ] Like you spend all your day on
YouTube stalking me because you wish you
was me. You don't have no wife. You're
not married. If you was married, you
wouldn't be stalking me every day, mate.
You fat [ __ ] ugly loser. Look at you
Peter Griffin with the [ __ ] fortunes.
Get out of here, man. You stalk me every
single day because you want to be me.
Every day you wake up and you make love
to your make believe wife that don't
exist. You're wishing you was me. I live
in your head. You stalk me every day. I
love it. Oh, another Listen, all night
Mike, you're boring, bro. Listen, you
said nothing to me. Okay. Okay. Let me
Okay, let me let I'm actually going to
block you, right? Can you stop
embarrassing yourself, right? When I was
in Scotland, you shut your mouth. When I
asked you to show where you was, you
shut yourself. You uh you you ran away,
bro. You You wouldn't tell me where you
are. You're a coward. You literally are
a coward. You can't trigger no one. No
one goes on your channel anymore cuz
you're a keyboard warrior. You know,
you've been doing it for three years,
mate. You're boring now. You shut your
mouth when I was in Scotland. You shut
your mouth when I'm in England asking
you to show where you are in Scotland.
Why do you think people don't go on your
channel anymore? You're
boring. Like, I get more money than you
will ever have. Look at my Look at my
You bullied me. Yeah, bro. I'm very very
bullied. Yeah, I'm so bullied. Well
done, bro. Yeah, so bullied that when I
come to your country, you can't even
show me where you are. Yeah, bro. You
bullied me big time. How am I going to
cope? I I can't take the bullying.
You're right, bro. I'm so bullied. Like,
I'm going to end myself. Yeah, some
Scottish little spaz kiltw wearing pipe
sucking dick sucking [ __ ] in Scotland
that can't show me where he is bullied
me for years. Oh dear, dear me. You know
that's not on my bucket list, bro.
You've successfully bullied me. Yeah.
Anyways, bye-bye now. You You've
successfully bullied me. I'm very
bullied. Yeah. You're a keyboard
lawyer. You're a keyboard warrior,
lad. They're such a [ __ ] Steven
Howard [ __ ] This is why I don't
really come on here anymore. It's the
same spastics. We got We got Peter
Griffin claiming that he's married, but
yet he's on YouTube every day stalking
me. But he's married. He's married, but
he's on YouTube every single day
stalking me. Oh, and he even tries to
stalk me on Reddit as well. I'm not
going to lie to you, bro. I don't think
you have this wife. I'm starting to be
less of a less of I'm starting to be
less and less of a believer, bro. Every
single time I'm starting to be less and
less of a believer in your marriage with
by your YouTube actions. And he's not a
loony. Steven Howard not a looney. He's
a keyboard warrior. Loonies are not
keyboard warriors. See, looney people go
on people's doors. Jamie Thompson along
with Tra and all of them, they're just
cowards. They're not loonies. They're
not lunatics. They're just coward
keyboard warriors. Yeah, he's think
about it, right? Okay, let's just go by
his logic. Steven Howard, Peter Griffin
is married, right? So, he's married and
he's got a better life than me, yet he's
on YouTube every day stalking me. Can
you please explain how that makes sense?
Can you please explain to me how that
makes sense? So, you're married, you got
all this money, your life's perfect, but
you're sat online every day trying to
stalk me. I'm being I'm becoming a less
I'm becoming less and less of a
believer. I'm not going to lie to you,
bro. Every time I go on your Well, I
don't go on your channel, but when I was
last on your channel like three months
ago, I don't think you're married, bro.
I really really don't think you're
married Peter Griffin. But to be fair,
at least you show what you look like
because most of these people like
Tradal, all of these people, they all
look like you. Fat, ugly skin, which is
why you do what you do every day. But
you're you're just one of the only ones
that actually show your face. That's the
difference. You're one of the only ones
that actually show your face. So
congratulations to that, man. I I take
my hat off to you. I take my hat off to
you indeed. But um most of you people
Yeah. I can't I can't h I can't cope
with the fact that I'm married, mate.
I've had more women than you. I have
more money than you. Yeah. Your wife
obviously can't be that good if your
make believe wife can't be that good
since you're stalking me every day on
YouTube. I can't cope. Who's the one
that's stalking me every single day?
Who's the one that's stalking me every
day? Mate, I've had more women than you
have had hot dinners, more [ __ ]
more sex. I get more money than you and
I can prove that as well. Like, please,
bro. Stop embarrassing yourself. It's really embarrassing.
Now, Peter Griffin. Peter Griffin. Calm
down. Peter Griffin of
Cohog. Could you actually imagine looking like
this? Imagine looking like that, bro. [ __ ]
hell. Imagine actually looking like that, bro.
It is something to boast about,
bro. You know, it is something to boast
about. I do get more money than him. I
have more money than him. More money
than he will ever have. How about that one? [Music]
Byebye. Bro, you are some
[ __ ] But I'm just No, cuz he's trying
to say that cuz he's married. No one
cares that you're married,
bro. Gripping out him in real life.
Yeah, he's not even married, bro.
Anyways, man needs to get some food cuz
man is getting
angry. Yeah, bro. So, I'll be back
later. Yeah, I'll be back later, bro.
About maybe 10 if you So, yeah, bro.
Oh, my face looks like a vagina. Well,
that's not me in the picture. So, yeah.
Yeah, he's he's got he's got
a he's got um he's got a wife, but he
sits on YouTube every day stalking me.
These people's lives are so perfect, but
they sit every single day on YouTube
stalking me. And apparently, it's them
bullying me. Yeah, I'm well and truly
bullied. I'm well and truly triggered.
I'm well and truly bullied. That's why
we come on YouTube every day laughing at
you. Like, bro, if these people's lives
were were better than yours, they
wouldn't be on your case every single
day. Think about it, bro. They wouldn't
be on your case. Like, nons legs, all of
these people. You know what I'm
saying? Anyways, bro, I'm gone. I'll be
right back later. Yeah. Peace.