Hey. Oh,
just wanted to see if it's still the same
if it's the same people in YouTube.
You know, I do my little uh weekly
checks, man. Just checking if it's the
same people on YouTube. Yeah.
But people that can't get off it.
People that can't get off YouTube. Hey,
these people can't go YouTube, man.
That cash back thing was a [ __ ] scam, was it?
I'm [ __ ] knacking, mate.
Got sunburn again. Oh my god. I need to
go to gym tomorrow.
Slack slacking a little bit.
But yeah, you know me, mate, and my
little uh you know me and my little uh
welfare checks, matey.
This 400 phone is actually really good, you know. [ __ ] ace.
Um, my back is [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, money. I've been out grafting all day, bro. [ __ ] hell.
I'm fat. I must have done about 100
miles today. Easy, bro. I need to go to gym tomorrow.
Yeah, man. You need to get off of
YouTube, man. I might have my phone off.
I I'll give you the box in a minute. Uh,
I'm going to send it, bro. But you need
to get off of YouTube. What the [ __ ] bro?
You need to get off of YouTube, lad.
Oh, [ __ ] My back is [ __ ] bro.
Jesus Christ. I need to give my skin a
break as well. It will go brown though. Yeah,
I took some good videos there as well. Monty, what?
Can you hear me? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I can
hear you. I'll turn it down. I can
barely hear you. One second. Let me
restart. No. No. No. It's I can't hear
you, bro. One second. I can't hear you
properly. Let me
Can you hear me now?
There you go.
No, he's falling. He's fing it. Yeah. Yeah,
I'm not going to bomb bomb you. Just
keep it like that. I'm not going to put
anything up. You're very The volume is very low.
Well, one sec. It might be my settings.
So, I might change my settings.
Sound better? Yeah. Huh? Is that
Yeah, a little bit.
You need to get off YouTube, man.
Why do I need to get off YouTube? Cuz it's [ __ ]
Can I send you a video page? Yeah.
Is it porn?
Yeah. Yeah. I send you a video.
Is it porn, mate?
Yeah. Why did you Did you sort the
police thing out?
Um, yeah. Yeah. I got I've got an
interview coming up soon. When is it?
Yeah. Yeah. They said they wouldn't test
me in it. So, yeah. But yeah, I'm getting excited.
Yeah. Make sure you tell them
everything. Yeah. And you showed them
everything. Yeah, I will do. I will do. Good.
I hate that, bro. You don't understand.
I hate that con. Yeah. Huh?
Okay. Watch it and tell me what you
think about it now. Watch it now.
Was you kipping all day?
No man, I've been getting whipped all day, mate.
Let me have a look. What's up?
Who is it? You.
Who do you think it is? You. Yeah.
Marty, when you went, how many times
have you been live today?
A couple, but I need to stop doing it.
It's the same people, isn't it? Yeah,
it's boring though.
Yeah. No, it can be funny like today is
being played funny on it on shoes,
babes. Let me check them out. Let me
[ __ ] [ __ ] hell. I'm tired, bro.
Are you tired? Are you being out? Are
you I cycled 100 miles today?
AJ, do you want to go do you want me to
give you a chat? Yeah.
You want to? You can't get laid.
Okay then. I bet you I can get you laid
in a second. Yeah. Really?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Do you want me to give
you a tip? Yeah. Okay.
Right. Next woman you see. Yeah. Uh right.
What you want to do? Yeah. Is that you
just want to
just just walk past her.
Just walk past her. Yeah.
But make sure you look at her eye color
first before you walk past her and all
that [ __ ] Yeah. and then turn back
around. Yeah. Tap on his shoulder and
just say you lost lace.
Okay. Oh [ __ ] Just say you lost that.
Okay. I'll give it a whirl.
No. No. Just say you got beautiful eyes.
Just say how you can hell. You are you
see this is what I said to
Yeah. But what if they say they have a boyfriend?
And then you just say so what?
You say, "So what?"
You got say, "Don't let Don't let that
stop you." Is it? Yeah. Just say, "So
what?" That's even better.
That's more of a challenge for