Oh, sorry, man. I was too tired yesterday. Yeah,
I just did my little weekly um check,
you know, just to see if it's the same people.
You know what I mean? Always doing it
just to see if it's safe. But you know I
I can take a day of YouTube see but
these people can't they have
their life maybe
it's their food and life It's gorgeous
today. It's lacking. Yeah.
Yeah. Just checking to see if it's the
same people every day.
You know, mate, you're still on YouTube. No budget.
Still on YouTube, are you
[ __ ] woke up the whole neighborhood?
I mean, I've just come on to see if it's
the same people. Obviously, I wasn't on
YouTube for 3 days. I' been busy. Some
people got a life, you know. I didn't
know you was still in YouTube,
you know. Yeah.
Didn't know you were still on YouTube, mate.
I don't cover much anymore.
It's the same [ __ ] every day. They people
I thought we see.
I just put a watch on.
Just put a nice wash on.
Go in. Put the clothes out on the line.
Have a shower. Come back. Lovely day.
What was your uncle? Oh,
I got some bad things to say about,
you know, I love It's saying that this
is such a um thick and twisted community
because I'd love to say everything but I
can't get too many glasses on here and
[ __ ] you know, and that's why I don't
like I don't share my life on here anymore glasses
dirty little grass like them little
keyboard warriors that don't show their
family faces. That's why they ruin it
because I can't share everything. Son,
anybody need glasses? Uh,
I can share that little thing. You know,
it's a shame though because otherwise
people can say where they're going, when
and stuff. Probably even give their
[ __ ] address to be honest. But on
this place, the little jealous grasses. So um
I left my [ __ ] keys at the escort's
house the other day all the way in
[ __ ] Wembley. I ain't stopped the
past couple of days, man. But good. Told
you I would be out this this week. I
will be going out Wednesday. My friends,
so I get Wednesday. It's going to be a
nice day. We'll go out drinking.
I do have
I told you I stick to my guns and when I
say something I mean it bro
I'd love to share more things but
fortunately I can't
these escorts are going [ __ ] bad mate
Let me see if he wants to come around today.
That Muslim woman randomly messaged me.
It's so weird.
I know she's a troll.
He's been [ __ ] stable
[ __ ] mentally [ __ ] unstable. [ __ ] parents
if you ask me. Yeah,
I was where I met my mommy yesterday.
Cactus Joe. Was it Cactus? Cactus Jack.
I was wearing my mama. Our bless
these jealous glasses. What do you think?
These little jees.
It's a shame though cuz we could have
like good combos and stuff.
Good workout today. My arms are getting
big as well, but
slack on the gym.
I don't know how people can be on the
YouTube every day.
You're not going to get this color arm
by [ __ ] staying in like you [ __ ]
Are you [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] paratants if you ask me? [ __ ] paradox.
I need a shower, but there's no point be
showering before going to the gym. So yeah, you might see
[ __ ] is such a [ __ ] I to call her a
[ __ ] 20y old. She's such a
Who the [ __ ] do these people [ __ ]
think they are?
I hate her, bro. I'm going to I think
I'm actually going to block her, bro.
You can't stand it, bro. I'm doing these
things to get away from these westernized [ __ ]
and I'm having to [ __ ] deal with
them. What the [ __ ]
I'm doing things to get away from these
[ __ ] westernized guns. I can't stand
them. And [ __ ] look what you just turned into.
I [ __ ] can't stand him. She's turning
into a [ __ ]
You wouldn't like She wasn't like this last year
now. She's just a proper [ __ ]
I'm so autistic, bro. One second. Hold
up. Let me Let me end this live stream.
Yeah, I just told her about herself, you know. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye now. Sorry I don't talk to [ __ ] So,
okay. Listen, stop calling me. Bro, I
swear if you call me mate one more time.
I'm not sure, bro. I'm going to go this
bitch's door. I swear she's winding me
up. I swear to God.
talk to him and [ __ ] off and stop
[ __ ] messaging me before I come on
your [ __ ] mommy's door. You're
winding me up now, bro. I swear to God.
Stop texting me and [ __ ] off. You know
what I'm saying? Cuz I'm going to come
on your [ __ ] door if you don't leave
me alone, bro.
that would have most in this [ __ ] Yeah.
where I'm going to go this bitch's door.
She winds me up again.
Going to give her one chance. If she
messages me again, I'm going to come on
your mom's door, bro. [ __ ] winding me up.
This [ __ ] 19year-old is pissing me off.
I'm going to write now. I said, "Listen,
by the way, it's Pday. You unblock me.
If you unblock me
and message me one more time, I will cly
be going on your mom's door. I will personally
your mom's door now. Leave me alone.
Stupid [ __ ] Yeah, I just texted her
that. I said, "If she doesn't if she
does this whole thing again, I'm
blocking. Block it." And basically one
more time, I'm going to go on her mom's
I don't give a [ __ ] bro. I was out all
day yesterday. I don't give a [ __ ] So,
you better hope you got brothers on and
and [ __ ] bro. You're winding me the
[ __ ] up. Leave me the [ __ ] alone.
[ __ ] can't stand this [ __ ] bro. I
swear to God.
I hate her. I actually hate her. And you
know what? She was actually all right.
That's a year ago. Now, she's just a
complete Leave me alone and stop [ __ ]
messaging me, bro. You want to talk
about me, talk about you, bro. You're
the one with mental issues. You're the
one that's blocking and unblocking
people and they don't even like you,
bro. What the [ __ ] man? People trying
to get on with their life and you're
doing all this [ __ ] madness and when
someone tells you something you don't
like, oh, you you run away again. [ __ ] off, man.
[ __ ] had a good day yesterday as
well. You know what I'm saying?
You don't have money. That's your
problem, bro. If you find your voice,
that's your problem, bro. It's not my
problem. Go to the [ __ ] work that
other people [ __ ] do. Leave leave the [ __ ] alone.
Trying to get all smart on WhatsApp,
bro. I told her about herself. What the
[ __ ] I'm not your ATM, bro. You know
what I mean? [ __ ] off.
For start, it all starts at a young age.
Well, no, sorry. They're okay at a young
age. 18, 19. They're a bit more like I
wouldn't like to use the word gull
gullible, but they're more sort of not
even that necessarily naive as well, but
they don't know as much. And when they
start getting to like 20, they just turn
into all the same [ __ ] I have to see
[ __ ] all the time. I'm in London every
day. I have to see [ __ ] everywhere. All
the time. Same dick ass.
What the [ __ ] I told her if you unblock
me and you message me again, I'm going
on your mom's door, bro. I don't care.
Leave me alone, bro. Start your [ __ ]
again with me on your phone and see what
happens. I'll come your [ __ ] door,
bro. I swear.
She's a strange. I was like, you're a
bum, bro. You don't even work. How do
you have no money? You don't even
[ __ ] work. It doesn't matter if you
work. You ain't got money, bro.
You're a broadcast [ __ ] and you're
messaging my phone. [ __ ] off, bro.
Hello, mate. Chill out. I'm not your mate, bro. Yeah.
When they can't get what they want, they
start [ __ ] doing madness. You've
already called the police. Call the
police on [ __ ] what, man?
Yeah. You can call the police as much as
you want, bro. Yeah. Tell the police. I
said, "If you don't leave me alone, I'm
going to come on your door." Yeah. If
you don't leave me alone, I'm going to
come on your door. Simple.
You know what I'm saying?
If you do not leave me alone, I will be
coming on your door. Leave me alone.
Yeah. I didn't say that. What the [ __ ]
man? You know,
the only one that's autistic is you. The
only one that's a broke ass [ __ ] is
you. No one else. You know,
good bro. [ __ ] off, man. You weirdo.
Stop messaging me, you [ __ ] creepy [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
Well, because people won't send you money.
Because people won't send you money.
No, bro. [ __ ] off.
[ __ ] [ __ ] man.
All the same. Gave up with it because
they're all the [ __ ] same. Whether
they're the same now or they turn the
same, they're all the same.
Look at them. What the [ __ ]
We met a lot met a lot of pickage
yesterday as well, bro.
Why is it these guys like these these
like Jack the L kind of ethics guys
always try and give it when they're with
other people, but they never give it
when they're by themselves. When they're
by themselves, they're [ __ ] bro.
They're all weak [ __ ] anyways, but
they when they're by themselves, they
say nada. But then when they're with
other people, they try to get all brave
and had a drink. [ __ ] off, mate. With
your four other [ __ ] behind you.
You know what I mean?
You're talking to five other people.
That's good then. So, stop messaging me.
You're speaking to five other people. If
you're talking to five other people,
then stop messaging me. Simple. Good for you.
So yeah, man. [ __ ] leave me the [ __ ] alone.
Who the [ __ ] do they think they are?
Man, are you mad? [ __ ] [ __ ]
Speaking to five other people. That's
good for you. So, leave me alone. Like,
I don't need you. I don't want you. And
you're [ __ ] messaging me. [ __ ] off,
You know what I'm saying?
Not stupid idiot.
It's a shame. It
see the same [ __ ] everywhere, same
women everywhere with the same attitude
everywhere. It's boring, mate. I don't
think I don't even talk to people
anymore. It's boring. Same people, same
attitude, same NPCs.
And know I'm going to I'm going to bring
this topic up now. Yeah. Again, cuz this
kind of pissed me off today. People say
that all women aren't the same. Never
ever met anyone that weren't want to
come. Literally like sat here saying it
right now. I've never met a good one in
27 years. That speaks volume, man. With
that age range, you know.
Yeah. Well, I have, but they're in their
50s. I mean, does that really count? Not
really. But no, I agree with this [ __ ]
They literally are all literally are all
the same and I don't even care about it
anymore because I don't care, bro. Like,
I'm leaving soon. So, and I don't really
care about that [ __ ] But they they are
literally all the same. Generally are.
And if they're not, it's because they're
18 and they're going to turn the same.
That's the only reason they're not.
They're just [ __ ] Complete [ __ ] [ __ ]
I may just on the phone to um
do more things to
if you're talking to five other people
[ __ ] leave beh. Simple Hey, Mage.
Not so hot roast today roast.
It's two [ __ ] football roast.
Yeah, it's too hot. Oh man. Hello CP
Yeah, I don't I don't watch it anymore,
man. I don't get with the drama and
[ __ ] It's boring. It's the same repeating people
swinging swing swinging around about Zine.
Yeah, I don't bother with it anymore.
Me, it's just a repeating people.
I just come watch them people in
YouTube. I do a little welfare check.
See you still on YouTube.
I like to see who's still on YouTube. You know,
they need to get off of YouTube. I don't
know what they're doing on the YouTube.
We need to get off of it. You know, no
life for anyone.
I need to go to the gym in a minute. I
know. Well, when this sport finishes,
go, eat some nice salmon, get some nice food later.
Love it. Nice, man. Love.
You need to get off your YouTube, Linds.
You need to get off YouTube.
And I'm going to do I'm going to do a
welfare check every Sunday. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. They get more entitled as they get older.
I wish there was just a woman that existed.
No attitude, no nothing. But nah,
you'll never find a woman like that.
They would have gone insane. It's quite
a shame, man.
Who would want to spend their life with
the rest of their life with someone like
that, you know?
just just to see if it's the same
people. You know me.
For me, man. Look at the arms. Look,
it's going to go brown tomorrow. I'm
telling you, it's going to go brown.
I need to go to the gym, bro. Cuz my
looking at my arms in the mirror like my
arms are looking big, boy. I'm going to
keep it up. You're going to get big and shrunk. just
so I know,
you know, just want to so I can say I've
done a good deed. It's the same people
on your channel. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
I'm I'm a bit hairy, man.
No, it doesn't need to be anything in it
for me. I guess speak to Joey. I mean, that's enough.
Yeah. I get I get to speak to JF.
Isn't that right, John? Yeah,
bro. Why is it got to be so hot? I hate
this weather, man.
I mean, the street will get tired, but
yeah. Want to go in the gym and make
some [ __ ] games, bro?
Little virgin. No muscle little virgin.
You know what I'm talking about? What a virgin.
A complete virgin.
This phone that's £400 is actually a
good phone. You know, it's got good
battery, too. But you know what? I
really want to get this Fold 7 when it
comes out, man.
I could buy it, but no,
technically could buy it, but you know,
uh, what I want to get the Samsung F7,
but this phone is just the one I got
from Samsung. It was £400. It's a good
phone though. It works fine.
It's a good phone, man.
No, lad. I really want to. But I could
get the 57, but
I feel like there's better things to be
spending money on. You know,
a phone is a [ __ ] phone. Once you get
have like a four00 phone, a phone's a
[ __ ] phone. [ __ ] know what I'm saying? So, yeah.
Yeah, man. I need to go for a drink at
some point. I've not fed the past a
week, man. But like I said, I said I'm
going to do my two weeks.
And yeah. So,
no, I don't like bullying people. It's quite nasty.
I'm not a bully, man.
Sorry, mate. I'm not a [ __ ] bully.
Nah, not a bully, mate. No bully, mate. Sorry.
All right, they want to come out. I'll
take it out and then I'll do one sec.
Yeah. One second, buddy. I'm just
putting a cool wash on. Who's that?
[ __ ] hell. But now I'm getting
hungry. Get hungry now.
It's all right. What time stomach? No problem.
I do need to go out this week.
Definitely. I need to take a break and
just have a drink.
I might get blackout drunk. [ __ ] ass. Yeah.
I don't know how people right work and
then try to make out that they're better
like they like working. They don't like working,
bro. I've worked before and it's proper
proper shy. Like these people don't like working, bro.
And I probably had like
mess jobs, bro. Like, you know what I'm
saying? Like, so this Joe and that I'm
going to wait until he comes and we'll
have a serious we'll have a serious chat.
I'll have a serious chat with him. But
they don't like working, man. Trust me,
I've worked so I know.
It's people do not like working. It's
what exactly I said before. How can you
work on top of all of these other
problems? You got women, bad
experiences. You can't, bro. You literally can't. Like,
there's not there's no there's no just
purpose. There's no nothing. Like, no.
Trust me, if you got other problems, it
makes the problems way worse.
It doesn't go away. You know what I'm saying? Like,
bro, if you can give me £50 for the
welfare check every Sunday, it' be good.
Yeah, I was out I I was out working
yesterday. I made [ __ ] 90 quid. Felt
good, man. Oh, mate, I'm [ __ ] But
what I kept looking at was these women.
Like, my whole thing is I'm going to get
as much money together so I don't ever
have to work ever again. That's the
whole point is I don't ever want to do it again.
I already put the box there. Like you
make as much now, I don't want to work
ever again in my life. At least I'm real
about it. But
obviously I'll do as much as I can and then
I'm I'll just not do it. But yeah, it
was lush screams. He was [ __ ] lush, mate.
Yeah, it was [ __ ] good, bro.
Good, bro. It's good. So yeah, you can
make money, but
it was like 160 in 3 days, but the other
two days weren't even that properly. So
yeah, bro, make some good money here in London, bro.
You know what I'm saying? So yeah,
but yeah, working is [ __ ] anyways, G.
You never want to work, bro. Trust me,
you never want to work.
Trust me, [ __ ] having to see all
these women and there's nothing you can
do about it and [ __ ] Especially if it's
like a security job. If you do like a
security job, you know,
renting my ass, bro. You wish. But yeah,
so now I'm thinking maybe get the fold
seven greasy, but I can't justify it,
bro. I can't justify paying fold seven prices.
So yeah, I said I weren't going to go
out for two weeks. So
yeah, man. I said I weren't going to go
out for two weeks tonight. So and I
meant it. So good.
All you see is these women out and about.
All that's all you ever see. And in the
summer you get [ __ ] horny as well.
I was drinking every two minutes. It's [ __ ] right?
We're going to go for a drink on
Wednesday. I think he thinks I'm going
to go for a drink on Wednesday.
Um, definitely me and my friends though.
Need to get my hair done as well. I have
to by then. I think it should be like 2
weeks or so. Yeah.
I don't know how you don't get obsessed
with these women. I'm obsessed. Like
literally. But at the same time, I know
they're all [ __ ] and they're all the
same. Oh, I had an argument with a
19-year-old this morning, Grezy.
Oh, I had a really bad argument with
her, Grezy. Can I tell you what
happened? And I basically told her at
the end where to [ __ ] stick it.
Yeah, bro. Do you want to know?
She's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
See, as they get older,
they just become they just they just
turn the same, you see.
So, she was asking me for money. I was
like, "If you come and meet me, I'll
give you money. I'll lend you some
money." And then she was being like,
"Oh, weird. Oh, you're autistic. You're
this. You're mate." I'm not your [ __ ]
mate personally. Yeah. I said, "Take a
look at your [ __ ] self before talking
about anyone else. Stop. Go look at your
[ __ ] self." I said, "You're single
yourself, you [ __ ] idiot." She know
I'm speaking to five people. You're
speaking to five people. Why are you on
my ass for money? Yeah, you're speaking
to five people, so don't [ __ ] message
me for money then, you [ __ ] idiot.
And I said to her, "If you message me
again, I'm coming on your mom's door." I
told her as well, I said to her, "Yeah,
if you if you unblock me again and you
message me again, I'm coming on your
door. I swear to God, leave me the [ __ ]
alone." She's a [ __ ] Grezy, a [ __ ] proper [ __ ]
That's what I'm saying. They're not like
that when they're when when when they're
younger, you know, and then they just
turn all westernized [ __ ]
I hate them, bro. They generally just
hate them. I really hate them going
around. See, you see the same people
with the same attitude. The same people,
You see the same people with the same
attitude. Literally, that's why I don't
even talk to people anymore.
Yeah, [ __ ] them, bro.
All these people that say, "Yeah, work
gives you a purpose." Squeezy. They're
talking utter shine.
Oh, I like to work. Working is, you
know, we're not made to work. We wasn't
born to work. There's so many things you
can do in your life. You're wasting your
life away working. Do you do realize that?
You know, you do realize that.
So these people in the Nile that say,
"Oh, I love working."
[ __ ] love work to my ass.
What do you think, Monty? What?
Why don't you get a job?
I give myself a hand job, mate. It's better.
Oh, it's so hard trying to speak to you
sometimes, Marty. You can be very slow.
Well, I just woke up. I just said give
you just said, "Why don't you go and get
a job?" And I just said, "I'd rather
give myself a job or rather give [ __ ]
someone a blow job." You'd rather give
someone a [ __ ] Yeah.
Can I give you a [ __ ] PJ? Nah, you
can give Rice a [ __ ] kind of
a small. I need someone with extra extra large.
Yeah. You want to have a sword fight?
Yeah. Do you want with you? Yeah.
Nah, you still argue with Timmy.
Nah, I'm done with Timmy. He's as fastic in it.
Huh? He's a [ __ ] isn't it, buddy?
Who Jimmy? [ __ ]
He's a [ __ ]
That's a fake money mic sister you got
in here, you know. Yeah, I know. I know.
Do you want my opinion, Monty? I [ __ ]
love Mike in here. They're all [ __ ]
Is it? I [ __ ] love that man in in
here, man. I meet him now. Me. Monty,
are you a [ __ ] Are you a [ __ ] No, I've
got a dick. So I'm a dick. No, but
you're a [ __ ] though, is it? No. Women's
Women's got [ __ ] We're just dicks.
I get horny walking around one seeing
all these women. I get horny, you know.
No, I got horny this morning. Me, man. Don't you?
Did you get a [ __ ]
No, she she [ __ ] left me. Why?
She left me hanged this morning last night.
Do you know if she gives you a [ __ ]
Does she swallow it?
Yeah, she swallow.
No, I don't know. Really?
See, she hasn't
talking about sex life, man. You're the
one that brought it up. I was talking
about hand jobs. You can't. Yeah. Oh man,
money. This is a proper pedo community,
isn't it? Yeah. Money might assist a
pedo, man. Why?
I don't know. She just look like one.
She looks like an albino like him in it. Yeah. In one, huh?
Two ugly bastards in one pot.
It's funny, isn't it? It's [ __ ]
funny. Looking mate.
Pair of [ __ ] Money. Pair of [ __ ] Jes.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. Money. Oh, what a
[ __ ] day I've had. 91 yet? Nope.
Hey, you said
you said that I'm obsessed with [ __ ]
No, you're obsessed with wanking you.
Not [ __ ] Do you find it? Do you
find it hard to even get one [ __ ] I
don't [ __ ] I just get [ __ ]
Why? I'll just [ __ ] man. Zagging is
better on the blow jobs.
Have you got a light?
No, [ __ ] are the best.
My [ __ ] are the best.
Well, you're going to give me one then
and I'll tell you if your [ __ ] are the best.
You're [ __ ] weird, man.
You're a proper [ __ ] Ch.
Oh, here's another thing. Yeah. One
second, Bonnie. Let me let me kick you
and I I'll let you back in. Let me try
and explain this to Grezy. So, after a
long day yesterday, I was like, you
know, I really fancy a [ __ ]
And um she said, um, oh, this is a story
I forgot. And she was like, oh yeah, we
can give you a [ __ ] but you can't
come in our mouth. I was like, huh? I
can't come in your mouth. That's
literally the point of a [ __ ] is to
to be able to finish. If not, then I'd
be masturbating my [ __ ] self. And
it's like, "No, no, you can't finish in
your mouth." I was like, "What the [ __ ]
is the point of having a [ __ ] then if
you can't even finish?" So, I had to me
I had to hit up one escort that I knew
and then I literally had to go all the
way to Wembley to go and see her. He
sucked my dick. She sucked my balls.
This country is getting worse, bro. You
even get escort so entitled now. So I
had to hit one up that I already knew
and I had to go all the way past Wembley
which is like the other side of London.
I was horny bro. [ __ ] really really
horny. I couldn't wait. I needed my
needs satisfied. And then I left my keys
there. So I have no keys now cuz I I
left my keys there and I was like
there's no point me going all the way
there because it's going to cost more
than just getting another key card.
So, I need to get another I'll just get
a key cut cuz uh
and she got fake tits. So, I won't even
be going back. Yeah, they've all got
fake tits. This country is just so
backwards. All of it is [ __ ] You got
escorts of entitled now. Why the [ __ ] if
you can't come in the mouth, you're
going to get a [ __ ] [ __ ]
And I'm thinking like it's like selling
a washing machine. Yeah. It's like
having a washing machine up for sale,
right? having a washing machine up for
sale when it be like, "Oh, no. Actually,
I don't want the money." It doesn't make any sense.
That's going all the way to Wimbley. It
was missions, mate. Missions, bro.
It's bad, man. It is bad.
It's a shame that all women are the same, man.
No. Set aside. They literally have the same attitude.
You know, why do you think I don't speak
to them anymore? Because they've all got
the same NPC stuck up attitude. Why I
don't even bother going out drinking anymore?
Just going to make money and that's it
because I don't see the point of it
anymore really, bro.
Nothing's ever going to change with them. So,
why would you want a [ __ ] if you
can't finish in their mouth? That's the
whole point of a [ __ ]
They don't need to swallow it, but
the whole point is to literally finish
in their mouth.
That's literally the whole point of a [ __ ]
It doesn't make no sense. But anyways,
I'm going to wait until this uh
Oh, for [ __ ] sake.
Basically, so the other day I really
fancy like some like [ __ ] So, what I
done was I went to um the escort and I'm
thinking, "Oh yeah, I'm going to get
one." I went there
and then um she was like, "Um, yeah, we
we give you a [ __ ] but you can't
finish that mouth." I was like, "What's
the point of
a [ __ ] if you can't finish in their
mouth. It doesn't make any sense. It
literally doesn't make any sense. The
whole point of a [ __ ] is to finish in
the person's mouth and it would be like
all weird about it. And there was two of
them. So then I had to come back home. I
had to hit up an escort I knew before
from two months ago. You know, the one
that gave me the really good [ __ ] I
say two months ago, maybe a month ago.
And I had to travel all the way to her,
which is past Wembley, which is like out
of London, like 30 mi. I was like,
"There's no way. I'm sleeping today
without getting [ __ ] There's no
way." Then I left my keys there. That's
another thing. I don't even have any
keys now cuz I left my keys there and
there's no point me going all the way
there to get the keys cuz it's going to
cost me more in trouble and I'm not
going to see her again because I don't
want to [ __ ] got fake tits. So, fake
tits will turn off. But he was sucking
my balls and everything grieves me. My
balls, my [ __ ] dick, everything. They
don't need to swallow.
They they don't need to swallow, but a
[ __ ] without coming in their mouth,
that's not a [ __ ] bro. You might as
well just wank. You might as well just
get a bit of lotion and wank, greasy, you know.
Oh, Grezy, I love that saying, you know, come random rand. Come rand.
Yeah, they don't have to swallow, but
they have it has to be in their [ __ ]
mouth. Otherwise, I'm not having it.
It's pointless. And their fake tips all
turn off. I got lots of women greasy
with like their boobs yesterday had like
no bra on that. And it's hard when
you're focused when you're trying to
[ __ ] make money and then you happen
to see that. But I'll be out this week
anyways. So, it's not a problem.
I'm going to do Wednesday cuz my
friend's coming. be Wednesday.
Wednesdays and Thursdays are the best days anyways.
That day is a [ __ ] So
you look at my timeline, we look at my timeline.
You like it? Look at my timeline, bro.
Ain't bad, ain't it?
Yeah. Put this wash on. Take this wash
out. Put this other washer on. No, Jim.
And I'll be with you later, Queeny.
I'll be with you later. Uh,
I was where I met my mama yesterday.
She took my vitamin supply away from me.
You took my [ __ ] vitamin supply away
from me, bro. [ __ ] hell.
That's not a lovely sight.
Oh, that is not a lovely sight.
That's a [ __ ] up slide, mate.
Okay, bro. I'm going. Yeah. Well, I need to um Yeah,
I'll be back later. Easy. Ciao.