Yeah, man.
Just having a quick breakfast before
hitting the gym. How you doing, man? Yeah, buddy.
I just Forsaken so [ __ ] late.
It's down here. Man
have some piggies and then you
come on man
supposed to be not [ __ ] standard.
Let's find out. I guess
[ __ ] bastard, bro. Lovely, lovely vehicle.
on your mercen. May
never mind that. Where's my bloody breakfast?
What is that problem with the internet?
Seems to be
Yeah, I gave that 19y old what for today, God.
[ __ ] hate her.
Think I [ __ ] hate her more than
[ __ ] to be honest. [ __ ] h she is. Oh, from sunshine.
Still waiting. Still waiting. Still work.
What's going to happen is I'm going to
eat it and then I'm going to have to wait till
like a little while. So I'll have a walk
around cuz can't go [ __ ] gym straight
up. Dude, [ __ ] everywhere. So, yeah.
Come on, man.
Why is it so busy today, man? It's a
[ __ ] Sunday. I'm tired as [ __ ]
So busy today. Why is it so busy?
I hope you guys Okay. [Music]
Hey, bro. [ __ ]
done some grafting yesterday, bro. Made
some uh decent money yesterday.
[ __ ] me. I went out I went everywhere,
mate. Everywhere. This 19year-old, bro,
is it's pissing me off, bro. I told her,
you message me again, I'm going to come
on your [ __ ] mom's door. I told her,
bro, she's pissing me off. She's trying
to say, oh, you're I was like, you're
the one with autism. You're the one with
mental health problems, bro. Like,
you're the one with these problems.
That's why you keep blocking me and
unblocking me. Like, [ __ ] off, bro.
Yeah. Why am I this? Why am I that? I
like, listen, bro, you're single
yourself. She's like, "Oh, no. I'm not
I'm speaking to five people." I said,
"You're speaking to five people, but
you're begging me for money. I'm not
giving you no money. [ __ ] off." I told
her straight, "I'm not giving you no
money." Yeah. You all vulture. If you're
talking to five people, go get money off
them, bro. What the [ __ ] are you
messaging me for?
The 19year-old. I hate her, bro. I hate
her. I actually hate her. She's turned
into a right [ __ ] And I said, "If
you message me again, I'm coming your
mom's gone. So you better hope you got
brothers or someone." Like, "Leave me
the [ __ ] alone."
Like, "Leave me the [ __ ] alone, bro."
I hate her, bro. Oh, you're going to
you're going to laugh at this as well. Yeah.
Where the [ __ ] is my breakfast? Listen,
you're going to laugh at this. Yeah. And
then she was just being a [ __ ] She's
just being a complete utter [ __ ] So I
just said I don't want to talk to you anymore. Bye-bye.
I didn't Oh, because I wouldn't give her
money. She's like, "Oh, can you give me
money?" I said, "No." I said, "If you
come, I can borrow you money. I'm not
just going to give you money, but you
can run away with it." And then she was
just being assy about it.
What? What am I your ATM or something,
bro? Like, [ __ ] off. I'm not giving you
no money. You can [ __ ] off, mate.
I hate her, bro.
How you ever going to save and do
things? It's my money. I'm not giving
you nothing. Go away, bro. Move. [ __ ] idiot.
Always wanting money, bro. Like, I hate it.
We're giving you no money. You're
speaking to five people. Yeah.
Don't [ __ ] with me in it. What the [ __ ]
What? Cuz I won't give you money.
You're that broke. You can't even [ __ ]
You can't even [ __ ] top up your
oyster. Allow it, bro. Cuz you're trying
to talk to me. Oh, yeah. Catch, you're
going to laugh at this. Yeah. So, the
other day, yeah, I was out and I was
like, I really wanted a [ __ ] So, I
was like, oh, let me just come back to
my area and get a [ __ ] Yeah. So, I
went to this to this escort house
and she said, um, oh yeah, we can give
you a [ __ ] but you can't come in our
mouth. And I was like, "Okay, I don't
want it then because I might as well
just masturbate myself if if if you
can't finish in someone's mouth. You
might as well just masturbate. What the
fuck?" And then she was being like
really assy about it. And her friend was
being assy about it. I was like, "I'm
not doing that." So then I had to
message this escort that I knew from
before. Do you know the one I told you
about before? Obviously, she moved area.
So I had to go all the way to [ __ ]
Wembley. I said, "I'm getting a [ __ ]
[ __ ] today, man. I'm getting a
[ __ ] today." So, I went all the way
to Wembley, which is like the furthest
away from me, and then I left my keys there.
What a [ __ ] day I've had. That's what
I said when I came back. Uh, just doing
some grafting yesterday, Joe. I done a
lot of grafting, man. Made some good money. Yeah,
but I'll tell you one thing. You're
lying to yourself if you say, "Oh,
working's good. Working's good." You're
lying to yourself, man. working. He
said, "And what I think with these
people on here, yeah, is when they hate
people on benefits, when they hate
people on benefits, it's because they
want to be on benefits themselves." And
I I've grafted the past couple of days,
so I know exactly what I'm talking
about. It's exactly what I knew it was
going to be as well. Your problems will
get worse because all you think about is women.
All you think about is women and sex.
So, how can you work when that's all you
think about? Yeah, but
you see all these [ __ ] sexy women. I
didn't speak I don't speak to them
anymore cuz they're all the same. But
like in terms of like the way they look,
I had to bin this 19 off as well. Um you know,
I had to bin this um 19 I had to bin
this 19year-old off. She's a proper
[ __ ] She was asking me for money. Yeah.
She was asking me for money. Yeah. And I
was like, I'm not just going to send you
money. if you want money, you can come
here and I will lend you money. And then
she started being all ass. She's like,
"Oh, you're so autistic." I said,
"You're autistic, man. Look at what you
do. You block me. Unblock me. Block me.
Unblock me. Have you looked at yourself,
bro? Who the [ __ ] are you talking to?
Cuz you're not [ __ ] talking to me
like that." Oh, cuz I wouldn't give her
money. I was like, "And you're talking
about single people." I said, "You are
single. You're a slag as well." She'd
not single. I'm speaking to five people.
My point stands. You're a slag and
you're single. Then she was trying to
say about how um I like if you're
speaking to five people.
Yeah. If you're speaking to five people
um if you're speaking to five people, you're [ __ ]
you're Why are you asking me for money?
You're speaking to five people. I'm not
giving you money.
And the other day I was supposed to go
to where she was. And then as I was on
my way, she's like, "Oh, don't come." I
was like, "You literally told me to
come. Now I've got to do a U-turn." So I
I just told her I'd rather keep my
dignity. I don't want to talk to her.
She was all right like a year ago, even
like 7 months ago, but the cluty
behavior just got worse and worse and
worse. Where the [ __ ] is my breakfast? I
ordered it 10 minutes ago.
So the the behavior has just got worse
and worse and worse. So she can [ __ ] herself now.
I'm done with the women in this country.
I'm gone next week anyways. So
I've literally done everything to get
away from these westernized women and
you were becoming the very thing that I didn't want
this to come to you attitude behavior entitlement
and it got worse and worse and worse and
worse and worse and worse and worse. See
when they're 18 they don't really know
much. You see
they don't really know any different but
then they just turn into [ __ ] So [ __ ] awesome.
I ordered this breakfast and I don't
know where it is.
[ __ ] I want to put some piggies down my throat.
I was where I met my mommy yesterday.
Cactus. I was where I met my mama.
I actually know the video as well. It's
sick views, man. So yeah,
she ain't getting nothing, mate. She
ain't getting nothing. for you. I have
to go all the way to Wembley to get an
escort cuz it was one I used before. Imagine that.
I said to her, "If you message me again,
I'm going to come in your door. If you
don't leave me alone, I'm going to come
in your door." She said, "I'm going to
call the police." I said, "You can call
the police. I don't give a [ __ ] I'm
asking you to [ __ ] leave me alone." Yeah.
So, no, I'm all right, bro. I'm good.
and then what's going to happen is if
you send the money, she's just not going
to meet you. Then it's going to be send
me more money and send me more money and
send me more money. Like, bro, ask your
[ __ ] mom for money, bro. Don't ask me
for money. I'm not giving you nothing.
I don't know how much she wanted, but
she was asking for money, bro. Like, who
the [ __ ] does she think she is, bro?
They're all the same. You know what? I
was thinking about this earlier, Joe.
They literally are all the same, aren't
they? Like, I don't care about anymore.
I'm leaving. But I'm literally telling
you, bro, that they literally are all
the same. They have the same attitude,
the same entitlement. There's literally
not one good woman in this in in a
westernized country. And I and I'll say
it out loud cuz it's the truth. So,
it's um there's literally not one. I've
never met one. Never met one.
So, I'm I'm still to be proven wrong,
but I don't think I'll ever be proven
wrong because they literally are just
all the same. They're [ __ ] idiots,
man. They're just They're just [ __ ]
Nope. You can't get a good woman. They
don't They don't exist if they're in their 50s. Nope.
In Unless they're in their 50s, there's
no such thing. So,
one just walk past me now.
And and it doesn't work like, oh, if if
you if someone can find a woman, you can
find a woman. That's not the way the
world works, unfortunately. Guess what?
I've literally traveled I cycled 100
miles yesterday. I bet your ass can't do
it. I bet you can't do it. I cycled 100
miles yesterday and I bet you any money
you can't do it. So, if you want to go
by that logic, bro, we can go by that logic.
I can go abroad by myself. Maybe you
can't. So, [ __ ] off, man. That's what I
said to her. [ __ ] off.
I'm waiting for this breakfast. I'm just
um I'm having some nice pigs today. See,
when my friend asked me, "What do you
have for breakfast?" I just say a load of pigs.
Where the [ __ ] is this breakfast, bro?
For real. What the [ __ ]
They better give me what I ordered. I
don't want chips. See, I had to go all
the way to Wembley cuz I wanted the
[ __ ] So, yeah.
And that's where I knew one was because
she moved from the area. So, and I left
my keys there as well. So, I got to get
some more keys cut.
I just told her I don't want to give her any money.
She's just trying to throw insults.
Never had autism in my life, mate. Trust
me, I wouldn't be able to do what I do
if I had autism. And I don't really give
a [ __ ] whether I have it or or I don't
have it. I know I don't. She doesn't
even [ __ ] know me, bro. Do you know
how many parts she's like? She's [ __ ] up, bro.
Everyone's got all to by the sounds of it. Yeah.
Yeah. She's just self projecting. She's
the one that cuts her arms. She's the
one that's got mental health problems.
She's the one that blocks and unblocks
people and then messages them. I told
her, "Don't unblock me. I blocked her."
I said, "You message me again. I'm I'm
coming on your door." That's it. I'm
coming on your mom's door, bro.
Yeah, cuz they're self projecting.
Yeah, they're not trolls on here.
They're just self-reflecting spastics.
Yeah, but guess what? Teachers tell
every kid they've got autism now.
How could I have autism when I've been
with normal women? I've got friends that
are normal people. How could I possibly
have autism? What trait of autism could
I possibly have?
Yeah. Literally. Yeah. What? Okay. Let's
let's let's put let's put it let's put
it realistically. Yeah. I don't date
spastics like that virgin. Never dated a
[ __ ] Never been with a [ __ ] All
of my friends are normal. What trait of
autism could I possibly have?
There's literally there's there's
there's no way because somebody that's
got autism is somebody like Virgin Boy
that could only target vulnerable
people, that can only go to certain
events, that can only do certain things.
Thank you, buddy. Yeah. Cheers, man.
Where's the egg, bro?
What the [ __ ] The guy just gave me a
breakfast with no egg.
So anyways, that's what I was saying is
what trait of autism could I possibly have?
She's talking about herself. Never had
autism in my [ __ ] life and no one
else had ever said it.
The guy gave me a a breakfast with no egg.
What the [ __ ] Yeah, she's self projecting.
You think I'm going to take it from
somebody that cuts themselves,
right? Somebody that cuts themselves,
right? And I said, "Stop calling me
mate. You're no mate of mine. Stop
calling me mate." I had to tell her
about a million times. How do you How do
you give a breakfast without a mad? I didn't
You didn't notice there was no eggs in the breakfast.
Doesn't even make sense, bro. Okay.
Thank you. Anyways,
he said he didn't notice that there was
no egg, which doesn't even make any
sense, but anyways. Sorry.
She's self projecting. Never had autism
in my life.
She must be having herself confused.
Just cuz someone's not a troll doesn't mean that [Music]
Thank you very much. Goodbye.
I hate you, bro.
You know what I hate about London? Yeah.
I was riding on a pavement yesterday.
Was like, "Oh, something about a
pavement pavement." I was like, "Yeah,
all right, mate. Act big when you're not
with [ __ ] four your friends, big
man." That's what I said. I said, "Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah. All right. You keep
acting big when you're with four
people." He said, that's what I said to
him as well. I said, "Have the same
attitude when you're by yourself and
you're not before your [ __ ] Jack
the lad mates, [ __ ] faggot." That's
what I said to him as well.
Proper proper [ __ ] Like you get
these white guys, right? And they'll be
in a group of three or four and they
only start when they're in groups.
Americans do it as well. [ __ ]
They're absolute [ __ ] Americans do
it as well. They used to do it in
O'Neals. They wait until they're in
their little group before they start a
fight with someone. [ __ ] [ __ ]
They never do it when they're by themselves. [ __ ]
You get a lot of [ __ ] in this
country, bro. I notic that.
Don't even need to cut though.
Don't even need to cut.
I'm not telling my business on here.
M. This will get the muscles nice and strong.
No, no, no.
I love bacon, guys. I love bacon. I love [ __ ] [ __ ] love piggies.
That's why I don't hate. That's why I
don't hate. Please, Grezy. They're my breakfast.
They're my breakfast every morning. Why
the How can I hate on someone I eat? We
have this love hate relationship, but I
can never hate him too much, bro.
They're my breakfast. Listen, bro.
I went to Toby. Yeah.
Two days ago. And you know, you can fill
up as much as you want. I had seven
slices of bacon, two sausages, and then
eggs as no word of a lie, bro. I had
seven slices of bacon. Not Not even
joking, bro. And I cobbled that up.
So, do you think the virgin will ever
get laid with you? I think he'll die a virgin. Me?
I reckon he'll [ __ ] die a virgin. I [Music]
reckon he'll die one. I'm I'm not even
saying it. I swear to God.
If you're 31 and still a [ __ ] virgin,
that's something to be concerned about. [Music]
Oh, this is lost, man.
Would you prefer sausages or bacon? I
must say I prefer bacon but need to wait
about an hour
then I'll go to the gym.
You can't go as soon as you ate. But I
like to have a big breakfast before I
work out. So
yeah, I bet you like sausages.
I bet you like sausages, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Of course you do. Push it.
I'm not back to square one. I'm going to
try that next week.
I'm not back to square one at all, mate.
So, I'm I'll be I'll be out here soon.
So, it's not my problem anymore, mate.
Why do you think he always calls people
a virgin cactus? Because he's the
biggest virgin himself. He he know all
the telltale signs. You know when he
used to do these videos and he'd mumble
under his breath, "Oh, sounds like
something a virgin." I said, "Yeah,
you're the biggest virgin, so you know
all about what they're like, what they
do because you are one yourself.
So you know from your own experiences
about virgins being the biggest one
yourself." I love that. I love that. I
love roasting that little virgin.
But that's why I always go to the police
because you can't take the Peter B. [ __ ] virgin.
[ __ ] virgin son.
Proper [ __ ] virgin is he copy mate.
Nah, bro. I'm done with her. I will not
have somebody talk to me like that, bro.
I'd rather have nothing. I'd rather have
You're not talking to me like that, bro.
No way. And I'm not your [ __ ] mate. I
don't know how many times I had to say
to her, "I'm not your mate. I'm not your
mate. I'm not your [ __ ] mate, bro.
So stop calling me mate when I'm not your mate.
What your mate?
No practice cuz what about USA is he?
What about USA is he bro?
Somebody's pitch me. Look at them arms,
bro. I'm going to work them out in a
bit. They're [ __ ] huge, bro.
I'll be with the T will come tomorrow, bro.
Ready to [ __ ] someone up. Old man.
today, but I have to
be up today. I'm sorry. Oh,
I know. I don't understand that. Yeah. Crazy.
She's talking about herself.
All of the people that I've ever met.
Yeah. They've never said I have autism.
Never. Not one person. They said, "Oh,
you might have ADHD." Um,
some people said you might have ADHD or
something, but they never ever said
autism. Never. Out of all the people I
met in real life, no one's ever said it.
Literally, no one has ever said it. If I
had a few people saying it to me, then I
be okay. But no one has ever said I have
autism. No one. Only the self
projections on here and her.
They're self projectors, bro.
It's like when the virgin calls people
virgin. He's a virgin himself. Watch out.
What is that?
Where the P?
Where did the pies go? They went They
went in my mouth. M lovely.
You see a nice brown
in my mouth.
Nom nom nom nom.
Yeah, I've never had that one before.
Oh, that Muslim one messaged me
yesterday. You know the one from a few months ago
with the Indian trying to say that she's
Muslim, but then she's she's in she's
she's drinking in a nightclub. You
remember that one from a few months ago?
Oh, is it? He's talking about himself.
That's nice, bro. I'm not even going to
watch it because
they talk about themselves every day.
So, this this community don't bother me,
bro. This is why you don't really see me
much on here cuz they all self-reflect.
We all know all of these people on here
who look like [ __ ] Jamie Thompson.
They're all fat self projectors. That's
why whatever they do,
that's why whatever they do, it doesn't
bother me because they're just talking about themselves.
Obviously, it's no good for their mental
health and stuff, but yeah. But yeah.
Yeah. Literally, man.
Look at that.
You know my piggies. Oh,
I'm stuck mama.
But USA is he never unblocked. Lucy Cactus.
She never unblocked.
She's a proper comp.
But yeah, if you notice over the years,
they're they're pretty much all the
same, which is why I don't talk to them anymore.
It's like when virgin boys say you don't
know all women. I know more [ __ ]
women than you. You [ __ ] virgin. You
[ __ ] [ __ ] virgin son. I know more
than you. Been with more women than you.
Slept with more women than you. Met more
women than you. I'm the expert. You know
what I'm saying? practice.
I don't have autism and I'm not talking
about this anymore.
I'm I'm moving conversation. And this is
what you need to do well on this
community. Yeah. They try to bring up
the same [ __ ] over and over again or old
[ __ ] over and over again. So, you just
have to move on. Stop it. I don't have
autism head. If you think I do, that's
on you. I don't care. End your story. Simple.
That's That's it. That's what you do
with these people.
Anyways, moving on.
See what I'm saying? Cactus. Yeah. Easy, bro.
Rest for a little bit. Go for a little walk,
get some water, go and smash this
[ __ ] workout out, bro.
before you end up like Lord J.
I need to get a haircut at some point,
but I haven't been going out, but I
haven't really bothered to be honest with you. Yeah, man.
Even my shoulders are looking bigger to be fair.
They're looking good, bro. [ __ ]
Yeah, look at my hair. My my hair and
beards getting along, bro. Look,
I know. That's what I hate about the
gym, bro. I hate about central London. I
hate it everywhere, bro. It's [ __ ] And
there's no point in talking to them
because they're just all the same.
That's the [ __ ] up thing about it is
when you talk to them, they're all the
same. So, they're all NPCs.
Same women, same guys, same [ __ ]
and groups starting [ __ ] with people.
It's the same atmosphere in this country. So,
but it doesn't matter. But I'll get a
workout done. I need to start changing
the times I go to the gym.
Yeah. I need to cuz it's like it's
forcing you to do it. But even if you do
it, there's no good that can come out of
it because it's just going to be the
same. I have boyfriend number. They
don't reply. T. So
there's no good that can come out of it.
There's literally no good that can come
out of speaking to a woman. Literally none. So
yeah, rest my stomach for a bit, go for
a walk, hit the gym, go outside, have a milkshake,
and then just chill today, man.
[ __ ] [ __ ] me.
Grafting. Grafting. Grafting.
I might go out on Wednesday. My friend's
coming, so I might go out on Wednesday.
If the weather's nice, it doesn't really
matter what day you go out.
Yeah, I might go out on Wednesday. [ __ ] it. Yeah.
Yeah, I already have one. Look. Well,
it's brown at the minute, but it's going
to in two days it's going to go brown.
Look, in two days it's going to go brown.
Yeah, two days it's going to go brown, bro.
And then I done three missions on GTA.
I'm going to try and complete that game
today, bro. But don't know if I can.
But I got some Yeah, man.
My shoulders are looking bigger, ain't it?
Oh, feel bigger, too. All them stakes,
baby. It's all them stakes.
Yeah, my beard's getting long.
My beard's getting long, bro.
Need to go gym, have a shower, get nice clothes.
Don't know if it's laney today. I don't know.
I do fancy like a good sleep. I might not sure.
I might go see Ley, bro.
Yeah, bro. Give this two days. It's
going to go brown.
It's going to go brown, bro. I'm tired.
At least I made some pizza money yesterday. It's good.
I don't get tired, you know. I think
there's something wrong with me, bro. I
don't get tired. I actually think
don't get tired. I'm just like do it all
again. I hurt my hand, though. Look.
Yeah, I hurt my hand, bro.
all the time, bro. And it's exactly why
I I said that as well. I knew that was
going to happen. I even said, "Yeah,
soon as you start this working [ __ ] all
you got to think about is women. It's
going to make your problems worse."
Like, if I had it my way, I'd never work
a day in my life ever again. I'm just
saving some money and then once I've
saved, I'm just going to try to get used
to living off that. I never ever want to work
cuz all you think about is women. All
you see is women.
And it makes you depressed as well. And
I had some dark thoughts today, the
other day as well. I was like thinking
of people's funerals and [ __ ] And I'm
thinking, what the [ __ ] is going into
me, bro? So, it's like if I was a
security, if I was working in security,
I couldn't do it. I couldn't do it, bro.
Cuz all you're going to see is these
good-looking women, and there's nothing
you can do about it. So, yeah.
Yeah. I mean, you're not you're not
missing out on anything, though. But
yeah, it makes you feel like it. Yeah,
it's just the same [ __ ] All you see is
these women that are not wearing bras as
well. I saw some sexy ones yesterday,
bro. [ __ ] hell. Some sexy ones, man.
But there's no point. They're all the
same. So that's why I don't even talk to them. [Music]
But yeah, if I had it my way, I'm never
working again, bro. after I've saved
enough money up this [ __ ] bro.
Anyone that tells you otherwise, they're in denial.
They're in denial, mate.
I would rather sit on benefits and get a
grand a month.
Yeah. Then [ __ ] work and get two and
a half grand a month. It's that bad,
bro. Like, what I'm saying? I'm not even
joking. Swear to God, bro. I swear to
God. I'm even joking. Yep.
Sexy, bro. So, I might go out on Wednesday and
give it a little well.
Give it a little Well, yeah, man.
See, why can't these people on YouTube
show their face?
Oh, they're all fat and ugly.
That's why they wolf fat and ugly. Yeah, man.
Country is a joke, though. Look at the
[ __ ] look at the [ __ ] escort thing
happen all the way to Emily.
N that's not looking right, bro.
But what would have happened if what
would have happened if I approached them, Cactus?
It's like you're damned if you do and
you're damned if you don't because if
you try to talk to them, they're just
they're never going to show you any different.
They're never going to show you any
different to be any different. Nothing.
They won't ever [Laughter]
get the chicken ide. So yeah,
I have to go to again some [ __ ]
No, even even if it was your own money,
just working [ __ ] working this [ __ ]
Just working [ __ ] It's not about money
on rent. Obviously, that is that, but
I'm saying even without that is [ __ ]
man. It is [ __ ] you know.
I was lucky to have that [ __ ] house for [ __ ]
that house for a few years. I made some
good money on that. So, I got some
savings and stuff. So, but still.
Yeah, man. I was lucky to have that house, bro.
Imagine that 3 years of your life you
didn't have to work, go out every week,
travel around the country. It was sick, bro. Sick.
And obviously, yeah, it gets boring if
you don't work. But then obviously
that's why you have hobbies like the gym
or obviously you can go to the gym.
You can go to the gym and [ __ ]
Yeah, you're taking a piss out of me in
a cactus. I know you're taking a piss,
mate. It's the truth, though.
Look at me, bro. I'm I'm getting a good
body now. Got some money. I'm going to
wear some nice clothes and I'm still
going to get the same [ __ ]
You're still going to get the same old [ __ ] So,
[ __ ] hell, bro. It's catching up with
me now. The tiredness.
[ __ ] me, bro.
But it's worth it. [Music]
At least it's cooling down a little bit.
some cold water. Yeah,
they're just not interested in this country.
Tactus, now I'll never know.
Now I'll never know.
That cactus. Now I'll never know. [Music] Yeah, bro.
I'm serious. If she unblocks me again,
I'm going to go on her [ __ ] door. Bro,
you notice my little eyes are tired now.
Is it Grezy? My little eyes
look tired now. It
want to go [ __ ] I want to go to
sleep, man. I want to go [ __ ] dead. [Music]
But I can't cuz I need to do this chill.
I haven't been for two days.
[ __ ] me. I'm knackered, bro. It's like
the hangovers. Yeah, they catch up with
you in the day. You think you're okay,
but then it does catch up with you.
Have you noticed my shoulders are
a bit bigger?
Have you noticed? It's getting It's
getting better, isn't it?
Um I saw her mom. I didn't meet her mom
cuz when she lost her phone, she come to
my mom's and her mom was her mom was with her.
I think it's quite a bit bigger in it.
Haven't been for a few days.
So yeah, just view
[ __ ] I'm going to [ __ ] fall
asleep, man. [ __ ]
got people drinking Guinness and everything.
People are drinking [ __ ] Guinness and [ __ ] man.
I'll go on her [ __ ] door, bro. I
don't give a [ __ ] She can bring any man
she wants. I'm not ass. I don't care. I
stood up to three people yesterday, so I
don't give a [ __ ] bro.
They always start when they're in
groups. These people, don't they, Grey?
these Americans, these these people from
Essex, they love to start when they're in groups,
but when they're by themselves, they
[ __ ] themselves. Have you noticed? Yeah. [ __ ] cowards.
They're the big man in groups in it, but
by themselves, they're all [ __ ] [ __ ] idiots. [Music] I'm tired. Yeah.
You remember USA? So why did my mommy
leave me? Katus, why did my mommy leave
Why did my mommy leave me?
USA is you. Why did my Why did my mommy
leave me? For what reason?
I'll keep blocking you till
you remember. I'll keep blocking you
till we're dead in the ground. What the [ __ ]
I'll keep blocking you until we're dead
in the ground. Horrible old [ __ ]
Horrible old [ __ ] man. He's a horrible
She is, man.
He's a nasty [ __ ]
Yeah, she took my she took my um she
took my milk supply from me, bro.
She took my milk supply from me.
I bet I'm making LT so proud going to
the gym. You know, when he's back here,
he's going to be like, "Oh, look. You
made some serious gains." I'll be like,
"Yep, I've been hitting the gym." So,
you're going to be like, "Um, yeah, I'm
going to make him proud, bro. I'm going
to make him proud.
I'm making you so proud of me." Oh, man.
I was [ __ ] mate. Yeah, man.
I'd love to say more stuff on here, but
you have too many jealous graphers.
People like Red Star ain't going to lie.
You know, Red Star. Let me let me tell
you something about Red Star. Uh Red
Star can never come on camera. Never.
You can post videos of my face and stuff
and screenshot where like you've made a
face, but he can never show his face in
camera cuz he's an ugly bastard. Cuz
he's an ugly [ __ ]
and they can never fat ugly [ __ ]
That's why they can never show their
face cuz they look like they look
exactly like Bob.
They look exactly like bombs. So
they can't show their face.
Yeah. I say on my secret channel. I put
everything on my secret channel. But you
have too many grasses on here. Like it's
a shame. If it was like a normal
community, then we could share more things. But
you don't want to just grass and community, bro. Yeah.
I'm falling asleep here, Grezy.
I'm actually falling asleep here, mate.
I go to JD and treat myself.
See if I see any gums or something.
So, I can spend money now. I can make
money and spend safe.
Bro, my whole hand is [ __ ] Look,
do you remember that Italian? I'm over
her now. It's a shame cuz I started to
really like her. I know she she's not my
mama like my real mama. My real mama
lives in America, but you know, it was
second best, I guess.
Fact is, I've got two mummies. One in
America and then one from Albania. I got two mummies. Two mummies.
No, I'm actually [ __ ] bro.
I need to go swimming at some point. I
ain't been swimming for years, man.
Yeah. But apparently I was too pushy
with the kisses, whatever that means.
Even though we was holding hands and
[ __ ] apparently I was too pushy with
the kisses, whatever that means. When
Nah, I'm good. I'm not I'm not saying
that autistic [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] that.
I'm [ __ ] tired, mate. I don't even
know what [ __ ] day it is, bro.
No, I'm not saying that though.
Yeah, I might treat myself. Is that okay
with you, boss?
Is that okay if I go and treat myself
today, Cactus? Spend a nice £250.
Is that okay with you, boss?
Imagine that, mate.
Straight straight in the gym, out the
gym. Nice shower, fresh gums, pump body.
That's a lovely sight, is it?
It's not okay with you. Oh, easy. Why not?
We got money to spend, bro. We're not
like that little virgin.
No, don't I'm not spending money, but
I might do.
[ __ ] what? Yeah.
No, I'm joking.
How you spell Thailand wrong, Grezy?
Anyways, I need to go now cuz I need to
My phone's going to die. So, and I need
the phone to get into a gym. I might see
you later. I might not. But Grezy, do
you know what? I'm going to start
calling you from now on. I'm going to
start calling you Captain. All right,
[ __ ] my finger, bro. All right, captain.
I don't know. I like that cuz some black
guy call me in it. So, I thought, oh,
that's kind of funny, bro.
You okay, Captain?
Captain, I've never heard that one
before. Anyways, bro,
see, if if I still had USA, I wouldn't
need a milkshake at the end of the gym.
I would just need to, you know what,
music? I've got to spend like £1
something or two pound in McDonald's
after to get a milkshake when obviously
if I had USA Izzy then I could just feed from her
I would I would be twice as big now. I'd
be like this instead of this instead of
this I'd be like this. Yeah, man.
Anyways, I'm out of here. So, I'll see
you later or maybe tomorrow, whenever.
I'll see you when I see you.