Yo yo.
What the [ __ ]
It's too much.
Yo yo [ __ ] you now matey again today.
supposed to be today, but friends wanted
to go out Wednesday, so I thought it
might be out again today
with the old tracksuit on
your team can.
What do you think?
Yeah, man. Got the old tracksuit on. Got the on
the day in the tracksuit, man. 100%.
A good old age track.
Let's put another wash on. It's good, isn't it?
Yeah. Watch. Extend it today, man. Some more.
I love this [ __ ] bro. I love this
adrenaline rush, you know. Yeah.
She turned her phone on.
Honestly, mate, what a [ __ ] day I had yesterday.
What a [ __ ] day I had. You know, one
of them days you just come back.
What a [ __ ] day I had.
Yeah, that was one of them [ __ ] days.
I think it's probably my last day. uh
forever for a very long time. I'm not
doing any street approaches. I'm just
doing them in a club
because of um I'll be bothered.
Go get a pizza soon. Go out. Get on a drink.
Need a graft tomorrow.
It's all just a bit of fun.
I think so.
some serious wonder man. Yeah,
I'm [ __ ] cher man.
I think it looks pretty cool to be honest.
Yeah, I think it looks quite cool.
I still can't get over the school thing
yesterday. [ __ ] it. Over it.
That's a [ __ ] madness.
I don't know about that school. Yeah.
Head on as well. So looking good.
I think it's better
and cubs cuz they don't know how to
socialize unless they're drunk cuz cuz
their uh dependency on social media,
their dependency to social media, they
don't know how to um communicate.
But obviously at least with when they
drink, they can. Yeah.
another way to look at it as well.
That's another way to look at it, man.
If you want to be technical,
I can't wait to leave though, mate. I can't wait.
[ __ ] virgin boy needs to come with
me. He'll finally lose his virginity and get laid. [ __ ] hell.
Opposites. I drink in a week day.
Drink in a week day and then
drink in a weekday then
basically work on the weekends.
could be [ __ ] on the weekend. Too
many [ __ ] [ __ ]
Know what I'm saying?
Yeah, there's too many [ __ ] man. Yeah, I
for some reason I still Yeah.
Oops. Wi-Fi problem there.
Still prefer this phone. You know,
I can't do Saturday cuz I need to go off Saturday.
I'd rather make money Saturday than [ __ ]
I'd rather make golf and go out Saturday
to be fair.
I'm gonna do it today, but I will do it.
What the [ __ ]
That's basically it.
Oh, hey. Okay. Yeah,
that whole escort thing is like how can
you offer a service? Yeah, you're
offering a service for [ __ ] money and
then say like you don't want to do it. I
mean it would make sense if they say
they don't give [ __ ] [ __ ]
They just outright say I don't give
[ __ ] then okay but
but for them to say yeah we'll give you
a [ __ ] but you can't finish in in in
in my mouth. What? What the [ __ ] is the
point of that? Like, how many people
with glow job benefits would say yes to
that? I'm telling you right now, none
of them say yes to be honest. I can't
see many saying yes to that.
That's [ __ ] that is mental. You know,
when have you ever seen all of the video
the porn videos you've watched in your
life? When have you ever ever seen
somebody get a [ __ ] and have to finish themsel?
That is insane, bro.
Like that's why I traveled past Wembley
was nothing. So yeah,
that is insane. But really is
that is that is unheard of, bro.
I don't think no normal woman would ever
say that either. Give [ __ ] don't.
It's not, well, yeah, we give you a
round job, but you can't finish this in
our [ __ ] mouth. That's [ __ ]
madness. It's like they're taking a
piss. It's like, do you know what? Yeah.
If if anyone else heard that. Yeah.
You'd actually think they're taking a
piss. Like if someone said that to you.
Yeah. If somebody else said that to you,
you would actually think that they're
taking a piss.
A liar. you been there for that [ __ ]
with this? I actually think they would.
I had to say so. Yeah.
Yeah. I would have stayed with that 20
year old, but she's too much of a [ __ ] now.
Yeah, she's too much of a too much of a
[ __ ] Well, to be honest, the [ __ ]
behavior was displayed from about December time
and now she's just a complete. So,
it's not good.
Yeah, man. One second. He's a one of
Oh, [ __ ] hell, man.
Yeah, you actually think they're taking a piss. Yeah.
When I leave, I'm going to be feeling
sorry for 90% of people in this country. Frank.
Good old Frank.
I'm going to be gambling no more now to the football.
Yeah. Only time I'll be gambling now is in football.
This doesn't start for another two months. Yep. [ __ ]
Also, most escorts have faked tips as well.
But I can go out today, [ __ ] send it.
I got three numbers from yesterday and I
know that I've tried. I can safely say,
"Okay, I tried." I can go doing it on
tried, but I can't [ __ ] help rude
people whenever I [ __ ] go, you know.
[ __ ] that, bro. It's [ __ ] madness.
I need to get my jet.
Yeah. So that's where we're at.
Oh, you can't, man.
I'm getting that phone next month.
[ __ ] expensive [ __ ] Yeah,
that's [ __ ] expensive, bro.
Go for a drink today. Hopefully they
play some bangers.
You would have thought so, mate. [ __ ]
All this thing.
Yeah, probably. Yeah, even though it's
going to be really expensive.
Like 2,000. I think this one is actually
going to be about two fucking,000.
[ __ ] hell, man. I'll be grafting
tomorrow. I'm going out today, Sunday
again. I got three yesterday. be
grafting tomorrow, be grafting Saturday,
and probably be rafting Sunday as well.
So, got nothing there to do in it. So, why not?
Yeah, I just be grafting straight, bro.
Yeah. Got the Got the kit ready, bro.
Got the kit ready. Got the tracky. Got the haircut.
Yeah, man. I'm a bit tired, but
Oh, well, that's impossible.
Really? Well, that's impossible because
I don't bike around London, so that's
completely impossible. Matey, did that
guy still stalking people, man? That fat
ugly bastard. Is he still stalking
people? What the [ __ ]
Is he still stalking people? The fat loser.
We're not talking about fat loss. Anyways,
fat double chin loser.
Anyways, moving on.
Yeah, good good friend, bro. Moving on now. Uh Yeah.
[ __ ] thought it's going to be hard,
isn't it? You just spend that money like that. But
yeah, it's [ __ ] in it.
[ __ ] way soon as well, mate. Yeah. Man.
Yeah. He's such a weirdo, man. I think
he's jealous of me. That Jamie guy. He's
definitely definitely jealous. He's done
it with LT as well. He's also stalked
LT. Yeah, that guy is jealous, bro.
People like him. Yeah. They hate
themselves so much. That's why they get
obsessed with other people so he doesn't
feel like they hate their lives as much.
Yeah, bro. That guy's got [ __ ] life. All
he does is talk men on the internet.
He's a weirdo. Like guys trying to tell me how
I have everything he wants. I've got a
wife. I've got this. I've got that. I've
got this. I've got that. But you're
stalking me on YouTube every day and I
don't even think of you. Ah, [ __ ]
Look, you know these people right that
come on him every day talk about
people's looks. I bet you know I'm wrong.
Why else are other people obsessed?
Well, well, there's two reasons. They
either want to [ __ ] you or they're
jealous of you.
There's no there's there's no other explanation
cuz they claim they got better lives.
So, I mean, they're obsessed. They're
obsessed cuz I'm better. I'm better
looking than them and I'm not fat like
them and I'm not skinned like them. It's
pretty self-explanatory, you know. Yeah.
Everything a virgin so obsessed.
Yeah, they're very obsessed. These
people on here, they're weirdos, bro. I
don't even really come on much anymore. Very obsessed.
What do you think of that escort thing,
M? That was weird, bro.
That was so weird. The escal thing was
so weird, bro.
I actually think it's like they're
actually trolling you
cuz you can't offer services. It's like
me. Yeah. I'm about to sell this [ __ ]
white washing machine and then somebody
comes and says, "Oh, actually I don't
like the color of your eyes, so I'm not
selling it to you." It doesn't make sense.
What? [ __ ] There's got to be no woman
in the world. I know people that don't
swallow, but I've never heard somebody
give a [ __ ] and not finish. I've
never heard of it.
I've heard the people don't know to it,
but that's not a big deal. Anyways,
that's not a big deal. [ __ ] it. Anyways,
the stands now, even if I were to use an
escort, I've got to travel [ __ ] an
hour, an hour and a half.
This country stinks, bro. It's really bad.
This country is so bad, bro. It's
actually really, really bad.
So yeah, it's actually bad though, but I
don't care. Like I [ __ ] just going out
and having a drink and doing it anyways.
No street approaches, no nothing, bro.
[ __ ] that. I can't be in a bad mood
tomorrow. I need to see do some serious crafting, man.
I've never heard of that, bro. So it's
even getting harder. All of it's gotten
harder now. The 19, 20 year old, she's
20 now, she's she's a [ __ ] now. The
escorts are all [ __ ] entitled.
Like, and then you obviously got these
[ __ ] on the street that don't even
[ __ ] talk. So, what the [ __ ]
Yeah, it's hard. This country is too hard, bro.
Doesn't matter. And I learned a few
different things, right? Well, there's
two things I learned. Well, one of the ones were
um all the excuses we used to hear. Oh,
you live with your mommy. Oh, you don't
have a job. Oh, you're ditch. Your dad,
bro, I go to the gym four times a week.
Work and I don't live with my mom. What
can you say about me? Nothing.
All excuses. What are these things? It's
like what Pat mustard used to say. It's
all excuses like you live with your
mommy or you're not working or you got a
beer belly or whatever [ __ ] excuse.
It's all just excuses
and I'm living proof of it, bro. I'm
independent as can be.
Yeah. And you still get the same [ __ ]
It's obvious, bro. I didn't need to do
all this [ __ ] to know, you know.
But I've never known. Um,
and I even told my 20-year-old about it
when she was 19. She said, "What?" I
said, "Yeah, they they say that they can
give you a [ __ ] but you can't finish
in the mouth." And she just looked
at me like, "What the fuck?" Cuz I was
thinking, "What the [ __ ] It's not normal.
So yeah, that's how it is, bro.
But you know what? Yeah, I I couldn't
approach for like four or five days, you
know, and I'm thinking, what the [ __ ]
Am I going back to being like 19 again?
Why can't I approach? And I was
physically and mentally exhausted by it.
I said, I couldn't even do it, bro.
was mentally and physically exhausted by
the whole bad experiences. There's so
much to this [ __ ] you know, that meets the eye. Yeah.
Yeah. But see that 20-year-old, she'd be
okay if she wasn't a [ __ ] She's a complete [ __ ]
I'm not dealing with there actually, but
titled entitled entitled
I've had more women than you've ever
had. McFly cook
your basement way more women than you
ever had. More than you ever will have.
More than you will ever have.
Let me guess. You're married.
Yeah. So, we're aiming for another three
today. I've got a live in the club
and I'm only doing them drunk today. I'm
not doing them so I can't be live with
it. I just want to say yeah.
So, basically only two options are
escorts or Thailand.
Well, actually it's not Thailand. It's
anywhere in Asia. depending on what you
want. That seems to be the only way,
Matty. It's either Thailand or Asia.
Sorry, Asia or um escorts.
Uh uh uh uh uh uh. That's the way it
seems. Buddy, bad bad.
Everyone pays for sex. It most
definitely does count. Don't make me
laugh at these people. Yeah, I
understand the whole like some people
like escort, some people don't. It
depends on like the reason. So, there's
no right or wrong answer. But when
people try to say they don't pay for
sex, it makes me laugh. Like I used to
have this um conversation before with
Virgin Boy. I mean, yeah, there are
times when people technically get sex
for nothing, but most of the time you do
pay, but people claim they don't pay.
They'll go on these mills or buy these
drinks and buy these cocktails, buy
these mills and be like, "Well, I didn't
pay." Well, yes, you [ __ ] did. You
bought stuff. You tried to impress her
with money, which is indirectly paying.
There's been times where I've had sex
before for free.
So, and mate, it's it's not a lot of
times. Everyone pays for sex.
Everybody pays for sex. It's not It's
easy. You pay for it because you can't
get it without paying for it. Everybody
pays for it. The chances of you going
into a place and getting sex for
nothing, bro, it's not happening.
It's literally not happening. Why do you
think if you was a big Tik Tocker or Instagram,
uh, you would get women, money, status?
You're delusional, bro. You are so
delusional. Everyone pays. Okay, let me
put it this way.
Let me put it another way. Yeah, money
is going to come out your pocket before
you get [ __ ] End of. Doesn't matter
how what it is, money is going to be
coming out of your pocket before you get
[ __ ] I can tell you that for a fact. Yeah, 100%.
There's only about two times, maybe
three times where I've not paid.
It's all about normal people.
Yeah, everyone pays for sex unless
you're [ __ ] married, you know.
Uh, unless you're married, you've been
for a very long time. But I'm saying generally speaking,
90% of people pay,
you know. So,
I have no problem paying. I just don't
like the escort thing because they've
been with so many different people. You
think if somebody said to me right now,
"Oh, yeah. If you give me £200, I say
you just pick somebody out and you said
to them, I'll give you £200." Yeah.
Like, I would do it 100%. I would 100%
pay 1 million%. If it wasn't an escort,
I actually no problem with that at all.
But, everyone's different. Some people
do, some people don't. It's not a right
or wrong answer, but I definitely would.
If I could get what I wanted and I'd
have to pay for it, I would I would pay for it.
If I literally could pay for if say for
example I saw someone and every person I
saw I can pay them to get what I want,
but I'd give up and literally just do it
like twice a month. Like honestly. Yeah. Yeah, man. Remember
that early one that used to
a second. Let me reply to this guy on
Instagram. Hold on.
This guy was [ __ ] annoying me on
Instagram, bro. I had to [ __ ] roast
him. I said, "Yeah, bro. I ain't even
going to lie. I did travel on a train to
go to a proy." I admit it, bro. I did.
Cuz she sucked my dick the best ever in
my life. And I don't want no single mom
like what you've been going with. So
yeah, I will travel on a train for
somebody in their 20s. Yeah. 20, 25.
Yeah. Yeah, I will. And you can 40 and
50 year olds. Yeah. Then no one wants
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] I think this
guy's off YouTube. He's got to be off
He has got to be
that guy's got to be off YouTube, bro.
He reminds me of that mock something.
The madness madness.
I need to go get some food soon, matey.
Matey, I need to get some food soon, matey.
Matey matey matey matey matey [ __ ] my gone. Yeah.
The only reason you get asked for is
because they're in their 40s and their 50s.
That's the only getting this used up ass
that no one wants.
Yeah. that Jane messaged me on uh she
emailed me actually the other day when I
come out the gym.
He's a big [ __ ] you know. Big [ __ ]
I can't get her, bro. You know what I mean?
That as an example,
yeah, I'm saying, bro,
yeah, you can get old pictures in their
40s and 50s.
Anyone can get that, bro. There you
go. [ __ ] sit down, man.
Can't believe we do it all again. Going
out, drinking, [ __ ]
It's all just a bit of fun. Oh [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] Bro,
it's definitely trolling, bro.
definitely is. Well, he's trying to try, but
who is he? It's got to be someone off YouTube, bro.
[ __ ] bro. [ __ ] one second.
Well, I'm good. I'll be back later
anyways. Need to message these numbers
and start getting ready.
But in a bit more, I go