Y some [ __ ]
somewhere to sit today.
Just a bit quiet. I ain't going to lie.
I can definitely be
Yeah. Yeah. Just drinking this uh Coke
and flushing it out cuz I'm still kind
of hung over from yesterday.
But there's no time to be hung over. again. Yeah, man.
Really? Good for them.
Yeah, good for them, bro. But guess
what? You can't you can't show your
face, so doesn't mean anything, bro.
Your opinion means nothing because you
can't even show your face. So
I think that's the number one rule. You know,
you can't show your face.
You're in no position to talk about anyone else. Oh, [ __ ]
Fact. 83%. How is it 83%?
The [ __ ] was 85? [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] it up. [ __ ] bro.
Time 3:20. I'm I'm going to do some I'm
going to do some approach on the street soon.
My friends are coming to five, which is
looking pretty dead. So, I just do some
on the street. [Music]
Oh, they're putting the light off.
What can you hear that in the background?
You hear that in the background, bro?
That's funny as [ __ ] Oh, mate.
should have bought my other phone in the
hospital off of it. Yeah, briefly.
And you hear that lovely noise.
I want to do an approach, but there's someone here.
I want to show you boyfriend
outside cuz the signal will cut off. There's no
but in a club there definitely
and all you're going to get Yeah, boyfriend
[ __ ] annoying, bro.
Oh man, just I had to stretch my
[ __ ] NPCs, dudes.
They're all [ __ ] NPCs.
Not playing characters. [ __ ] What?
That's not good. Oh man. [Laughter]
No, no, no, no, no. Facebook.
Watch where he's going, Grezy. Cuz he if
he knocks my phone over, I'm not going
to be happy.
I'm not going to be [ __ ] happy, lad. [Music] Yeah, man.
I want this guy today. I want this
Indonesian guys today to actually
approach. I don't want to hear any
excuses as to why he can't approach. I'm saying
cuz he wants to [ __ ]
tell me. You know what I'm saying? Lots
of [ __ ] time. So, we'll see. Yeah.
I'm going to go on the street sooner and
start doing him, bro.
Cuz it's dead here and he's not going to
be here for like an hour or so.
an hour and a half. That's something we
want to do. So yeah,
wish me luck, Greezy. I'm going to need it.
You never know when you fall in bull's deep.
That one. Let's have a look.
Yeah, no approaches here. piss [ __ ] send
didn't do any because I quite frankly
could be [ __ ] like
oh [ __ ] man bro
[ __ ] legs Huh?
Oh, you open the [ __ ] door for
someone. They don't even say thank you.
[ __ ] [ __ ] man. [ __ ] hell.
You're the first ones to moan in range
when you don't do it. [ __ ] [ __ ]
And I'll come right
hope that ain't [ __ ] piss on the
[ __ ] door handle.
I hope that ain't [ __ ] piss on the
[ __ ] door handle, mate.
They ain't going to be [ __ ] happy if
that's [ __ ] piss. Yeah.
So, Grey, I'm going to go out on the
street now and do these approaches. Is
that okay with you, boss? Is that okay
Is that okay with you, boss?
I have to I have to run it by you first.
This Bob's kind of dead.
Is that okay with you, boss?
I hope that's okay with you, boss.
Because if it is, I'm going in.
Oh, it is okay with you, boss. I knew
the other day there was something that
weren't okay with you. Do you remember,
Greasy? There was something that weren't
okay with you.
Well, let me finish this beer and I'm
going to go on a stream.
Wish me luck, Greasy. I'm going in.
I'm going in, mate.
Wish me luck. You know, I've heard that
before. I've heard that quote from
somewhere before. Wish me luck. I'm going in.
Oh, I think it was something about going
out or something.
No, no, no. It was I said, "Oh, I'm
going to go out. I'm going to go out.
I'm going to go out." And I think he
said that's not okay with me, boss. Save
it for time. I'm going in
and I'll come back in about I'm going to
do about five on the street. Yeah. And then
I'm going to tell you what they say.
Cut my life.
Right. Going to finish this beer and uh
go outside and do it.
Wish me luck. Going to need it. I'm going in.