Oh [ __ ] almost [ __ ] got my phone there. [ __ ] Grezy Grey,
you never guess what I just got. Look at
Angel Greavesy joins. I know. Yellow. He
loves my live streams, man. You know,
that's a sign. What?
Better not [ __ ] spit on me, bro.
[ __ ] hell. Greasy, man. Grey grey.
Oh, bro. What the [ __ ] man?
This [ __ ] will never end. Boyfriend. Greasy.
Boyfriend. You already know, man. And
you know the madest thing is she
actually got her phone out and showed me
her boyfriend. Okay, but maybe I wanted
to be friends, you know. And and this is
what I was talking about earlier. It's
not just about relationships. It's not
just about sex. It's you could be
looking for friendship, you could be
looking for sex, you could be looking
for relationship. Whatever it is you're
looking for, you're not going to get in
this country. It doesn't matter what the
[ __ ] it is. So,
Yeah, boyfriend. She had a boyfriend apparently.
Well, she actually did, but you know,
most of them they chat [ __ ] cuz the
maths don't add up.
That one was just telling the truth. But
uh what if you wanted to be friends? I mean, you
could still be friends with someone with
your boyfriend, but
Yeah, man. No worries, man. [ __ ] me.
Just [ __ ] [ __ ] man.
You reckon I'll get any numbers today? Greasy. Yeah.
Yeah, you got to get a number, man. got numbers.
Yeah, that 70. Yeah. Yeah, bro. They've
all got boyfriends. I think
they've all got boyfriends. M
I said I was only going to do it in the
bar today. The bar in the club, but
yeah, I got bored. So don't judge.
There's no music. There's no vibe, man.
You want me to do another one on the
street? Grezy, I don't know if I can be bothered, man.
I'll do some on the street on the way to
the club. I'm not going back outside. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that, bro.
It's [ __ ] really early, is it?
I'm not going back on the street just to
come back, though. But that
[ __ ] crazy, is it? Greasy, man. What the [ __ ]
I will call some later when I'm in a
club. Yeah, I'll stay live and you can hear some.
You can hear some later.
I'll do him live, bro.
It's so bad, bro.
Well, you can watch it back. This I
agree with you. What's your What's your
opinion on this? I I don't think this is
ever going to end. Like, all jokes
aside, like we laugh about this, but I
can't see this ever ending, bro, in this
country. Like, for real, for real.
Like, I I can't see it, bro. Honestly,
I'll show you me if you want. Yeah.
Can't see I've ended though. Got the bags.
Yeah, man. I've got the as well
trying to get goodness. Yeah, man.
Can't be that truck.
My goodness. Oh, [ __ ]
It up to here with big boo. I've had it
up to [ __ ] here with it. That's what
me That's what me and Fraser used to say.
Literally add it up to here with it.
Right up to here. It's annoying. Damn boyfriend.
Now, I was going to put 20 in it to be
fair, but I never I just done an
approach Mr. be an boyfriend. Hey, boyfriend.
Mr. B. Hey, man. Boyfriends.
I'll never forget the way I had man said
that. I was like, "How's it going, bro?"
Cuz we used to do it. I used to go out,
then he used to go out. I said to him,
"How's it going?" He's like, "They broke
our boyfriends. I was dead." I was like,
Grim, I was laughing. It was funny, is it?
Yeah, I'm going to be grafting tomorrow,
bro. I'm going to be doing some hard
work tomorrow. Make some money. So,
today is just sort of like, yeah.
Just going to keep sending it, I guess,
and then see.
[ __ ] Well, I'm not going to do on a
street again. I don't think
12 week. I'm too tired.
Honestly too [ __ ] tired, man.
I can't be asked.
When it gets to 72, I'm going to end the live drinking.
It's hard. Uh, Mr. B, did you hear about
the escort story? [ __ ] crazy, bro.
They were like, "Oh, we can give you a
[ __ ] but you can't come in my mouth,
which doesn't make any sense."
So, I had to go all the way [ __ ] past [ __ ] Wembley.
To get that school, I already knew it.
It's crazy, bro. This country is [ __ ]
This country will never change ever.
Like, for real. For real, bro. It'll
never change. Never change, bro. Yeah, man.
Let's hope it gets better later, is it?
What? 7 hours ago.
Wait, I can actually charge you.
Yeah, charge us on a machine, man.
My friend said this [ __ ] will never end. Yeah, funny.
Nah, it's not funny, bro. It's annoying.
I can't even see how anyone can find it funny. Me
say, "What about you? This [ __ ] will
never end." He said, "Yeah."
I hate it. I hate boyfriend, but I hate
I would play thank you, but there's no
cash machine. I was going to put 20
pound in it, but there's no cash machine.
Yeah, there's no cash machine around here.
Charging a good old creeps. Get out.
Cash machine, man. What do you think,
Greg? You £20 on Frankie?
Is that okay with you, boss? I have to
run it past Grey for that cuz the boss. Okay, boss. Uh,
I'm sorry. I can't do it. It's not okay
with our boss. Okay, with you, boss. But
you said the approaching thing was okay,
was it? [ __ ]
I want to put 20 on Frankie, man. Man, I
I pay for like a month.
Class machine. Class machine.
Class machine. Touch machine. Class
[ __ ] hell. my eyes, bro. [Music]
What about 20 pounds?
What about 20 pound creams? Are you sure
that's not okay with you, boss?
Even just 20. Are you sure that's not
okay with boss?
Yeah, I'll lose all of 20.
Yeah, I'll lose all I'll lose all of 20, bro.
If I leave my phone here and go to the
cash point, my phone will still be
there. Like, [ __ ]
[ __ ] with it.
Gre [ __ ] with it. Good old
reckon we will at least get a bonus. Griezy,
you reckon we at least get a bonus?
You reckon we'll at least get a [ __ ] bonus?
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
Give it a while.
What do you reckon? Give it a while.
Would you say give it a while? Huh?
I'm going to give it a while. I think on
the way there I'm going to do some
approaches as well. Well, at least one
and I'll be back with you.
20 is it?
Okay. You sure boss?
What a [ __ ]
Oh, Greasy. Do you like what I just said
to the person?
What a [ __ ] you looking.
You like that? You like that little
voice, don't you? I'll do the 20.
Let me leave my drink somewhere. Yeah.
Make sure it
god draw 20 and come back. We're going
to do an approach as well, please.
Give me about 5 minutes.
Find me about five minutes. Right. The