Sorry about that. Time, but got the cash. Yo yo
we meet again Frankie.
Bonus day. Bonus day.
Bonus today. We got a bonus.
We got a bonus, bro. 100%.
All right, we need to put on the back.
Yeah, just 20 pound, mate. I just
approached someone. They said they had a
boyfriend. Same old [ __ ] Boring.
Been playing this for ages.
Oh, wonder why.
I don't anymore.
Come on. Give us a pointless man at least. No.
Can't get a bonus to save my life, man.
Why you don't gamble, kids?
That's what happened.
Why you don't gamble, people? at tour.
Ah, it's not happening at two or Mr. V. Nank. Uh,
you can't get a bonus on this game, bro.
Why? I don't gamble anymore. I just 20
pound on it. Come on.
thought and congress
gambling so they say. Yeah,
it's just gambling though. So they say
what they said.
I feel like smashing someone's [ __ ] face in.
That's also an indication of there's no
such thing as gambling responsibly.
Doesn't matter if it's money you can
afford to lose. It doesn't make it one
big difference. I want to get this glass
and and put it through someone's neck.
But I want to get this glass and put it
through someone's [ __ ] neck more.
Literally, bro. Doesn't matter if it's
money you can afford to lose. Doesn't
make a difference. Could be £5, 10, 20.
Just losing is annoying. Simple. And
that's exactly why I don't get money.
And you don't see any content on my
channel. Like honestly, if this was not
a pub where people know me, this machine
would be going out the [ __ ] front
door. Doesn't matter if it's money you
can afford to lose, it doesn't make a difference anymore.
It doesn't make a difference if it's
money you can afford to lose. Where did
that come from? Right. Where just
because it's money you can afford to
lose, that makes it okay. Where did that
come from? Like who invented that? Like
out of curiosity cuz we're gambling. So
cuz you lose money, you can afford to
lose it. Oh, it's okay. No, bro. That's
not the way it works. The only people
that say that are people like secular
slots that use secular slots. What?
Secular slots that uses fake money. It
doesn't matter if it's like I I want to
get this machine and put the glass
through it over 20,000. Like that's
definitely like 100%. It's exactly why I
don't gamble anymore.
Oh [ __ ] That's exactly why I don't
gamble because it controls your whole
body, your whole mind. It doesn't matter
if it's money you can afford to lose or
not. And I've been gambling longer than
that sick of slot. And I knew and I knew
when to give it up. No, mate. I'm not
doing anymore. I'm good.
I don't even know why I done that to be honest.
Yeah, but it's just gambling. So they
say, "As long with this money you can
afford to lose, it's all well and good."
It's not good, bro. Honestly, if this
was not a cop I was thing, I'd be
smashing every single one of them
machines. I'd smash every single one of
them and made them pay 200 times a thousand.
Yeah, that's how it gets me. That's why
I don't gamble. That's literally why I
don't gamble. Because of how it gets
you. This is exactly what I'm saying.
This is why I don't do a number. There's
no same conversation anymore about this.
It's [ __ ] degrading losing on it. It
doesn't matter if it's only 20 pound. I
feel like I've been degraded.
I feel like I've been degraded and laugh
at. That's how it gets me. Like you
don't understand. That's literally how
it gets you. It don't matter if it's 20.
It feels degrading. Like you don't
understand. You really really don't
understand. Like you do not know what
I'd be doing to this pub right here
right now if the people in here do not
know me. The people in here know me, bro.
Like it doesn't matter if it's 20 pound.
I feel degraded. Like that's it. It's
simple as that. And that's why I don't
gamble no more. That's exactly why I
don't gamble no more. That's why you
don't hear the same conversation anymore
cuz it's boring. It's not just gambling,
bro. You can't lose 6 months in a row.
There's no way you can justify that as
bad luck. That's as simple as that. It's
literally as simple as that.
Yeah. You're talking about yourself
again. You're the only one with autism,
Mr. [ __ ] stop talking about
yourself, Mr. Autism. Yeah, you have got
autism. Stop talking about yourself.
[ __ ] boy. [ __ ] boy, stop talking
about yourself. [ __ ] hell, man. I
told you about it not being good for
your mental health. Stop being a
40-year-old [ __ ] and go off of
YouTube. Stop writing shitty little
comments, bro. I swear to God, bro,
right now. Yeah. Tell you what I feel like doing this.
Putting my fish through it, bro. I swear
to God I I would put my whole fist
through the whole machine. That's how
strong I am.
I would literally put my whole fist
through it kind of like you don't
understand. It's annoying. But they know
me now. So I know like a [ __ ] bro.
Like I'm friends with the staff and [ __ ] So
otherwise, trust me, bro. My fist will
be going through it. I'm telling you
100%. 100 fucking%. Doesn't
matter if it's only£20. 2020. 20. It's
annoying. I don't care. I don't give a
[ __ ] if it's only 20, bro. So what if
it's only 20? What's that supposed to
[ __ ] mean? Cuz it's what? So because
it's only £20, that's okay then, bro.
Come on. It's boring. Come on. It's
boring. Please stop.
Because you're only 20. That's okay.
No, it didn't bon us. Not one single
bonus, but it's just gambling. So they
say, so they say, but we know ain't just
gambling because you can't put that
amount of money that I used to put
through it and not get a bonus. You're
not even going to try and justify it to
me. You're not even going to sit there
and try and justify to me. So what did I
do? I gave up. Simple.
I gave up, lads. That's exactly why I
gave up because because of this whole
[ __ ] It's [ __ ] degrading. I feel
like a woman that's been raped. Like,
I'm not even joking. I feel degraded.
It's horrible. It's evil. I hate it. I
don't even know why I done it. You know,
it's not just gambling. It's degrading.
Know that secular slot says, "Oh, uh,
it's just gambling. It's just gambling.
It's a form of entertainment. Do I sound
Do I sound entertained?
Do I sound entertained? I'm asking you a
question. It's a serious question. Do I
sound like I'm entertained? I want to
put my [ __ ] fist through this whole
machine. Do I sound entertained?
No, I don't.
Swear to God, man.
No, cuz I'm [ __ ] not, bro.
It is a big deal for me. It is. No, no,
no, no, no, no. For me, it's a big deal.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. For me, it's a big deal. It's
[ __ ] degrading and annoying. That's
why I don't do it no more. It is
annoying. It's You feel like you've been
degraded. No, it generally makes me feel
like that. I'm telling you, I'm telling
you right now how it makes me feel.
I'm literally telling you how it makes
me feel. It's more than annoying. I'm
I'm literally sat here telling you how
this makes me feel. And I got people
looking at me. It is degrading. It's
horrible. It is. It [ __ ] is. It gets
under your skin. It controls your whole
mind. It's a very big deal. A very
[ __ ] big deal.
No, I just lost 20 on this rock.
I don't do it, you [ __ ] idiot. I
don't even gamble anymore. This is the
first time in a [ __ ] month.
I don't gamble. This is the whole point
is I don't. Only today, the first time
in a month.
That's what I'm saying. I don't gamble.
You said from today, which is the first
time in a month. It makes you feel so
low. It does. No, no, no. It really,
really does, bro. It really, really
does. No, no, no, no, no, no. Bro, it
really makes you so low. It doesn't
matter if it's 20. It's everything. It's
the whole playing on it. The whole
playing and losing. It's a [ __ ]
proper big deal. If it weren't such a
big deal, I wouldn't have [ __ ]
quit. I'm my own worst enemy. Bro, are
you a [ __ ] I just told you that I've
not done it for a month and I only lost
20. Bro, are you a [ __ ] [ __ ] I
literally told you, bro.
Bro, listen. I just told you that I've
done it once in a month. Are you a
[ __ ] And you're trying to tell me
that I'm my own worst enemy, bro. Is
this a Timmy Elders channel?
I suck your mom. Yeah,
trust me. If this was not a pub, if this
was not a pub, right? If this was not a
pub, a pub I knew, I would have put that
glass through that [ __ ] machine, bro.
I swear to God. And I know Timmy
chatting [ __ ] I'm going to do this. Oh,
I'm going to do that. No, the glass
would be going through the every single machine.
I'd buy four Guinnesses and put every
[ __ ] in it. How many Guinnesses? One,
two, five Guinnesses and put them all
through the [ __ ] machine.
Yeah, I probably would. But you can't
get a woman in this country anyways. I
done an approach today, Richie. I done
an approach today. Guess what? Boyfriend.
They both got boyfriends.
[ __ ] off, man. I suck your mother, bro.
And I've got people on WhatsApp. Yeah,
messaging me. Leave me the [ __ ] alone, man.
Leave me the [ __ ] alone, bro. I'm not
even allowed to go out in peace. I'm not
even allowed to go out in [ __ ] peace.
I wouldn't mind. So,
yeah. People meet me at work and stuff.
Oh, Ghost, do you want me to tell you a
story? I'll tell you a story if you want
since you seem like you're legitimately
okay and you're not a troll yet. Do you
want me to tell you a story? I can tell
you a story if you want.
It's going to blow your mind.
Yeah. Okay. Now we we're finished with
the gamb. Yeah. So, I go to the gym now.
I work now. I live by myself. I don't
live with my mom. I need to work
tomorrow and I need to work the next
day. Listen to me. Yeah. Uh day before
was it yesterday? Day before yesterday.
Um no, it was yesterday. I'll tell you
exactly what happened. I come out the
gym and I'm three approaches. I didn't
even plan to do these approaches, right?
And one ignored me, gave me a dirty
look. Other ignored me and then the then
the third one said that she had a
boyfriend. They said she had a
boyfriend. Now I'm thinking, bro, we're
thinking further ahead now. We're
actually thinking further ahead. If you
can't even get a conversation out of
someone, means you can't get a
friendship, you can't get a
relationship, you can't get sex. This is
what it's like in this country now. And
it didn't it didn't bother me too much.
I think oh it's cracked up. But like
people tell you oh you need to move back
your moms. You need to work. You need to
go to the gym. Done all of it. Still
dealing with these shitty experiences.
They [ __ ] same [ __ ] when I went out
yesterday. I went out yesterday. I got
my hair done. I look groomed. And it's
the same old [ __ ] time and time and time
and time again. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Time
and time. Yeah. Yeah. That's what I'm
saying. Is it? Yeah.
And so and then and then a week before
that and then a week before that guess
listen to this ghost ghost thing. Yeah.
The guy didn't want no smoke. He would
have got [ __ ] up. Listen. Yeah. Listen
to me. Yeah. It's not even that. A week
ago when I finished work I thought,
"Okay, let me go to an escort. Let me go
to a Why is it so charging? Let me go to
an There it is. Let me go to an escort.
Let me go to a brush. Yeah.
You know what happened, Ghost? So, my
thing is [ __ ] I don't care about
sex. I haven't had sex in ages. I only
care about blows. You're going to laugh
at this. Yeah. They said to me they can
give me a [ __ ] but I can't I can't
finish in their mouth, but I can't
finish in their mouth. And I'm thinking,
what the [ __ ] I'm thinking, bro,
they're taking a piss. Look, you either
give [ __ ] or you don't give
[ __ ] I have never had a woman say
to me that she does give a [ __ ] and
you can't come in her [ __ ]
mouth. Like that that doesn't make no
[ __ ] sense. I'm thinking what the
[ __ ] Like you're paying you're pay
you're putting you are sending a service
for my leave. Yeah. No, nothing. I I had
to go to [ __ ] Wembley. I had to come
back to where I live and had to travel
an hour to go to Wembley. I don't know
if you know where Wembley is. I went
past Wembley to get with an escort I had
already been with. I knew then this
country was [ __ ] up. I knew then.
Yeah. After then I knew, yeah, this
country is [ __ ] up, bro. I'm telling
you. It's full of NPCs. It's full of
[ __ ] [ __ ] It's full of people
that are brainwashed by [ __ ] Tik Tok
and Instagram. And then you got [ __ ]
escorts. What the [ __ ] Yeah, I'm in
East and I traveled all the way there.
This country is [ __ ] bro.
It is a sad sad state of affairs. And
guess what? You know, another thing that
happened yesterday is
when I done these approaches with these
three women, I didn't even want to go I
I didn't plan to go to work, but I
thought I'll just go to work anyways.
Yeah. And you know what she done? Yeah.
You know what she done? You know what
she done? Yeah. She [ __ ] um What was
it? What did she do? Uh
sorry. I went to work and then Yeah.
No. Are you an idiot? Yeah. I went to I
went to Wembley for an school that would
let me cuz the ones in my No, no. The
ones in my area didn't. Yeah. So, I had
to go to an escort I had already been
with and she moved area. So, I had to go
all the way there and they had neighbors
and everything. I thought, bro, what the
I was taking I was taking a break from
dating and everything, wasn't I? So, I
was taking a break from dating. So, I
thought, [ __ ] it. Let me just go back to
my area. It's not a big deal with making
money. I was like, "Bro, what the [ __ ] man?"
Yeah, it's insane, bro. It's not normal.
It's not normal, bro.
That is not normal at all.
You're you're you're putting a service
out there for money
and yet you don't want to. It doesn't
make sense, man. It don't make sense.
It's really bad. This country is really,
really bad. It's nothing like anyone
says it is ghosting. Oh, women go for
personality. They don't, mate. I go to
the gym. I approached three women. Yes.
No. No. I approached [ __ ] five women
yesterday, bro. Sober. Completely sober.
It is nothing like anyone says. Nothing.
Again, this is real life, bro. Where
we're standing, we're standing in real
life. This ain't Grand Theft Auto. Do
you understand, bro? They're like, "This
is not Grand Theft Auto. This is real
life. This is not Reddit. This is real
life. If there was somebody right here
now I could approach, I would do it and
show you. Bro, it's [ __ ] And you know
the mad thing is what [ __ ] with my
head. Yeah, Corby is that.
It's not like you're money mike looking
or Timmy looking cuz then you're like
you're playing this [ __ ] at your own
risk. You're above average looking. You
go to the gym, you got money, dress
good, you smell good, and you can't even
get a conversation out of someone. That
ain't looking right, bro. That is not
looking right. I'm telling you that is
not looking right, bro.
You know, it's not looking right. And
anyways, so then when I went to work
yesterday ghosting, it affected my whole
mood for like 2 hours. I didn't think I
was I was going to be able to work cuz
it was [ __ ] with my whole mind. So,
it's [ __ ] up. Like, it's it's proper
backwards. It's [ __ ] No, bro. That is
[ __ ] crazy, bro.
You can't get nothing in this country,
bro. They're all NPCs. Like I think
they're brainwashed by Tik Tok and
Instagram. Like that's the only thing I
can say. It's [ __ ] up. You know,
it's not it's not normal, bro.
Doesn't matter what work I'm doing, bro.
I'm not going to say on here in front of
these glasses, am I? But the thing is,
it's like that woman that just was
copying what I was doing. I just
repeated back to her. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. This is the kind of [ __ ]
chick you're dealing with in this country, bro.
Like, I weren't going to say nothing cuz
you got a guy there, bro. I'm [ __ ]
smoking, bro. And of machines. It's not a joke.
Like, it's impossible in this country. I
don't know how other people have met.
Maybe they got lucky at work. Maybe they
got lucky through a sister or they met
before social media. I don't know. But
I'm telling you, [ __ ] what I'm
experiencing, bro. And it is not normal.
It is not normal, bro. I don't know who
does this or who does that or whatever,
but I'm telling you now, starting from
now, 2025, bro. What the [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm going on Wednesday.
It's not normal. It's not normal, bro.
It's not normal. I swear to God, it's
got three numbers yesterday. None of
them [ __ ] replied. What the [ __ ]
It's not normal, man. It's not normal.
It's really not normal, bro.
It's the same old [ __ ] No, I'm going to
send it to the club, bro. I don't give a
[ __ ] I've had enough, mate. Literally
definitely [ __ ] had enough of it all, man.
I go gym now and everything. Sorry, but
I'm a bit sweaty, man.
I miss Well, look, I got groomed and
everything, bro. Look, I'm groomed and
everything. The lights my face, man. I
got everything, bro. Look. Got my floors. Yeah, man.
You still get the same [ __ ]
You still get the same [ __ ] in this
country. I've had enough of it. It's not
even funny. It's boring as [ __ ]
Right. Listen. You're a little keyboard
warrior that lives in Milton Ke. Shut
up, man. Look at the state of you. You
want to be London, [ __ ] mate. You've
been yappy, yappy, yappy in [ __ ]
Milton Ke for ages now. You're boring, buddy.
You're boring, mate. You're a bore. [ __ ]
off. You want to be an L gangler. Like
the amount of [ __ ] that you have been
saying to me and LG, you're yappy,
yappy, yappy. No one cares, bro. You
know where I live. You know where I am
right now. You're like 20. You're
realistically about 35 minutes from
where I am. You got something to say?
Say it to my face. Simple. Done. You
[ __ ] silly little son. How you've got
all this time to be yappy, yappy, yappy
behind the keyboard, but you ain't got
that train to London to come and do
nothing. [ __ ] off, mate. They're a [ __ ] [ __ ]
Isn't that right, ladies?
Pair of [ __ ]
[ __ ] pair of [ __ ] mate.
Yeah, it's the truth though. It's the truth.
This guy's been yapping on for so long
now. Yeah. But he's not willing to do
anything to anyone. He's a little [ __ ]
There was somebody here. I'd give it a
whirl. I want to show you how bad it is.
I want to actually show you how bad it
is, bro. I'll show you later. I'll go live later.
It's so bad in this country. Like, and
some of the people grievy. Yeah. Some of
the people that you actually approach,
they're scared cuz they don't know how
to socialize. They've got this person
coming up to them. Yeah. Approaching
them and they're like, uh, you could
tell, you can actually feel the anxiety
in them. You can actually feel the
anxiety in them because they're not used
to like talking to anyone.
And you know, it's not even that as
well, bro. Like you open a door for someone. Yeah.
And they don't even say thank you. How
mad is that, bro? open the door for
someone, they don't even say thank you.
This country is just full of [ __ ]
It's not even one thing. It's just
[ __ ] everywhere. I don't want to
[ __ ] work in it as well.
It's bad, is it, bro? This country will
never change. Oh, yep.
I literally I was I was cycling on the
pavement yesterday. Yeah.
This guy's kid almost ran into the bike.
Yeah. And the fountain was pouring
pouring. Pouring. and the kid almost run
into the fountain and he tried to say,
"Oh, you should be cycling there." I
said, "Mate, I I can cycle there. It's a
park. It's not a pavement." And
furthermore, if you really believed
Yeah. that I can't cycle there. Why
didn't you say anything before your kid
almost ran into me? Your child, you
should be watching your child, not
blaming other people. Yeah. You don't
see other people [ __ ] complaining.
It's just full of [ __ ] It's full
of [ __ ] [ __ ] And and London is
the worst for it,
bro. London is the worst for it as well.
It's full of [ __ ] I'm telling you,
bro. They give us a bad name, man.
Put the [ __ ] [ __ ] in this
country, man. Well done.
Well, we hit the club soon.
Bothered when I go out as well, mate.
Always get bothered.
It's bad, bro. And it's only getting
worse as well. Um, Ghost, it's only getting worse.
But it doesn't matter whether it's
getting worse or I'm just waiting for my
friend. He should be here soon. I was
going to go out by myself, but my friend
wants to come. So
what is it? Hey, boyfriend.
It's like that girl trying to mock me. I
said it back to her. I said, "Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah." [ __ ]
[ __ ] Fun [ __ ] off though, didn't
they? This country is just full of
[ __ ] And have you noticed in
England? Wherever you go, everywhere it just stinks.
Everywhere you go, it just stinks, man. I'm saying
and don't even try and say I [ __ ]
spin cuz I [ __ ] don't. Yeah. Don't
you dare say that. Yeah.
Uh they're just not interested in this
country, Rich. Uh Cor you got to admit
and man's right about that, bro. They're
just they're just not interested in this
country. Like for the most part.
Obviously it's true, bro. Cuz if if it
was if it wasn't true. Yeah.
I bet you they make money from Tik Tok
nowadays as well.
Obviously, bro, it sounds mad, but
obviously he's obviously right, ain't
it? Cuz why is it as soon as someone
goes Asia, it could be anywhere in Asia,
they don't have these problems.
Where the [ __ ] are these [ __ ]
Is that right, Grezy? Where the [ __ ] are these [ __ ]
What do you think of that, Grezy? What charging?
Grezy, where the [ __ ] are these [ __ ]
Oh, I love him. I love him. It's like
that Smokey. He acts hard behind a
keyboard. It's boring, bro. Like you you
live half an hour away and you've done nothing.
You live 20 minutes on a train to London
and you've done nothing. You're boring, mate.
It's not looking good, but we'll get
some numbers later. No, you're worried.
We will get some later. Huh? I do one
now, but there's no one here. Oh, no.
A [ __ ] sausage best.
That's what it is. It's a [ __ ]
sausage best, mate.
Yeah, I got a number yesterday at the train station.
It's sad, bro. It's so sad.
Oh, where's my
Anyone would think you look like [ __ ]
Tim Eldridge, mate.
Anyone would think that you look like Tim Eldridge,
a [ __ ] [ __ ] man.
They hold the boyfriend.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
Antman said, "What do you want?" You
know what Antman said, Greasy? He said,
"What do you want me to say about it?
It's just the same old."
Yeah. He said, "What do you want me to
say about it? It's just the same old."
It's the truth, is it?
Just the same old
same old, isn't it?
This [ __ ] will never end.
American Morgan didn't reply. Hey, the
one I met yesterday. I wonder why that is.
She didn't reply. I wonder why that is, mate.
Yeah. The only thing I can think of is
they've been brainwashed by social media, bro.
Like that's that's all it is, man. The
only thing it can be.
It's the only thing it can be.
And man said, "I don't need to think
about it. I'll be living it." I said,
"You're going to have to think about
when you come, you know, when you just
come back to um England." Yeah. From
Thailand. I said, "Um, right.
You're going to
you're going to have to deal with this
[ __ ] again. How do you How do you think
about it?" He said, "I don't think about
it. I'll be living it."
[ __ ] depressing, bro. Yeah. I hope
you live in there.
Yeah, that smoke is a keyboard warrior,
man. Another basement dweller. See, the
thing with most of these people on this
community um they're just basement dwellers.
They're just 40 life failures that never
made it in life. So, they just come on
YouTube and sell the blank. no job,
skin, virgin, fat. Uh they call people
ugly. It's just a reflection of what
they see in the mirror every day. That's
why we can't take any heed of them.
They're just talking about themselves,
you know? So, but I'm surprised Monty
takes heed of them. They're just little
Monty's that talk about themselves.
Little 40y old basement dwellers.
And that's a word I actually made up.
Basement dwellers. That's literally what
they are. They ain't got a life. They
got no money. They got no job. They've
got no life. They've got weight
problems. They can't leave the house.
So, they're coming here in self.
They're something to laugh at, bro. At
this point, they really are. [Music]
I'm going to go to the club in a minute. So
yeah, I'm going to go to the club in a
minute and uh yeah, I'll go back live
later when I'm in a club. I'm going to
have to smash some approaches. So um
yeah, I'll be back. Be back later 100%.
See you, man. and I'll be back in a bit.