Back at the good old spot. Bag now.
Don't need this [ __ ] bag,
mate. You're not You're not living in
this country. You're existing.
That's what you're doing. You're [ __ ]
existing. You're not living. You're
existing. That's what you're doing, bud.
You're not living, mate. You're existing.
So coming in now it's bit early but
wanted to get before the bounce so I
didn't want them to uh [ __ ] the whole
track suit up in did it don't really
want to be wearing these jeans but got I got it.
You're not living, bro. You're existing
in this country.
You're not living in this country.
You're existing, man.
So bad, bro. It's so bad. I just done about [ __ ]
two or three approaches down that
[ __ ] road. Can't even get a
conversation out of them.
My dating life in this country is not
looking good, is it?
Ain't looking good, mate.
So bad, bro.
So sad. This is a country that you're
actually existing in. You're not You're
not You're not living, bro. You're
you're existing. Oh, the JD bag. Okay.
So in case the B got here before me and
you got to wear jeans and I didn't want
to wear jeans today. I wanted to wear
the good old Trekky, you know, cost a
lot of money. So I bought the bag with
the jeans in it just in case.
You're not you're not living in this
country. You're existing.
You're existing, bro.
This is no life for anyone, bro. I'm
telling you, bro.
Yeah, bro. Listen, listen.
If you got anything to say, come and say
to my face. End of. I'm not interested
in you typing behind the screen, I don't
give a [ __ ] about that. If you've got
anything to say, say to my face. And if
you're not going to do that, I'm not
interested. You can say what you like.
this that whatever. Well, I don't give a
[ __ ] Unless you're gonna say something
to my face, I'm not interested.
That keyboard warrior [ __ ] ended when I
was like 11 years of age, mate. People
used to do it on the PlayStation. It's boring. Yeah, man.
Go down. Yeah.
Like, bro, if you ain't going to come
and say anything to my face, I'm not
interested. I'm not going to argue with you, bro. pointless
[ __ ] work tomorrow as well. It's just
going to get [ __ ] busy, man. Come on,
man. They used to send you the approaches, bro.
It's pointless, bro. It's pointless
arguing with a keyboard warrior, man.
Come on. We're [ __ ] adults and you're
still doing this [ __ ] some [ __ ] Anyways,
don't [ __ ] ch like four today. Maybe bro
is going through me. [Music] Yeah.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] 69
to be on 69. Yeah, man. [Music]
It's [ __ ] up, man.
All jokes aside, it's actually proper [ __ ] up.
I'm going to definitely do a video on
it's not normal. You're existing in this
country. You're not living. You're existing. [Music]
Hey, he's coming a bit later. [ __ ] hell, Grezy.
What a [ __ ] day I've had. I done two
approaches right down that road.
Nothing, man. Dead.
You can't get nothing in this country,
bro. It's dead. You're existing. You're
not living. You're not living. You're
not living. You're existing. That's what
you're This country is [ __ ]
It's sad, bro. It's sad. I got to do
[ __ ] 10 hours tomorrow, bro. What the
Mad, man. I'm going to be hungry as [ __ ] as well.
It's a sad It's a sad place to be bro. England. Sad.
It really is.
I teach you for lunch.
Yeah, I'm [ __ ] bro. I'm w
I'm waving just on be.
Look at that, bro. Look at that traffic.
Tell me you like it, Greasy. Look at that, man.
It's good, isn't it, man?
This is bad, bro.
Look how busy that [ __ ] NPCs,
Grezy. They're all [ __ ] NPCs, lad. I
can l go outside and record an approach
right now and show you exactly what it's
like. They're MP [ __ ] seas, bro. non-playing characters.
You can't even get a conversation out of them.
Let a friendship, let own a [ __ ]
relationship. [ __ ] man.
It's really bad.
They've all got boyfriends.
I never got yet, but it's so early. I
will go then.
How the [ __ ] He called her the
[ __ ] gim. To be fair, she kind of
looks like an accident, bro. 67%.
Wait, we need to go. I need to end this live stream.
I actually want battery work.
They will by charge.