Yeah. Same [ __ ] That boyfriend.
This country will never change. 54. Bro,
you're so [ __ ] weird, man.
Yeah, bro. It's boring as [ __ ]
I got [ __ ] [ __ ]
You're existing in this country.
It's [ __ ] Hey, listen, Daz. You're
only existing in this country. You're
not living. You're existing. You're not
living, mate. I've done about three
approaches in this [ __ ] place. I've
got a boyfriend. I've got a boyfriend.
Bro, listen. I look like [ __ ] Timothy Elden.
I look like Timmy Aldridge.
Bro, you're existing in this country.
That's all you're doing. You not living.
You're not living.
You are actually existing, bro.
Swear to God.
Look at me down here. Look at me now.
Do I look like Timmy Eldridge? Do I look
like [ __ ] to the Eldridge? No, I
[ __ ] do not.
It's madness, man.
It's not a way of living. It's not a way of life.
You're existing. You're not living. Uh,
it's so bad, bro. It's not even funny.
It's [ __ ] up.
It's actually proper [ __ ] up. You
can't even get a conversation out of
anyone, Dad. I don't know if this works
like that in if it works like this in Liverpool.
It works like it here and it's [ __ ]
boring, mate. Mate, I've done three
approach. It's getting busy. I've done
three approaches. I've got a boyfriend.
I've got a boyfriend. It's [ __ ] boring.
It's [ __ ] in terms of that.
Same people, same attitude. [ __ ]
I might do that one in the dress in a bit.
You will get enough. I don't want
They're just so interesting this country dance.
Good old dad. [Laughter]
How about let me know 50
maybe like 20 30 quid.
You can't get anything in this country.
I won 53% for the
I'll do tomorrow.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] up, bro.
Just in this country, you're not living.
You're not living your existence.
Yeah, but they've all got boyfriends apparently.
Yeah, I've done four approaches. They've
all got boyfriends apparently.
So they say, "Yeah, man." [Applause]
Yeah, bro. They've all got boyfriends. I got four.
Look at that one in that dress.
Might give it a whirl.
playing over there. Get a drink. I would [Music]
I would [ __ ] it. [Music] When?
Yeah. We'll never change in this
country. Roll on Wednesday, man. Roll on
[ __ ] Wednesday. I'm out of
roll on Wednesday and I'm [ __ ] out of it. Simple.
Oh, he is with us. He is today. [Music]
Anyone Anyone got any um pickup lines?
If you give me a pickup line, I might go
buy someone. I'll go and fight someone.
I don't find any of it funny, mate. I
think it's [ __ ] weird.
You want to pick a line? Tell me I'm
going to buy it.
No, Wednesday, mate.
I can finally leave this [ __ ] old
country full of stuck up people.
I need to go.
This is not normal.
This life ain't normal here. Telling you
it's not no way of living. [Music]
How about that one minute?
I'll do that.
Well, I need to go here. I'll be right back later.
We'll do this one in a dress and [ __ ] off.