These
[ __ ] [ __ ] are going my [ __ ]
nerves, bro. I swear to God.
I said, do you do realize, [ __ ] It's
got it's got that has no substance to
that word anymore. It's like your best.
It's mad how much they reply when it
when it's something that they can argue
against. Like you're just proving my
point even more right.
Like you're just she's just proving my
point even more right. Like you're fast
enough to reply when it's something to
argue against and you're still doing it
as well. It's not even like you've done
it once. They are all the same. Bro, I
can't wait until tomorrow bro. can
finally get out of this [ __ ] whole
country. Like every in like bro, if I
come online Yeah. and I start an
argument, I already know what you're
going to say. Oh, women don't owe you
nothing. You're an insult. It's boring
now. It's the same as calling a woman a
[ __ ] It has no substance to it.
Leave that [ __ ] sign, bro.
Yeah, these these words are balling now.
She's still messaging me, bro. I want
This is why I don't even like argue with
these [ __ ] bro. Cuz I know what my temper's like.
[ __ ] hell, bro. They're pissing me
off, bro. I swear to God. [ __ ] off, man.
You silly [ __ ] little [ __ ]
want to go to a house and smash the
[ __ ] patient, bro. This is why I
don't do this [ __ ] anymore
with these [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] off, man. You stupid [ __ ] Trying
to tell me I can't speak English. You're
from [ __ ] Australia, you [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Yeah,
I love how they're so replying so fast
when it's something they can argue
against. It's so mad, is it? It's so backwards.
Again, something you never hear on Reddit.
You never hear this stuff on Reddit. And
it's not that you decided you done it on
purpose, which I don't even care. Like,
what the [ __ ]
You done it on purpose anyways. Why are
we even talking about that?
Yeah. One second.
Sorry about that, bro. I just argue with
this Australian [ __ ]
Yeah. So, you're trying to stick up for
the westernized women, but then you're
admitting to what you've just done. They
are start [ __ ] in this country,
bro. I I can't wait till tomorrow. I
really can't wait.
Like, we knew you weren't seeing anyone,
you [ __ ] idiot. You don't see someone
in 5 days. The [ __ ]
But it is cute how fast they are at
responding when it's something that they
can argue against and they keep replying
and replying and replying.
It's lucky I don't know where one of
these [ __ ] live, bro. And I don't want
to be dealing with this anymore, bro. I
don't want to be this person anymore.
But they keep drawing you out, bro. Just
like these people on this [ __ ] YouTube.
Who the [ __ ] Who the [ __ ] did they fre, bro?
Going to message a [ __ ] on my free
number. One second. Yeah.
[ __ ] I would go [ __ ] her up today,
bro. I swear to God.
same the same um offer I gave Morgan I
would do in front of any man obviously
to make it fair bro.
But it's cute though. It is cute. It is
cute how fast
they are to reply when it's something
that they can argue against. That's
cute. That is very cute.
I tell Grezy about that one.
Exactly why I'm leaving.
And it's not even just that. It's the
people as well, the whole country.
That's exactly why I'm leaving.
It's not look inwards. It's look
[ __ ] outwards. You don't have
any of these problem with [ __ ] Asian
people. Asian people, you got none of
these problems. Even people that are not
with from the um from third world countries,
but stupid little Australian [ __ ] like
yourself and [ __ ] stupid Americans
and [ __ ] English, you're all [ __ ]
stuck up [ __ ] Yeah.
Swear to God, bro.
Doesn't matter what I'm getting, bro.
You don't need to know what I'm getting.
Stop trying to find out what terminal
I'm going to cuz you're not going to
find out. So, you're not stopping the
madness, so don't even try. I want to
[ __ ] this Australian woman up, bro.
Like, this is this is the whole this is
the whole point I'm talking about now.
Yeah, I've started it. Now I will finish
it. You understand what I was saying
earlier about these little mongos on
YouTube? I've started it now. I will
finish it. You understand, Grezy? This
stupid little [ __ ] Greavvesy. Oh my
[ __ ] god. It's cute how fast they are. Yeah.
Yeah. You don't need to know, bro. You
don't even know what airport I'm going
from, so stop it. You don't even know
what airport I'm going from. Anyways,
Grezy, this stupid little [ __ ] Yeah, I
find it so cute how they reply so fast
to something that they can argue
against. It's quite cute. I think it's
quite cute. Like, they ignore normal
messages and then they reply straight
away to things that they can argue
against and then they keep doing it.
I'm not answering any of your questions,
bro. You're not going to find out what
terminal I'm going from.
You know what I'm saying?
I think it's so cute, Grezy. I basically
said to her, "Yeah, how like [ __ ] up
the dating is in this country. You can't
meet people." No, no, no, no, no. And
then she started like trying to be a
[ __ ] I was like, "You're trying to
teach me English, mate. You're from
[ __ ] Australia, mate. Why do you
think most of the people that come here
from different countries can't speak the
language properly? Cuz they learned
Australian and American English.
I said, "What do you prefer me to speak
like [ __ ] crikey mate in a [ __ ]
Barbie joey can?" Is that how is that
how is that is that your way of English?
Is that where did the [ __ ] language
[ __ ] come from? You stupid [ __ ]
I swear to God, bro, it's lucky I don't
know where these people live.
Seriously, Grezy, it's lucky I don't
know where these people live, bro. you know,
and she's like, "Oh, I wasn't really
seeing someone else." And she thought I
was pissed off. I was like, "I'm not
pissed off like that. I expect it, lad."
Yeah. Like, do you know what? Like, uh,
she was like, "Oh, you you're I I don't
care about that." Like the thing is I
like you replying and then not meeting.
I wasn't asked about that. I expect it.
You're westernized. You're a [ __ ] What?
We're not talking about that. We was
talking about 2 weeks before.
And it's like I I wasn't pissed off
about that. I expect that. I don't
expect anything else. Just like if I
went to if I got a number right now,
Greavvesy, I would expect the [ __ ]
It's to be expected.
Well, you why would anyone be pissed off
about what they would expect? It's
stupid, bro. That's See, does she really
think that bothers anyone?
We knew We know what you [ __ ] do.
You've been doing it for years.
You know what I'm saying? And then,
oh, bro. And then she was like, "Oh,
what did she say?" She's like, "Um,
yeah." And then she's like, "Oh, I
wasn't really seeing someone." I was
like, "Yeah, no [ __ ] Sherlock. You
don't see somebody in 6 days. We know
that. We're not arguing about your
[ __ ] What you do?" And then she
was, you know what she said to me, Grey?
She said, "How is me replying and then
not me and then deciding not to meet you
unacceptable?" I said, "Firstly, I don't
care about that. That's not what the
conversation is. But since she wanted to
ask, well, yeah, it is unacceptable
because you've done the whole thing on
purpose because you're trying to take
the piss out of someone. So, how is that not unacceptable?
You know, if a woman that messaged you,
you wasn't interested in, you wouldn't
reply and suddenly just not meet them
and say that you're seeing someone. So,
yes, it is very unacceptable since you
brought the whole thing up, [ __ ]
And every and you know what I noticed
about them? They're not intelligent at
all, are they? Like, they really don't
know anything other than play victim and
reply to negativity. They literally
don't know anything else. Oh, and to
call someone an incel, I said to her,
darling, listen, that incel word is so
boring now that it has no effect. It's
the same as calling a woman a [ __ ] But
like, stick to what you know, bro. Like
replying to negativity and playing
victim. That's all you can do.
You're boring now. They're so boring, bro. Thank you.
Yeah, that's all they know how to do,
bro, is is reply to negativity and play
victim. This is why I don't care anymore, bro.
I don't care about it anymore, Grezy.
This is why I don't bother with it
anymore, bro. I'm leaving tomorrow. It's
not my problem anymore.
It's not look inwards. It's look
outwards. Look at all these Asian people
that you ain't got. Look at all these
Asian people that you ain't got problems with.
And yeah, we knew you weren't see. So,
you've just And I've just said to her,
hold on a minute. So, you've just
admitted to trying to take the piss out
of someone, then you're asking me to
look inwards. They're not very
intelligent, are they? They really,
really are so stupid, these women. They
really are retards, bro. They know
better than these people on here.
And it's not funny cuz I would end up
hurting one of them. Trust me, if I knew
where any of these people, cuz the way I
see it is they're messing with my mood.
They're messing with my mood, bro. I
would go and I would go on one of their
doors. This is why I don't like these
people to draw me out, bro. Just leave
me the [ __ ] alone. Yeah.
I swear to God, I would have went on one
of their door if I knew where they live,
bro. Just stop drawing people out. You
know what I'm saying?
Yeah, bro. It's good, isn't it?
I hate him, lad.
These people are not trolls on here.
These people are spastics.
These people on here are [ __ ]
completely out of spastics.
So, they're not even trolls. I just I
just messaged her saying, "Oh, like the
dating thing is [ __ ] isn't it? Like
you can only speak like you can't even
get a conversation out of people
nowadays and how just saying that the
West is [ __ ] and that." That's all I was
saying. Then she starts trying to be funny.
No [ __ ] You weren't seeing anyone.
You're just a piss taker. No one
expected anything different. It's been
going on for years. No one cares about
that. You know what I'm saying? Like
I hate them, bro. These are from numbers
from before, bro. I hate them. Which is
why I was actually complaining to them.
Like, you really don't understand, Grezy.
You really really don't understand.
hate them. like you really don't understand, bro.
But yeah, it's weird how they reply
with they reply so quickly to something
that they could argue against. What they
think they can argue against, but then
they lose the argument,
which is mad. And I weren't even saying
anything. I just said, "Oh yeah, the
dating is all [ __ ] and that." And then they,
you know what I mean?
It's mad how they're quick enough to reply to
things they can argue argue with,
though. That's cute, man.
Like, we know you're not seeing someone,
bro. You're just a typical westernized
[ __ ] with unrealistic expectations. How
could you be seeing someone? You've got
unrealistic expectations. But that's not
what the conversation's about.
But you don't need to look inwards. Nah,
it's these westernized [ __ ] It's the
people in this country because you will
never get this problem with Asian
people. You will never get these problem
with Chinese people. You never have
these problems even with the people
that's got money. It's not even like,
oh, you can say, oh, it's third world
countries. It's not third world
countries. It's English people. Do you
understand? It's Australian people and
it's American people.
That's what it is. It's not you, it's
them. Yeah. And you'll prove it cuz when
you finally [ __ ] with these people from
different countries, you will understand
it. You will understand it, bro.
They're brainwashed by Tik Tok. They're
brainwashed by Instagram. They're not
normal, bro. Do you understand?
I'd love to go to a yard and smash her
up, bro. I hate them, bro. They just
ruin your mood. You don't understand.
They ruin your [ __ ] mood every time.
I hate them, Grezy. I actually do hate
them. I'll punch one up in front of any
man. I don't care, bro. It's annoying.
I hate it, bro. Like, I'm not even
joking. It's annoying, bro. Like, I
would even say anything insulting. Like,
they're trying to be funny. Don't
message me back trying to be funny, bub. You know,
it's like what Izzy got that day.
Remember I went on Izzy's door? They
deserve it, bro. [ __ ] them. You know
what I mean?
So, how is that not unacceptable
behavior? So, you give Okay, let's go
back to that. So, you give someone your
number, you message them back
continuously trolling them, but you
don't see that as unacceptable. Are you
okay in your head, bro? Like, are you
actually okay in your head?
Well, I'm getting away from it tomorrow anyways.
I'll be away from this tomorrow anyways,
bro. So, it'll be Grezy's problem, not mine.
No, I don't care that you didn't want to
go out with me anymore. What the [ __ ] I
was complaining to you about the dating
game, you [ __ ] idiot. What the [ __ ]
You think if I got a number right now
and someone didn't reply, I would care?
No. or they replied and then stopped
replying. No, because it's the same in
this country. It's the same in America.
It's the same in Australia. I would
expect that to happen.
What the [ __ ] Why the [ __ ] would I care?
I'd be more surprised if it didn't happen.
Like, all they know how to do is play
victim and reply to negativity or to
reply to something that they can argue
against. Rather, they're the same, bro.
They're all NPCs. They're the same.
Non-playing characters. Grezy
brainwashed by Tik Tok. Brainwashed by
Instagram. Oh, look up when you're out
and about. Yeah. When someone's on their
phone, go and see the app that they're on.
You should try, bro.
They're all brainwashed by these
um applications that it's why they're
the way they are, [ __ ] You know what I'm saying?
That's why I don't deal with these
[ __ ] These are like
ages ago. These numbers, bro.
Why do you give your number?
Reply. keep replying if you're not going
to meet anyone anyways.
But what what is actually the point of
it? It's strange, you know?
I [ __ ] hate them. I do. I really hate
them. Anyways, moving on to this Smokey
B. He's not replied, has he? No.
Don't expect me back on here in two
weeks cuz I won't be back on here.
Not for a very very long time. It didn't
even take two days this time, bro. It
took one [ __ ] day, bro. And it the
weirdness already started. As soon as I
went live, the weirdness already started again.
They will never leave me alone. Never.
Never. It's like what that account said.
They will never leave you alone.
These people will never leave you alone,
bro, on this YouTube. I'm telling you,
it's really sad, bro.
I'll be leaving.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] One second.
That's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
And you got these people on here trying
to find out what terminal I'm going to
make across. What is it with you spastics?
Huh? What is it with you little mongos
on here? Anyways, let's let's talk about
you people now. Enough with these stupid
[ __ ] women, right? What is it with you
disabled grasses? When are you going to
get a life?
So, this is the last live stream um for
the month. Yeah. When are you people
really going to start getting a life and
stop being spastics every day on YouTube
and you people know who you are?
I think it's a good discussion. Greasy,
what do you think?
We should have a conversation about this, man.
enough to reply to negativity.
It's funny that ain't it? Or something
they can argue against. So backwards.
I hate them, bro. I really hate them.
Really don't know, bro. I [ __ ] hate these scans
so much, bro.
You know, I [ __ ] hate him.
[ __ ] hate him, bro. If I knew where
this can't live today, bro, go a [ __ ]
door and knock around in front of any
man. I hate him, bro. It's why I don't
like involving myself with them anymore
cuz I don't want to be around them. I
don't even like talking to them. I one
simple vent and look what happened, bro.
[ __ ] off, man. You know what I mean?
And I feel no way about it. I don't give
a [ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] bro. Like I
said, I'll do it in front of any man.
It's not a problem.
They're just boring, mate. I'm away in a
few hours. I said I'm going tomorrow,
you [ __ ] [ __ ]
I said I'm going tomorrow, you [ __ ]
And you don't even know what time I'm going.
You [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Bro, if I knew
where that [ __ ] lives, I'd be going on
her [ __ ] door, mate, in front of any
man, bro. Nope. You're not coming in. Bye-bye, [ __ ]
I hate these [ __ ] bro. I swear.
I hate them, bro. I hate them. You
really don't understand. I hate them, bro.
You can have I'm not spoken to any of these [ __ ]
Any of these [ __ ] I done one rant
and then the [ __ ] started. Okay, I'll finish it.
I [ __ ] hate them, bro.
message on my other phone, bro.
Stupid Australian [ __ ] Sort your
[ __ ] attitude out, you silly [ __ ]
You know what I mean? Yeah.
I'm so lucky. I don't know where one of
these people live, but I don't give a
[ __ ] if they're a woman. I'll [ __ ] them
up. I don't give a [ __ ] I don't give a
[ __ ] I will smash their face in.
Like, you don't understand. I will
really smash one in their face in my
neighbor if they wind me up enough. I
don't care if it's a woman. I don't give
a flying [ __ ] I don't care, bro. Know
what I mean? It's annoying, bro. [Music]
Go the [ __ ] away, bro.
No, I don't gamble anymore, bro. You
should know this.
Yeah, this woman's like, "Oh, let's go
out." She I'm not going out, bro. [ __ ]
off and leave me alone, bro.
Just [ __ ] [ __ ] off, bro. I hate them.
Seeing someone. Yeah, no [ __ ] You
weren't seeing someone because you can't
see someone in six days, you silly [ __ ]
I do gamble. Okay, bro. I gamble. I
gamble every day. I lose all my money.
Okay, bro. I'm not going to argue with you, bro.
Yeah, I'm not going to argue with you, bro.
I'm going to Mexico. I have a phone.
[ __ ] this, bro. I told you I get these
mood swings, bro. You don't understand
what I'm like, bro.
You don't understand what I'm like. I'm
a [ __ ] bro. I swear. Yeah.
Watch, bro. I'm going to get the last
word. You watch, bro. [ __ ] this.
I'm a crazy country. Let me turn this
part back on though. One second.
I'm gonna say, "I hope you get aed by a
kangaroo." That's what I'm going to say. Watch.
Let me think of something to say. Yeah.
I'm going to say, "I hope you get aed by a kangaroo."
And let me think of something nasty to say, bro.
I'm going to violate this con. I think I
already have another, don't I? Maybe one second.
I'm going to have to think about
something to say here. Yeah, I'm all
packed. I need to think of something to
say here, bro. One second.
Give me one second, bro.
I want to say something, bro. Listen,
you [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] I love how you
[ __ ] block me. Yeah. After you think
you got the last word and Yeah.
Obviously, you wasn't seeing someone
because nobody would go with you, bro.
You look like you're transgender. Yeah.
You ain't got any [ __ ] tits. And your
attitude [ __ ] stinks. Yeah. For
someone that's a [ __ ] three out of
10, you know? Okay. I'm guilty. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I started it, but I'll
finish it. But you can't though. You can
only come back and give attitude, but
you can't actually finish anything.
You're a stupid little [ __ ] [ __ ] And
you're making excuses that you're you
you're making examples about how you're
going to get circumcision. Bro, listen.
You're already [ __ ] trans
transgender. And at the end of the day,
if you got anything to say, you can say
it to my face. Like, I will meet you and
say what I've got to say to your face in
front of any man. any man you know
Australian if you got some Australian
friends I literally don't care so
there's no point you replying back now
unless you wear anything to say to my
face I will call you everything
literally to your face you will never
say anything to my face you stupid
little slag I hope you get [ __ ]
[ __ ] by a kangaroo and drop dead you
silly [ __ ] [ __ ] off and if you got
anything to say um yeah you can come say
to my face so bye-bye now [ __ ] Done.
Stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] piss me off, bro. I
don't think you're going to get a last word.
Uh, okay. I'm not going to Thailand,
bro. Okay. I'm just agreeing with it.
I'm just going to agree with everything
that you say. Yeah. I told her I'll tell
her about yourself in front of any man.
Bro, you mad? What the [ __ ] is this?
Think you're going to [ __ ] try and be
all smart and that, bro? I'm not going,
bro. Whatever you say, I'm not going.
I'm not doing anything, bro. I'm not
going to sit here and argue with you, bro.
And stop trying to um find out where I'm
flying from as well, so you can try and
get the flight stopped. Stop asking stupid questions.
Don't get [ __ ] by a kangaroo, bro. Stupid [ __ ]
[ __ ] ruin my mood, mate. I had enough
of these [ __ ]
spastics on here earlier.
I don't talk to these [ __ ]
Yeah, bro. I'm not going. Yeah. Yeah.
Good for you. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm not
going, bro. You're right. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm not going, bro. No. No. Yeah. Okay, bro.
I can turn this phone off now.
I'm blocking the [ __ ] as well. One sec.
I might call this Muslim. What's up,
bro? I'm not answering any of your questions, bro.
You told me that I'm not going, so I'm
just going to go with it. I'm not going
Yeah, bro. Okay, bro. I'm not going.
You've said it about a million times.
I'm not going. Okay, I'm not going to
argue with you.
I'm literally not going to argue, bro.
I'm not trying to convince you that I'm
going or not. If you're telling me I'm
not going, okay, I'm not going. You've
said it about a million times. Have you fooled?
[ __ ] hell, bro. If you if you're
telling me I'm not going, okay, I'm not
going. If that's what makes you feel
better, bro, what why am I going to sit
here and argue with you all day?
[ __ ] argue with you all day, bro,
about whether I'm going somewhere or
not, bro. Like,
[ __ ] hell, bro. That's pointless. [Music] Hello.
What are you doing? You going out? Yeah.
where you going central? Yeah.
You're not drinking, are you? Oh, no.
No. No. No. You need to pack that in.
You know, you'll go blind if you don't
pack that in. What do you mean pack that in?
I like you that drinks every day. I
don't I haven't drunk for about two
weeks, actually. No, you drank the other
day. Oh, yeah. Well, I had two with my
sister. Yeah. Yeah. Well, I had two
drinks. No, I don't go out and drink all
the time. I do go out and socialize.
Yeah, but you need to [ __ ] that in. Yeah.
Yesterday Oh, yesterday you thought I
was drunk in it. Yeah. So, [ __ ] I
couldn't stop laughing it. I know.
Yeah, man. But
Oh, I might I might I might come. I
Yeah. Where where do you want to meet?
Meet in this square somewhere.
Okay. Then what time?
What now? In it. Whenever you're ready.
Okay. Well, I'll leave in 10 minutes.
Yeah. Yeah. Leave in 10 minutes. Well,
I'll text you in it. I I'll have number.
Yeah, I'll text you. No. Have you got my
other number? No.
Oh, well, quickly take it down because
um in case this battery died. Just can't
you just text it? All right, I'll text
you it. All right,
I'm not going.
Straight. I'm not going, bro. [ __ ] that.
She needs to pack that in. She'll go
blind if she don't pack that in.
I can't believe I told her to get [ __ ]
by kangaroo. Yeah.
You need to pack that in.
You just [ __ ] pass that in, mate.
I said get [ __ ] by a kangaroo in it.
You need to get [ __ ] by a kangaroo.
That's funny, bro.
Do you want my opinions to be?
Uh uhhuh. Dell [ __ ]
They're all the [ __ ] same is what
they are. All the [ __ ] same.
that they can argue against.
They're all the same.
They're all the same, mate.
They're all the [ __ ] same Harry.
I'm generalizing them and putting them
all in one basket.
No, they definitely all the same. Definitely. But
that's why [ __ ] with them.
Waste of time. Waste of money.
trying to be on Batman.
You remember that rainbow um greasy [ __ ] bag?
He had to pack up work.
He had to pack up work because of the
shame being caught by the Nun, isn't it? [Laughter]
I can't stop laughing at that, bro.
How the [ __ ] work? Well, as I say this,
I got my friend M to contact this girl I
met in Slog last Friday.
And she replied
and he replied uh she replied to him. I
said, "Why did you contact her?" I said,
"She blocked me, bro." Yeah, that was
the same with me in USA is he Yeah, we
want we have we have we want answers,
Grezy. Remember we want we want answers.
Do you remember Grievy? Do you remember
Grezy? I love Grezy. Grezy, do you
remember? Do you want my opinion, Zippy?
Uh. Uhhuh. Yeah. All comes.
It's so lazy.
Do you remember that one? Grezy.
Yeah. They're all [ __ ] That's what I
say to my mom. Yeah.
And you you fly. Yeah.
You have to [ __ ] pack that in.
Why do you think my prick's so sore,
Grezy? You need to pack up that wanking
[ __ ] in, Grezy. You need to pack it in.
Why do you think my prick's so sore?
Do you remember
I always tease lady in it? Ladies, man.
Do you like my little hat, Grezy? Peter
belly and his little hat. It's cute, isn't it? Oh.
Do you like my little hat? My mama
bought it for me, Grezy. Yeah.
I'm going somewhere tomorrow. You need
to go somewhere. Harry, you've never
been a broad lad.
Yeah, you need to go, bro. You've never
been abroad, lad.
I'm going away tomorrow. You've never
been abroad, daddy. You need to go somewhere.
You didn't go Mexico, bro. You It was
supposed to be this year, actually. [Music] One second.
Grey, do you think I've got anxiety? Nah,
it was last year, bro. You didn't go.
Sorry, it was this year, but you didn't go.
How can I call anyone a liar?
Um, easy. You're a liar. Didn't lie
about America. Try again. Yeah, keyboard warrior. Bye-bye.
Yeah, I love you, Greavvesy. You know me
and you will always be friends to the
end. But you can see why I don't come on
here much anymore, ain't it?
You can see why I don't come on here
anymore, is it, bro?
It literally is the same [ __ ] It's literally
literally the same [ __ ] bro.
It's the same shite, bro. same people.
But apparently it's a community apparently.
No, no, no, no, no.
My friend said he wants to sue these
women. Um, Grezy, he wants to take legal action.
He said he wants to take legal action. Action. Sorry. Yeah. Bye-bye,
Harry. Listen, lad. I'm not Monty man or
Timmy. Try another channel. Gregie knows
what I mean by that, bro. Listen, I'm
not Monty Man or Timmy. Take it
somewhere else, buddy.
Gregie knows what I mean by that. Yeah. Uh,
me and Greavesy are boys.
Timmy's not in Turkey. Do you believe
Timmy's in Turkey, Greasy? Nah.
I think he's not a turkey, bro. [Music]
Anyways, you see how no one called out
that smoky beef for being a [ __ ] Yeah.
But no, this is why I don't come on here much anymore.
Ruby, this is why I don't really come on
here much anymore, bro. It's just a
weirdness. Like, I know you find it
funny and that, but I don't find it
funny. I find it really weird.
It's really, really weird, bro. Like I
know you find it funny and [ __ ] but yeah, mom. Yeah.
Yeah. Love you to me, mate. Love you to me.
All of you to me, mate.
I like getting the last word.
The last word, bro. for you.
But yeah, man. I mean, if you can't get
a conversation out of someone, Grezy,
you wouldn't even be able to get a
friendship out of someone, would you?
the [ __ ] non-playing characters.
But somehow, like I think you get to a
point where you just lose hope.
I think Ant-Man lost it a long time ago.
I've lost it the past 3 weeks. I've been
too busy. But yeah, you do lose hope.
You'll get to that point one day where
you just lose hope. Everyone's different.
Mine is like if anything if nothing's
changed in years, it's not going to all
of a sudden change now because the
amount of people that you've met,
they've all proven to be the same one
way or another.
You can't get a conversation out
someone. So, it's not all of a sudden
just going to change overnight, you know?
So, you got to be logical about it.
These women will never change ever. This
country will never change ever until you leave.
Yeah, I just told this Australian woman
to go get [ __ ] by a kangaroo.
Yeah, I told her to go get [ __ ] by a
kangaroo. The silly [ __ ]
This country annoys me, bro. I can't
wait until tomorrow. This country annoys me.
I hate the women. I hate the people.
I hate them, bro. I literally hate
women. Like, I really, really do. [Music]
I [ __ ] hate him. Greasy, bro.
I would love to get one of them and give
them a good hiding, bro.
I mean, greasy. Just a good oldfashioned hiding.
A good old [ __ ]
one big fashioned hiding. Well, you
don't even know. But a good oldfashioned
hiding, eh? You know what?
You know what that means?
Yeah. Do you know what that means?
You know what that means? [Laughter]
Good old fashioned hiding.
I hate him, bro. I [ __ ] hate him.
I hope they get you know what. I'm not
even going to say the word, lad.
You know the word. I'm not going to say
it on here, but I really hope it
happens. It's like what Ronny used to say.
It's like what Ronny used to say, lad.
[ __ ] them, bro.
[ __ ] hate them, bro. Really, really,
really hate them. Like, you don't
understand how much I hate them, bro.
Really, really bad, bro. Like, you don't
understand. They're not even women. They're NPCs.
Why do you even call them women? They're
not women. They're [ __ ] non-playing characters. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, they're non-playing characters, bro. Yeah.
I'm off to Turkey. I'm not going to
Turkey. Wrong person. I never said I'm
going Turkey. And it doesn't matter cuz
I hate women. And one pissed me off
today and I wanted to smash her [ __ ]
face in. I told her to tell me where she
[ __ ] lives. Silly [ __ ] [ __ ] Feminist [ __ ]
Don't get [ __ ] by a kangaroo, man.
[ __ ] off. Silly [ __ ] I hate them, bro.
I hate them. You don't understand, bro.
With a passion. I hate them.
I'm not even going to say all the things
I want to say, bro. Trust me.
But I'm not going [ __ ] Turkey. You
got the wrong person.
I never once said I'm going turkey.
Wrong person, bro.
I really want to smash this cunt's face, bro.
Cuz they annoy you because they think
they're smart, but they're not smart.
They're just stupid little [ __ ]
and they just piss you off, you know?
Like, they just piss you off. And I want
to do it in front of a man as well, cuz
you know, you get these men greasy that
think they're all hard defending women.
I want to do it in front of a man. Like
I want to do it in front of a man, bro.
Cuz they all think they're all big
defending women. These little [ __ ]
problem causes. You know what I'm saying, bro?
You know what I'm saying? I can't even I
I can't I don't even get LT's point now.
You know what I'm saying? Like I'm
different now. I don't go out
approaching anymore. Like,
bro, I'm stable, but these [ __ ] piss me
off, bro. You should have let me carry
on with that Morgan thing, bro. [ __ ]
her. She deserves it. She deserves a
good oldfashioned hiding, bro. She
deserves it, bro. [ __ ] it. They're not
meant to defend themselves. They want to
be [ __ ] They want to try and be
smart with people. Let them get
battered, bro. Leave them. You know what I mean?
That's as harsh as it sounds.
And I'm not drinking, bro.
I don't really drink anymore.
just been too busy, you know.
See, I think it's okay to hit women.
There's nothing wrong about it all. They
want to be funny little [ __ ]
and awkward little [ __ ] Try and be
clever. [ __ ] them, bro.
They deserve it, bro. [ __ ] them. Yeah,
just one punch though. Only one punch.
Just one punch across their face and
that's it, bro.
Just like if that USA Easy was here now.
Just one punch.
Just one hard punch across that face and
that'll be it.
Yeah. Nah. [ __ ] off, bro. You're boring.
Allow it, bro. No one cares about you.
[ __ ] off, bro.
You're borrowing, lad. You're not You
want a little talk? Come to London, bro.
And you can have a talk. You're
borrowing now. Bye-bye.
[ __ ] off, bro. You're gone.
You want a talk? Come to London. You
know where I'm at. Bye-bye, [ __ ] I
don't do talks with keyboard warriors anymore. Bye-bye.
You're boring, mate. Get a life. Get off of YouTube.
Like, unless you're going to do
something, bro. I'm not talking to you.
Unless you want to talk face to face, I
ain't talking to you. You're boring,
bro. You done it on Monty's a couple of
weeks ago. [ __ ] off.
So, yeah. No, it's not. What the [ __ ]
These women deserve it, that boy. They
want to argue and try and be smart and
try and be funny.
I would love to [ __ ] that Australian one
up, bro. You don't even know. I would
love to just go to where she lives if I
knew where she lived. They just gave her
give her a good hiding, bro. Just a good
old ass whooping. just to kick up the
backside. They annoy me that much. I
hate them, bro. And then when you've got
them [ __ ] replying to you trying to
be all smart and that like
I hate him, bro. Like really, really,
really hate them. Like, you don't
understand how much I hate them. You really don't.
So, I don't get involved with these
[ __ ] no more,
you know, cuz they just give they're just annoying.
Just like that. USA. Is it bro?
No. I just argue with this stupid
Australian [ __ ] He was trying to be
funny with me. I told her to go get
[ __ ] by a kangaroo. I got the last word. Stupid [ __ ]
Yeah. Stupid [ __ ] I hate him, bro.
I really hate women, bro.
I really, really do, bro.
I really hate it, bro. You have no idea
how much I hate them
in the West. Anyways, yeah.
You know what I mean?
No, I just hate them.
just the way they are. All of them stuck
up, ignorant, try to be smart. I just
hate all of them.
I'm not even going to say what I really
want to say on here, bro. But I'm
thinking it, bro. Like, I hate them,
They all programmed the same.
Yo, in London. Oh, really? Well, you
know, you know where I am, mate. If
you're really in London. You're in
London. Oh, really? Well, if you're in
London, you know where I live.
So, hurry up.
So, doesn't matter about what? Yeah.
Okay, bro. Listen.
Same as what I told the other guy. Come
to Plasto and I will meet you in Plasto.
If you don't know where it is, look it up.
Simple. Just like I told the other guy. [ __ ] freak
though. Go look it up.
P L A P L A I S T O W.
Yeah. Come, bro. It'll be uh it'd be
nice to see you get [ __ ] up.
Yeah. Come through, bro.
Nope. It's P L A I S T O W. There's no Y. Yeah. Simple.
The nearest tube is plaster. Yeah.
Get [ __ ] up, bro. It's going to be so
funny. Oh my god,
bro. You really think you're going to do
anything? Bro, you're a [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah, I will see you there. Don't
hide, bro. No one hides. The only one
that hides is you.
You don't scare anyone, bro. You caught
somebody off guard once about 2 years
ago. Hide from you, bro. You're a fat
[ __ ] What are you going to do to anyone?
And you're not even in London anyways.
[ __ ] off, bro. You're not even in London
anyways. You're boring. Pull through
They're scared of you, bro.
scared of you.
You're boring, bro. You're boring. No
one needs to ban you. No one's scared of
you. You fat mess.
Boring [ __ ] Don't do anything, mate.
You're not in London. [ __ ] off.
You're not going to do anything to
anyone. You're not even in London. Shut
up. What the [ __ ] would you be doing in London? You're boring.
You're not giving me anxiety, bro. Stop it. Yeah.
You really think anyone is scared of you, bud? Really?
You stupid [ __ ] [ __ ]
Watch what I'll be putting through your
[ __ ] head, bro. Watch. Yeah.
You're a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Just
stop it. You don't scare anyone, bro. I
want you to come so I can put something
through your [ __ ] head.
Like, I'm banking on it, bro. You're
coming? Yeah. Okay, I'll wait, bro.
Yeah. You want me to turn up, bro?
You're not even in London. Shut up.
You're not even in London, bro. Shut up.
[ __ ] off, man. You're boring. You're not
even in London. What the [ __ ] would you
be doing in London?
Just stop it, bro.
We all know that your anxiety will never
you to come to London. He was even
anxious that time in [ __ ] Newbury.
Like, give it up, bro. You're not
anywhere. Shut up. You're boring.
After today, for more than a month, bro.
Oh, even though I've only got away for
two weeks. This is so weird, bro. Not
even 24 hours and it's weird again.
This is weird again, bro.
So, you're in London, but you're
traveling all the way to see me, but
you're going to get your ass whooped,
bro. You don't scare anyone. You don't bother anyone.
I won't be going nowhere. Oh, okay, bro.
I won't be going nowhere. You keep
telling yourself that, man.
You keep telling yourself that.
You're boring, bro. Bye-bye. Now
just turn up and see, bro. Just shut up,
man. And you're boring.
This is why I don't come on here
anymore, Steven Howard.
This is one of the main reasons I don't
come on here anymore, lad.
That's why I don't bother with this anymore, bro.
Don't even bother anymore with this [ __ ]
Yeah, man. So, don't expect me back, bro.
Will I come back then?
I can't even remember, bro. I can't even remember.
He's just some stupid
why I don't come on here much anymore, bro.
This is literally why I don't come on here anymore.
Cuz it's just the same [ __ ] every time, brother.
Same [ __ ] same people, same repeating, same atmosphere.
Oh, say boring. Y boring, bro.
I bring it on myself. I'll bring it on
myself, bro. You [ __ ] [ __ ] I went
live today and I had all of these people
starting on me. I had people started on
me a few days ago when I wasn't even on
YouTube. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. You people bring it on, but you
can't finish it. That's the difference.
You people starting anyone that's got a
better life than you, that's better
looking than you, that's got more money
than you, you continuously go for them,
but you can't finish it. No, no, no. You
people bring it on yourself.
You people bring it on yourself. Cuz
even even when people are not on
YouTube, you still do this. You still do
this. You people are jealous of anyone
that's got a better life than you.
Like, so no, you people bring it on
yourselves cuz you also do it when
people are not even on YouTube. You
never stop this [ __ ] You do this all
the time. I I went live today checking
to see if it was the same people. You
all started I done a video to this
Smokey B and he didn't reply. Starting
what you can't finish. You're boring,
bro. This is why I don't come on here anymore.
It's why you don't see me for weeks, 10
days, two weeks. It's going to be a [ __ ] month
from tomorrow, so I can't be asked with
it anymore. It's the same old. It's the
same people. All night spas. We've been
seeing the same people for years. Doing
the same [ __ ] for years.
So, I can't be bothered. I can't be
bothered anymore, bro. You always do
this [ __ ] bro. Should someone go live?
I shouldn't even be on it, to be honest.
These women are [ __ ] being rich.
They're real [ __ ] But
they're proper proper [ __ ] lad.
I hate women, bro.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking of
doing, Stephen. Me, you,
you can't. Well, obviously me, you, and
Grezy. I was going to add Joe in there,
but you can't do Joe cuz he's a he he
goes on J's channel. So, yeah.
Yeah, this Australian woman was pissing
me off today. Big Rich. Yeah, she was
trying to be like really, really funny
and smart. I wanted to smash her face
and bro. It's a good thing I didn't know
where she lived, bro. Cuz it it gives me
mood swings, bro. I don't want anything
to do with them anymore. You know, I
gave up on them because they're all
NPCs. You can't get a conversation out
of them. They all play victim. They all
reply to negativity and I don't want
anything to do with that. But this [ __ ]
was winding me up today, bro. Like just
earlier. I swear down if I knew where
she lived, I would have smashed her face
and it's why I can't be bothered with
them, bro. I hate them, bro. I really hate them.
Really, really do generally hate them, bro.
They're just [ __ ] They're all the same.
All the same [ __ ] All the same
I'm surprised I dealt with them for as
long as I did. To be fair,
they're they're all the same, but I
don't [ __ ] with them anymore. They're
all the same. They're all NPCs.
They're all non-playing characters.
Yeah, I was just saying I I just said to
her like, "Oh, the West is shit." Like,
you can't even get a conversation out of
a woman nowadays. Like, I went out two
weeks ago. out outside the gym and I
tried speaking and you couldn't even get
a conversation then the only
conversation you do get is I've got a boyfriend
and then she was like oh look inwards I
was like no it's not look inwards it's
look outwards because you don't have
this problem with Asian people Chinese
Thai anything but westernized people you
don't have this problem with so no it's
definitely definitely outwards it's
literally outwards because if you speak
to anyone right from South America
anyone from Asia uh even places that are
not third world countries, you don't
have these problems. Only with Australians, Americans, um
and English people, Canadian people,
they're all the same, bro. All of them
from the West, they're all no good. They
all watch Tik Tok. They're all
brainwashed by Instagram.
And what done it for me, uh, Big Rich,
is when I come out the gym two weeks ago
and I tried to start a conversation with
three people, I didn't even plan it and
you you got ignored by two of them and
one said they had a boyfriend. I was
like, bro, that is worrying. You can't
even get a conversation nowadays. If you
can't get a conversation, you wouldn't
even be able to get a friendship. And
with you wouldn't be able to get a
friendship, you wouldn't be able to get
a relationship. They're all [ __ ]
They're literally all [ __ ] They
have nothing in them, bro. The only
thing that they have in them is I've got a boyfriend.
It's boring, bro.
Super boring, lad. Yeah. I don't even
speak to them anymore.
Like I I I
don't even um talk to them anymore, bro.
The last time I tried was not last
Wednesday, the Wednesday before that.
Got a number, they didn't reply.
But you'll notice that they are all the
same, bro. They all um reply to
negativity. They all try to play the
victim. If you notice, they all do this
cuz they're all the same.
Yeah, they're all the same, bro.
They will never change.
Yeah, I hate England, rich. I hate
England, bro. I hate the women in
England. I hate the people. I hate
pretty much most things about this country.
I hate the people in the street starting
stuff they can't finish. Like, I hate
everything about this country.
You know what I mean?
Yeah. He's a real fat ugly bastard, bro.
Yeah. These women aren't normal, bro.
They're not normal, man.
Never change. Never.
Like I I'll tell you an example. I had
Big Rich, right? Big Rich. I've told
this story many times. I'll tell you,
lad. So, um, I was in I was riding a
bike in central London two weeks ago.
And you know how I was crossing I think
it was London Bridge. Maybe it was
Westmin Minister Bridge. And you know
how No, no, it wasn't that. Sorry. It
was I think I was on I weren't on the
pavement, but I think I went past the
red light, which I was nowhere near
crashing anyone. Like nowhere near
anyone. Nowhere near anyone's kids.
Nowhere near anything. And this fat
[ __ ] said, "Oh, uh, you're not supposed
to be there." I said, "Uh, I will go
where I want." Um, because obviously I
was nowhere near crashing her. It's none
of your business. It's you're not a
police officer. And I knew what I was
doing. I knew where I was going. Then
she started running up her mouth. I
parked the bike. It has like a stand. I
said, "If you got something to say, come
back and say it." She was with a man
running up her mouth, running up her
mouth and then walking away. Which then
thinks, well, what the [ __ ] bro? Even
dating is weird in this country because
it's not even just dating. Sorry. It's
the people. They start things that they
can't finish. They have a bad day. They
take out on other people. They then ruin
your mood, but then they walk away.
So, it's like, what the actual [ __ ]
bro? And then I was lost somewhere and I
was asking people for directions. They
don't know. They don't know. Even though
they were working in the place, I'm
thinking I shouted I shouted out loud,
"Well, I hope I don't get knifed there.
I hope I don't get [ __ ] I don't get
robbed here cuz everyone's going to watch."
They instigate stuff that they can't
finish. That's typical [ __ ] in this country.
Now with these Asian people, Big Rich,
um I had to lift my bike up something
that was damaged and it was hard the
same two weeks ago. It was done in the
same day. These two Asian people, they
stood on it, they helped me. By Asian, I
mean Chinese. And then they said, "Take
care." What lovely people, e what lovely
people. Um and then you compare them to
these English [ __ ] You know what
I'm saying, bro? Like they love to
instigate and start [ __ ] they can't
finish. They all do it, bro. In this
country, they all do it.
Like we get it. You got to we you have
you've had a bad day. You're pissed off.
You know, I I've got anger issues as
well sometimes, but I don't start
something I can't finish. That's the
difference. You know what I mean? Don't
start something you can't finish. You've
got me in a bad mood now. So, what is
it? you know,
and I weren't even that rude. I just
said, "I'll go where I want cuz it's the
truth." Like, you're not a police
officer. You're not the law. I will go
where I want. You're not You're not You
haven't got no authority to tell people
where they should go.
But they're all [ __ ] in this country, bro.
I just can't stand this country, bro.
It's not even just the women. It's all
of it. Right.
And then you there was this guy before.
Yeah. He almost crashed into this
bicycle. He said, "I'll smash your [ __ ]
I'll almost smash your face." And I
said, "Bro, if someone said that to me,
that bike would be going over their
head. That bike would like, you know,
cyclists in London, right? They will
find any excuse to start on people. Even
though you know when you're crushing
them, even though you know when they're
hitting them or they're hitting you,
they will look for any excuse to be a
[ __ ] and then not uh and then not
finish it. They seem to do this a lot in London.
Like they seem to find any excuse,
right? And it's not people from third
world countries, it's people from
London, but then they won't be able to finish it.
So what's the point of starting
something you can't finish? You know,
you've just put everyone else in a bad
mood because you've had a bad day and
now you're walking away like a little
[ __ ] Stupid, bro. I hate this country.
Hate it. Hate it with a passion. It's a
very depressing country, bro.
Like, I knew this when you couldn't even
get a conversation out of someone, bro.
I thought, nah, this country is [ __ ]
And then obviously with the whole bike
thing as well,
South America as well. Big Rich, you can
also go South America, but
the West is not an option, bro.
These women will never change here.
all the same NPCs nonplay characters.
But it's strange, Big Rich, cuz people
will tell you that you'll meet someone
and then [ __ ] but then your life
experience is so different. Your life
experiences show that you can't even get
a conversation out of someone big rich.
So what you go from that to all of a
sudden being in a relationship? Sorry,
bro. It's not believable.
It's really not believable. Unbelievable, bro.
This country will never change. Yeah.
Why would you want to go southern America, bro?
Why would you want to go to a westernized country? Yeah. Yeah, man.
Do you work big rich? If you if you
work, how much do you uh earn a month?
I told these people I was working even
though I don't work and they tried
making fun out of me.
I told them that I work Steven even
though I don't even work. But uh it's
funny but they believed it.
I said to them I was getting£10 an hour
and they were taking the piss out of it.
They were taking the piss out of it.
even though I don't even work. But yeah, it's funny.
What do you think of that greasy £10 an hour?
Yeah, that's all right. Is it?
What do you think of £10 an hour? Big Rich,
£10 an hour.
What's it like a100 pound for 10 hours? Greasy works.
Greasy is a hard worker, bro.
Yeah, I work in a bank, bro.
Yeah, it's like £13. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, baby. [ __ ] him.
Yeah, it's about 30 I think minimum wage.
Yeah, I can't give information on here, but
The thing is big rich there's too many grasses lad. So
I can't even say much on you think really bro
you can cuz people don't know who you
are but these people are real grasses on here bro
sados like proper sad spastics. Yeah,
proper sad and that they'll hate on
anything you do, bro. You work, you
don't work. They're always going to
hate, bro. These people are always going
to hate, man.
They'll never stop, bro. They'll never
stop. But I shouldn't even be on it,
bro. I was off here for like 10 days.
I'm going away tomorrow.
Like I shouldn't even really be on there, lad.
Cuz this place ruins your mood, bro.
This place really ruins your mood. I
tried to go to the gym today and it was
just ruining my mood.
I was going to go Milton Ke today, bro,
without even announcing that video. I
swear to God, bro. Yeah,
I told them I'd done one job. I made 90
in a day, bro. They started hating. What
the [ __ ] I told them I'd done one job.
Yeah. And I made 90 in a day. Oh, 90
nothing. Oh, no, no, no, no, no. Yeah,
these people are the ones telling you to
go to work. What the [ __ ]
Then they say, "Oh, 90 is nothing."
And I'm thinking these people are sat at
home, bro. Projected every day like the
same old [ __ ] These people. Oh yeah.
Yeah. But they just hating it. Big glitch.
What I did Yeah, bro. [Music]
So if you made £80 a day
for and you don't and you worked every
day a week, that's £2,400. [ __ ] hell.
That's quite a lot, ain't it? But who
could work every [ __ ] day, bro? Imagine that.
Who could work every day, bro? [ __ ] hell, lad. hell.
Do you work? Steven Howard
80 times. Yeah, it's
you can but
yeah. So you still make you still be
making over thingy a month. Two grand a
through the weekends.
Yeah, I make money big rich, but I don't
tell these people how I make money. The
little glasses, lad. Little glasses.
Little glasses. Do that. Yeah.
Yeah. Exactly, bro. Yeah.
I told her I made 90 pound in a day.
And then they're hating.
I could probably make about 110 in a
day, but it would be [ __ ] hard, lad.
Nah, obviously I didn't, bro. What a
stupid question to ask.
Just somebody that met me, we held
hands. Then when I tried to kiss, she
didn't want to kiss. Just the same old
[ __ ] in this country, is it? It will never change.
What a silly question asking me if I'm
rid her in this country. Nah, not a chance, mate.
I think I kind of gave up really from
then to be honest.
I just see it as a waste of time.
It's never going to change in this country.
You know, you've got nothing left to
prove. It will never change. Never. And
it was getting depressing, bro.
Like they even go on dates to waste your time.
Like they don't even go on dates to want
to be with you. They just do it to pass time. So uh bye-bye.
Yeah. There you are, loser. Bye-bye.
But yeah, they they go on dates to pass
time, Big Rich. So, it got to a point
now where there's literally no point
even going out.
There's literally like no point even
going out, bro.
Cuz the first step is
they're even going to say they've got a
boyfriend. If you get a conversation out
of them, they're going to give you a
number. Even if you get the number,
they're not going to reply. They're
going to reply and then stop replying.
Or they're just going to meet you and
never meet you again. Very rarely. So,
you don't really get anything out of
really trying anymore.
You don't really get out of you don't
cuz it's never going to change. So,
you're just delusional. You're just
eluded if you think it's going to change
cuz it won't.
You know, it's not negative. It's real.
It's positive in a way cuz you're
leaving the country. You got to be real
about these things, bro.
I just had like a long think about it
and think, oh, like it's been going on
for years. It's been going on for years.
Was a m was the main thing as well. So
commenting yourself by keep trying.
You're just humiliating yourself by keep
trying because it's never ever ever
going to change, bro. Like 3 years does
not lie. It's a long time. It's a very
very very very long time. You know
what point do you what point now do you
have to prove
like why would you meet someone to hold
hands and stuff and not kiss? I don't
get it, Big Rich. I really don't understand it.
Why they waste their time and your time?
I just don't bother with it anymore. It
just annoys me. I don't even like
talking about it to be honest, bro. It's
just annoying. All of it is just so [ __ ] annoying.
I really, really hate them. My hate for
them, you really don't understand. And
it's justified as well, you know. It is
justified as well. Yeah.
I really really hate them, bro. Cuz
like I don't care about smashing one of
them up. Like I don't really really
care, bro. Like about going and beating
one of them up. I don't care. It's just
like that USA Izzy that Morgan. I would
gladly [ __ ] her up. Like I I said like a
month and a half ago, listen [ __ ] I
wrote a load of [ __ ] on her Facebook. I
said, listen, what day are you free to
meet next week, Thursday, Friday, let me
know. All I wanted was a response. I
would have went up there and I would
have [ __ ] her up in front of her boyfriend
like a month and a half ago.
I I will [ __ ] a woman up in front of her
boyfriend that like you don't know me.
This is why I stay clear of them, bro.
And started this [ __ ] and to get away from it.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
Like you think I give a [ __ ] that it's a
woman. I don't care, bro. I literally don't care.
I I keep saying [ __ ] them up. I wouldn't
even [ __ ] them up, bro. All I would do
is give them one bang across their face
and that would be it.
And that would be the end of it, bro.
Just smash them in their face one time, bro.
You know what, Grezy? You know this
whole Morgan thing? Yeah. This whole USA
Izzy thing. I'm surprised her dad had a
go at me.
You know, like I don't know what they expected.
Like I don't know what her dad actually
expected to be honest.
Like did Yeah. You contacted her family.
Yeah. But I don't know what he actually
expected you to not do it when you got a
child basically mocking someone.
I don't think I done anything wrong. Me? No.
to be honest with you.
But I couldn't work with this um woman
[ __ ] women [ __ ] big like I tried to work
a little while ago. Yeah. And I had to
deal with these stuck up women and it
affected my work the whole day. There's
no there's no way I could work and and
deal with this problem. But
like there's no way you can work and
deal with the this this issue, bro. It
was giving me like mood swings when I
was trying to do it. You know what I'm
saying? But nowadays, I don't care about
it cuz I don't even try. So,
he doesn't look hard. I would smash his
[ __ ] face, bro. I'd rip them tattoos
out. Like, that's why I said to her,
I'll do it in front of your boyfriend.
I would do it. I would literally do it
in front of your boyfriend. I I'm not
asked. Right. That's what I'm saying.
I tried going to the gym as well, being
rich, but I've been slacking.
You can't work. Also, going to work and
and trying to fit the gym in is very hard. Yeah.
Also, when you work, it's very hard to
fit the gym in with when you're working.
Um, I noticed that. Yeah.
No, that that I don't need to go to the
doctors and get it sorted. It's already
been sorted. Give up with the [ __ ]
I've already done it.
I've already done it. Problem solved,
bro. The problem is dealing with them.
Once I stopped, all the problems went away.
It's not on my mind anymore. It was only
on my mind today cuz this stupid little
[ __ ] was arguing with me. I don't give a
[ __ ] about them, bro.
I don't give a [ __ ] about them. They're
all the same. They're all evil and love.
I don't care. I don't think about them.
They're never going to change. So,
what's the what's the point? Never going to change.
Like you once in the end big rich you
lose hope. I've already lost hope. I
don't care cuz I know there is no hope
in this country which is why I'm leaving
this country cuz I've been to Wales.
I've been Scotland. I've been all around
traveling. Having had to work for years
and I've not met anyone.
So I mean putting that together and
things get worse. You you you're in your
rights to lose hope. It's never going to
ever ever change.
I went out on Monday with my sister just
to the local pub to have like a few
drinks. I don't even go out anymore. You know,
I've completely lost hope.
And and you should lose hope. You're in
your right to lose hope. You're 27. You
got nothing left to prove, man. You
don't need to keep doing this till
you're 35. If something was going to
happen, it would have happened by now.
You know, it's it's as simple as that.
No, it's not. Sometimes I wonder what's
the point. I know there's no point.
There is no point.
That's why I've given up with it. I
don't care about it, bro. I don't even
use the escorts anymore. It's just I
can't be asked with it,
which is why I bought the TV. I've got
into like GTA and [ __ ]
It's not I wonder what's the point. It's
I know there's no point. It will never
change. 3 years is a long [ __ ] time, bro.
Now you can't even get a conversation
out of someone,
you know? It doesn't look good, does it? So yeah, man.
Why would you keep trying, bro, when you
know that you're going to get old and if
something was going to change, it would
have changed by now. You know, you you
can't see it because you might have not
been trying for years, but I see it, you know. It's
Yeah, it's depressing
and making me and when I was trying, it
was just depressing me and annoying me,
you know, and then when I gave up and
that then it wasn't I was just getting
tired and [ __ ] So yeah,
you need to lose that hope, bro. Cuz
there is none. Once you lose that hope
that cuz there is none, you will
understand your life will get better, bro.
No one ever, you know what I find so
mad, big riches, no one ever told me
this on the internet. If you speak to
women, they're stuck up or they'll
pretend they've got boyfriends or they
only reply to negativity. No one ever
told me this. When I was younger, they
made me believe that if I went out and
spoke to women that they were different,
that they'd give you a chance. I learned
they were all [ __ ] from my own experiences.
I learned from my own experiences trying
to speak to them and socializing with
them and ones I've been with that
literally, well, I can handle my heart
saying at 27, I've never met one that's decent. Never.
I can't even think anyone I've met, any
woman that I've met as decent. They're
literally all the same.
Literally, they're all programmed the
same. Just like exactly what you said.
So, why would I want to talk to someone
that's all the same? That's got the same
attitude as the last one and the last
one and the last one. It's stupid, bro.
I was um you remember that 20-year-old I
was meeting Big Rich when she was 19
and now she's 20. She turned out to be a
[ __ ] She turned out like when I met her
at first like when she was 18 she was
all right. Then when she was 90 like me
and then she turned out to be a [ __ ]
Really like entitled like she's a proper [ __ ] now.
Like a real [ __ ] like
she was like she just like being
demanding. She was always asking me for
money and money and money and if I
didn't give it, she'd have the armp and
[ __ ] You know what I mean? So
I had to cut ties with her cuz of the
entitlement and yeah, she was all right
at first, but then again, this is how it
starts. They're okay when they're young,
18, 19, but then they turn into [ __ ]
westernized [ __ ] the older they get. So,
so there's no point in even dealing with
them anymore, bro.
I'm like tired from the whole thing. So,
they would never change, never.
And the point is is like why even if you
get someone that goes on a date with
you, the date is going to be the same.
So, what are you actually going out for?
To get a number. They're going to say
they got boyfriends. Okay. You might get
a date. Okay, you might get a date, but
what's going to happen on a date? It's
always the same thing.
So why? It just doesn't make any sense
to even try, bro. So
it makes literally no sense even trying
in this country. Yeah.
Oh, and also they take the piss out of
people as well, being rich. Did anybody
on Reddit ever tell you that? Never told
me that. Did anybody
Did anybody ever tell you that on any
forums? No one ever told me that.
So the life bar really
bad bro big you can be decent looking. I
had a decent body as well. I've still
got a decent this body but I had a better body
before I used up all my time. I couldn't
and I couldn't go to the gym anymore.
And that's another thing that [ __ ]
with my head as well cuz it's like what?
So, you can be decent looking, you can
have a decent body, and you still can't
get nothing. That is strange, bro.
I've already worn a suit before. It
doesn't make a difference. You're still
going to get it. I've got a boyfriend.
I've got a boyfriend. I think the only
the only way of finding someone in this
country, big [ __ ] is if you're a
famous Tik Tocker
or like you got a million subscribers on
YouTube. I think unless you're one of
them, bro, you're not going to find
anyone in this country. [Music]
I think unless Yeah. you're a big
YouTuber or Tik Tok or or Instagram,
you're not going to find anyone in this country, bro. For real.
Don't know what your opinion on that is, Gez.
It's like what Ant-Man said. Unless
you've got a million subscribers on
YouTube or like million like a lot of
Instagram followers, they're just not
interested. I think he's right though. Yeah,
honestly, bro, cuz people watch people
like them apps nowadays, you know. I
think unless something like that, you
got no chance in this country.
Yeah, it's true, man.
What do you think, Grey? I think that's true. Yeah.
What do you think, Gregy? Huh?
Do you want my opinion, Zippy? Aha. Arrow Hunts Daryl CS.
Yeah, Greasy. That I don't know why that
USA is he didn't say yet. Like her
boyfriend couldn't beat me, bro.
He looks hard. He don't look hard at
all, bro. Oh, [ __ ] him up, bro. I ain't
got no tattoos.
Am I out tonight?
Did you listen to what I just said for
the past 1 hour or so?
I guess you didn't listen to anything I
was saying, huh? More for me, eh?
I guess you didn't listen to anything I said. Whoops.
I know that made you laugh in it, Greezy.
I know that probably made you laugh in it, Greezy.
I've literally just been explaining
stuff for like the past hour, bro.
But I wouldn't go out to this trip
because I don't like drinking.
Cuz I don't like drinking, bro. I don't
drink much anymore.
Why would I go out and just drink? It
don't make sense.
Yeah. Well, I'm not her dad.
Yeah. She keeps contacting me. She's
Muslim, man. And I'm not converting to Muslim.
I'm not converting to no Muslim, bro.
Nah, I don't find it fun, bro. I've got
big bigger things to do. I'm going to
Thailand tomorrow, man. I've got bigger
things to do, bro.
Don't waste time and money here anymore
trying to get me to convert. Why would I convert, bro?
I'm never converting.
And that Pakistan girl was a [ __ ] as well.
She stopped replying. See, they just
meet people to waste their time, your
time, and their time.
It's pointless, isn't it?
This [ __ ] Right.
Can't tell to be by
me, bro. I can't become them. I like
piggies too much, Rosie. I like piggies.
I love piggies.
What are we going to do moving forward?
Well, I'm going to Thailand tomorrow
and I don't plan to ever try again in this country.
Yep. Sounds about right.
To be honest, I don't even like talking
about it. It's just depressing, bro.
Yeah, I'm surprised Scott was uh
surprised I was messaging him to be fair.
I mean, his daughter did start it. Yeah. Yeah, man.
I hate her, bro.
I try [ __ ] with her, but she never
replies. Even outward, she never
She never replies. Yeah.
Why does this [ __ ] never reply?
They don't know about me, mate. They
don't know about me. Uh
You make family in it.
You'll never know when you fall in BS deep.
It's so weird how she went bipolar like
that. Is it?
Wonder what the bitch's problem is, bro.
She had my comment again. I'm so
you need to chill out.
Yeah, I got some mad message, boy. It's
still there, is it?
Oh, bless you.
[ __ ] [ __ ] boy.
Something wrong with that, mate. Stop [ __ ]
Hold up. I'll beat you up in front of
your boyfriend, man.
And yeah, I don't like guys that try to
defend women, but nothing more annoying than that.
They say they're weaker and they can't
defend themselves, but the whole point
is they're not supposed to defend
themselves. That's the whole point.
They're not supposed to.
That's literally like the whole point is
they're not supposed to defend themselves.
We're not fight We're not making it a
fair fight so they can defend
themselves. You know what I mean? small my Stand bar,
bro. I want to I want to smack her on
her face, bro.
But I really do.
enough to just give a punch in her face,
but like this.
Know what I mean? But just a big punch.
Oh, I lost my little cap. Yeah,
I'd love to punch her, bro. I was
getting a good body in the gym, bro. But
I couldn't find a time to go.
I didn't find the time, bro. Yeah, man.
Not my bed.
I ain't got time for anything to be honest, bro.
Yeah, big rich.
So, how do you get sex nowadays? I guess
you just have to use escorts, isn't it? Yeah, bro.
See, I would have stayed at I would have
stayed with that 20-year-old if she was
if she weren't such a [ __ ] She would
have been good enough for me. But she
just turned into a complete [ __ ]
asking me for money. Get your own money, bro. Yeah,
What? Do you use escorts, big witch?
How do you get a [ __ ] nowadays
without an escort? I don't think you
can, can you?
No, I don't think you can, bro.
I was saying that big bricks, I've got
an escort story for you as well.
You want to hear it quickly?
Ah, you're going to laugh at this, but I
can tell you it quickly. Even escorts
are not the answer.
I can tell you if you want.
So basically, I was grafting all day.
I came back to East London. I was like,
"Oh, I fancy a [ __ ] because [ __ ]
are my thing." So I went to this escort
house, which I normally go to. And there
was four of them and there's like, "We
can give you a [ __ ] but you can't
come in our mouth." And I said, "Well,
no, I don't want it then. Why would I
want a [ __ ] if I can't come in your
mouth? If you can't finish, that's ridiculous.
So then I had to contact an escort that
I already knew and I had to go all the
way past Wembley,
which is about 30 mi. And I was like,
"What the fuck?" So
it's like you can't even use escorts
anymore really unless you get with one
that you know. Who would want a [ __ ]
if you can't finish in their if you
can't finish? That's so dumb, bro. You
might as well masturbate. So,
no, I'm off tomorrow, bro. Off tomorrow, lad.
This [ __ ] Australian woman, Mr. B,
was giving me grief today.
I'm off tomorrow, bro. I've got my bags
packed and everything. I'm off.
No, she was giving me grief, mate.
I wanted to give her a good hide. And
so yeah, like even the escorts, they say
that like they've got attitude problems
now as well, bro. So
there's nothing in this country, bro.
You're basically [ __ ]
You're basically [ __ ] now, bro.
You can't, bro. [Music]
How do you get women in this country,
Mr. B? Like, what do you have to do?
Yeah. You can't you can't get anything
in this country, bro. [Music] Mr.
Mr. B, how do you get women in this country? Huh?
Would you ever do deliveroo big rich?
Would you ever do deliver as a job?
Yeah, it's good, bro. [Music]
You should do deliveroo big rich.
Yeah, man. To give it a little whirl.
I done it like three years ago, bro.
Yeah, I made like 40 pound three years
ago. Should try it, bro.
Give it a little while. Yeah, bro.
Deliveroo is a good job, isn't it? Big Rich Deliveroo,
you should do Deliveroo, though.
Yeah, that's all right. That
And you know what I hate about escorts?
They clean your dick before they suck it
big rich. Like I prefer dirty [ __ ]
that don't clean your dick.
I don't know, bro.
I prefer dirty [ __ ] And to be honest
with you, when I come back here, you
know, I was thinking about this the
other day, bro. I want to go for a drink somewhere
that ain't London. Like maybe I was
thinking again like Nottingham
just by myself, you know, some head
space. You know what I mean? Mr. B. Less
stuck up [ __ ] less competition. Just a
nice drink somewhere else, you know?
Just jump a train somewhere. Jump a
train somewhere I've not been or I've
not been for a very long time and just
get some head space. You know what I mean? Gy
like just some just a head space
somewhere. You know what I mean? Grezy
just jumping on the little train with my
little cap and just go for a drink
somewhere out of London. You know,
you never know. Grezy.
Oh, I lost 20 pound in the pub on Monday
when I was with my sister, bro. I swear
to God if my sister weren't there, I was
going to put a chair through that
[ __ ] machine, bro. It weren't my local pub.
It weren't my local pub. But
yeah, I was going to put a chair through
that [ __ ] machine, bro. I'm not even joking.
It was a pub, but it wasn't the pub that
I usually go. I was going to put a chair
for it, bro. [ __ ] annoying as [ __ ]
man. I put 20 pound on the far roulette,
but apart from that, no, I don't gamble,
bro. No, no, nothing. Nah.
What do you think of that, Greasy?
Jumping a train somewhere and just
having a drink somewhere else, you know?
It's cute, isn't it?
Oh, what the [ __ ]
What the [ __ ]
What the [ __ ] Grezy?
What did you do to my my phone?
What did you do to my little phoney?
But yeah, [ __ ] women. I'd rather just
play the little characters.
I don't even get a sex drive anymore to
be honest, bro.
I don't even get much of a sex drive, mate.
I'm not bothered.
You know what I mean?
Yeah. I'd rather just play the little characters.
Greavves, if I don't go to work, how am
I going to afford the little characters?
How are you going to afford the little characters? Greavvesy.
They're little characters. They're not
cheap, you know, bro. at
not having it at all at all.
I'm going to miss his lady.
Why you still there, Grezy?
I like greasy greasy.
I need to buy GTA 4, man.
You're scared of a zipper.
Oh, bro. I love this. All night spas,
bro. I see him everywhere, man. All
night spas. I see this guy everywhere.
I don't know how you can still do this,
bro, after years. I really don't know.
I really don't know how these people
this off the years, but they're [ __ ] bro.
I just asked Jane to give me a little
call. You know, one of my friends the
other day. Yeah. When I come back from
grafting, I asked her if she could give
me cuddles and rub my feet. Like nothing
sexual, Mr. V. Just like foot rubs. I
was [ __ ] mate. I was [ __ ] Yeah.
Just a little Just little rubs. Yeah.
There's little footw clubs.
Yeah. Rubs. Oh,
that's so cute.
I'll never forget that day. I was at my
mom's and my foot was pounding, bro.
Just parano tentitis [ __ ] I was going
to wake my mom up for foot rubs.
Have you ever had that big [ __ ] peranal tentonitis? Oh, mate.
Oh, it almost killed me, bro.
And had to go on some of these dates
with a limp.
I don't know how I got I think I might
have got the police station or I might
have banged it and had to be on these
painkillers. It lasted about 6 weeks.
Yeah. It's [ __ ] horrible, mate.
It's basically where your foot frogs.
Um, and you can bar I could barely walk,
bro. I had to get my friend to like cook
me stuff and things. I couldn't walk,
bro. And every time I tried to walk, I'd limp.
Yeah. I went to a date limping, bro. Oh,
it's horrible times, bro. And he'd wake
me up at like 4 in the morning, grooy.
And I said, "Oh, yeah." I said to the
woman like, "My I had I had a foot
injury in it." So I might be limping.
Oh, it was stinking, bro. It was
stinking. 6 weeks it [ __ ] took to go.
It used to wake me up at 4 in the
morning pounding. Grezy, I was at
ladies. I was looking for tablets. I was
looking for tablets, bro.
It was horrible, bro. Horrible.
Horrible, mate. And I remember having to
go to the doctors and walking to the
doctors, bro. Oh, mate. Oh, they they
they put me on [ __ ] Dakota. Couldn't even walk.
Gy, I wanted I wanted foot rubs. Foot massages.
I'm going to ask Jane to give me some foot rubs.
Yeah, I was looking for tablets, bro. I
woke up. Yeah, I was at my mom's 4 in
the morning and I was looking for pills,
mate. I don't know how I got down the stairs.
What? He used to wake me up at 4 in the morning.
Bro, wake you up, bro. Wake me up, man.
Grezy, who's your favorite character
from GTA? Mine's Nico.
There's some uh Instagrams where he goes
flying. He goes
and he goes flying. Right.
If I don't go to work, I won't be able
to afford the little characters.
[ __ ] hate work, bro. It's [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
I hate it, bro.
I hate it, mate. Would
you do you hate work being rich? You
must hate working in it. I think everyone does.
Everyone hates work, I think. But
I guess it depends, isn't it? Yeah, [Music]
you should get into subleting, big witch.
You should get into subleting houses,
bro. You'll never have to work again.
But to be honest, bro, it sounds easy,
but there's a it's a lot of
responsibility, you know,
like subleting and [ __ ] It's a it's a big responsibility.
Like it sounds easy. It is easy compared
to most jobs, but it is it's like
it's not the same as making money from
YouTube, but it's still pretty good.
I mean, I had to work for three years. So,
imagine that big witch. 3k a month, right?
3k a [ __ ] month.
Yeah, but the responsibility is [ __ ]
They claim some cons as well, but yeah.
How much have you got in savings? I
don't even have that much in savings,
bro. I've got like maybe one and a half in savings.
Just savings. But it's better than
nothing, is it?
Yeah, I guess it's better than nothing.
But you wouldn't want the responsibility of it.
That's the annoying thing really is the
responsibility of it
cuz it is a responsibility. Whereas if
you work, you don't really have a
responsibility. You just work. You earn your money.
Yeah. I ain't got nowhere near that,
bro. I'm slacking, bro.
I ain't got nothing. I ain't got that
kind of money in savings. I whisper.
There was this guy. He used to make [ __ ]
40k a month on YouTube. Big Rich.
There's me. I didn't make nothing on YouTube.
I didn't make anything on [ __ ]
YouTube the whole time I had that channel.
Would you like to be a landlord, Big Rich?
You should be a landlord, bro.
You should be a landlord, Greavvesy.
Yeah, there's no way to make money now,
Big Rich. There's no way to make money.
There's not really a way to make money
anymore. There's no money in gambling.
It's not as easy to get jobs. And then
when I done deliver like 3 years ago,
bro, it's not bad because with that,
yeah, with Deliveroo, you can work when
you want. You see,
when you want, start when you want, and
finish when you want.
That was the only good thing about that
years ago, you know. Now you can't even
get accounts from them, but
that was a really good thing about that.
It's still [ __ ] But
that was the only good thing
about them kind of jobs.
Start when you wanted it.
I can imagine Greavvesy on the little
bicycle. Oh, bless you. Imagine little
Greavesy on the bicycle. E,
that's so cute.
on the little bicycle and delivering food. Bless you.
But the thing is with that, you can only
make money in London as well.
If you do them kind of delivery jobs or
something, you can only make money in
London. That's the only problem with
that. So, if you live out of London,
it's not an option.
Trust me, bro. You can make money with
it in London,
but not out of London as much.
What do you mean?
You should do um you should do delivery.
You should do deliver
So Gre, you sure you've got it, bro?
Or have you just self diagnose yourself?
You self diagnose yourself in it, bro.
Yeah, but there's bikes where you don't
carry it on your head on your back. Sorry.
Yeah, but there's there's bikes to sign
where you don't put it on your back. You
just put it on the back of the bike. Yeah, man.
That's the thing. Greasy. Greasy
delivering food. Oh, bless you.
Bless you, Graves. Bless you in life.
Ah, bless you.
Bless you in life, Grezy. Yeah, mom. Yeah, Grezy. Gy.
But yeah, there's bikes where you don't
have to do where you don't have to put
in your back,
you know, Greavves, you know, years ago,
I don't know how I used to do my job, you know, [Music]
under the stress I used to be under
grievy. I don't know how I used to do my job. Really? Yeah.
Don't know how I used to
Don't know how I used to do my job. Yeah.
Grezy used to like it when I used to go
mad, didn't you, Grezy?
Now me and Grezy, we're going to meet up
for a tea party.
We're going to meet up for a little tea party.
God bless you.
Bless you, Grezy.
So if I go out today clubbing greasy and
I approach a woman, what will she say to me? Boyfriend.
Oh, I hate that boyfriend [ __ ] It
really grinds my gears.
They say they've got boyfriends, isn't
it? Boyfriend, bro. [Music]
must be stuck in their head, bro.
Yeah, most of the Now, you know they're
trying [ __ ] because most of the guys I
know, they're all single. Now, don't get
me wrong, some of them are in relationships. Yeah.
But a lot of them like are single.
I'm trying to think like there's so many
guys I know like and so many of them are
single like people that I've met in real life.
That's how you know they ain't got boyfriends. Russia,
they just they just aren't interested in this country. Yeah,
Franklin is a gorgeous character, isn't it? Grezy
little Franklin. A He's cute, isn't it?
Oh, man. He says, isn't it? He's a
lovely little character.
I like Franklin. He's a good character. Yeah.
Yeah. But there's one problem with that, bro.
There's one problem with that.
There's only one problem with you doing that.
Let me put this handsome fellow on.
Um, the problem with that is,
listen to this greasy.
The problem with that is
you said that you're going to Spain,
but Spain is full of English people. They're westernized,
so you're still going to get my friend.
Yeah, you're going to Spain, but Spain
is full of English people, so you might
as well just stay in [ __ ] England.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's full of clunge.
It's full of English women that aren't
interested. Same as this country.
Yeah. Full of dis I've never been to
Spain, but Ant-Man's told me. And
obviously it's full of English. It is
for the English people. I know that. So,
but try it, bro. I'm not telling you
what to do, but don't cry if you if when you hear boyfriend.
Look at look at um Franklin.
He's such a handsome fella.
You know, sometimes I go downstairs and
there's some people playing GTA um five
on my Xbox. They must love the little
characters on the TV, in it.
Yeah. Portugal was good and France, too.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
Cuz you could easily get women in
France, isn't it? Yeah.
Yeah. They never say they've got a
boyfriend in France.
[ __ ] say it everywhere, mate. I told
you, Big Rich, the only place you're not
going to get that is Asia.
The only place you're not going to get
I've got. But I don't know. But go if
you want. I don't know. I'm sure you've
been to Spain. From what I'm assuming,
it's English people. So,
it's the same people you get here. So,
Western is no good. I think the only
place you're not going to get I've got a
boyfriend is Asia. Maybe South America.
Asia and South America. That's the only
place you're not going to get it.
Like when they say they've got
boyfriends, how many do you think they
do? I'd say three out of 10 do.
I think three out of 10 actually have boyfriends.
Most don't have boyfriends, bro. No way.
Load of single men out there. About one
in four, one in five guys have boyfriend have girlfriends.
So they don't have boyfriends. They're
full of [ __ ]
No way, bro. Nope.
How many do you think actually have
boyfriends? I think three out of 10 have boyfriends.
I think most of them are full of [ __ ]
Cuz you got to understand, you got a lot
of like feminists nowadays.
You got a lot of single men, you know? So,
who are their boyfriends?
Think of it, bro. Like they all are
utterly full of [ __ ]
Yeah, maybe some do. Like there was one
the other day I approached and she
showed me her boyfriend on the phone
which Yeah. Okay. That was the rare one
that maybe had a boyfriend, but most of them don't
because you get loads of feminists,
right? You get lots of single guys. You
get more. There's more women on Earth,
but yet all these women have boyfriends.
It doesn't make sense.
What countries have I flown to? That's
for me to know and you find out.
I've flown to more than you. Put it that
way. But yeah, they hate men and um so
it just doesn't add up how like
you have all these
women that are feminists that hate men.
Like you said, all these men that are
struggling, more women on earth than
men, but yet all these women have boyfriends.
It doesn't add up, bro. The numbers
don't add up. I sure have.
And it's not a suitcase. It's a duffel
bag. The duffel bag.
Not used a suitcase for years. Yeah.
But I'm off tomorrow anyways.
Yeah. Go bag, bro. The duffel bag comes everywhere.
Yeah, bro. P F A I K7.
Yeah, I always travel like wherever I go.
I'll never forget that day. Yeah, I went
to Scotland. I literally went to
Scotland to [ __ ] escort and come back.
I went to escort I went to Scotland.
Sorry. I checked into the hotel.
I done some approaches, got nothing,
[ __ ] an escort and come all the way
back. I was a crazy [ __ ] back then,
big rich. I was a crazy [ __ ] back then. Anyways,
add me on Snapchat, bro. Did you add me? [Laughter]
Um, am I not getting an early night for
my flight? Um, well, considering it's in the evening, no. No, bro.
Yeah, I won't be on YouTube for a month
um after today.
It's too weird. Joe,
I'm not telling you where I'm flying to
in in Thailand.
I'm not telling you.
And I never said it was first thing in
the morning. No, I never said that. Bro,
don't you worry. I will be there. Stop
all of these questions trying to get me
to slip up. I am going tomorrow. I will
be there. Stop asking all these silly
questions trying to get me to [ __ ] um
trying to uh trying to um You can only
go to Bangkok. No, you can't. Never. You
mind? I will be there tomorrow. Well,
I'll be on the plane then.
Don't you worry. It's happening. Stop
with all your little questions trying to
get me to slip up with that. I'm not
answering none of them. Simple.
There's nothing wrong with apple bag. What?
Yeah, I just mistake myself. I just corrected myself.
Yeah, I just corrected myself.
From the UK, you can only fly to
Bangkok. No, you can't. You [ __ ]
Uh, no you can't, you [ __ ]
I'm not answer I'm not answering any
more questions now. Anyways, bro, I will
be there tomorrow. Don't you worry. I'll
be on the plane there tomorrow. You
[ __ ] idiot. You think that you can
only fly to Bangkok? Okay, bro.
Are you still there, Joe?
Yeah. I sent you um two approaching
videos, Big Rich on Snapchat, and one of
the numbers didn't even [ __ ] reply, bro. So,
just to give you a um Yeah.
Oh, this Australian [ __ ] was annoying
me today, Joe. I wanted to go and [ __ ] her up. Yeah,
I wanted to go and [ __ ] her up, bro.
I hate her, bro.
No, they're new ones.
I'm just sending them to Rich.
Yeah, I wanted to [ __ ] her up today, bro.
I swear if any of these women piss me
off and I find out where they live, I'm
going to give them a hiding jar.
They start an argument and they're not
intelligent enough to finish it and then
they play victim. Boring.
Yeah, I just sent it to Rich.
No, you ain't getting that problem in Thailand, mate.
I tell you what happened, Joe. Right.
So, I messaged her saying, "Oh, like
dating's been hard." Like the past like
two weeks ago, I tried to start a
conversation with three people and they
they just weren't. It's hard enough to
get a conversation with them and these
westernized women are just like a tough
nut to crack. And then she started
coming on and being funny saying, "Oh,
like you need to look inwards. It's not
inwards. It's outwards." Cuz I never had
this problem with Asian people. Cuz I
told her I met different kinds of
people. And then she was being funny and
she thought I was referring to her and
she's like, "Oh, women don't owe you
anything." I said, "Isn't it funny how
women don't owe anyone anything when
they do shitty behavior? Isn't it funny
how that saying only goes when they do shitty behavior?"
And then she was like, "Oh, um, what's
the problem with me messaging?" She
thought I was referring to her. "What's
the problem with me messaging you and
then deciding not to meet you?" I said,
"There's no problem. I expected that.
We're not talking about that. I expect
all of the [ __ ] that comes with you cunts."
And I said that the problem is is you
done it on purpose. So what do you mean
what the problem? What was the problem?
You literally do it on purpose. You take
the piss on purpose. You leave people on
on purpose if you wanted an answer to
that. Well, we're not even talking about
that. But yeah,
I hate them, bro, so badly, bro. I don't
[ __ ] with them no more.
They're all the same, bro. Isn't it
funny, Joe, how they're fast enough to
reply to something that they can argue against?
And this time I didn't say about women
being this, being that. It's funny how
they're always somewhere to be seen
when they can argue.
They're always there when they can
argue, but apart from that, they're
never anywhere to be seen.
Makes you wonder, isn't it?
I told her to get aed by Kangaroo Joe.
She says, "Um, oh yeah, you speak in English.
I don't think you speak in English, she said.
I was like, mate, listen, you're from
Australia and you're trying to talk
about people speaking English. Really?
And I've done her stupid accent. I was
like, you want me to talk like you
[ __ ] criy, mate? Is that Is that Is
that English? [ __ ] off, you silly [ __ ] [ __ ] off. You know,
they're absolute [ __ ] mate.
What do you mean I never learn? I never
learn. I don't even try anymore, you idiot. Yeah, love.
Joe, you should do deliver.
You should give Deliveroo a go, man.
But I do learn, which is one of the
reasons I don't speak to them anymore. You know,
you would be buzzing. I'm not buzzing.
You know why I'm not buzzing? Cuz I
shouldn't have to leave my country
because of these [ __ ]
I'm having to go to a foreign country
because of these women and these people.
It's not even about women, just women.
It's the people as well. Nope. Yeah,
what do you think of it all, J? I think
it's all weird. Me, lad.
Yeah, but LJ's full of anxiety, bro.
That guy has got really bad anxiety.
That guy's got really bad anxiety. Like,
yeah, you you might have went on a plane
for 10 hours, bro, but it doesn't mean
anything. Like, the guy still got
crippling anxiety. Like, when have you
ever known this guy to work? Whenever
you ever known this guy to go out, like
he actually does have crippling anxiety,
bro. Trust me,
he is taking something before going on
that plane. That guy has got crippling
anxiety, bro. Trust me.
He's never been to Asia, bro. He's got
anxiety, bro. Just cuz he goes on a
plane for 10 hours, bro. He takes
tablets. I'm telling you, this guy, he's
not outgoing, bro. I don't know who this
guy what he tells you he is.
But he there's not going to be no next
um community barbecue because cuz no one
cuz no one ever comes.
So, I'm not doing it again.
I'm leaving my country because of these
women and these people. And after
meeting so many Asian people even
recently, I mean, like, [ __ ] Asia is
the way to go.
I don't know why they all shook to come.
They know where I am. They knew the
time. I wasn't joking.
I was [ __ ] with that USA Izzy a month
and a half ago, Joe. It keeps taking me
to where I met her, Joe. The bike keeps
taking me to where I met her.
It's like a troll, isn't it, Joe? Yep. Yeah, man.
No, Chinese women are nice. Chinese
people are nice.
But where do you live?
I ain't got no bad words to say about
Chinese people, bro.
They're the nicest people you'll ever
meet. Even the people that have got money.
I said to one, "Oh, sorry I'm a bit
late." I said, "Sorry." He's like, "What
are you being sorry for?" I said, "Oh, I
was a bit late." He said, "Don't worry. Don't worry."
No, I don't remember that.
No, Chinese people are they are nice,
bro. I even went to the gym today. There
was a Chinese guy. He was really nice.
He said, "Oh, how many sets do you have
left?" He said, "Take your time."
They're nice people, man. You know, you
take the piss, but they are actually cool people.
They're nice people, bro. They really are nice.
They're nice, bro. I'm trying to think
of any other Chinese people I met. Oh,
I've been to Middles, bro.
Uh, because it's not that.
It was actually a job interview. So,
did I cancel it? No, cuz I'm only going
for 2 weeks. Why did I cancel it, bro? No.
No. I was late to a job interview.
That's what it was.
And then you're asking me, which, bro, I
don't do that. I swear. I've already
swore in my mama's life I don't do that.
But then you've Listen, bro. Listen to
what you've just said. Why don't you
admit what you're doing?
Well, there's two reasons. A, cuz I'm
not doing it. And B, why do you think I
would not ever admit anything on here?
Like, use your brain. But I'm not I'm
actually not doing it. But why do you
think I wouldn't admit what I'm doing
even if I was doing it? Just use your
brain for a second, bro. It doesn't take Einstein.
Answer your own question that you just
asked me. I know I haven't booked the
hotel. I'm going to stay at different hotels.
So, yeah, you need to answer your own question, lad.
Just read back to what you've wrote and
answer it yourself, you know? So yeah,
listen, bro. I'm not answering any more
questions. I'm going and that's it. If
you don't believe it, don't believe it.
Stop asking questions to try and trip me
up, bro. If you don't believe I'm going,
that's on you and it I know where I'm
going. So simple.
End of story, bro. If you don't believe
me, then don't believe me.
No, I'm asking Joe. You asked me a
question. Can't you answer your own
question that you just asked me?
You just asked me
why don't you admit what you are doing, bro?
Yeah, I'm going to be tight for funds,
bro. I mean, a hotel was like £20 a
night. Yeah, I'm going to be really
tight for funds, bro. Yeah, really tight. Yeah.
Yeah. Super tight, bro.
Yeah, man. How do you know I'm going to
be super tight, bro? M.
Yeah. And man's been homie. I've looked
it up as well.
Yeah. 300, which would still leave you
with 1.2K. and 2K. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Yeah. It's because they ain't got a
life, Big Rich. It's because these
people ain't got a life, bro. Like, I
don't really comment here much anymore.
cuz it's just the same old [ __ ] Like
you come on here, these people start I I
don't really come on here anymore, bro.
You know, I go to my mom sometimes, she
follows my channel, but she sees I don't
really come on here anymore, bro.
You know, cuz it's just the same.
It's just the same [ __ ]
you know? I've got a lot of stalkers as
well, Big Rich. Like I've got a lot of stalkers.
A lot of [ __ ] stalkers, bro.
They'll never leave you alone either,
bro. That's another thing.
That's one country. USA is he's not been
a a Joe a bro.
But yeah, let's go by Yeah. Everyone
should admit what work they do when
people know your full name.
Yeah, bro. Everyone should do that.
Yeah, everyone should everyone should do
that, you know.
Yeah, everyone should admit what what
they do for work, bro. Especially if
they have your full name, bro. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
Why have you ever been to Asia, Joe?
Yeah, man's out there. He lives there now.
Yeah, man lives there now. [ __ ] Yeah, bro.
Yeah, he he's not coming back. He's not
coming back, bro.
That's actually fun. They made you leave
your own country and never come back.
But with me, it's not just the women.
It's the whole um
It's the whole like
It's the whole [ __ ] um
thing, bro. It's the whole [ __ ] up country, bro.
Yeah, I But I'll be coming back, mate.
Yeah, but I'm not doing that work.
That's the problem. I'm not doing that.
I'm not doing that roll of work.
Otherwise, I would.
You're not supposed to tell these people anything, bro.
I told I told these people I lost the
house Joe, but I never You see, I I tell
people what I want them to know.
You know what I'm saying? But like I I
told people I lost the house. I never
So, you know, I tell people opposites to
things, but the same really. I mean, you
should tell people you shouldn't tell
people. You should be able to tell
people four things, but you can't. [Music]
Me and you both, Richie,
I would love to [ __ ] these one of these
women up in front of their boyfriends
in front of one of these simps. I'd love
to do it, bro. You You and me both,
mate. [ __ ] hell.
America is not hard to believe, bro. I
messaged that USA Izzy about six weeks
ago on Earth Facebook and I said I will
come there on Friday um I think it was
Thursday Friday and I will [ __ ] your
[ __ ] up in front of your boyfriend.
Yeah. If they were about anything
then they would have just said Yeah.
It don't matter if they don't care or
not, bro. I done what I had to do.
Simple. I done what I had to do, whether
they care or not. Simple, bro. Like,
what the [ __ ] But I can start. I'm the
only one in London that can start [ __ ]
and finish it.
Well, it might sound like I am, but I'm not. So,
it might sound like I am, mate. Telling
you I'm not. Believe what you want, bro.
If you think that's what I do, that's
what I do. But I
what I had to do in regards to them. So
yeah, and I was thinking back on it, you
know, I didn't really do anything wrong
like messaging family and that. Nah,
they deserved it, bro. I I don't know
why the the dad had a guy at me. It's to
be expected, bro. It is to be expected.
You know, I used to have people mess
with my [ __ ]
family and [ __ ] and but
I don't think I've done anything wrong
to be honest.
Well, we'll be we'll have a better life
tomorrow anyways come tomorrow. So,
don't we have a better life?
We will have a [ __ ] better life, bro.
For two weeks and then we're back again.
Sorry, bro. Somebody sent me a voice and
uh Oh, what happened to you, boss? Oh, man.
You ever masturbate after you've drunk Coke?
You ever drunk Coke and then
masturbated? Oh, my burns your dick, mate. [ __ ]
I don't know if you've ever done that.
Really? Maybe. You drink Coke and then
you [ __ ] masturbate, bro. What the
What's the time?
Let's go get some milk, man.
My [ __ ] penis stops burning.
Oh, bless you.
Bless you, mate. Bless you, mate.
I don't know. [Music]
Joe's in denial if he says that he loves
working. No one likes working, bro.
No one likes [ __ ] work.
If they said you can get 3k a month
working or 1k a month on benefits, I
think I'd choose the 1k, bro.
Oh, no. In a way. No, but in a way, I
guess working is actually good because
you don't have to think about women and
all of that [ __ ] You know, you're so
busy with other feelings, you won't even
have time. But it is [ __ ] Like, it is [ __ ] bro.
It is [ __ ] But you know what it comes
down to at the end of the day. Like um
it is [ __ ] bro.
It is [ __ ] mate.
I won't [ __ ] live a [ __ ]
[ __ ] if they said 3k a month working
or 1k a month. I choose a 1k a month, bro.
What I would do maybe is maybe work
until I could basically get my own business.
Um, I do something like that. Maybe I
wouldn't want to work more than 6 months, bro. Get on [Music]
say he works Joe. Yeah. USA.
It's Tim. He says, "Imagine thinking
it's okay to proclaim hatred for all
women and think there's no
consequences." Followed by a Reddit ban.
A s a wild s appears.
You have to do a sound effect as well.
It sounds like someone's being strangled outside. Judge,
what the [ __ ] I want to play Franklin. I like Wait. Uh,
I might go and see Laney in a couple of days. [Applause] Ly
lane. I'm trying to download you, but you're
I don't read them. Yeah, man.
Yeah, man. Get yourself the Asian big
Mitch. You deserve it, bro. You work hard.
They're just not interested in this
country. Get yourself the Asia.
How am I going to see how am I going to
see Laney in a couple of days? Because
I'm going to see Laney via WhatsApp message,
you know, little cameras and stuff.
That's how I'm going to see Laney via the phone.
That's how Yeah,
bro. Why have you people like, you know,
going on holiday is not a big thing?
Like, bro, do you know what? I'll do a
video at the airport tomorrow. But I'm
not going to upload it until I come back.
I'm not upload I'm not uploading it. I'm
not uploading a video until I come back,
though. Two weeks. You I'm going to
upload it, bro. 100%.
Not that I have to, but I will do it.
You've been spending all day, bro,
trying to literally trying to get people
to slip up. Like, do you not see
yourself as you don't have a life, bro?
You've been spending literally all day
banging on about this Thailand thing.
You've banged on about it literally all
day. Like, bro, you're going to get an
airport video. That Why do you keep
banging on about it? You've said about a
million times, you're not going. You're
not going. You're not going. And when I
said, okay, if it makes you feel better,
I'm not going. You still keep asking
questions about it. I don't understand,
bro. It's so weird. You've been doing
this for hours, bro. I've been live
about three times today and all you have
gone on about is just time lapping.
Questions upon questions upon questions
upon questions upon questions upon
questions. Then you said, "I'm not
going." Then I said, "Okay, I'm not
going." So, what the [ __ ] bro? I swear.
It's weird, Dad.
They always hate, bro. I don't know why
they do it. Like, Big Rich, I How long
have you been on this community, bro?
Like, I don't go on here anymore because
of the same keyboard warrior [ __ ] the
same atmosphere, the same [ __ ] bro. I
don't really come on here anymore. Just
today I had nothing better to do cuz I
was just chilling today, bro. Well, I
did go to the gym, but
that's why I don't come on here anymore, bro.
It's so It's just so weird. And to be
honest, I don't even gamble anymore, lad.
I don't gamble anymore. So really, so
like there's not really no point in me
being on here. So
Oh yeah. Yeah. But
yeah, give yourself that Asia, bro. You
work it. It's not It's not too
expensive. The flights are like 600 700 pound.
You know, you like it there. I think I
think I will tomorrow, but I'm not there
yet. So anyway, it's got to be bad in
this country, bro.
Just the country just annoys me. The
people annoy me. The women annoy me.
They just This country is just so I just
hate it, bro. I really do.
I got older. I hated it. I hated it more.
I can't wait to get out to be honest.
It's annoying waiting around for things.
The rude people, the [ __ ] women,
the [ __ ] whole system. It's all [ __ ] bro.
Scotland, bro. I was in Scotland. Is it
easier? I've been to Scotland twice, but
I've only been to Edinburgh.
Even I was thinking of maybe going there
when I go back. Like I said, I wanted to
have like a time away when I come back
just for a drink somewhere.
Maybe Nottingham. I was thinking
Scotland, but Scotland's a bit too far. But
I was thinking of moving to Scotland at
some point, but I can't cuz my mom lives
here and she needs me. She's ill or
something. So I can't I can't um move
anywhere like that
in case um emergency with my mom or
something. He's quite elderly so
um but I've been thinking wouldn't be
able to move
to be honest.
Yeah, bro. What do you want?
Yeah, I've been to Scotland, bro.
It's not any easier in Glasgow now.
I ain't been Glasgow, but is it any
easier? Well, I've only been to
Edinburgh and to be honest, it gave London vibes
like stuck up tourist. It weren't as bad
as London, but the good thing about
Scotland was like it was a lot cheaper.
I mean, I could definitely just go
there, work there, and move there. But
it's my mom that lives here and stuff.
But I do like Edinburgh. It's my second
favorite city because it's nice. I just
like the whole the way it looks, you
know? It's nice. I've not been to Glasggo, but
um [ __ ] tall buildings, bro. Like, I
went into this woman's flat, this
escort's flat, bro.
Um [ __ ] it was so tall. The the the
the the ceiling was so tall, bro.
Oh, you're 20 minutes from Edinburgh.
Yeah, it's nice, bro. But in ter but I
think Newcastle was better, bro.
I kind of got women in Newcastle. But
they still played games and [ __ ]
but I don't know how Scotland is, bro.
I've only been twice. But
yeah, it should be easy in Glasgow.
But Newcastle was better than Edinburgh
or night out. Not the way it looks. I
ain't been Glasgow. So they said Glasgow was better.
They said Glasgow was better than [Music]
it is the same everywhere,
but I still think London's the worst.
It's the same everywhere, but I still
think London is the worst, bro.
Like, it's really bad in London.
Really bad in like my first one night
stand was Manchester,
big rich. But then that become [ __ ] And
then the women started becoming all the
same there as well. So, I've been
Manchester like 10 times, bro. I used to
just go there when I was born. I used to
just get the train there. But they're
all the same like you said. Yeah. But
hey bro, I need to go shop quickly. I'll
be back later. Yeah.