That one's fin. [Music]
I think you should join Oh
Yeah, I'm tired, bro. [ __ ] tired, but
put this fan on, mate. On all day. That's Yeah.
Where are you?
What the [ __ ] They just
what a mapping to save.
They just aren't interested in this
country. I'll do
in this country. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. What are you saying, man?
They just aren't interested in this country. Al,
they just aren't interested in this
country. You right, Captain?
Oh, you all right, Captain?
I'm trying to get on with my bloody
life, mate. And you're emailing me over [ __ ] YouTube.
You all right, Captain? One second. You
Yo, can you hear me now? Yeah.
You all right, Captain?
Can you hear me now, Captain?
Huh? Stop singing son. Yeah,
your old [ __ ] pair of [ __ ]
That smoke you be is a [ __ ] bro. I
done a video today. Yeah, 7 minutes
long. I said, "Show me your own key.
Reply to the message the video and I'll
come and slap you up, bro." I was
getting some mad mood swings today, bro.
When I was in the gym. This is why I
don't come on here anymore, bro. I don't
You see, I don't come on here anymore
cuz it's the same people with the same stalkers.
It's boring, bro. It's boring, bro. I
went live. Yeah. 2 seconds later,
another thing on that Red channel. I
don't understand, bro. Like, how they
can do this for years. It's got to be
autism, in it, like with these people.
Like these people, it's got to be autism
that they can do the same thing for
years and years and years, bro. Like,
it's got to be autism. Got to be some
disability in it. It's got to be, bro.
About 20. I've been slacking lately,
though, cuz I've been really busy. But I
have been like I have been going. These
people give you mad mood swings, bro.
And these [ __ ] give you mood swings
as well. I would just slap this [ __ ] up
today, bro. You don't even know, man.
You should let these [ __ ] get [ __ ] I
deleted it, bro. I just deleted it. I'll
put it back up if you want.
I'll put it back up, bro.
I called him a little Milton Kees boy.
Little [ __ ] bro. Little reject trying
to be from London. But I violated him,
bro. All he had to do was do a video and
I would have went there and slapped him up
cuz uh All right, I will. One second. Right.
Two seconds. It's uploading, bro. I had
it on all day. This guy was pissing me
off, bro. Yeah. And since he's come with
the hangouts and he I was going to go
straight to me and cleans, but then it's
the excuse. Oh, you didn't give no
You can't win with these clowns, bro.
They know where you live. They don't do
nothing. You go to the area, they make
excuses. You try to arrange a fight,
they they ignore you, bro. That's why I
don't come on this [ __ ] anymore, bro.
It's uploading, mate.
Yeah, man. Just waiting for the video, lad.
Got a couple of minutes remaining, LT.
But yeah, bro, I don't really come on
here anymore, bro. I've just been busy.
I wouldn't come on here anyways. [ __ ] mate.
Yeah, they're all the same on there,
bro. They're all the same on there.
They'll never stop, bro. He needs to
leave this um website, bro. They will
never ever ever stop. They will never
ever ever stop, bro. Yeah, man.
Yeah, literally, bro. Literally, man.
One second. The video is coming, bro.
I also mentioned you in the video as
well cuz he's bothered you as well. This
guy has also bothered you.
So I I just put your name in there as well.
He didn't do a video, did he? So you
come on here to annoy people every day.
Yeah. And then when somebody wants to meet you,
you you [ __ ] yourself.
What's the [ __ ] point, bro?
You come on here,
you bother people,
and then you start something that you can't finish.
This is me out.
One second. This is me at the pub the other day.
He He used to bother you, did he not?
I don't know. He He said that he used to
bother you, so I thought he did. Huh?
You do know who he is, bro. That Smokey B account.
You do know who he is, bro. Smokey B.
That [ __ ] annoying [ __ ] You do know
who he is, bro.
That Smokey B account.
How the [ __ ] do you not know who he is,
bro? He's been doing it for years.
Just like All Night Spaz. But we don't
that all night spaz is not even worth
talking about, bro. Like bro, man went
to his country two times. He shut his
mouth. We're not talking about him and
he he's too scared to come on Hangouts,
but that Smokey B has come on Hangouts
and he's been doing it for years and he
shuts his mouth. Look, the video is
coming in a minute, bro.
I know who it is, bro.
That stupid [ __ ]
Yeah, I've heard him speak. I've heard
him speak. That's the only reason I done
a video, bro. It's because I heard him speak. [ __ ] Yeah, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Go and watch it, bro. Yeah, man. Watch it.
Yeah, I violated him, bro.
Yeah, he didn't reply, bro.
Yeah, give it a while. [Music]
Yeah, give it a while. [ __ ] it. I would Yeah, bro. Yeah, mom.
Take your lights, bro. Devil comes.
I'm about fighting him because he didn't
do a video back to me cuz he's a [ __ ] Yeah.
See what I mean?
They start [ __ ] when they can't finish it.
All right, Timmy, you and um no teeth
need to go out on the pool, bro. You
both need to lose your virginities.
You're going to [ __ ] You two are both
going to die [ __ ] virgins, mate.
You don't want to die a [ __ ] virgin
to me. You know I like you, bro. Like,
you're my friend. We go way back.
You know, I met you through the roulette
videos, but I don't want you to die a
[ __ ] virgin, mate.
You and the [ __ ] no teeth [ __ ] with a rat face.
I don't want you to both die virgins.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
S me, man. I don't want you to die a
virgin like [ __ ]
virgin boy. the two virgins. You know,
you two are going to die virgins, mate.
You two are going to die virgins, mate.
I'm telling you.
Seriously, Timmy, bro. I love you and
that, bro, but you will die virgin, mate.
Just like the other one.
I don't anymore to me. Timmy.
Jimmy. Have you ever been in love to me?
I'm going Thailand tomorrow. Timmy,
I'm going Thailand tomorrow. to me, lad.
Yeah, I'm going Thailand tomorrow, bro.
Are you jealous?
I'm going there for a better life to me.
For a better life, lad.
Cuz I deserve it, you know.
I think you must pair of [ __ ] if you
ask me mate.
Are you there?
Oh, what gone out? Oh man.
One second, bro. I need to find this
[ __ ] black plug.
Hate it when it does that, man. Annoying, bro.
I'll never be as skinn as you, mate.
Listen, Timmy Aldridge, you are skin.
Timmy Aldridge. Listen, listen, listen, listen.
You know when you call people skin. Yeah,
Timmy Aldridge. It's You're talking
about yourself. Self-reflection of your own life.
You know all about skin. You're the skintest going,
man. You little self-reflective.
[ __ ] crazy, man.
You self reflectors.
That's what you are. Self reflectors. People asking
why you going about skin every day cuz
you are skinselves.
You're sc yourselves.
That's why you can't get over YouTube.
These people are skin, bro.
Where's London gone?
Bro, who [ __ ] with that? Uh, why did
you watch my video? Uh, gains. What did
you think of that, boss?
I was saying to that Morgan about a
month ago, boss, I'll slap you up in
front of your [ __ ] boyfriend, bro.
these silly tattoos
cuz I wouldn't do it unless a guy was
there, bro. Like I'm not I wouldn't
[ __ ] beat a woman up unless another
guy was there
cuz I don't like people that offend
women in it. So
them kind of people annoy me. So unless
another guy is there, I ain't bother
[ __ ] doing it, bro.
Like I told this woman today, I hope you
get [ __ ] by a kangaroo, bro. I'm not
going to say the real word on here, bro.
But you see what I'm saying, bro? They
they come on here and they bother
people, but they can't finish it.
They come on they start mad [ __ ] bro,
but they can't finish it. I would have
slapped him up today, bro.
Why pop? Like, they don't stop, bro. I
told you this. Yeah.
You need to leave this community.
They're never going to stop, bro. As
soon as I come on here, Harry Fraud,
sorry, not Harry Fraud. [ __ ] Jamie
Thompson, Red Star. They're never ever
going to stop, bro. Do you not understand?
They will never stop. None of them will
ever stop, bro. Do you not get it?
Doesn't matter what year it is, they're
never going to stop, brother.
They will never stop though. Yeah, man.
I can't be bothered, man. Yeah.
[ __ ] That virgin ain't following me
anywhere, mate. You [ __ ] mad.
That [ __ ] virgin ain't following me anywhere, mate.
You're [ __ ] crazy, mate.
You already know what the plan is, boss. Yeah.
Want to [ __ ] with that Morgan some more,
bro. I will slap her up in front of her
boyfriend, bro. I'm stronger, but guess
what? I've got no tattoos. Um, LT,
Just because someone has tattoos, it
doesn't make them stronger. LT.
Ah, [ __ ] me, mate.
We're going to Thailand tomorrow. LT, I
didn't tell you on the phone, did I?
Yep. I'm meeting Antman over there.
We're going to get into some trouble.
We're going to get into a lot of trouble, lad.
Bro, I don't care what what you believe.
I know where I'm going tomorrow, bro.
You can believe it. You cannot believe
it. I'm I'm going,
bro. He can believe it. He cannot
believe it, bro. I'm going. It's up to
you, bro. You believe what you want, lad.
I'm meeting Ant-Man tomorrow.
Yeah, I'm meeting Ant-Man tomorrow. You
know these people? Yeah. Let me tell you
something, Alie. They've been banging on
all day about this Thailand thing. Yeah,
I told him I'm going Thailand tomorrow.
They have been banging on all day about
it. This Thailand thing, they have been
banging on all day about it, bro. Trying
to find out where I'm um the exact place
I'm going. the flight. Like they've been
trying to find out madness, bro. That's
how you know they're just glasses on
here. They have not stopped about it,
bro. Cuz do you know what? Yeah. I tell
you something. If I didn't believe
somebody was going somewhere, I would be
like I'd ask like one question and then
I'd say, "Yeah, whatever. I believe it
when I see it." But these people have
not stopped, bro. All day. They've been
going on all day about this, trying to
make me slip up all day. That's how you
know, bro. They ain't got no life. Like,
it's not a big thing to go on holiday. You know,
they have been banging on all day about
this Thailand thing, bro. Like, no word
of a lie.
That's how you know they got no life as well. You know,
it's not like they asked one or they've
been on about it all day, bro.
It's [ __ ] madness.
They've been banging on about it all day
so they can try and grasp they're such
sados. You know the thing is LT, you
know when I done that video earlier?
Yeah. Do you know that's only being on
here one day and this guy was driving me
mad. I was going to injure this guy
today, bro. I'm not even joking. I was
even going to injure that guy. I was
going to even injure that woman.
If I knew where any of them were.
Like bro, it's not a joke, bro. I was
going to go there today and [ __ ] that
guy up, bro.
I'm going to meet um I'm going to meet Ant-Man.
Bro, why would I need to be excited?
I've already been abroad two times. Why
would I be excited?
It's going abroad, bro. Once you've done
it once, like, what's there to be excited about?
I'm not saying exactly where I'm going,
bro. Because of these people, bro, you
know, once you've been abroad, the first
time, oh yeah, you're really excited.
The second time, bro, it's nothing like
the reason L J gets excited about it is
cuz he's got crippling anxiety. And that
[ __ ] takes pills before he gets
on that plane. Cuz, bro, that guy does
not have a normal life, bro. He does not
have he he has got anxiety. He really
does have anxiety, bro.
Like no one's like like no one's like L
J. L J's got crippling anxiety. That's
why like he gets excited. Oh, Vegas.
Vegas. Because bro, he's got anxiety,
bro. You understand? So he's excited to
be able to actually go on that plane.
But nah, bro. Not even.
You know what I'm saying?
But at the same time, I can't wait. But
because I shouldn't be having to leave
this this country, bro, you know,
and I don't know why he he went mad
about Vegas, bro. Vegas is [ __ ] I've
never wanted to go to Vegas ever in my
life, bro. Like, even when I was bang on
the gambling, like I'd never be excited
if somebody was saying, "Oh, go to
Vegas." Never. Cuz I wouldn't even gamble there.
But again, he's his anxiety, of course.
You know what I'm saying?
Because it's not exciting, bro. It's actually depressing.
I'm having to leave my own country
because of these women and these people.
That's not exciting,
you know? There's nothing exciting about it,
you know? It's [ __ ] disgusting, to be honest.
All because of these people and these
[ __ ] women. I'm having to leave my
own country. What What's exciting about that?
You can't live life here anymore, mate.
It's It's a depressing life in England.
It's a really depressing life in
England. I hate everything about this
country. Everything annoys me about it.
The people, the public transport, the
women, the pedestrians, everything
annoys me about this country. literally everything. So, so yeah,
I hate this country with my passion, bro.
Yeah, I hate it so much.
Yeah, the weather, the women, the pedestians,
the system, the public transport. It's all [ __ ]
England is a depressing place, bro.
It's a depressing place to be. Really,
it's no life for anyone in this country.
There's no life in this. It's no life
for anyone in this country, you know.
What do you think, LT?
I'd love to [ __ ] slap that [ __ ] out, bro.
Yeah, I don't gamble anymore,
bro. You're you're still banging on
about this holiday. You've been talking
about it all day, bro.
Like, give it a rest. You've been
talking about this holiday all day.
They've been talking about this all day.
You know, LT,
they've been talking about They've been
talking about this all day.
They live off other people's life cuz
they ain't got a life of their own.
But that [ __ ] didn't reply back a month
and a half ago, bro. She knows she'll
get slapped up in front of her
boyfriend. You think your silly little
boyfriend with tattoos could ever step
to me, bro? Please, bro.
I would [ __ ] not the [ __ ] flying out, bro.
I'm dangerous, bro. You know, I I Bro,
listen. I'm really dangerous. I should
You don't understand my temper, LT.
Like, you laugh at it. Yeah. You really,
really, really, really laugh at it, but
it's not even funny, bro.
You know what I'm saying,
bro? Cuz I hate them, bro.
And that little And that Damon, bro, as
well. Who the [ __ ] does he think he is?
Cheeky little [ __ ] I'll spit in his
mouth, bro. Make him swallow it. Silly
little [ __ ] Bro. Yeah,
bro. I a Bro, listen.
I really wanted to [ __ ] do some I
wanted to release some anger today, bro.
You know, but can you do me a favor?
Don't ever argue with any of these
people again on here, please.
Please stop. Don't stop arguing with
these people on here cuz it [ __ ] ruin
my day today at the gym.
Cuz of these [ __ ] bro. If I ever catch
any of these people, they get a good
hiding, bro. Like, you
you think I'm joking, bro? But I'm being serious.
No, Joe. But do you know what we won't
be doing? One day to Vegas, two days to
Vegas, 4 days to Vegas. Unless I had
anxiety because Vegas is [ __ ] No, bro.
We're not all like um [ __ ] Lord Jay
Vegas. Two days to Vegas. Three days to
Vegas. Four days to Vegas. Bro, no one
does that. Especially someone that's
been to Vegas like [ __ ] four times.
It's all anxiety.
That was his anxiety. I've got to get on
that plane. You do realize, bro, it's
all self-p projection on this website.
This is what I was trying to say to you,
bro. He has got anxiety. What, bro?
Listen, listen, listen. If you're going
to the same place four times, that is
anxiety, bro. He counted down the days
where he had to go on that plane.
That is literally anxiety. If you have
been somewhere, bro, you've been
somewhere four times. Yeah. It's like if
somebody said to me, you're going to
Amsterdam tomorrow, I'd be like, I don't
really care. Been there, done it, worn the t-shirt.
Bro, that is some severe anxiety. That L
has got anxiety, bro. I don't know why
he hides the fact he's got it.
He has really, really, really got
anxiety, bro. Like, think of it. He's
never worked a day in his life. I do.
He's never worked today in his life,
bro. No. People really, really don't do
that. They really, really, really don't
do that. Especially a place that
someone's already been like [ __ ]
Vegas for [ __ ] sake.
But that's his anxiety, bro. Cuz he's
scared of flying. He's got a fear of
flying. It doesn't matter that he's been
on a plane for 10 hours, bro. Antman
hates flying and he's and he's been he's
flown long longer than Lord J has and he
will tell you that he's scared of flying.
You know, it's all self-p projection.
It's cuz he's got anxiety. Do you not understand?
Who's the one that works and who's the
one that does not work? He doesn't work.
You understand? Cuz you got anxiety,
bro. There's different forms of it, man.
There's different forms of it.
He might not have it as bad as say like
triple hate, but he's definitely
definitely got it. And I'm not
projection projecting cuz I don't have
anxiety. So why would I be projecting
when I don't have it?
You know what I'm saying?
No, he's definitely definitely
definitely anxiety, lad. 100%.
time I was excited to go abroad
when um is when I when I went the first time, you know. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. It was actually the first time.
Nah, bro. Once you've been abroad once,
l's got a fear of flying. So
been to Belgium,
Amsterdam, I've been another place and I
was never ever.
But the first time I went, I was excited.
Three times actually, but never never after that.
Once you've been, you've been, bro. Simple.
I think LJ's got crippling anxiety.
Really, bro? I actually think he does.
Really, really bad anxiety. Yeah,
really bad anxiety, mate. Yeah, bro. [ __ ]
Oh, he's got really bad anxiety, mate.
Really bad anxiety, matey.
It's a shame, isn't it?
I'm scared of flying. Yeah.
But yeah, like this woman today out
here, I would have smashed her face in.
If I knew where she lived, I would have
smashed her face in today. But
yeah, I'm not even just going for the
women, bro. I've had enough of them. I
don't care about the [ __ ] It's only
just bits [ __ ] pissed me off today.
Just pissed me off today, bro. Why the
[ __ ] would I care about them, bro?
They're all the [ __ ] same [ __ ]
And then they wind you up and they make
you want to smash their face up. That's what happens. Yeah.
Oh yeah. I just will have a normal life
on our land. I won't have anything I
want when I land. I'll just have a
normal life cuz this life ain't normal,
bro. This life in this country ain't normal, bro.
It ain't normal. I'm telling you, it's not normal.
You got people that start stuff they
can't finish on the [ __ ] street.
You got these stuck up [ __ ] Then the
[ __ ] system's [ __ ]
And it's like even on public transport,
I hate being around people. I hate this
country and I hate people in this
country. Like you don't even understand.
I just hate the whole country like
waiting for things. I hate it, bro. With a passion.
It's just an annoying country to live
in. I can't even explain it.
I hate everything about it. the [ __ ]
people, the women, the waiting around
the system, the [ __ ] public transport,
just everything you can think of I hate
about this country. You know,
I was telling LT about that woman that
said, "Oh, you shouldn't be there when I
was riding the bicycle." I said, "I'll
[ __ ] go where I want, silly cunt."
[ __ ] who the [ __ ] do they think they
are, bro? Like you say that they don't
owe us anything. Yeah,
but no one's saying anything. They're
biting their nose in. Why don't you
[ __ ] mind your own [ __ ] business? Silly [ __ ]
I was telling L about the story as well.
Soon [ __ ] walked away, didn't you
know? [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah,
I'd love one of these cyclists to start
on me. I'll smash a bike in their
[ __ ] head, bro. I swear when I You
don't understand, bro. The other day I
was on a bicycle, bro. I was going to
run someone over, bro. I said if someone
starts on me today, bro, I'm going to
run them over with this bike, bro. I
swear. It's a heavy bike as well. You
know, it's a good bike, bro.
They're good bikes. They are, bro.
[ __ ] run them over with my bicycle,
mate. That's what I'll do. Yeah. Do a [ __ ] U-turn.
[ __ ] hate this country, bro.
And then you get And then you get them guys
And then you get them guys that act big
in groups. The typical white [ __ ]
And they still don't scare me even when
they're in groups.
Yeah. Nothing's happening, Joe.
Whatever. Yep. Yep. Yep. We've heard it
all before. Nah, none of them, bro. None of them. But yeah.
Yeah. Nothing's happening, bro. You keep
telling yourself that. We've been
hearing the same old for years, bro. Do
you remember why I told you about the
same repeating [ __ ]
Yeah. Nothing is happening. I'm scared
of flying. I've got anxiety. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. We've heard it all before. Like,
come on, bro. Yeah. We've heard it all
before. We've heard all your [ __ ] before
as well. Yeah. We've heard all your [ __ ]
before as well, bro. Yeah, man.
Doesn't matter, bro.
actually quite cheap actually.
But I was saying to this [ __ ] guy today,
uh, America did happen actually. Yeah.
And we're not getting into this again.
This is one of the reasons I left this
community because it's the same [ __ ]
with you people. It's the same old
boring with you people. This is why I
don't come on here anymore. You didn't
see me for two weeks because you're the
same old boring. You're the same old
It's been happening for years now.
You're the same old boring. This is why
people don't come on anymore. This is
why every time you sub to my channel, I
don't come on here. Because it's the
same old boring. You're boring, bro.
You know what I'm saying?
You're the same old boring. Like look,
you started on me today, you people.
I've tried to meet one of you. You all go quiet.
You're the same old boring. This is why
people don't come on here no more. Well,
I don't come on here no more. I don't
know why other people don't come on here no more
because I've realized that you people
are never ever going to stop what you're
doing. So there's no point. You're
clearly jealous of something. You you
don't leave people alone, you know, and
then when people try to meet you, you're
nowhere to be seen. So it's pointless, you know,
that's it. You people will never stop
the jealousy towards me. And I accepted
that. That's why I I don't come on here
no more, bro. You know, it's the
jealousy, the stalking, the weirdness.
Like, I'm not even joking. I'm being
deadly serious, bro. It's why you don't
see me on here no more.
Like, you don't understand. If that guy
showed me where he was today, I would
have smashed his face in. I swear to
God. And the only reason I didn't go
today is because if I went unannounced
Oh, wow. You didn't arrange it. I was
being serious, bro. Deadly serious.
Then I had another guy that claimed he
was from Tottenham starting another one
that didn't back up his talk.
You know what I'm saying, bro? It's mad.
Why Why start [ __ ] if you ain't
finishing it? I don't get it, bro. You
know, you come on here every single day
bothering people, bothering people,
harassing people. You know what I'm
saying? And then you never meet anyone.
What's the point, bro?
You laugh at it. But I was being
serious, bro. Like, if I didn't know any
better what these people do, I would
have went there today. I would have went
there today, bro.
I would have smacked that little Milton
Keen [ __ ] up. You laugh at it. Yeah,
bro. You laugh at it. One second. I need to piss.
But if I didn't know any better what you
people do, I would have I would have
fell into the trap. I would have went
there. I would have wasted my time. I
would have wasted my money. And none of
you [ __ ] none of you people. Me, bro.
You're annoying. When I catch one of you
people, it's not going to be funny.
Like, you can laugh all you want. It's
not going to be funny. I'm deadly
serious, bro. I didn't make a video for
no reason today,
you know, and I know what my temper's
like, bro. You don't You laugh at it,
but it ain't funny, bro. Like, people
don't do videos for a joke.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Yeah.
You're laughing at it now, bro. You're
laughing at it now cuz
you're laughing at it now, LT, cuz
you're not involved in it. But watch
when you get involved again. You're not
going to be laughing.
You're not going to be laughing at it,
mate. You're not going to be laughing,
bro. Trust me, you're not going to be laughing.
These people are not normal, bro. They're [ __ ]
You remember I told you before, bro?
You're laughing cuz it's not happening
to you. But when it happens to you again, you know,
you're not when it happens again to you,
you're not going to be laughing, mate.
They're all the same keyboard warriors, bro.
You go on that Red Star channel, it's
the same [ __ ] You know, I went on that
Red Star channel today. Yeah. And it was
the first time in months as soon as I
went live, literally two seconds later,
he was he put up something of me like,
"Is this guy all right, bro?" Like,
"What the [ __ ] bro? Is this guy okay in his head?"
And it's actually the truth.
Like they never ever actually stop, do
they, bro? Like they really really
really never stop, do they?
Um, his name was O DG E or something.
These people never stopped, man, did
they? They never ever ever ever ever
ever ever ever ever stop.
I don't think they'll ever stop, bro.
And I was trying to say to this guy in
Tottenham, he's like, "Oh, you said
stuff about these people's kids." I was
like, "Bro, I don't care about these
people. I hate them. I hope they all
die." Like, do you not understand? Do
you think I care about anybody on this
community? I hope they all I I wouldn't
care if they all died. I hate them.
And I said, "If you got a problem with
it, yeah, come and meet me." Oh,
changing the subject. Changes the
subject. Changes the subject.
You know, we've we've we've even got
people now in in London doing this [ __ ]
Starting [ __ ] they can't finish.
London cyclists. That's what I call them
now. I call them London cyclists.
That's why I don't even feel like going
out sometimes, bro. Cuz if anyone talks
to me, bro, they're going to get hiding
one day. And the only one that's going
to get in trouble is me. Yeah. You understand? There And
I don't need to be up early tomorrow cuz
it's not until the evening. But still.
Yeah, bro. And you know the worst thing
about this community is you can't get
your hands on none of them, bro. You
can't get your hands on none of these people.
You can't get your hands on none of them, bro.
I wish I could get my hands on one of
these people on here, but yeah.
Yeah, I was busy for like over weeks
though. I could have come on here, but I
didn't really want to come on here anyways.
Um, my favorite is the flies. My um
my favorite is the flies, bro. Yeah.
Nah, she's not laughing at anyone. She's shook, love.
I love the flight. That That's my
favorite. But to be fair, today I only
went for like half an hour because it
was only um
it was so busy, bro. I couldn't do it.
It was so busy. That's why I like to go
in the morning, you see.
I like the bicep curls as well, but my
favorite is the flies. Yeah.
No, but they're not dumbbell flies.
They're the They're the flies with the
um that attached to the machine.
But it was too busy today, bro. I only
done it for like half hour to be fair.
It's hard to fit in time for the gym, you know.
Really, Captain? She's not laughing
though. She should, bro.
I would match her up in front of her boyfriend.
I do in front of that diamond as well, bro. Yeah.
Do you remember that time before you
were saying that I was um I was looking for trouble.
No, I'm not even looking for trouble, bro.
I didn't even I didn't even choose,
bro. I didn't even choose the fug life.
The fug life chose me, bro.
Remember that. I didn't choose the fug
life. The fug life chose me.
Yeah, for real, bro.
[ __ ] life chose me, bro.
Yeah, that Australian [ __ ] was getting
cheeky today, LT.
Yeah, I love I love your little story.
They really get cheeky, these [ __ ]
don't they, lad?
Yeah, he's bullied me off YouTube. Yeah,
man. And you keep telling yourself that.
Yeah, he bullies me off YouTube, man.
But guess what? Guess what, bro? I bully
him in real life.
I bully him in real life. He can't show
me where he is cuz he knows better.
Yeah, bro. He can't show me where he is.
I've got that power over him. See, LT LT
lives in um the West Country. I live in
London. I live in East London. See, we
can we can say where we are. But you
know, you know, people like Red Star,
they can't even say where they are
because we've got that power over them.
We control them. They can't tell us
where where they are, you know, because
they know better because they're
controlled by us. Well, by me, you know.
Timmy lives in Birmingham. I live in East London.
Um, LT lives in the West Country and Red
Straw lives Oh, he can't say where he
lives cuz he knows better.
He knows he can never say where he is.
It's nice to have that power over some
people, you know,
where they can never say where they are.
Imagine having that power over someone.
I mean, it's not even about the law, you
know? I mean, LT,
you live in East London. You do not live
in no East London, you [ __ ]
If you lived in East London, you
wouldn't be on here being a keyboard warrior, mate.
You do not live in no East London, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
You know, you do not live in no [ __ ]
East London, mate. Yeah, you [ __ ] wish.
You live in Dston. Well, Dawson's not
East London, so try again, [ __ ] Yeah,
you live in Dston. Well, guess what?
Dustin's not East London, you [ __ ]
So, try again.
You don't [ __ ] [Laughter]
You don't live in [ __ ] East London, bro.
Why are you moving back to London anyways?
Me and you need to go to the gym together.
Oh, [ __ ] off, mate. You're like that
virgin saying London. Promise London.
Problem is London. [ __ ] off. You're not
East London, you [ __ ] [ __ ] I can
tell you every single place in East
London since I'm from there. Do you
remember though? Do you remember that,
bro? Um, I mean, East London from
probably London. If you look up, it's
London. You're saying it's London, you
[ __ ] virgin. You don't even sound
nothing like London.
[ __ ] off, mate.
Why are you sick of them? Is it because
they all talk like that? They all talk
like Hermes. They all talk a bit like
that. Is that why you don't like them? Yeah.
Yeah. You know how dead I was going to
start talking about Milton Kees. You
know how dead Milton Kees is, bro. I
went there before for an approaching
session and the population is like 10
year olds, mate. 10 year olds and single moms.
[ __ ] Milton Kings is a [ __ ] [ __ ]
hole. I don't know if you've ever been there, but
there's just loads of roundabouts.
And he tried to put like he tries to
sound London that smoke you be like,
"Don't force it, bro. Don't force it."
You know what I'm saying? Don't force it.
Yeah. Force it in it, LT.
I met a black cockney um yesterday. He
delivered me some food. LT. Yeah.
Yeah. He delivered me some food, bro.
Yeah. It was black [ __ ] me, man.
Yeah. Delivery delivery driver friend.
He was ordering He ordered me some food, man.
I was sat in the house and he and he
bought me some food. You ain't even got
no friend, you little loner. Yeah.
You ain't even got no friends. You don't
even have a job. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
You jobless friend little [ __ ]
Yeah. Talking about yourself. You ain't
got no friends.
Sand bastard. Can't get off of YouTube.
And you ain't got no job either. You batty boy.
You basty boy. [ __ ] weasels.
So many weasels, bro.
Man's worked for a week. I don't even work, bro.
But guess what? You don't even work yourself. Yeah.
Allow it, bro. Listen, you allow it. You
little [ __ ] Come and meet me right
now, you little [ __ ] beg. Come and
meet me right [ __ ] now. I'll go suck
your mom, bro. I'll say it to your
[ __ ] face. Come and meet me now. Simple. Yeah.
Don't suck up your mom, bro. So, you can
say anything to these people, bro, but
they'll never meet you. But they'll
They'll never meet you, these people.
These losers will never meet you, bro.
These people will never ever meet you.
Just keyboard warriors.
Come here, bro.
Yeah, you because you're running up your [ __ ] mouth.
You don't bully me. Red Star don't bully
me. Cuz if you people really bullied
people, they wouldn't come back on
YouTube laughing at you. Like, you got
to understand the definition of
bullying, bro. Bullying is what you
people get. You've been bullied your
whole life, bro. You people are bully
victims. You're not bullies. You're
bully victims. And we can come on here
every single day and laugh at you. But I
don't come on here anymore cuz you're
boring as [ __ ]
It's the same spastics every day. So
that's why I don't I don't really come
on here anymore. But I can come on here
every single day. You know, you people
are something to laugh at. You embarrass
yourselves every day.
In a way, it is amusing to to be honest.
It is amusing that you do what you do
for years and years and years and years,
but you never say anything to anyone's
face. Like to me, that's funny. Like
being from London, it's funny to me in a
way. Strange, but funny.
Like you've got all this stuff,
you got all this energy behind the
keyboard for years and years and years
and years and years and years
and you never stop. But then when it
comes to meeting anyone, you will never
meet anyone. It's funny, bro. It is funny.
You people are you're something to laugh at.
You know what I mean? These people are
something to laugh at.
You don't bully anyone. You bully
yourselves. You show yourselves up. Yeah.
Have you So, have you noticed LT? It's
the same people every day
and they call it a community, but what
what community is it? cuz no one does
gamb videos. No one puts content videos.
So, it's not a community. It's full of
spastics. Like, do you actually know
what a community is?
You actually know what a community is.
Yeah. What's the chance today?
It's not a community, bro. Do you know
what a community is?
You want to get in USA? is Nick Nick. Yep. Yeah, man.
But even [ __ ] Donna Birmingham left.
Even Fraser left, bro. They never come back.
Even Ant-Man left.
Yeah, loads of people left, bro. Loads
of people left.
Oh, I remember him. Captain,
you all right, Captain?
Are you all right, Captain? Yeah.
LG, you all right, Captain?
You all right, Captain?
No, I like it, mate. It's a lovely picture.
I want to put Franklin back up. Anyways,
this looks like LT, by the way.
This looks like LT.
Nah, mate. Nah, not at all.
You know why I started the gym, don't you, LT?
Um, well, I have been slacking lately, cuz
I have I haven't had time, but it's cuz
I felt like my belly, oh [ __ ] this is
how bomb started. This is how these
little self-reflectants started. So, I
went and I'm still going to go and then
it kind of went down and [ __ ] cuz that's
how these people start. You see,
that's how these people start in this community.
Now, that's you, bro.
You're the black guy.
You're a black You're the black guy, bro. That's you.
That's you, man.
I don't think this Jane applied. This [ __ ]
that [ __ ] Jane really pisses me off,
you know. So, you best not piss me off,
though, cuz I'm the kind of [ __ ] I'll
just go in the door.
But I'm a [ __ ] like that. But I would
just go to Wales and go in her door. I'm
a [ __ ] like that.
You know what I'm saying? She better not
start winding me up cuz I will put her
windows through, bro. Trust me. I'm I'm
a different I'm a different person now, bro.
I don't take [ __ ] from no [ __ ] you know.
No, serious though. No, no, no. But it
is funny hearing it. But I am being
serious, bro. I'll just put a window to it. Yeah.
All jokes aside, bro. Like, I was wound up today.
I was wound up today, bro. You keep
laughing and laughing and laughing.
I heard you was going to pack up work.
There's a rumor going around that you
was going to pack up work.
Is that true?
Are you going to pack up work? No, you can't, bro.
You have to feel You have to feed your
your your little uh youngsters. Yeah.
I don't know, bro. Maybe you just got
sick of it in it.
You might You might got sick of it. I don't know.
You are you are bro you know yeah I I I
was like so high yesterday bro like from
lack of sleep you know it starts [ __ ]
with your mental health and I couldn't
stop laughing I I was high on
I was high on life for life, bro.
I'm just watching this incel [ __ ] before
I go sleep, bro.
I like watching it before I go to sleep.
I don't have any other pictures.
What does a scrag mean LT? Does it mean a slack?
What is a scrag me? I've never heard of
Must be some black word they used.
Bro, you're you're calling her a slag.
That's your girl, bro.
You and you wanted to get in her knickers, bro.
You wanted to get in her knicknocks, mate.
Calling her a slag and that, bro. Wanted
to get in her nickn
You would have happily went in her got
in her nickn,
bro. Listen, if you didn't have a child
yet and she wasn't trying to manipulate
you, you would have easily went to Boston, mate. You know,
you know this community, bro, you know,
you know, um, if it wasn't for this
community, if it wasn't for me, bro,
this community would have been a happy place.
It wouldn't have been perfect.
It would have been perfect. LT.
Um, but it would have been um it would
have been good,
you know, without me in it. Is it?
Well, actually, it wasn't me that caused
it all. It was actually Timmy. If you
actually go far back, bro, it was
actually Timmy. It was actually Timmy in
a way. Because
I tell you why. Because Timmy, what
started the kid [ __ ] he didn't say as
much bad stuff. Then I copy Timmy to
prove a point that yeah, no one's going
to go for Timmy like they go for me. So
in a way, bro, it was sort of Timmy as
well. I just like said, "Fuck it.
They're not going to go for me if I say
that shit." So Timmy's got a lot to
blame for as well, bro. Even if it's like 30%.
Yeah. I met an Australian um one I
didn't tell you about
about uh 2 weeks ago, 3 weeks ago. She
was she was Thai Australian LT and I
thought I was in love again.
I thought I was falling in love again. I
wrote her a little poem.
We met in a nightclub. She was Thai Australian.
Yeah. LT. Why do they have people
blocked as well, bro? What the [ __ ] is
up with that? Huh?
You need to unblock some people, mate.
You got Steven Howard blocked. Oh man,
you said you [ __ ] run over a [ __ ]
You're a crazy [ __ ] mate.
I tell you what though, mate. This
Smokey B is like a pedigree dog, bro. In
real life, he is a pedigree dog.
Do you understand? He ain't He needs to
remove He needs to remove smoke from his
name Buff cuz he's not on no smoke. Yeah. Like, bro,
that it's so mad how that Jamie Thompson
discovered your channel though, ain't
it? I think that's how they discovered
you, bro. You must have been commenting
on other [ __ ] cuz I've got a new channel
and none of them has found me yet. So,
LT, you might have commented on
something. That's how they discovered you. But that's
that must have been how they discovered you.
Yeah. Cuz my found my channel. That's
how you was discovered.
That's how you was discovered. Yeah.
I wish I was black sometimes, bro. I
wish I looked like this guy.
Then I'd get all the punani.
I'd get all the Punardi then if I look
like this guy.
He's a lovely little character. Yeah.
He's a good character, mate.
I got a new TV out. Look, I got a new telly.
I was playing all the little characters. Yeah.
All the little characters, bro.
I don't know how to dance. Maybe we can dance together.
Maybe me and you can dance together. LT,
imagine that in the Simmons. Me, you,
Mark, and um Terry Dancing.
Just imagine that, bro. Is it the meet
up in it? Yeah. But they don't want to
meet, bro. They don't. I arranged these
meetups. They never come, bro. They're
scared, bro. They're [ __ ]
They never meet. But they're [ __ ] Yeah.
They never meet, but they're [ __ ] hoes, man. Them Yeah. Nah,
LT hates uh nons legs.
Everyone hates nonss, don't they, LT? Yeah.
He's the worst for grass, bro.
Still does it as well, you know.
He still does this whole um kind of like
bait people and [ __ ] bro. He still does it.
He's such a [ __ ] little virgin, bro.
He He still does it, bro. He still does it.
He's a proper virgin, bro. He's a proper
[ __ ] virgin, mate.
I should have carried on meeting him, bro.
I would just tease him on how much of a
virgin he is.
But yeah, he still does it, bro. He
still does this whole stupidness, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, he still does it, bro.
Do you like Reddit?
Yeah, exactly, bro. Exactly.
Who is behind the haters?
Oh, [ __ ] me.
I'll be on the other side tomorrow, LT.
I'll be on the other side, lad.
It's not my problem anymore, this
country, but I'm leaving tomorrow.
It's not my problem anymore, mate. It's your problem.
It won't be my problem anymore, mate.
Don't remind me how depressing it will
be in two weeks, mate, because I'll be living it.
I won't I'll be living it, mate. I will
be [ __ ] living it.
That's what I'll do. I'll be living it, bro.
I won't need to think about it. I'll be
[ __ ] living it. [Music]
Let me just go sleep for a minute, but
And I'll see I'll tell you all about it
when I see you again. Get it?
Yeah. They know how to treat a man as well.
And they don't have boyfriends over there, too.
Yeah. They don't have boyfriends there,
too, bro. They've got a very good attitude. Antman
said the only place you're not going to
get I've got a boyfriend is Asia.
So we'll see in it. We'll see if he's right.
That's the only place you're not going
to get it.
That sounds funny.
The only place you're not going to get
LT is Asia.
That's the only place you're not going
to get out of a boyfriend.
Oh bro, I hate that bro. I hate it, man.
I say it, bro. It's annoying, isn't it?
Do you know when I first went to the gym? Yeah,
bro. I couldn't put my arm straight for
like 4 days, bro. The first time you go
gym again in [ __ ] a long time, it
[ __ ] your body up, bro.
I couldn't put my arm straight for like 3 days.
But it's a nice kind of pain, you know?
It's a nice kind of pain. Yep.
You know, they don't have boyfriends
over there, bro.
They don't have boyfriends over there.
And if they do, they're not going to
tell you they do.
cuz I've got a lot of friends out here
and a lot of them don't have girlfriends.
Maybe like it's like one in four have girlfriends
and there's loads of feminist women
nowadays. So, how can they all how can
like 85% of them are boyfriends? It's [ __ ] lad.
cuz there's I've got loads of friends
I've met from different places and a lot
of them are single, bro. A lot of them are single.
We got a lot of um a lot of single friends
from like different places and stuff.
So, how can all these women have
boyfriends, bro? It's it's [ __ ] you know?
They act tough in it, LC. They act tough
a lot, bro. They act up a lot.
One place I've never approached LT is
the gym. I'm not interested in
approaching in the gym, bro. I'm not interested, man.
That's the only place I've never done it, lad.
I done it two weeks ago after the gym, but
we never do it in the gym, bro. Never.
Never ever do it in the gym. I can't be [ __ ]
I just don't see a point in doing it in
the gym, man.
And I'm not I'm not like LT. I haven't
got LT's body, so they're going to say
no. Cuz Audi is a big strong black man.
So they will want your sausage.
They're not going to want mine, bro. So salamkum.
LT assalamu allayikum [Music]
that's how I greet that's how I'm going
to greet you now by yeah
it's funny is it Yeah.
Yeah. We're not all [ __ ] magnets like you, Alie.
Nah. Could you imagine Terry in a club,
bro? With his little short ass. Imagine
Terry in a club, bro. He's such a short
ass, isn't it?
I'm about to in the gym, bro. It's funny that
I'm in the club. Sorry. Yeah.
I don't Hey, I bet you've got favorites
in it when it comes to your children, in
it, you know. That's bad, you know, to have favorites.
I bet you've got favorites in it, LT.
You should never have favorites, bro.
You've got favorites.
I don't have a daddy. My daddy died when
I was 11. So I've only got Laney now
cuz my daddy died. Yep.
I don't have a daddy. I have only got a mama.
But I bet you've got favorites.
Yeah, you've got favorites, bro.
Yeah, you probably like the baby more in it.
You got favorites, mate.
Nah, you got favorites, bro.
That time I come back from Nottingham
that day. You're kind of dangerous, bro.
You was going to commit a murder.
Like we should look back on them times
and have a giggle over it. You was
actually going to commit a murder.
You crazy. You was going to commit a
murder, bro. You was going to commit a
murder over YouTube.
You was going to commit a murder over social media. Wow.
That's scary, bro.
That's really scary.
I said I was going to have a baby with
the Somalian in it and my child and your
child could play together.
Imagine that, Ali. You said if you had
it now, they could be friends, in it.
They could be friends.
Imagine that, bro. They could be friends
and then maybe they could have a baby. Imagine,
imagine your baby and my baby met and
then they grew up and then they had
their own child.
How mad is that, bro?
Ah, what a lovely sight. Yeah,
the baby would be Somalian, bro. It' be
[ __ ] weird, man.
Stop talking about my sister, you creep.
They were both born in January. What the [ __ ]
How does that work? Yeah.
Why would you have both your children in
January? What the [ __ ]
January is a [ __ ] month. You know, the
best month is March
cuz March is not too cold and it's not too hot. Yeah. Oh, okay.
January is a [ __ ] month though, man.
Yeah, it is. But it's a [ __ ] month, man.
January is [ __ ]
January is a [ __ ] month,
bro. I can't stop looking at that guy.
Look, he looks like you, bro.
He looks like you, bro.
don't, bro. It's too light to be you,
bro. You're You're from Ghana, bro.
You're from Ghana. This guy's too light
to be here, bro.
You're from Ghana, is it?
You're from Ghana. LT,
you look like KSI, bro.
You look like KSI, brother.
You look like KSI, bro. Yeah.
All right. What's happened with that um
young Philly? Has he been released or is
he still um
or is he still uh is he still in prison? Hello.
I think he got sent down, didn't he?
Well, for now.
Did he get sent down?
Sure. He got sent down, didn't it?
Yeah, he's [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, that guy is [ __ ]
You think it's funny, is it? Yeah. Yep.
Why did I talk? He's He's a pretty good [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, bro. Hey, it's a good it's good
though, bro, cuz they they've got it
right, Asia, you know,
they're they're strict. That's why
everyone's so nice there. Here, they're just [ __ ]
They're just [ __ ] here in this in
this country, bro. Yeah. Anyway,
but I'm going to sleep here. So, see you later, man.