Bro, I'm going to stop joining the
Spastics Hangouts chat. You just keep banning people
in my face, bro. Listen, you just keep
banning people, man.
Sorry, bro. It keeps banning me. Had to
come here. Delayed.
Bro, Lord J's followers are [ __ ]
bully victims. I literally called them all out.
They're proper bully victims. You know
what? Yeah, I actually thought I'd come
on today for the lows just for one day.
Bro, he told me that Boly Jun weren't a
[ __ ] And I'm telling you, he's a
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. I own all of
them, bro. They can't meet me. I tried
to meet that Lord J about a million
times. I tried to meet that Smokey B.
They were Listen, listen, listen, bro.
They're just keyboard warrior little
bully victims that ain't got nothing in
life but an application. That's all
they've got, bro. All listen, you know,
on Lord J's channel, all you have is
complete bully victims that have failed
in their life. Bully victims, but on in
real life, not on YouTube. They're bully
victims in real life, bro. Proper bully
victims. Yeah, I'm not meeting anyone.
I'll meet you. I'll meet you. And you
keep going on about the prime thing.
I've already explained it. It's boring,
mate. Listen, stop living in the past.
Like, you need to get to a certain age.
Yeah. Where you stop living in the past.
Stop living in the past. We're here
today. I've tried to beat about three
people today. They're [ __ ] Bro, there
will never be anyone. You have you
noticed, bro? Yeah. Cory, have you
noticed how it's the same disabled
people there every day? Red Star the
bully victim. It's the same low life
40year-olds. It's the same low lives.
Have you seen it, bro? I know you've
been off of here for 9 months. Yeah. But
come on every day for a week, a week, 5
days, whatever you It's the same
disabled spastics living their worst
life. Have you noticed it, bro? It's the
same disabled people that can't get off
it. Like, that's the thing that
surprises me the most here. Whenever I
rarely go on that channel yet, I'm
thinking, "What? It's the same
spasticated people that can't get off."
It says a lot about their lives, bro.
Look, the web is nice today. I've been
busy today, bro. And they're sat on
YouTube. Think about it, bro. It's
They're living their worst lives, bro.
They're self-p projectors. That's what
they are. They're self-projecting little
bully victims. They live off reactions
that people give them because they have
no life. They have no excitement in
their life because they're skint, fat,
ugly. So obviously like when people give
them attention, they feel special. Bit
like them cuz they're special needs. But
you know what I'm saying, bro? Like they
they live off attention from men on the
internet because their their lives are
that empty, that sad, bro. Facts. I
don't need to be a scientist or a
psychologist to to know this stuff out,
bro. But this is literally their life.
Like YouTube is their life. YouTube
ain't my life, bro. After today, I won't
be on it again for a week, two weeks, a
month. YouTube ain't my life, bro.
YouTube is their life. So, whatever they
say about me, think of it, bro. Let's
Let's put two and two together. Who's on
the Who's the one that's on YouTube
every day? Who are the ones on YouTube
every day, bro? I ain't on no YouTube
every [ __ ] day.
I ain't on no [ __ ] YouTube every
[ __ ] day, bro. Hey, I'm not on no
YouTube every day, bro.
I ain't on no [ __ ] YouTube every
[ __ ] day, bro. They're on YouTube
every day, but I ain't on no [ __ ]
YouTube every [ __ ] day, bro. That's
the difference. They are. Why they on
YouTube every day? They've got nothing
else. It's simple, bro. They just want
to be little keyboard warriors.
Whoa, bro. It's hot out there. And they
never stop as well, Kyle. Like I was
saying to you, brother, this is why I
don't come on here. It's okay for a day.
Yeah. A day maximum, bro. But you can't
be on here every day. You don't want to
end up like these spastics. You become
one of them as well. You are what you
surround yourself with. You understand,
bro? You don't want to be like these
spastics. Spastics on YouTube ain't got
a life. Self look self-reflectors.
Yeah, bro. I like this little cut now.
So, that's it, bro.
Facts. Yeah, man.
That's it, bro. Yeah, bro.
That's as far as that goes, bro. So,
yeah, one day is fine, bro. And then um
that's it, bro.
But it's mad how they all come together,
bro. Same sad people. I tried to meet
like three people today. And then this
prime clay bro, he wasn't anywhere in
London. You don't understand. This whole
thing is for attention and for um it's
for attention and for like
information and attention. That's why
they do what they do. Information and attention
and attention basically. Yeah.
Don't know, bro. So yeah,
they're not ever trying to meet anyone.
And you know, like the thing is, yeah,
it's not even that they're on here every
day. It's all they do is hate on people as well.
All they do is hate on people as well.
Here is hate on people. That's what they
do. It's not even like they they they do
they do anything but hate on people.
It's weird. This proposic place, bro. [Music]
Yeah. You think Pip is living the dream?
You think what? You think being on Pip
is living the dream, bro? Get real.
I don't give a [ __ ] about saying stuff
about his kid. These kids is mouththed
up on YouTube many times. [ __ ] him, bro.
He's been to Birmingham like three or
four times. You know what I'm saying?
You know, sometimes, bro, I don't come
on here, but like I'm just sick of
seeing him coming on here like he's
something. Coming on here like he's some
sort of hard man. When we like, yeah,
you've been to London. No one said you
didn't go to him, but tell the story
straight, you know. Tell the story
actual actually straight. What did you
do when you was in London? You done
nothing. You could have kicked the door
in my face two times. You ran away when
other other people tried meeting you.
Do you know what I'm saying? So yeah. Yeah, bro.
I destroyed all of them, bro. They're
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. I That's why I
come here like once a week, bro. I can't
deal with these people, bro. They're
[ __ ] idiots. And they never off
YouTube as well.
Yeah, bro. I've been going through some
mad [ __ ] at the at the moment. Rocky
Road, bro. It don't drag you down, bro.
It's just I don't like that channel,
bro. Like, if the spastics project on my
channel, I just block them. I just block
them. They don't get you down, bro.
Like, they they just, bro, they don't
even get you down. They're just self-reflectors.
Like they just do what they do, bro. But
it's not you. Yeah. Basically, I hope
you're doing good, bro. So, yeah.
Yeah. But I'll go with a mad [ __ ] roid,
bro. You be smoking private. I'll tell
you everything. It's a madness. Um, yeah, bro.
What's the time? I need to keep an eye
on time. Yeah, I don't really come in
here much anymore, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Live as [ __ ] bro. Put some Uber videos up.
Yeah. I was doing this Uber thing for a
bit, bro. I need to go shortly cuz I
basically do some stuff.
So, yeah, man.
Yeah, man. I a few people, but they
don't seem to get it either. They seem
to think, "Oh, there's you don't know
what brings this tomorrow." But, bro,
we've been dealing with this stuff for 3
years with this whole women [ __ ] and
this other stuff as well. So, I mean,
nothing is ever getting better, bro.
I think I would have been better off in
prison. I was just saying that to
someone, bro. I would have been better
off a few years ago. Yeah. Trying to rob
a bank and then just taking a risk and
going to prison. To be honest with you, bro,
this ain't no life in this country, Ro.
It's funny we talk about um Weather
Spoons and stuff, bro. I ain't been to
that Weather Spoons in a month, bro. I
don't even have time for myself. I ain't
had time to do nothing.
So, but I just don't like how that L J
only goes for like what he sees as vulnerable people.
So, that's why I went on the channel.
So, yeah, man. Yeah.
I'd rather be dead right now, matey.
Be dead right now, matey.
Yeah, bro. This Uber thing, Roy, you're
actually genuine. So it made me start
really hating people, hating the country
more. Um, it really is a depressing
country to be in. I found myself even
depressed on public transport
was in this country, bro.
Pull up on him. He wasn't even here,
bro. It's the same old [ __ ] with these
people, bro. They come on, they try to
annoy you, and then they don't meet
anyone. It's just the same old with
them, bro. They're boring.
They're [ __ ] boring, bro. They're
just sad 40 year olds that try to ruin
other people's life cuz they ain't got a
life of their own. So yeah, that's
that's their life, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. Life is damn bad. As in
America, bro. What they would say in
America is you're basically down bad.
I'm [ __ ] down bad, bro. But like I
was saying earlier, you don't see me
going in central London starting on
innocent people or Liverpool Street and
starting on innocent people, bro.
You know, [ __ ] all that.
Literally just do nothing but stalk you.
Like, this is what I mean, bro. Yeah, he
um that prime guy did embarrass you
though. Yeah, bro. No one cares. Keep
living in the past. No one cares. You
can keep living in the past. No one
cares about it. It's boring now. Um, and
yeah, Sunny, like they just do nothing
but stalk other men on the internet. I
don't [ __ ] with this community no more.
Obviously, I delete my stuff anyways,
bro. So, you don't see how much I post. But, um, basically,
um, they they're just losers on this
community. Just losers and haters. Like,
if you come on there every day for a
week, you will see what they do. They
just they just sit on stalk people that
they're jealous of. They just hate on
people that they're that they're jealous
of. Cuz we need to really think, bro,
what is really going on in these
people's lives where they have to sit on
YouTube all day doing what they do. It
doesn't take a psychologist to
understand that it's not normal what
they do. Do you understand? You know
what I'm saying? Had the element of
surprise, you could have had a weapon or anything.
All right, bro. No one cares about that,
bro. All these people do is live in the
past. They're just repeating sados, bro.
They just live in the past. Like they
can carry on living in the past if they
want, bro. That's on them, bro. No one
cares. It's boring out. Why don't come
on here anymore? It's the same repeating
people. I mean, look at it, bro. Give
you two examples. How long has this Red
Star been doing this? How long has this
Jamie Thompson been doing this? How long
has some of these accounts been on here
doing this? Like, ask yourself the question, bro.
And they never stop as well. They never
ever stop doing what they do. They never
ever stop. Never. That's why I don't
come on here anymore, bro. I'm on it
now, but you get what I mean. Yeah. So, yeah.
What's good, bro?
Whoever it is, they're just low lives.
Yeah, it was good, bro. I need to
[ __ ] live there now. It's literally
between you leave this country or
suicide. That's as bad as it gets in
this country. It's really bad. So, you
either leave this country or you or you
kill yourself. That's literally what
leave the country to move or you kill
yourself. Really, bro? Or you go to
prison. That's really your only hope
when you're in this country. It's a very
very depressing depressing uh depressing
country. I hate the people. I hate
everything about it. I'm ashamed to be a
part of Great Britain. It's there's
nothing great about it. I [ __ ] hate
it, bro. Like, I've got so many cyclist
stories s like where like random people
would start and then they would be able
to finish it and like, bro, I hate this
country. Like I was telling my friend
the other day, I don't know how you can
fight for this country. I hate England.
I told him straight, I hate it. Um, and
he said, "Oh, it's a job and I don't
really like England." I said, "Mate,
[ __ ] tell the [ __ ] truth." When
the Euros was going on, I was cheering
[ __ ] Amsterdam. I was cheering
[ __ ] Spain. I didn't want this
country to win. [ __ ] them. I hate them.
Full of [ __ ]
So many [ __ ] in this country, Rocky
Ride. I [ __ ] hate him, mate.
Yeah, I really, really hate this
country. It's so depressing. It's super
annoying. And it feels like a bug in
your in your body even being there
waiting around for things. I just hate
it made me like I said, bro, I was
saying this earlier to Cory, but it made
me really start hating people,
which I had no opinions on other people
before. Obviously, the women are always
stuck up [ __ ] That would never change
in this in these westernized countries.
But I mean, in terms of like the people,
like normal people, I didn't know normal
people were like it. Do you understand?
like pedestrians on the [ __ ] road and [ __ ] So yeah,
but they were so
weird. It's a weird place, bro. It's no
life. We call it a place, but ain't no
life, mate, for anyone in this country.
Why Thailand? That's why Antman lives in Thailand now.
He hated flying like you did. He hated
Um, Rocky Roy, he hated it. He swear
he'd never do it again. Now he's living
in Thailand. What this country drives
someone to do. E, what this country? I I
was just saying earlier, I'm surprised
I've never done anyone in or done
something extreme. You really have some
level of patience. E, I didn't know I
had this amount of patience. I'm
surprised, bro. Cuz it's not like I'm a
laidback person. I just Yeah.
Like I mean like punch someone that gave
attitude or something. You know what I'm
saying, bro? But these these low lives
on here will never stop, bro.
And I know what you're doing, bro.
You're trying to get evidence on people
and whatever, but you got to understand,
bro, that they're never going to stop on
here. They're never ever ever ever ever
going to stop.
Once you realize that, bro, like you
think like just don't come on here anymore.
know what I'm saying? Or once a week
like what I do, they will never stop,
bro. They will never stop. All it is is
trying to get information and trying to annoy people.
That's all they do.
Positive things like, "Oh, I like this
person. Oh, this person's done this."
Or, "Oh, it's never anything negative."
Uh, positive. Sorry. When you see these
people what they do every day, it's all um negatives.
Like it's all negative.
Like there's no one ever like bigs
anyone up or it's all negative. Have you
noticed that? Apart from them being
little low lives, little YouTube
dependent losers that it it's just
negative and hate,
you know? And it's every it is every day, bro.
It is every [ __ ] day. They do it
every day of their lives as well.
They do it every day of their lives. So yeah, bro.
I think this country makes people depressed. Yep.
I heard you make the most money in America. But yeah. Yeah, bro.
I've been messaging people this
situation and they just keep giving the
same advice. They say things get better.
Things never get better. Things never
ever get better. I've got like three
different worries now apart from one
except from one. So,
yep. And I'm not putting them on here.
So you got like three or four different
movies now. So
go anywhere with the Uber thing, bro.
So that's where we're at basically, bro.
Obsessed as well. They're still going on
about this, bro. They're still going on about this.
obsessed on YouTube. It's mad, bro. Why,
bro? How about one day on your channel
you just write good things?
Write good things.
I'm sick of people's false positive
advice. It's not a blip. It's serious
and no one cares. So, no one gives a
[ __ ] They just say, "Oh, things will come up."
about nothing. Yo, when you're down bad,
you're down bad, bro. It's not a blip. A
blip is getting your phone stolen. A different, you know. So yeah,
that don't ring right though cuz if a
certain thing has been going on for 3
years, three and a half years when you
was in a more of a lucky position than
most people, that's a long time, you
know, and that's just one of the things,
you know what I'm saying? So why do they
keep lying to themselves? Cuz at this
point now, no one's just going to
believe anything that they the advice
that they give cuz they're just lying to themselves
about things getting better. And they're
literally just lying to themselves cuz
again with the women thing, you should
have met someone by now in 3 years.
Especially the money we used to go
through. Um and then other things and
other things and other things. So if you
wanted to use that as an example, then
it doesn't ring right. You know what I'm saying? So
they're my little sayings. So
something was going to happen, it would
have happened by now, bro. All that
seems to happen in years is you've lost,
not actually gained anything. And it
seems to have gotten worse as well with
different things. It's not one thing,
it's different things. So
over Lord J's channel anyways. But I see
what they do though. I see what they do,
bro. I do see what they do. They wait
for content. They wait for content to
um write about other people. They wait for content
so they go on about other people cuz
they don't have a life of their own.
That's what I'm saying. So it's important Yeah,
I'll be on here for today and that and
then I'll be off again for a week, two weeks.
It's not my life. This community ain't
my life. So good.
Sunday just said depressed in bad year.
What the [ __ ] do they want me to say?
You know what I'm saying?
really started hating people.
As why would I want to socialize with
anyone from this country, bro? Like it
might seem like I'm being awkward and I
might be being difficult, but I don't
think these people understand the
severity of I don't think anyone
understands the severity of any of it.
To be honest, people wouldn't have even
made it to my age to be honest with all
of this [ __ ]
[ __ ] hell. 3 years,
bro. All I'm picturing in my in my mind
here is£50 notes, £50 notes, bare t-shirt, blazer.
Like [ __ ] that is unbelievable, bro.
It's just a bit to to add to the
unbelievess of it. Yeah. So yeah,
rather you mate, rather you than to me,
mate. I'm [ __ ] depressed as [ __ ] bro.
So yeah, thinking about the 50 notes,
the bare t-shirt.
I I just keep getting flats back in the
casino, bro. It's madness. Not because
of the gambling, but cuz obviously it
was part of the money. You know what I mean?
But nah, just nothing now
to do. Nothing to do now in it. It's bad.
[ __ ] hell. I'm sure people would have
killed themselves by now if they me
100%. Even times before, I'm sure
somebody would have done themselves in
people would have done themsel in, bro.
100%, bro. I'm sure they would have
and the only way is down now. So yeah,
had a little video greasy. So yeah,
little videos, matey.
I just wish I was born in the 1980s. We
wouldn't be having this conversation.
There'd be no [ __ ] There'd be no
stuck up women because there'd be no
social media. Just imagine life back then.
Now I'm basically forced to give up with
life. Imagine that. No, nothing gets
better like this. Nothing does. I'm sure
of it, bro. Cuz I'm somebody that
doesn't give up with anything.
So again, like I said, a blip is getting
your phone took from the police. A blip
is a foot injury. A blip is owing twice
your bill. This is not a blip, bro.
[ __ ] three and a half [ __ ] years,
bro. Jesus Christ.
I'm surprised you ain't met anyone in
three and a half years.
Like all jokes aside, Gre, I'm I'm very
very surprised now. The traveling I
done, bro. [ __ ] me. Used to wake up
every 6:00 in the morning. I used to get
the train at 8:00.
So, I used to get a train at um Sorry
about that, bro. I used to get a train
at I used to wake up at about 6:30 in
the morning. Used to get a train [ __ ]
somewhere out of London. Every week,
bro. I used to do it every week.
Literally every week I used to do it.
Every [ __ ] week, bro. Jeez.
Nothing will ever change. I've been
saying it for years, but you know, it's
like what else really does you have to do, bro?
What do you think happens when we die,
bro? Hopefully, we turn into like a dog or something.
Imagine that, a being a dog. Could you
imagine that being a dog, eh? Huh?
Imagine being a dog, bro, where everyone
loves you. No work, no stress, no nothing.
You imagine, imagine reincarnation actually existed. [ __ ] me.
I reckon if Greavves was me. I think he
would kill it. I'd think he'd kill himself
if he had to deal with 20% of what I
have to. I reckon he'd kill himself. Yeah,
maybe wake up in like two years maybe
other things. Yeah, this is to you
Smokey B. I don't care what you say on
the internet, bro. You're a keyboard
warrior. You've been running your mouth
for [ __ ] years. I've offered to meet
you god knows how many times, and you
just avoid me. So, no one cares what you
say behind a keyboard.
Stop being a London cyclist. Simple.
No one. It's just all hate and
negativity on this community. Have you
noticed that, Grezy? It's all hate and
negativity. This person is this, this
person's that, this person's this, this
person's that. Have you noticed that
over the years?
Yeah, I think it would be cruel bringing
someone to be honest with you. Like, I
think it would be very, very cruel um
bringing a child into this world now.
Lack of opportunities.
It's hard to get money nowadays. Um the
dating game is going to be well and
truly [ __ ] by the time they're your
age. I mean, you can't even get a
conversation out of someone nowadays.
That's how bad it's got. You can't even
get a conversation out of someone. You
can't even date properly. I mean, you'd
be it. It's not so much financially.
It's what you're bringing them into, you
know, a very very hard life where
someone don't have a chance. You know,
what's the point of of bringing a child
into this life when they have no chance?
You know, it'd be a very cool thing to do. So,
you know, look at me for example, I
can't even get a conversation out of someone nowadays.
Barely. The last time I approached, I
couldn't barely get a conversation out
of someone even though it was weeks ago.
But yet, people on the internet tell me
that you will meet someone and
everything's going to be okay. And no,
no, like they're living in fantasy
world. Ain't nothing going to be okay.
You're going to be depressed your whole
life, then you're going to die. End of.
Like, that's that's the real that's the
truth of it.
I wanted to go out every week just to
have a little drink, but I can't do that
anymore. I've got stress and other things.
No one really cares either cuz they don't understand. So,
yeah. So, that's it, bro.
I always say to Elaine sometimes, "Oh, I
wish you had me in the 1980s. I wish you
had me in the 1980s." I've said it a few
times. not over and over again.
But even if they have finance and they
have all of that stuff, it's what
they're bringing them into. Well, if
it's a man, well, if it's with a boy
that what chance they have in these
westernized countries, you can barely
get a conversation out people you can't
date. Like, do you really want to bring
in do you really want to bring a child
into that world?
You know, I still think about the bad
experiences I've had to this day, you
know, and then like continuously they
happen as well. So, and it will never
ever change, ever, ever, ever, ever
change. People have been telling me that
loads of times. People have been saying
that for [ __ ] years.
You just have to accept that no one has
the answers and you're [ __ ]
See, certain things are temporary, you
know, like lose your phone, get robbed,
lose £500, whatever it is people doing.
I am really [ __ ]
I've got two, three extra stresses now,
except from uh apart from one. So,
I just want to die, bro. I feel like
I've lived my life anyways, bro. I've
done what I've had to do. Been on a
plane, been abroad.
I just there's nothing else now, bro. You know,
cuz life was bad enough, but it was
tolerable when you didn't have these
stresses. Well, now you got all these
And the thing that's the most annoying
is how you've tried for 3 years and you
shouldn't be dealing with this alone.
You should not be dealing with this alone, bro.
You're [ __ ] traveling all over the
[ __ ] place for 3 years. You should
not be dealing with this alone, bro. You
know, but you are. So, so yeah,
suicide the only way, bro.
Yeah. There's no one for me. And I'm not
even fat and ugly. No offensive people
are fat and ugly. I'm not even fat. I'm
not even ugly.
Um, I think I just look normal and you
can't even get anything.
Worked, live by myself. Makes no difference.
Make it make sense, Mon. Oh, yeah.
You're saying that behind the keyboard,
bro. No one can take you serious. Yeah.
Yeah. Do you people do anything about
hate every day? It's a serious question
I'm asking you. Yeah. I'm actually on
LJ's chat right now. Do you people do
anything but hate every day?
Do you do anything but hate every day?
Like honest question I'm asking you now.
Like no skin, no no nothing.
Let me go back on it. Do you do anything
but just self-reflect every day? Like no
no repeating [ __ ] No, nothing. How long
can you do this for, man?
People can't even spell properly, bro.
You know when somebody was like this
before, they robbed the bank, music,
they robbed the bank and then they done
like a year and a half in prison, which
ain't bad if you can keep the [ __ ] money.
Go rob a bank. Say you got 20 grand. You
go gym. You get a nice body in the gym.
You come out refreshed. But people do do
it. People do commit crime.
It's not like breakups, bro.
Two weeks. You know, when people have
breakups, they might seem like they're
forever, but you just meet someone else.
Like if you compare it to other people's
problems, everyone's problems are like
temporary. Most people I am really
really [ __ ] unless a miracle happens
and people don't seem to understand it.
So I am really really [ __ ]
Do you know what? If you only had one
problem or two problems, it wouldn't be as bad.
But yeah, I'm truly truly [ __ ]
Truly, truly, truly [ __ ] bro.
Oh [ __ ] Didn't get any views on that video. Yeah,
but like I said, the eight the dating
thing just adds to it.
It's not the main cause. Like I said, 20%.
Yeah, you should have met someone in 3 years.
3 years, bro. Definitely. Oh, the
seven's old. Seven's out now. Won't be getting that.
Won't be getting that, mate.
Won't be getting that greasy.
And I think what's really depressing
about this country is there's no
opportunities as well.
There's no opportunities. Um,
what's popping? Nothing, man. Just
letting everyone know that I'm [ __ ]
Won't get into the reasons, but yeah, just depressed.
Hoping I really, really die.
Yeah, bro. This life ain't this life
ain't the one birth. Oh, I called USA Izzy
yesterday. No, not yesterday. Day before
she picked up, I told I got I told her
to go suck her mom.
I actually wrote her message if you want to see. Um [Applause] um
you know I said laugh my ass off. You're
nothing but a waste girl. Why didn't you
reply to my little Facebook message? I'd
love to give you a slap in front of your
tattooed hippie boyfriend.
I like that. That was cool.
Yeah, I like that, bro. That was cool.
Yeah, that was cool, bro. Yeah. Well,
we can hope and pray we die. That's all
we can do, mate. See, it's easy for
people to give advice to people because
because um because they're not going
through it, so they can say, "Oh, yeah,
better things to come. You never know
what's around the corner."
I'll call them again.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, but I don't need a job. I done it
cuz I was bored.
Yeah, I said I don't I don't need a job.
I just done it because I was bored and
it was something to do. I still don't
need a job.
Call it, bro. I Yeah,
talking about a [ __ ] job whilst you're
sat at home on benefits. Um, you do
realize it's not a main job and I didn't
need a job. I just done it because I
wanted to do it. And second of all, you
don't even have a job. You're sat on
benefits. So before like judging other
people what other people do, you know?
Like look at your own life. You're sat
on YouTube on benefits. You don't even
have a job. You don't even work on top
of your benefits. Who the [ __ ] are you
to talk about anyone else's job, bro?
Like come on, bro. You ain't got
You know what I'm saying, bro? Let me
call this [ __ ] She's bl
I don't have enough credit to make this
call right now.
What the [ __ ] I want to have credit.
What the [ __ ] This is my other phone.
Yeah, I [ __ ] the credit up, bro.
Calling that [ __ ] American number.
Can't remember to top it up, bro. It's
my other phone,
my bro. You're sat on benefits.
Yeah, I [ __ ] rinsed all the credit
calling that number. Oh, bro.
Can't even pull a bike, bro. Anyways, go
self-reflect on another channel.
Some of these self-reflectors. Yeah, bro.
Hope I die in my sleep, bro. Let's all pray. [Applause]
You You understand my point though,
don't you, Greasy? You do understand my point.
This has been going on for years. Like,
it it has been going on for years. See,
like I knew like when my phone got
stolen, I knew that like it's just a
stressful thing and eventually things
would have got better cuz I'm just
buying a new phone. Like I knew back
then like things would have got better,
but now ain't nothing going to change, bro. Nothing.
We got about three or four different
problems on top of the women thing,
which is only 20% of it.
[ __ ] this life. I want out of it, bro.
For real. For real.
But when I am if I ever ever do get
settled again or whatever, I'll have to
be done with people.
Like I said, sorry to keep repeating,
but I do I really do hate people now cuz
people are big re part of it. You know,
people is is a big part of this problem.
So cuz think about if there's no if
there was no one in this country, right?
Would you be moaning about this country? No.
Do you understand, bro? Like you you wouldn't be
I don't have Okay. Okay. Let me give you
an example, Greezy. Okay. By attitude. One second.
Let me get a message from the other day up. Right. So, uh,
so I wrote I didn't tell you about this
cuz this happened the other day, so you
wouldn't have known. I wrote to this
person, "Hi, it was nice meeting you
yesterday. How was your day going?"
They didn't reply. So, I did. I reply. I
messaged again two weeks later, 3 weeks
later. I always message him one more
time and I'm thinking, yolo, you got
nothing better to do. Hi, what are you
up to this weekend? I was thinking we
could go to Burger and Lobster. YOLO,
right? They replied, this is somebody I
met in a train station, by the way. Hi,
that's very kind of you, but
unfortunately I'm flying out on Monday,
so I'm a bit cramped for time. It was
great meeting you, though. And I'm
thinking, wow, [ __ ] hell. Like Burger
and Lobster is like one of the most expensive
places you could not one of the most
expensive but it's kind of like a really
expensive place to go. So you can be
decent looking, have money, and you
can't even get a date. That tells you
all you need to know, bro. That's
literally what they wrote back. It was
great meeting you though, bro. You're
not even given a chance. Do you know how
long it takes to get to know someone's personality?
Like they're just not interested in this
country. It's that simple. Like I know
we laugh about it and we joke about it
and you know, look, you've just seen it
right there. Like I've got so many
messages. You know, I've got one here. I
said, "Hi, it was nice meeting you last
night in ter you. How's your day going?"
They ignored. I then reply back saying,
"Want to go for some drinks on
Thursday?" "Hey, sorry. I'm like
speaking to someone at the moment." Bro,
when is this going to change? Like like
now be be real with yourself now though.
Like you put yourself in my position.
I've got some um I got one here. Right.
These are some from
um Hi. It was lovely meeting you last
night. How was your day going? Hi. Very
I'm very tired. I've been at work since
7:30 a.m. How are you? I said, "Oh,
yeah, I'm good, thanks. Luckily, I
didn't get hangover as I as I stuck to beer."
Then I said, "We didn't get to talk that
much last night. was going to suggest we
could meet up on Thursday if you wanted
and they literally blocked me which I
was very surprised why they would reply
with such interest and then when you ask
them out or you carry on messaging them
they then block you well not all of them
but maybe 10% of them and then there's
some more here.
So what chance
do you really have in this country?
Like all all jokes aside, what you tell
me what chance you really really really
have in this country when somebody
doesn't even give you a [ __ ] chance.
Then there was one by the corner shop.
Hey, it's the guy who we talking to. I
arrived home. For some reason, I tried
to call you. Didn't let me. This is my
number anyways. Didn't even have the
decency to reply. So, we need an estimate, bro.
How long are we going to keep dealing
with this [ __ ] You know, we've been
doing this now for three and a half
years. I've gone through loads and loads
of money on dates. I've gone through
[ __ ] wasting time going out
approaching, [ __ ] drinking three
times a week. When do we call it a day
and say, "Bro, there's no one for us."
Like, when when when do we really call
this a day? Now, like don't don't don't
forget like I'm not some rookie that's
been doing this for a month, 2 months, 3
months, 6 months. This has been going on
for years and it continues to go on.
Even though this was 3 weeks ago, 3
weeks, I think. Yeah, they were 3 weeks
ago. They're not recent. They were just
numbers that I that I picked up. I said
to this one, let's go to a steakhouse. I
have a boyfriend now. Blocked me. When
does this end? Cuz you're saying to me
that I can't predict the future. And
how many times are you going to keep
giving people the beneficiary of the
doubt as Timmy would call it? Come on,
bro. Like, we're all, you know,
the ignoring the [ __ ]
you know, it doesn't change. It never
changes ever. It's one thing that never
changed in 3 years. Loads of things
change, but that never.
And then you go through some other ones
like Grezy, come on. When do we call it
a day and we accept defeat and we accept
that there's no one for us in this
country? And the most annoying thing
about it is I've said it once, I'll say
it a million times again, is there's
nothing wrong with you. You're not ugly.
You're not fat. You don't have any facial disfigurements.
You know, you know there's nothing
really wrong with you.
It's not normal, bro. Whatever normal
means. This ain't normal. You
understand? It ain't normal, bro. You
should be getting dates, [ __ ] some of
them up, not [ __ ] some of them up.
You should be having an active dating
life. Whether some of them worked out or
they didn't work out.
Even if you're fat and ugly, you just
know your place.
you know, your place in society. So
then they treat you like you're ugly
when there's nothing wrong with you and
then that adds to other problems. It
just it's just never ever ending.
See, if dating were a problem,
then it'd be okay. If data was the
problem, but money weren't the problem,
it'd be okay. But we can't deal with a
million and one different things at
once. We can't we can't
you know if it's not one thing it's
another. You know what I'm saying? So
I've got money. I can't be wasting it
anymore here. So
yep. I nicked free food because they blocked the
they blocked the road off.
So I don't really know where you
actually go from here.
So yeah, I was nice in them messages.
Nothing at all. No interest.
Not interested at all.
You know what I'm saying? And then they
have you doubt yourself. It's It's bad,
bro. It is bad.
It's really bad.
And then because of this Uber thing
steward, I started hating people because
of it, like pedestrians and people on the road.
Um, so then it got to a point where you
couldn't even go to work without dealing
with it, even when you weren't even
trying to speak to people. So
yeah, it's not good.
I wish there was a light at the end of
the tunnel, bro, but I don't think there is.
I really really don't think there is
cuz I would have just been happy going
out once a week and then just obviously
drinking and expecting this [ __ ]
Yeah. Then you had to deal with the
people when you was actually trying to
work and none of the people were the customers. So Yep.
Yeah. You should have been with someone
by now. You should be in a relationship
Or at least I'm like a really close
friend that's a woman with the amount of
times I've been to Wales, Scotland.
Think about how crazy that is, Grezy. Scotland.
And as much as they were fun times, you
should have met someone. You really
should be with someone now.
You should be with someone
with the amount of
times that you tried.
I thought people just lose everything
because of um addiction, but it seems
people don't even need to have an
addiction to lose everything. So,
yep. Many more. And I can't believe like
like I was saying, sorry for repeating,
but some people ain't heard it. You get
a guy that said, "Oh, I've only been
Manchester once." Then you've been
Manchester 10 times and there was only
one reason you was going there. how mad
that sounds, how they're just Uber guy.
He brought his bike to central London.
And he said, "This is the first time
I've been to Manchester and he's 3 years
older than me." And all I was thinking
of by traveling, the money I used to go
through, and you're still in a [ __ ] position.
You don't need to wear a bad pit m
um a bad pit mask. cuz there's nothing
wrong with the way that I look.
I've never approached in Bristol, but
I've been to Bristol. I've been to
Cardiff three times.
It's crazy to think that you couldn't
even you you couldn't even find anyone there.
It's a big thing of traveling. I used to
do mate 8 every 8:00 in the morning, I'd
get a train out somewhere
and we're still in the same position. Yeah, it's
really bad, bro. Honestly, the only way
out is death
literally greasy. It is.
What What do you say to them
screenshots? I'm legitimately trying.
Oh, I'll give you one here.
I said, let's meet on Saturday. I'm
Hello. I'm sorry. I've just left I've
just left you stranding my messages
here. Very rude of me. Making a mental
making a mental note to check my
WhatsApp more often. Eek. I'm
unfortunately working this weekend. It's
okay. And oh, I see. Well, what day next
week are you free? Let's do next
Thursday. Question mark. I'm
unfortunately working on Thursday. My
router is all over the place. I said,
"Oh, what days are you free? We should
go to a steakhouse luxury, mind you.
This is a good question. Let me check."
I said, "Did you check?" They wrote,
"Not yet. Sorry. Currently in the gym
and never heard anything after that."
So, I mean, from where I'm sitting, cuz
I'm not standing, it seems like this is
going to be a problem forever,
you know, with these people in this
country. People can say it's not people
to country, but I mean, these messages
say a lot different, you know, it's like,
yeah, so it's it's the same old. There's
one person here claiming that they're
not even in the UK when they are
this is real life, isn't it?
Yeah. I don't know, bro. I think we're [ __ ]
That Uber thing helped me forget the
fact that I'm completely screwed as well. So,
yeah, one day it will change, mate.
Maybe there's a better afterlife.
Maybe there's a better after.
Even when people move, people get mental
breakdowns from just moving. Greasy.
Like, you know, when people move house,
people can can just get mental
breakdowns like that.
They can just get mental breakdowns from um
one second. I'm trying to I'll try to give it
I could understand if I was still
gambling then I'd understand it like you
could blame yourself like okay well we're gambling
we could say that you're gambling or you
got some sort of addiction
But you ain't you ain't got nothing like that, bro.
I don't know why it doesn't send me it
doesn't let me send me a link. Hold on.
Let me try, bro.
It's just stress upon stress upon stress
upon stress upon stress.
I do have credit. I do have credit. I
just don't have credit on my other
phone, you idiot.
I do have credit. I've got unlimited
minutes. I've got unlimited internet. I
do. Just not on that sim. I've got two phones.
You [ __ ] idiot. That was my Uber
phone. This is my main phone. This is my Uber phone. You idiot. So, yeah.
So, if you had like an addiction like
gambling, then you could kind of
understand like you're [ __ ] You know
why? You can kind of blame yourself. But
I'm basically [ __ ]
There you go.
Yeah. So, we're basically [ __ ] bro.
I just messaged some people on WhatsApp. I'm [ __ ]
And even if um you get like like even if
you get a date and stuff, the date
doesn't have most of it to do with it,
but it has some to do with it
cuz it's still it's still a thing that
happened that should have happened.
It's not coming out until next year.
Nothing will ever change.
I wish I wasn't born, bro. I wish I
really wasn't born.
Wish I was dead, bro. All right.
I just gave you the link, you [ __ ] So yeah,
that funny that USA is he picked up the phone. Hello.
Hello. [ __ ] hell, bro.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] up, bro.
No, not the text message. The [ __ ]
ain't going to, bro.
They ain't going to They're not going to [ __ ]
Oh, yeah. Was that linked to my light?
Oh, yeah, it was. Wasn't it? [ __ ] me.
One second, bro. Yeah.
DJ ain't coming out until next summer, bro.
It's not coming out until next summer. Lad. Yeah.
Oh, she didn't change the number. She
just took the SIM out of the phone.
She just took the number out. Uh, took
the SIM off the phone. I called it,
mate. Yeah. [ __ ] stupid. She's a stupid [ __ ]
She's a stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah,
[ __ ] She's a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
Hope she gets [ __ ] run over by a bus.
Yeah, that's another shitty experience I
had. I've got so many shitty experiences
in the [ __ ] collection. It's
unbelievable. I've got none left to add.
I've got no room left in the [ __ ] collection,
Grezy. I've got no more left in the in
this [ __ ] collection anymore, bro.
I ain't got none.
No, I ain't got none, bro.
These people victimizing themsel as
well. Something they like to do. Victimize himself.
Yeah, it's quite hot.
Quite hot, bro. Yeah.
Put my little cap on. Going to these caps lately. So, yeah.
I don't know why Laneany watches my YouTube.
You need to get a life, man. You need to
get yourself down bingo or something,
man. I don't even watch this place half
the time. It's got a spastics. The only
time I watch is when I go live.
I don't think she understands how much I
hate these people. I hate them, mate. If
I ever find out where one of them lives,
like Smokey B or any of these red star,
I'm going to be banging on their [ __ ]
door live, man.
I got two phones now, so I'll be going
on that door, banging the [ __ ] door down, bro.
Get some wet towels on
[ __ ] They're just spastics on here.
Suicide's the only way out, buddy.
Sad to say.
Sad to say, bro.
It might sound funny to a lot of people, but
And then I would tell people, yeah, and
I'll tell people and they'll be like,
"Oh, don't be silly. What? Why am I
being silly?" Like, if you've just
explained a situation to someone and
they're saying that you're being silly
because people don't care because it
don't affect them. You see, when when
things don't affect them, they either
well, they don't understand and they don't care.
They just think, "Oh, something's going
to happen. something's around the
corner. But it don't it doesn't mean
that cuz look how long we dealt with the
dating thing, right? We dealt with that
whole [ __ ] from America. We dealt with
all of these other people and nothing
has ever changed. Like think of how many
years people have been saying, "Oh,
things get better. Things get better.
Things get better." But nothing ever
changes. Nothing. From the time I was
15, bro, you know the amount of times I
heard the same advice, the same
[ __ ] And also, I can tell you as
well, I was going to the gym and I was
working. So, and I didn't even my mom
either. That was another excuse you used to hear. So, yeah.
vent about these things, right? You'll
notice that like you'll notice that women women
like if you went if you went to like if
you if you went to like men, they'll
reply back. Most of them reply back. But
if you've met to women, you'll notice
that none of them none of them care. If
it's something that they can argue with
you, they will reply. But if it's
something serious, they literally don't care.
Yeah, they literally don't. They
literally don't care, bro.
They don't give a [ __ ] But yeah,
but yeah, people don't care, bro, cuz
people don't understand and and things
don't affect them. So, so they don't care.
But she tells me like I like these
caning hate these people on YouTube.
Most of them. Most of them I hate them
on YouTube. People still tell me about them.
Nah, I'm not still alive. But
kids not innocent. You know the amount
of times he's run his mouth up. That
child has run his mouth up on [ __ ] YouTube, bro.
Yep. It's only down from now, mate. It's
only down from now. I mean, people get
mental breakdowns from just moving
house. Remember that. Like, it doesn't
take much for people to get a mental
breakdown. And all people keep saying to
me is, "Oh, you'll be all right.
You don't know what's around the corner.
You don't know what's going to happen
tomorrow." Like, I've literally all I've
been And if I genuinely didn't believe I
was [ __ ] I genuinely would believe
it. Do you know what I'm saying? But
people just keep saying stuff that
doesn't make any sense cuz they're not
blips. None of this stuff is a blip. But
because it doesn't affect people and
they don't understand, they don't give a
[ __ ] So marful me for even saying it to
any of these people to be honest.
So yeah, it is a big mess and it's only
down for now. Like I said, when my phone
got when when my phone got robbed, I
knew that it was a blip. It was
stressful. I knew that I was going to
figure it out somehow. You know what I'm
saying? I knew like it sucks, but it was
what it was. You know, I just took as
life experience, but this I am really [ __ ] So,
the only way is down, bro. Scoutfield,
if you're listening to this, mate, the
only way is down. I know you like to say
the only way is up, but the only way is down, [ __ ]
No, I got my phone robbed a year ago,
but I'm just using it as an example.
Scales Phil used to tell me that the
only way is up, but nah, the only way is down.
I hope I die in my sleep today, bro.
More than anyone. I really, really do.
But people think you're being silly. You
see, when you tell these people, they
don't they don't believe you. They
think, "Nah, you're being silly, you know.
Um, you don't know what's around the
corner. You got to think, well, nothing is guaranteed.
Nothing is guaranteed. You know, when
nothing is guaranteed,
it doesn't look good, does it? It's not
guaranteed. You can't say that [ __ ]
So, what's guaranteed is
if you got your phone robbed, for
example, eventually it would sort itself out or But yeah,
my life is probably worse than Tim
Aldridge is now.
N I don't. But he but with him, he's got
a gambling addiction.
See, I don't have any addiction. So,
it's it's really weird how how like
stuff really never does improve, does
it? cuz we also packed that that in as well.
Now I'm not doing the Uber Eats again,
bro, which is why I told people I done it.
Well, I'd love to tell people everything
on here, but I don't like giving
spastics like Red Star Ammo the little
low life and that Jamie Thompson. I
can't be bothered, bro. Get a bottle.
Huh? You think that I can drink with
amount of stress going on in my life
that I can just go and get a drink? Huh? Nah, bro.
I'm really [ __ ]
Like, you can laugh at it. Laugh all you
want, bro. Laugh all you want, bro. I'd
laugh. I would laugh as well if it
weren't happening to me, bro, to be
honest with you.
And then it's also the frustration as
well. So, it's more than depression.
It's it's also like frustration. You've
got to deal with not being able to
change your situation. They're trying
for 3 years to [ __ ] all you can do, you
know? It's It's [ __ ] bro. I really want
out of this life, bro.
I really want out of this life, bro. I
already had chicken. I already had it today.
I already had it today just before I went live.
It doesn't matter what stress I've got,
bro. But just know it's enough in it. I
don't need to say my [ __ ] life on here, bro.
People like Red Star the little low life. So yeah. Yep.
The dating thing is really bad, bro.
The dating thing is really, really, really bad.
Do you not think it's [ __ ] up, though?
Do you not think it's [ __ ] up, Greio?
You've been lied to your whole life
with the whole uh dating scene. You
don't think that's a bit [ __ ]
Bit bit [ __ ] up. I'll probably get a
beef chow made in a bit.
I'm spending money like I've got loads
of money to spend. Uh that's the funny
thing about it.
No, I [ __ ] don't. [ __ ] Yeah,
but don't worry, Grezy. You never know
what's around the corner, do you? As
long as I'm fine. [ __ ] any other [ __ ]
You know what I mean? Greasy. [ __ ] any
other [ __ ] mate. As long as I'm fine.
Me, me, me, me, me.
You know, [ __ ] everyone else. As long as
I'm all right. That's the impression I
got from a few people. Nope.
So, yeah, I think suicide is really the
only way out.
No, it didn't bother me cuz I was making money.
It was the people that was bothering me
on the roads.
Yeah, I haven't gambled. I haven't drunk
for [ __ ] ages.
Bro, [ __ ] me, bro.
So, I'm not even doing any bad things.
But yeah, I'm [ __ ] So, yeah.
Some people are born in life to be
tested and and tormented.
Like, you got to understand that some
people in life are meant to be tormented and mocked.
You understand, bro? Nope. It's not that. So, yeah.
And no one cares because it don't affect them.
All they say is, "Oh,
look what's around the corner. You don't
know what's around the corner when it's not guaranteed."
You know, how how can anyone be um
how can anyone be certain, you know? But
some people are are just meant to be
mocked by life. And I mean by life itself.
See, I could understand if you had like
an addiction or, you know, you you cuz
you blame yourself. You know, deep down
it's your fault. But none of this is my
You know, that's the that's the whole
that's the whole thing of it is that
like none of it is actually your fault
cuz you know we can't even blame oursel, you know,
bro. But as long as everyone else is all right, mate,
that's fine. Is it?
I'm not entertaining you, LJ. Like I
said, come back when you show them tickets.
Yeah, but you're single forever though,
Harry. You're single and you're a virgin.
So, you need to worry about yourself,
bro. Cuz you're single forever and
you're still a virgin.
So, I mean, you're in the same boat.
You're single forever and you're still a
virgin. So, at the end of the day,
you're talking about yourself as well.
So, yeah, I think suicide really is the
only way out. I told my mom about this
grievy. She's like, "Oh, you're being
silly. You're being silly." Like, it's
like they don't care. They don't
understand so much that it comes across
that they don't care because they're fine.
They're happy being old in a house and
not going out and doing anything. So, it
doesn't affect them. It doesn't bother
more. So, they don't understand.
Obviously, they it's it's more that they
don't understand and it don't affect
them. So if it does if they don't
understand and it don't affect them,
then why would they give a [ __ ] It
doesn't matter who it is, but they don't
really really really understand.
And then everyone else, they just said,
"Oh, you don't know what's around the
corner and all of this [ __ ] I know
what's wrong. I've got a pretty good
idea. I've got a" And you know when
people say the whole with the whole
dating thing, Greavves, you can't
predict the future.
um they tell you I I'd turn around and
say, "Well, I've got a pretty good idea.
I've got a pretty pretty pretty good idea."
Think of it. I've got a pretty good
guess of what the future holds, you know?
No, it's not that they've heard it all
before, cuz now it's worse, cuz I'm
actually [ __ ] Like, I've got four
different problems. Like, I'm actually [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's not even one or the other. I'm
actually [ __ ] [ __ ] and no one gives a
[ __ ] because it don't affect them. So,
no, we're not talking about one thing.
Think of it, Grezy. Yeah. If West Ham
played every week for three years and
they kept getting their ass whooped.
Yeah. Would you have faith in that team?
Would would you put your money on that
team? The next game that they play,
they're going to win. Think about it
like this, right? West Ham keeps getting
their ass whooped by [ __ ] Liverpool.
Every [ __ ] every time they play
Liverpool for the past 3 years, they
keep getting their ass whooped. Yeah.
And it's happened, say it's happened
several times in the past four years and
then they play Liverpool again. Who's
your money going to be on? Let's use
that as as an example. Would you say,
"Oh, well, you can't predict the
future." No, they're going to get their
ass whooped again,
you know? So, you need to be realistic
about the the how long it's been going
on for. It's been going on for [ __ ] years.
Absolutely years. And you know what,
right? If it's been if it happened for a
year, I'd be like, "Okay, well, a year
is not really a long time, you know, but
3 years, bro. Like, get real.
I didn't even barely have a beard them
three years ago. You know, yep.
I've done my balls and I've literally
told you about a million times I don't
gamble anymore, bro.
I've literally told you about a million
times that I do not gamble anymore.
And you're telling me that I've done my
balls in, bro. Bro, if I done my balls
in, I'd blame myself and I wouldn't be
wondering what the [ __ ] I'm going to do
and how I'm completely [ __ ]
I wish I had done my balls in, mate, cuz
I knew where the [ __ ] I knew where
like the [ __ ] upness has come from.
I wish I had done my balls in, mate. If
that was my only problem, I'd be happy
if that was my only problem, you know?
No, nothing to the police. Nothing to
that virgin. Yeah, everyone's heard of
gambling [ __ ] before, which is why we
don't gamble anymore. Everyone's heard
of women [ __ ] before, but no one's heard
this before. And I'm legitimately [ __ ]
And it's not my fault. And yeah, so no
one gives a [ __ ] either cuz it don't affect them.
It don't affect them. So,
I really want out of this life, bro.
Really, really, really want out of this
life. The sooner the better.
See, other people doesn't bother cuz
they've got loads and loads of money or
they're past their prime or the
situation in the hand does not affect
them. You understand, Greavesy? They
don't have that stress. It doesn't
affect them. So they don't they don't
care. They're like, "Oh yeah, something
will come up. Something will come up."
But it doesn't, bro. So I'm screwed.
I should have gave up a long time ago in
this life to be honest with you. But yeah. Yeah. [Music]
It's not just about women, bro. The
women thing is 20% of it.
It's It's literally 20% of it, but it's
still a thing that has to be added on
cuz obviously the trying for you poor
years going through the money, you know.
I don't know what real stress is. Yes, I
do know what real stress is, mate. Yeah.
I I'd love to tell you what it is, but I
can't, bro. There's too many. I don't
want to give people ammo on here. Like,
do you think pip is any life? Think
about it, bro. Okay. Okay. Let's just go
about what you're saying. You think
getting piped is any life? Come on.
Come. Let's Let's Okay. Let's just say,
for example, that I get piped and I've
got all my bills paid. You think that is
any life? You know, the amount I I've
traveled. Yeah. I should be in a [ __ ]
relationship having to deal with these
problems with someone else. You know, I
should be [ __ ] somewhere other than here,
you know? You You think pip is any life,
bro? You think Pip is any life? You
think that kind of money they give you
is any life?
Yeah. Not when you're used to the high
life like me, bro. No, it's not. Sorry.
No, that's not even the problem. Listen,
Harry, that's not the problem. It's just
20% of it.
You understand? It's 20% of the problem.
Yeah, I have got real stress.
Yeah, bro. Like,
if I told you, you're just going to shut
your mouth cuz you don't know what the
[ __ ] you're talking about. Yeah.
You don't know. You don't know what
you're [ __ ] talking about. If I told you, yeah,
you wouldn't um you you you would shut
your [ __ ] mouth, bro. Yeah. Cuz just
because you're in your 30s, bro, it
doesn't mean you've got all this life
experience. What are the stresses? What
a woman. You think that's what all of
this stress is about? Why would it be,
bro? I gave up 3 weeks ago. I was doing
my own thing. I barely spoke to people.
Like, bro, you have no idea what you're talking about. Yeah.
No, I'm proper [ __ ]
Proper proper [ __ ]
No, Greasy gets £800 a month. But yeah,
I'm pro I'm proper [ __ ] anyways.
It's that simple.
Well, I don't know where to start.
Should we start with an Uber account?
Well, my Uber account got banned,
but apparently I don't know what real
stress is. So, yeah. Basically, my Uber
account got banned,
so I can't make money on that. Should I keep going?
I don't think you really want me to keep
going because you'd think twice before
telling people that they don't know what
stress is. So that's one of the things
and now I'm unable to make money on that now.
Um, so that's one of the things. I've
lost a house. So I've lost the income
coming from the house even though I've
got savings and I've still got all my
belongings in here including a TV, a
console. So that's two forms of income
gone. That's a house gone. That's other
people's life gone. So what about me not
knowing about stress, bro? You really
want to keep going? I don't think you
really want to keep going, bro. You
know, just because you're in your
[ __ ] 30s, don't [ __ ] sit there and
try and tell me what is and what isn't
stress. That's two incomes as it is. So
now it's not about oh women or about all
of this. You also have to worry about
getting money. Now you've also got to
worry about how you've been living a
high life. now. No, no one done it. No
one done it, bro. It's something that
happened. You're living this life, bro.
You're living that high. And And And let
me tell you something, um, Harry. Let me
tell you something, Harry. I did know it
wasn't going to last forever. And why do
you think there was the whole point of
the Uber thing was? Why do you think I'd
done the Uber? I was fully aware that it
wasn't going to last forever. And do you
know what? I didn't miss it when they
said, you know, no, they're going to
take the house, whatever. I didn't miss
it. Do you know why? Cuz I was making
money on Uber. I didn't miss the
responsibility of the house. I I was I
was I I accepted it. Okay, they're going
to take it, bro. It's fine. That's why I
done the Uber and it was good. I had no
problem with that. Then they banned my
[ __ ] Uber account cuz I couldn't
deliver pe to people cuz they blocked
the road. I'm [ __ ]
Like it's a simple I'm [ __ ] I have to
sit around now on benefit. I'm not used
to sitting around. I don't like sitting
around doing nothing.
You understand, bro? you know, like
that. It was the whole gay pride thing.
It was the whole gay pride thing. Um,
and I couldn't get I couldn't live in
the food because they blocked all the
roads off. And they done it they done it
two weeks straight. They did. So, yeah,
I knew about the house, which was the
whole point of the Uber. And now I can't
do the Uber, so I'm kind of [ __ ] Do
you understand, bro? And then and and
and that ties in with the whole women
thing. Do you not understand? It ties in
with the women thing. Yeah. It ties in
with the whole women thing. And I tell
you why it ties in with the whole women
thing. Um Harry. Yeah. Remember, bro,
you're making that kind of money on that
house. Yeah. You're making that kind of
money at a house on that house, bro.
Yeah. And I had no responsibilities.
What was I doing, bro? What was I doing
for them three and a half years? What
was I doing for It's got nothing to do
with keeping it private. It had nothing
to do with anyone on this community. No
one made me lose the house. No one made
me lose Uber. They didn't even know I
was doing Uber. It's nothing to do with
anyone on this house. Do you know what I'm saying?
When gay pride was on, bro, I just told
you that they blocked the road last
week. Anyways, listen. But it wasn't
about being private because no one made
me leave the house. It was nothing to do
with anyone on this website. They didn't
even know I still had it and it wasn't Uber. Anyways,
people on YouTube can't make you lose a
house. People have to go to court.
Anyways, so as I was saying, bro, as I
the only, bro, the only reason I've told
them about Uber is cuz they banned my
account. When I get something else, I'm
not telling no one.
Yeah, I'm not telling anyone, bro. I've
only told people because they banned my account.
Do you know what I'm saying?
So that's how it is, bro.
Listen, bro. I know where I was.
Anyways, so Jay Will. Anyways, Harry,
right, let me get on to what I was
saying. these people deflecting. Yeah.
So in them 3 and 1/2 years, what was you
doing in 3 and 1/2 years? Yeah. You was
um you was traveling and like it doesn't
matter where it was, you was
approaching. You went through so much
money which were good times that you've
traveled, but do you not understand how
somebody can see now why they're pissed
off they've not met someone? Do you not understand?
No. There is no other delivery jobs cuz
they're not taking new riders. Bro, I
live in London. Do you understand, bro?
It's not just about the house. I
accepted the house. It's fine. I was
making I can make money somewhere else.
It's not a problem. Yeah, the house
obviously is a problem. You lost a lot
of money on the house, but we had a
substitute for that. And you've also
wrecked other people's lives now. They
have to go. You don't understand. And
that means I've got to deal with people
now, bro. You don't get it, bro. And for
you to try and tell me that I don't know
what stress is. I'm not used to being a
lazy bum like these people, bro.
Do you know how long it took me to earn
£55 the other day?
Do you know how long it took? It took
eight hours, bro. Still done it cuz it
was better than nothing. Yeah. No matter
no matter what these people are saying
on this community, I didn't care what
they said, bro. Because at the end of
the day, it was better than nothing. I
accepted this is what it is now. Nothing
lasts forever. Like, so that's two
things. And yeah, it did tie in with the
women thing cuz by rights, you should be
with someone. the amount of approaching
that you've done, the kind of money that
you've gone through, bro. If I told you
that the casino stories, the whole like
you would be surprised. You wouldn't
even believe it, bro. The amount of
money that I used to go through going out
and then you got like you should be with
with and all you've been is shon and
anyone would think you're like a [ __ ] Timmy Aldridge.
You understand? Like you're we're
[ __ ] Simple. It's just plain and simple.
So yeah, but they don't take new riders
on. But yeah, to let you know, Harry, I
don't tell people my business. I told
people cuz I don't do it anymore. So
like I don't I don't do anything any I
don't do it anymore. If I did, bro, I
wouldn't tell people. I would have made
them lose lose this whole thing. So,
I've got to deal with this whole
country, the people, the women, and now
I've got to deal with money,
which believe it or not, you don't even
think it's you don't even get that [ __ ]
money. But, bro, I can't do that.
I've got savings, but it's not it's not
the point. It's not the point, bro. You
know, it's it's only down from now, bro. So,
that was just a [ __ ] Sunday as well.
Yeah. Sunday was Sunday was quiet, bro.
I done it on a Sunday, but
then that made me deal with [ __ ]
people and stuff like, so it is what it is.
No, my money hasn't stopped, just some
of it. So, so yeah,
and that's the most frustrating thing
now. So, I need to try and find a way to
get money. Oh, so I've got money. I
still have money. But I mean, from now
on, like none of this is about being
skimp. But you know, I need to figure out something
cuz I'm not living off a grand a month.
There's no way I'm living off [ __ ]
11,200 a month. No way. That makes me
sound like so like you got the likes of
Venny living off £300 a month, £400 a
month. Some people live on [ __ ] not
living off that, you know.
And I always said as well like
I always said as well like to people
like you're lucky that you don't have to
worry about money as well as all this
and what happens when you stop you know.
Yeah. Like 1,100 maybe. It's not even
[ __ ] but it's just not enough for my lifestyle
about Is that it? It's not bad but it's
just it's not enough for my lifestyle.
Yeah. And I just told you that I lost
some of my income. Yeah. And I've lost
Yeah. So, I'm no longer on 3K a month. Duh.
So, nope. Never gambled a grand more
than once in my life. That's [ __ ] So,
yeah. I'm pretty screwed now to be honest.
No, you're not. Anyone would think
you're starving and that, but I am. I am
[ __ ] Simple as that.
Nope. I wasn't doing that on stakes. Try
again, buddy. Stop trying to troll.
We're not We're not on here to stop
[ __ ] trying to troll. So, yeah. Like,
you can understand the situation now, is it, Grezy?
And obviously, you should have met
someone by now. So,
and you haven't for whatever reason, you
still haven't met someone, which I think
is a good reason to add add on. You know
what I'm saying? So,
I will be, mate, cuz I won't be on it
for long cuz I'll have to get a job cuz
I'm not living off [ __ ] that money a
month. No way am I living off that money
a month. I'll have to try another
delivery company or something. I'm not
living off that money a month. And
theoretically, I can cuz I get over a
grand a month. So, I can still call
Virgin Boy by a grand a month, boy.
So yeah, I still can.
yeah, I can and I will do
cuz I'm not the one sat on [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. The whole point Yeah. The whole
point is that people on benefits don't
pay rent. Let Let me explain something
to you, right? You know, your outgoings
is not the same as what somebody gets on
benefits, which is something that you
need to understand. Like, bro, my
wardrobe is worth more than your whole
life, but you don't see me bragging. You
got to understand, it's a it's a bit
like Uber. It's a bit like these
delivery companies. They're not a main
job. You You understand? They are
literally not a main job. And it's over
£250 a week. It's over a,000. They're
not a main job. That's that's a part
thing. You do realize they're not for
people for a main job. And they you also
realize people on benefits do not pay rent.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that,
buddy. I'm the one that lives in London
and you don't. So that's it. And your
rent is not two grand a month cuz you
don't even live in London. So yeah, you
keep telling yourself that, bro. Your
car on finance. Yeah, bro. I mean, your
car is on finance. So yeah, you keep
telling yourself that if it helps you
sleep at night, bud. Two guy a month
rent and you don't even live in London.
Yeah, in your wet dreams. Do you know
what? I read a comment uh I think it was
about two weeks ago. Somebody was
claiming how they got um I said I done
some hours I got £160
and he said that he got 160 uh you it's
actually more than £1,000 a month which
I've explained about a million times.
And literally what happened was
what what was I saying now bro? You made
me lose track of my [ __ ] thoughts now
bro. Um, he was saying that he gets 160
a day. I said, "What?" on YouTube. What?
Do you get 160 a day on YouTube? Yeah.
On YouTube, bro.
Yeah. You spend 250 on a night out?
Yeah. In your dreams, bro. In your
dreams. In your dreams. You do. But
nothing else but your dreams.
I don't even spend 250 on a night out, mate.
Yeah. You keep telling yourself that,
bomb, who I believe is on that account.
See, you do get the fantasy as well. You
do get the fantasy on here as well. You
get the fantasists on here, too. Dom was
a big one. So, yeah.
And it's actually not 1k a month. It's
actually a bit more than that. But yeah.
Yeah. It's great. And it's great that
I've got more money than you in savings
as well. Yeah. It's fine, bro. But I
still got more money than you.
I still got more money than you savings.
Got more assets than you.
Yeah, man. That's great as well. I'll
always have more money than you, no
matter how much money I get. And that's
the whole point.
So yeah, at least I'll never have your life.
Might be a grand above, mate. But got
more money than you still. So yeah.
Yeah. I had to I've just explained to
you about a million times why I've done
the Uber Eats thing, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah. You don't even have a job. I've
just I just explained it to you. Listen,
Chbby, you're in your 40s and you're on
about £300 a month. Get real, kid.
You're on about 300 pound a month and
you're in your 40s. Take a look at your own life,
bro. I explained to you about a million
times why I done I done the Uber Eats.
I've literally got more money than you,
bro. Listen, how many times have I
played the money game only for you to
lose time and time and time and time and
time again? [ __ ] I'm still
waiting for people to show me 8 grand.
There's no point talking about money cuz
every time you're shown money, you run
away. I can literally take out money
right now. I can take out the maximum
right now from an ATM and you will run
away. Like there's no point you even
talking about money, bro. Because every
time you get shown money, you run away
every single time. So there's literally
no point you even talking about money.
And you got eight grand to show me
anyways, bro. I swear I never show money
again until you show eight grand. All of
this your whole broke, your skin, you're
talking about your own lives. You don't
bother anyone. It's just self-reflection.
winnings, income, [ __ ] borrowed
money. You've been shown 5.7 grand in
cash and none of you have shown me anything.
So, at the end of the day, just stop
talking about money, mate. Whether it's
winnings, borrowed money, money or
yours, you ran away. End of. There's
nothing to say, bro. So, yeah.
So, yeah, bro. Anyways, moving on now.
You can get gone. So, yeah.
These people on this YouTube is on £300
a month. They're literally on £300 a
month and they're talking about 1K a
month. Crazy in it, bro.
Anyways, moving on now. I need to block
this account as well, bro. These wannabe
trolls are terrible at trolling, bro.
Terrible at it. They're so terrible.
They can't even troll. So, yeah.
So yeah, that's the story of Balamorei really.
So yeah, it's a pretty uh it's a pretty
[ __ ] up position to be in to be
honest. And it's like look at it, bro.
Like even if you rise back up with the
money thing, you're still going to deal
with the dating. So isn't it time to
call it quits with this life,
mate? I'm not taking money out. Every
single time I have took money out,
you've run away. When you come back and
you show me 8 grand, lad, right? Oh,
come back to me. Like, bro, bro, bro,
you have been shown thousands upon
thousands upon thousands upon thousands
upon thousands. No one has shown me
anything. When you show me your 8 grand,
come back to me and we'll play the money game again.
So yeah, you have been shown money time
and time and time and time again. When
you have shown me that 8 grand, come
back to me.
So yeah, said hello and then and then uh
answered. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, it's cute, eh?
Is that cute, lad?
Yeah, bro. Anyways, come back when you
can show me money. Anyways, this ain't a
competition. When you've got money, come
back to me.
Yeah, it did.
Yeah, I was just telling these people on
YouTube how I'm completely [ __ ] as far
as like money goes now. Well, you're not
completely [ __ ] You're just not going
to live a high life. You're nowhere near
completely [ __ ] but you're you won't
But in my eyes, I am [ __ ] So, even
though you're not [ __ ] but um
you're not [ __ ] but you're
you're going to have to Yeah.
Yes, SL. So,
just lucky had some savings, isn't it? really,
you know, you got to deal with the money
thing, you got to deal with the women,
then you got to deal with these people.
It ain't worth it, bro. Just life
really, really, really ain't worth it.
It really, really, really ain't worth it.
But that's fantasy land. Like, you can't
live off 111,200 a month. You can. It
would just be It wouldn't even be below
the poverty line really if you don't
have any rent. It just won't be a high life.
That's all it is. You're not going to
starve. You're not going to go without
paying bills. You're just not going to
live a high life.
Um, anyone would think you're you're on
[ __ ] £200 a month for [ __ ] sake.
You're just not going to be living a high life.
Um, or maybe a month or so. So,
you won't be living a high life.
So yeah, you couldn't live off a grand a
month. You [ __ ] could, mate. You live in Liverpool.
So you can live off a grand a month
because you live in Liverpool. So I'm
pretty sure, mate, if I could live off
it with a bit of difficulty, I'm pretty
sure you can.
Like, bro, you can live off £1,100 a
month. You're just not going to have a
high life. You're not even going to be struggling,
you know? like, uh, I don't trust you,
bro, because I've done it myself. I've
lived off £700 a month. So, yes, I could.
So, yes, you could. How is it possible?
Because you don't have any outgoings.
Like, you people, there's no point
trying to explain anything to you cuz
you're all fantasists. So, that's the
whole point. You don't have to pay rent.
If you have,00200
yourself, yes, you can live off it.
Yeah, life is just not going to be as
good. But you can proper proper live off it. Like
if you don't have rent and you've got a
bill or two bills, of course you can
[ __ ] live off it, bro. You're not
going to starve. You know what I'm
saying? You're not on [ __ ] £300 a
month. You got no outgoings. Yeah, you
can live off it off off of it. It's just
not going to be a very high life. So,
you won't be able to do a lot of things
for like a little while, but you
definitely can live off it 100%.
It's just not going to be a high life.
So, but you're not going to struggle.
You're not going to [ __ ] starve. You
know what I mean?
How much rent do you pay? Yeah. Again,
but you're seeing it from your point of
view. You're See, some of these people
in here might work, right? Some of these
people on here might work and get some
of these people might get two grand a
month, right? Or 2.5k a month and then
um they might have to pay rent and then
they think of it like that, but then
they're left with a grand themsel.
That's how they see it. You get someone
on here that gets like 2.3k a month,
right? And then pays £1,300 a month and
says and then they get left with £1,000.
Then they're like, "Oh, I can't live off
a £1,000." When theoretically, you're
actually living off basically £1,000 by
the time you've paid your rent.
So, they're seeing it as themselves
paying more in rent when people on
benefits do not pay rent. So,
yeah, it's not as good as that virgin
used to make out, but you definitely
would more than enough get by on it. But yeah,
it's the stress of other things as well, you know. But yeah.
Yep. Everyone's got different
lifestyles, I guess. Isn't it?
Nothing's easy, bro. Nothing's easy.
Yeah. So, how much do you pay? How much
do you get a month?
Yep. And imagine having imagine having
money problems on top of it as well.
Yeah, I know. At least back then, I
didn't have I didn't really have to be
careful with money. That's the only
thing I used to say, like, oh, it's not
that bad. I mean, at least you don't
have to work or worry about money.
But look where we are now.
I mean it happens to everyone you know
people lose their YouTube channel they
can't make money from YouTube anymore or
but by that time they would have settled
down with kids anyways so it wouldn't
have bothered them
but yeah just to get you like you
understand how severe the situation is.
So when someone tells you that oh it's
going to be okay and no they're talking
out their [ __ ] ass.
So yeah, it would be enough for you to
live, bro. You live in Liverpool. If
it's enough to live in London, it's
enough to live in Liverpool.
Yeah. And I'm still going to take the
piss. I'll take the piss out myself, mate.
Yeah. Stop talking about yourself. You
sad. Go get blocked on that. Trust me,
you could live on a grand. Listen,
Harry, you live in Liverpool, brother.
You live in a place where their houses are£1.
You understand? Know what I'm saying? Like
you couldn't live off one grand a month,
bro. Stop being silly.
You just wouldn't be able to [ __ ] go out much.
Yeah. And I'll still take the piss out
of it. And I'll take the piss out of
myself. But guess what? I've got
something they don't. And that's savings. So yeah.
Bro, you don't even get a grand a month,
bro. Listen, Harry, you can live off
1.1k a month if you have no outgoings.
You know what I'm saying? You of course
you can. It's just not going to be an excellent life.
Do you understand? It's just going to be
a bro. Listen, I've gone out and I've
spent more money than you would ever
have, brother. You live in Liverpool.
I've been to Liverpool. You're
forgetting me, bro. I've been all over England.
But not in that, bro. So, yeah. Yeah, man.
It won't be a broke life. It will just
be not a very good life. You're talking
like you can't live off it a month.
You're talking like, bro, you people,
you don't even leave your house and
you're talking like you could live off a
grand a month. You people really are
fantasists. It's either you're fantasist
or you work and most of your money goes
on rent because bro, you got no life
experience. Like the amount of times I
had a grand in a bank in the bank or
£500 in the bank even when I was on that
income and bro
you really really really really I still
have money. I still have money. I've got
savings. You really don't know about life bro.
You really really don't. Like there was
times even then.
So yeah, I can go on dates. I've still
got money. Yeah.
Well, how much do you get a month, Henry? Huh?
All loft eaters. Yeah. How much do you
get a month
by now? Grezy, do you understand the
situation? Well, I won't I won't be
taking them out because I want a waste of time.
But you can understand why people would
think of like suicide in it. You can
understand, in it, now
even though there was literally people
that had no money at all. But you can
understand it now, isn't it?
Yeah. You come out with 3K. Even 3K is
nothing. Even when I used to get 3K a
month, that was nothing. And I had no
outgoings. And let me guess, how much
are you left with after all your bills are paid?
Yeah, I used to get three grand and even
that weren't tons and tons and tons of
money, mate. So, I wouldn't be showing
off if I was you. You know what I'm
saying? And anyways, how much outgoings
have you got every month?
This is where this guy's going to [ __ ]
himself up now
and none of it's going to make any sense.
So yeah, but honestly you can you can
understand the situation, bro.
Like you can understand the situation in
it, Grezy. You understand it? Like the um
the problem in it. You can understand the situation.
Like Melanie doesn't seem to understand it.
She seems to think people are being
silly. You know what I mean? Um,
I told my sister as well and she still
doesn't understand because it doesn't
affect them. It doesn't it doesn't
affect it doesn't affect them.
You know, they've not had your
experiences with women. They're not
having to be on lower income now. And
even if they are, you know, they're old.
She's old. You know, old people don't
really go out and and stuff. Do you understand?
So, they don't care. And to be honest
with you, I wouldn't blame them to be
honest. You know, it's not happening to
them. So, you understand my point, Grezy.
So, like, yeah,
I'm [ __ ] screwed basically.
I'm not even I don't know why I'm saying
I'm screwed. I'm not even screwed.
Screwed. It's just not going to be as
good. I got savings as well still, but
still it doesn't matter, bro.
Still got a couple of grand. So, um
I need to start figuring something out,
bro. Really? But yeah,
I have to start shoplifting like Ant-Man does.
Like the thing is with the whole Uber
thing, it was okay. Like even if I was
getting 1.5, 1.8 a month, it's okay. Cuz
the way I saw it is I lived life. I knew
what the women were like in this
country. You know, I was okay just going
out once a week and earning the money
once a week. It was fine. I'm okay with
1.5, 2K. Like, you've been there, done
it. You've worn the t-shirt. You know,
all all good things come to an end. But
then when that account got banned and I
couldn't even make money back that I had
spent that's that was like oh [ __ ] You
know what I'm saying? That was a really
really bad like that was a really bad time
cuz I wouldn't mind 1.6 1.8
you're only going out drinking beer a
week you know. So
but then you know cuz I had to get used
to it. I had to get used to it because
of the um the situation. What's up? Yeah. So,
it is a [ __ ] situation.
I won't even be able to go out for a
month anyways now. Not due to money.
I've got so much stress. It's unbelievable.
It really, really, really, really,
really is unbelievable. So, yeah.
I have to try and figure something out, bro.
So, I think that's the most baddest thing.
And the fact that you should be with
someone as well
cuz matter how much savings you have or
had, it's all going to come to an end
because you're not getting that sort of
income anymore. So,
I generally don't think there's a way out, bro.
Well, I've got the gym for a month. I
pay the gym. So, I can go to the gym and that.
What would you do if you was me, Grey?
I'm pretty much [ __ ] in it.
I'm pretty much screwed.
Or [ __ ] if there was to be one.
No, I still got money. It's not about
memories. I've still got money. I don't
know why you're trolling. I've still got
more than enough money. I need to sell
something from my house as well, which
I'll make money from. Nothing like a TV
or anything. I've still got money. So, I
don't know why you're going on like I'm
skimp, but it's not about that. It's the
whole situation is [ __ ] I've still
got money, mate. I could go out and
still do it today if I wanted to. So, um,
what would you do if you was me, Greavvesy?
But yeah, Laney doesn't seem to really
understand much. I I don't like I don't
want to say that she doesn't care cuz I
think that's not
I don't think that's um
that's fair to say cuz I think she does.
But the whole point is is like,
yeah, there is going to be more£400
nights out for me
cuz I still got money.
Just everything now. Basically
everything. But you got to understand,
she's old, man. She's had her life.
She's got her kids. She's retired. I'm
literally 27. I'm [ __ ] I've got to
deal with this whole women thing. They
just don't understand. So,
so yeah, bro. I mean, um,
well, yeah, in terms of money basically.
In terms of money. Yeah. And then it's
going to be frustrating because there's
not going to be any other way to make
money in that.
Maybe I'll just give my money away to my
mom and just kill myself. Just write a suicide note
cuz I don't think they really understand
how serious this is.
Like you settled down with a kid, now
your life is you got Uber and that.
You know what I'm saying? It's not like
you settled down with children and your
life's different now. You know, cuz all
good things come to an end. I accepted
that. I'm not [ __ ] losing that as
well. Do you know what I'm saying?
I was fine with the the house thing. In
many ways, it was a good thing cuz I
didn't want the responsibility of it anymore, but it's [ __ ]
I've already got money. I've already got
money. You don't need to tell me that I
could save, bro. I've already got money.
Nah, Uber is good. I'll tell you why
Uber is good. Cuz you can do it when you want.
I could have saved thousands, mate. I've
already got money and I'm still due a
payout. But anyways, um
and no, Uber is actually good cuz you
can do it when you want and it's extra
money. So yeah.
So yeah, bro. Oh [ __ ]
One second, bro.
I just have to start shoplifting, mate.
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Bro, like um that's why lady doesn't
seem to really understand. I don't
expect people to understand, bro. You know,
but the annoying thing is there's
nothing you can do to change it. It's
not like we're lazy people. Do you know
what I'm saying? We're just lazy people.
So, we're not lazy people, bro. So, she
doesn't understand how serious it is. Do
you understand what I'm saying, Grievy?
How like they don't understand how
serious it is. I was talking to my
sister about an hour and a half ago, and
I don't think she really understands. You know,
again, you've got a child, you've got
probably near enough £20,000 in your
account. At the end of the day, they
don't really seem to care much. They
don't understand the severity of it.
Then you say, "Oh, it will get better.
Something will come up." I mean, you've
got a child. You've got near enough
£20,000 in your account. Your going out
days are done, mate. You're set for life.
Um, and then my other sister's obviously
got a partner to help her out. I'm legitimately [ __ ]
So, suicide is the only way out for me.
If it was one or the other, then it
would have been fine. But that's two.
That's two now.
So, and I shouldn't have to adjust. I
shouldn't have lost my Uber account. I
was making money on that Uber account. I
shouldn't have had to lose that. the
house you were going to lose whether you
liked it or not. You know, that's just
it was going to happen. You know, it's
you would have lost it, but the U
account you shouldn't have lost.
So, it's sort of like
it was good in any way. So, now we are
generally [ __ ] Oh, bro, there's
another [ __ ] app here, bro. And I
don't want to think about how like I'm completely
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying, bro?
But I don't want to have to think about
every day how I'm completely [ __ ]
Yeah, I didn't stay at my mom's either
to be fair. I stayed overnight. I was
like, I don't think I should stay here
again cuz you don't want me around you
when I'm like this. So yeah.
Uh, long story. But
just know that I'm uh
yeah, completely [ __ ]
But she doesn't understand. She doesn't
understand the lifestyle that I was
leading having. Like it slowed down a
bit. No, bro. To be fair, it slowed down
a bit. Like I didn't want to go back to
them days where I was like spending
hundreds and hundreds. I didn't want to
go back to them days. I weren't going
back to them days, you I was just happy
with the Uber and spending, you know,
maybe 150 a week going out, which the
Uber would have paid for. It weren't a
problem. I had to accept that this is
the life now, you know, and in many ways
it kept you um it kept you it kept you o
occupied, you know, we were never going
to go back to the high life, you know,
even if we could afford it because we've
been there, done it, won the t-shirt,
but now you are literally literally completely [ __ ]
You're just going to have to try and
live off. You're just not going to have
to go out for a month. I'm not going to
go out for a month anyways. I can still
afford to go out, but I'm just not going
to go out for a month anyways because of
the um go out for a month anyways
because of the whole um
No, I'm not renting accounts. I don't
trust renting accounts. So, I shouldn't
have to rent accounts cuz they b my
account for no reason. So, to be honest
with you, I'm just going to go to a gym
for a month anyways. So,
I won't be going out for a month anyways
to be honest.
Even when I was doing the Uber, I just
have too much stress.
And I said to my mom as well, I was
like, "You do realize you had a mental
breakdown when you moved?" Yeah, I have
to move. I've lost two incomes. I'm
completely [ __ ] I have to deal with
this whole women thing. Anyone that was
anyone else would have killed himself,
bro. I'm telling you, anyone else would
have killed himself.
anyone else would have um you know
Yeah, bro. I'll just find something.
Yeah, they paid me. Yeah.
Nah, it's a long story, bro.
Nah, I'm not homeless. Nowhere near
But yeah, you just won't be able to do
much now, to be honest. So, yeah,
you'll just be fat.
You won't be fat. Fat.
A little [ __ ] So yeah,
this is just going to make life just 10
times harder. I think that's I think
that's like the right word for it.
No, it's nothing to do with a customer.
All the customers were fine. None of the
customers were rude. It was just the
[ __ ] It was just the [ __ ] on the street.
But yeah, I don't think lady understands
the severity of it. She just thinks
everything's going to be okay when it's
not going to be okay cuz you're literally [ __ ]
Like you have no one to support you,
which you should have someone to support
you cuz the amount of traveling and
trying you've done,
you know, since having a house, you
should be with someone. And if it wasn't
that, then the dating should have been
easier. But it's everything. So
what am I going to do? I'm going to have
to sell my ass.
to sell my ass or shoplift.
But no one cares anyways. It don't
affect them. So they just say, "Oh, you
don't know what's around the corner.
You don't know what's around the corner.
Don't be silly." That's what they say.
That's literally literally what they say.
You know, I expect them to look like
more bothered about it. You know what
I'm saying? But but
there's nothing I can do. Um, I'm [ __ ]
There's nothing else you can do. But
really, you're not. See, with the Uber
thing, he wasn't [ __ ] because you
don't need to be going out spending
£500. You know what it's like in this
country. You know what these women are
like. It's been for years.
It was a bad, bro. So,
I'm going to have to think of something rapid, bro.
I'm going to have to start thinking of
this thing of something rapid.
I like the area. I like the house. I
don't want to live with my mom. It's
just No, I can buy escort. I can buy it,
bro. I was with an escort [ __ ] the other day.
Bro, I was with an escort the other day,
mate. And I can buy stonies whenever I
want. I've already appealed a ban and
they denied it.
They've already I've already appealed a
ban and yeah, I'll be [ __ ] I'll be
I'll be [ __ ] shoplifting and [ __ ] selling stuff.
Unless you shoplift is the only way and
then you can end up in prison.
We need to stop thinking of other ways.
There's no other ways. What's the point
of even wasting your time thinking of
other ways when there's no other ways
except except from shoplifting or
selling your ass? There is no other way.
basically all the things the government
don't want. So, uh
I've already explained what I done, bro.
I'm not explaining it again. So,
this payday tonight,
it's not my bike, bro. I didn't I rented
it. I need to sell this washing machine.
I've got some things to sell cuz I'm not
taking it with me. Um
yeah, bro. Cuz I'm not taking it with
me. I'm not taking it with me. So um
um so I'll make money on that as well,
which is mad cuz my [ __ ] isn't your
[ __ ] Like I don't have no money. I'm
not starving. I've got a TV. I've got an
Xbox. I won't end up homeless. But
I think we in this house, we tease each
other because we realize that we're all [ __ ]
We tease each other cuz we realize that
we're actually all [ __ ] So, we just
laugh at it. But I don't know who's more
[ __ ] me or them. Probably me, to be
honest, cuz I've lost two incomes. So,
even where I move, I don't pay rent. I'm
[ __ ] I'm more [ __ ] I think they're
also [ __ ] too. We have to laugh about it.
I don't know, mate. I don't know whether
I'm coming or going.
They have to deal with people as well.
So, but lady's all right, man. She's got
kids. She's retired. She lives by
herself. She doesn't Roy understand
these understand these problems.
No, I didn't [ __ ] up cuz the house had
nothing to do with losing the these
people had nothing to do with me losing
the house. These people had nothing to
do with me losing Uber.
So, no, I didn't [ __ ] up. And the only
reason I'm telling you is because I lost
the Uber account.
You know, these people didn't make me
lose the house. The landlord went to
court. Yeah. He He was trying to get
back for for court. Yeah. And the court
won. It wasn't anything to do with
people on YouTube. And the Uber wasn't
to do with anything on on YouTube cuz
people didn't know I was doing it.
So, yeah. It weren't anything to do with
these people on YouTube.
So, I don't know why you keep blaming
YouTube, bro. Like,
so, and even the whole um Yeah,
it had nothing to do with these people on YouTube.
It had nothing to do with these people
on YouTube, bro.
So, yeah, I'm not talking about it
anymore anyways. No, I don't want to
move in with Laney, man. She wants her
own peace. She's old, man. She's old.
She's old. And you know, I was there
yesterday. No, just what I don't need to
take accountability cuz it was nothing
to do with these people on YouTube,
which I've explained about a million
times. Anyways, I'm not talking about it
no more. We can just say that we're [ __ ] anyways.
So, yeah. So, we're [ __ ] anyways. Um,
so what? You get a grand a month, Grezy?
No, I won't miss the escorts cuz I got
one the other day and I can get one
right now if I wanted to.
I don't have to pay it back. I've got savings.
savings, but it's not the point. Now I
need to find another avenue of income.
£1,200 you get more than me. I think I
get about 111 maybe but I had to pay
stuff out of it which it would have been
about 1150 maybe.
Nope. It wasn't anything to do with that
mate. People knew I had this house for
[ __ ] 3 years. People knew I had this
house for three years. It had nothing to
do with anyone on YouTube. Anyways, I'm
not talking about it no more. But yeah,
obviously I took some loans out and
stuff greasy. So that's why the money's
a bit less.
That's why the money's a bit less. So yeah.
Um but yeah, probably roughly the same
if I didn't owe thingy.
Yeah. And I've still got money, mate.
I've still got money. The only reason
I'm not showing you any money. Only
reason I'm not showing you any money,
mate. I'm I'm I'm still better off than
you people on YouTube. I've still got
money, mate. I can show you 50s right
now. Well, what's the time? Yeah, but
there's no point because none of you
people ever show anything.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Like, bro, I've still got more money.
I'm still better off than most people on
here, but it's just the whole situation is [ __ ]
So yeah, anyways, I'm not talking about
it no more, bro. But anyways, Grezy, you
understand the position now, is it? You
understand the situation now, don't you, Grezy?
You understand the the the You
understand the situation?
Yeah, I've still got money. Yeah, and
I've still got money, bro. I've still got money.
No, I don't. Okay, you keep telling
yourself that, buddy. If that if that
helps you sleep at night. Yeah, I don't
have no money. Okay, bro.
Why not take a loan out?
Anyways, you can go. Bye-bye now.
But um yeah, Grey, do you understand the situation?
Yeah. Okay, bro.
Yeah. Okay. I have nothing, bro. Okay,
whatever. You can tell yourself that.
So, anyways, you understand the situation? Yeah,
you understand the situation now. Yeah.
I think Greavesy would kill himself if
he was me, bro. Honestly, I think he'd kill himself.
Like, about me being completely [ __ ]
mate. I've still got money.
I've still got money. I don't know why
you think I ain't got money, but that's
on you, bro. It
Well, what would you do, Grezy? You'd be
[ __ ] You'd be [ __ ] up like me.
Yeah, but I'm [ __ ] in it, Greasy. You
have to admit I'm [ __ ]
I am [ __ ] bro. Right. There's no
point trying to deny it. I'm like 1,100.
So it's like I got some savings. Yeah. So yeah,
thinking reply back.
Yeah. Would you be depressed?
But it doesn't matter to Laney or anyone
else because it doesn't bother them.
It don't bother them, does it? though
because it's not them it's happening to
um so why would they give a [ __ ]
anyways I'm getting blocked as well
get my head down and and work hard
yeah really bro
I I don't know why people don't
understand how bad it is.
Do you not understand how bad the
situation is, Grezy?
Like, do you really not understand how
bad the situation is?
It's really bad.
It's a really bad situation to be in.
Like would you admit Grezy that I'm completely fat?
Yeah, I'm not buying no accounts, bro. I
don't trust them.
So, but at least I still got more money
than Virgin Boy. Nonss,
which is what I basically been saying
the whole time,
you know, as I got savings and [ __ ] but
still doesn't really mean anything, bro.
So greasy. Am I [ __ ]
Be honest. Greasy. You [ __ ]
What? You say I'm completely [ __ ] Yeah,
but they don't give a [ __ ]
You're not very [ __ ] or skinn, but you
are you are you're long-term [ __ ]
That's the thing. You're you're [ __ ]
long term. And it wasn't any of these
people on YouTube, bro. So, I don't know
why these trolls keep saying that, but
yeah, you are you are screwed. But don't worry,
you'll be on the same uh you'll be on
the same as as him. No, I won't, mate.
No, because by that time I would have
figured something out.
Yeah, but I think Laney should have
tried to understand a bit more. Like
your whole lifestyle is gone
and they don't seem bothered cuz they're
okay. They don't care because they're
okay. You see,
not trying to slay family, but they
don't really really care. Like, no one
cares. They just think, "Oh, I'm happy.
I got my little house. I get £1,300 a
month. You can live off that. You can
That's what they That's what they say. So yeah, £600.
Yeah, it will drive me drives you into a depression.
I was thinking of [ __ ] taking
anti-depressants to be honest, but no
one cares. So, not drinking.
I w I weren't thinking of drinking.
Maybe I need to go out for a drink just
by myself, you know.
One of the other reasons that will help
you forget the fact that you're
completely [ __ ] So, yeah.
So, you with Uber, your lifestyle
weren't gone cuz you could still make
money and you can still save. You understand? um
you know you can make £300 a week, you
can make whatever. It doesn't matter how
hard it was. You spend you make doesn't
your lifestyle weren't really changing
with that you know just the fact that
you had to go out and work for it but
you know it would have happened one day in it.
And you're dealing with this problem
with no one. No one,
you know, like you don't you're not
dealing you're dealing with this problem
all by yourself.
To be honest with you,
no one around you. No one really cares.
They just say, "Oh, there's better days.
Things get better." No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no. That's what they say.
Got a phone. Got a telly.
No, because there there's too many riders.
There's too many riders, bro.
And then the whole women thing was like
20% of it because it's like, well, hold
on a minute. You spent all of this money
traveling around. Why are you not with a
woman? You spent all of this money
traveling around. You've been Wales.
You've been in Scotland.
You should be with someone now. You
know, I was thinking about that even
with the Uber. Like even when I still
had an Uber, I was I've accepted it. I
said like I didn't make a big thing out
of it. I said to admin like you know
we've been trying for years like we got
haircuts every week. We send it every
week. Bro, I'm telling you anybody else
would have just killed himself now.
I never knew I had this level of
patience. And it's only down now. It's
only down, bro.
Yeah. Either one of them. It's like if
you had a woman and you was dealing with
this, it would be not as bad. If you
never had a woman and you still got the
income, it wouldn't be as bad. We could
go out and enjoy ourselves every week.
So, we've actually got every problem
now. You see? So, you know, if you had
if you had a woman and you had your Uber
Eats account, you'd be laughing, bro.
You've done everything you had to do.
Yet, you proved your point. You met
someone. Slow down with life a little
bit now. You lost that. You're single,
which you shouldn't be single with the
amount you've tried. And you've also lost like
pretty much 90% of your money. But
people don't seem to understand. And
then one day when you're dead, when you
when you commit suicide, people are
going to wonder, well, why did you
commit suicide? Or if you end up in
hospital or when you just have a mental
breakdown, you know, then they'll wonder
why. You know, it's not a small thing.
It's a big thing.
I don't have any right, bro.
I rented it.
So yeah, uh
I didn't buy it, but I rented it.
I didn't want to buy it in case someone
stole it. So I was just renting the bike every day.
Yeah, I called that USA the other day,
Nicola, and then um she picked up said
hello and then hung up. So,
but has it given me anxiety?
Just stressed me out to be honest.
Yeah. Go away with that now. Harry, you're boring.
Yeah. Answered and then um I just told
her to suck her mom.
You know, I haven't blocked you. But
who's a loser in the end? Me.
Cuz think about it. Everyone's gone with
their life. I'm screwy [ __ ] I'm truly
truly truly [ __ ] Cuz if you lost your
house, Yeah. So say say you lost your
house, right? Think about it like this,
J. Um um Harry. Yeah. Say you lose your house, right?
Say you lose your house. Yeah. You're um
say you lose your house or like
whatever. You you're you're theoretically homeless.
You know, when people lose their house,
when they when they lose their house, um
when they lose their house, um when
people lose their house, they are
um they're homeless. So, they have a
mental breakdown. Um but imagine losing
the house, losing the people in the
house, losing the food, and then losing
all your money basically.
And then people are telling me I'm going
to be okay. Bro, every stress in my
life, I knew I'd be okay in the end
because I knew that um cuz I knew that
like I can just get a new phone. Yeah,
it got stolen, but it'll be okay.
Everything's going to be okay.
So, but now what are you really going to
do? And then I hate people in this
country as it is. And then dealing with
the frustration as it is. So, it's
So yeah. Did I lose a gambling?
Nope. Haven't even gambled. Don't
gamble. Don't drink anymore. I haven't
had time even before all of this when
this whole Uber thing started.
So yeah, I'll probably just end up
killing myself to be honest with you,
bro. And I know most people that say it
don't don't actually do it, but I will
[ __ ] do it. I will [ __ ] do it, bro.
It's like what And man says, it's like
you don't have to just worry about women
now. You got to worry about money. Truth.
So yeah, that's basically
No, it's a little bit more than that, but
it's a little bit more than that. And I
got my TV and Xbox, so I've got and I've
got savings, but still
whoever wants it.
But I don't understand how like she
doesn't understand how serious it is.
I don't know why, bro. It's probably cuz
they deep down hate their lives. And you
know, the thing is PC with working, I
started hating people. Sorry if I'm
boring all of you people, but it made me
start hating people. It made me start
giving it is it made me start having an
opinion that I never had before. It made
me like really start disliking people. I
share the road with um
you know what I'm saying like
um and then you start hating people.
Um so yeah saying I need to get all that
[ __ ] dry cleaned.
The tenders are going to be [ __ ] They
got nowhere to go. They will be [ __ ]
which I don't really to be honest either. So
it's okay man. and someone having 20
grand in their bank, they're all right.
Doesn't bother them.
They don't care because why would an old
woman care? She, you know, she like
obviously she's lost somebody before.
I'm not going to get into it and I get
it, but I've lost [ __ ] thousands now.
Yeah, about 2,000.
Well, no one cares. So, as long as
they're okay in it, Nicola,
it's a serious serious serious serious thing.
I'm surprised I'm not I haven't had a
heart attack yet to be honest with you.
Then I need to move the TV.
And I just said to my mom, I keep saying
this. Do you remember that time you had
to move and you said you had a mental
breakdown? Do you remember that? It
happens to people. Do you remember that?
So, think of my position.
Do you understand?
Some got to [ __ ] move that TV without breaking it. So,
but no one cares as long as they're okay.
Yeah. I'll get like three grand a month.
Maybe a bit over three grand a month. So yeah,
I was living a life, bro.
I was living that damn life, bro. So yeah.
You remember people that's killed
themselves over roulette, Grezy?
Remember them people that's killed
himself over roulette?
Yeah, a lot of people's committed
suicide over it.
Bro, I wish you could actually blame
gambling, bro. That's the thing. You
don't even have any addictions as well.
Which is the whole which is the whole
[ __ ] up thing about it is you don't
even have any addictions.
Yeah, bro. And have to deal with more
and more and more and more people.
Yes, it would happen because it's got
nothing to do with people on YouTube.
People on YouTube did not make me leave
the house. I had the house for 4 years
and the Uber c and the Uber Eats. No
one. No one made me lose my account. And
I'm not saying it anymore. If you want
to keep thinking that it was people on
YouTube, then you keep thinking it was
people on YouTube. It was nothing to do
with people on YouTube. They didn't even
know I had the house still. And I'm not
explaining it anymore. Simple, bro. If
you want to think it's people on
YouTube, think it's people on YouTube.
How can they grasp on something they
don't know about?
But yeah, they are snitching on here,
which is why they don't know my business
until after things have happened. Yeah,
they are snitches. That's the only thing
that you got right there. They are
snitches. Look what they done to Monty
man in the hotel. Yeah, people guessed I
was doing Uber Eats, but they didn't
know. No one knew what I was doing. And
guess what? When I do something again,
if I ever do anything again, no one will know.
So, I'm saying like where no one would know.
So, you know what I'm saying? No, they
did. Okay. If they if they knew about
it, why did it take three years then?
Okay. Okay. Okay. Why did they do it for
three years then? Why did they do it for three years?
But I do think my mom is selfish. Like
you're telling her you've lost the whole
house and she's like, "Oh, get better.
You don't know what's around the corner. Stay positive."
I was like, "Huh? Are you right? I've
literally just told you I've lost my
whole life here and you don't give a
fuck." But then they're going to wonder
when you kill yourself. When you But the
thing is though, bro, is if you if you
kill yourself, right?
You know, like when you kill yourself,
they're going to wonder that that that's
what I'm saying, bro.
Bro, it wasn't Listen, listen. They were
on me before anyone on YouTube even
knew. They knew about it even before
this whole YouTube thing. You know what
I'm And I'm not talking about it
anymore, bro. It's nothing to do with
YouTube. I'm not talking about it
anymore. Simple. If you want to think
it's YouTube, you think it's YouTube.
No, I've still got the house until a
certain date. I've still got the house.
I'm in it. Until a certain date.
I'm just going to have to [ __ ] beat
the baiffs off and get beat the baiffs
up and get [ __ ] You know what I'm
saying, bro? Because there's no way I'm
living off that money, bro.