Thanks for the evidence, bro. Thank you
for the evidence. Thank you.
>> I'll be calling Bill tomorrow.
>> Oh, [ __ ]
[ __ ] I didn't realize it was coming
from your channel.
I'm reporting this little stalker.
I'm reporting this stalker, bro. [ __ ]
tomorrow. When I wake up, I'm over as
[ __ ] I'm reporting this little virgin.
Yeah, man. Calling the police, bro. I'm
calling old Bill.
You know what? I don't give a [ __ ] about
any of you. Yeah. Listen. Listen, listen
then. You tried to get me banned from
places. Doesn't matter that you didn't
and there's a million places in London.
You tried to get me banned from places.
[ __ ] all of you, bro. Yeah. [ __ ] the lot
of you. You have had my address for
[ __ ] years. You've had several
chances to meet me and all you do is
resort to grassing. You can [ __ ]
yourself, bro. I'm calling the old bill
tomorrow, mate. For your spoken. [ __ ] you. Yeah.
And same with you, Ricky Millinton. You
[ __ ] [ __ ] YouTube face. Little
[ __ ] Little keyboard lawyer. Get
alive. Get off of YouTube. Go get some rum down.
>> Come on, brother.
I'm in a playing [ __ ] music.
Weirdos, man. I'm calling the police
tomorrow on you, Virgin boy.
Well, I should say calling the police.
I'm actually following it all up to be
fair. You ain't got a life. You sit on
YouTube, mate, every day. You ain't got
a life. [ __ ] off it.
Come on, play some tunes, man.
Come on. Play some tunes. Play some
tunes. Play some tunes.
Play some tunes, man. Make this bad ass move. [Music]
I didn't do any more street my brother.
>> Yeah, I'm reporting you to the police
tomorrow, Virgin boy, for harassment again.
Stop [ __ ] harassing me, little
weirdo. [ __ ] virgin.
>> N there's no one here yet. Just mate,
time to send it. I'll send it [ __ ] in
about 3 hours ago. I done three
approaches and I got one number. When it
um gets more busier, there's not
anywhere else. I'll send it. I don't want
me get let there be opportunities. I'm
going to send it. What?
Got one number on the street so far. Um
on the street, got one number obviously.
Now I'm in a club waiting to
opportunities. I'm going to [ __ ] send
it, man. I'm on the white room as well.
Yeah, he's a loser. He's a [ __ ]
I'm reporting him to the police tomorrow
as well, bro. [ __ ] them, bro.
They trying me to They tried to get me
kicked out of one place. They're
stalking me. I'm pulling them again tomorrow
when I wake up over.
>> Yeah, I will send it hard when more
people come. There's no one here.
Trying to see if there I think that
Italian one's going to meet me again,
you know. Uh Steve
got one member got that Italian one and
I think she's going to meet me again to
be fair. We've been talking.
>> Yeah, man.
There's no one here yet. We'll get busy.
We'll get packed. Don't worry about it.
It'll be worse to hang over 100%. I only
got one number in the street, so
trust me, bro.
No, she's working. She's working today.
So, I can't I messaged her saying calm
down, but she's working. So,
I want to approach me. She weren't that
good-look. She had a boyfriend as well.
Mad She approached me, is it? Now, she
weren't that good, man. And she had a
boyfriend as well.
And she had a boyfriend as well.
This is where we're going.
>> Yes, she weren't that nice, man.
>> Still got approached. Oh, [ __ ]
>> But I'm I'm reporting these people
tomorrow, right? I'm reporting them
tomorrow, 100%. Stalking and harassment.
Stalking and harassment. I'll open up
the case again on this virgin ugly [ __ ]
I'm going to I'm going to I'm going to
mate. There's no one here. I want to
start sending it soon, but there's no
one here. There he is. Got a virgin opportunities.
We're going to get the virgin mad today,
bro. We're going to get the virgin mad.
That [ __ ] virgin.
That [ __ ] virgin. I'm just out on a session, bro.
He's such a virgin. Steve, he's such a
virgin. He's a [ __ ] complete virgin.
He really is. He's not going to He's not
going to spoil no madness. Trust me.
When more people come, they're getting
sent. Bro, even Howard, I'm on a
session, bro. I only got one number
and I'm free approaching. I got one
number. And I had one woman approached
me saying, "I like the track suit."
Which is why it's ideal to keep the
track two on. But
>> yeah, I'm reporting tomorrow anyways.
>> I'm reporting tomorrow. Definitely, bro.
>> Yeah. And you're and you're hyped on two
grand a month thinking that you're rich.
I know, Henry, but you're sat at home on
two grand a month talking about other
people's income. And you're under an
account called Henry. [ __ ] out of here,
bro. Thinking you're rich and you don't
even live in London. You don't even live
in London and you think you're rich.
[ __ ] hell, mate. I remember speaking
to you yesterday talking about a grand.
You don't even have a grand, you silly
skin [ __ ] You sado. I'm homeless.
Yeah, bro. I'm homeless, bro. I've got
more money than you. More money than
you, bro. If I knew, bro, listen. You
don't even get one grand a month. I've
got more money than you. Listen, I've
got thousands more than you, Skinflyn.
Think Listen, bro. Listen. You really
want to play the money game again and
lose? You're not even on a grand. You're
on £300 a month. Not even £1,000. You
shin Flynn. So what the [ __ ] are you
talking about? You don't even have a
grand load a month. Yes. Upset my
washing machine and fridge because I'm
moving house. [ __ ] Yes. Because I'm
moving house. Skinflyn who don't even
have a grand. You don't even have
£1,000, let alone a grand a month. I am
selling it because I'm moving. You
stupid northern [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah. Yeah,
I'm going to be homeless. Yeah, you
wish, bro. You're already homeless. You
get £300 a month, you little skin flint.
You sad [ __ ] You don't even have a
grab. Talking like you're rich and you
don't even live in London, bro. Remember
the word I used on here? Fantasy land. Fantasist.
You got no money. You're on benefits.
Why are you talking about money? You're
on benefits. I don't have a place, bro.
You're sat on benefits. Why are you
talking about money, bro?
Why are you talking about money when
you're literally sat on benefits? Not
even a penny to your name. Why are you
talking about money, bro? Anyways,
bye-bye [ __ ] These people ain't
stopping the madness, bro. They ain't
stopping the madness. [ __ ] off, you [ __ ] weirdo.
People must think I'm [ __ ] mad. You
people that are here. Well, I'm off this
I'm off this community again tomorrow. I
need to file this police report again
tomorrow and then I'm done.
[ __ ] I'm [ __ ] bro. Yeah, I'm I'm
literally I'm going to file this police
report, then I'm done, bro. Well, maybe
two weeks. It gets too weird too fast
with these little stalky little low
lives. So, yeah, I need to open that
report back up again. I've screenshotted
everything. So, thank you very much.
Just something to leave, bro. You know,
coverage are back. You know what I'm
saying? Only takes 10 minutes.
They got nothing in their life but an application.
Like I'm not joking. Bro, I know we
laugh at many things
and we take the piss. She looks all
right, but she's with a guy.
I've had loads of beers, loads of rum.
Hold on a minute. I'm trying to look.
Let me see. Is she with another I think
she might be with a girl or a guy.
>> Could be worth a while.
>> One second. Hold up. Let me get my
goggles on here.
I think it's a girl.
>> Oh yeah, I'm giving that a wall. [ __ ] it.
One second, bro. One sec.
I think it's a girl on it. I'm going to
give that a wall. One second. Let me
have a piss. Very can't do that. Can't
do that. Lanky cut from head can't do
that. One sec.
Give it I'll tell you when I'm going to
do it. Yeah. One sec.
Give it until 4.
441. And I'm going to do it. Then a
little drink that
these people don't even have a grand a
month. They're [ __ ] on benefits. 300
grand a month. [ __ ]
Yeah, she's nice. I'm going to give that
a Well, one sec. Once it hits 41, I'm sending it.
Hopefully, no boyfriend, please. No boyfriend. One sec.
Got 3 minutes, guys.
He's [ __ ] sexy, though. I'm sure that's a
guy. Wait a minute. Sure.
I've got a feeling I'm going to go I got
a boyfriend though, but I'll do it. One sec.
Anyone nervous? I'm not nervous at all.
I do it. I don't give a [ __ ] I'm a
crazy company. I'm a crazy [ __ ] like
that. Now I say I'm a crazy bastard.
I'm going to pause him. Do it once.
Is that all your anxiety? Hey Zippy. No
man, not me. Actually, I'm going to do
when it's 40.
I'm going to do it when it's 40. One
sec. We got one minute. You ready? I'm
going to mute this mic. I'm going to
[ __ ] go over there, bro. One sec.
Nice white ramen. One sec.
>> Virgin boy can't do this. [Applause]
All right. One minute.
nervous at all. One sec.
Let's start walking. Right.
Should we do a walk of shame? Grieves
you. The walk of shame.
I love that walk of shame. I'm doing it. One sec.
Mic. Oh, [ __ ]
She weren't having it at all at all.
She weren't having it at all at all. She
wasn't having it at all at all.
Cory, hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Crazy.
Listen, listen, listen. [Laughter]
She wasn't having it at all at all.
Right. So, like I I say she was No, no,
no. You have to do this, right? Yeah.
So, I'm going to say she wasn't having
it at all. And you have to say at all.
She weren't having it at all. That's all
eight. Trust me. But I'm the one that
can't commit apparently. We're all good.
We're having a nice drink. We're chilling.
Um, she didn't really say much. She just
said she's not really interested.
Basically, same old England, right? But
we got one number anyways. We're going
to get more numbers. You weren't having
it at all at all. I've only got one number.
These drinks are two pound. What you
have to lose, bro. Story of your life,
Harry. You're always going to be single,
man. Story of your life.
She weren't even that nice. I don't know
why, done her.
At least she didn't say she had a
boyfriend. I mean, I'm sure not he yet.
Don't speak too soon.
But yeah, listen. What I'm saying,
Grezy, is you speak about people not
being able to commit and people. I just
went and spoke to someone and they
didn't even give me a chance. Do I care?
No, not really. But I mean, it's an it's
an example is what I'm trying to say.
Like you're saying that I'm scared to
commit to one person. I've just gone
over and spoke to someone and they
weren't having it at all at all. No, no,
I care. I'm drinking, bro. I'm I'm cool,
bro. But I'm It's obviously again still
point. I'm sending it. I done four
approaches. I got one number, but at
least at least I've not got I've got a
boyfriend. I've not got that yet. And
Nicolo, I had one woman approach me
today. So, I mean, that's the start to something good.
But this will be me for the month, I reckon. But
yeah, that's the point I'm trying to
make that they don't even give you a
chance. But we're drinking anyways.
We're having fun anyways. But again,
it's still that thing we have to remember. But
not a problem, bro.
>> Yeah, man. I'm fat.
Yes, I did. Son, don't worry. The night
is still long, bro. She ain't She
weren't even that good, but she was all
right enough. But yeah.
>> So, do you understand what I'm saying
now, Grezy? Grezy, do you understand
what I'm saying?
It's not a big deal cuz we're out drinking anyways.
Like, it doesn't matter because we're
we're having fun, is it? But I'm saying
like, do you understand now? Well, I I
you hear it, but she weren't having at
all at all. do whatever that all moment
when someone else is here I'll send it
they ain't interested in this country s
thank you Tik Tok
we don't care anyways we're having fun
man I like this quite Boom. Hold on.
How much did I lost?
10 million. Oh, [ __ ]
That's me. on for a month, bro.
But yeah, like this is what I'm saying,
bro. Like, you get all of these people
on the internet, they give false advice
off after false advice after false
advice, you know, like, yeah, I will do, bro.
Thank you. More evidence for the police.
Thank you, Virgin boy.
I'm calling the police tomorrow before I
come off for two weeks. Thank you.
Police is being called tomorrow. Virgin
boy, you might want to stay tuned today
cuz there's loads of approaches that's
going to be had. So many of them, mate.
So many of them.
Your anxiety will never allow you to do it, mate.
But honestly, yeah, it's [ __ ] up, bro.
So, it's not all what you hear on the
internet. You understand, Reevesy? It's
not what you hear on the internet. You understand, bro? [Applause]
two number one number. Sorry.
>> Yeah, man.
>> Yeah, we will do when more people come.
I just done one. I just done one, bro.
I'll do one more. I'll do another one
when more people come. It's all right, though.
She didn't even know how to talk, mate.
She was so scared. I went up and spoke
to her. She's like, "Uh, I'm not really interested."
Um, she didn't really know what to say,
to be honest. And you know where that
comes from, Grezy. It comes from Tik
Tok. It comes from Instagram.
Where people are so relying on these
apps, they don't know how to socialize.
They were [ __ ] scared, bro. They
don't know how to socialize because of
social media, which is similar to what I
was saying earlier. But it doesn't
matter, bro. Send it to
Am I lying, tell me I'm lying.
Tell me I'm lying, bro.
One second, bro. I'm [ __ ] [Laughter]
Yeah. Really? Is that why I've not got
I've got a boyfriend yet, Grezy? Is that
why I got approached and I've got one number?
Is that why, Grezy?
This hangover is going to be so wild tomorrow.
But I don't give a [ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] mate.
Yeah, it makes it stronger. The ice
makes it stronger, too.
>> Yeah, I'm reporting this country to the
piece tomorrow as well.
Yeah, stalking and [ __ ] mate. I'm doing
it tomorrow, bro. 100%. I ain't done it
for like 3 weeks.
Oh, [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, some I need to get another drink.
>> I sure did. Oh, I did. I had that
burger, didn't I?
I'm better than slug. Everyone's better
than slug. You can
I need to get a drink, mate.
There are people nowadays, they don't
even know how to socialize, man. What
the [ __ ] is going on?
Need some more. I need some more run.
I'm going to get a double.
Can I get a double right on my please?
It's going to kill me just [Music] as well.
It's going to get really messy.
But we're not on We're not skin like
Virgin Boy, are we?
>> No. Wasn't having it at all.
Thank you. Well, I want a store.
Yeah. No, they weren't having it at all.
Crazy at all at all.
They weren't over there at all at all.
I really like don't really like [ __ ]
Oh, I love it, mate. I love it. I got
the Roman. Oh, man. I got a double Roman time.
See, I would take non I would I would
take non legs with me, but he will scare
them all away with his ugly face. I mean,
scared him away with his ugly face with
his ugly face.
I'm saying I don't want him to scare
them away with his ugly with their ugly
with his ugly face.
And I can smell a virgin from the mile off.
[ __ ] hell. Why is a straw gun in a drink? [ __ ] bro.
They weren't having it at all at all.
Not at all at all. Oh, strong, bro.
[ __ ] [ __ ] strong [ __ ] [Music]
I need to go soon, man. I got some
approaches to do and [ __ ] Sorry. I need
to go soon, man.
I'll be back in like [ __ ] 3 hours or something.
Imagine that Grimsy that virginity mate
has been haunting him for 31 years. That virginity
and I don't care about a [ __ ] fat
wolf. He is literally a virgin. He
literally is. And I'll say I'll say it
in front of it. I'll say it. I will say
it in front of everyone, bro. He's a
[ __ ] virgin. He's the biggest virgin
going. You love that, don't you, Greasy?
He's a proper virgin.
[ __ ] off, you virgin. Go get laid, you stupid virgin.
Go away, you [ __ ] virgin [ __ ] Go and
go and masturbate over USA, mate.
All cuz I had no booby lungs.
What are you jealous? All because I had
a All cuz I had a booby lungs.
You know what I'm saying?
You're such a virgin. I just [ __ ] up
the drink, bro.
It's better now.
You know all about virgins. You are one yourself.
Yeah. I'm calling the police tomorrow,
bro. Don't worry.
I'm opening the case back up tomorrow, bro.
>> I'm opening the case back up tomorrow,
bro. Don't worry about that. Why is no
one here, man? Yeah, it's cuz he's a
virgin. He doesn't want anyone getting
laid because he's a big virgin. Listen,
bro. Do not follow tracks.
>> Yeah, he'd get hurt, would he? Yeah,
Harry. Yeah, man. That's why when I when
I come up to Liverpool, you all shut
your mouth and you all went quiet in it.
Yeah, I know you love my reaction, but
it Yeah, he'd get hurt by Casper the
ghost, bro. That's why when I came to
Liverpool, you all shut out, would it?
Huh? I know we love each other, bro. It
shut up, bro. You would do [ __ ] And the
thing is, Harry, you know that he's a
grass and you're still talking like
that. Like, he's a known grass and
you're still talking about people
getting hurt and him getting hurt. Bro,
he's a grass.
Like he is literally a grass and you're
still talking like that. You ain't from
the hood, bro. You're not about that
life, bro. Listen, you know that he's a
certified grass and you you Anyone know
Everyone knows that. No one would go on
to where you're going, bro. He's a He's
literally a grass. I hurt by who? He's a
He's a grass. He's a big grass.
All right. [ __ ] What's that?
>> Yeah. Okay, Harry, you keep telling
yourself that, mate. I am [ __ ] lazy,
bro. I'm lit, bro. [Music]
I am [ __ ] lit, bro. I'm not even
joking. I am [ __ ] bro.
I am I am [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] Imagine we
actually went out all night today. We
would be [ __ ] bro.
We're staying here, bro.
Stay in there, Mike.
You weren't having it at all at all,
Grezy. Why did that make you laugh? You
think me getting rejected is a laugh.
Why do you think that's funny, bro? It's not funny.
It won't happen at all at all. You were
the first one to laugh, is it? Don't
worry, mate. We'll get some more people later.
We'll go on the street as well. [Music]
Yeah, I'm drinking. I'm [ __ ] [ __ ]
I'm drinking. I'm [ __ ] wavy.
I'm [ __ ] wavy, bro.
Oh, you're making a lot of noise.
I agree. I'm fat.
I'm really [ __ ] bro.
Oh, there's some more people that's come. Okay,
give it a while. One second. Listen,
lads. I really need to go. Yeah,
we need to get to scrap Grezy before
them fish head [ __ ]
Grezy. We need to get to [ __ ] for
them fish head [ __ ] One second.
You need to literally get to scrap
before them fish head [ __ ]
Is that right, Grezy? Before them fish head [ __ ]
Waiting for some people to come in.
>> Listen, I'm out of here. Yeah, I'll be
back later with some live cold
approaches. I'll be back with some live cold approaches.
Be about a couple of hours. Yeah, don't
worry about that, bro.
I'll be back here in a couple of hours.
>> Yeah, man. But I can't stay on because
of my battery and [ __ ] I'll come back,
bro. 100%. You got my word. 2 hours, 3
hours, I'm back.
Make the virgin jealous.