[ __ ] get up there, son. B, get up.
Come on, God.
>> There we go, son.
Them [ __ ] were laughing at us. [ __ ]
that m [ __ ] making a mug out of me, bro.
[ __ ] that, mate. Okay.
Yeah, I've had enough, mate. I was going
to [ __ ] him up, man. Yeah, grievy.
Griezy. Them thugs were laughing at us.
I said, "You can't even grow a beard,
you fat belly bastard." I got a video,
mate. I'll put it up. I told him to come
around the corner. Come on. Come on, big
man. [ __ ] stupid little stimp
[ __ ] [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
There's a way about things, bro. You do
not own the country, mate. Do your job
properly and be a normal citizen. Don't
scare me, bro. None of you scare me,
bro. No one ever has
me. [ __ ] that one.
He ain't about it. He ain't about that lie.
about that life, mate.
>> This country will never change. Green Z,
what I learned from tonight, I mean,
I've got one number so far. I'm going to
get more on the street, but what I've
learned is this country will never ever ever change.
Never change this country. Never. the
people, the women, the [ __ ] Mate, listen.
I think be fair, bro.
I was very in denial for many years.
Didn't like by that I mean I was very in
denial thinking that I would never end
up in Asia or even some other country
other than England. Like I was very in
denial. Do you know what I'm saying? But
it is what it is, bro. Like this is but
like this the whole way the country
works. But I done nothing wrong, bro. I
tried speaking to three people. When
they said no, I just moved on. I carried
on drinking cuz I expected it. I didn't
cause no problems until the guy come up
to me and start thinking that he [ __ ]
rules the whole [ __ ] place. Know what I'm saying?
And then he shot his pants. Another one.
He would run to the police, bro. He
would literally run to the police.
That's the kind of guy there that he
would run to old Bill. I'm telling you,
bro. I'm telling you. He's the type,
He tried to get his camera out. I'll get
my [ __ ] camera out.
[ __ ] idiot, bro. Ain't about that.
Come on, man. Stay in this. Stay in the
stay in the in the in establishment.
Okay. Ghosted. Yeah. Listen, bro. So, I
was in a place. No, bro. I was in a
place for like an hour and a half, maybe
two hours. Yeah. I approached three
people. I done nothing wrong. I wasn't
acting weird. I was speaking to some
people that was talking to me. normal
chat. Whatever. Yeah. The bouncer comes
up to me. [ __ ] And I thought, "Okay,
I'm wearing tracksuit bombs. He's going
to give me sick." Whatever. Yeah. I'm
trying on walk with him. He starts
giving attitude. Yeah. He's like, "Oh,
yeah. We've had complaints that you've
been speaking to people." I mean, I
mean, yeah, it's a nightclub. What do
you expect? I was speaking to people
normally. Some people come up to me and
they started conversation. Yeah. I said,
"At the end of the day, you shouldn't be
letting people in your clubs if they
don't want people talking to them." And
he started saying I was like, "Oh, don't
give me attitude." I said, "I'll give
you attitude when I want." Yeah. Well,
you you ain't got you ain't the boss of
me, bro. Yeah. He tried [ __ ]
snatching the drink out of me. Yeah. The
drink went everywhere. I said, "Listen,
[ __ ] Come around the corner. Come
around the corner." I was slating his
race, his culture, his belly. He would
not come around the corner, bro. He
would not leave them cameras. Yeah.
Yeah. All for talking to three people,
bro. And I weren't even drunk. I was
like 20% drunk. So I was like, "Bro,
what does this country really come to?
You can't even speak to people nowadays
without it being a problem." But he
didn't say, "Oh, come back later or
stop." Like, he was a proper [ __ ]
And I was like, "Bro, you don't rule
this country. You do not rule this
place. You're not talking to me like that, though."
I don't know, bro. I don't know. But
it's like, bro, you know how bad this is
getting? You can't even speak to people
now. It's got to point you can't even
barely speak to anyone now. It's like it
seems to be some crime. Bro, I'm out of
this country again. Ghost, bro, that
that that that dictates it, bro. I'm out
again, bro. I'm leaving again, bro. [ __ ]
this. This is not no normal way of
living, bro. Bro, listen to me. Yeah, it
happened about maybe an hour, no, 40
minutes ago, bro. I was like, I am not
doing this again. I am out of here,
Limple. I'm not doing this [ __ ] again,
bro. I was telling the guy to come
around the corner time and time and time
again. I'm out of this country, bro. I'm
leaving. Like, bro, I didn't care about
the people that said no. I was enjoying
my drink. I wasn't causing any problems.
I wasn't swearing at anyone. He thinks
he could come over and start being
abusive. And then when he I told him to
come around the corner, he wouldn't come
around the corner.
Nah, I'm not going out. I'm leaving this
country, bro. Again, [ __ ] this. In one
month, I'm leaving again. I'm I'm gone
again in a month, bro. [ __ ] this.
Nah, it's not loads of places. Loads of
places with loads of [ __ ] I'm
leaving again in a month, bro. [ __ ] it.
I'm going to find something and I'm
leaving again, bro. [ __ ] this [ __ ] I'm leaving again.
I'm gonna do today. I'm gonna do tomorrow.
Um cuz obviously tomorrow's Saturday.
I'm leaving. I'm leaving the country
again. I can't deal with this, bro.
I don't care about the bounces. I'm not
scared of them. And guess what, bro?
Even if he did, I would go back with a
hammer and smash his head in. You don't
know me, bro. I don't care if they can
handle themselves. I would go back and
smash his head in with a hammer. Even if
he put me in No, listen. Let me tell you
this. Yeah. When I stand my ground, I
stand my ground. I don't give a [ __ ] I
will smash his Polish head in with a
hammer. With a back of a hammer. I don't
care. Yeah. I'm not saying I can beat
him face to face or whatever. I don't
know that. But I'm saying even if he
beat me, I would smash his head in with
a hammer. Bro, you don't know my temper.
Please. Like, you don't understand. I
don't care about some Polish pig. Even
if I ended up in an ambulance. Yeah.
Even if I ended up in an ambulance, I
will get the back and I'll smash his
head in. You don't know me, boss. Please
stop it. Yeah. No, he didn't throw me
out. No, no, no. He asked me to leave
and I said, "I'm going to finish my
drink." I said, "I'm going to finish my
drink." Okay, let me finish my drink.
And then he's like, "Oh, don't give me
attitude." I said, "I'll give you
attitude when I want. You don't control
me. You're a bouncer." He tried. He
tried pulling the drink away from me. I
pulled it back. I said, "Don't [ __ ]
put your hands on me, you silly cunt."
Yeah. I said, "Come around the corner,
Polish." He would not have none of it,
mate. But he was not a Wait, bro. I told
the guy, "Come around the corner, Polish
pig with a fat belly and a silly
haircut, and he would not do it. I I
even tried going towards him, toward
him, toward him. [ __ ] stupid Polish
cunt." You understand? Yeah.
You [ __ ] Polish. That's what I said
to him. Come out the corner, big man.
Come on. You're supposed to be You're
supposed to be argumentative and fight.
Come on. I'll [ __ ] you up real life.
Come on. I will [ __ ] you up real life.
[ __ ] old, bro. Yeah. You're supposed to
do your job properly and not give
attitude. He won't have a none of it.
[ __ ] Polish bake.
I was there for about 5 minutes. I said
you [ __ ] fat belly Polish. He might
have done a bit. He had he fake laughed
the whole time. [ __ ] [ __ ]
He would sit on me and guess what? I
will go back and smash his head with a
hammer. Yeah. I don't know who it was,
bro. And and he wasn't even all right
about it, bro. He was trying to be a
[ __ ] about it. I said, I'll go and smash
his head in with a hammer. If he put me
in hospital, say he put me in hospital.
Well, I done nothing. I told a guy to
come around the corner. He done nothing.
You [ __ ] Polish [ __ ] That's what I
said to him. Yeah. Nothing but a Polish
[ __ ] And then he laughed. He would have
come around the corner. See how London
they would actually come out the corner.
Yeah, you would come out the corner. You
[ __ ] Polish. That's why I said to
Yeah. Listen, bro. That's it. I did
video it. I did video it, bro. I did
video it. No, it was somewhere else, bro.
And I'm not saying I would have him. I'm
not saying that I could beat him. I'm
not saying that. I don't [ __ ] know.
He could probably knock me out. But But
let me tell you something. I'm coming
back with ammo.
off. Yeah, man.
It's not Yeah, it doesn't matter, bro.
It's not a big deal. It's not a big deal, bro.
But listen, Ghosting, I'm not I'm not
I'm not Hulk Hogan, bro. I can't beat
everyone. I'm not saying I can beat
everyone, bro. I'm not Hulk Hogan. I
don't know who I could have beaten, but
just know if I lost, I'm going back.
Just know that if I lost, I'm going
back. And I was smashing him in that
face with a hammer. Trust me, bro. You
do not know me, right? Trust me. I'm not
saying I can win. I don't know who I
could be, but I know I'll get the last
laugh. Trust me, you don't know me. But
anyways, moving on from this [ __ ]
Anyways, we're moving on now.
I'm out of here in a month.
>> Yeah, I'm out of here, bro. I'm
literally done in I'm going out of this
country again in a month, bro. Like,
bro, listen. Like, listen, bro. All
jokes aside, like, no shouting out.
Yeah, ghost. Listen, bro. Like, all we
all calm down. Like, I spoke to three
people in the space of 3 hours. Yeah.
Trying to get to know people. I weren't
being rude to anyone. I weren't being
inappropriate. I weren't even drunk. I
was like slightly tipsy. And then it's
like, bro, like, think of it, bro. If
you can't even speak to someone. Yeah.
I've got money. I've got savings. I
don't need to save. Think about it, bro.
Like, what has this country really come
to? It's going to come to a point now.
Yeah, bro. Where it's frowned upon to
even speak to people. It's [ __ ] bro.
It's It's bro.
This country will never change. They
will never change, bro.
>> Yeah, bro. It wasn't groups. There were
two people. Like, bro, no, no, no, no.
They weren't groups. There were two
people. Like, there were two people,
bro. Like, it was a club. It wasn't even
a pub. And there were two people. There
weren't three or four cuz they're
groups. There were people in twos. You
know, if you can't even speak to someone
nowadays, this country has got even more
bigger problems than we thought. It was
a club but a park.
Um, what I say to them, um,
I said, "Oh, I thought you look nice. I
thought I'd come and say hi. What's your
name?" Just talking to them, trying to
get to know them. And they didn't really
say much. And I just moved on to next
one. I chilled out. Mate, I didn't even
say anything bad.
No, I wasn't weirding them out at all.
Not in the slightest was I weirding him
out. Stop being a s. I was not weirding
him out in the slightest.
The thing is ghosting, bro. Listen,
the problem is Oh, [ __ ] The problem is
is there's too many stuck up [ __ ] in
this country now. The thing is so many
people are in denial about it. I don't
care. I know what it is. I went out for
a drink anyways. I'm still out. It's not
a problem. This is the cold half truth
of it. People don't want to admit it.
That's on them. I don't care. There's
too many stuck up [ __ ] in this
country. That's literally the problem.
There's nothing else. You know, I had a
black guy coming over speaking to me.
We're talking whatever. There's too many
stuck up [ __ ] in your country. That's
what somebody said to me before. That's
what it is. Like it's the people in this country.
So yeah, I just was trying to get to
know them and they weren't having none
of it at all at all. Which is fine. I
just moved on. But wait, hold on. You
get kicked out for trying to start
conversations with people. Bro, this
country ain't normal, bro. I'm telling
you, bro. In a million, bro. This
country is not normal. Gamble. I'm not
going to gamble. I don't need to gamble,
bro. I don't gamble anymore. This
country is not normal. I don't know what
normal is. I'm not going to claim what
normal is. This country ain't normal,
bro. Bro, I'm telling you ain't normal.
Like if I had done a video right now,
well, tomorrow when I'm not as like hung over
this guy, it's it's this country ain't
normal. Like we go to places trying to
speak someone. You know what I'm saying? Like
it's not normal, bro. You're going
you're trying to speak to people. You're
trying to get to know people. If people
don't want to know, that's fine. But to
grasp your bouncer for no reason. Yeah.
And and then the B's giving me like it's
a madness. What the [ __ ]
It's really bad. [ __ ] I will have to go
on the street soon and do some approaches.
>> Yeah. Easy, bro. Very easy. Easy going.
But after now, I'm just going to get an
escort at the end of the day. I'm just
going to get an escort. At the end of
the day today, I'm just going to get an escort.
Was it busy? It was getting busy. Yeah.
Then I'll probably do it again to photo
and then I'm gone in a month. So trying
for the gym that I paid for, bro. Yeah.
Like let's leave it for now. Let's leave
it for now, bro.
Cuz I I don't want to chill. You know
what I mean? It's too hot, bro. Allow
it. There's no one in this cup. Listen.
>> Yeah, it's too hot, bro. I'm just
drinking this Guinness. I'm not even
drunk to the point.
leaving in a month, bro. So, it's up to
you, bro. I got one number so far, but
>> I sold Adman in. So, yeah, [ __ ] him.
Anyways, but you can't even speak to people nowadays. [ __ ]
>> What is life, bro? This it's like what
Antman said. He left England for a better life.
>> He left England legitimately for a better life,
you know? And I was a ner for all them
years thinking that I wouldn't end up
there to be honest with you. Like, you
leave for a better life. This ain't no
life in England, you know? It sounds
funny and like, no, it's not, bro. It's
not spoiling my night, bro. I'm I'm I'm
chilling, bro. I'm drinking. It's what
it is, bro. But the country is [ __ ]
It is literally gone shambles.
I don't know.
I'm going to do some approaches on the street soon.
So yeah, I'm going to end this live
stream. I'm going to do some approaches
on the street and then yeah, see where
where I go. I'll be back live when I'm
back home. So yeah, I'll be out soon.
But yeah, it won't even him, bro. It's
the whole thing. It's the whole all of
it, bro. It's [ __ ] up. [Music]
>> Nah, it's got nothing to do with mindset
and personality. That means nothing,
mate. Anyways, I'm done, bro.
Anyways, [ __ ] him. [ __ ] that, bro. It's
irrelevant. Yeah, I'm going to go. I'll
be back later. I'll come back with how
many numbers I got or whatever. So, I'll
be back, bro. Later. Peace. See you later. Yeah.