Yo, we go.
This country is finished delayed.
Oh, is that your name.
Is that your name, Zippy?
She's from his island, mate. That's
where she's [ __ ] from,
bro. This country
is [ __ ] Give me my nugget.
Give me my chicken nuggets.
[ __ ] chicken nuggets, bro. [ __ ]
[ __ ] bro. What is that?
Oh, what's to do, bro?
It is a madness. E
[ __ ] really [ __ ]
What is this? This country has well and
truly gone to the shambles.
To the [ __ ] shambles. Oh [ __ ] I need
to repeat. I need to um report that
virgin today, don't I?
Report that virgin today as well. [ __ ]
Where the [ __ ] is that?
Got a banging headache. I'm going to I'm
in for a nasty hangover.
Nasty hang over, bro. Yeah.
Stink one, bro. [ __ ] [Music] Oh,
never know when you fall in BS deep. [Music] Nope.
that [ __ ] you know you can bro I just
got back just banged an esco I ain't had
sex in like a year cuz obviously I'm
just a whole [ __ ] and [ __ ] so
this country is finished bro got three
numbers I think but this country
and truly finished
What the bro? This country is well and
truly truly finished.
I need to I'll do a video on it when I
cover it, bro. When I actually have
time, but it is really really really it
gets worse and worse and worse this
country, bro. But I got
I had sex the first time of the year cuz
I don't really have sex. Just get the [ __ ]
But so just got just [ __ ] the [ __ ] So yeah,
I'm out of here in about a month anyways, bro.
I'm out of this country. So uh
mate, it won't be mine. Um 14 minutes.
Yeah, I've got some numbers. Three
I'm speaking because a woman from New
Zealand from before for about half an
hour, you know, it's actually good
actually um speak to people.
It's hard to get conversation out of
people nowadays and yeah, she might have
had freckles and no, but I was speaking
to somebody on the train back, these
these two people from Essex. They're
elderly, not elderly women, but maybe
30s, maybe late 30s. We was just talking
about how [ __ ] up this whole country
is. Um, what was going on and the
entitled people and I was speaking to
some guy that's got kids and we
basically saying how there's no discipline nowadays.
Um, we just get I was getting some deep
conversations with probably about three
people. They weren't very long, but this
country is definitely finished. It 100%
is done, bro.
Yeah, it's a sad sad depressing place to
be. In a depressing place to be.
>> You can leave though.
[ __ ] up. I'm [ __ ]
What are you talking about, bro? What
the [ __ ] you about?
The escort. She She didn't want anyone
coming in my mouth, so I thought [ __ ]
it. I ain't [ __ ] for like a year anyway.
So, who cares?
But yeah, this country really finished.
Truly truly truly finished. Um,
you need to leave, bro. It's simple. I
got a month, I think, and I'm out of here, bro. Um,
see, like, I was having deep
conversations, right? And this guy, the
manager was trying to get into my head,
but at the end of the day, like you got
to understand, these people don't know
what you've been through. They don't understand
half of it. So, I mean, you know, for
these people to give advice,
um the the whole country's [ __ ] I
mean, bro, like you can barely even
speak to people in a in a nightclub. And
no one complained.
Um no one complained.
It's finished cuz the women are all
stuck up. The people are entitled. The
people do not let get do not let people
get on with their [ __ ] lives. I hate
England. I hate being a part of
um this country. I hate everything about
this country, bro. Um
the women are the worst thing, but
there's different things as well. Like
even when people are trying to get on
with their lives,
um they're not allowed to. So I'll do a
video on this. I got to do a video on this, bro.
Um, it's [ __ ] up, bro. Yeah, man.
No one complain about anything, bro.
People sat down drinking their drink.
So, you can't even speak to people in
your own country in a [ __ ] social,
you know. What can you do now, mate?
how that's that's sort of come out and
you know and and sort of whatot
you got no chance in this country but
anyways that was me done for the month I
think I got enough numbers anyway so I
won't go out again tomorrow but yeah good old Never.
It's a sad sad place to be, bro. Like
what Antman said, you can keep living in
the past, but I won't be.
So you can keep living in the past. I
won't be, bro.
I get the manager's point. I get the
pub's manager's point. Um, and and you
know, it might come across I'm being
awkward and I'm being difficult, but you
need to really look outwards. It's not
inwards. It really, really, really is
outwards. You know, think of this
problem, right? If somebody doesn't even
need to go to Asia before they've even
gone to Asia and they notice a
difference in their own country with
these people, bro, it's it's very very much outwards,
you know, like we're scared to, you
know, you might be scared to say these
things for whatever reason, but it is
definitely definitely definitely really
really really is outwards. Like even
even even the [ __ ] the most like you
can't even speak to people in in your
own country, bro. What what is that type [ __ ] bro?
This country gets worse. You got [ __ ]
9year-old kids trying to [ __ ] steal bikes nowadays.
It is a sad country here in England,
bro. Sad life here in England. I feel
sorry for anyone in England, bro. Especially London.
You're not living here. You're you're existent
in every single way. Yeah, bro.
And then I'll be back later. I might
make a video tomorrow. I don't know,
bro. I don't know what I'm doing. Yeah, bro.
Got a nasty headache last night. See you
tomorrow, man. Peace out.