That's me for a month.
Oh, I thought as well yesterday. Unless
Unless it just starts capping up on me,
then I'm [ __ ]
Yeah, I I said I was going to go out
again say, but I'm not going to get some
more numbers today. I'm supposed
to report that [ __ ] virgin rap virgin.
Sorry, we had to do that
ugly bastard. Sorry about that.
I'm probably going to eat this and
probably going to be fat. But
um I need to
thank you basically. It's fine. Oh my
Yeah, I'm sending it again to there.
This basically where I can I can go now.
I mean, you never thought it'd come to
the point where you can't even speak to
people in your own country. It's a
madness in in a club, mind you, in a
bar. I can't get over that.
This country just gets worse and worse
and worse. I'll be happy when I'm out of it again.
Be honest with you.
I can't wait to get out of this country [Music] again. Yeah,
to me I can't wear track ones. No, you
haven't left YouTube. You're still on
YouTube. Yeah, we know you haven't left
YouTube, bro. Listen,
I've been off of YouTube for a week, two
weeks, 3 weeks, a month. You can't get
you you come on it every day. You can't
take a day off of YouTube. Practice what you preach.
I am leaving YouTube to be fair. I don't
come on here much since I've just been
addicted to going live lately.
And I realize how spasticated it is and
how you people just never stop. You just
never leave people alone, which is one
of the reasons why I don't come on it anymore. Um,
so yeah, you just never leave people
alone as well. You just never ever stop,
do you? It's It's sad. It really is sad, bro.
You can barely even carry the [ __ ] Hey,
bro. You good? Yeah. I'm going to be out
again today cuz that'll be me done for the month.
Um, yeah. So, I'll be out again today. I
got three numbers.
I was speaking to this woman from New
for about half an hour. It's so nice
when you can actually get a conversation
out of someone.
Feels like you're not in the right day
and age. You know what I'm saying?
Going to catch up all these things.
I'm not even Do you know what the thing
is? I'm not even hung over
at all. I told
must be the FL or something but I'm not
hung over Nick.
I'm saying that but it probably will
just catch off on me in like 2 hours. But
imagine that you get banned in your own
country for speaking to people in a in a
club. Only approach three people in a
space of 2 hours.
It's madness, bro. I can't believe that.
That is That is insane.
You can't even speak to people in I just
went back pubs, which is probably what
I'm going to do today. I'm probably just
going to pub call cuz
I think it's cheeky, right? Them trying
to tell you that you can't wear traction
bottoms when you're paying their prices.
Yeah, it does happen. But it's not normal.
And no one complained either because
everyone sat on the same chair
and yeah, it's
and the bands were like, "Oh yeah, if
you give me attitude, I'm going to take
the drink out of your hand." I was like,
"You're not going to take no [ __ ]
drink out of my [ __ ] hand. I don't
know who the [ __ ] you think you are."
Then he tried and the drink went
everywhere. The guy was trying to put it
back. He made a scene. I told him to
come around the corner numerous times.
He would not come around the corner. Um, typical [ __ ]
cuz they can't do that stuff in London,
you see, because they lose their badge.
They can lose their which I'm not saying
I could beat him. See, I'd say the same
stuff drunk when I'm sober. I'm not
saying I could beat I don't [ __ ] know
this person, but I know I'd get the last laugh
cuz he would not be working there
anymore, bro. Trust me,
>> I would wait. Yeah. I would literally,
you know what I would do? I would wait
until like 9 10:00 at night. say like he
beat me and I would smash his face in
front of everyone, bro. The most
cowardly way possible. Like, trust me, bro. Yeah.
Not saying that I would win. I don't
[ __ ] know, but thank you, boss.
Got some nice piggies.
I've got some nice piggies to eat.
Oh, you can't beat some nice piggies.
I won't be able to afford to go out anyways anymore.
I'm not dipping into my savings, you see.
So, I don't want to spend savings, go
out. Obviously, if I get a date in that,
it's a different story. I'll go out. But
in terms of that, if I don't get a date
or anything, I'm not wasting money in
this country no more. So, it is
Yeah, you need to apply that comment to
yourself, but still haven't left
YouTube. You're on YouTube every day. Self injector,
man. Load up.
Cory, I said to this guy, I said, "Do
you know what chopper means?" He said,
"It means rammed." I said, "Yeah, but I
said, do you know what it's short for?"
And he said, um, he said, "Shock block."
[ __ ] a block.
I love piggies.
I made some new friends yesterday.
I was speaking to these two women on the
train ride. There must have been about 37
and we was just talking the whole train
ride about how this country is and how
entitled people are in London and
so nice when you can get it weren't like
a romantic thing. It's just nice when
you can actually get a conversation out of someone
other than I've got a boyfriend. It's lovely.
We were just talking about um
yeah, there must have been 30s, late
30s, maybe 40 maybe. So nice. Mhm.
There'll be no live stream today cuz
yesterday I just wanted to show you. But
now I want to actually enjoy myself today.
And yet people try bringing up clubs and [ __ ]
which I don't think is coming from Lord
J side. It's obviously the Virgin doing
it. Um cuz
people watch me all the time in pubs and
then no one no one does it. I think it's
it comes from the diversion side.
Redstone that base
I don't know why he would do that.
But I was going to help him try to lose
his virginity so he would shut me in a
virgin and he's trying to get to places.
been trying to get me out of places.
I just want to help him stop being
that's the I [ __ ] get the car this puck. Yes,
I love the juice. [Music] Not this. Let's do this.
Oh, I banged yesterday which is the
first time in about
I thought the last time I banged maybe
seven months ago
seven months ago.
I admit it. I don't pretend I'm a
virgin. I don't pretend I'm not a virgin
at 31. I just told you I had sex in six
months from yesterday. Oh, lovely.
Yeah. You know why there's no phone
balls with virgin boy sleeping? Um so
um yeah basically
I can handle my drink. I don't go around
like pulling over and
you know I've had too much to drink or whatot because
never never have I knew I weren't too
drunk yesterday. I knew I weren't
maybe a bit high on life
and obviously not about his fault. I
mean someone said something to him but
you're not [ __ ] talking to me like
that. I don't care who you are, how big
you are. You're not [ __ ] talking to
me like that.
There was I think it's more the whole concept but
there's establishments where they sell
alcohol in in in
hopes to meet people. You try to meet people,
you don't take them out. So
the country just don't make sense.
There must be three bas.
>> You must be.
Please don't cut when we lay off. I'm
>> trying to think how alcohol affects me.
I think it affects me where I just say the truth.
I just think the real me comes out. Cuz
I know exactly what I do when I'm drunk.
Don't fall over. I don't do anything.
Well, I do drunk. No way.
Good old Scotland. Good old Scotland. [Music]
I'm actually tired now.
I forgot how it effect.
I'll be out with this.
There he is. [Music] I'm done. >> Don't
So, it's just like