No,
you know, I said I was going to go live
for a little bit, but
just waiting for my uh dinner to be cooked.
Waiting for my dinner to be cooked.
Dana Dana Dana.
[ __ ] hell, man.
Come on, Franklin. Turn the [ __ ] car around, mate.
Oh [ __ ] wrong [ __ ] one.
That's the left there.
What a [ __ ] human, man. Dead. Turn around.
So anyways, yeah, let me ask this question.
Why do you people come on here every day
talking about yourselves?
And when are you going to stop coming on
YouTube every day talking about yourselves?
I think it's a good question to be fair.
Where are you going to stop
coming on YouTube every day
backing talking about yourselves? Seriously,
like you come on here, right, and
you talk about people's lives, but you
don't know about anyone's lives. But
I'll tell you what I'm eating today.
I'm eating £23 worth of lamb.
Lamb, the most expensive meat.
But apparently I'm skin, mate. You
people are skin. That's why you're on
YouTube every day.
23 pounds worth of lamb. That's what I'm eating.
It's been cooked nicely. And I got a
nice Ben & Jerry's ice cream. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Yeah. You But guess what?
But guess what? I can take a day off of
YouTube. You people can't.
Yeah. That's That's something that I can
say safely that you people can't take a
day off of YouTube. Not even one single day.
Isn't that madness how you can't even
take one day off of YouTube?
Imagine how sad that is. Like not even one day.
Not even one day off of YouTube because
it's all you have in your skit lives.
Imagine that. No, I couldn't imagine it.
Not even one day. Not even one day
says a lot about your lives. Really does.
I think most of you people on £300 a month.
I generally generally think that you pe
a lot of you people on £300 a month
cuz it doesn't it doesn't add up.
Nothing adds up, bro.
I'm just chilling playing GTA, man. I
got some lamb cooking. I can't wait to
yam it down with some nice Ben and
Jerry's ice cream.
So anyway, you're gone.
Um, no, they are disabled, but the
government just doesn't want to give
them pit. But they're definitely
definitely on 300 pound a month because
like I keep saying, I don't want to
sound like a repeater here, but if these
people are not skin and they've got all
this money, they wouldn't be on here every day,
you know, hating every day. It just
doesn't add up, but none of it adds up
at all. So, I'm having a nice lamb and
some nice Ben & Jerry's ice cream.
Greasy. Fresh start Monday. I'm going to
go gym for a whole month. No drinking.
Look how much money I'm going to save in that month.
I got a lot saved for six uh six weeks before. So
yeah, I got a few numbers. They didn't
reply back yet, but I don't really care. But
yeah, man. I feel [ __ ] today cuz I'm
going to rubbing it. So
hopefully the lamb lamb and the uh ice
cream fixes it. Yeah,
I really want to get that Samson fold.
Ask yourself that because you are an incel.
What would you do if you was merely?
Would you go out three times a week, two
times a week, every week? I'll start
going out every week again when I get
myself sorted out. And I'm not talking
financially. I'm talking about like um
I'm talking about like um settled and
[ __ ] you know what I mean? Maybe once a week maximum if that
I would do more than once a week, man. It's pointless.
It's pointless, man. Yeah. So,
football starting again soon, is it? Yeah, man.
What would you do, Greasy?
Would you give up?
Would you go out once a week? Yeah.
I basically gave up to be fair.
Everyone gets reassessed though, don't they? So,
I took this whole moving thing quite
calmly, didn't I, Greasy? I didn't have
a mental breakdown or anything.
I want my [ __ ] dinner, man. I'm [ __ ] starving.
So hungry, bro.
Lamb always takes ages to cook. Mind
[ __ ] I had I had a Weather Spoons
today. I had a burger and I'm having
lamb. I definitely eat good, don't I? Grezy.
I definitely good, mate. That's one
thing about me.
I must have spent about 50 quid today.
Yeah. People get reassessed. Yeah.
What are you on pit for, Grezy?
Yes, I'm quarter Turkish. Yes. Every
Yes, it's every couple of years. Yeah.
Yeah, but I'm mostly white,
but I'm no religion cuz I love my little
biggies, don't I, Grezy?
Yeah. Anyways, they basically launched
the Samsung Galaxy Fold,
but I can't really I don't really have
to spare money to go get it now. You
know what I mean? Uh,
I could get, but
I need to really start saving. So, it's
only a phone. So, yeah.
Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ] launched it, didn't
they, when I was out? Um, yeah.
I reported Virgin Boy to the police, by
the way. It took about 20 minutes to
[ __ ] report. I said, "This [ __ ] is
stalking me. He still won't stop. He's
obsessed with me. I uh I had to open up
the whole case again, bro.
I couldn't be bothered, but I was like,
"No, I have to do it." So, I done it. I
done it earlier, bro.
Cuz these people are fast enough to run
to the police and, you know, play victim
and that. I thought, "Fuck it." Yeah. Yeah, bro.
What do you want out of life, Greasy?
I'm h I'm more than happy enough to sit
and play GTA,
have some nice ice cream,
some nice hammer,
and I'm happy me.
No, I would never get a second phone
cuz of the battery. Yeah, man.
Bye-bye. Let's self reflect on another channel.
Yeah, it's a it's a good option as well.
Wasting time. I've not wasted any time. I've traveled,
been out drinking, made new friends, had
loads of sex. I haven't wasted I haven't
wasted any time.
Wasting time doing what?
Like you said, you're new to the
channel. Greavves never even been
abroad. Greavves never even been to Scotland.
I don't even care about women anymore.
Grieves. I just went out cuz I wanted to
go out. I didn't really care.
It was just about to piss me off
yesterday. And I don't care about these
women, but I expect it.
I expect their [ __ ] now.
I wonder why it's going harder though.
Yeah, Virgin Boy didn't go broad until
he was 31. Imagine that. he done at 31
what I done at 23. Typical virgin
and he likes to convince people that
he's got all this money when he
literally has not a potent.
I had a ride yesterday from an escort
and I had a [ __ ]
Me honestly, if I could get this Uber
thing back, I'll just do Uber and use
escorts and travel and I'm set for life.
I don't give a [ __ ] about it. These
women, bro. Like, just they all But I
wonder why it's gotten harder, bro.
Sorry to say this again. Why is it
gotten harder, man?
At least [ __ ] a couple of years ago. Um,
you could actually get dates
and [ __ ] a few years ago. Well, why do
you reckon it's got harder greasy? You
know, I've done a video about this and I
was like, anyone that brings children up nowadays,
well, you can do both. Uber and escorts.
Well, the whole point is you do both.
Go gym and just travel, bro.
To be honest, I don't even enjoy the
drinking anymore. I just went out
yesterday cuz I had nothing bad to do.
But I wonder why it's changed all of a
sudden in two years. I mean, this
country's always been [ __ ] for the
[ __ ] but I mean, it's definitely gotten worse.
I reckon some people have moved on to
Tik Tok more now, even though Tik Tok's
been going a couple of years. Um,
I reckon more people are.
And you know what my friend said to me
like, you should you should start Tik Tok.
This is all like Tik Tok now. You see
more so. So
unless you've got a million subscribers,
they're not interested. So
yeah, I got free numbers yesterday. None
of them replied. And I was speaking to
this woman from New Zealand for about
half an hour. Grezy. We was having a
good chat on the street drinking.
Didn't even reply.
So it's not off the card, you know, me
going Australia. Well, she's from
Australia, but she lives in New Zealand,
but she's moving back to Australia. Me
with the pet kangaroo. Grezy,
that Polish bouncer, he wouldn't have
beat me, mate. Trust me. Like, at the
end of the day, the bigger they are, the
harder they fall. Trust me, he wouldn't
have beaten me. He wouldn't have beat me, bro.
And even if he did beat me, I would have went back.
But that's the kind of person I am.
Yeah, they're proper weirdos on here,
bro. They're proper weirdos, man. Yeah, man.
You need to go to Scotland, Grezy.
And I was speaking to these two women on
the train and we were talking about how
they were from Essex, right? I think
they were 40 3740.
We were just talking. It started off
they they sat next to me. They oh, can
we sit next to each other? I said, yeah.
So, I moved on the other seat. I made a
comment about their McDonald's and we're
just having chat about life and how
people are and
we were just going on and on and on and
on and on. It was a good chat, man.
Um, so you do get some people that do talk, but
it's nice when you can get a
conversation out of someone. Really is.
Yeah, they're weirdos on their brick bong, man.
They call me skinned because they're skinned themselves.
No, they they went off the train because
they had to go on another train and I went home.
But I think only way the dating game is
going to change in this country is when
is when um when you're like 40 maybe.
Maybe when you're in your 40s, I think
then it will change.
Which is what someone said to me on
Instagram. I didn't actually listen to
them. They said, "You might just use
escort and just travel and shit."
Cuz it's not too late when you're in
your 30s and you're in your 30s, 40s.
Obviously, you're you're young now and
you want sex, but unfortunately people
are not interested because they're
influenced by [ __ ] Tik Tok and all
that [ __ ] So
yeah, but it has definitely got harder.
It has definitely gotten harder.
I used to have loads of dates.
That time that I met Izzy, [ __ ] Izzy,
[ __ ] USA Izzy.
That whole April, I had so many women fingering [ __ ] all sorts.
I don't really enjoy the drinking now, bro.
I just want that Samsung Galaxy Fold.
I want to play GTA and just bang
escorts, bro. That's it. Yeah,
I want to get that Samson fold seven greasy, but
I can't really
really do it, bro. To be honest, there One second.
But yeah, Grezy, what do you want out of life?
And I love going to the cinema.
I love watching horror films in the
cinema. I love playing GTA. [ __ ] Yeah, man.
It's fun, bro. It's great fun.
I'm playing it right now. I can show you
if you want.
Well, one of the things you should do,
Greavves, is is is go to Scotland.
It's summer. You can go Scotland on Saturday
or, you know, whenever you have the
money. Just go to Scotland. I think
that's a great start. Go Scotland, you know. But uh Franklin badlin
Franklin's driving a car now. Yeah.
I love this. Yeah.
He went flying.
See, I'm easy entertained by this.
Yeah, my phone keeps [ __ ] trying to
steal my fan. I said, "Mate, it's my fan."
Yeah, bro. I decided not to go out
today. I was going to go out today. Give
it a whirl, but I got three numbers and
none of them replied and I don't really
care anyways, bro.
Nah. And I won't be going out for a mob.
I won't be going out now for a mob cuz I
need to go gym and [ __ ] and sort myself
out with certain things. So I Yeah, bro. My whole
I didn't, bro. I didn't care about the
whole women [ __ ] Um because
Yeah, it was from last night numbers. I
didn't care about the women [ __ ] bro,
cuz I just re I just know it's never
going to change.
So I don't really care about that. It's
just a bouncer, you know?
[ __ ] not the bouncer really. It was
the stupid rules and the idiots in this
country. But I I'm happy playing GTA,
getting escort, going to the mall. I
don't really care, man. To be honest,
how could you care when it's always the
same old? Like, what is what is there to
moan about? You hear I've got a
boyfriend, you get a number, they reply,
they they don't reply, they play mind
games. It's the same old but worse.
Do you know the maddest thing is is I was um
um I was uh speaking to this one from
New Zealand for about half an hour ago.
So, you know, like in London, you know,
like you got a strip in Soho. I
approached her. I didn't know she was
from New Zealand. And we was talking and
talking and talking and talking
and [ __ ] ages, bro.
Um, and then she um she didn't u reply. Uh,
and then I got one on the street. She
didn't reply even though she was asking
me questions. And then the other one,
she was from Ireland. So, it's like it's
like what Antman says, they're just not
interested in this country. Yeah. At the
end of the day, just come back in 20 years.
Like look what he done. He he changed
his life for the better. He went to
Thailand and he's living there now. You
know, we've all got to do things that's
going to make our life better. And he
hated flying as well. Like he hated
flying. Like he hated flying, bro.
I don't And what I don't understand,
Ghosting, but I'm done trying to figure
it out. But since we're on the topic, is
why they're not interested.
But I did have a woman approach me
saying, "I like your track." And we was
talking and stuff.
Yeah. I don't understand
why why they're not interested.
But I'm not going to sit here and try
and figure it out. But nah.
Yeah. He's living in Thailand now teaching English.
But that thing yesterday with the
bouncer, let me tell you what happened.
Ghosting. Yeah. So I approached like
four women not over and over and over again
over the part over I don't know what he
does over a period of about 3 hours
right I wasn't rude didn't assault
anyone didn't argue with anyone didn't
make any sarcastic comments right so get
back onto that right so this was over
like a period of 2 and a half hours it
weren't just like I was talking to one
and then talking to one and talking to
one and at the end of the day even if I
was doing that which I wasn't doing that
I'm a single man, this is a club. Like,
isn't that the whole point? I'm a single
person. We're told that we can't
approach on the street and then they
tried. I personally think what it is is
two things. They either didn't like you
in there with a tracksuit, so they made
up an excuse or the staff has seen you
like speaking to people and people's
approaching me as well, like just normal
people. Um because there's no way three
women went and complained about you
because out of all of my years of
approaching, I never had anyone ever
complain about me, complain to the
police, never in in 3 years. So what
people that weren't going to stay in an establishment
um would just sit there and no, like
they made they made it up. They probably
saw you going and I'm thinking like
whatever the reason is, it's like what
the [ __ ] This is a bar.
It wasn't a group. It was two women.
They were all two women.
So, but it doesn't matter. You're a
single guy. You're in a club. You're
paying their prices. It's a free
country. Like, it's not awkward. It's
normal. You're a single person. You're
trying to meet new people, which I don't
even get to do much very often now
anyways, that it's not a big deal.
like it's it's supposed to be a free
country. He wasn't doing no harm to
anyone. And then the bouncer was trying
to say if I give him an attitude, he's
going to snatch the drink out. I said,
"You're not going to slap no drink out
my hand." And he tried to snatch the
drink and the drink went everywhere, not on me.
And I told him to come around the
corner, but that none of that matters
anyways. [ __ ] all that
because none of that matters. The whole
that's irrelevant. I'm sure it's going
to happen one more time in your life,
but it's not that that doesn't matter
anyways. The matter the matter is
the thing is is that you should be able
to talk to who you want.
No, I'm not going around in circles,
Ghosting. I I hadn't been out for a
month. I'm not going around in circles,
bro. I'm just saying that it gets worse.
And what I'm not going I'm not going
around in circles. I won't be out now
for another month. I'm not going out in
circles, bro. I went out yesterday to
have a drink and I expected the same
[ __ ] It didn't bother me cuz you expect
it in this in this country.
So, it's that wasn't what what was
[ __ ] up. The whole thing that was
[ __ ] up is that you can't even speak
to people in your own country in a social environment.
Yeah, get creepy. No, nothing creepy
about me at all, mate. Stop self projecting.
You would know what creepy is if it hit
you around the [ __ ] face.
No. Yeah, I'm acting creepy by starting
a conversation with people. Yeah, it is
the same cycle, bro. Yeah, bro. It's
never going to change. Why do you think
I use escorts?
You should come back to dating when
you're like 30, I think.
Nothing wrong with that. I mean, you're
not old when you're 30. In your 30s, is it?
Somebody told me in my 40s, but no, you
weren't acting creepy at all. So,
um, but then, but it doesn't matter
anyways, Ghost, because what was it
again, bro? Don't approach people on the
street. You approach people in bars and
clubs. And then when you approach people
in bars and clubs,
apparently they boot you out. Make it
make sense. Like, that's when you need
to like really put into the thing is
like, make it make sense.
And no one complained about me at all at
all. They literally just saw you down
here and they thought, "Fuck it. We just
boot this [ __ ] out. He's wearing track
bottoms anyways." No one complain about anything.
Never once have I had somebody on the
street complain to a police officer.
Yeah, but the whole Yeah, but the thing
is ghosting, bro. I'm not going out
expecting it to change. I'm going out
because I want to go out anyways.
And yesterday I went out cuz I had
literally nothing else to do.
Like I wasn't expecting it to change.
I'm not moaning about it. It is what it
is. It's the same old England.
But the thing is, bro, like it has
definitely gotten worse, bro. Like,
sorry to be like repeating and whatever,
bro. Hey, it's um
the thing is bro and I embarrassed him.
I embarrassed him in front of the two
women as well. There was these two women
standing there. I was slating him off
calling him uh
um calling him [ __ ] Polish and
everything. Like you're not going to
embarrass me, bro. I try and look the
try and look the big man. But the thing
is, bro, I went out um yeah, like two
years ago ghosting, you could actually get something.
Like when I met that [ __ ] in America, I
had two I had about three one night
stands that year. Um I had three one
night stands. I had dates. I had dates
that I [ __ ] up
um because of that [ __ ] So man, like if
you see it from now,
2 3 years ago, it was so different. It
was still hard, don't get me wrong. It
was still [ __ ] but like it weren't as
bad as this. It ain't It weren't as bad
as this, bro.
Like now it is virtually impossible to
even meet someone, to get a conversation
out of someone.
Yeah, it's creepy. No, it's actually
called trying to meet someone.
So, sitting in a club approaching is
creepy. Approaching on the street is
creepy. Yeah. Make it make sense.
Make it make sense, man.
But the thing is ghosting like um
there was a time a couple weeks ago I
was so mentally exhausted I couldn't
even I couldn't even approach anymore.
Like I'd go around my area and I
couldn't I couldn't even do it. I was
that mentally and physically exhausted
by it all.
So, but no, two years ago was goat, bro.
Even a year ago was goat.
Yeah, I got booted out cuz the staff got jealous. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Yeah. Stop being a
hater, man. Stop being a hater on my
channel. [ __ ] off. But yeah, the thing
is, Ghosting, like, you got to
understand that it's been going on for
for years. I mean, nothing's going to
change. You understand, bro? like it's
never going to change in this country.
You might say, "Oh, you'll meet someone and no."
But if something was going to happen,
you would have met someone by now. But
I'm not contradicting myself by going out.
I'm I'm going out because I had nothing
better to do which is stupid really cuz
I've got so much stress I can't even
enjoy going out the whole moving and
[ __ ] and not financially but just like
the whole moving and where you going to
go and [ __ ] like it's but still I had
nothing better to do so when them when
there's days where you got nothing
better to do then deep down I know it's
never going to change but what else can you So,
it's weird ghosting how they don't give
you a chance. It is weird. It is. It is strange.
But I've been all over the country.
Been to Wales three times.
Been to Scotland two times. Been to
Manchester 10 times. been to Liverpool,
lead Nottingham three times, Birmingham
about seven times,
[ __ ] Sheffield about three times.
It's not different, bro. It's the same.
Newcastle is easier, but yeah, it's
never It's It's not the same. They're westernized.
It's It's that It's It's that simple.
But the only place that's easier is Newcastle.
No, bro. I don't have the money to be wasting.
I'd rather go abroad. Like, what's the
point of wasting, right?
You know what I'm saying? What's the
point of wasting 3400 when I can just
leave this country again? It doesn't make sense.
Cuz at the end of the day, like, think
about it. You've done all the traveling,
but you're still single. So, at the end
of the day, like if that [ __ ] really worked,
but obviously, well, not necessarily
because you could turn around and say
like you've only been out three times in
Newcastle and it was better. I got
kisses. I got [ __ ] people approached
me. Obviously, that's three times. You
know, you can go out three times in
London and get nothing, but it doesn't
mean that you're never ever going to get
anything. So, you'd have to literally
live somewhere for a while. You'd have
to maybe like live in Newcastle for a
month and then go out every week and see
if you if you find a relationship in in a month.
But yeah, it was a lot easier than
London. I can't lie, bro. A lot easier.
And because I was from London, they
liked me more.
I was thinking of going back to Nottingham.
Newcastle was a bit too far. I was
thinking of go like when I'm settled
down and that I was thinking of just
going to Nottingham and having a drink
scenery because where I was where you
work in London and you're in London all
the time you get bored in London. I was
thinking of of it but not Newcastle. I
was thinking of Nottingham
cuz Newcastle's too far.
You know, even Nottingham is different.
You get slagged.
Um this anywhere, bro. But Newcastle,
every time I've been there, bro, I
remember I always wanted to go. Like,
I've been everywhere but Newcastle. Then
I went to Newcastle.
Literally snogged about three people.
[ __ ] it was it was easy pickings.
And then the last time, right,
this woman said to me, "Oh, you're too
handsome for Newcastle. Like, you're
good-look." And then she she approached me and
I think London's better with street approaches.
Newcastle that is better with bars,
bars and clubs.
Cuz in London ghosting, you get these
stuck up Indian people. And by Indian, I
mean Indian heritage. And they've all
got the same attitude. They're all stuck up.
They're literally all up their own ass.
But they weren't born in India. come
here. I mean, the ones that were b the
ones that were born here, the ones that
are from here, but Indian heritage,
they're literally impossible. Like,
they're just stuck up their own ass.
But Manchester is no good. Ghosting.
Manchester is no good. Manchester is
just the wannabe London, bro. And
they've all got the same attitude there as well.
Which years ago in Manchester, I was
talking, we were talking about this. Me
and these two women were talking about
places and we were saying that basically
it's discussing how you can't even go to
work in this city without dealing with [ __ ]
But yeah, I know where Warrington is.
Yeah, I know where it is. I've been to Liverpool once
um and I think I got I've got a
boyfriend. I'm not interested there. But
that was on Monday and it was only once
so you can't really compare it.
I do want to go Liverpool again but I
don't know man. It's dodgy is it?
I've only been Liverpool once, man.
If I if I had a choice to go Manchester
or Liverpool, I'll choose Liverpool. Yeah, that's it.
But Asia is where it's at. Ghost said
Now, even Irish people are cool, man.
But I was speaking to this Irish guy. He
was quite cool. Um,
yeah, I can't remember. It was a few
years ago, but
I done Liverpool, bro. I remember doing Liverpool.
I think I definitely got I got a
boyfriend there. I definitely did.
Birmingham is [ __ ] Birmingham is [ __ ]
Yeah. I remember meeting somebody in Nottingham.
She was from Sunny Hole. She gave me a [ __ ]
Yep. Never been black before.
I was thinking maybe going reden.
Yeah, I've got a bit of Irish,
bit of everything.
Cuz basically what the the crux of it is
ghosting is you need to basically take
the competition away from these women.
You know, that's what a lot of it comes
down to. And and obviously money as
well. Cuz if these people don't have no money, right,
if these people don't have much money
and there's not much competition, right,
they would have to choose you. Whereas
in London, people can choose anyone and
people are busy cuz you are decent
looking. you are good-looking me, you
know, but in London where where there's
so many people and you know, you go
somewhere like Nottingham, it's like
three women to one man and they got
hardly any money. So, um
that's what it basically is.
That's why it's easier in places like
Newcastle and [ __ ] because they're more
like it's they have less money and
um they have less competition. So, you
understand what I'm saying, bro? Like,
it's like when that woman's like, "Oh,
you're too good looking for Newcastle."
No, no, no, no, no. And [ __ ] Like, you
think you'd ever go to London and
someone would say that to you? They'll
probably [ __ ] slabber at you, mate.
cuz that's it, bro. So,
I remember when I got nicked in
Newcastle, even the police was funny.
Yeah, they trying to Trump. All these
people are, Listen, they're just skin
little sad bastards that ain't got a
life, ain't got no money, ain't got no
life. They just self-reflect.
Cuz if they had money and they had a
life, they wouldn't be on here.
Um, I'm only on here sometimes, but I've
been off here for weeks and weeks and
weeks before. They ain't got a life,
bro. They're 40y old little losers, bro. 100%.
It's even like that virgin legs, right?
You are the only one that's skinned.
You've lost the money game millions and
millions of times against me and you've
never had a job. You're just some lanky
little [ __ ] virgin that ain't got a
life. That's what you are. Yeah,
they're all losers, bro. That's why I
don't really come on here anymore, brother. So, yeah.
But why would she why would she be on drugs, bro? Um,
what do you think of London when you
come to London, Ghost?
London is good. Me and these women were
saying the same thing. If they took
people out of London, if there was no
people in London, it'd be perfect. If
there was no people here, it'd be perfect.
Yeah, they're all snakes on here as
well, bro. They don't go out. They're sados.
Try to call me skate cuz I'm selling my
fridge and washing machine because I'm
leaving. I'm leaving because I'm moving
house. Why would I be skin?
Like I'm moving you idiot. The only
thing I'm bringing with me is my TV and my Xbox.
Yep. I know, Eden.
I had a date in Elen before. She was a
complete and not a [ __ ]
You remember that day I had an Elen
ghost? Oh, [ __ ] me. Yeah.
Yeah. Not I had a date there in Eden once
and she was trying to bareface lie to me.
Yeah, I went to Elen before and I met
this stupid woman from Maiden Head.
Yeah. No, it's easy to get to Elen now
from the Elizabeth line. You just go
Stratford Elizabeth and just go straight
to Elen. It's far, but you can get the
Elen. You can get a direct train now.
Nowadays, it's easy to get into West
from east. Easy. The only thing that's
hard to go to is south um southwest.
That's the only hard place to get to
basically from East London and Cuden.
So Cudon and um
like yeah I went on this date before and
Elen she's from Maiden Head. So we kind
of met cuz obviously from Maiden Head
they go to Elen, right? and I just went
all the way to Elen and there was this
guy from Manchester and he kept talking
to her and I didn't really like her that
much anyways and I was like okay it's a
bit dodge and then she kept going back
out and then like we said oh we'll see
each other again I don't really care
about her to be honest we kissed and
that which is the maddest thing we
actually kissed and [ __ ] and then she's
like oh yeah and then I was like she's
like go before me I was like why do you
want me to go before you
um I said that dodgy. Like, why do you
want me to go before you? I said, "You
can go." And then she would went with
him to the train station with a kid and
someone else. And I was like, "Bro, just
let them go, bro. I don't even like her.
Like, I already kissed the bitch." And
she was trying to point back blank lie to me.
Um, when I've seen it with my own eyes
and I don't care. You know what I'm saying? So,
I remember that. Yeah.
Last time I went to Elen and it it was a
good bar as well. Good staff.
I tell you where you'd like, bro. You'd
like O'Neal's in um Water Street.
I got barred from there, but I had some
good times in there, bro.
Um I had some good times in that O'Neals.
Got loads of [ __ ] there. Fingered
Got a [ __ ] there. [ __ ] good times, bro.
But yeah, if you ain't ever if you've
never been to O'Neal's
W Street, bro, check it out. That's why
I met all the army threat my army pals.
Yeah, the Soho one.
Yep. I [ __ ] an escort yesterday. Oh,
funny story ghosting.
I went to an air school yesterday and
you know how I just like blow jobs and I
don't like [ __ ] I can't be bothered
cuz oh you can't come in my mouth. I was
like oh not this [ __ ] again. And I was
like you know what [ __ ] it. I'm just
going to [ __ ] her. I'm just going to let
her suck my dick and [ __ ] her cuz I'm
not [ __ ] in like months and months and
month. I can't remember the last time
maybe a year.
I just get blow jobs me. Oh [ __ ] it. I'm
just going to [ __ ] the [ __ ]
Yeah, I just like [ __ ] Me?
I don't like I don't care about sex. I
only care about boobies and [ __ ]
I think I'm I don't know, bro. Like,
whenever I watch porn, I just watch
[ __ ] I don't watch I don't watch
sex. I don't care about sex, bro.
The only time I'd give someone sex is if
I was with them, obviously to pleasure
them. But I won't eat [ __ ] That's disgusting.
Only desperate white people do that. But
I would [ __ ] Obviously, I was with
somebody, I'd [ __ ] them. But when that
[ __ ] used to come around, she used to
just suck my dick. I never [ __ ] I I
stopped [ __ ] her. I [ __ ] her like I
[ __ ] her three times, but when she'd
come round, she would just give me a
[ __ ] and that's it. I would even [ __ ] her.
And she said she'd be up for anal and
everything. I just never done it. Yeah.
Someone says they wouldn't give me a
blow job, I wouldn't get with them.
That's just boring, mate. [ __ ] boring.
driving ghost is boring, ain't it?
I remember Sig wouldn't suck my Willie.
She's like, "You have to eat me out. I'm
not [ __ ] eating you out."
Yeah. I said to this escort, "I'm going
to glue my dick to your mouth." And she
put praying hands on the uh on the message. Yeah.
They must hate that in it because
obviously you know they're escorts,
right? But they probably must like
getting [ __ ] as well as getting paid.
And then you come and you just want a [ __ ]
and they think, "Oh, [ __ ] this. My jaw
is going to start aching." No, no, no.
At least with like sex, they kind of
get something out of it.
Does that make sense? Yeah. Yep.
What's your favorite ghosting?
Do you like [ __ ] Greasy?
Or you don't care?
A lot of that stuff originated in Germany.
I want my dinner.
It should be ready soon. Come on. I'm starving.
I'm [ __ ] starving, Goozy, man. [ __ ] Cuz
a lot of the
a lot of the porn comes from Germany. I
like a nice I like a Do you know what my
favorite porn is actually? Vintage porn
when it's like in the 1980s and it's a
1990s and they're proper making love.
Like they're making love and then like
the guy's seducing her and they just make love.
Not this [ __ ] Johnny Sin [ __ ] I
can't watch him. It's all fake. Obvious.
It just looks so fake.
I like the ones where they seduce them
or just like make love.
Like I can't I can't explain it, bro.
Like this old really really old ones
cuz I like the story lines.
Johnny Sins is just all fake. You know
who Johnny Sins is, don't you, Greasy? Sure you do.
I was in Spec Savers today with my
friend. Yeah. I couldn't stop laughing
at Sippy. He said, "Can you be normal?"
He's like, "Can you wait outside if you
can't stop laughing?" I couldn't stop
laughing, bro. All I kept thinking of
was like Bungle the Bear.
Um, all I kept thinking of was Bungle
the Bear, man. Yeah.
No, porn stores don't like doing it.
They get paid.
I like the vintage ones. I like vintage
porn. I didn't watch vintage porn go.
Yeah. Bungle. I was in spec and I kept
thinking of rainbow and my friend was
like, if you if you're not going to stop
laughing, can you go out? I can't stop
cuz he says that he needs some shies. prescription,
but the internet's not working.
And then he said the
And he said the internet ain't working.
Yeah, man. I like it when they get
seduced like really upper class women,
you know? Like not up class. I can't
explain it, but like back before social media,
you know? Hey bro, you know my friend
Ghosting? Yeah. You know how I got him
to say [ __ ] and my other friends say
[ __ ] cuz I always use that word. So he
was doing his security job and he said
thank you [ __ ] to one of the supervisors
by mistake and the supervisor was like
what did you say? And he was like oh I
was sip of a tongue.
Um yeah I was dead bro. He said thank
you K. He said I was it was a slip of
the tongue. And then he said, "You need
to watch your tongue." That's what he
said. I was dead. He come back and he
said, "We need to stop using that word."
I said, "Why?" And I thought like
someone else said something. I knew
someone had said something.
I was dead, bro. I was on the phone to
my mom. Just imagine that in it. Thank you.
What did you say?
I was dead. But I could just imagine him
in his little uniform. Yeah, he's a beautiful
bungle the Hey, you ever watched that? Have you
Ghost? Have you ever watched that? Um,
Rainbow for adults. Oh, just thinking
about it. You know when you shouldn't
laugh. Yeah. And you think about funny things.
Thank you, God. Yeah,
we said that. But he was going to say to
a woman the other day as well, but I was saying [Laughter]
yeah, he said that. Oh, um, he need to
show his prescription, but there's no internet.
And it just made me laugh, bro. Yeah.
He says I need to stop laughing.
He says I find everything funny. Yeah.
I don't find anything funny.
Wow. Well, you don't know anything about women.
Yeah. Well, you don't know anything about women.
Yeah. I kept thinking of Jeffrey Grezy
and you, you [ __ ] Yeah. Mhm.
>> I still want that pet kangaroo. Grezy
Peter belly and his pet kangaroo and his
little cap. Ah, beta.
Yeah. Jeffrey when he's swearing in it
and I kept thinking about inspect
savers. I was laughing and everyone was looking. Yeah.
I remember when I went to go to court
for that thing. Yeah. It was so hard not
to laugh, man. Like I was I had to
literally think of some funerals and
[ __ ] Like I literally had to think of
funerals greasy to stop laughing. And he
says, "So you you you don't think
calling somebody a Kent Wanka virgin
with a [ __ ] girlfriend?" And bear in
mind the c the court thing is is all
silence, isn't it? So they're for like
serious matters. Um I I had to think of
like funerals I've been to to to stop
laughing, bro. than to not laugh because
it's the most pathetic thing. I think
you you know and obviously you can't
laugh in the court with it. He said so
so you think calling somebody a gay Kent
wanker? That's literally what what he
said, bro. A gay a gay Kent wanker with
a [ __ ] girlfriend is is is is not
malicious. He's like, "Okay,
so come back in 3 and 1/2 years."
That's what he basically said.
[ __ ] it. Now that that you wouldn't be
able to Yeah, that's what the judge
said. Yeah, it was the most pathetic
thing, bro. You You think you would ever
went to court for
Yeah, I was trying. I was really trying
not. I don't know how them judges don't laugh
to be honest.
And even like the police interviews,
like you know on a police interview they
will say things you've said. Like say
you call somebody a [ __ ] [ __ ] they
will say it. I don't know how they don't laugh, you know.
I don't know how they don't laugh, mate.
I piss myself. Yeah.
You remember the thing with my mo on the
motorway when I was like, "Oh, get me
off that motorway." Yeah. And then my
mom tried coming off cuz she didn't like
she didn't want to go on the motorway
and she had to stay with my sister and
she said she was [ __ ] herself the
whole way I was dead. She thought she
was going to come out with me. Grezy,
she thought she was coming out with me.
Nah, mate. You're saying it? [ __ ] that. Yeah,
you've never been nicked. I've been
nicked. [ __ ] god. I've been nicked
many times, bro.
More times than I've had hot dinners.
Only for stupid things. Yeah.
You never been nicked. That's good, bro.
I've been nicked so many times
over. social media. They always let me
go though. So,
and then the thing is when you come out
the police cell, Yeah. the first thing
you you want is a McDonald's.
Yeah. in the McDonald's. Don't know.
Yeah, I had McDonald's yesterday actually. Yeah. No good.
Yep. I've stayed in the police cell when
I got nicked last time. I was in the
police cell for 2 days and I had to go
to court go to the court sale and then
the court let me go. I don't I didn't
eat when I was there. I don't eat. I
just have the tea and biscuits.
I just have the tea and I just have tea
and biscuits. I I didn't eat. I I can't Sorry.
Yeah. I can't eat me.
Yeah. They treat you like royalty over
here, mate. That's why people are so
dick. So That's why people are [ __ ]
because there's no punishment.
Yeah. Cuz there's no punishment. They
know that they can just be a [ __ ]
Go prison, get treated like royalty,
come out and get a house. Yeah, they
treat you like, you know, like
better than probably your friends would
treat you. Yeah, please do in this country.
I didn't pass the time. I just stayed
up. And to be honest with you, it it
goes quite quickly.
I didn't sleep. I remember not sleeping.
No, I didn't sleep cuz I was worried
about if my phone was still going to be
in the garden cuz they they tried taking
my phone but I put in the garden so they
weren't getting that phone. So it was
like oh what's going to happen?
Obviously I had the house as a responsibility.
Um there was a few things going through
my mind if my phone was going to still be there.
um if they were going to let me out cuz
obviously I had the responsibility of
the house cuz obviously I had the
responsibility, what's going to happen
with the house and that so you know you
can't eat when
when you got that kind of stress and you
don't know what's going to happen and
you've got responsibility as well. So it
was bad, bro. It was bad. That's how I
got that foot injury cuz I ran back to
see if the phone was still there. That's
how I got that paranal tentonitis.
That was a nasty foot injury.
Oh, I went over that [ __ ] virgin
months ago, bro. So, yeah. Um,
nah, bro. I think I banged it or
whatever. It's gone now.
Yeah, it was so bad that my friend had
to cook for me. I couldn't even walk.
Whatever. It was like my whole foot was swollen, bro.
Yeah, I think I just sprayed it or
something, but it was [ __ ] stinking, bro.
who would wake me up at 4:00 in the
morning in pain. I had this foot injury
ghosting called uh
never, bro. I'm never going to get
nicked ever again, bro. [ __ ] that.
How do I know the diagnosis? Cuz I done
research on it and everything
was exactly the same. the pain, the
waking you up, it coming at night, it
taking six to nine weeks to go away. It
It was that
It was stinking.
I'm telling you, bro. It was stinking,
bro. I'll never forget that time I was
in Lane I was at Laney's. Yeah. Woke up
4 in the morning. Bam, bam, bam, bam,
bam. It was like having a brain tumor in
your [ __ ] foot. Yeah. And I went down
the stairs to look for tablets.
Yeah, it went it did go in the end, but
yeah, I asked the doctor. Yeah. So, I
had to walk all the way to the doctors
and they said, "Oh, yeah, you've
probably just overused it. Um, you need
to put ice on it and just rest." And
then they gave me a prescription and it
weren't ready for hours. So, I had to go
all the way back home and then all the
way back out. Bear in mind, I could
barely walk. So, they gave me like a
code, but it did go.
It went in at the end, but [ __ ] hell.
It was stinky, bro.
I generally didn't think it was ever
going to go away, but it was painful.
It was really bad, bro.
No, they just gave you.
I like though. It makes you feel high.
You know when I used to be pissed off
about that USA Izzy thing? Yeah. I would
take three cacodamals and it and it
would make me feel good, man. I think of
all like the positives and [ __ ] It was
like being high.
I actually got addicted to them at one
point, but not now.
So yeah, bro.
No, it was a nasty injury, bro. It was a nasty injury.
What do you think caused it? Do you
reckon it's where I ran or maybe I banged it?
I think what it might have been is Yeah.
When I was in the police cell, I kept
walking in circles and circles and
circles and I would not stop walking cuz
the stress because of obviously stress in it.
I think it's that and the running maybe
cuz cuz obviously you're constantly
walking and walking and walking and
walking, you've overused it in it. So
even though you're not walking anywhere,
you're walking in circles.
But it was not it was nasty, bro. It was nasty.
And like every time you try to walk it
would just go you go back to square one
like you think it's better and then you
just go back to limping again until it
was fully gone. It was horrible. [ __ ]
horrible guy. I had to explain to the
I tried to explain to the to the date
that I went on that yeah I kind of got a
limp cuz I got a foot injury and she
says oh it's no problem.
Yeah, I had to limp on a date, bro. He mad.
Yeah, exactly. Bro, I don't I don't even
um I don't even bother with them anymore.
No, I don't get round up over the women.
I didn't get round up over the women.
Like, do you know what? Yeah. Only two
of them said they had boyfriends
yesterday. Ghost, I'm telling you, the tracksuit helps.
Only two of them said they had
boyfriends, which is the way it actually
is. Two or three. Like in a whole night,
bro, only about three people have boyfriends.
So I just put it down to they had
boyfriends. I don't really care. But
yeah, that's the real statistics is two people, bro. So yeah,
there's loads of women that hate men.
There's loads of women that live without
men. Like loads of men live without women.
So when 90% or when 80% of them claim
they're in a relationship,
it's not true, you know? So
I hate that boyfriend [ __ ] though. It's [ __ ] annoying.
Like even people from Germany say it nicola.
I hate it, bro. I [ __ ] hate it.
That must be stuck in their head in it.
Hey, bro. It's annoying.
Can't believe USA Izzy found a new partner.
So, and man's right. Um, Niko though
that they're just not interested in this country.
It was so bad when I went to Sheffield.
Yeah. I kissed like three people and
Antman didn't get nothing.
One I tried to pull for Ant-Man ended up kissing me.
She said, "Who cares? You're way better looking."
But this whole um this whole ringing up
pubs is really weird
cuz firstly, right,
staff change all the time and there's a
million pubs and bars in London. So why
would you even ring a pub up?
It don't make sense. Why even ring a pub
up when you know that I can just go to
the next place and next place and the
next area? It's just stupid. Ringing up
pubs is so weird.
Yep. They all say no.
They're not interested.
They're not interested in this country.
No, but seriously, is Antman right? Then
they're not interested in this country.
But that steak I had with USA Izzy was
the bomb, bro. It was [ __ ] amazing.
It was [ __ ] lush, mate.
We wanted a roast dinner, but they only
had steak, so I was, "Okay, we'll just
get the steak. Let's get the steak." I
got ribeye cuz I prefer sirloin.
You know what's so weird
and Stephen Albert is me and Lamey. It's
so weird. I I come from Laney, but we've
got complete different taste buds.
Like nothing we like is the same.
Like me and Laney.
Strange, isn't it?
I can name you a million things. I like
the orange Lugusade. She likes the
original. I prefer sirloin steak. Well
done. She likes ribeye um rare. I like
sugar in my tea. She doesn't. I love
pizza and spicy food. She doesn't.
We got different complete different taste buds.
I like pork loins.
She likes the bellies.
You know, we we're completely different.
We are actually so different, you know. Um
I'm sure there's something I'm missing.
We both like salmon.
No, leave lady alone. She's been through
a lot in her little life.
Lady's been through a lot.
Leave lady alone.
He's been through a lot, man.
Well, I'm going back. I'm going to have
my tea now. So, yeah. See you later. Yeah.