[ __ ] it. [ __ ] amazing. [Music] Yeah, that's
the you need to do one by yourself. You
need to do by
yourself. I love it. Come on. What is
happening in that in the group of four
pretty? Yeah, you
should listen to me. Pretty girls are
already and the other two are not so
pretty. So, they're like quite insecure
But you as soon as they go there, the
inseure ones are going to protect them.
Like no one is listen.
But what I'm saying is you
should some other You should have got
her [ __ ] number one. Come. That's
what I'm saying. You was there for
[ __ ] 10 minutes. No, she said that
she's chatting with her boyfriend, bro.
She was You was there for 10 minutes,
bro. I watched you like 10 [ __ ]
minutes. I I had a chance that
she was just there because she don't
want to reject me. No, you should have
asked for it, bro.
Yeah. Get in on it, boys. Got two
numbers so far. There you go. You should
have bro. You was [ __ ] there for 10
minutes. 10 minutes. You're there for 10
minutes. You're [ __ ] bro.
10 minutes. 10 [ __ ] minutes.
I said he should have got he was there
for [ __ ] 10 minutes. Oh, sorry. I [Music] toilet.
I was saying that he went for 10
minutes. You should have asked for the number.
Yeah. Go on,
go [ __ ] yourself. Go
on. for him, not me. Don't ask for me.
Wait, I'm not even You [ __ ] You are
said she got a boyfriend. Why the [ __ ]
She ain't got a boyfriend, bro.
See, I'm not single. She said, like I
said, like she was chatting with her boyfriend. Why?
Go buy me a drink, man. [ __ ] it up.
Go buy a drink.
as much as you want. Don't be
m I bought you one. I don't even work.
You bought me a drink last week. Why? [ __ ]
off. I told him to [ __ ] up
to two numbers so far, [ __ ]
Baby, buy me a [ __ ] drink, mate.
I've had to deal with a lot of [ __ ] bades. [Music]
Yeah, but get me a drink. Buy me a
drink, mate. Go
on. [ __ ] you. [ __ ] you.
Yeah, I got two numbers.
I done about seven approaches to get one
number. I done seven approaches to get one [ __ ]
number of bollocks. Seven [ __ ]
approaches to get one fancy number. Hey, it's [Music]
abandoned. Who leave your house?
And what's the time? 8:21.
I'll be on it all night, babe. All
night. I will do Saturday as
well. Guna Chan, you are Oh, loser.
Guna. Guna. I'm your city. You didn't come out.
Gona. Ga, I came to your city. You
didn't come out,
Ga. Ga, I come to your city and you
didn't come out. Get me in the caravan.
Oh my god. You [ __ ] Welsh
prick. You [ __ ] Welsh prick. Get me
in the caravan or
the [ __ ] Welsh
prick. I went to his
son in the
caliban in the calibad or
gun you prick shut up you wal
[ __ ] I went to I've got a passport I've
passport there you go want to see my passport stamps
I got two numbers. I got two numbers. I
got two [ __ ] numbers.
B outside. My mates are
outside. They're coming
back. B. I got I got three two numbers.
One of them was in my area. Yeah. [Music]
I got a
little some push as well. Get a
bad coming in as well, mate. I got paid
over a glam today as well. Yeah, living that
life. It's good to be out there living
that life, mate.
to get them numbers first. Living our life.
living our lives [Music] up
or you're [ __ ] well done. [Music]
I know cuz Goon is a sad
bastard. Is a sad [ __ ] Goon is a sad
mate. Guess what? I sold £1,000 today
and no one showed me
nothing. They couldn't show me
nothing. All right, P. I got I got two
numbers. Where the [ __ ] are these
[ __ ] No, they're not Americans. They're not
Americans. They ain't Americans, man.
Give it to about 10. Give them to about
10 American boy. Wow. [Music]
30. Where the [ __ ] are these [ __ ]
Where the [ __ ] are these [ __ ] They
were supposed to be a 10 minutes.
Out about, mate. Out and about. That ratfaced little
virgin. That little ratfaced virgin with no money.
I need to be careful. There's a woman. I
just approached you past me. I need to
be careful. I need to be careful. Stop. [Applause]
You're on your way. You don't know what happened.
O one, two,
three. Yeah, there.
Go. Come on. [Music] Hey, good. Wait, wait. Thank
you. Thank you, boss. [Music]
Barbers, give me a shot. Give me a
short. Give me a shot.
Give me a short. A short? Yeah. Give me
a shot. Yes. Stop.
Shambuka. Get some. There we
go. That's my
friend. I got paid today, Mr. me. I got
paid. I got paid a couple of G. [Music]
Never. Like I said, Harry P. I get over 3K above
land. Over 3K above
land. Over 3K above that.
I over 3K above Mr. B.
Yeah, I will. [Music]
over hiding from the women. I've only
got two numbers
left. I'll do it in my own
time. I'm chilling with my friend at a [Music] minute.
Sure. Yeah. Thank you,
boss. I'm live on
YouTube. I got YouTube channel. Tell
them how many of people have I
How many people have I put?
Yeah, there you are.
Yeah, the shot. Hey, go over to them
girls, bro. I don't [ __ ] hate you. Go
on. Go on. Go.
All right. Now, go and do it.
I'm lying. Boss, get up
there. Go over. Go over.
I don't [ __ ] care myself, bro. You show me
God. God. God. She's going to pull you.
She don't do it. She's going to pull you.
You don't do it. She's going to pull
you some. Yeah. Like the first one. Like
one like [ __ ] after shave.
Give it some time. I'll do it. Wait.
Thanks for the shot.
Give me some time, bro, cuz I want to approach someone
and I don't want her to see me talking
to other women. That's the reason I'm
I'm trying back on it.
Wait, that's why I'm doing it.
I think you two should get together. Why?
Just having fun.
Yeah, but friends,
go on. Get up there. I'm going to record
you, bro. Go on. Go
on. Go on, son. Go on. Go
on. Wait, mate. W. Listen.
Tell them what happened last week. We
met last week. Remember? Tell them. I'm
not recording you. I'm telling what
happened last week. You scared me. I
didn't scare you. What are you talking about?
Damn it. You kept [ __ ] texting me.
sh You are shy.
You tried. You converting me. You tried Yes, you
did. You tried converting me to Muslim.
That's how you tried it. Yes, you
[ __ ] did. Why you walking away then?
Yeah. You tried converting me to Islam.
Yeah, you did. Yes, you did.
And cuz I wouldn't get cuz I wouldn't
circum cuz I wouldn't circumc by
Willie. What's that?
Dr. Two for one coffee. Okay. What was
one? Two for one. Okay. Tell them what you want.
I want some
shots. You get two for one.
It's normal now. Yeah. Let's get two.
Let's get two double ramen coats. Yeah.
Two double Roman CS. I'll pay for you.
Yeah. And you're going to get some [ __ ] today.
Yeah. I think you've already booked,
mate. You've already booked. Yeah. Right.
When money's no object, mate. When money
is no object.
When money is no [ __ ]
object. When money is no
object. 23 quid gone.
23. Let me put the call in. [Music]
This is my last night out before my
passport buying. I'm getting my passport
renewed tomorrow, so I want to make the
most of it with my
friends. Oh, yeah.
Hey, good. Take it. Take it. Thank you, D. There's
23. Yeah, trying to be bad. We got money to burn,
bro. You got money to burn.
I'm on live YouTube.
Talk to me. I'm not showing you. Tell me
what you want. What do you want? No, don't do
that. You're lucky. 22,00
You need to go and get some women. I
[ __ ] got [ __ ] scream in front of
you. Yeah. Come on. Push it
off. There you go. I think you too. You
too. Come when you can. When you can. I
love it. I love
Burn over there. Go over there. Over there. Hey.
Easy. Over there. Over there. Go
on. When money is no object. When money
is no object. Tell them. Tell them. Tell
them. Bro. When money is no object. Tell
them. Tell them. Money is no object.
Money is no object. Wait. That's what
you need to tell us. Yes sir.
We don't care about
money. No objects.
Yes, mate. I'll never be skipped. Mr. B,
I got 3k today, mate. I get 3.3K a
month. Listen, Mr. B. Mr. be I get 3.3K
a month, right? We don't care about money.
3.3K. We don't care about money, mate.
Tell them money is no object. I do care
because I am in debt. I'm not [Music]
intend to pay my debt. You're there. I'm
paying there. I'm no objecting.
All way. Easy, easy, boy. You're
welcome. Tell them I got that girl's
number. Tell everyone on YouTube how
many how many people
say how many numbers?
We're going to renew our passport. We
going America again. I'm going to
America again. Are you? Yeah. Yeah. When
I do this
pass, you're coming with me. Yeah. You are. Why
not? Why don't you come with me?
Huh? Come to
Boston. Come to
Boston. No. Come to Boston. Why not?
No. Me and you will go. Have you got a pass
for America? We're going to America. All
of us. Yeah.
No. Let's stop. Let's
Hey, I told you money is no object, bro.
It doesn't matter.
I got two numbers. Got two numbers. I
got two. I got
two. Look at that. Babe, money is no object.
No, you don't know [Music]
where. Come here. Come
Why didn't you want to get with me?
Honestly, I didn't want to get with you.
You wanted to get with me. You didn't
want to get Yeah, because I was over there.
Why should I have to do her? That's
racist. That's racist. You didn't want
to. You're racist. Walking away. He
wants me to convert to Muslim. I'm not
converting. You know what? You're not
Muslim. She wanted me to convert. I'm not
converting to get with me. She wanted me
to convert to Muslim. I'm not
converting. No. [ __ ] You know what I'm
saying? No way.
She want me to convert to [Music]
Look. Hey, Ethan.
Hey, you can go and talk to some [ __ ]
now. Come on. Oh, there's so many women.
Go and send it. No. I want I want to see
what they do. They're not doing nothing.
You already went over. scared. Yeah.
No, I saw I
saw a moment.
Hey, there's a lot of burden. Find a
moment with somebody. What? Hi. Are you
okay? You got one woman there. There you
go. She likes
it. She likes you. Why? Yes, she
do. Okay. That's why you keep texting [Music] me.
Listen. If I give you 20, you do it. No.
Okay. How about this? You give me £20,
I'll vote for anyone. No. I'm not
scared, bro. You're scared? No. I know
that I risk it.
Going over. Come on. Listen. Listen. Come over
here. You go over. Listen. You go over.
Anyone speak to them. I will give you 30 quid.
30. No object. [ __ ] Anyone? No.
Wow. Cuz if you don't cuz if you listen,
you offered me £30. Now I'm blowing.
I'll give [ __ ] 100. I'm going
The thing is, bro, you need to work on
your confidence because this is going to
haunt you. You're scared. I told you,
bro. I would do it. If you're a coach,
I'll Okay. If I do it, would you give me
money? I'll do it. No, I'll do it. I
know you'll do it. You know how to do
it. That's what I do.
Okay. Just doing a punch. I go. I want
you to get
another number. I want you to get a
I got two numbers already. Come
on. You scared? Yeah. Why? I don't like
how many of you
object I just paid £22
on you know I said I offered him £30.
I'm not following you. I offered him £30
to go against
any he said. I said, "Okay, if I do it,
you give me
and that's that's how you know I'm a crazy." Yeah. face.
We're going to say and we're going to
dance like the next round. People are
[ __ ] on the floor sitting on the chair. Exactly.
I thought like Easy. Come here. Sorry about
hey the next round. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I say 23,000. Yes.
[ __ ] got butterfly. [Music]
You're going to get a number today.
You're [ __ ] mate. If you don't, I'm
gonna floor. Yeah. Hey.
Hey, mate. Get us another drink. I'm
drunk. Listen. We've been on it since 4 hours. [Music]
No, no, it's not.
It's two hours. There you go. Over
there. Come on,
[ __ ] It's run close. Run close. Yeah. Yeah. Go.
I'm way too
stuck. Way too bad. Don't like it.
[ __ ] out of there, mate.
You [ __ ] No, don't touch my face.
Don't touch my Don't touch me. Don't
touch me. I'm not
touch. Don't touch me. Okay, I'm going
to let you try. That's massaging me.
Hey, don't touch the phone. [ __ ] off.
You're going to have to pay for it. tell you listen. Yeah. What [ __ ]
look? I don't. No.
No. You're not [ __ ] up. She got the
same name as you. No. No. No. No.
Honestly, you're trying your [ __ ] You
ain't done. Babe, listen. I've done
eight of postes today. He
only look right. It's mine. Yeah,
exactly. No, do it myself. I offered him
money. I offered him money to do it and
he would do it. Yeah, he's you talking
to you. I can dance right now. Can you
dance right now? Yeah, I don't need I'm
going to wait until like
9:00. Hey, listen. Listen. Don't call
them. Don't call
them over there. Don't call them,
please. Who that lie?
You want me to dance? Yeah. Okay. Go and
approach a woman. I'll dance with you.
You tell him to approach first and I'll go. Yeah. Go.
You think I'm scared of God? Okay. I
approach a woman by yourself and I'll
dance with you all night long.
No, you [ __ ] didn't. No, you [ __ ]
didn't. No. By yourself. By yourself. Go on.
Go. I'll dance with them all night long.
Go over there.
Fun. It's fun. It's fun. Go over there
and I'll dance.
I'll talk to you
now. Who's scared
of? Who's scared now? Who's scared now?
You want to dance with me? I don't know
how to dance. Huh?
I want Can we dance
together? I want to dance with you. Listen,
I will dance with him, but he needs to post.
You turn out 30 quid.
You said you're in debt, but you won't
post 30. I'm done, bro.
I drink. That's why
[ __ ] for 30 quid. 30
quid for 30 quid.
Can't lie to that boy.
I got two numbers. You need to send this. No way.
Arsenal box, you're a [ __ ] [ __ ]
I've gone to your area two times. I've
gone to your area two times, you little
[ __ ] And you didn't come
out. I went to your area a few times.
You little [ __ ] And you didn't come
out. You're [ __ ] [ __ ] you and
[ __ ] that. I went to this country area
two times for [ __ ] didn't come out. He's a
[ __ ] [ __ ] you and [ __ ]
James. Get the [ __ ] out. Awesome. [Music]
Come here. Come here. Come here. Come
A [ __ ] Tell them
what is a [ __ ] Tell
them the [ __ ]
The [ __ ] [ __ ] over there. Arsenal Arsenal.
I don't support football.
Why do you support Arsenal?
Arsenal. A [ __ ] Argus.
He's a [ __ ]
man. He's a [ __ ] I meant to
be a [ __ ] [Laughter]
It's getting a bit chopper
block. It's getting a bit cha block, mate. [Music]
Go. Busy. It's getting busy. Pick it up. Yeah.
Go on, mate. Go on, son. [Music] [Laughter] Yeah.
What the hell? [Music] [Laughter]
Hey, listen. Mark Samson, you're in your
50s and you're a
[ __ ] How about that, Arsenal Mark?
You're in your 50s and you're a [ __ ]
baldy prick [ __ ] When you meet me
tomorrow, you can come
on. Arsenal Mark, you're in your 50s and
you're a [ __ ] baldy [ __ ] Time to
make you look good, [ __ ]
Thanks. Get some pictures. We're going
to get some pictures.
Arsenal Mark, you I've been to your area
two times. Haty Rick, you're a [ __ ]
You don't come out. You balding wick. Little poke
head. A [ __ ] You're [ __ ] [Music] [Laughter]
What the [ __ ] Yeah. Introduction. [Music]
Go over there. sir. Go.
[ __ ] go over. [Music]
I only got three numbers. Hey over Go
easy. Come on. Okay,
look at you two love bird. Okay. [Music] away. Hey Hold on.
I need to go. I need to die. [Music] I'm
coming. Wait, give me a
minute. Wait, I'm coming. I'm coming.
coming. I'm coming. Wait. I'm coming.
I'm going to talk to you. Give me 10
seconds. Give me one minute. I'm coming.
coming. I love it. I love it. All right. I'm coming.
I'm confident enough to step in.
Yeah. Let's go. Come on.
Say goodbye to everyone.