One second.
Biski briski. I need some [ __ ] Oh [ __ ]
this, bro. I think that's another thing
to add on to how the country is [ __ ] as well.
Definitely. That's another thing to add
on to death, man.
Oh [ __ ] I got that thing as well.
I thought I did know what the [ __ ] I was saying, but
it's clear as day what they do, bro.
They favor nons and women.
Do you not see that? Do you not see the combination?
Uh, oh [ __ ]
Yeah, bro. Definitely.
I'll be putting my foot down tomorrow.
100%, bro. Definitely. Now, hold on. Jesus.
Yeah, man. That's another thing to add. what's
[ __ ] up about this country.
Also, I find it mad how like you'll get
these people on Instagram,
they'll be so fast to like start [ __ ]
Yeah. Um but then they'll report you to
the police as well. I've noticed that as
well as they love doing it actually. Yeah.
Another form of victimizing. What's that?
Yeah, they generally generally generally
do have their favorites in this country.
That was that was the first thing in the
morning, bro. They generally generally
generally are still trying to figure
this [ __ ] out. I was asking my mom. I was like,
"Oh, bro, I've got a headache." It's
it's some form of racism. Maybe it's
something not right there. like we need
to speak to someone higher up to understand
um what the problem is,
you know, but again, they're always
going to have their favorite. So, I
mean, there it's no point stressing
over, but I couldn't believe the
audacity of it. I told her you like you
can't play I told her that you can't
play two sides of a coin.
You know what I'm saying? Like, you
can't play two sides of a coin. But I've
got that video thing tomorrow.
And if they don't remind me, then I'm
just going to have to call into the new
address cuz yeah, something is being
done here now, bro. 100%. [ __ ] this.
They're trying to take a [ __ ] piss.
Honestly, they are. And that's why
people hate them. Oh, here we go. So,
I've got one tomorrow
and we will see see you by appointment.
So, what is it? Is it a face to face one
or do they call you?
What is that appointment then? Hold on.
I've never had one of them before.
Maybe they'll call you, I'm guessing. Um,
yeah, [ __ ] knows. I can't move. Yeah.
And he's like, "Oh, this is a different
thing." I was like, "It's not a
different thing, bro, cuz you're
contradicting your [ __ ] self. Stop
contradicting yourself." Literally, stop
contradicting yourself, bro. Stop
playing two sides of a coin. Like, are
you involved or are you not involved?
Like, you know what I'm saying? They're
[ __ ] They're just They're just
[ __ ] racist, bro. I swear to [ __ ]
God, bro. They're really racist. And And
And you know what they are? It's not Yeah,
I don't think now they change the
[ __ ] appointment again.
They'll get a right someday they'll
help when it's literally like self-explanatory favorites racism just justly everything
it literally litally
literally is everything
they literally generally generally
generally generally You do it. And now
it's a complete
to the other. That generally generally
is what it actually seems like.
Well, no, it's not what it seems like.
It's It's what it is.
That's what it is. [Music] Private number one sec.
I can't believe this, bro.
And they're contradicting as well.
That's the funniest thing that when they
contradict themselves because they'll
tell you all of these reasons why they
can't get themselves involved over
social media. Oh, it's Instagram. Oh,
it's Facebook. Oh, it's wherever
whatever the platform it is you're using.
But then when somebody reports you,
they're up your ass again. So, I mean,
make it make sense. I'll be lying on
them, bro. When that guy calls me, do
you know what? I wasn't even going to
go, but I thought, you know what? I
think I'm going to go now, and I'm going
to [ __ ] start lying it down on them,
bro. I've had enough of them. Yeah. Do
you not want to do you not want to start
giving some of the stuff that you you
took a couple of years ago back before
you start getting yourself involved
again and playing two sides of a [ __ ]
coin? I've had enough of them, bro.
Yeah, I told Antman about it.
Yeah, I told Antman about it now.
They literally have their favor, but
they genuinely generally do like it's
actually confirmed now, bro.
Like I said, I thought at the start it
was just a madness and you know people
just would leave them alone. That's why
they done stuff. But no, they generally
Well, that New Zealander replied, didn't she see
She had to [ __ ] reply, bro. The
conversation was too slick, bro.
But no, they generally generally favor
nons and women.
Oh, yeah. She replied, "It only took two days."
They literally have their favorites. You
know, I'm going to go to that voluntary
interview, bro. I really, really am
going to go there, bro. But you know
what? I'm going to say to the guy on the
phone, I'm just going to keep going on
about my problems. So, I mean, there's
not no real point. There's not no real
point of me actually being there because
I'm just going to keep going on about my
problems. Stop playing two sides of a
coin. You're either involved or you're
not involved. Which one is it? [ __ ] idiots, bro.
Yeah, I knew she had to reply, bro, cuz
the conversation was too good. But know
that whole police thing is a joke. And
you know, when I was working like,
"Okay, they're not too bad. Let's just
call it as as a oneoff and take the L.
They got there before you." But no, now
even that man says, "No, it definitely
don't seem that way now." It definitely
definitely does seem that way now.
Yeah. I'm going I'm going to have to lay
on thick really really bad tomorrow,
probably in two days. And then when when
they call me cuz there's no point saying
you're not going to go and then they try
coming and arresting you and then you're
just going to complain to them anyways.
Just [ __ ] stick it on them. This is
what I was going to do last time, but it
wasn't over that.
It wasn't over social media. So, it was
over [ __ ] with like my bubble and that
cuz this is really really really got to stop.
Really, really, really, really, really
got to stop, you know. Yeah.
And this is why people hate them. This
is generally generally why people really
hate them. I used to make jokes stuff
like, "Oh, piggy piggy, you're a like I
used to just make jokes and didn't
really have any problems with them
because I don't I put it down to like,
okay, well, I don't really have any
problems with them because I don't have
dealings with them." But
you the day somebody is sitting next to
some sitting there telling you about how
they can't report this and how they
can't report that and or how they can't
do anything because of social media.
Then you've got a completely different
person reported you 7 months ago on
Instagram for the smallest thing and
they're up your ass again. Bro,
something needs to really really really
really really really be done. Trust me
cuz it's it's not normal, bro. Just just
tell us what it is. Is it racism? Is it
the name? Is it really what? Cuz we're
going to come to these conclusions where
we can't figure this [ __ ] out.
So it we need to really That's what the
whole I'm going to make a whole
interview about that. You know that.
And why do these people do that start on
Instagram if they're just going to
report you to the police anyways? What's
the [ __ ] point? The country is
[ __ ] Our whole law system is [ __ ]
now. You know, is there anything normal
about this country? Well, I've got the
appointment right here. Yeah. Simple.
What's the date on it?
But it doesn't seem that way. It
literally is that way.
It It is that way. I don't know what it is.
They must favor a certain kind of kind
of people, women and pedos. That that's
that's literally what it's it has to be.
It has to be something something like
that, bro. It's nothing your race, your
name. I don't know what it is, but we're
going to find out what it is, bro.
You know, don't sit there and try and
tell me how I got told to come here. By
the way, I couldn't even be bothered
telling me how like you can't report
this that this that this that this that
this that this that and the other. And
I'm going to make sure when I go there,
when eventually I do need to go there, I
want a Merlin on my I want a Merlin on
my address. Simple. I want a Merlin on
any address that you find. I want a
Merlin cuz you clearly can't be bothered
to deal with anything else. So, stop
coming up my ass, you know. And I and
I'll say it to them continuously,
continuously, continuously. I said
there's no point me being there cuz I'm
just going to cause a scene.
That just pissed me off this morning.
That actually pissed me off, bro. It
really really pissed me off. I swear to
God, it's annoying as [ __ ]
Annoying. That is. God, that is so
[ __ ] annoying. Can't you leave people
alone? Can't you let people just move
house and live their life?
You know what I'm saying, bro? But no,
you can't do that. Doesn't matter that
you're not arresting people. You should
not be getting involved.
Yeah. You shouldn't even be making them
threats. You You clearly are not
interested in social media. You've
stated it many times. Yeah. Well, when
when I report, but then when someone else
It's [ __ ] weird, bro. [ __ ] who the
[ __ ] am I arguing with on Instagram?
And it's like, I'm making it your
investigation. You're trying to make it
that you're trying to say that it's a
separate one. Well, I'm going to make it
this one 100%. Yeah, I'm going to make
it this one 100 million%.
You know, I'd love to just not go and
then just smack them up if they're
trying to arrest me, but really and
truly, like, it's just not going to
prove anything. You just should just go
there and just lie down on them. That's
what I'm doing.
Yeah. And that's it, bro. Like, and I
will do it. I will do it, bro. The only
reason I didn't do it last time is
because it wasn't even over that. It was
over my mom. So, I thought, "Oh, fuck."
Do you know what? The last time I went,
I think it was last
November. No, it was December. I
remember we was talking about the whole
like Christmas presents and [ __ ] right?
Yeah. And um I said, "Mate, if this is
over any form of social media, bro, I'm
going to go [ __ ] mad." Like I
remember I was talking cuz obviously
they claim they can't do anything about
social media but they're so far up your
ass when someone reports you. They're up
your ass out your mouth, right? And it's
getting boring now. Yeah. And then it
was like, "Oh, it's about your mom." So
I was like, "Okay, fair enough." Then it
was just like something else. But now
I'm I'm going to be lying it down for
the condemn. And I'm also going to be
bringing up on that video call as well.
You either the law either applies for
everyone or no one. So which one is it?
Which one generally generally is it? You know,
we got to find out the the the truth
behind this is because this is not
normal, bro. It really really is not normal.
Just [ __ ] I had to go. You're going
to laugh at this, bro. Yeah,
you're going to laugh at this. Really
going to laugh at this. So, the police
were supposed to come around um in a
couple days, but obviously I'm moving
and [ __ ] So, they told me to go to the
police station and report this thing.
So, I thought, "Okay, I'm out now. I had
some food. Let me go to the police
station." Right. And you're going to
laugh at this. They were like, "Oh, um
yeah, report it to Instagram. Report it
to this. Report it to YouTube." Like,
any excuse as usual why they can't deal
with anything when Peter Belly report I
literally got told to report it. Like,
they literally I had to go there. Yeah.
And then the police officer comes. Yeah.
And he's like, "Oh, you, Peter? I've
never met this guy in my life. These are
these these pigs are are are corrupt,
bro. I'm telling you." Yeah. And he was
like, "Oh, yeah. Uh, yeah. We're not
going to arrest you, but you need to um
come come in for a uh voluntary inter."
I said, "You you what?" I said, "What?
What do you mean a voluntary interview?"
He said, "We're not going to arrest
you." And there's like, "Oh, yeah.
Something to do with a woman on
Instagram many many months ago. It's not
serious." I'm thinking, hold on. You've
just said to me that you can't do
anything even though I've reported so
many time and time and time and time and
time again coming from here to [ __ ]
to Australia and you're trying to tell
me that I need to come in over the same
thing that you're telling me that you
can't report. I said, "You know what?
Yeah, do your worst and [ __ ] arrest
me cuz I ain't coming." Right. Simple.
[ __ ] this this time. But then I changed
and then I changed my mind and thought,
"You know what? Yeah, you should go
there and I'm going to make the whole
thing about me." That's what I'm going
to do. I'm going to make the whole thing
about me because eventually that's going
to that will happen when you get
arrested. Anyways, yeah. I told the
woman, you can't play two sides of a
coin, right? You have bothered me years
and years and years and years and years
and years over social media, right?
Years and years and years. And I said, I
don't care if it's a separate
investigation. I'm making it my
investigation now. And I'm making it all
about me. So, when he calls me and he
invites me, I'll come. Well, I'm going
to make the whole thing about me and I'm
going to make a big fat complaint. I've
got I've got a I've got a thing coming
out. Um, they need to call me in two in
two days and I'm really going to lie the
fit down on them, bro. I'm telling you
cuz this has got to stop. Yeah. So, what
if you argue with somebody on Instagram
months and months ago? It's got nothing
to do with this community. And is that
any of your business? You said that you
can't deal with stuff to do with social
media, pig. That's why. And you know
what? Yeah. The last time I put it down
to, okay, somebody just reported me more
times. Um, they gave the police grief
and I just put it down to an L. And I
thought, okay, the police are not really
that bad. But now it it really is
favorism that now that even Antman said
like now it is cuz Antman like changed
my mind on that. He said, "Oh, maybe the
person reported you more times." This is
a completely different person who was
reporting me once and they're up my ass
again. You know, it doesn't matter if if
they're going to arrest you that they're
not going to arrest you. That's
irrelevant. I should not be dealing with
you the same reason you don't want to
deal with me when I report stuff. Simple
[ __ ] pigs, racist pigs, time and time again.
Like, so I'm going to I will know
everything to say in two days. I'll be
like, listen, this has been reported numerous times
and um you know, and and I I got bored
of doing it, but they just kept telling
me to do it. So,
and also a weirder thing is why do these
women start [ __ ] on Instagram and then
run to the police
victimizing? But that doesn't even
matter anyways. All [ __ ] But, and I
know I wouldn't have said anything that
bad anyways. So, cuz they're saying that
was from months and months and months
ago and it's not serious. So, why are
you getting yourself involved? Why can't
you leave people alone? You're clearly
not interested when someone else is
reporting stuff. where people almost got
killed and people got their bike stolen.
So, but you could do all that stuff.
Don't go and then try to arrest you and
smash them up. But in reality, that's
not going to solve anything. You just
need to literally just
you need to like really lie down hard on
them, bro. And you need to really speak
to someone high up because this is racism that
this is really this is a problem. I was
telling my mom about this now. Yeah.
This is generally something is up here,
bro. I'm telling you because it's not
normal how you can have all these things
done to you over the years, report it,
and they claim they can never do
anything because it's social media,
which is the woman was saying, and then
you got somebody next door saying that
they want to invite you to involuntary
interview over social media. Make it
make sense. Which one is it? You can't
play and she's like, "Oh, I'm not
playing two sides of a coin." You are
playing two sides of a coin. That is literally all
you're doing. Yeah. Law for another.
That is what it is in this sexist racist country. it is. So,
do you know what I'm saying? What the [ __ ]
Um, so I'm going to say to him as well
when he invites me. I'm just going to
keep showing him my phone
saying not interested. Not interested.
Do something about these people. Not
interested. Reported. I'm just going to
be a [ __ ] the whole way through. So
there's is there really a point to be I
will come. I am going to come, but I'm
just going to be an awkward bastard.
So it's like there's just no point.
Which I would have done last time if it
was actually over social media, but it
was over my mom. I'll be like, "Oh,
report to Instagram. Instagram. Yeah.
Yeah. We can't. This is This is not a
police, man. I'm just going to be a [ __ ]
the whole way through. There's just
literally no point in me even going
there because Yeah. You [ __ ] dirty
racist pigs. Dirty [ __ ] That's what
they are, bro. They really, really,
really are. They're dirt. They're dirty,
bro. They're racist. [ __ ] racist.
No, I I know I sound like a black person
that's getting stopped and certain my
race, but this is generally racism. This
generally is racism at its finest, and
it's sexism as well. And it's still
weird. I think I might have said the
worst thing is like, "Oh, maybe your kids [Music]
They're [ __ ] racist, bro. We're going
to get We're going to They definitely
definitely are. They definitely
definitely definitely are. And he says
that he's going to um he's going to say
that he's uh he's going to say that he's
um so this was a random womanized. She
said, "Oh, it's something you said to a
woman and another woman's witnessed it."
But again, you've just said that you you
you're telling me to report stuff that
these people are doing to social media
on social media like Instagram. And I'll
be like, "I reported it and reported and
reported it." So, I've got this
appointment in two uh days cuz obviously
they can't come to the house cuz I'm
moving. And yeah, I'm going to lie down
on them really hard, bro, cuz this has
got to stop.
Like, so yeah, they're definitely um
but normally when they've got like when
they when they're being prejudiced,
normally it's it's a big YouTuber that's
like pissing the police off. Normally
it's like somebody keep pissing the
police off and getting under their skin
and they need to find any ways to get
them. This is more like they've got favorites.
You understand? This is more like not
trying to make an example. It's more of
they've got favorites.
That's what I'm saying, bro. But it
doesn't seem anyone listens cuz there's
big YouTubers that [ __ ] with the police
and the police will continuously watch
them and then they will they'll wait for
them to [ __ ] up and then they'll get
them. But here it seems like they have literally favorites.
Like it's not even about making example.
It's just having favorites. [ __ ]
they're racist as [ __ ] Racist pigs.
That's what they are, bro.
And then you're telling me to respect a
bunch of racist sexist people? Really,
bro? Come on.
So, it's Yeah,
maybe they look up that maybe
maybe they target you cuz they think
that you're vulnerable or something
something's not right there. Yeah, I'm
sure we'll get to the bottom of it one
day, but something's definitely not right there
cuz you're you find any excuse to get
involved with social media when it's to
do with me. You love getting involved
with social media when it's to do with me.
But then when it's other people, oh, you
can't do it because you need to report
it to this or you need to report it to
that. Like practice what you preach. I'm
going to tell them about that. I'm going
to tell them a million times about that
as well. When a guy finally calls me
because the way I see it is you're
trying to put stress on me now. I'm
moving. I'm doing all of these things.
Doesn't matter if you're not arresting
me. You're still bothering me.
How are they racist? Well, it's
something. What? How is it? How is it
racist? Cuz I don't have an English
second name. I don't look fully English
and it is something. It's definitely definitely something.
It definitely definitely something where
it's not right there, bro. I'm telling you.
So, we're going to get to the bottom of
it. And I'm going to say to them as
well, if you don't do anything, I'm just
going to make a big fat complaining. And
I'm saying to them that I'm talking to
them because it's like, you're fast
enough to keep bothering me over
nonsense, silliness, [ __ ] even what
you you said it yourself months and
months and months ago. Something that's
not serious. [ __ ] off then. Go catch a
[ __ ] rapist. Go catch a [ __ ] murderer.
You know about you're not playing two
sides of a coin. You are playing two
sides of a coin. Yeah, let me finish.
Yeah, you know what I'm saying? [ __ ] idiots.
But you don't look for It's something.
It's definitely something, bro.
Cuz if somebody reported me now, mate,
they'd be on my [ __ ] door.
So it's there's something there's
something not right there, bro.
And you don't even have a big YouTube
channel. So it's not even like the
police can have a vender because it's
not even like So it's definitely
that's also the the conclusion that I've
come to as well even if you look at like
the sentences and stuff as well. So,
but yeah, bro. It's uh
and there's also crime reference numbers
as well, so they can't even say that
you've not reported it. So,
yeah, we need to get to the B
in 2025. Still bothering people, but you
don't want to get involved in it.
Someone else reporting. [ __ ] stupid
idiots, bro. What the [ __ ]
It's be one rule for one. One rule for
another. But it's one law for one. One
law for another. But yeah, in that whole
interview, I'm just going to be awkward as [ __ ]
I'm just going to be like, it's social
media. What am I here for? You told me
I'm just going to be an awkward bastard.
Awkward awkward [ __ ] That's what I'm
going to be.
And I'm going to report um at the
counter as well, bro. Trust me, I'm
That pissed me off. Pissed me off.
I can actually see why my dad stabbed
one in the eye. I can actually see why,
you know? I can actually see why like he
actually done that. They're [ __ ] aggravating.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah, I can
understand people are drunk and you know
people do it and they're annoying, but I
can see why he actually done that now. I
wish he was [ __ ] alive, man. I would
have [ __ ] bought him a [ __ ] beer
for it. They're [ __ ] aggravating. I
bet they weren't so cocky then, were
they? When they were picking up their
[ __ ] eye out their [ __ ] face.
[ __ ] aggravating [ __ ]
I'm starting to really hate them again,
bro. Really hate them again. Oh my god.
The other one I put it down to experience, but
[ __ ] stupid aggravating cent. We're
supposed to respect sexist people.
You know what I'm saying?
Why? And man's like, why why are they
inviting you for voluntary interviews?
It's because it's not bad enough to get
arrested and because they're racist and sexist.
That's the answer. Yeah.
This is It's not bad enough for them to
rescue. But again, they have to make
people's life hard, but we'll get to the
bottom of it anyways, bro. It doesn't matter.
He said, "You can't even tell you're
caught Turkish." Of course, you can, man.
Can't even tell that you're quarter Turkish.
You [ __ ] can. I don't look fully
white, but there's something not right
there, bro. I mean, look at my [ __ ]
surname, bro. It's not [ __ ] English, is it? Voluntary interviews.
Crazy, isn't it? They need to leave
people alone, bro. They seriously just
Oh my god. They don't want to get
involved, bro. When other people do
stuff, they're [ __ ] idiots, bro. What
is it, bro?
Yeah, [ __ ] them, bro. Trying to threaten
me. Yeah, I I went in to follow a
report, but it's okay. When he calls me,
I'll be lying it on him as well. Yeah,
I'll be saying I will be coming there
and I will be showing you everything.
Yeah, you're not going to [ __ ]
threaten to arrest me. I don't know what
I'm going to say as well
because eventually like they're going to
I'll be in contact with them again
anyway so I might as well go.
I think the only way you're going to get
get rid of them is leaving the country
like because they obviously s seriously
have a problem with you.
They don't want to get involved with and
this is a completely different person.
You know what I'm saying? Why are you
getting yourself involved? You don't
want to get yourself involved with
social media when other people report stuff,
you know, so why are you, you know,
trying to Yeah. He says that, "Oh, yeah,
you Peter. Don't even know how he knew
who the [ __ ] I was. [ __ ] get the [ __ ]
off my ass, bro." You know what I'm
saying? You [ __ ] annoying bastard.
They're annoying, bro.
[ __ ] bent system. But then Joe F
wonders why people hate police. This was
like 8:00 in the morning as well, bro.
8:00 in the morning. No word of a lie.
8:00 in the morning, I went to Greg's. I
went to the police station
to follow up with a report, which is
what I got told to do. Yeah.
And then they're trying to say, "Well,
this is a different thing." And they
said, "It doesn't matter. You're
contradict. You're contradicting
yourself." You know what I'm saying? So
So yeah, man. Something really, really,
really does need to get done about this. Seriously, bro.
So what if you argue with someone on
Instagram? So what?
It's social media. No. The [ __ ]
[ __ ] favorites. Them and their
favorites. E, it's like having a child
as a favorite, isn't it?
They really, really, really do have
favorites in this country, matey.
The only thing that could be justified
is if it's to do with that Morgan, you
know, if it's to do with that Morgan. Um,
obviously we we done a lot of [ __ ] to
her. But if it ain't, then
yeah, but either way, I'm still going to
go mad anyways because I've reported
nothings, mate. I've got about 200
[ __ ] screenshots on my [ __ ] phone
on a different folder.
But I don't think it is. I think it's
that person when I when I said, "Oh,
your child's ugly." I think I know
exactly who it is, you know. So, yeah.
And I want you to tell me the exact
crime and I want you to uh to tell me
why am I here and why do you keep
bothering me? Oh, and where are my
devices that you also took as well? Yeah,
[ __ ] idiots, mate. You know, I can
see myself really going to prison one day, bro.
Really, really do. I can actually see it
because of them. Like, and it's not
good, bro. It's not a good thing to to
to think of. But the thing is, bro,
you're trying to get away with your
life. Yeah. You have no involvement with
these people. You don't break the law.
you work. You don't do anything illegal.
[ __ ] You don't do anything illegal. And
they still find excuses to bother you
when, like you said, you're trying to
help them with their inquiries.
It's so mad, bro. Like,
and it ain't nice, bro. It ain't nice.
You know, like these people haven't even
got a warning. I don't know how many
people I've reported in my life. [ __ ]
knows. But I know they've never as much
as got a warning. Ever. They've never as
much as got a warning. Yeah. As soon as
you [ __ ] say something to some some
[ __ ] they'll wh your [ __ ] ass.
We need to get to the bottom of this.
Anyways, that's on
that's on the 17th.
So [ __ ] man.
Yeah, that New Zealander replied.
She had to reply, bro. The conversation
was so good.
She doesn't look that doesn't matter.
Hey then, bro.
No, nothing to do with that.
Nothing to do with that. But I'm going
to be lying on hard with these the the
these police officers when I finally
have to go there cuz it seems like it is
one rule for one and one rule for
another, you know, and I'm going to I'm
going to make several complaints. It's a
completely different person.
So, I'm going to really need to be lying
it really really on hard now, bro. I
couldn't believe the cheek of it. And it
was and it was a complete different
person as well. You [ __ ] racist bastards.
And he's saying that, "Oh yeah, we won't
arrest you. You can just come in because
he see me." But no, don't worry, bro.
I'll be coming in anyways.
Yeah. And I'm going to make it all about
me. That's what I'm going to do, man.
I'm going to make it all cuz I'm sick of
them. I'm I'm quite frankly sick of
being targeted by them time and time and
time and time and time and time and time
and time and time again. Being sick of
targeted by these people. You know what I'm saying?
You know what I mean? had to deal with
one some cunt's attitude on the phone
yes the other day and and he was like,
"Oh, the Statford one's not um open for
the public." I said, "Well, yes it is."
You know, cuz I know cuz I live there
and he's just being an awkward [ __ ] on
the phone. Anyways, like it's corrupt.
The whole system's corrupt, bro. It is.
It is. They've been doing this for
years. It [ __ ] is. They're [ __ ] ra
like and I'm going to ask them as well
like no swearing no like are you are you
racist or what what is it like tell me
what I'm I want to understand you know
and I'm sick of trying I'm sick of
driving myself insane trying to
understand is it racism is it sexism
yeah he was like oh he was like oh it's
not open to the public I said well it is
open to the public cuz I live here and
And I know cuz I've been there. And he
was trying to give like proper attitude
on the phone and that like I was like
[ __ ] I was like half asleep like bro
sort it out man. [ __ ] corrupt pigs. Yeah.
So yeah man they're [ __ ] idiots. But
yeah I'll be lying it down thick on them
on the 17th anyways. Bro,
they're [ __ ] racist. But it like at
the end of the day it doesn't matter how
many times you do it. They're still
going to just have their favorites.
Anyways, that's the thing.
I think that's one of the reasons I come
off social media, you know, bro, because
they kept targeting me on remember when
I stopped coming on social media. It's
cuz they keep targeting you, bro, and
they find any reason to get involved.
Any little excuse.
It's I'd love to know what it is, bro. I
don't even think a solicitor could tell
me what it is, you know?
Let's wait for the call.
And I'll be like, "Yeah, I'm I'm I'm
going to be coming, but it's just going
to all be about me, me, me, me, me, me,
me, me, me. So, there's no point you
asking this, that, and the other because
I'm not answering any of your questions.
[ __ ] off. Simple.
I'm going to be asking you the [ __ ] questions, [ __ ]
understand this, bro.
Really, really, really understand it.
Racism, sexism. It's something, bro.
It's definitely something this time. I
thought I was overreacting last time,
but I don't think I was, you know. So
I think that's even a bigger reason to
leave this country to be honest because
of the whole system you know
you know what I mean
so I've got this person um calling me
so yeah and it's the same thing. If you
if you was to go to a police officer, a
police station, we can't do this because
of that, we can't do this because of
this, we can't do that because of them.
You know, you hear all the excuses in
the [ __ ] world why they can't deal
with anything that you report cuz
they're racist and sexist, right? But
then when someone else reports you,
they're up your ass. So it's like
we need to yeah we need to understand we
need to really really understand this you know
so a woman started on Instagram they
argued back with her and your point okay
and your involvement is Mr. I can't deal
with anything that's to do with social
media. And your point is
cheeky. That is so cheeky. That is
even though you're not going to go
caught or get arrested, it's it's the
cheek of it, bro. They're [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] They're corrupt. They
are corrupt as [ __ ] Corrupt as [ __ ]
You know, even when you take the L's,
they [ __ ] are, bro. I love my dad for
taking one of their eyes out. [ __ ]
legend. [ __ ] absolute legend. Weren't
so I wonder how many people they were
telling to whine their neck in when they
were [ __ ] stabbed in their face with
a [ __ ] knife. I wonder how how brave
they were then.
I wonder how brave they were then.
Probably not very brave when you were
picking your [ __ ] eye up from your
from the [ __ ] far. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] nonsloving [ __ ] sexist bastards.
And don't don't get me wrong, they're
sexist as well, bro. Don't get it wrong.
They're also sexist as well. They're not
just doing the law. They are sexist.
They are sexist, bro.
Rather you than to me, mate.
Rather you than to me.
It's not the fact that it's serious or
it's not serious or the fact that you're
not arresting anyone.
You should not be interfering with me.
You understand? Yeah.
Yeah. Rather you than to me, mate. I
don't even gamble anymore. Rather you
than to me. Going to go see King in a bit.
Why don't they just leave people alone?
You're not interested, bro. [ __ ]
Leave people alone. You don't leave
people alone, do they?
Why don't you leave me alone?
system as [ __ ] bro.
Rather you than me, mate.
I'm going to get the fold seven soon, I
think, cuz my phone's going to pack up. So,
uh, so basically, right, you're going to
laugh at this. So, I followed up this
report of this stalker, which is what
I've been doing for ages. Uh, and
basically they arranged me appointment
date and obviously I couldn't make the
appointment date because I'm moving and
[ __ ] So, um, basically,
um, I I spoke to the guy on the phone.
He had a nasty attitude problem, but we
got there in the end. And they said,
basically, you need to go in and report.
So, can you go tomorrow and report
report it? So, I've gone into the police
station, reporting it for the millionth
time because that's what they've told me
to do. They're like, "Oh, we can't you
need to report it to YouTube. We report
it to uh in uh you need to report to
Instagram. We can't do anything about
that." I said, "Hold on a minute. One
second. One second. So, you're playing
two sides of a coin. So, you can only
deal with things on social media when
it's to do when it suits yourself."
She's like, "Oh, I'm not playing two
sides of a coin." And I said, "Well, you
literally are playing two sides of a
coin because how many people how many
times have you been on someone's door
over silliness on social media, yet
you're telling me that I need to report
stuff to social media?" You need to tell
yourselves that before coming on
people's door, bothering them, taking
people's devices that you haven't even
given back. Tell yourself that. Don't
tell me that. Tell yourself that. Then
this other officer come out of nowhere.
He said, "Oh, you Peter. I don't even
know who the [ __ ] he was. He's like, "Oh
yeah, we was going to arrest you, but
we're just going to like you can just
come for an involuntary interview
because yeah, you was arguing with some
woman on Instagram." I said, "Hold on a
minute. You're just contradicting
everything that your colleague has just
said. You just said that you can't get
involved with social media when it's
doing me reporting stuff. Yet what?" So
I've argued with someone on Instagram
what, like a year ago, and you're
getting involved again. [ __ ] sexist pigs.
[ __ ] racist sexist pigs.
Yeah. Yeah. So, you're more than happy
to get involved when I'm when I say and
he said, "Oh, it was months and months
and months and months and months ago,
right? And it's not serious. So, why are
you getting involved then?
Why are you not getting involved? And
why are you up my ass again? Do you know
what I'm saying?" And then basically
what it was is uh um they basically I
said, "Oh, I'm not going to go to the
involuntary interview, but there's no
point. I might as well go cuz um and
nons they they protect they protect
nonses as well. Um that's another thing.
Um so uh what basically it is is um I need to um basically
know it's not just the women. It's not
just women. It's it's it's against me
because this has been going for this has
been going on for years and years and
years. So there's no point in me not
going there because I'm going to be in
contact with them again anyways. I'm
just going to go there and just make it
all about me. All about me me.
Yeah, that's what I'm going to do. But
I'm going to lie on them in this phone
interview in two days. I'm going to lie
on them when they call me up again. Yeah.
Simple. So I'm going to really really
really start having to say something
now, bro. Properly.
because it's not like they don't deal
with your report and then don't deal
with theirs, they will literally find
any excuse to harass you, but then when
you report something, they're not interested.
So, it's like that's the that's the most
annoying thing. Like with the other one,
I just took the L and put it down to,
oh, they called the police more times
than me. They done it before me. They
wouldn't leave the police alone. The
police just wanted to get rid of them.
So, but no, they generally have their
favorites now. Like, that says that
literally says it all. They literally
had their favorites.
Like there's there's no doubt about it.
Now at at the start of it with a few
examples, you could have said, "Oh,
well, they got there before you." But
no, they generally have their favorites, bro.
But yeah, I'm going to be contacting
someone higher up about this as well,
bro. Especially about that thing because
it is it is not right. It generally
generally generally is not right that
these people, right?
Yeah. And I don't care if they're
dealing with me. I'm not dealing with
them. So when I'm when I'm in Yeah.
Yeah. I know that's what they'll say.
But what I'm going to be saying in the
interview is I'm not dealing with you
and I'm just going to keep going on
about my problem. I'm going to keep
going on about how I've reported this,
how I've reported that. You don't do
anything. I'm dealing I'm dealing with
you. Yeah. I don't care if you're
dealing with me. I'm dealing with you. I
don't care. Like But I am going to go
there because that's what I'm going to
say is I'm dealing with you. So I don't
care what you're dealing with. I'm
dealing with [ __ ] you. Keep [ __ ]
bothering people every [ __ ] year.
You've got [ __ ] devices you've not
you've not gave back. So I'm dealing
with you and I'm not interested in
anything you've got to deal with in me
until you do something about these
people. It's about time someone start
putting their [ __ ] foot down, mate.
Yeah. Cuz it's been going on for years
and years and years and years and
[ __ ] years and I'm [ __ ] sick of
it. You know, you've told me to go into
a police station to report [ __ ] to help
you with your inquiries. Yeah. So simple.
Yeah. Bro says, "I don't give a [ __ ] if
they'll act like a [ __ ] I'll be the
biggest [ __ ] ever. I literally don't
care. I'll be the biggest [ __ ] ever.
I'll be a big woman's [ __ ] I don't give
a [ __ ] I've had enough of them. I've
literally had enough of how bad they
are." Like, I genuinely just don't care.
I just say I'm not going to answer any
of your questions until you start
dealing with what I've reported and I'm
just going to keep showing them and I'm
not going to say nothing. Simple. So
there's no point the hot there's no
there's literally no point of any of it. You know,
I'm going to say my bit for about 5
minutes and I'm going to shut my mouth.
That's what I'm going to do. Yeah.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] idiots, bro. Yeah.
[ __ ] sexist racist. I've never known
it in my whole life, bro. That's what
I'll do. Yeah. Let them abuse their
power. I don't give a [ __ ] But I'll
just say what I need to say and then
just just I'm not answering any of their questions.
Yeah. [ __ ] stupid racist pigs. Yeah,
that's what I'm going to I said, "You
[ __ ] pigs keep coming on my [ __ ]
door [ __ ] year in year [ __ ] out.
[ __ ] keep bothering me." You know
what I'm saying, bro? Yeah.
Or one of the two. Anyways, but I don't
care. It doesn't matter, bro. That's not
serious. Do you not understand the whole
point? They're bothering me. They're
trying to put me through stress, right?
They're trying to put me through stress.
You at the end of the day, they're
trying to put me through stress. It
doesn't matter if it's voluntary or it's
not serious. It doesn't matter. They Yeah.
Simple. They're in trouble with me. I'm
not in trouble with them. They're in
trouble with me.
I'm They're in trouble with me. I'm not
in trouble with them.
So simple, bro.
Simple, bro. No, no, no. I want to go.
No, I'm going to go. No, I'm going to go
to I am going to go because I want to
go. So, if I get a phone call from this
guy, I am going to go. I am definitely
definitely definitely definitely
definitely going to go.
No, I'm definitely definitely going,
mate, cuz this needs to stop. This
generally generally just needs to stop, bro.
Yeah, I am going to go cuz I'm sick of
them and I'm going to I'm going to be in
contact with them again. So, I I I might
as well go, you know.
Yeah. And trust me, it's not going to be
a pretty sight. Trust me, it's not going
to be a pretty sight cuz these people
have not even got a warning. Not even so
much as a warning on all of the things
that they've done in the whole time
they've been in this house. People
getting a house broken. I'm just going
to go on a big rant. I'm just going to
go on a big big big [ __ ] rant.
And to be honest with you, I I know I I
can probably defend myself more than a
solicitor to be honest with you. So
what? You argued with a random woman on
Instagram and you're and you're you're
bothering me again. you're up my ass
You know what about when this house got
broken into? What about when people
could? What about when the bike got
stolen? What about when the windows got
smashed? What about when somebody almost
got killed? Like, I'm going to bring up
all of this stuff. I'm going to bring up
every single thing, each and every one
of this stuff. And I'm going to be doing
it again in two days.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Like,
that's it. I'm sick of them, bro.
Nope. No threats. And even if and even
if there was threats, remember what they
said? They can't get involved if it's
social media. But whether there were
threats, there weren't threats. And
there wasn't threats either. They said
to me that they can't get involved with
social media. That's generally what they said.
No, no, no. Even there wasn't any
threats. No. Right. But even if there
was, you just said to report things to
social media. You just said that. which
is another thing that I'm going to bring
up that well they can't refresh because
I've showed these people threats and
harassment and gloating and they can't
do anything. So yeah,
they find any excuse to come here.
They've been doing it for years. They've
literally been doing it for years.
You know, practice what you preach. You
just told me, this is what I'm going to
say to him as well again. You just told
me the other day with your colleague
that you can't do anything over social
media. You just said that. You just said
that. I'm not putting I'm not putting
words in your mouth. And then I'll ask
why are we here?
Are you racist? Are you sexist? No, I'm
not gonna be nasty. I'm cuz I'm I'm
curious. I'm I'm curious at this point.
I'm generally generally generally
generally generally curious. I don't
need to go around being violent and
[ __ ] doing all of that stuff. My dad
already done that for me, mate. He
already done that for me.
You know what I'm saying? I don't need
to do any of that [ __ ] My dad already
done that for me, mate. So, I don't I
don't really care what attitude they
give. I don't need to do all that extra
[ __ ] but I'd like to know why, you
know? I' I'd like to find a reason why
so we can understand it better
and time again, bro. [ __ ] It's [ __ ]
annoying. It's cheeky as well. It's so
cheeky, bro. So cheeky.
Yes, but I've reported that stuff and
I've reported stalking and I've reported
harassment, but somehow they can't do
anything about it.
So, I mean, uh, mate, they they've
arrested me for small small things
before. They've reported me for the most
smallest things before, bro. Smallest
things before. Like, I can't even I
can't even tell you. So, nah, it's just
an excuse. And even if you didn't do
anything, they would make up a law just
for you. They literally have been over
the most silliest different things that
weren't threats. That weren't threats.
So So yeah. No, they get they get they
get involved and it suits themselves.
It's not to do with threats. It's not to
do with threats. I've reported stalking.
I've reported harassment. I've reported
blackmail, which is one of the worst
things. and they can never do anything
about it if you're not anyone other than
PJ. So, I this need to be addressed. I'm
going to I'm going to talk to them about
this on the 17th when they call me up on
this video, I think, right?
And I'm really really really going to
get to the bottom of what what this
problem is, you know?
And it doesn't matter really threats. If
somebody threatened me right now, they'd
be like, "Report it to YouTube."
They literally would tell me to report
it. They will literally make any excuse
not to investigate it. They they would
they will literally make up any excuse
in the book not to investigate it.
Any excuse like anyone that they can find.
So yeah, there's something not right
there. We need we need I just want the
truth out of them to be honest with you,
you know. And I've got crime reference
numbers numbers to back it up as well,
which also would prove that they still
don't do anything about it when they've
got a crime reference number. So, at the
end of the day, how are they going to
talk their way out of that one? You've
got the reports. You've got every single
cab number on your phone. Let's get to
the truth. Like, let's really understand
it now. You You know what I'm saying?
Oh, basically, right? um
station today to follow up a report cuz
I couldn't make the appointment that
they made cuz basically um I'm moving
and stuff so I wouldn't even be in the
house. So they told me to go to police station
and then they basically said uh I live
in cuckoo land. Well, did you just did
you just did you literally not listen to
what I've just explained to you or do
you want me to explain it to you again?
Okay, let's ask let's let's go let's ask
Cy this. Yeah. So, Cory, I'm going to
I'm going to um explain the story. Yeah.
Right. If you want and don't be biased,
like if you think I'm wrong, tell me I'm
wrong. No one's going to get banned. And
I want you to tell me what you think
this is. Anyone who's watching this
right now, right? I want you to really
tell me what you think this is. Right.
So, you know how I was reporting these
people for harassing me and stalking me
and I got told by the the court and the
and the and the police to continuously
report it and report it and report it.
Like, I've got mad [ __ ] at what these
people done. They weren't interested.
Reported to YouTube. Any excuse
basically not to um not to follow it up.
So, then I followed it up uh um the
other day. Then they called me yesterday
and they were like, "Oh yeah, um, here's
the appointment. We're going we're going
to come to your house." But I had to
change the appointment because I'm not
in I'm not going to be here anymore cuz
I'm moving. But then they basically
said, cut a long story short, they said
go to the police station. I've gone to
the police station again with complete
fresh evidence. Oh well, yeah, you need
to report it to YouTube. You need to We
can't do anything about that. So I was
like, "Okay, so you pay two sides of a
coin then because when somebody reports
me, right, you're on my door before you
can say Jack Robinson." But then when I
report actual serious stuff, um, you
can't do anything about it. So you're
playing two sides of a coin. So which
one is it? Are you involved or are you
not involved? Because I'm here because
obviously you like to get involved with
social media. You've proved your point
time and time and time again. I've took
advice to follow up reports and you're
claiming that you can't do anything. And
then another officer come next to me and
said, "Oh, is that uh Peter, right?" And
he's like, "Oh, yeah. You got to come
for an involuntary interview because you
were saying something to a woman on Instagram. Hypocrisity.
Do you understand? The colleague, her colleague literally
come beside her and contradicted
everything that she just said." You know
what I'm saying? So, can you not
understand how at this point it's
looking like racism? At this point, it's
looking like something is not right,
bro. Something is not right, bro. I'm
telling you. I'm telling you. Yeah.
So, yeah, there's definitely there's
something wrong there, bro.
Um so yeah so obviously when when um
obviously you don't have to go to that
voluntary interview but um I will be
going there with all the crime reference
numbers and all the things I've
reported. I want to know why they have
not done anything. So like her colleague
literally just contradicted everything
she just said. Yeah, they're racist,
bro. I'm telling you they're they're
racist. There's something not right
there, bro. They're [ __ ] mad. I'm
telling you they're [ __ ] mad.
how you can think that's normal. You're
just lying to yourself. They like to
play two sides of a coin. That's what
they do. They have their favorites.
That's what they do, bro.
Even Ant-Man says it now.
No, they said they were going to, but
they said, "Oh, because we've seen you."
Um, so I'm going to address this with
the police officer that's calling me in
two days. I'm going to be like, "What
what is actually going on now?" you
know, and this time I'm not going to
leave it until you actually do something
like what is going on now? Like, are you
you're involved, right? So, what is it?
You know what I'm saying?
So, I'm going to um Yeah, I need to
They're calling me in two days as well.
So, it's like you really do have your
favorites, you [ __ ] pigs. How Mike
can't say they have their favorites. He
is literally He's the one living in
cuckoo land. He's living in [ __ ]
land. If you genuinely don't think there
is not anything wrong with that, you're
living in [ __ ] land, let alone cuckoo
land, mate. [ __ ] hell. They literally
have their favorites. You remember all
that time in in uh in Newcastle as well?
Um when I got nicked like think of all
of the [ __ ] Yeah. KBY I've been through
on this community with these people and
you know with these police and that and
these people ain't even got a warning. I
think you're the one living in [ __ ]
land, not cuckoo land, mate. If you do
not think there is something wrong
there, they there's something wrong with you.
Yeah, they they they they generally do
have their favorites. They generally
And instead of writing about me making a
complaint, I'm going to say it to them
to um when they call me in two days,
I'll be making a complaint as well. A
complaint. Um, and yeah, and I'm just
going to keep I'm just going to keep
reporting it now every 5 days. That
pissed me off, you know, that. Yeah. So,
and and they're going to say that
they're dealing with me. That's nice.
I'm not dealing with you. So, you can
deal with me all you want. I won't be
dealing with you, bro. Simple.
I don't know. The whole thing is just
cheeky. The whole thing is that just
annoyed me today. No, they will call
you. They will call you.
Maybe in a month they will call you.
They definitely will call you. They don't say
um they're going to call you then don't
call you. But they they they generally
have their favorites. They really do
They generally generally do. What do you
mean they're not going to call me? Of
course they're going to call me, man.
It's a [ __ ] appointment. It's
scheduled. They're going to have to call
me. So, I'm going to have to talk to
them about what I've reported. Um and
I'm really going to have to make one of
these people understand. So yeah,
they're going to call. It's scheduled.
They have to call me. I've reported something. So
yeah, they will call me, but they have
to call me. I'm reporting something.
So well, it's actually another thing. So yeah.
got a bit anyways. I'm busy. So,
just thought I'd rant about the place.
Uh, one wolf for one, one wolf for it for another
in this country.
madness to see. And it's mad for the
women as well. Why do they start [ __ ] if
they're just going to run to the police?
Why do people do that? I don't understand.
And then run to the police. Who knows?
It could be over that Morgan thing. Who knows?
No, I don't think so. So many grasses in
this country as well.
one of the reasons why I come off social
media as well.
But anyways, [ __ ] all that [ __ ] I I'm
going to sort it out anyways. Um, but yeah,
I can't believe you people are still g
you people still [ __ ] gambling.
So, no one's talking about vendettas.
People got a vendetta. They don't have a
vendetta, but something ain't something
ain't right, bro.
Something really really ain't right. So,
for real, for real. Something ain't
right there, bro.
Doesn't even sound normal, bro.
Yeah, that one from New Zealand replied.
She had to reply, man.
That conversation was too good. How did
you not reply?
I don't gamble anymore. What part of I
do not gamble anymore?
Do you not understand? I do not gamble anymore.
[ __ ] me. I think you um
that police thing did piss me off today.
Racist, sexist bastards. Yeah, [ __ ] pigs.
No, just got fed up of it. Having the
same conversation, having the same mood
swings. Nah, just can't be bothered with
it anymore. You only live once. I don't
want to waste my life gambling and
[ __ ] wasting my life and money
gambling. Just can't be bothered with it.
I've got other things to worry about as well. Nope.
I'm sick of it. [Applause]
I'm not talking about that.
You don't need to know that.
[ __ ] load of old bill. Load of old [ __ ] bill.
Going to bust my teeth again. Had some
sausage roll this morning. I need to go
as well. I need got stuff to do. It's
not one thing, it's a [ __ ] another.
Them police are [ __ ] racist.
They hate the nons women. Oh, nicest bastard.
You don't need to worry about me, mate.
He's got new phones, too. So yeah. Yeah.
The police have their favorites in this country. Yeah,
they've got their favorites in this country, man.
They ain't got their favorites,
but somehow we're supposed to respect these pigs. A [ __ ]
I don't know who come up with that, bro.
Must be [ __ ] [ __ ] today.
Yeah, you're very bad at trolling, bro.
You're really bad at it. Yeah,
you're really bad at trolling, bro. Stop
being a weirdo, man. [ __ ] Anyways,
I'm going anyways. I need to do some stuff.
Talk some stuff out. See you.