[ __ ] Caps.
Three caps for £11.
That's a [ __ ] bargain, mate. Just
been out in the bloody corner out days.
You would love to see little characters,
I think. Yeah,
I feel [ __ ] today. I need to go out
today, but do some
serious sending today. Um, yeah,
it's going to be a problem trying to get
anywhere today, but yeah,
I'll send it because that's what I do. sand
be last time.
It never changes in good old England. E, nothing does.
Nothing ever changes in good old England. Nothing. Maybe
the [ __ ] hell. Oh man, [ __ ] me. England. >> [ __ ] Bye-bye.
That's going to be funny, bro.
Some popcorn downstairs.
I take the bites of it. Oh, [ __ ]
It's a bit weird, but
Virgin Boy, stop stalking me.
Trying to get in my [ __ ] Hangouts
yesterday. Call the police. You [ __ ] weirdo.
[ __ ] Go get laid. Nice though.
my boyfriend. They're typical.
Oh man, do you know [ __ ] these
videos, bro? I hate watching them.
[ __ ] hate watching them, bro.
It's [ __ ] boring, bro. I don't know
how people laugh at them.
I don't know how people laugh at them,
mate. They're [ __ ] boring, bro.
Oh, it's the same old, bro. This was
posted [ __ ] 27 minutes ago.
So, I was going to do this video to Joe
Fier last night. Said a few things,
didn't post it.
I'd like to know
how it doesn't dictate your future. How
your past don't dictate your future when
it comes to this. I'm all ears, but I
mean I'm watching some [ __ ] on
the [ __ ] street going around
approaching people and he's doing the
same [ __ ] So, I mean,
I don't know, man. It seems like it does, but
it does dictate your future.
Look at that. 27 minutes gone. Where's
Where did it go?
Hey, notorious man. I went out uh I went out yesterday.
You need to ask me how it was before I answer it.
No, I went out yesterday, bro. No. Um I
went out on Thursday. Sorry. I'm going
out again today cuz why the [ __ ] not?
But welcome back, boss.
Welcome back, boss.
[ __ ] I'm [ __ ]
You You didn't You didn't ask me how it went yesterday.
You asked me, I will tell you, boss.
Where the [ __ ] is that?
Well, it was the same old England if
that answer your question. So,
yeah, same old England. Hope that answer
your question, boss.
Um, same old uh
it's the same old
same old England, bro.
I need to show my email here.
Yeah, same old, bro. Don't be depressed, boss.
If I'm not depressed, you won't be
depressed. I lost a house. I lost money
from the house.
I basically lost some friends and stuff.
Don't be depressed, boss.
Trust me, I've got a lot worse than you, buddy.
But um it's so [ __ ] Yeah, man.
At least you at least you [ __ ] found
someone. I can't even find someone. I
can't even get a conversation out of the
[ __ ] So you should you should be
[ __ ] proud of yourself, mate.
I can't even get a combo out the [ __ ]
No, I can't even get a combo out the
[ __ ] All I get is I got a boyfriend.
That's all I ever get. So, you should be
proud of yourself, man.
It's the same old England.
So, uh nothing really much to say.
That's how I'm going to I'm going to
voice it from now. I'm just going to be
just England, same old.
I've got a question. Notorious. Yeah.
So, this Joe guy says that you can't
your past don't dictate the future. But
I don't understand how he can say that
because this has been going on for years
and it's still happening. It is still
happening. So it seems like it has it
has dictated your future. It feels like
your past has dictated your future
because it's still happening. It's still going on.
I don't know if that's just me or
but it seems like it does dictate your
future cuz it has done for the past 3
years. You know what I'm saying? So, and
for probably more than 3 years now. So,
I ask yourself the question, bro, when
does it stop? When does the [ __ ]
stop, bro? Like, I'm all ears. I'm all
ears. I'm all for listening and
listening to other people's advices and stuff,
but when does the [ __ ] stop then?
Been going on for a long time now. So,
I don't know what your opinion is, but
you heard that your your past don't
dictate your future.
So why haven't you met some of them? If
you've tried like for years, why haven't
you met somebody if your past don't
dictate your future?
What's indicating? It's the same old.
It's like when you used to go out, bro.
It used to be the same old, didn't it?
It used to be the same old with you.
It's the same old with me.
It's the same old England. Same old.
So, what's the chance of finding someone
here? I think
well I got three numbers for James
tourist and um one of them replied then
when I asked them to hang out they
stopped replying that's just same old
England isn't it?
That's just the same old England ain't it?
So we got to go through a lot of [ __ ]
today bro. We need to find someone that
don't pretend they got a boyfriend. We
need to find somebody that gives us our
number, their number, and then we need
to find somebody that will actually meet
up. It's not likely, mate, is it? It's not likely.
One in about maybe 500, maybe
to even get a meet up. I would say
probably to even get a meet up and then
Yeah, it's [ __ ] up, bro.
They boarded a whole [ __ ]
whole house been [ __ ] boarded up
until two years. But yeah, bro. So
it never changes, bro. That stays the same.
I want to show this guy some my videos,
but I don't want that stalker getting my
[ __ ] new um new YouTube channel, bro.
That [ __ ] stalker.
That Jamie Thompson weirdo.
[ __ ] weird [ __ ] fat low life. Oh, [ __ ] Oh man,
I think the popcorn's going to dodge now.
Oh my goodness.
Seems like a kind of Saturday today, doesn't it?
But yeah, they ain't interested in this country.
See what one?
I said, why are you ignoring Andy Pandy?
Why are you ignoring Andy Pandy?
I've noticed there's not rats in this
country as well. By rats, I mean like
snakes. so snaky.
Like I call somebody twice and then they
block me. They're [ __ ] snakes
as well. That's another thing, bro.
Oh, [ __ ] I don't know, bro. Um
going out today or whatever, bro.
Chance of me getting somewhere [ __ ] slim.
Well, now I could
[ __ ] bro. Next level. I'm [ __ ] man.
This country is depressing, in it, bro.
I'm just waiting on a few things. I've
just got out drinking for now cuz
basically I've got nothing better to do
now. But I'm just waiting on [ __ ] But
it never changes. Never.
It don't change ever, bro, in this country.
But my bad. It does. It gets worse. So,
actually, yeah, it does. It actually
does change because it gets
>> Where's my uh
It actually does change actually cuz it
gets worse. Why did I say it doesn't
change? It changes, bro. It's worse.
Oh, [ __ ] Oh, [ __ ]
Back as [ __ ] Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah. [ __ ] go on TV. Go on. Oh [ __ ] Everybody knows.
No, I don't want to game. So, I want to
play GTA. [ __ ] off.
Franklin, you're being a bit loud, mate.
[ __ ] first thing in the morning. [Music]
I'm so tired, bro.
Where's all that stress? I think
let's see what uh six is saying. Hey,
let's see what six is saying. Hey, Zippy.
Let's see what six is saying. Hey, Zippy.
We're kind of stuck here for now. So, yeah.
That's the good thing about Thursdays.
You drink on the Thursday,
you're fresh on the Saturday. You see? So,
that's what I'm doing today. Anyways,
but it never ever ever ever ever changes.
Bad though, cuz we could have went out
on a date today. We've got money. We can
go out, spend two, £300, go on a date or
whatever. But nah, nah.
So, we need to go back September.
Something's coming in September. And
there's one coming out October as well.
N not in this country, matey.
Oh, my [ __ ] back, bro. What the [ __ ]
We got the cinema out the way, so
hopefully we can go and [ __ ]
I'm waiting for Joe. I want Joe to give
me an explanation about how your past
does not dictate your future when it
comes to this.
I just want an answer.
I just want an answer how it doesn't
predict your future when it is still going on.
So, make sure you make them two valid
bullet points that it's been going on
for years and it still continues to happen.
So, I don't know how it doesn't predict your future,
but you're just going to wake up one day
and women are not going to be stuck up
and women aren't going to pretend
they've got boyfriends and they're no
longer going to be westernized.
Please, bro. It doesn't even sound believable.
That That doesn't make any sense.
And people are just going to know how to
start socializing. It literally doesn't
make any sense.
That makes literally no sense.
But they live in thingy, don't they? So, yeah.
always do the same over there.
I want to try and get like Oh, I know
where I'm going today. I know what club
I'm going actually.
Sorry. Actually, I actually do know
where I'm going today.
It's just like one last [ __ ] just
like one last wall. Obviously, I need to
get the phone and Yeah,
it never changes.
Never changes in this country.
It is sad, bro.
Very, very, very sad.
I think that's why I used to gamble, you
know, some sort of buzz, some sort of
I think that's that's why I used to do it,
but then I realized that just makes your
problems worse and so on and so forth
and whatever. So,
it's a sad country to be. It's a sad
place to be.
It sure is. Sad, depressing old England.
It's a really depressing place. You have
to wait for everything here as well. I
noticed that hate. You have to wait for everything. So depressing.
The dating, the people, the weather, the system.
The system is [ __ ] as well, bro. Like
Right. Go slow motion.
Yeah. One day you're going to go out, right,
and it's just going to be completely
different and you're not going to deal
with any [ __ ] Just doesn't make sense.
How can things just change like that? I
don't understand. How can things that
get worse just just get better? It's
just it's been going on for I'm sure
he's taking a piss. He's got to be
That Joe ref has got to be he's got to
be taking the piss, bro. Because things
don't change like that after the years.
I'll be out today.
What's so [ __ ] up is I I don't really
go nightclubs anymore, but I'll be
getting it today. I know for sure I'll
be getting it today.
Boyfriend. Boyfriend. Dude, they even
get in the nightclubs
to be honest.
I swear this just straight up bored him,
bro. Swear that I do this out of boredom.
Let's just say Saturday was a bad day, right?
and today is better.
That's wishful thinking.
You can't even be positive because it's
always negative. It's always the same old.
Same old England.
If it's bad today, I'll tell you that
it's just the same old England.
Same old England. Never changes.
It's bad as well cuz where you're not
working at the minute, you got money.
You got you got you got time to spend
with whoever you meet,
you know. the same same thing for years.
Like you had time, you had you had all
the time in the meet, all the time in
the world to spend time with these women
as well. That's that's that's the
maddest thing about it.
It's just mad how people can be so I
think they're in denial. I don't think
they I don't think they believe it. I
don't generally think that they believe
it. I think that they're in denial
and then they say that when they pretend
there's not a problem or anything. I
think they're just in denial to be fair.
They're in denial.
And then this, oh this Indonesian guy,
he messaged me. He was like, "Oh, I
don't know what to say. There's nothing to say."
That's that's that is the whole point is
that there's nothing to say or [ __ ]
but you shouldn't be telling people this
that and the other when you're scared to
approach. It's just ridiculous.
When you're scared to approach, you
shouldn't be giving people advice.
That's how I feel anyways about it. Um,
it doesn't rain all day today.
This is fast. Wow. They're up. Hey, bro.
This guy creeps the old [ __ ]
These people need to give it a [ __ ] break, bro.
You almost [ __ ] killed me there.
Oh, it's the same old England. Oh, baby.
It's the same old England.
I actually lost stuff. I actually lost
money by [ __ ] buying this [ __ ] bro.
Yeah. [ __ ] Oh [ __ ] Oh my god.
What [ __ ] are we going to deal with
today, lads? All right. Oh, [ __ ]
No [ __ ] run. I'm not African, bro.
Are you mad?
I only have African people.
Why there so many homeless people? Why?
This is why you see homeless people from [ __ ] England. No. Oh, [ __ ]
and today we must maybe 100 maybe maybe [ __ ]
Anyways, I'm [ __ ] out of here, [ __ ]
So, well, I mean, [ __ ] off off this [ __ ] Um, [Laughter] Well,
I'm out of it anyways.