The maniac. Maniac. Oh my god, bro. That
[ __ ] almost killed me, but I can't lie.
The madness, bro. So [ __ ] madness.
There we go. Come on. Yes. Yeah. There
we got two, bro. Oh my god. It was so
long today, bro. Some videos to
come. I need to eat a burger, bro. I'm starving.
That almost killed me, bro. It's not
even funny. So, I got a video coming on
my channel, bro, of a
burger. That was a [ __ ] I had the
Caroline Reaper burger. It was a madness.
One second, bro. I'm
[ __ ] That burger almost killed me,
bro. It's not even
funny. It's going on my channel. That was hot,
mate. And for me to say something's hot,
mate, it's [ __ ]
hot. Trust me,
bro. Well, it's fine. Anyways, got four
numbers anyways. It's the whole
day. [ __ ] hell, bro. It's not even a joke,
bro. I'm ordering another burger at 20
quid. [ __ ] hell, bro. But it's not
funny. The madness was
hard. Yeah, it was fun. It was
fun. It was fun nonetheless.
That they got nothing to say,
bro. I don't see a
Are you just That's not him,
mate. That's not even him,
lad. Bro, I I tried the hottest burger.
It almost [ __ ] killed me, bro.
Totally a joke. I'm putting it on my
channel. They're a good channel. They're
things. It almost killed me, bro. I
literally have to sign like two
receipts to say that if anything happens
to me. Yeah.
Oh, that's no joke. That was crazy, bro.
That was crazy hot. That was
hot. That was [ __ ] hot, man. I ain't
even joking, bro. [ __ ]
me. It was last. So I got red this passport
tomorrow. Um and then I'm going to
probably do football. I got 20 in my
pocket. I need to do a football bet tomorrow. Yeah.
[ __ ] bro. That's not even funny. Well,
say it's actually the first of March, so
we kind of like followed it through. It
was good, bro. It was
good. I got the stamp on my hand as well.
I'm a crazy [ __ ]
mate. I am a [ __ ] crazy bastard,
bro. Oh, come on, McDonald's. I'm
[ __ ] I need a McDonald's, bro. I need
a McDonald's, bro. [ __ ] But at least
I'm not going to have a hangover. at
least, bro. Baz, I got four numbers.
Um, yeah, I was dancing. I got four
numbers in the end. Like, all in all,
today [ __ ] I went, bro, and I had
this burger. It's called a Caroline
Reaper burger, bro. Almost killed me. I
It's like the world's hottest burger.
The world's hottest jalapenos. and had
to sign my life away to say that if
anything happens to me then
um yeah like it's bad I don't know how
much I spent bro probably
like good couple hundred maybe a good
couple hundred pound but I need to get
my pass I need to do football bet
tomorrow cuz I got I had an escort as
well I got an escort at the end but I
couldn't come because um yeah I had too
much to drink escort burger was a good life
But I need to do football tomorrow. I
need to get my passport sorted. I've got
the pictures and then Yeah, that's
it. Yeah, I'm done for few weeks now,
bro. That was that was my fun. So
yeah, probably try and save a thousand
and a half every month. Be good at
it. Be it be a lad.
L didn't pay.
[ __ ] Yeah. So, I got 20 quid. I'm going
to do football at tomorrow.
Yes. Oh [ __ ] I'll tell you how much I spent
today. I probably spent about 350
today. 350 quid
maybe. A lot of money, mate. A lot of
money. That Caroline burger was mad,
man. Almost killed me sweater. It's not
even a joke.
You don't have to sign your life away
for nothing. Why have I only got 20
pound left? Because I withdrew 80 and
the escort cost 60.
Yeah, I've got a lot more than 20 quid,
mate. But 20 on
me, if you listen properly, I withdrew
80 to get an escort. It cost 60. So that
left me with 20. I've got [ __ ] a lot
of money, mate. A lot of
money. Yeah. And it's in my bank. Yeah.
And I put it back in my
bank. Yeah. And I put it back in my
bank. Decent to be fair.
I love that. It's ace,
lad, bro. I'm putting this I'm putting
this burger video
up. I at least do this passport [Music]
tomorrow. Oh, it's going to be
long. That's going to be
this. One second. second. 17.
I got some stuff to do for my still
after this Mackis
lad. But yeah, I got far numbers in
that, bro. I got chatting to some
people, but a lot of make believe
boyfriends today, Baz. [ __ ] hell. I
dealt with a lot of them. Probably more
than usual, to be fair. I got my hair
done and everything. Got the good old Stony on.
Oh, but it's England for you in it.
Nothing will ever change in this
country. But at least we tried like
Yeah, we got four numbers anyway. So,
is it four numbers?
Yeah. Not anyway. So, could have been worse, lad. Um,
yeah. Why is it going cold all of a
sudden? That one's
sexy. Sexy, bro. Well, there's a few of
them as well to be
fair. Anyways, I'm out of
here. I'll see you tomorrow. I'll be
live tomorrow with football
bear. Yeah, I'm too old for clubs, bro.
You're boring. Shut
up. Shut up. Okay.
Yeah, I'm out of peace. Be live
tomorrow. Peace. M it.