That [ __ ] me.
I'm all right in this [ __ ]
I can't believe that woman in the junior
said to go cooking classes.
[ __ ] hell, man. [ __ ] cooking classes.
I just want one of these accounts so I
can make money and [ __ ] off again, bro.
I'm just waiting on it.
Go out once a week for two months out.
This country is really [ __ ] depressing, bro.
Yeah. You'll also find women that
pretend they've got boyfriends as well.
It doesn't matter where it is, Grezy. I
don't know why you seem to think that it
matters where you are. It doesn't matter
if it's a club. It doesn't matter if
it's a cooking class. It doesn't matter
if it's a pub. It doesn't matter if it's
the street. They're the same. They're
all westernized. It doesn't matter where they are.
I mean, yeah, bro. You're telling me right
that you can't get a decent woman in in
a Weather Spoons. Of course you can. Of
course you can get a a woman in a
Weather Spoons. People go to Weather
Spoons all the time. People go to to
Weather Spoons all the time, bro. It
doesn't matter where they are. They're
the same everywhere. Not interested. It
doesn't It's not a specific place.
Um I I done a video yesterday, Joe, uh
dedicated to you, but I didn't upload it.
Um I went out yesterday. Well, not
yesterday, Thursday, cuz I hadn't been
out in ages. wanted to go out, had a
haircut, and same old England.
Same old England, but uh you say that
your past does not dictate your future.
Well, I disagree with you big time with
that one when it comes to dating
cuz it's been happening for years and it
continues to happen.
Just about how you've got to be
trolling, is it? Cuz if your if your if
your past did not dictate your future,
you wouldn't still be dealing with this.
You wouldn't still be dealing with this.
But you you are still dealing with this
because I went out on Thursday cuz I
wanted to go out anyways.
But I can tell you that it was the same old.
Like it always will be the same old in this country.
What? One day you're going to wake up
and suddenly everything's going to be
perfect when it comes to women. Nah. Or
the dating game. It doesn't doesn't even
sound It doesn't even make any sense.
Oh, by the way, Grey, I bought some
caps, by the way. Yep. I got three caps
for £11. Mickey Mouse, Donald Duck. I
got a panda one. I got black, cream, and
navy. It made me think of you. But
[ __ ] £11 for three caps. Yeah,
they're like30 pound. They're normally
like30. I was like, that's a bargain,
bro. I don't even know why I wear caps.
I've got lovely set of hair. Set a head
of hair. I just I just like them in the
sun cuz it blocks the sun out your it
blocks the sun off your face, you know.
So, I'm just used to wearing them now. But
I like them. They're they're quite cute. Boozy.
Donald Duck. You know Donald Duck. But
yeah, it does. I'm going out today cuz I
got nothing better to do and it will be
the same old today as well. Joe,
want to put money on it? Come, I need to
make as much money as I possibly can.
Now, I'll bet you £1,000. I'll give you
£1,000 in cash that
I will go out today
and it will be and I won't even get a
date by next week.
Yeah, I can I can I can I can I can I
need to make some money now so I can
make a quick thousand. Yeah, let's do it, bro.
That's how certain I am.
Yep. Never changes here.
But it doesn't matter if it's where it
is. It doesn't matter where it is. You
You can find decent people in Weather Spoons,
you know. You can find decent people.
Oh, I met so many friends on Thursday.
Made so many new friends. Sorry.
Like, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. I I do go out and not bother
with them. I just do it when I'm drunk.
But it doesn't matter anyways. It's the
same old It's the same old boring in
this country. I just need to get one of
these apps so I can just leave again. I
can't wait. Honestly, I just want to leave again.
You know, you got the football starting
on in August. I just want to I I want
out of this country again. It's depressing.
It is really really really really depressing.
I spoke to somebody in a train station
on Thursday. They they said they were Turkish.
I said oh I am. Do you speak the language?
Then they said uh
no. I asked for their number like
[ __ ] 5 minutes later. They said
they're not interested. Anyone would
think you look like Timmy Eldridge the
way you're treated in your own [ __ ] country.
Can't even get rehoused if unless you're [ __ ] African.
This country is just a sad, depressing
place to be.
Seriously, it really, really is. It's no
life for anyone.
It really is no life for anyone here, man.
They don't even help you with housing
unless you're [ __ ] African.
Like that's literally I'm not racist.
That is the the the the truth. No. No, I haven't.
But I'm just using it as an example.
Like you can't even It's like this
country is designed to just annoy you.
It feels like it really is just designed
to just annoy you. I don't know. Like it
feels like that. It really does feel
like that. Oops.
Just like I don't know. I can't explain
it. It It does.
No, I'm not even I just went out
Thursday cuz I wanted to go out. I
haven't been out for ages. But the same
thing with the women thing never changes.
The women thing will never ever change.
So, I don't understand how you can sit
there and say that your past don't
dictate your future. It does. It's been
dictating it for the past three years. I
know we can we can say right now here
and now it's been dictating it for the
past 3 years. And do you know the thing
is we don't care. That's the whole
point. You you're you
uh that's a misconception that you think
that we care. We don't care, bro. We're
just we it's just unbelievable. That's I
think that that's where you you've got
it all wrong. You've got the wrong end
of the stick. Like you think that oh we
we live for women, we go out for women.
Oh, but I'm not in denial. Do you not
understand? At the same time, I'm not in
denial. Like, Ant-Man's not in denial.
It's It is messed up in so many
different ways. It's not normal.
It's I'm not in denial, man. I'm not
going to pretend, oh yeah, everything's
fine. I had a good time. And no, it's
it's not normal. It's [ __ ] up to be
the way I am, to look the way I am,
getting these bad experiences. It's not normal.
That doesn't mean people live for
[ __ ] women. Oh sh Oh [ __ ]
That's where you've got the wrong with
the stick. You know what I'm saying? I'm
just not in denial, bro. You know,
it's not normal. It isn't normal.
Someone like me should should have found someone.
Someone like me should have should
should be on a date today. You should be
on a date today or tomorrow or maybe
next. You should have a date scheduled
for for a week.
You should have a date scheduled. That's
normal. This is not normal. And I had
such a good time as well, man. I met
some really cool people.
You're going to laugh at this, Joe.
Yeah. I was speaking to this uh guy. He
was 18. Yeah.
And we was talking for about half an
hour in the pub and he come back 5 hours
later to see if he got my right the right number.
It's madness. It's madness. That's how
you know it is women that are the
problem as well. You know, I must have
met like six, seven people. I know
they're not gay and know I'm not gay.
That's how you know it is them. That's
how you know they are the problem.
Definitely. That's how you definitely
know that they are the problem.
It's just called it's just called
networking as well, you know. But it
isn't normal. There's nothing normal about it.
Yeah. You get on better with men because
they're not stuck up [ __ ] with
unrealistic expectations. Yeah. Yeah.
That's why you get on better with men.
Yeah. Cuz they don't think that they're
better than everyone like women. That's
probably why you would get on with men.
You it because the thing is with men,
Joe, uh you could actually get a
conversation out of them. So, it's it's
it's a lot easier because they don't
pretend that they've got boyfriends. So,
it's very much easier to get on better
with uh people that aren't stuck up that
pretend they got boyfriends. Yeah. No,
you get conversation. The only people
that you get conversation out of
nowadays is either like an older woman,
like a really older woman, an Australian
person or a [ __ ] man. That's
literally the only conversation. I was
speaking to some woman. She was
Australian. Uh, and she must have been
about [ __ ] knows 40s maybe and was talking talking.
You can't get a conversation out of
anyone my age.
They don't know how to socialize because
of Tik Tok and and Instagram.
But the thing is, let me tell you
something as well. I was thinking about
this in in the cinema yesterday. I was
like, "Oh, yeah. You might not get as
much money now. You've got savings and
but I mean, you're just it's like what
you said. You're you're just back to
reality now. You're not [ __ ] You're
not skinned. You're not going to be
skinned. And you're not going to be
rich, you know? You're just back to
life, back to reality. That's all you
are. We We don't know what's going to
happen. But with women, we know exactly
what's going to happen. We know that it
will never change ever. Um so I'm not
even asked about the money to be honest.
So I just know that like something will
happen, you know, in in the future. But
I know when it comes to my my material
status, it ain't changing in this country.
And I'm living proof of it. I'm living
proof of it. So
now you might think I'm being a bit
awkward and I'm being a bit difficult,
but I'm not. It's not normal. This is
not no way of living, bro. Here.
Yeah. That's why you get on better with
men. You can actually get a conversation
out of them.
You can't get a conversation out of a
woman other than I've got a boyfriend.
It's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
Concerning more than annoying.
I didn't even do any approaches. I might
do some sober today. I might do.
But it will never change. If it's not
changed for 3 years, what hope do you
possibly have that one day it's all
going to get better?
I think that's the stop saying turn gay.
Literally, bro, you people have got you
need to grow up. This whole gay thing,
oh, you're gay. You You really really
need to grow up, bro. It's getting
really boring now. Really boring. Really immature, you know?
Hey, Joe, do you know what I said
yesterday when somebody was talking
about my sexuality and they and they
shut their mouth? Do you know what I
said to them?
Let me just make sure you're here before
I ramble. And they couldn't say anything
back to me. Right.
Yeah, but you're saying turn gay. Why
would I turn gay when you know that I'm
not gay? Anyways, I turned around and
said to them, "Okay, I I was speaking to
women and I come across men when I was
drinking. Yeah, these guys are really
cool. What about you people? You sit on
YouTube every day talking to men. All
you do is sit on YouTube talking to men.
LJ goes to another country to meet men.
That sounds sus to me. That sounds
really, really, really sus to me.
That sounds very, very [ __ ] sus.
Because you sit online talking to men
all day, every day. You go to different
countries to meet [ __ ] men.
You know what the [ __ ] bro? I would
even go to another country to meet a [ __ ] woman.
I I I I tell you this right now. If a
woman said to me, "Oh, come to Scotland
and meet me." I wouldn't do it. I don't
think I would do it, to be honest. You
would even do it for a [ __ ] woman,
let alone a man. I don't think I would do it.
I don't think so.
They'd have to be really [ __ ] good
looking for me to go to another country.
So that's how you know just LJ is just
like some bully victim of Belfast is
just some lone above. Like he can talk
about connections all he wants. Bro, you
do not go to Liverpool to meet men
because you got all these friends. Come
on. Like we need to make it make sense now.
It doesn't make sense.
I'm about to crash and Franklin's about to die.
So why are you You know what I mean? Why
are you going to different countries to
meet men, bro? The [ __ ]
But yeah, it's very rare you get a
conversation out of a woman nowadays,
unless they're from Australia or something.
Has had a family, but he doesn't know
because he's on YouTube every single
day. Like, do you know that he has a
family? Like, okay, bro. He has been on
here years and we've never seen him with
a woman. We have seen me with multiple
women. So what you're saying doesn't
even make any sense. L has had a
relationship. He's had a relationship.
When have we ever seen LJ with a woman?
Never. We've seen me with a woman. But
the thing is I still complain. And that
got that gets my whole point that I'm
not in denial. That's the whole point.
Like I I'll give you an example what
you've just said. LJ is a s. Yeah. You
can say that he's been in a
relationship. He's not. That doesn't
matter. L J has never ever ever been
seen with a woman on this community. He
has never been seen with not even one
woman. But he doesn't have a bad word to
say. Remember what I was saying earlier
about being in denial
cuz people like that are in denial. He
he's been in a relationship, bro. We've
never even seen him with a woman.
I mean, not even one woman. And he has
been on here years, you know? I remember
before he even started showing his
[ __ ] face. So nah, like he's he's
he's we've never seen him with a woman ever. So,
and I mean, at the end of the day,
uh, he can have a family all he wants. I
wouldn't want a It'd be cool to bring a
child up in this day and age. Why would
I want to bring a child up in this day and age?
Not when there's all Tik Tok and [ __ ]
Instagram. [ __ ] [ __ ] that. God knows
what it's going to be like in another 27
[ __ ] years when they're my age. I
think anyone that has children now is
child not not it's not child abuse, but
it's um I think it's cruel to be honest with you.
I think it's quite cruel
cuz of um the day and age that we live in, you know.
Yeah, but he's never been with a woman.
Yeah, I know. I I respect it as well,
but he's never been with a woman.
Any woman. That's That's the whole point
we were speaking about. He's never been
seen with any woman. Not different
women, women, the same women. He's never
been seen with anyone.
And he's a s as well, which means he
doesn't get women. And he's also in
denial as well. See, that's me. I'm not
in denial, mate. I'm not in denial.
Why do you think I went to different women?
Because they couldn't stick to you.
That's what it was. You know, I got some
numbers. I got some numbers on Thursday.
I would stick to one, but they're not
interested. Simple. They're not
interested in this country. What do you
think? We're going around, bro. What was
the whole point of going around and
approaching different women?
What? What? What? So, what was the whole
point of going around approaching
different women? was to find someone.
Was to actually find someone.
Yeah. To keep your options open to find
someone. That was the whole point of
approaching different people. Okay. Let
me give you an example. Say I went out
today and the first number I got I
stopped. That would be pointless because
the chances are they're not going to
reply. So then you get four or five
numbers and then you find someone that's
interested and you stick with them.
That's the whole point. You're saying it
like we're going around [ __ ] with
different people for the sake of it. You
got the wrong end of the stick. You've
You know, you think a woman is sticking
to one guy. Think about this. Yeah. When
a woman goes on a dating app or she's
out, do you think she's sticking to one
guy? No. Is she [ __ ] sticking to [ __ ]
one guy? What the [ __ ] bro? So
I think man's right. They're just not
interested in this country. So I think
he is he's definitely right.
I I get bored. No, I don't get bored. No.
But either way, this country is just I
want to I just need to get out of it
again. Simple, man. It's too much.
How you don't even get me house being a
British citizen. I shall never know. But
then they'll they they'll house a they
they'll [ __ ] house Africans and and
women with kids, which shouldn't even be
a priority because it's their choice to
have kids. The whole country is wrong.
The whole having a kid is not like
somebody contracting cancer.
It's a choice.
So that's any nationality. You know what I'm saying?
This country is all wrong, man. It's all wrong.
But it is what it is. So yeah,
my friend in the army according to me. But yeah,
and this woman was like, "Oh yeah, maybe
people maybe people uh maybe
uh maybe people like oh
scared to be approaching the street.
This is what this woman in New Zealand
was saying." I said, "Yeah, but what
about dating apps? What about [ __ ]
the pubs? What about the [ __ ] clubs?"
No one's saying people don't get scared
of being approached on the street, but
it's more of
Okay, but it's not just the street
though, is it? It's dating apps, it's
bars, it's clubs, it's everywhere.
They seem to think that. Oh, okay. Well,
they just they just don't understand.
Working is [ __ ] [ __ ] man. And you
know deep down it's [ __ ] You know deep
down working is [ __ ] Working don't give more options.
So yeah, see, believe it or not, I'm
still better than a lot of people.
I was actually weighing this up. Yeah, I
was saying that even if you get 1.1K a
month, yeah, you're still going to be
better off than most people. You got
designer clothes, you've got a yard, you
know, yeah, you might not it might not
be coming in as fast, but you're not
going to be broke. You're not going to
be skinn. You got no out. got like one
outgoing, two outgoings. So,
you know, the whole you're not even
going to be that worse off to be honest
if you think about it.
And you you ain't got no kids either. So,
you still be better off than a lot of people.
You already you've already had the life
as well. So, yeah.
But yeah, they shouldn't be on the
bottom of the list. It's bad. It really,
really is bad. They shouldn't be because
if if you got someone that's disabled. Yeah.
Is it their fault that they're disabled?
No. So why should they be the bottom of
the list? That doesn't even make any sense.
That doesn't even make any sense. Why
should they be bottom of the list when
it like say you got no [ __ ] legs and
you got something wrong with you and you
was born like it? women. It's women's
it's it's women's choice to have kids. Like
you know what I'm saying?
They should be they should be bottom of
the list though. That's what I'm saying.
They should be bottom of the list. So
that's the point I'm trying to make it.
They should be.
So anyways, [ __ ] all that, bro. Women
with kids should not be the bottom of the list.
It's their choice to have them and to
keep them. So they they literally
So yeah, I don't believe in that to be honest. Yeah.
Anyway, I can't be bothered by
talking about is negative.
Well, the order should be then.
Well, I think no one but English people
should be entitled to any housing.
Um, firstly, like unless you're a
British citizen, they shouldn't help
you. Probably disabled people, men and
women, and then women with kids. That's
what I think it should be. But anyone
that's not from this country shouldn't
be getting housed.
Um, because it's it's England. So, you
know what I'm saying? Hate England. I
[ __ ] hate this country. It [ __ ]
depresses me. It really does.
It annoys me. It's like one man used to
say, actually annoys me. But, um, yeah,
I'd say uh disabled men, disabled women,
and then women with kids should come
second. I think that's I think that's right
to be honest. So
told them about the foot condition. They
just didn't care. They just didn't give a [ __ ]
They didn't care. Unless you're African,
they don't care. That's why most of the
workers are African. So
yeah, only they only care for Africans. Yeah,
I don't really care anyways. [ __ ] it.
It's bad, is it, bro?
Cuz if you was African, I'm not even
racist. It's not even a black or white
thing. It's just Africans. But if you
look up anywhere, it is true. It is the
truth. Like if you think about it, I am
white. I might as well not even be
Turkish cuz I'm only quarter. All my
family's English. My granddad and my
grandma spoke English. They were white.
My grandma was white. So I am actually English.
So it is that's it. You're not even like
anything else really.
You might as well not even tell anyone.
You're less than half. It's not even. Yeah. So,
that's what made me laugh. We were
speaking about Bomb yesterday when I
come in from the cinema. How he seems to
think that you can just go and get
housed or like you can go and show them
a house and they'll pay it for you. It
doesn't work like that. Like they will
give you the smallest budget possible
and you can't even find a house that that uh
that does that. So, yeah. But the money
side of it, I'm not really asked now. I
just know that it is what it is. There's
no point worrying about something that
you can't change
cuz yeah, I just need to wait for some
of these applications to go through,
work, and then leave this country again.
That's the that's the that's the plan anyways.
Now you're just living normal. Now
you're just back to reality for a little
bit. No, there's nothing. And it weren't
the worst thing to be put back to
reality. I still got sabers out there.
It wasn't the worst thing to be put back to reality.
You're just not living in La land anymore.
No, I won't, mate, cuz I got family.
So, it would never happen. It would
never ever happen. Um,
so, and I was saying to the woman on the
phone, well, who is eligible then? And
she couldn't answer me. Like it doesn't
none of it makes any sense. Like if you
notice here with this country, it
doesn't make any sense. None of it makes
But anyways, but yeah, it's not the
worst thing like being put back to
reality for a little while. So
I'll make some money on the football
next month. any wears.
I'm not scared of the neighbors. I'm not
scared of anybody.
And the neighbors don't bother me. And I
don't and I won't bother them because
there's no point.
I've got other things to think about
rather than [ __ ] fight stupid people.
But the neighbors, I've been there
millions of times. No one says nothing
to me. Well, I said that time, but no,
they can't. What can they say? Like really nothing.
I'm not scared of the neighbors, mate.
I'm not scared of no one.
I was going to take that [ __ ] Polish
bouncer on the other day.
I was going to take him on, bro. Silly [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, nothing in this country makes any
sense. Literally like nothing does. So yeah,
I think it's disgusting, man. I
generally think it's disgusting. This
country is disgusting, bro. No,
it will never happen
because no one bo no one will bother me
and I won't bother anyone. So, it will
never kick off ever. Nope.
I visited her the other day. I come back
drunk when I was drinking. I didn't say anything.
See, that's the funny thing is you think
that I'm scared, but I'm really really
really really really not. Have you ever
heard of like don't [ __ ] where you eat?
>> I don't care, bro. I got better things.
I don't really care. I wouldn't give
anyone an excuse.
So, that's called doing a smart thing.
But it is bad to be honest. It is bad.
But if I was staying here, I wouldn't
cause any problems anyways because it's
like what the [ __ ] you if someone's
letting you stay somewhere for you to
not be homeless. Why would you start
issues? Why would you start problems?
Like it was bad enough the first time,
but obviously you sort of had somewhere
to go if you don't have anywhere to go
and someone's letting you stay. Why
would you cause problems for them? It
doesn't make sense. That is a madness.
Why would you cause problems? It doesn't
make sense for people. It don't make sense, bro.
Doesn't make no sense,
bro. That would never happen, bro. Like,
that would never happen.
Yeah, I caused the problems, but I
didn't know these people were going to
be like silly little grasses like
writing posters and [ __ ]
Yeah, I Yeah, I caused the problems, but
it's what people done, the posters and
all that. It's [ __ ] [ __ ] Now I know
what they're like and what they do on
it. I'll never say madness because
they'll never ever like if somebody
would come on your door and start
problems with you, I would cause all the
problems in the world, but they don't.
They do these cowardly posters and
[ __ ] and stuff. That's why I would
never like ever do any of that [ __ ]
because it's it's they they do
cowardness. They never face you
like the [ __ ] virgin. Why the virgin
was trying to get my attention so much yesterday, Joe?
The [ __ ] Orington virgin. He was
trying to come and hang out and and
everything. What is wrong with these people, Joe?
They control what I say. Well, guess
what? I control what they do because
none of these people can tell me where
they live. So at the end of the day, if
you want to go through that route,
listen, listen, listen, bro, if you want
to go through that avenue, I can turn
around and say, "Well, I control what
you do because none of you can tell me
where you live and none of you can go
live and show me where you are. So I can
just say the same thing back at you. I
control everything that you do and I
keep you behind the keyboard.
So if you want to go through that
avenue, I can say exactly the same thing
to various different people that you
will never tell me where you are cuz you
know what's good for you. I can say
exactly the same thing. So at the end of
the day, that's not going to work
though. That's not going to work. Um
yeah, cuz like I I'll give you an
example, right? Medstar, he will never
show me where he is. He would never tell
me where he is and he would never say anything
and he would never say anything to my
face. I control him in that way and
that's not even by law. That's not even
by anything. So I can say to you that I
also control you as well. So that's not
going to work, mate. I control what you
say. That's not going to work cuz I I
control what you do and say.
Nice try, though. It is. It is good. But
you have to wake up pretty early to fool me.
Or I can turn around and say, "Listen, I
will say you think that you control me
what I say." Then I will turn around and
say, "Meet me." And I'll say everything
to your face. And then if you don't meet
me, then I control you.
Bro, it's not going to work, bro.
There's only so much you can do behind
the keyboard. Yeah. And he is back at I
think he's he's got to be jealous or
something, is it, Joe? Do you know what
I was thinking yet? Do you know when I
was at my mom's the other day? Do you
know what I was eating? A lamb shank? I
was eating a lamb shank. I actually had
two lamb shanks. Uh
I had two lamb shanks actually.
And I was like, "Oh [ __ ] this reminds
me of a certain person's mom that used
to starve him.
Used to [ __ ] starve him, bro." And
that's where all of this um stuff comes
from. It's all through trauma, you know,
mommy issues. Cuz again, I was we were
saying ear well earlier that like um that basically
you know how people say they ain't got
no father figure, right? You need a
mother figure as well because your mom
carries you for [ __ ] 9 months. So
nothing can be a mom and dad relation, a
mom and son relationship cuz your mom
actually carries you and breastfeed you
and stuff. And obviously he never had
his mom. Um, and obviously he's still a
virgin. So, I mean, he's got all of
these problems, bro. Um, and that's why
he's so like he used to say to me when I
was 18, 19, maybe 20, oh, you still live
with your mom. You still live with your
mom. I mean, a lot of people live with
their mom nowadays. And it all was
trauma because his mom never wanted him.
I was like, "Yeah, I'm living with my
mom at [ __ ] 20. You're living in a
bedit with no bed in it. I'd rather live
with my [ __ ] mom and save money than
live [ __ ] in a bedit with no [ __ ]
bed in it. Like a [ __ ] Literally, I
would like to be a few of these [ __ ]
places. And it all comes from um
childhood trauma. I I noticed that as well.
It comes from trauma in his life
and the fact that he's still a virgin as
well. We were also saying about how
like, don't you think it's weird, Joe,
that he's he's contacted all of these
women trying to get reassurance that
you've not slept with them? And then I
just said to this [ __ ] Steven Hwood
just yesterday. I said, "What if I did
lie about sleeping with all of them?
What if I didn't even kiss any of these
people?" What? What? Let's just say that
I was lying about all of these women,
like every single one of them, which I'm
not. But let's just play let's just play
let's just put the head on the other
coin now. Yeah. Let's just say that you
was actually lying. Yeah. And you were
lying about it. Why does he care?
Why would he care? Why does he seek out
every day to get validation that you
haven't slept with people? It's cuz he's
a virgin himself. We was all trying to
We was all trying to figure this [ __ ]
out, bro. And we couldn't we couldn't
figure it out.
Like I know you're saying that, you
know, he's got a girlfriend, but no,
bro. Something is not right there. I'm
telling you, something is not right.
Something is seriously seriously
seriously seriously seriously not right.
So, we just put it down to he's he's got
to be one himself. There's nothing else.
It can be more than autism, bro. It has to be
like he will go out of his way
to Oh, the wheels are gone, bro. to find
out that you've not slept with people.
That's so weird. Do you do you understand, bro? So,
I think it's cuz he's the biggest one
himself. Me, even though you you say
that he's not because he's got a
girlfriend, whatever. Well, you tell me
a normal person with a girlfriend that
does this [ __ ] on YouTube all the time.
I I think he is one me. I think I think
he'll die one. I think he'll die a virgin.
Like between me and you, I think you'll
die a virgin.
I'm not even joking. I think you'll
[ __ ] die one.
Don't tell anyone I said that. But
[ __ ] you know what I mean? Then what
else can it be, Joe? Give us some
suggestions, bro. Come on.
Let's just say you did lie about all these people.
Come on. Why? Why would it matter?
to someone in a relationship. Come on. Um,
you know what I'm saying? Why Why would
they Why would it matter to anyone, bro? Like, so yeah.
Yeah. But that's what I'm saying.
There's something not right because he's
life. That is exactly what I'm saying. I
don't rise to it. I don't rise to it at
all. But yeah, that's what I'm saying.
He's the life his life is crap. That is
what I'm saying. That's literally what
it is. And he does. It's not
entertainment because he just
embarrasses himself to be honest with you.
Like I don't rise to it. I just say that it's weird.
Some sad little virgin [ __ ] stalking
people that I've been with and it's
weird. I don't rise to it.
I have not rised to it since I knew the
[ __ ] was a police informant.
That's the whole point is I don't rise to it.
I don't [ __ ] with police informants,
matey. Sorry, matey.
But yeah, he is a virgin. Definitely a
Definitely. You can say he's not. I know
he is. Simple
cuz why did he used to do that [ __ ]
before when I used to meet years ago?
before this whole YouTube thing, before
this whole Izzy thing, why did he used
to do the same old saying, "Oh, you've
not slept with Escorts." When I
literally have, and I've done it ever
since. It's cuz he it he's a virgin himself,
but I'm not I'm not rising to it, bro.
I'm I'm I'm trying to tell you what it
is, cuz there was no beef back then.
And I said, "Well, I have." And then I
had to get my mom on the phone. It's cuz
he's a virgin. It's cuz he's the creepy
virgin that can't stand anyone else
being loved by their mother and getting
laid because he's never been laid.
That's it. That's the only thing I I I
can think of, bro. Like,
and it's like if you lived with your
mom, so what if you lived with your mom
for 3 months before you moved out or
whatever? Like, for [ __ ] sake, it's
not the worst thing in the world. It's
just because your mom didn't love you
and your mom starved you.
You know what I'm saying?
Not really, mate. Cuz I go out to have fun anyways.
But it's not a good thing to be a virgin
at [ __ ] 30 31 cuz look at the
problems it [ __ ] causes.
But yeah, I'll be dealing with some more
crap today. But with them as well, I'm
going out later. So hopefully it don't stop raining.
Yeah, I'll be dealing with some more
crap later, mate.
Joe, I'll be dealing with some more crap later.
More boring later.
But no, like I think like the whole the
most [ __ ] up thing about this Joe is
what I keep saying is that you're not
Timmy Aldridge. You're not Tiger. You're
sorry. You're not Tiger. You're not this um
[ __ ] One sec. You're not this uh Get
back in the car. You're not this fat
ugly person, which I think is the
hardest thing to accept. That's why it's
so hard to accept, I think. And even if
people just gen, you know, even people
judge you by your race, it's still
[ __ ] up really. So, I mean, even if it
is your [ __ ] race, it's still [ __ ] up.
That's that I think that's the worst
thing. I think that is the worst thing.
that is I think that is the worst thing about it.
Yeah. Anyone would think you're [ __ ]
Timmy Eldridge, mate. The way you get [ __ ] treated.
Whereas if you went into the gay scene,
everyone would love you.
Everyone would be hitting on you. That's
that's the that's the maddest thing
about it. So yeah.
So that's that's the worst thing I think.
But I mean you're not the only one. I
mean 80 90% of people struggle. So I Yeah.
But yeah, the crap you get from women
ain't nice. It isn't nice to be fair.
I need to put this back in the freezer,
man. This has got [ __ ] warm.
So, I went to the pictures yesterday. I
saw some couples. It doesn't bother me,
you know. It used to bother me, but it
doesn't bother me anymore. It used to
bother Ant-Man, but it doesn't bother me,
to be honest. I've not even been Oh,
[ __ ] [ __ ] Yo, I didn't tell you. Guess
who I bumped into Thursday.
You're not going to believe this. Please
tell me that you're still there. Um,
please tell me that you're still there, Joe.
Yeah, you never guess who I bump into
Thursday. You ain't been watching my
[ __ ] I forgot to tell you. Yeah,
Thursday was such a weird day, bro. It
was a good day. I met some really good
people, man. So, you know that Pakistani
girl, right, that um I um met I think it
was two months ago where he was walking
everywhere, went Nandos and [ __ ] and
then she tried saying, "Oh, you're not
Muslim." And using that as an excuse. Um so
Well, so yeah, I was just telling her
like some of my problems and [ __ ] like
with the house and that. So, um
yeah, but yeah, man.
Yeah, I bumped into her and then she was
like, "Oh, she" She said, "Oh, she would
get married. She wouldn't date. She
doesn't date. She gets married." I said,
"Okay, let's get married then.
I said, "I'll convert to Muslim." "Oh,
no, no, no. We don't really know." I
said, "We don't know each other. We've
met three times and you you said you
just want to marry someone." It's like
this country never ever changes, bro.
Like, it really doesn't. Yeah, I knew
there was something I forgot to say.
I mean, like I was saying earlier, bro,
you say that your past don't dictate
your future, but it seems like it does,
bro. It seems pretty much like it does.
Well, at least I had it for 3 years. At
least I can say I've been there, done
it, won the gray t-shirt. I can say that for nothing.
That's why I'm not really asked about
the house, to be honest with you. You
know, I knew I was living the life for 3
years. I know I'm still going to be all right, but
Oh, [ __ ] It's bad though. It is still bad.
Yeah, man. It never changes here.
Never changes in good old England.
I don't even see a point of really going
out today, to be honest. What?
No, I don't actually see any point.
Very gray outside as well.
part of the UK. Bro, someone was saying,
"Yeah, oh, have you tried other places
in UK?" Why? Why would it be different?
Why would other play places in the UK be different?
That doesn't even make sense.
Manchester, Liverpool, they're all stuck
up. So, it's like why why does it matter?
The only thing is different. The only
thing is different countries
cuz that's just silly really. Like I was
delusional really as well thinking that
like going to different countries is
would be different because think of it,
you're in London, right?
You get people come from everywhere and
some people don't have a lot of money
just because they're in London. They
don't have a lot of money. They're not
interested. So why would all of a sudden
like going somewhere else? I think I
used to just do it cuz I was bored
anyways. Why all of a sudden would would
they then start being interested somewhere else?
cuz you get loads of people in London
just not interested. So like what what is it? You know,
I don't think it's good to talk about
this squeezy. It's actually depressing.
You know, when they say like when you
talk about stuff it actually makes it worse.
I think it's depressing me here. I don't
know about you, I think it's [ __ ] depressing, bro.
It [ __ ] it gets me down just talking
about it. You know what I'm saying? But
I hate focusing on the [ __ ] subject
cuz I know people's advice is is for the [ __ ] bro.
If you was to meet someone, you you
would have met someone by now.
I feel like sometimes you you got to
stick to your guns, bro. Like if you if
you was going to meet someone, you would
have met someone by now.
Like I I don't think I'm wrong with
saying that. I think I think I've got a
valid point with that. 100%. I think
I've got a valid point. So,
like I said, I'm only doing today cuz I
want to go for a drink anyways. I got my
haircut done and um soon as I get one of
these apps, I'm out of here. So, simple. That's it.
No, I had I had Burger King last night.
Greasy. I had a Burger King. Yeah,
but your past don't dictate your future.
I'm playing a bit of Franklin.
Can you hear it?
I want to show you King. I want to show
you King Greavesy.
King's not with me. Nah,
I love King, man.
You know sometimes Yeah. You know these
dogs are really good like
they help with mental health and [ __ ]
Well, I don't have mental health but
like you know with the whole women [ __ ] and that
cuz you know you can just go and see
their cute little faces and they cheer
you up. Grezy loves King and King loves Greavvesy.
You love uh King Guzy.
Everyone loves King, man.
Do you love King?
I hope I don't get I got a boyfriend
today. Greasy. Do you reckon I'll get it?
I hope I don't get it, man.
It makes me laugh, bro, when people say social circles.
Oh, it makes me laugh when people say
social circles, bro.
Yeah. People that out for themselves. Uh
yeah. Yeah. Social circles. But uh
this country will never change.
I'll be on a baby Guinness today, lad. Yeah.
He just designed to annoy you.
You know how like gambling Yeah.
Oh, Franklin got knocked over. Like it's
it's designed to make you lose. It feels
like this country is designed to annoy you.
[ __ ] dog is attacking me, bro.
Where the [ __ ] do these dogs come from,
bro? What the [ __ ]
I look we [ __ ]
Look. Who's that? Franklin
[ __ ] I need to make a [ __ ] deal.
[ __ ] off soon. Thank you.
Feel like [ __ ] today.
I feel like stight today, bro. What the
[ __ ] Yeah, I went to the pictures to
see I know what you did last summer. I
watched the new horror film at 9. I had
a snooze. I woke up at 9:00 and I went
to the cinema.
Yeah, I went cinema.
Is that cute, Grezy?
My little caps should be here in a
couple of days.
£11 for free caps. Animated caps. That's
a [ __ ] bargain, bro.
I hope it don't rain. I don't know what
to wear today, lad.
I don't think it will rain.
Remember Peter B and his little cat?
Peter B and his little cat.
Peter Belly had his little cup. Yeah, that's cute. Go up.
He's dying to see King in it. You're
dying to see King.
[ __ ] king. I love the king, isn't it? Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] We Oh, [ __ ]
The car's going to be
when said that he doesn't have no home.
What do you think, Greavves? I was
laughing at it. He said I still haven't
found a room. It's not funny though.
Grezy. Nah, it's not funny. It's not
funny. Do you think it's funny, Grezy? I
don't think it's funny. Do you?
Nah, it's not funny, bro.
It's not funny, is it? No. Yeah. But yeah,
no, it's not funny, bro. Oh, [ __ ]
Anyways, I'm out of bit. Yeah, catch you
later. Maybe when I come back or something.