This one
here, bro. Out here, bro.
definitely out here. It's done like 10
approaches or so, but
remember your your past don't dictate your future.
Dictating it three [ __ ] years. Yeah, man. Help me.
>> Help me.
>> Never change in this country. Never.
Nicolo, I just about 10 sober, bro.
Like, literally before I just started
drinking. I've had three sibs. I had to
drink, bro. It's impressive.
Like, it's enough to get anyone on a
[ __ ] drink. It's just the same old in
this country. It is still predicting it.
People are saying, sorry, not predicting
it, still dictating it. People are
saying that it doesn't dictate the
future. It does because it's still
dictating it even now. Yeah, I know
about 10, bro. One from Newcastle, one
there, one there. Just not interested.
They said they weren't interested. It's
dictating it, bro. I'm not going to lie
to you. It's still dictating it.
You're still [ __ ] dictating it. You
will never change. Sad, sad, sad.
>> It's enough to get anyone on the [ __ ] drink.
Um, no. Same old as it will always be in this country.
>> I mean, you expect it. Just say old
England. What would you really say?
Yeah. It is the same old England.
Same old England that never changes. So,
I'd say, yeah, I you can predict the f
you can predict the future cuz it's
dictating it. It is still dictating it,
Nick. It's still dictating it.
It's still dictating it. You know what
Joe says about how the past don't
dictate the future, but it's because it
is and it has and it's still doing it.
You know what I'm saying? So, yeah.
I look fresh as [ __ ] today as well, bro.
You see what I'm wearing? Oh, two where? One sec.
I'm going in a minute anyways. I'm not
staying on here. I'm not staying on here
all day, but I'm just going to I can
show you, bro.
Wanted to switch up the switch up the
show you man. Yeah. Look at top baby.
I had to switch on the merch and that in
it. So, [ __ ] it.
Got no hair on the sides. I ain't saying
it, but I'm [ __ ] off. But yeah,
look at this.
It literally dictates the future. Your
past dictates the future in this
country. Living proof of it. Yeah, man.
Sad. side of this face.
I'm [ __ ] I'll get
what the I about 10 [ __ ]
I ear [ __ ] 10 [ __ ] approaches.
What the [ __ ] October.
Ain't done a session like this for ages,
bro. I ain't done a session like this for ages.
Like [ __ ] 10.
Literally like [ __ ] 10, bro. I swear
even done yet. I'm not even drunk.
This country will never change. Never.
This country will never change, bro. Ever. Ever.
about the past don't dictate your
future. Of course, it dictates the
future. Don't be sick. If it didn't, you
wouldn't be here. We wouldn't be having
this conversation right here, right now,
and I wouldn't be on it. So,
same old suckup people, same old
attitude, same old people, same old
England. Same old people, and same old
England. I was supposed to meet somebody
today. Yeah. And they weren't having
none of They They said they were going
to meet me. I said, "Oh." They said,
"What time?" If I told them the time,
they didn't come. I said, "I'm going
here at this time." And then all of a
sudden, they went quiet.
All of a sudden, they went [ __ ] quiet.
So, what the [ __ ]
It does when it comes to this. It does
when it comes to dating in this country.
Yes. Normally, don't. But dating in this
country definitely definitely definely does.
[ __ ] 10 approaches sober. I'm a [ __ ] bad
10 times sober. I'm not interested.
Yeah, I've done 10 sober. 10 complete
sober. Only just I've only just started drinking.
I need to start drinking that. Not interested.
>> Not interested, bro. And I'm 10 completely sober.
Anyone would think I'm [ __ ] Timmy Eldridge.
You never know. I know. I know because
I've been doing it for 3 years. So I
know. I know exactly what's going to
happen as well. So, you don't know, but
I know. I've got a good idea of what's
going to happen.
You do know because it's been happening
for 3 years and it's continuously
happening. It continues to
it continues to happen. So, I know I
know you might know, but I How the [ __ ]
can you say to someone that's been up
and down the country that they don't know?
What the [ __ ] bro? Come on, man. It's
[ __ ] stupid to even say that.
>> I [ __ ] know
that sense. You see what I'm saying? You
can't be positive. There no positive in
this situation other than leaving the
country. Yeah, there is a positive.
Yeah. Well, there is a positive.
There is a positive. Leave the country.
You can't be positive. It's so negative. I don't [Laughter]
think changing in this country smell.
Anyways, I'm going anyways because I
need to um see what I'm going anyway.
So, um I'm cutting the live stream off
now. Anyways, uh see you later. I might
go live later. Maybe not. I don't know. But
>> I'm going to that one over there, I reckon.
>> Yeah, I'm going to give that one a
little while. One second. I'm in the
live stream. I need to