Oh, [ __ ] hell. [Music]
Sorry, man. You coming a bit too late.
Sorry about that.
Isn't it mad that the only person that
comments on your on your channel is Red
Star? You need to get a life. Honestly,
you need to get laid.
See, the one thing about me Yeah. is
when I'm when I'm drunk. Yeah.
I'll say the same stuff as I'm drunk as
when I'm sober. That's the difference.
[ __ ] I really really get laid. I feel
sorry for you. You need to get a life
and get laid.
Stop showing off your benefits trying to
betray cuz the people that try to betray
betray that they've got money right are
the ones that don't have money. You understand?
So the more they do this like showing
all of these£10 notes and 20 pound
notes, it just goes to show how skinned
they really really really are. How they
have to try to portray
that they that they have money. It's
really really really really cute. to me.
I keep all mine in the bank cuz I know
that no one showed me [ __ ] no [ __ ]
10 grand, which they were supposed to
show me 10 grand and no one's been able
to do it yet. So, um yeah,
people that try to betray they've got
money or the ones that ain't got money,
just remember that. Remember that. Dad, [ __ ] hell.
That is weird, bro. I'm telling you,
definitely some jealousy for these
people. For these people to do what they
do every day. It has to be some form of
jealousy. Mental health jealousy. It's
really, really sad. I couldn't imagine
being jealous of someone every day. Me,
I really, really couldn't.
Every single time you get your housing
benefit, you withdraw all your housing
benefit, show the money, thinking that
you got money, and then you put it all
back in your account for when they take
it out your [ __ ] account. [ __ ] hell.
Jesus Christ. That is next level [ __ ] skin.
This guy needs to [ __ ] lose his virginity.
Seems every year it seems to get worse
for him, bro. Really does.
What is What is with all of them
fucking10 notes as well? What are with
all of them£10 notes? Who the [ __ ] has
that many10 notes
trying to make it seem like you got
money? It's [ __ ] cute.
Oh my god, it really is cute. How
desperate someone has to be to try to
convince people that they've got money. Oh [ __ ] What is
got five numbers yesterday, but I
preferred Thursday me. I just enjoyed
Thursday more than than I did Saturdays.
I don't really like Saturdays.
Then they tried to charge me. I need to
Yeah, I need to email LT about that.
Anyways, and he say you don't guess how
much they're charging to go and [ __ ]
fabric now. [ __ ] 35 quid
to go into [ __ ] a nightclub, bro.
That is madness.
Who the [ __ ] would play that? That's ridiculous, bro.
Seems a lot of [ __ ] changed, huh?
Seems a lot of [ __ ] has changed
since I've been there in two years.
Yeah, seems a lot of [ __ ] has changed, bro.
Anyways, we're waiting for Joe. Anyways,
come on, Joey.
Come on, Joey.
But I'm glad I've got that all booked,
bro. I needed to do that [ __ ] last
night when I come back. It's just too depressing.
This country is too depressing, bro. You
need to have a plan B otherwise you'll go mad
predicts the future. Well, you got
enough numbers anyways.
That 18year-old laughing from Canada
said you're from Canada, which was got
to be one of the worst places.
Oh, I can just imagine it. He said he
was from Toronto as well. Imagine trying
to date over there. And he was laughing
about it. I said, "You laugh cuz you're
immature, but you're not going to be
laughing in 10 years when you're 28,
mate, and you can't find someone and
you're going to end up in [ __ ]
Thailand. You won't be laughing then.
You [ __ ] won't be laughing then, mate.
It must be hard, but it's it's your life
that you're living. Yeah, man. You
should know. You're living that life.
You tell me, bro.
It must be. You're the one who's living
that life. No one else. So, you tell me.
Yeah, man. Bro, listen. There's
literally no point coming on here self projecting.
Anyways, bye-bye [ __ ] No spastics on
my channel. Bye-bye now.
Oh yeah, I meant to do a video to Lord Jay, but
I just couldn't be bothered. Um,
I just can't be bothered to be honest. Um,
Yep. Talking about yourself.
No talking about yourself on my channel.
No self projected on my channel. [Music]
Stop talking about yourself. Bye-bye. People
seem more and more um
they seem more and more closed off
nowadays as well.
which is another uh weird thing.
Can't believe what got three caps for £11.
That is a [ __ ] bargain, bro.
That is a bargain. One second.
Yeah, this guy was like,
"Wow, you just made four accounts just
to get blocked. Says a lot about your life." Self-reflector.
Imagine that. Yeah. You've just been
blocked. Yeah. And you've just made four
accounts just to get blocked. says a lot
about your life, eh?
So, yeah, I need to address this whole uh
uh law thing to be honest with you.
Can I be bothered
No, he didn't get it, which is weird.
I was worried about that stalker get my channel, bro.
Yeah, I used to be more confident than I am. Yeah.
And escort yesterday, mate. I can't
afford to be doing that [ __ ] now.
Can't afford to be doing that. Bollocks.
Like I was saying that this whole going
out and [ __ ] is it's purely through
boring. Once I can work again, mate, I'm
[ __ ] I ain't doing this [ __ ] anymore anyways.
Once I can f I can thingy again. So
like I was saying last night, it's not
that I care. It's just not normal. It's
just [ __ ] up. All of it's [ __ ] up.
[ __ ] up, man. Something A [ __ ] Yeah.
But like I said, you see so many guys,
right, that are sort of like normal
normal looking and they're with [ __ ]
mining, bro. And some of them not even
with mining. They're just with your
they're just with plain [ __ ] Jane
that you wouldn't even approach. So
you're not alone in it at all, you know,
which are people that you wouldn't even
approach. It's madness. So you're not
you're not alone in this situation, bro. Oh, bro.
I was [ __ ] moving. You know what I'm saying, brother?
Well, like I said, I think if you went
out every day for a week, yeah, even
doing sober approaches that you I don't
even think you would get a date to be
honest. Nowadays, I don't even think you would
unless you got extremely extremely extremely lucky.
People just don't trust people nowadays.
It's It is sad.
you know, so
but it's their loss at the end of the
day. No one else is.
Social media won't be able to save them
in 10 years. So,
we've got that booked. It's all good. I
think we don't need to uh
think about this anymore.
person was supposed to meet me yesterday
which we agreed to meet even though I
got out yesterday. What the [ __ ]
happened? You know,
one second. Someone listen to me.
Are you there, Joe? How are you, man?
How are you, pal?
Um, I went out yesterday.
I was waiting for you. Sorry about that.
I was just talking to man. I went out yesterday, bro. Yeah.
I don't know if you're still there.
Yeah, I went out yesterday, mate.
went out yesterday. Me? Um,
yeah. No one said I had a boyfriend. I
[ __ ] five different women. I got 20
numbers. Yeah. Yeah. I'm very very
lucky. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, man. very
very very very lucky because in in in 3
years right the day yesterday
everything became better was it [ __ ] it
was [ __ ] [ __ ] it was worse than Thursday
it was worse than Thursday I still got
these five numbers I've not text them
yet no it was bad really really bad
[ __ ] it was [ __ ] [ __ ] same old
England I booked Thailand when I come
back by the way I was like I can't live
like this anymore Well, mate, I was in I
was in that weather I was in I done 11
approach to sober then I done an
approach in the weather spoons. I
thought, "Nah, I'm getting out of this
country, bro. Just I can't live like
this no more."
You know, I can't live like this no
more. You know, at the end of the day,
if I if I live right, if I live if I
if I go out now, I ain't going to be I'm
not going to be bothered. I'm not going
to be bothered, bro, what happens cuz I
know I'm out of here. That's the That's
the way to go around it. Oh, and guess
what? I was going to go to this
nightclub that me and LT used to go to.
Do you know how much they're trying to
charge to go in now? £35 to get into it.
It weren't even like a proper rave. I
I'm not paying £35.
I'm not paying £35 [ __ ] pound. You mad. So
yeah, I I just went back home. I went to
that other place. I was like, I'm not
paying £35, bro. That's ridiculous.
So, I know it's not success because if
the numbers, if the numbers don't reply,
it's not success. Yeah.
There was this guy yesterday. I was
trying to get into this pub. Yeah. And
he's like, "Oh, like you're a bit like
you can't come in." I was like, "Okay,
whatever." I said, "Oh, it's disgusting."
And then um and then uh no one cares
about that virgin. One second. We'll get
on to them in a minute. One second, bro. Listen.
Um, and he's like, "It's not
disgusting." I said, "Well, it is." It
was like some guy with this long beard
and stuff. And then he was being like
argumentative and I was like, "Well, it
is. It is disgusting." And he's like,
"Oh, that's not the word." I said, "Yes,
it is." He was trying to be awkward,
right? And I was standing in the same
place the whole time. And he's like,
"Oh, you're being violent." I was like,
"Being [ __ ] violent. I've stood at
the same place the whole time we've had
this argument. No one's moved forward.
No one's gone to anyone. Who the [ __ ] is
being violent? They're such [ __ ]
stupid little [ __ ] bro, in this
country. Violent. I'm I've never been
violent in my life, mate.
Oh, bro. This country is finished.
Oh, yeah. And Yeah. Anyways, back to
that. Anyways, Joe, [ __ ] I find it so
cute how he has to try to convince
people that he's not skint showing his
benefit money off again. I mean, bro,
you can show any amount of money that
you want, but you haven't shown 10
grand, which is what I'm waiting for.
So, the only time you're going to spike
my interest is when you show me my 10
grand, which is what I've been asking
for for the past 2 years. Like, I admit
it right now, I've got about two grand,
you know? I'm like got two grand on my
own money. Yeah. You know, I don't need
to go out and [ __ ] withdraw 2,000
[ __ ] pounds to show you the same
thing over and over and over again. You
have been showed money time and time and
time and time again and no one has
beaten me. So, it's you can show your
benefit money all you want. You know,
trying to convince people that, you
know, you're not, you know, that you're
not skin. It's relentless because you
haven't shown 10 grand, which is what
I'm waiting for. I'm waiting for 10
grand. I'm waiting for 10 grand. Um,
so yeah, you save your benefit money and
then you show your benefit money off. Okay.
Why have you got so many10 notes as
well? That's a bit sus.
But I don't need to go out and [ __ ]
withdraw. Maybe I've got like a little
bit over two grand. I could go out right
now, withdraw two grand, and have 300
left in the bank. I don't need to do
that. You know what I'm saying? I don't
need to do that, bro.
I don't need to convince people try to
convince people that I have money.
Oh, are you still there? By the way,
Joe, as well,
let me tell you about this Lord J guy
quickly also as well cuz I caught up on
some of his live stream um yesterday.
Yeah, I want to tell you about uh this
this this guy as well.
how literally nothing he does makes any sense.
So, uh, yeah.
One second, bro. Hold up.
I need to
I need to see where my caps are coming.
He went on his live stream saying about
how, oh, why does PJ say that he's got
savings? What is it? Cuz I do have
savings, personally. And he was like,
oh, I don't even have £500. Why would I
have £500? I bought a TV the other day,
right? That was like almost £500.
Why wouldn't someone have savings? I
should have a lot more than that at 27
to begin with, right? And then and then
think about it like this, right? He's
another one that comes on here tries to
convince that people that he's got all
of this money better t Yeah. If you go
on his YouTube channel, you see that
he's he's put a star out where he's
selling merchandise. Think about this,
bro. How this doesn't make any sense.
Yeah. He claims that what he gets
thousands and thousands a month and he
owns property da. If he was getting all
of this money right, he would not be
swallowing up his pride to try to get
extra bit of money on YouTube. A tiny
tiny extra bit of money on YouTube. He
wouldn't even bother. Say, for example,
you got three grand. Let's just say for
example, you got three grand a month,
right? Let's just say you got three
grand as an example. Would you swallow
your pride and beg for money when it's
only going to get you what? Another
150,200 a month. It doesn't make sense.
And also another thing is with his
merch, right, it has no substance. It's
it's it's stupid. Like big YouTubers
used to do that. But the thing is with
big YouTubers with big YouTubers, right,
they would make millions. They knew that
they would make millions. So you would
turn down extra money. If you was
getting thousands a month, why would you
swallow your your pride for a couple of
extra£100? It don't make sense. It
doesn't it does not make any sense.
It would make more sense if he was free
on three for £500 a month doing this.
So if you're getting all of this money,
you wouldn't do that madness for a
couple of extra£100. It makes no sense.
It makes no sense. It's like the whole
Uber thing. I only I only done that
because I was losing the [ __ ] well I
was losing the house otherwise I
wouldn't do it and you would make more
money on the Uber. So it's like it's it
doesn't make no sense whatsoever and
he's also swallowing up No, no. It's the
fact that which makes no sense about it
is a he's swallowing his pride doing it
and b he's making barely anything from
it whereas like big YouTubers would make
millions and millions and millions and
millions which is the whole point of why
they started selling merch. People used
to do that like [ __ ] KSI and all of
that because they knew that they'd make
millions. He is not going to make he's
going to make literally probably not
even 10% of his income. So, it all
points to him being on a lot less money
than he claims he is. That's the only
way it would make any sense.
Like, do you understand? That's the only
Who would swallow their pride even for
an extra 250 a month when you're making
all that money? It don't make sense. It
literally does not make sense. You know,
that whole time I never ever come here
begging for money.
So, it seems that you wouldn't be that
desperate for a tiny bit of extra money
if you had all this money. That's the
point I'm getting at. Unless you was
going to make tons and tons and tons and
tons and tons. That's what I'm saying, bro.
No, it doesn't it doesn't matter if it's
a joke, if it's not a joke. He's trying
to make money from it, you know.
I'm never begging anyone for money.
I would never beg anyone for money. I
don't want money from anyone.
He's in Thailand. But I know what I'm
saying is true. Anyways, he's trying. He begs people.
Uh L doesn't matter. Why? Okay. [ __ ] all
of this. And here's the thing is it's it's
all of this membership, all of these
things that he's doing to try to make
extra money. He wouldn't be doing this
if he was rolling in money. That's what
I'm trying to say. That's the whole
point I'm trying to make. But I don't
think you understand what where I'm
getting at. So yeah.
So he wouldn't if he had all of this
money, he wouldn't be begging for donations.
He wouldn't be [ __ ] trying to get
people's money. That's what I'm trying to say.
But because look at his audience.
He's He's not even on Pit, bro. He's on
[ __ ] maybe£3400 a month cuz that's
the only way it would make sense. That's
Say I got 2 grand a month. Yeah. Say I
got 1.8 a month when I finally be able
to find something. I don't need extra
money. 1.8 2K would be enough for me.
So I don't need I don't need,
you know, extra money, bro.
But you know, I I'll be fine with that.
I can make my what if I and I can make
my own extra money.
I know I'm making sense, bro, cuz I I
know how these things work.
I know how these things work. If
someone's that desperate for a tiny
extra bit of money,
something ain't right. That I know I'm
making sense, bro. I'm I'm I'm more
intelligent than he will ever be. I know these things.
And he's also swallowing his pride
whilst he's doing it as well. Which so
makes sense because if you're coming on
here right calling people skin sk skin
skin like listen to yourself.
I don't have 500. Why would I have £500?
Why the [ __ ] would I not have £500?
I'll be honest. I got about 2k and a
little bit more. Oh wow. you know. So, yeah.
Oh, I'm obviously gay, bro.
That's boring now, man. That whole
you're gay thing is really, really, really boring.
I mean, it's not as gay as traveling to
another country to meet a man. But, you
know, do you know, and and this is the
thing, Joe. I don't need to I don't need
to I don't need to block any of these
people. You're saying that I'm gay for
[ __ ] um drinking and giving a guy my
number? Okay, fair enough. But you
people sit online talking to men all
day, every day. We even get people
traveling to another country to meet a man.
I mean, that's even more sus. I met two
guys yesterday from Nottingham. They
were Indian seeks. Gave them my number.
Got their number.
And and and and your point is I don't
sit on YouTube all day talking to men
like LJ. I don't travel to different
countries to meet men. So yeah. Yeah, man.
Nah, it's not at all.
Not at all at all.
I'm having some pork today. Greasy.
Oh, you still there Joe? Hi Joe, are you
still there? There's another thing I
need to address with you as well.
Oh, uh, King come in my room earlier,
Grezy, and he was giving me kisses. He
loves me. King King loves me.
Yeah, King loves King loves Peter Belly.
Anyways, you're gone. Yeah,
but I know I'm making sense with the
whole RJ thing cuz no one that's getting
all that money would swallow up their
pride or a tiny tiny extra bit of money every month.
Unless he's making thousands a month,
then obviously it's a different story,
but he's not. So,
um it just doesn't make any sense whatsoever.
And then when you look at it, it all
points to him being skinned again. So yeah,
everything points to him being skint.
You know when you got arrows? Yeah,
greasy. The arrows are pointing and
pointing and pointing and pointing to
him being skinn. Do you understand?
I mean, yeah, I was doing Uber because I
was losing money and I wasn't begging
people for [ __ ] money, you know? And
then if you added up your actual
monthly's money, right? Yeah.
Yeah. But no, what I was saying, Omar,
is basically he was saying that
why do I keep saying that I have savings
when I do have savings? And he was
trying to say how I don't have £500. And
I'm thinking, hold on, if he gets all of
this money, why is he doing these
things? Why is he trying to do anything
and everything for a tiny bit of extra
money? It doesn't make sense. Only
people that are skinn would do that.
That's what I'm saying. Are people that
would make loads and loads and loads and
loads and loads and loads of money,
which he's not going to make loads of
money because all of the people on his
channel are just skin.
It doesn't make no sense. It makes no sense whatsoever
because the only thing it would the only
reason it would make sense is if
um he was on a lot less money. He's got
to be on £400 a month, bro.
Like for him to be doing that is
desperation. No one's that desperate,
bro, for a tiny extra bit of money if
they're racking it in. Trust me.
But I only don't [ __ ] Uber cuz I was
[ __ ] losing money on the [ __ ]
house and [ __ ] So like I had to do it.
But even then, like, yeah, I wouldn't I
wouldn't have done it. But to be fair,
sometimes I would maybe do it once a
week cuz I was bored. if I had nothing
else to do. But bro, he is swallowing up
his pride for a tiny bit of extra money.
It just doesn't make no sense. It don't
Literally doesn't make any sense.
Look, if you've got a following of
3.6,000 subscribers, they're all skint.
All of the people that watch him are
skint. Think of it, bro.
He is a fantasist, bro. [ __ ] proper fantasist.
going on about me drinking baby
Guinness. What the [ __ ] What?
He's a [ __ ] idiot, man.
I don't know why people like him and
Virgin Boy need to try to con need to
try to convince people they ain't
they've got money. I don't get it.
Like, I don't know why they need to
convince people that they've got money
when they really don't.
You got [ __ ] virgin boy showing these
benefits off again.
What am I doing? I'm just chilling, bro.
I went out last night. I'm going to go
I'm going to go get some pork in a bit.
Have some roast pork later.
Yeah, it was raining bad yesterday, bro.
[ __ ] bad. It was raining bad. I'm not
moving back in.
And that's another thing. Virgin boy
only talks about people living with
their mom because his mom starved him.
There's nothing wrong with living with
your mom. It really isn't that bad. I
live I lived by myself. I lived with my
mom. I lived with [ __ ] tenants. And
it it ain't that bad. It's nowhere near
as bad as that virgin makes out.
It's nowhere near as bad as that [ __ ]
virgin makes out. Trust me.
You know, it's actually very common
nowadays for people to um live with their parents
or they live with their brother or
some of them live in a room, but most of
the time they live with their parents to be honest.
It's nowhere near as bad that Virgin
makes out. Trust me. Yeah.
Cuz you've never worked a day in your
life. You [ __ ] lazy [ __ ] So you
wouldn't know how expensive things are.
Yeah, nice bit of piggy, bro. Yeah, I
went out yesterday. PC, lad.
But there's nothing really wrong with
living with your mom, you know,
especially when you're out all day. I'm
out all day anyways. Well, normally
there's literally nothing wrong. It's
not that bad. It really isn't even that
It ain't that bad, bro. It ain't that [ __ ] bad.
It's nowhere near as bad as that virgin
makes out. Trust me, bro. What do you do
all day? Do you Do you go out? I mean, I
I was out yesterday for [ __ ] hours.
All day. I don't ever stay in Yeah.
He needs Do you know what I wish? Did
the council take that house from him? So
he's forced to work and then you know
and then he would be crying [ __ ] to
his dad because he won't even be able to
afford to pay rent.
You know what I mean?
He's obsessed with people living with
their mom because his mom starved him.
It all comes down to projection. Do you understand?
You should say, "Oh, you live with your
mom?" I was like, "Yeah, I'm 20 and your
mom starved you, which is why you don't
live with your mom, which is al which is
also another normal age that I'm in." Yeah.
See, people like Lord Jay and stuff,
they very they're very easy. Do you know
what I mean? Because they're so stupid. Yeah.
The only reason I didn't move back in
with my mom is cuz I was I was used to that house.
I was used to that house sort of thing.
So that's the only reason.
But let's not start talking about
independent because you've never worked
a day in your [ __ ] life. You know, it
got to a point where I wasn't getting
rent for ages because it would all come
at the same time. So, I was making my
own money on the Uber and I was
basically living by myself as well.
That's what independent is. It's not you
live off the government, right? It's not
that you live off the government and the
government gives you a house. That's not independent.
Independent is going out and making your
own money. I was living off the own
money I was making.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah. Homer, I went out yesterday doing
some approaches, bro.
All got boyfriends in it. They've all got boyfriends.
Somehow make it to this [ __ ]
supermarket. I'm [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
Nothing wrong with living with your mom or
nothing wrong at all with thinking
thinking of it. Nah,
very hard to live by yourself nowadays in London.
Yeah. Bro, I'll show you what I was
You want to see what I was wearing yesterday, bro?
I'll show you, man. I actually looked good. Austral definitely definitely
It's definitely gotten worse.
It's definitely definitely got Oh no,
wrong channel. [ __ ]
One second, bro. Yeah, it's definitely
gotten worse, lad.
It's definitely got worse.
They just aren't interested.
One second, but I'm going to show you.
It's just uploading.
You think it will ever change? Never.
It will never change in this country. Never.
Meet me yesterday.
No, it won't ever change in this country. Never.
It will stay the same forever.
And you know the maddest thing is right
I met some um I was speaking to like
some guy on the train right guy average
to above average like just a normal guy.
This is how [ __ ] up it is. You will
see that some of the women that people
are with are just like the plain Jane
that you wouldn't even approach. They're
either mingers or they're just like
average looking and you wouldn't even
you wouldn't even approach them. That's
how you know like dead you're down bad,
bro. And they're like fully fully white.
So I mean like look, you got all of
these guys, right? Even even when they
have partners, bro, they're like plain janes.
Like fours, fives is something that you wouldn't even
there's no like attractiveness to them,
if that makes sense. So that's how you
know it's getting worse. Definitely.
Definitely is definitely getting worse.
1 million% bro in the last sort of 18
months bro it has I'll show you one second bro
so now you're getting guys are actually
yeah settling yeah
and some of them are even better than me
like they've got good jobs they're fully white
I don't look fully white as well so
that's you know what I'm saying like
yeah they are definitely settling
I'll show you me bro one
This is what I was wearing yesterday,
bro. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, they're settling, bro.
There you go, bro.
There we go, bro.
It's just a boss t for from ages ago, bro.
I forgot all about it. But yeah, as you
can see, bro,
this is not [ __ ] up. Because I think
like, oh, like you're not ugly, you look
good and [ __ ] you got some money, you
can't find someone. But then you have to
think that there's also people that are
better than you, better than me, and
they can't even find anyone. And if they
do find someone, they're [ __ ]
they're [ __ ] playing games.
Like, so it's like that's there is
actually people that are also better
than me as well that can't even find anyone.
people that are better looking, people
that are people that have got better
careers. That's that's another thing.
But it doesn't it doesn't change, bro.
It doesn't change.
I think the [ __ ] up thing about it,
Omar, is you're not fat and ugly.
So, it's hard to like sort of
accept how [ __ ] [ __ ] up it is. Do
you know what I mean? It's weird. It is so weird.
But then look around you. You know, you
see it for yourself. So,
it's crazy, isn't it? It is bad. It
really is bad.
Shouldn't be this hard.
I wonder what it's going to be like in 10 years.
Bye-bye. Yeah, it don't make sense
because if you was like if you look like
Timmy Eldridge, right, or you look like
Lord Jay, then it' be like, "Oh, okay,
whatever." But you don't like you
shouldn't be easily be able to find someone.
And then I was going to go Fabrics
yesterday. I don't know if you've ever
been to Fabrics and they were trying to
charge £35 to go in. I met some [ __ ]
woman on the bench. She gave me her
number. She was [ __ ]
And uh yeah, I might pay £35 to get him,
but no way. But yeah,
a been fabrics in like two years. So I
thought, [ __ ] it, give it a whirl.
And it's like you're going to pay £35
and then it's sort of getting back and
where I'd already got five numbers. Um,
and it's like you're going to be paying
£35 just to get I've got a boyfriend
cuz you're going to get in there as
well. Fabrics is good. Fabrics is
I ain't been for two I think it's been
about two years. Yeah, it weren't last
time. It was It was somewhere before
that, but I don't know about 35 quid.
Bro, that's a bit steep. But I thought
20 was a lot, but I ain't paying £35.
So yesterday I thought, okay, I spent £7
including food. I got five numbers. You know,
you know what I'm saying? I to be honest
with you Omar I like to stick to pubs
now like Weather Spoons or just like a
normal pub like an Irish pub. I just
prefer pubs because
the thing with clubs is right it's it's
a cockfest. They try to tell you that
you can't wear tracksuit bottoms.
Um you know they discriminate as well
and it's just like I'd rather just stick
to a pub. Um
I don't know. I just prefer pubs. I
don't know about you and yeah, it's I
mean I got banned in in in a club for
talking to people [ __ ] the other
week. I mean yeah, God knows but I just
prefer honestly I just prefer a pub
just like a nice pub, you know,
or even might maybe like a cocktail bar.
I just don't like these. I don't like clubs, bro.
the bounces discriminate and yeah
and there was one yesterday and he was
just being awkward. Um I don't know like
can I use the toilet? I had a drink in
my hand. He's like we can't let you and
just use the toilet
and then he was like oh you can't stand
on this line and he was just being
awkward and I just said listen I'm not
going to give you a highlight of your
night. I just couldn't be bothered with
it bro to be honest with you. He's just being awkward. So,
another thing you got to deal with in
this country, [ __ ] awkward people.
I know. I think I I think I make sense
with what I'm saying, in it. I just
can't be bothered dealing with it.
That's why you should just stick to like
a spoons or any pub or even on the
street or or something like that.
I don't know about you. I don't know how
you feel about it, but
I don't know.
I feel like London's better for pubs in
the street and then out of London is
better for clubs. Does that make sense? Hopefully. Who knows? Yeah.
Do you know what? To be honest with you,
Omar, it's because I'm bored. I like I
can't work at the minute. So, I'm just
This whole women thing is purely because
of boredom. To be honest with you, I've
got like some money. I can't work at the
minute. It's purely because of boredom.
You know, I like to get out of my mom's
hair and I don't like to keep put stress
on my mom and stuff. So that's why I
just like just like leave her to it and
[ __ ] to be honest with you. I I think
mine is just purely boredom. Like when I
was like when I was working, bro, I
would just get an escort once a month
and that's fine. I don't really care
about it when I you know when you're
making money. But when you can't really
do anything and you're bred, you don't
have anything to lose by spending
[ __ ] 60 70 quid.
Like on Thursday it was really good,
bro. I met some really cool people. It
was sound. I prefer Thursdays. I also
prefer Thursdays as well. I don't know
what it is with Saturdays. It's just I
don't know. I just prefer Thursdays. But
I I just do it purely cuz of partying, bro.
purely purely bored and
recently I've had nothing to do. So
yeah, and that's the thing is when I
went out Thursday Oh boy. Yeah. It
wasn't for women. It's because I just
wanted to go out anyways. But the thing
is is I was not it was I can't I can't
help but acknowledge how [ __ ] up it is
because it is [ __ ] up. Someone like
me, you can't find anyone. Like I'm not in denial.
Like I don't think I was moaning. I
don't think I was complaining but I'm
not in denial.
That's the difference. I'm not in denial.
And I think a lot of these guys are in
denial. Like there was this guy from
Canada. He's 18. And I was telling him
about we was talking and that and he
just thought all of it was funny. And I
said, "Bro, but the thing is like you're
from Canada. I wouldn't be laughing if I
was you because in 10 years or 9 years,
you won't be laughing, mate, when you
end up in [ __ ] Thailand.
And trust me, I got 10 years on you. So
if it's bad for me now, think of how
it's going to be for him in 10 years in
Canada of all places. I wouldn't be
laughing, bro. But he's immature
cuz he won't be [ __ ] laughing, mate.
When he can't get laid and he needs to
go [ __ ] Thailand, Canada of all
places as well. Bad, bad, bad.
Yeah, but it's never going to change.
No, I don't want kids. I don't want children.
just do it purely out of boredom.
But it doesn't change. But the thing is
with this Omar, it doesn't ever change.
That's the problem. I don't have any
hope. That's the whole problem is the
point is I don't have hope. I only do it
because I'm bored and I have nothing
else to do. So there is there is no
hope. Deep down, you know, you ain't got
Oh, little Pierre.
Well, they'd have to be French. But no,
there is there deep down there is no
hope. Cuz you know the thing is, yeah,
obviously I lost some money and [ __ ]
from the thing and that, but I was
thinking I was thinking, bro, like,
yeah, but you don't know what's around
the corner. You could win a football bet
tomorrow. You could win some money. You
don't really know what the future holds
when it comes to this. But with women,
you do know where it stands. You know
exactly how it stands.
Stop talking about yourself. Um, yeah.
So, like you you you do know where you
stand with it
because it is literally the same old,
you know. It is literally the same old.
So, you you do have an idea.
I need to try to find ways to make
[ __ ] money now. Good luck with that.
I don't think you can, though. I think
the only thing you can do Yeah. is maybe
take a loan out and maybe try to start
your own business. It's hard nowadays,
bro, to to to make money.
I can't be wasting it on [ __ ] £35 to
get into clubs. It was all right when I
you know you get loads of money but now
it's it's like you you don't
there's like no like side hustles at all anymore.
It's so hard to make money nowadays.
I think the only thing you can actually
do gre is save benefits there. There's
literally nothing else.
There's there it's hard to make money nowadays.
It's really hard to make money nowadays, bro. [ __ ]
Yeah. So, you say you get benefits and
you save 250 a month. 250. 250. 250 is
all you do. It's all you really can do.
There is really no other way.
Really, really is no other way.
It's bad, is it, bro?
That's why most people are skin. Why do
you think most people don't go out
drinking? Cuz they're all skin. All of
the people that come out, all of the
people that go, you don't understand,
Harry. All of the people that go out
drinking in central London are mainly
tourists. Have you noticed that?
Because they don't have money now.
People don't have money nowadays in this country.
That's why most of them are not even
from here. The ones that do go out
drinking, have you noticed that? Because
they don't have money.
75% of people I would say struggle with money.
You know, probably about 75% of grievy I
would say struggle with money because I
would remember like back all them years
I'd meet people grieving and they'd
always struggle with money. Like more
more people struggle than don't struggle 100%.
Like I remember a woman that was 37, she
said, "I don't really have much money."
Um I know people that didn't even have
20. Like trust me, people are struggling
hard. That's why people don't don't
don't go out. And if they do go out, but
obviously you get people that go out,
but people are struggling with money definitely.
So, even now I won't be struggling. I'll
just have to be careful with it. Like, I
won't be struggling. I won't be scared.
But I'm not going to have loads and
loads and loads and loads to keep
wasting, which is fine. I'm I'm I'm okay
with that now. I've had the life. Got my
stonies greasy. Got my little caps
coming. I've lived the life, bro. So, I don't really
It is what it is, bro. What What can you
do in it?
It took a while to accept it, but it is
what it is. There's nothing anyone can do. So,
yeah, most people are definitely definitely suffering
really. Like, it's bad. It is bad.
You're lucky to even have two [ __ ]
grand in this day and age, mate. [ __ ]
hell. I think that's one of the reasons
I don't gamble anymore cuz where money
is so hard to get, you don't want to be [ __ ] gambling. [Music]
Why are you asking silly questions, bro?
I need to try and get this fold phone as
well over which is going to cost me £500
up front as well. That's another thing I
need to try to
uh It's not It's not It's not easy, bro.
It's not easy.
I need to pop to the shop in a minute. Oh, [ __ ]
Have I ever been in love? Never.
Nope. I'm 27 and I've never been in love. No.
What does that mean?
What does What does being What does
being in love mean? I don't know what that means. No,
I don't know what that means, bro.
What does being in love mean?
No, I don't know what that means, bro.
No, I I I never ever heard of that
saying before in love. Really?
I didn't know that. I didn't know that.
even know that, bro. Jeez.
I'm being sarcastic if you didn't if you didn't know.
27 yard if they've ever been in love. Of
course they have. What the [ __ ] Um,
I became an incel.
Um, basically when your mom stopped shagging me.
Uh, basically when your mom stopped
shagging me, I became an incel.
Yeah. When your mom stopped shagging me, bro.
Uh, made me become a big incel. Yeah,
I need to [ __ ] somehow go to the shop. Oh,
it's so far away as well. I'm [ __ ] knackered, mate.
But yeah, anyways, most people are
struggling nowadays anyways.
But you've got people like [ __ ] L and
Virgin Boy trying to portray that
they've got loads and loads of money
when in reality they got [ __ ] all, mate.
Why do they do this though, Harry? and
like Virgin Boy and Lar, why do they have to
why do they have to betray that they
they have loads and loads and loads and
loads of money? Why why do they do this?
I don't understand.
When in reality, they have nothing
because if they did, they wouldn't be
doing [ __ ] things that swallow up all
the pride they've got left to make a bit
of extra money.
This doesn't make sense. It don't make
doesn't make no sense.
Doesn't make any sense, bro.
But they have to convin they have to try
to act like they don't that they have
money. It's weird. It is weird that,
don't it? It is weird that um we Bro,
anyways, I'm going to go and get text
these numbers, get some piggies.
I'm [ __ ] out of here, man. So,
bye-bye. Bye bye bye bye bye. I might be back later.