Oh [ __ ]
Oh [ __ ] It's not plugged in, is it?
So therefore, that can't be
cuz it's not plugged in. Oh [ __ ]
£35 to get into a [ __ ] rave. [ __ ]
that, bro. Anyways, I'm coming off this
[ __ ] I'm after today. Anyways, man,
it's getting [ __ ] weird again with
these little creepy losers.
It's getting weird again, bro.
It's getting [ __ ] weird.
Five. That is five. Yeah.
One, two, three, four, five.
What do our pictures nowadays? Any
success? Um, what do you think? We're in
England and it's been the same old for years. So, no.
And I need to get this phone as well and
they're not it's not in stock. trying to
get this old phone and it's not in stock
until the 7th.
So once I get this phone, I could
probably go out one more time and then
I'm done cuz I need to save now
cuz I booked these flights. So I can't
afford to be spending any more money in
this [ __ ] old country. So once I get
this phone, that's me.
So So yeah,
why would you think anything would
change when the same thing's been going
on for years?
I don't understand that. How you
possibly think it could change when it's
been going on for years and it continues
to get worse and it continues to
dictate. You know what I'm saying?
How why why would it change? I don't
understand. How could it possibly change? Huh?
I get I'm getting some nice pork from me as well. Yeah.
Obviously I did, but we're not in
Thailand now. We're in England.
But no, you'll never get success here.
It would always be the same boyfriend
[ __ ] The whole country is a dive, bro. The [ __ ]
It will never change in this country. Never.
Even Joe Even though Joe says your past
don't dictate your future. Well, it's
still dictating it. It's It dictated it
yesterday. It dictated it Thursday.
It dictated it the week before that. It
dictated it the past of a few years. I mean,
the same people are in England. The same
people have got unrealistic
standards. So, what's going to be
different when you go out again?
I done 11 of them sober yesterday. It
reminds me why I don't do them sober.
What? What's going to happen literally again?
What will happen again when you go out again? Bro,
I only went out cuz I had nothing else
to do. So, yeah.
Yeah, good for them. There's also
millions of people that are single.
There's also millions of people that are
single. And there's also millions of
people that have to lower their
standards. So, my videos prove
everything when you try to start a
conversation with a stranger. There's
also millions of people that are single.
Um, most men are single. About one in
four men are in a relationship. Tells
you all you need to know. Every single
person, not well, not every single
person, but lots of people I come across
are single. Most of the people I know
are single from different social circles
from which is how I know they don't have
boyfriends. Most of the people that I
come across are single. So nice madeup
statistic. And also the people that are
in relationships or with ugly women.
Most of the days nowadays, most of the
people that are with women nowadays,
they are hunching below, mate. That guy
that I was speaking to on the train
yesterday, he must have been [ __ ] a
normal looking person, right? And his
girlfriend was a plain jane with glasses.
Tells you all you need to know. And I
saw it a few times as well. I'm thinking
[ __ ] So even now when these people are
getting in relationships, look at the
people who they ended up with.
And the fact that most most of the
people I know, most of the men that I
know, so whether they're tenants,
whether they're people I met on a night
out, whether they're people I know
online, they're all single.
They're literally They literally are all single.
Like the most of the people I know are
single. I'm I'm not even joking. Let me
let me see. I'm trying to think
of them are single. There are some that
are in relationships.
These people are single.
These people are single. The tenants are
This guy's single.
So what you're saying doesn't really
make a lot of sense because most of the
people are single. Most men are single.
One in about four men are in a
relationship. And when they are in a
relationship, look at who they're in a
[ __ ] relationship with,
mate. There are many, many, many, many
single people. Many, many, many, many single people,
you know. So, no. [ __ ] mate. I
know. I've gone out. I've been there.
Done it. Worn the t-shirt. And it
doesn't matter even if there were loads
and loads of people in relationships.
You've proved with your videos that you
can't get in a relationship. So other
people are irrelevant. Even if that was
true, even though it's not true because
I know people and I know that most of
the people that I know are single. So
that doesn't make any sense. Whatever
statistic you're trying to come up with,
it don't make sense because most of the
people I know are single. That's what I'm saying.
Yes, there are. And I've also had
chances of being in relationships. And
yes, there are people that's not been in
relationship. There's people out there
that are virgins.
And I've had chances to be in
relationships. And I basically have been
in a relationship. So again, try again.
Stick to what you first said. Yeah. And
don't try try and change the subject
because you're you're wrong. Like it's
it's [ __ ] I can go on my WhatsApp
right now where I I can tell you all
these people that are not connected to
each other and they're all single. Yeah. So,
yeah, most of the people I know are
single and they're not connected to any of them.
Uh, it's not about a mindset, it's about
reality. It's not about mindset. It's about reality.
It's not a mindset thing. It's reality.
I went out yesterday and I'm living
proof of it. them pretending that
they've got boyfriends. I'm living proof
of it. It's not being optimistic. It's
being real with yourself, which is what
the approaching videos show. It's
reality for not getting success.
And we just go round and round in
circles. And this is exactly why I
booked Thailand because of these same
conversations. Like as soon as I got
back in here yesterday, I booked
Thailand because it's no way to live.
We're just going round and round in circles again. So yeah,
you know, and it's even I noticed even
the people that were in relationships
who they were in relationships with,
which also told me a lot about myself.
So you got one decent looking guy who's
fully white with a plain Jane.
So I mean that just tells you there's
better people than me that are single.
There's people that go to the gym.
There's people that got six packs.
There's people that have good jobs and
they still can't find nothing.
Like you think of yourself, but there's
people that are better than you that
still can't find no one. And if they do
find someone, they're [ __ ] the plain
[ __ ] jame. You know what I mean? So,
it's not about mindset. There's too many
stuck up [ __ ] in this country. That's
literally what someone on Reddit said
and that that is the truth.
I'm not in denial. all of this whole
like, oh, it's mindset and all of this
stuff that people make up. I'm not in
denial. It's not even about me
complaining. I'm not in denial.
I'm really, really, really, really not
in denial about this. So many people are
in denial. Just like that guy in Canada,
I said to him, "You can laugh all you
want. You're in denial, bro. You won't
be laughing in 10 years when you're
[ __ ] especially in a country like that."
So, no, they're definitely suckup
[ __ ] in this country. Like, I I I've
even watched other people approach.
Yeah. And they get the same [ __ ] Ain't
ain't that a thing.
Ain't that a thing that you're watching
other people get the same old black,
white, [ __ ] whatever skin color that
they are. That just goes to show you
that it's them. Two people that are
completely not related, right? Doing
completely different approaches and
they're getting the same old. Isn't that
a coincidence? Huh? No. It's these
[ __ ] in this country. 1 million%. You
have none of these problems in Asia.
None of them at all. At all. All of
these people that blame other things is
called in denial.
And they'll learn that as well. You
know, as they when they're old and
they're rocking in that chair and they
still haven't found anyone from sing.
They just would know all along that
they're just [ __ ]
in denial. What the [ __ ] is going on
here? Autism, mate. Yeah, you have got
autism. Stop talking about yourself.
Yeah. Yeah, you do have what been refunded.
One second. What the [ __ ] is going on here?
They might refund me the money and they
gave me the cups for free.
But yeah, the thing is I'm not in denial.
One sec. What the [ __ ] is going on here?
I just bought these.
I know there's nothing wrong with being
autistic. Tell that to yourself because
you're the one that's got it. There's
nothing wrong with being autistic. I
know. Tell that to yourself. You're the
one that's got autism.
I know, bro. What the [ __ ] Hold on.
Of course there's nothing wrong with it.
You've got it yourself,
you know. So yeah, one second.
What the [ __ ]
Oh, I received two.
That doesn't make sense. One second. Hold on.
I don't understand. This doesn't make
any sense, brother.
You've never had a woman in your life.
That's why you're sing. But that's the
thing is you've never had a woman in
your life. Yeah, you have got autism.
That's why you resort to uh that's why
you resort to sing.
This don't make no sense whatsoever,
mate. You've never had a woman. So, I
mean, that's that's that's not possible.
You've got a bird next to you right now.
Keep telling yourself that. I swear
these are the same spastics, bro. I'm
leaving after today. Anyways, this um
community anyways but I've got stuff to do.
I'm leaving this. I said this earlier
that these these people here are proper proper spastics.
So many in denial simps. I don't know
how how many years can people live in denial for?
You would think that I would simp women.
Here's the thing, Greavvesy. Yeah. You
would think, right? I listen um Harry,
you have always been single and you will
always be single. Tell yourself that.
You know the thing is Grezy, anybody
would think that I would be the one sing
women since I've had more women than all
of these people. Anyone would think that
I'd be the one I'd be the one sing. But
they don't get no women
and then they simp
bullying me. But no one in here could
ever bully me. Are you [ __ ] mad? You
people bully yourself. Anyways, I'm
trying to [ __ ]
understand what what what is the refund
about? But um anyone would think I'd be
the one singing women, but I'm not in
denial. I'm not living in denial. I'm
not scared to say what I see. I say how
I see it. But these people don't get no
women and they simp over them. It's
weird. That's so weird.
I'm not scared.
I don't understand. This doesn't make no sense.
What the [ __ ]
I don't want I want them caps. But yeah,
I'm not in denial. Yeah,
I've had five one night stands. I've had
[ __ ] I've had kisses. I've had
dates. Basically been in a relationship.
But I'm not in denial.
That's the difference. I'm not in denial
about what they're like. And I won't
defend them because I'm not in denial.
So I don't know why they children.
Yeah. So, oh [ __ ] Why are they in denial anyways?
These people really are in denial. They
don't get no women, but they still Why
is it always the people that don't get
women are the ones that simp?
Because they think by sing it will get
them women. I don't know why they do it.
Simp will never get you laid, which is
why you're sing in the first place, cuz
you can't get laid. It's [ __ ] up, is
it? It's actually a madness, bro. Yeah.
And you know what's so mad, Harry, is
that you talk about depression, but
you've been on it for years and you
can't get off YouTube.
So, what does that say about your life,
bro? You've been on it for years and you
can't get off it. And you're what, in
your 30s, 40s?
That's what you call depression, me, lad. Yeah.
I don't know why they defend women. It's
so strange. I [ __ ] hate him, bro. And
I've had more than anyone on here.
I'll be honest, bro. I went out the past
couple of days cuz I was [ __ ] bored.
Sorry about that. My internet was [ __ ] up, bro.
So why is it that
these people that don't get women defend
them and people that's had women like me
is not scared of the truth.
I don't understand it, man. Must be some
sort of mental condition.
In the Nile. Definitely in the Nile.
100% in the Nile.
Just like that 18year-old from Canada.
He's [ __ ] in denial, mate.
Yeah, they're in denial, bro.
And then you talk about people that are in relationships.
But you're wrong though because one in
four men are in relationships.
And then even if they are in
relationships, they're in relationships
with somebody that's a lot lower than
them, which proves the whole point.
which proves my whole point again. And
that doesn't even matter anyways. That's
not even a proper proper statistic cuz
some people meet at work. Some people
met through social before social media.
Some people might have done a cold
approach once and got lucky. When people meet people,
it's to do with luck. So therefore, it
can't be compared. And a lot of people
met like even before social media and
[ __ ] It's not a a thing to compare to
because some people never meet people.
Some people are compatible with no one.
So it's not a thing that you can even
compare it to.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, bro. He always is. He always will be.
So is LJ, man.
Yeah, but he's skint as well. [ __ ]
Virgin boy and [ __ ]
um Lord J, bro.
It's cute though how desperate they are
to try to convince people that they've
that they've got money. It's cute, man.
It is cute.
They're skinting skin. Flint, I say.
Yeah, virgin boy is super skinn.
[ __ ] hell. Proper proper proper skin.
I'm being cooked a nice pork dinner by
my bar. Is that nice greasy?
Nice roast dinner. E.
Certain person can't say their mom done
that for them. Nah, mate. Nah. Yeah,
but I don't know why so many people are
in denial about this whole dating thing.
I really don't understand. They're so in
denial. They're so in denial, bro.
It's just in denial.
And one in four people are in
relationship. One in four men are in
relationships. That is facts. cuz I know
loads and loads and loads and loads and
loads of people and most people they
they're not in relationships. Most of
the people that I know from different
angles that have no connections to each other
and the ones that have been single never
really got into relationships.
I'm trying to think no
is the women in this country. It's like
that guy that I was speaking to on the
train. Like I keep saying, we was
talking the whole journey and he had his
girlfriend with him. His girlfriend was
about a five out of 10. You know, so yeah. So yeah.
she wouldn't want to meet. She wouldn't
give me a chance because I'm not because
I'm not her social circle. But I
wouldn't want to date anyone in the social circle. So
y it's all it's all well and good you
saying that. But the only way is clubs
and street approaching cuz if you didn't
Okay. Okay. So look at what you've just
said, right? What you need to understand is um
doesn't matter. That's just [ __ ] up
that he's had to lower his standards in
that way. He's a cool guy and she was
cool as well. But what you need to
understand is is being is been what what
you need to understand is being in
relationship is based on solid
foundations. Meeting someone in a bar
club as a stranger isn't that and will
never last either way. But if you didn't
do that, you'd be a virgin. So
everything you would you say, you just
contradict yourself because you're
basically saying that that's not the
way, that's not the way. Okay. Well, if
you didn't do that, you wouldn't have
met that 19year-old. If you didn't do
that, you wouldn't have met USA. If you
didn't do that, you wouldn't have met
Sig. You wouldn't have met Sig. So, you
would be a virgin.
So, you would be a dateless virgin if
you didn't do any of that [ __ ] So, that
just doesn't that just contradicts
everything you've just said. No,
it has worked out. You know, it used to
work. It just doesn't work anymore.
Has any of them lasted? There's been
chances of them lasting. And it doesn't
even matter if they did last. They did
last. You got dates and you got sex.
It's better than nothing.
No, no, no. I get your point, but you're
missing the point.
You're missing the point because if you
didn't do Okay, so where would you be
now if you didn't do any of that stuff?
If you didn't do them approaches on the
street and you you didn't go to clubs,
where would you be now? You'd be a
virgin. A dateless kissless virgin. So,
I'm not missing the point. I get the
point, but you're missing the point.
You're missing You are completely
completely missing the point. So,
and it's like when people say, "Oh,
people don't feel comfortable being
approached on the street," which is um I
get that, but it doesn't matter if it's
on the street or a club or a bar. It's
the same thing anyways.
You're interested. So, it doesn't need
to be one place or the other.
Cuz even if you go to a club, then
anyways, this point is talking about
this. I'm going to Thailand anyways.
It's not my problem anymore. It's your
problem. It's not my problem.
But I just know if I took people's
advice, I'd be a virgin.
That's all I know. Because I've only
ever met one person on dating apps.
So, how can people's advice work? They
tell you to use dating apps. I've only
ever met one or two people on dating
apps and one was a psychopath.
So, if you took people's advice, you
would you would be [ __ ]
You'd be a virgin, like virgin boy,
never been on a date, nothing. So
yeah, so now I'm not missing the point at all. So yeah,
it's not my problem anymore anyways.
But yeah, some of them could have lasted
maybe like two years ago. Yeah.
What's the alternative? I think that's a
good question. That's that. What's the alternative, Grezy?
What is the actual alternative?
Wait a million years. You might meet
someone through friends, never happens.
Meet somebody at work, never happens.
Like, what? What is the actual alternative?
[ __ ] Oh, I can smell that pork, man.
It's [ __ ] banging.
Yeah, and that is what I have done, but
I've just been bored lately cuz I
haven't been able to work.
I just said the whole thing was boredom.
But it's still [ __ ] up at the same
time. I've done it through boredom and
it's still But it is still [ __ ] up how
someone that's decent looking can't find
anyone in their own country.
I'm just acknowledging it, bro. I'm not
complaining. I'm just acknowledging how
it's [ __ ] up. It's weird.
It's It's completely abnormal.
>> Yeah. The fact you struggle on dating
apps suggest you can't maintain
relationship over messages. No, that's
[ __ ] You You can match with
somebody on dating apps and they don't
even reply. They literally go on dating
apps to troll people. They literally go
on I have got hobbies. I'm leaving this
country again soon. But I'm not in
denial to say how [ __ ] up it is. It is
[ __ ] up. It's not normal. Yesterday
was not normal at all. You know, so
but no, they go on dating apps to troll
people. Dating apps do not work. And
then we're just going to go on another
thing about how
dating apps have worked for other
people. Oh, and then we'll just get into
another conversation about other people
again. Listen, [ __ ] I know I'm
right when it comes to this because I'm
living proof of it. I'm the one who's
been everywhere. I'm the one who's who's
been all over doing this. I met loads
and loads and loads and loads of people.
I know exactly what I'm talking about.
And it doesn't even matter about the
past. We can just erase the past, but it
continues to happen. So it's like that's
all you need to know.
This is what boredom does to people,
man. [ __ ] went out Thursday and went
out Saturday all through boredom.
And then I just got reminded how [ __ ]
up this country is again.
It's such a [ __ ] up country.
As soon as I can start doing one of
these delivery jobs again, I'm just
going to be doing that.
But yeah, it's not the point. It's just
weird. It's [ __ ] up, you know.
But it is them. It definitely definitely
definitely definitely one million% is
them cuz you can get ghosted by people
that even kiss you. You can [ __ ]
somebody in and they'll ghost you. It is
it is them. It generally generally is
them. Them them approaching videos prove it.
them approaching videos. Prove it. Cuz
how have you not got a date then? You
went out Thursday, Saturday. Yeah. How
have you not got a date lined up for
next week? What the [ __ ] You know, you
get to know somebody on a date, right?
Well, you should have a date this next week.
You don't have a date next week. Why?
What the [ __ ]
It is just not normal in this country.
It's nothing about this country is normal.
And then you get these stupid people
trying to be funny with you. I said,
"It's a bit disgusting how you can't
even get into a pub in your own
country." He's like, "It's not
disgusting." I said, "It it is." Then he
was trying to be awkward and I said, he
said, "It's not." I said, "Yes, it is."
And then he tries to accuse me of being
violent when I stood in the same place
the whole time. This country's gone
through the [ __ ] shambles, bro.
What's it going to be like in 10 years?
really what is it going to be like in 10 years is bad. So yeah.
Yep. I have a lot of free time nowadays.
I wonder when they're going to have this
[ __ ] phone in stock. This Samsung
Galaxy I want to get it, but it's in stock.
Going to cost like what 90 something a
month for the phone contract. I can pay
I'm already paying like 30 for just a
sim. So, keep up with that.
Have to get that new fold, man. I've got
to I've got to matey. I'm going to start
betting on the football next month.
Both teams to score coming on strong. Yeah,
I couldn't pay 35 [ __ ] quid to
[ __ ] go into a [ __ ] club. That's
ridiculous. I have to fork out £500 for
this phone when it's finally in stock.
But I may never work again. I'm not sure.
I don't need to.
I don't know. It's a good thing because
you'd get distress from the work which
you did have to think about dating in
this depressing country. That was a good
thing about the working.
But I don't want to deal with I don't
want to deal with people again, bro. Uh,
that's the thing I hate is the people. I
[ __ ] now like I don't really think
about it anymore now cuz I don't do it anymore.
But oh people, I [ __ ] hate people. >> Yeah,
>> that's another thing. Got all the free
time in the world now, bro.
I done 20 I done two days. Yeah, I done
more than two days, matey. I got more
than two days, matey. And if I done two
days, that's two more days than you've ever done.
I've done about 10 days.
Nah, you're the one that's by, Harry.
You're the one that keeps talking about
people being by. That's cuz you are by.
Takes one to no one, isn't it?
See, Harry says that the women in
Liverpool are stuck up as well. He's not in denial.
Even though we don't like each other,
he's not in denial. A lot of people are
in denial. You see,
I stick to escorts. Me, once I get this
thing again, I'll just be sticking to
escorts when I come back.
Yeah, [ __ ] it.
That's not even be bothered.
£35 to get into a [ __ ] nightclub. E Jeez,
that's some madness, isn't it? No, [ __ ] Starving.
dude. They're just not interested in this country.
country. I just want some pork, bro. I'm [ __ ] starving. [Music]
I'm so hungry, bro.
I'm really hungry, lad. I just want I
want this subs Galaxy F. That's going to
be a lovely site. But let's say they
ain't going to deliver it to the seven.
I don't get depressed me, mate. I don't
have much time to be depressed.
That Muslim girl gets depressed, not me. Yeah.
Not me, matey.
Just want some piggies.
Greasy. Some piggies.
You should come round one time. But yeah,
it's mad you can't find someone in your own country.
Boyfriend, boyfriend, boyfriend. I feel
like once you've met one woman, you've
met them all. I feel like did anyone
else ever feel like that? Once you meet
one, you meet all of them. They're all
nom nom playing characters.
Yeah. I feel like once you met one,
you've you've met them all.
That boyfriend thing must be stuck in
their head, isn't it? It must be like me
and Antman was talking about that
before, you know. It must be like stuck
in their head.
Yeah. But do you know what? It's a good
thing though, to be honest with you. I I
don't It's not Do you know what? It's
not even the worst thing cuz they're the
one that's got to be [ __ ] in 10 years
when they can't find someone and they're
old and social media can't save them.
They're the ones that will be [ __ ]
No, you're not. No. No. No. No. No. No.
you don't make any sense what you said.
If I did not approach, I would be a
dateless virgin. Well, except for
escorts. I would be a dateless virgin.
So, whatever you say don't make sense.
There is nothing else you can do but
approach. That is literally the only
thing you can do. So, it doesn't matter
if it's frowned upon or whatever.
That is all you can do. So, there is
nothing else you can do.
It's like, let's just say about Buddy
right now. There's nothing else I can do
for my buddy. We can sit here moan and
winge, but there's nothing else. It's a
waiting game. I don't get annoyed
anymore about it. I don't really care.
There's nothing you can do. Just like
when you approach, that's all you can
do. Approach and get rejected. That's it.
None of those numbers have replied back.
None of them five back.
I I don't think I will work again unless
I can get a self-employed job. A
self-employed job. I probably won't
probably work again to be honest.
I don't need to [ __ ] So yeah. So yeah,
I met this woman yesterday. She told me
she works in McDonald's.
Yeah, people are struggling nowadays.
I'm surprised he's able to [ __ ] go
out for a [ __ ] rave. She's working in
McDonald's. People don't even go out
nowadays. People have no money. You know,
I think Virgin Boy needs to get a job.
He's never had a [ __ ] job.
He needs to get himself a little job.
Where do you think Greavves?
Rather you to me, mate. I'm having a
nice I'm reing some nice piggies.
I need a fresh start to buy. I need to
really start saving now, bro.
I don't want to end up like Virgin boy.
Yeah, I know. That's I'm back to
reality. See See the tenants were like,
"Oh, you're [ __ ] You're fucked." Cuz
obviously I'm not getting as much income
now. But I was like, "You don't realize
that I literally have like the only
outgoing I'll have is my phone and then
the rest of the money is just to live
off. So actually I'm not [ __ ] and have savings.
I was trying to like explain and they
didn't really understand. Yeah. So what,
bro? You don't get as much money. Who
gives a [ __ ]
I'll make some money next month from the
football. Don't you worry about that.
Don't you worry about that, matey.
Don't you [ __ ] worry about that. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, I got this woman's lobby
yesterday. She left. I said, "Where did
you go?" And she blocked me.
Just sounds like England to me.
I can smell that, man.
Just sounds like England. Nothing else.
Sounds like this shitty country.
shitty country. E.
And I only go to pubs now, Joe.
I only go to like Weather Spoons now. Yeah.
Yeah. I used to get 3K a month, but
not anymore. But it doesn't really
matter to be honest. I still have
savings and stuff. I'm only leaving now. side. Yeah.
When is this phone going to be on in stock? Yeah.
It wasn't It wasn't a lot for me when I
was on three grand a month. You get used
to it. Any money you get, you get used
to. Now I'm back with a little amount of
money. I'm used to it. So, it is what it
is. Nothing can be done.
There's nothing that can be done. So,
you're still actually living really,
really good. I've already calculated it.
You know, 1 [ __ ] 8 1.8K
single, no outgoings. Quite a lot of
money for one person, is it?
You're just not going to like be able to
like spend a lot more often. That's all
that's all it's going to be. I don't
really care to be honest with you. I've
got food. I've got money. I've got a
bed. Screw it off for me. It
like they don't understand. And what I
was trying to explain to the tenants is
I've lived the life. I've had the
escorts. I've had the women. I've done
the traveling. have had the restaurants.
So to not be on as much now, it's not
the worst thing.
You know, there's a lot of you're still
a lot better than a lot of other people.
They but they didn't really understand it. Um
so even though it's a loss, I've already
adapted to it. I'd already adapted to it
ages ago cuz I knew that that was it was
going to happen. So it is what it is.
So, but yeah,
just have to Yeah, that's it. Is it
cuz I remember Yeah. like I was meeting
up with a friend and he'd go to like uh
there was two of them actually. I got a
friend from Italy and he'd go to the
Tesco's to get the beer. Oh, I just need
to save a bit of money. I said, "What
are you talking about, bro? Just go to
the club and just buy drinks. You know,
I want to start off here first and then
do it." And now I'm probably going to be
doing exactly the same as him.
Now I'm going to probably be doing
exactly the same as him now to be honest.
Oh [ __ ] So I mean just most people are
skinned in it. That is basically the way it is.
Most people just don't have any money. So yeah,
I don't know why Virgin Boy has to try
and make out like he's got money
when he really doesn't have anything.
He really doesn't have anything.
The only thing I can't do as much is
obviously the escorts and the [ __ ]
and the um
Yeah, that's it really.
Cuz obviously I I didn't do it
yesterday. I have the money, but I just
wanted to not spend it on that yesterday.
Just like I didn't want to pay £35 to
get into a club. I still have the I
still have the money.
So, I just didn't want to spend it on that.
But yeah, then my virgin boy has to try
and convince people he's got money.
It's ridiculous, isn't it?
[ __ ] ridiculous, Joe.
You ain't got a [ __ ] pot to piss in the lad.
He ain't got a fing to piss in, lad.
Who? That is a stupid question to ask
because no one knows where they're going
to end up in 3 years.
That is the most stupidest question to
ever ask someone
because nobody knows where someone's
going to end up.
Nobody knows what they're going to be
doing in their [ __ ] 3 years [ __ ] time, you know?
It's a silly question really.
Who knows where what they're going to be
doing? What? Then you know probably
living in Thailand probably. Yeah.
Yeah. The guy on the train said like
what what are you going to do?
He said oh you need to go to Thailand
like your friend's been saying because
we've had a conversation about it in it.
And that's what he said like, "Yeah, you
need to go there even if it's just for
big that he just that's what he was
saying like basically cuz Yeah.
Do you reckon more people use uh
Yeah. No, I've already done what I've
wanted to do. I've traveled a bit, have
some nice clothes, been to restaurants.
There's nothing there's no other goals
to really have.
Yeah, I told him I'd been as well, but
he said you you know you need to go back and stuff.
Yeah, we was talking. You know when
you're drunk and you get the train back
and someone else has had a drink as well
and then you just start talking and
stuff. It's quite funny.
Uh, no he didn't, Triple H. And stop
bringing trouble on my channel. Stop
bringing weird drama on my channel, bro.
Uh, no he didn't.
And bro, even if he got me bad bred from
one pub, there's millions of pubs in in
London. It's the most stupidest thing to do.
You know, trying to get somebody banned
from somewhere is just silly because
there's like so many different places in
London and staff change all the time.
It's just just a really silly thing to
do. A staff change. B there's millions
of pubs in London. So why would somebody
even try to do that? It doesn't make any sense.
So yeah, that's really all you can do to be honest.
I've lived a good life. escorts,
traveled, good food, good outings.
I feel like I've done a lot, man. I have
done a lot. So, yeah.
Anyways, I'm not I'm moving on from
this. Anyways, trip 8, stop trying to
stop trying to bring weird drama on my channel
because if you keep winding me up and
winding me up and winding me up, I'm
just going to go to Newcastle
and show everybody what you're about the fourth time.
Like, and it ain't going to be funny,
bro. Cuz we all know, bro, like you come
on here, you tried to start trouble,
right? I've been to Newcastle [ __ ]
three times and you would not come out.
Everybody remembers it.
You did not come out,
[ __ ] boy. You did not come out. I went
to Newcastle three times and you did not
come out. Do you know how funny that sounds?
And you did not come out, bro. And
you're trying to cause trouble on my
channel. Please [ __ ] off. Uh, so yeah,
bro. So yeah,
I owned you in your own city, bro. You
didn't even come out.
That virgin doesn't own anyone, just
like you don't own anyone. You're a pair
of keyboard warriors. He owns me. How
does he own me, bro? I have more money
than him. I'm better looking than him.
I've had more women than him. He has to
run to the police on me. Owns me in what
way? By being a lanky virgin with no bed
and no teeth. That's to prey on
vulnerable people. Just like you don't
owe any You don't own anyone. You're a
bunch of keyboard warriors. Why do you
think no one really comes on here
anymore, bro? Because we're bored of
you. You're keyboard warriors.
Yeah, that's good for him, bro. But
what's so funny is this mas had more
women than him. This m I'm such a m
Triple H. Yeah. That all of the women
that I've had, he can't get out of his
head. That's how much of a m I am.
Bro, the guy looks like a [ __ ]
disabled rat. Have you seen that ugly
face? Every single time he he he says m,
he's talking about himself. Have you
seen the state of that ugly [ __ ]
face? It's the ugliest face I think I've
ever seen in my life.
It's It's pure ugliness, bro. He is the
ugliest thing I think I've ever seen in my life.
Bro, get real.
And at the end of the day, you're just a
bunch of keyboard warriors, bro. Really are.
You know, we was talking about that
chase as well. If I ever see that chase,
I'll slap him up if I ever see that
chase as well.
Yeah, I said to him, "Bro, I was saying
this earlier. Why don't Chase tell me
when when them when they're back in
London again? They should both tell me, bro.
He doesn't do anything to me, mate. I I
live in his head rentree. He's got a
whole channel dedicated to stalking me.
He doesn't do anything to me. I live in
his head. I live in his head rentree. It
should be what I'm doing to him. Living
in his head, rentree.
I'm literally living in his head, rent
free. He is obsessed with me. He can't
go a day without mentioning me and being
obsessed with me. I'm doing a lot to him.
He can't get me out of his head. That's
how much I torment him. So, I don't have
a channel dedicated to stalking someone.
I ain't got a channel dedicated to being
jealous to someone, bro. No one's doing
nothing to me.
Yeah, I've got a track record of doing
nothing. Yeah, bro. Just like when I
went to Manchester three times. Just
like when I've tried to meet people.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay, bro. And exactly what
do you people have a track record of doing?
Okay. Okay. And um what do you people
have a track record of doing?
Exactly. Go on. Go on.
And what do you people have a track
record of doing? You people have known
people's addresses for years and you
haven't done nothing.
So what the [ __ ] are you talking about?
Doing nothing, bro. I've met several
people in this community.
Embarrassing. I know. I've met several
people. Yeah. He doesn't bully me. He bullies himself.
Yeah. No one has ever bullied me on
here. He's the one that ran to the
police, not me. I didn't run to the
police or no one.
They have a track record of cord and you
just don't get it. They don't. Listen,
listen, listen, bro. What inconvenience.
Listen, bro. You and him don't bully no
one. You can't say anything to your
anyone's face. And you know what, Trip?
I'm going to come to Newcastle again and
I'm just going to start talking about
you and your family and it ain't going
to be nice. And we'll see everybody what
you're about cuz you've also done this
to London Taylor as well. I've seen
where you've baited people and tear,
but please don't make me come back
there, bro, because it ain't going to be
nice. And I'm not going to stop. Like,
simple. Like, that's it, bro.
Bro, but I'm still here having more
money. Yeah, but that's just cowardly
stuff, Joe. That's cowardly stuff. It's
cowardly stuff. That's not beating
someone. That's just jealousy. Listen,
bro. Okay, let me tell you something, right? Huh?
This is how I tell you how I bully them.
I'm better looking than them. I've got
more money than them, which kills them,
which is why they do what they do. It's
jealousy for them to sit online every
single day being jealous of you. You're
already bullying them. They're You are
in their head every single day. In my
mind, that's bullying someone. If
someone has to wake up every single day
jealous of someone, you're bullying
them, bro. It's it's straight. It's
straight. And no one made me leave pubs
for a long long long long time. And you
know what, bro? Even if that is the
case, that's cowardly stuff. That's not
an inconvenience. None of these people
control my life. Any of my none of these
people on here has ever controlled my
life. Yeah. But listen, Triple H, I
bullied you when I went to Newcastle
three times and you didn't meet me. You
couldn't even come out, bro. You
couldn't even come out them three times
I went there. You little [ __ ] Shut the
[ __ ] up, bro. Go suck his dick on his
channel. You're both a bunch of keyboard
warriors. You and him are made for each
other, bro. You're both a bunch of
keyboard warriors. Bully victims. You
know what I'm saying? And bro, when I
come to Newcastle again, I'm going to
start talking about your misses as well
and your family.
Like, bro, you're made for each other.
You're both a bunch of keyboard
warriors. Yeah, you remember every
single time. It's the same with um Harry
Freud, another one that does not show
up. Isn't it funny how all of you people
claim you bully people, but you don't
meet anyone? You're all keyboard warrior cowards
that are jealous of me, but you think
that you own me. This is what I don't
understand. You Okay. Okay. Let's go
over this one more time. Right. I went
to Liverpool. I went to Liverpool. Harry
F was nowhere to be seen. I called
everyone out from Liverpool and no he
was nowhere to be seen. Every single
person from Liverpool run off. Every
single person from Liverpool ran away.
Just like when LT went to Liverpool,
just like when I went to Liverpool,
Harry was nowhere to seen. As soon as I
come back to London was back on YouTube
again, right? This was the peak of
[ __ ] YouTube, right? just before the
[ __ ] um just before the lockdown,
right, bro? I own them because they're
jealous of me, bro. It doesn't matter.
They're jealous of me. So, I'm doing
something right. They don't What? So,
you getting a reaction out of someone is
you owning them, bro. I'm better
looking. I got more money. I'm I'm
living a better life than them. That is
me owning them. Having more than them,
being better looking than them. And
that's why they do this every day. It's
because it's jealousy. You own them so
much that you rouse them in their brain
that they've got a channel dedicated to
you. They won't leave you alone. It's
because they're jealous of you. That's
the thing. So, you're owning them. For
them to be doing this, they're so
jealous of you that they have to do
this. You're you're already owning them.
It doesn't matter what [ __ ] reaction
you give them. You start [ __ ]
shouting. You're already owning them in
every aspect. Think of it. You, no one
just sits online stalking every day.
They are jealous of you. You are doing
something right. You have something they
don't have. Bare looks, bare money. You
don't understand. You're already owning them, bro.
So, shut the [ __ ] up. Listen, Harry
fooled. You didn't turn up when I went
to Liverpool. Shut the [ __ ] up. You
scouts are not about anything. You you
all you skeleston ran away when I was in
Liverpool just like Triple H ran away
when I was in Newcastle. Bunch of
northern keyboard warriors. I don't know
how much yet how many times between me
and LT we went up north and none of
these big hard northerners were anywhere
to be seen.
Isn't that a madness? None of these big
scouse lads were anywhere to be seen.
Isn't that a madness? We must have went
about a hundred times between me and
London Taylor. Not one of these big hard
northerners were to we probably about
100 times to be honest.
Probably aboutund I'd say about 100
times. I think it was 50 times just
myself to be honest. Maybe 50 times. So
tells you all you need to know in it.
Okay. It just goes to show that you was
never anything about anything. So yeah,
it's the truth.
So that's it, bro. Yeah. Listen out,
Triple H. Why didn't you meet me when I
was in Newcastle?
I'm going to go to Newcastle next week.
[ __ ] this. I'm going to Newcastle again.
And I'm going to start talking about
your kid. I'm going to start talking
about your [ __ ] your misses. I'm
going to go to Newcastle again and I'm
going to slate the [ __ ] this. I'm
booking this now, actually. [ __ ] this.
One second. Let me go on the train line.
Let's see what this jeweled little
[ __ ] with his ugly kid is about. I'm
going to start talking about his [ __ ]
kid, his [ __ ] slaggy misses. And if
you don't come out right, I'm going to
come to Durham and I'm going to and I'm
going to and I'm going to slag you off
and slag you off and I'm going to show
LT the video. Don't let this little
Jordy [ __ ] try to [ __ ] start on
anybody on YouTube ever again. I'm
booking this right now, bro. One second.
Hold on. [ __ ] this. And I'm also I'm
going to make sure as well, LT, do not
let this well eye [ __ ] ever come on
here again and start [ __ ] stirring
this [ __ ] pot between you and Jay. You
and Jane, you and Mark Samson. Yeah.
Don't let this guy start anything again.
This Well, I man [ __ ] Do not let him,
bro. Yeah. Do not let him. I'm booking
this, bro. I'm booking this. Joe, do you
not understand that I'm the one that's
traveled all over the country and none
of you turn up? Who are you talking
about, bro? Who are you talking about,
bro? You don't live with your mom at 30
because your mom starved you. Your mom
almost starved you to death, you mter.
That's why. You ugly rat. You don't live
with your mom. You live in a bedsit
because your mom hates you. That's why
your mom starved you almost. Your mom
almost starved you to death. You live in
a bedsit with no bed in it with a
[ __ ] girlfriend. Yes. Nobody Nobody
wants that life.
You couldn't live with your [ __ ] mom
because your mom hates you and starved
you to death. That's what almost starved
you to death. You [ __ ] 30y old virgin
in a bedsit. I'd rather live with my mom
than [ __ ] live in a bedit, bro. Are
you mad? Living in a shitty bedset with
no bed in it. Imagine that, bro. Imagine
that. Even if it was temporary, you
[ __ ] ugly ratfaced, ugly [ __ ] virgin
skin boy. You ain't got no [ __ ]
money. It took you to [ __ ] 30 to go abroad.
You dress, you buy your clothes in a
charity shop. You show £800. Who the
[ __ ] shows £800, bro?
Allow it, bro. [ __ ] off, you ratfaced,
ugly [ __ ] virgin. Go suck your dad's dick.
Literally, bro. Yeah. Simple. It's a
madness. You You got a face of a rat.
You live in a bedsit. Your mom hates
you. How can you talk about anyone, bro?
Your mom [ __ ] almost starved you and
you live in a bedit with no bed in it.
How can you talk about people who people
live with? Who the [ __ ] You would
literally be living with your mom if
your mom didn't starve you. Know what
I'm saying? But anyways, all of you
little [ __ ] keyboard warriors, you
just want a reaction. Go and [ __ ] get
a life, you sad little bastards. [ __ ]
hell. That's another thing as well. But
I'll just tell L2 about that [ __ ]
trip rate as well when I go back up
there. Three different times. But that's
the thing with you northerners. You've
got no shame. Like I know all of you,
right, you do this for reaction, but I
would be so ashamed if but again, I know
you got no you got no you got no uh
shame. So I would be so ashamed if
somebody could come to my city and make
me run out of it like I done Harry, like
I done Triple H. I'd be so embarrassed
if somebody could travel 200 miles and
run me out of my city without showing my
face. I would be so embarrassed. Like I
know you do this right for like like a
reaction. Okay, but but don't you feel
embarrassed like at all?
That is so embarrassing. Like all jokes
aside now. Yeah. All trolling aside, I
have pulled up to Newcastle. No one come
out three times. I have pulled up to
Liverpool. Do you not have no shame?
Like, and then you and then you just
come back like nothing's happened. So,
aren't you like embarrassed, bro? I
would be so embarrassed if somebody
could [ __ ] run me out of my [ __ ]
city, bro. I would be so embarrassed.
You know what I'm saying? I would. But
you come on here like it's normal, bro.
You don't know where I live. And I'm
nowhere near 30. You don't know where I
live. So, try again. You know what's
even more embarrassing, bro? You you
claim that you've got all Oh, look at
that video that I said about you as
well, bro. Saying about how you uh how
you get all of this money, but you're
begging and I don't have £500. Why the
[ __ ] would I have £500, bro? Listen,
you're begging for extra money on
YouTube. You're the definition of skint.
It's exact. It's exactly what I said on
that video. You're getting all of this
money, but you're begging on YouTube. It
don't make sense. It don't look right.
Why do you come on here like you got
money? Just act like a normal person
like the rest of us. Oh, [ __ ] I get
this. Why? Why do you lie about where
you get your money, bro? You're on £400
a month maximum. It doesn't make sense.
Everything that you do on your channel,
you claim you got all of this money, but
you're begging for money. What? Begging
for an extra what?£150 a month, but
you've got all this money. Doesn't look
right. It does not look right. You
understand? It does not look right when
you're claiming that you've got all of
this money. It doesn't make sense.
You're prepared to beg for money, lose
all your pride. It doesn't make sense.
You remember before you was trying to
say about how people say [ __ ] that does
not make sense. D. That makes no sense,
bro. You were sat in a Weber spoons
begging for drinks last like was it last
month? You was begging people for drinks
in a Weber spoons. in a [ __ ] Weber
spoons. Bro, if that's not skin, I don't
know what skin is.
That is a madness, bro. You were sat
there in a in a black pot begging for
drinks, bro. You are sklin skintter than
a [ __ ] skin flint.
But you come at it like you're not.
That's the thing. You come here like
you've got all of this money. It's
madness. It's a [ __ ] madness. You
claim that you've got all of this money.
If you had all this money, bro, you
wouldn't be begging on YouTube.
You would not be begging on YouTube if
you had all of this money. You would not
be begging on YouTube. You know, you know,
like literally, you would not be begging
on money. You would not be begging on
YouTube for money if you had all this
money. It doesn't make sense. The only
thing that would make sense is if you
got a lot less money than you're
claiming you do, trying to get extra money.
Uh, bro, you're begging. Begging. Why
are you begging for money on YouTube if
you have all of this money? Can you explain this?
Anyways, I'm banning these little
[ __ ] now. Anyways, you're banned. You're banned.
And you're banned. What the [ __ ] I
thought I'd all these block these
[ __ ] spastics to be honest. You're
banned. You're banned. And you're
See, the thing is, bro, I would love to
go to Belfos and kick the [ __ ] out of
this [ __ ] but I've had this
conversation with my mom numerous,
numerous, numerous times, but I don't
want to waste my money on it, and I
don't want anyone giving me money. I
would love to go there and and [ __ ] him
out of there, bro. Like, you really
don't understand. It annoys me how he
seems to think he's some kind of hard
man, but bro, he's not. He's not about
anything. He really ain't about [ __ ]
Like, bro, like I really You can ask my
[ __ ] mom. I've said it a million
times. I would love to go there and put
that crown on my head, bro. Like, you don't understand.
Just happens, man. You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. I'm going to eat my um pork now
anyways, but I wouldn't accept any money
from anyone. That's the thing. And I'm
not wasting my own money on it.
You know what I'm saying? Cuz he he
needs to understand, bro, this isn't real life.
You understand? This is this is this is
[ __ ] London, bro.
Yeah. This is London. You understand?
This is [ __ ] London, bro. Not [ __ ]
shitty [ __ ] Belfast.
But you people clearly have got issues,
jealousy, whatever it is. You coming
here doing this [ __ ] every day for
reaction. You're clearly jealous of
something, you little low lives. You clearly are.
You don't believe I'd go to Newcastle.
Why would I go to Newcastle, bro? I've
been there many times and you people
never show up. You're all just
embarrassing keyboard warriors. And like
I said, you you northerners have no
shame as well. You have no shame with
anything that you do.
You're just little jealous of something
keyboard warriors. You know what I'm
going to do? I'm going to come back
later, bro. I'm just going to chill and
eat and we're going to we're going to
get to the bottom of this before I go.
We're going to get to the bottom of what
you people are jealous of in life and
why you come back. [ __ ] Why you
come and you do this [ __ ] on YouTube every day?
We're going to get to the bottom of it.
We're going to get to the bottom of this
cuz this is not healthy, you know.
I'm going anyways. I'll be back later.
So, we need to figure this out later. Yeah.
Why these people with perfect lives come
on YouTube for a reaction every day even
when they don't get a reaction?
Yeah, I'll see you later anyways. I'll
do that later. Trying to figure it out.