Yeah, man. I just wanted to talk about how
these little bongos on this community
have got no life.
How the skint on 300 pound a month. They
can't take a day off for [ __ ]
YouTube. They've got no friends. They've
never been seen with a woman. They've
never been seen with a friend ever
because they ain't got gun. It's why
they're on YouTube every day and they
can't get off of it because they're
absolute skint spastics of life.
Uh which is also why
uh they come up with the word skint cuz
it's themselves that they're talking
about. They are skint on YouTube every
day. And I'll be living proof of it. Uh
cuz when I'm gone from today,
they will still be on YouTube every day
cuz they ain't got no life but YouTube.
That's why cuz it's their life. That's
why they need uh reaction from men. You
see, that's why they need to wind people
up on YouTube because they don't have
anything else. No money, no life, no
friends, only each other. So, uh that's
why they need a reaction because they're
clearly jealous of something in life. Uh
their uh their lives are empty and they have nothing.
What I wanted to say really,
you people can't even take one day off
of YouTube. Huh? Imagine that. Not even
one day off of YouTube.
You should tell these people it's okay
to have a break. They can't take one day
off of YouTube.
Yeah, it is okay to have a break. You
need to tell these people that, bro.
They can't take one day off of YouTube
and projecting their skin [ __ ] life onto other people.
And I know that you go for me and you
try to troll me and stuff and I like it
to be honest because it just shows that
you're jealous of something. I like it
to be honest with you, man. You know,
trying to get a reaction, me living in
your head rentree. I kind of like it
because it just shows that I have
something that you don't have that you
want. So, at the end of the day, I'm all
for it to be honest with you.
But in all fairness, I mean, you can't
even take one day off of [ __ ]
YouTube. How embarrassing is that? Not
even one day off of YouTube. Imagine
that. Not even one day.
Tragic, mate. [ __ ] tragic. Not even one day.
[ __ ] hell. That just goes to show
that skin on here. Yeah, man. I was
saying to Ela on the phone earlier.
Yeah. When I was on the phone today, I
said, I'd love to get my hands on one of
these people. Just one of these people.
I'd love to get my hands on one of them, bro.
Like it could be any of them, bro. It
could be like Terry, Virgin Boy,
Lord Jay. It could be any of them. I'd
love to get my hands on one of these
people, bro. I was telling Laney this as
well. I I told her as well, like the
only reason I have been to Belfast is
cuz I'm not wasting my money on it.
That's literally the only thing. That's
the only reason.
Yeah. I'd love to get my hands on one of
these people badly, bro, and make like
an example out of them. a proper proper
example out of them, bro. You know how
they ain't turned up in the past. You
know what I mean?
So yeah, I mean the fact that like I
live in your head rent free.
Clearly I've got something that you want
and you're in denial, bro.
You know, s on YouTube every day.
It's [ __ ] tragic, mate.
They've got you have something that they
they that they want, bro.
But we need to figure out what it is.
Is it more money, better looks? Is it
uh cuz you have a mom
and them I'm starve them? Like I'm
trying to I'm trying to work it out,
bro. Like I need I need some help here.
Steven Allen, I need some help here.
Right. These people have got all the
money in the world. They've got all
these friends. Their life is perfect. So
why do they come online triggered every day?
Triggered over you,
stalking you every day.
You clearly have something that they want clearly.
And I'm trying to figure out what what it is.
Just trying to think
to be honest. I'm trying to I'm trying
to figure it out.
You got that Jamie Thompson still stalking me,
um, trying to email me and stuff. I
mean, come on, man. Let's talk about
this. You got all this money. Your life
is so perfect. Why are you on YouTube stalking men?
I'm trying to I need some guidance here,
bro. I'm trying to figure this [ __ ] out.
Madness. I'm trying to figure this [ __ ]
out, but I don't I don't have all the answers.
But it's got to be something that you
have that they want. Definitely, bro.
Definitely. Definitely. Definitely.
It has to be.
Has to be, bro. one uh
one number reply [ __ ] stuff. pretty much.
Yeah, they're definitely jealous of something,
Stephen. I would, would you agree,
Grezy? They've got to be jealous of
something. They've got to be. Like, they
can try to say that you're triggered and
you're reacting to them and ret. No, the
truth is they're triggered because
they're the ones that can't stop every
day doing what they're doing.
So, actually, no, they're actually the
triggered ones because they wake up
every morning obsessed, stalking.
They're the ones that are actually triggered.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
They do this even if they don't get a
reaction. And listen, listen, listen,
listen, listen. Even if they don't get a
reaction, they would still do it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. There's
people that don't even get mentioned.
They don't get a reaction and they still
do it. But even if they do do it for a
reaction, says a lot about their life.
Think of it, bro. They're putting all of
their life into trying to get a
reaction. Think of it. It says a lot
about their life. If your life is so
perfect, why would you be spending all
day on YouTube trying to get a reaction?
And even if you don't give them a
reaction, they still do it. That's how
you know that they're jealous. And I do
not react to these people 90% of the
time. It is jealousy. It has to be some
form of jealousy. I'm trying to figure
it out, bro. I really, really, really am
because you don't react to these people
90% of the time. You could ignore these
people for a whole year and they would
still do it. I think it's jealousy. I
think you've got something that they
want. I'm telling you, bro. You have
something that they want.
I'm telling you 1 million% you have
But no, it's not for a reaction because
even if you don't react to these people,
they will still do it. They will
literally still do it, right? There are
some accounts, right, that I have not
reacted to for [ __ ] months, seven,
eight months, right? And I'll stumble
across their channel and they're still doing it.
You've got something they want, bro. I'm
telling you. I'm telling you, man. For
them to do this every day. It's They've
got to be jealous of you. They have to
be. They literally have to be jealous of
you. You've got something they want. And
I'm trying to I'm I think it's my looks.
I think it's because I'm better looking
than them. I've got more money than them,
more assets than them. I'm I'm trying to
figure it out. Like I'm I'm helping for
some guidance cuz it ain't for a
reaction because they don't get a
reaction 90% of the time. And even if
they don't get a reaction, none of the
time, they will still do it. They will
So it's not for a reaction. People used
to troll Timmy for a reaction.
It's deep down rooted jealousy.
You see where people like used to go on
Timmy's channel? Yeah. They knew that
they could rattle him and rattle him and
rattle him and rattle him and rattle
him. Um, but then eventually, you know,
he would he would he would reply. But
I've got actual channels dedicated to
stalking me. It is jealousy. It
literally literally is it is jealousy
for someone's life to revolve around
you. It is jealousy. I know I don't know
who that is, bro. But yeah, it is
definitely definitely definitely jealousy. Um,
so it definitely is jealousy. It's
definitely definitely jealousy because
even even even T uh even Timmy, right? Even Timmy um
even Timmy, right? I don't know who the
[ __ ] that is, bro. But even Timmy, you
don't have channels dedicated to Timmy.
Why do you have all of these men life
revolve around you?
Uh, bro, you got all of these men that
life revolves around you. I think it's
cuz you're better looking than them.
That's what I think it is. I think it's
better looks and more money, easier
life. That's what That's what I put down
to you, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, do they get trolled? No, I was just
basically wondering that boy why I've got a
What the [ __ ] Oh, you tell me. You're
[ __ ] obsessed with me. You won't shut
the [ __ ] up about me. So, you [ __ ] tell me.
No, listen. Bro, listen. You You [ __ ]
tell me. Oh, yeah. Surprise, surprise.
They trolled them. Isn't it funny how no
one else gets trolled on here? No.
Timmy, no. No one No one has ever got it
like I have.
And I think it's because I'm better
looking than them and I've got more
money than them. Personally, they don't
do it for a reaction. Even when they
don't get a reaction, they still do it,
you know? So, you're asking me the
question, ask yourself that because it's
like your life revolves around me. I've
got somebody emailing me every day. So,
you're jealous of something.
Yeah. I'm a local. So, your So, your
whole Think about this, right? I'm I'm
trying to put myself in this in in in
this position, that boy. Yeah. Well, [ __ ]
If you knew you was better than someone,
would your life revolve around them for
a reaction? Even whether that you got a
reaction or not? No, you wouldn't. Put
yourself in put yourself in their shoes,
right? No. That Jamie Thompson weirdo.
If you are better than someone, would
you be stalking them every day? Would
your life be revolve around them? No.
No. No, you would not. No, it would not.
So, it is obviously jealousy for people
to do it every day. It is jealousy
because you're actually tormenting them.
You're talking about yourself. I've got
more money than you, more assets than
you, designer clothes, and I've had more
women than you. Stop talking about
yourself. No girl had plenty of girls.
Was with a woman yesterday. I've got
more money than all of you. And I've got
more clothes than you. Stop listing
everything that you don't have yourself.
You don't have no car. You ain't got no
money. You've never had a girl.
Stop talking about yourself. And if I
don't have no house, what do you think
I'm in right now? Let's Let's talk about
you people in your 40s. No money, no
girlfriend, no life, no friends. Let's
start listing every single thing about
you little mongos coming on YouTube
every day, mongoing it out. Can't get
off of YouTube, right? I doubt any of
you people have anything in your life
when you can't even get off of YouTube.
Let's look at the evidence right on
YouTube every single [ __ ] day by
yourselves. No life. Never been seen
with a woman. All on YouTube talking to
each other despite claiming that
everyone else is this, everyone else is
that. Let's look at the evidence. Yeah.
Let's look at the actual evidence on
here. Right. I've took weeks off
YouTube. I've been seen with friends.
I've been seen with money. I've been
seen with women. You people have been
seen with nothing. You continuously come
on YouTube every [ __ ] day. A bunch of
40year-old life's losers. Let's start
talking about you people. Let's stop
putting the [ __ ] coin on the other
[ __ ] head now and start talking about
you life losers that can't get off of
YouTube. Oh, what? You don't like it
though, do you? No, you people don't
even have a [ __ ] friend to your
[ __ ] name. Which is why you come on
here telling people that they ain't got
no friends. You your life is nothing
without YouTube. Yes, that boy. You
would get on with your own life, bro.
That boy, you would get on with your own
life. Exactly. You'd get on with your
own life. But yeah, but you don't take,
bro, you don't take the mick out of
anyone. You take the mick out of
yourself. You're in your 40s and you've
got nothing. I've just listed
everything. You No, no, no. What you do
online, I tell you what you people do
online, right? You got no life, no
money, no friends, no girlfriend,
nothing but YouTube. You're a bully
victim. Yeah. All of you people in this
community are complete bully victims in
real life. So that's why you come on
YouTube trying to bully other people
that's got a better life than you.
That's what it is. That's why you come
on YouTube because you are the real life
bully victims. And you coming on here,
bro, trying to [ __ ] do this and do
that and do this and do that. And also
um even they don't do it, Joe. Even if
even if they don't get a reaction, they
still do it because they're jealous
bully victims. And also another thing,
Joe, they do it even if you don't react
to them, which is the whole conversation
we was getting into. Yeah, you're
talking about yourself again, bully
victim. Bro, listen, they do it even if
they don't get a reaction. This is what
I was just telling Greavvesy. I'm not
reacting to these people. I'm trying to
figure out why they're doing it. And it
all points to jealousy. Something that
you have that they want. It's not
reacting. It's me trying to figure this
out. Even if they don't get a I quote
reaction, they will still do it. No, no,
no. Okay. Okay. Wait, hold on. Hold on.
So, you No, it's not because you will
eventually react. Even so, you come
online all day wanting a reaction of
someone and you're telling me that's not
you being tormented. Hold on. Hold on a
minute. So you wake up all day every
day, right? And I hate these people,
bro. I was telling my sister about, not
my sister, my mama about this earlier on
the phone. I really want to go and [ __ ]
one of these people up. You know that?
Like she actually had to stop me doing
it. I was like, "Bro, I would love to go
to that Belfast." You know that, bro.
Like I hate these people. I [ __ ] hate
these people, bro. You don't understand.
I I want to catch one of them, bro. You
don't understand. I was telling my mom
about this earlier. It could be anyone,
bro. Triple H, Virgin Boy, LJ, I want to
give them a good big old [ __ ] hiding,
bro, and make a fool of them online,
bro. I don't like them, bro. Do you
understand? I do not like these people.
You know what I mean, bro? And at the
end of the day, And at the end of the
day, bro, even if they don't get a
reaction, they still do it. Even if they
do not get a reaction, they still do it.
People used to troll [ __ ] Timmy for
reaction because Timmy used to react.
These people, you could ignore them for
2 years and they would still do it. They
would still do it. Yeah. My history says
otherwise. A bit like your history,
right? Knowing where people live and
you've never gone on anyone's door, bro.
Yeah. You never going on people's Yeah,
bro. Listen, listen, listen. I have
turned up to more places than anyone on
here. So, you don't need to be sorry,
bro. You need to be sorry to yourself.
Yeah. And that's how I knew all of you
people was [ __ ] [ __ ] when I used to
travel all around the country and none
of you would show up and it doesn't matter. Yeah,
you people are the losers. Anyways, what
about you, National Cribe Agency? You in
your 40s, no girl, no money, you're sad
that can't get off of YouTube and L
won't do anything to anybody. You're all
a bunch of losers. Life losers. It's
just what this guy right said here.
They're all scumbags, bro.
They are literally low life scums that
ain't got nothing. That's all they are,
bro. Yep. Talking about yourself again.
And that's what they are, bro. They're
all [ __ ] lowife people that ain't got
nothing but YouTube. Remember that, bro.
No matter what they do, remember that.
So, anyways, uh So, anyways,
you have to come on YouTube every single
[ __ ] day. Yeah.
I come across like a loser, bro. You are
a loser. You are a big loser in your 40s
and I'll say it to your face. Like, you
can say whatever you want to me behind
the keyboard. That's fine. But guess
what? You're a big loser. And when I was
mentioning you about being in your 40s
and that you couldn't say nothing. You
are the people that are in your 40s, the
life's losers that don't even fit into
society. That's why you have to come on
here every single day because you're
absolute bully victims. That's why you
do it, bro. I know more than anybody why
you do what you do. You're big fat ugly
bully victims. Bully victims in real
life. That's what it is. And another
thing, Joe, even if you do not react to
these people, they still do it. And you
know that. So why are you saying that
they do it for a reaction? Even if you
do not react to these people, they will
not leave you alone. You can even ask LT
the same thing. Even if you ignore these
people, they won't leave you alone. It's
jealousy. This is one of the reasons why
I come off of it last time. You know
what I'm saying? You do not leave people
alone even if people ignore you cuz
you're jealous of them. And I've just
explained it to you, bro. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. You, bro, maybe in your dreams,
40year-old. Yes. Just like most of you
claim that you've got a job, but you're
sat on YouTube every day. We've been
over this, bro. We've seen the same
people every single day. Listen, bro.
And another thing is, right? You s Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay. So you sit on YouTube
all day stalking someone and them living
in your head for reaction.
One second. One second. One second. One
second. No, you don't leave people alone
because they're better looking than you
and they got more money than you and it
kills you. That's what Bro, do you know
what? I I will always remember that
Ronald Pump. He's like, "You're better
looking. You got more money than them
and it kills them." Raw, bro. It is the
truth. You know, when I look back on it
now, Yeah. I actually think of it. You
are better looking. You have got more
money than them. Anyone sell it is the
truth. I was like, "No, this guy's just
chatting [ __ ] He's like better looking,
more money than them, better life than
them." And it is the truth. It honestly
is so true. Like looking back on it now,
bro. I actually do understand. But it
doesn't matter. Anyways, you are
obsessed with me all day, every day on
YouTube. Whether you get a reaction or
not, I've got something you don't have.
I know that for a fact. Yeah. And I was
saying this to my mom earlier, bro. I
know this [ __ ] Yeah.
I know this [ __ ] I know this [ __ ] for a
fact. I know why you fat losers on
benefits do what you do every single
day. It's cuz you're jealous. That's why
you're on here. You know, if somebody
actually come on here, yeah, started
talking madness, and then they just
[ __ ] off for a long time, then I would
get it. But it makes sense why you
losers are on here every day and you
can't get off it. It is clear as day why
you losers can't get off of YouTube. You
know, I can I can say it more than I can
say it better than Monty Bad. Ever can ever can.
And I also just explained the reaction
to you as well. Why would you spend all
day being tormented trying to get a
reaction? It just goes to show you a low
life that's jealous. Think of what
you're saying is true. Yeah. You're
going to come on YouTube every day being
obsessed stalking someone for reaction.
Does that not show you how jealous that is?
You got something they want and I know
it. I know 100%. Look at this. Right.
Even though this person actually shows
their face. You look at Jamie Thompson,
right? Yeah. You look at You look like
Look at Johnny Jamie Thompson. Look what
he looks like. Look how old he is and
then look at what you look like. That's
the prime example. And then it will
understand that you probably better
looking than him. You probably got more
money than him. It all makes sense when
you actually add it up. It does all make sense, you know.
Yeah. And you can [ __ ] off as well. Bye-bye.
I'm I'm I'm not I'm am I in a better
position, bro. I've got more money than
them. I'm not a loser like them. I've
got money. I can do what I want when I
want, you know? And you know what I
think is hilarious? That you're a
[ __ ] loser pretending that you're 20.
We all know you're in your 40s. Come on,
bro. And that's what it is. It comes
down to jealousy. Cuz if it wasn't
jealousy, people would just leave you
alone, but they won't cuz they're
jealous of you. And that's the truth.
You can laugh all you want and be in
denial all you want. But that's what it
is. Guess what, bro? I'm not on YouTube
every day stalking people for a
reaction. I wouldn't sit on YouTube all
day stalking people wanting a reaction.
I ain't jealous of no one. I can safely
say, bro, as a normal person, you would
never see me doing that. The only people
that do that are [ __ ] people in love
or someone that's [ __ ] jealous of
you, bro. I'm telling you straight. But
yeah, it is funny, but it's in denial,
you know, and and and but and and I am
listen, I am in a better position than
most of these people. more clothes,
better looking, more money.
Like, yeah, no one gives a [ __ ] about
you, bro. You're in your 40s. Yeah,
you're not in a 40. You're not in your
40s and you've got a girl. No, come on YouTube, bro.
And I'm telling you as well, I'm not
reacting. I'm trying to explain it to
you and you're not listening, bro. I'm
not reacting. Reacting is like, "Fuck
you. You're this. You're that. You're
this." Bro, I'm literally trying to
explain to you that even if they do not
get a reaction, they will still do it.
And also, why would they come on YouTube
every day for a reaction? It's because
they're jealous of you. Because anybody
that is better than someone would not
sit there and stalk somebody all day on
YouTube for a male's reaction. And even
if you don't respond, they will still do it.
And no, I'm not responding. I've
literally just explained to you about 10
times I'm trying to figure out why
they're so jealous of me. It's it's it's
a normal thing. It's not being c it's
not being in denial. I want to know why
I've got these men so jealous of me.
That's all I want to know cuz Timmy
doesn't get it. And Timmy's actually reacts. So,
I think I've got something these people
want deep down, bro.
And bro, you can tell me what position
I'm in. I'm in a better position than
they will ever be, bro. I've got more
money than them. I'm better looking than
them. I'm young, you know? I'm better
[ __ ] way better than these people.
Sack on YouTube every day. I'm not the
one that has to be sat on YouTube every
day hating and repeating myself like these people, you know?
Um people [ __ ]
no Monty's different. Monty's very very
different. Monty People go on Monty's
live stream. Monty goes on people's live
um and they take the piss out of him.
People do not have channels dedicated to
him. He does not have three main
stalkers that don't leave him alone.
I've got three main stalkers that won't
leave me alone. Whether they get a
reaction or whether they don't get a
reaction, Monty doesn't have it and
Timmy doesn't have it. People go on
Monty's and take the piss because they
get a reaction that he actually gives to
them. But I mean, there's a four there's
a four uh line between between them.
With me, it's just pure jealousy. That's
that that is literally what it is
people because I used to do I used to go
on Timmy's and write something just to
get a reaction like once but the whole
having channels dedicated to people it
is jealousy that's when it becomes
like every everyone wants like a
reaction and [ __ ] but no it is
definitely definitely definitely deep rooted jealousy
trust me there's a huge difference
because I used to do it to Timmy cuz I
used to be like oh you remember when
Timmy used to react Mr. and you you'd
spend like one minute and you'd write
something and then he'd react. But if
Timmy didn't react, people um people
wouldn't do it.
Um people wouldn't do it. Do you
understand? If if he didn't react,
people wouldn't do it. But if I never
react to people, they would still do it.
Do you understand? That's where the
jealousy comes from, [Music]
which is um I mean they're jealous of a
few people to be honest, but not like me
and you can [ __ ] off as well. No, I'm
not being ridiculous. It's okay. Okay.
Okay. Let me let me ask you this
question then if I'm being ridiculous.
Why do you people come on YouTube every
day ain't got a life, Mr. Lonely? Let me
tell you what I think is ridiculous.
Right. I think it's ridiculous how you
come on YouTube every day telling people
that they ain't got this, they ain't got
that, when you're just sat on YouTube
all by yourself every day. I think
that's ridiculous. I think it's
ridiculous how in denial you are.
But yeah, I mean it is it is definitely
definitely definitely definitely
jealousy. 100 million%. You're never
going to admit it to yourself. People do
not [ __ ] come online every day
stalking people for no reason, bro. You
know what I'm saying? They they don't do
it for no reason.
And it's the lengths that they go to as
well. It's the lengths that they
actually go to.
So, mate, you're laughing at yourselves,
bro. I've explained to you about a
million times. You people are only
laughing at yourselves.
You're all alone on YouTube every day.
You ain't got a life. If you ain't got a
pot to piss in,
you are literally laughing at
yourselves. No one else. But I mean, if
it makes you feel better, then I guess
you're laughing at me. But deep down,
you're laughing at yourselves.
I find it strange how no one can show
what they look like on here and then
when they do actually get exposed, we
all actually see what they look like.
But no, you laugh at yourselves. you
know, being on YouTube every single day,
can't get off it because you ain't got a
life. You just literally laugh at yourselves.
You don't go out. You don't go out
drinking. You don't go out with your
friends. You're just sat on YouTube all
day. You're laughing at yourselves deep
down. That's what you're doing. But yeah,
um yeah, pretty much
laughing at yourselves.
Think about it. Think about it, bro. 3
years, shown more money than you people,
got more money than you people, had more
women than you, lived a life for 3
years, been abroad. What have you done?
You've done nothing but sit on YouTube
doing the same old thing. sat on YouTube
doing the same old [ __ ] thing. You
know what I'm saying? So, I mean, what
the [ __ ] bro?
Sat on YouTube doing the same old thing.
The same old the same old thing, man.
Yeah, I still have money. I still have
money. But the only reason why I'm not
going to the ATM,
where are they right now? I was with a
woman yesterday. Where's your woman?
Trevor Dawson. Where's your woman?
Exactly. Self-projecting, bro. You
40year-old self-reflectors don't bother
no one. And what I was saying before you
rudely interrupted me, you've been shown
money time and time and time and time
and time and time and time and time and
time and time again. Time and time and
time and time and time again, you've
been shown money. And the only only
reason why I don't go in my bank account
and pull out over two grand is because
bro, you you've got to show me 10 grand,
bro. I've shown you 5.7. You have to
show me 10 grand. So until you show me
10 grand, I ain't showing you nothing.
So you can think I'm skin. I don't give
a [ __ ] mate. I've got nothing to prove
to a bunch of music that can't get off
of [ __ ] YouTube. It's nothing to me,
you know? That's the only reason I don't
do it anymore because we all know that
deep down they're talking to themselves.
They're talking about themselves.
Yeah, of course you do.
And also another thing is uh and one
second I said I hate all women. Um I'm
not in denial.
That's the difference. I know. No, I'm
I'm not in denial. I was stating earlier
that I've had women been with women and
they're all stuck up [ __ ] Yeah. I'm
not in denial. I'm not in denial like
you people that don't get women that
stick up for them. Yeah. I'm not in denial.
Yeah. Oh, guess what? Do you know who
Trevor Dawson is, Joe?
You know who Trevor Dawson is? How can
you link me and Trevor Dawson together?
Yeah, I'll give you the link. One second.
But unless you show me 10 grand, I'm not
showing you anything. So you can say I'm
skin. Yep. Yep. Yep. I'm the skinnest
person going. Trevor Dawson is somebody
that used to come on YouTube every day
taking a piss, being a keyboard warrior.
So, I thought one day I'd go to
Middlesbrough and call him out. And
guess what? Not a [ __ ] peep.
Yeah, he's uh he's an old man that lives in Middlesbrough.
Yep. You're all the same old on here,
aren't you? You know what? I don't blame
LT for not coming on here anymore. You
people are all the same on here. You You
I noticed that with you people. You're
all Bro, I would love to get my hands on
one of you. You really don't understand.
Like, not not not Joe or anyone, but but
like Tip, not even Timmy. Not Not even
Timmy to be honest. [ __ ] uh
[ __ ] uh Yeah, bro. Listen,
Middlesborough is a very very small
town. Not not Timmy, just just some like
I don't know, even Triple H, [ __ ]
Smoky B. I'd love to get my hands on one
of these people, bro. But they're not
worth it, bro. Cuz do some serious
damage, bro. I would love to get my
hands on one of these people, bro.
For all the annoyance over the years
they've done to me, LT, other people
bothering people. Like, it's just
annoying just watching them. I'd love
to, bro. I'd love to.
Doesn't even need to be Prime. It
doesn't need to just anyone. You know,
the only good person on here is [ __ ]
Charlie and Wormy Clock. You know what?
He's actually a nice guy. He's actually
down to earth.
Charlie. Yeah, I tell you, Charlie is
actually a cool guy. I'm Wock.
I've actually met him. He's actually
sound. He's actually sound. But I' I'd
love to get my hands on one of these
people. Yeah, stop talking about prime,
bro. It's boring. Stop living in the
past. Stop living in the past. You're
boring, bro. You don't need to worry
about prime. If I ever catch one of you
people or know where any of you people
are, that's the end. Simple.
So, at the end of the day, bro, you you
can keep living in the past. No one
cares about the past. That's why if I
ever find out where any of you are, not
Joe or [ __ ] Greavves or anyone like
that. just anyone like Triple H.
I find it weird how like you can let
somebody go to your city, right? Not
even Harry F to be honest. Not not even
him because to be honest, they've
already been shown up when you've gone
to their [ __ ] cities multiple times
and they don't show up
to be honest with you. Not anyone like
that. No, not even Timmy. No, no, no. It
s people. The one I want to get is
people that's been bothering people for
years that's done it to different people.
You know what I mean? But just that kind
of [ __ ] thing to be fair to me.
>> Hey PJ, how's your Sunday been?
>> Yeah. Do you know where Kitty Minister is?
>> Do you know who what
>> do you know where Kitty Minister is?
>> Yes. I don't live far from it, PJ. live
about 5 miles from what I mean.
>> Yeah, I met I met and it's next to
Stalport and it's I've got a friend I've
got a friend that lives there. >> Really?
>> Well, I met made a new friend that lives there. Yeah.
>> Right. PJ, can I ask you a simple
question and don't?
>> Yeah. Yeah, he did. One second, Timmy.
One second. One second. Hold on. One second. Timmy,
>> you know what self projecting means, PJ?
>> Yeah. It's what these people do on
YouTube all day, every day. Exactly the [ __ ]
exactly the same.
>> You're giving them their attention by going
>> I'm leaving YouTube.
>> Timmy, I'm leaving you. I'm leaving
YouTube. So, I don't care, bro.
>> If you do, maybe it do you good. Might
help you do your mental health better.
>> And you don't even you don't even meet.
I said to you so many times, we should
go to Blackpool and you always ignore it.
>> Because I don't want to go to Blackpool.
It's a [ __ ] hole. That's where D goes.
The the Bacons, Harry, Fraud and all
them. I don't want to go around the area
for the bacons, PJ.
>> Yeah, but Timmy, it's the West Midlands.
So why wouldn't you go there?
>> West Midlands. It's [ __ ] Lan. It's
not Lancasher. It's
>> Yeah, it's Lancasher. Blackpool must be
Lancasher. Is it Lan?
>> Are you still Are you still Are you still gambling?
>> Mercy count. It's not Lancasher.
>> So you still Are you still gambling?
>> Even I'm standing as thick as Mongol here.
>> Are you still gambling?
>> No, I haven't gambled in nine days. PJ,
>> nine days. How much did you lose? How
Big pancake roll, chicken balls, curry.
>> How much did you lose? How much did you
lose 9 days ago?
>> 300 pound.
>> A grand.
>> You're rich nowadays, Timmy.
>> Peter, you should know these machines
are big now. So why do you still play?
>> I don't play them. I don't I ain't
gamble for two months.
>> I've [ __ ] with it, bro. I've heard that before.
>> Well, bro, believe what you want. I'm
not gambled. You should have lots of
money. Show me.
>> I do. I I've been out. I Timmy listen I
have shown 5.7K it's your turn now it's
your turn to show me
>> 10 grand on a look got that much
>> you know what I mean bro like I don't
[ __ ] do that [ __ ] £1,000 in5 notes page >> really
>> I did yes
>> if you look back on some old [ __ ]
troll channel you'll find it >> really >> yeah come
Miller uploads his [ __ ] tons of my
videos and that does Tiger.
>> Does Tiger know where Kitty Minister is?
>> Yes, he's been there.
>> Yeah, you're a Brummy, lad. You to me.
>> So why do you self project PJ and then
blame others? You do exactly the same.
>> I don't I don't self project.
>> Yes, you [ __ ] do, lad.
>> Oh, really? Really?
>> PJ, you're moaning about the trolls.
That's self projecting.
>> Yeah, cuz they're [ __ ] idiots.
>> You self projecting on him, mate. Cuz
they're [ __ ] Timmy cuz they're [ __ ] idiots.
>> Yeah, I know that. So why are you still entertaining them?
>> You don't go live anymore, do you?
>> Not really, mate. I can't be asked for
this place. Just full of the same old
[ __ ] [ __ ] I want new drama.
>> We all know [ __ ] fat Dan's a bacon.
We all know whiff rats is a packy
supporter. We all know [ __ ] Harry
Freud will never [ __ ] leave Liverpool
cuz he's scared money.
>> Timmy Timmy, you Timmy, why do you hate
Muslims? That's racist, bro.
>> No, I don't like their religion, PJ. So
you agree I'm Muslim. I'm Muslim.
>> You agree with a nineyear-old getting
married, PJ? Yes.
>> No, but I'm Muslim.
>> So you So you So you like to you like to
see nineyear-olds get married then, PJ?
>> No, I'm not saying that, but I'm saying
that I'm Muslim.
>> You are, PJ? Because the Islamic
religion states that, you know, Muhammad
married a 9-year-old. So you tell me
where the biology of that is. Why?
>> I'm Timmy. I'm Muslim.
>> I know you are. And I'm and I'm talking
about your religion here and I'm owning
you. So you tell me the biology where it
is right to marry a nineyear-old.
>> Timmy, listen. Yeah.
>> Very simple question.
>> Muslim people. Muslim people.
>> So you support a 9-year-old getting married? Yes.
>> No. But they they are cool people.
>> You're Muslim.
>> Timmy. Do you know the people who you
want to who you want to hate? Yeah. Let
me kick you cuz you keep talking about
it's not people. It's not Muslim people.
It's Africans. They're the ones that are
taking all the [ __ ] houses and this
that and the [ __ ] other. They're the
ones that are taking the [ __ ] houses and [ __ ]
[ __ ] He ain't even he ain't even
Muslims, bro. This guy has got no life
experience, bro. Really has got no life
you know? I actually feels [ __ ] sorry
for And yeah, it's it's He's mad.
He's mad, bro.
Muslim people are cool, man. I don't
know what his problem is.
Yep. Yeah, I pulled today actually. Hey,
Joe, are you still there? So, this woman
replied back. I was supposed to go to a
rave, but I didn't want to pay £35 to go
in. So, but yeah, she's replied back to me.
Maybe she'll meet. Who knows?
One reply out of five numbers. Yikes. Eh,
that's bad, bro.
Because Timmy, you're talking nonsense.
Why does Timmy want me to show £500?
I don't know why Timmy wants me to show £500.
Yeah, I was going to go Fabrics, but I
didn't want to pay £35 to go in.
I don't gamble anymore, bro. Really, I
don't. Well, I tell you, I gambled £7
last week when I was in the Weather
Spoons, but I don't gamble, bro. And I
go to Weather Spoons all the time. I
can't gamble no more, bro. Money's too
hard to come by. I don't I don't I don't
I can't gamble, bro.
I've already wasted enough time and
money on it and [ __ ]
stress. I can't.
But I I will go on a football. Well,
I'll gamble on the football, but I won't
gamble on anything else.
All the problems it's caused and [ __ ] I
wish I could [ __ ] win like four grand
now so I can buy that phone.
I can't pay £,700 for a phone, baby. No
way. That's steep. Like, I can't even
justify it. 1.7K for a phone. Nah, no
chance. That's [ __ ] America right there.
Nah, bro. Maybe come in two days.
We gambling is not but I might do a 200
pound both teams to score next month
maybe. But after today I'm gone. Bro,
this is this is weird again. It's weird.
These people are weird.
Oh, Timmy knows how to use question
marks now. Huh? Yeah.
I need to find a way to make money now, matey.
Oh, there's a fake you going around,
Daz. There's a fake one of you going
around. I didn't know if it was the real
you at first.
Oh, [ __ ] bro.
This is so sad, bro. Trying to [ __ ] Yeah.
Can't pay 1.7K on a phone.
No, bro. I can't. That's ridiculous.
Yeah, cuz you were speaking [ __ ] about
me, bro. I was kind of starting you, but
then I realized it was a fake you.
But no, I was actually telling my bro,
listen, Daz, between me and you, bro, I
would love to go to I would love to go
to Belfast, bro. I really would love to
go there, bro,
and just own that [ __ ] Like I said, I
was telling my mom about this on the
phone like badly and that. She's like,
"Just don't watch." She's like, "Just
don't watch it. Just don't watch it.
Just don't watch it." I was like, "It's
annoying, bro." And you know, even
watching them is annoying, man.
Just go there. Yeah. Smack him up, bro.
And then take the crown and you can be
the new lord. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
I want to get my hands on that triple H
as well. Cheeky bastard.
Cheeky [ __ ] bastard at Triple H is
trying to [ __ ] troll me. Yeah. Like
I've not been Newcastle three times and
he wouldn't come out.
He literally wouldn't come out.
He literally would not come out, bro.
He wouldn't come out.
You know that Daz, you know that Triple
H Yeah. This might be before your time,
bro. But I went Newcastle three times
trying to meet him. Yeah. And he
wouldn't come out. He literally would
not come out, bro. And then he comes on
here trying to like troll and that. And
I'm thinking, bro, these people are all
the same. You know that? I'm actually
feeling like these people are actually
all the same on here.
Do you know what? I'll be honest with
you. Yeah. If this was like two years
ago and I was a [ __ ] crazy bastard,
bro. I've calmed down since I would have
just went Newcastle tomorrow. Me.
I would have just went just like the
same thing with that Milton Kings.
That's That's what I used to do, bro.
Same as when I went to Manchester to go
to see Bomb the next day. I used to do
it, bro. just madness. But then I wait.
They never meet you, bro. They're all
the same. And then they all stick
together. They're all the same on here,
bro. All the same.
All the same, bro. Yeah,
they're all the same on there, bro.
All the same. That Triple H is a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
He always used to say, "Oh, come
Newcastle. We'll meet up and that." Cuz
he he didn't think I'd ever travel that far. Yeah.
He didn't think I'd ever travel that far. No.
Do you like that trip rate Steven Howard?
The only one who I wouldn't hurt on here is Greavvesy.
I wouldn't hurt Greavvesy. I wouldn't Steven Howard. Um Joe
unworthy clock. But there's some of
these people on here, bro. I'd love to
get my hands on
some madness, bro. Monty,
is that the real you, Monty?
Well, I didn't say I hate women. I'm
just not in denial.
See, the thing is with me, Dad, I'm not in denial.
That's not Monty. Monty left.
But I'd hurt someone like Trevor Dawson,
Smokey B, LJ, any of them. Virgin boy.
Even if it's just one of them. It
doesn't matter who it is.
You know what I mean?
Terry as well. Oh my god, that Terry.
Oh, [ __ ] me, bro. I'd love to get my
hand on that Terry.
He's another one. He's probably one of
the most, bro.
Yeah, certain people, bro, I'd love to
get my hands on, bro. On here.
Stop calling yourself a M. Huh?
Let's see what this plunker wants.
>> I'd love to come to Belfast, man, and do you >> in
except you're afraid on the
>> Yeah, I'm afraid
you was afraid.
>> I can't I can't hear you.
>> Yes, man. Timmy, just like you was
afraid when you was uh when you didn't
go in J. Yeah, I was but I went to Europe.
>> If you if you if you Yeah. And you done
absolutely nothing. And you were heading.
>> Anyways, listen. Why don't you book this
flight for me or give me half the fair
and I'll come?
>> I told you if you come to Belf,000.
>> I don't need to take anyone's money.
I've got more money than you. So why
would I need money?
>> Why did you ask for money then?
>> Why did I ask for money? Because I don't
want to spend my own money on it, bro.
You know what I'm saying? I don't want
to spend my own money on it, idiot.
>> But PJ, think about what you just said
there. You said, "If I Why don't you
give me half the money back?" And I
says, "Well, if you come to Belfast and
go live on the on, I'll give you
£1,000." And you I don't want just book
the flights. I never said that. No, I
>> Book the flight. Book Book the flights
and you've got my email.
>> You just got my email. Book the flight.
You've got my email. You just
>> said it. Why would I?
>> Just book the flights. You've got my email. Why?
>> So I can come and [ __ ] you up. You're [ __ ] annoying.
>> Why aren't you think about Think about how
Let me ask you this. How much How much
money do you get a month? >> Uh
>> yeah, less less. Yeah. Yeah. Go on.
>> How much money do you get a month
>> after? What do you mean? Like after I
pay my bills, how much money am I left over with? >> Yeah.
>> Probably about 2500.
>> Yeah. But then you come on YouTube
begging for money. You see how none of
it makes any sense?
>> You see how none of what you say makes any sense?
>> You've opened up a merch shop.
>> Listen, how much extra do you get a
month? How much extra do you get a month
from that gone?
>> From what? YouTube.
>> Begging for Yeah. Yeah. But begging for
donations and a membership.
>> Probably about the same amount of money
as you get off the brew from
>> Yeah. Well, I Yeah. Really? If you had
all of this money, you wouldn't you
literally wouldn't be begging for money.
>> Do you think you need money, but he puts on videos?
>> Do you think But the difference is he
makes millions, [ __ ] You don't
That's the difference. You're begging
money. You're begging money. You're
begging for a tiny bit of extra money,
but you're claiming it. Does it It Okay,
he's just not He's He's talking over me,
right? Listen, [ __ ] The reason why
Mr. B puts advertisements on his channel
is because he's going to make millions
and millions and millions. You are
barely going to make £200 extra. Why
would you swallow up your pride just for
£200 extra a month when you're making
all of this money? It makes no sense.
That's the difference. That's the
[ __ ] difference. Because his
followers are not skin losers. That's
the difference. Yours is
You're left with 2500. Oh, you [ __ ]
Left with 2500, bro. You was You was
begging for [ __ ] One sec. You was
begging for drinks and spoons. >> Yeah.
>> You was You was You was begging for
drinks in Weather Spoon.
>> You don't like people
>> Well, why was you drinking Why was you
begging for drinks in Weather Spoons?
>> Like, can I answer the question? >> Yeah.
>> Okay. Why? Remember uh a few years back
you were walking around a McDonald's at
6:00 in the morning asking answering a
question with a question. See, doesn't
make any sense. Nothing he says makes
sense. He's just making up a story that
never ever ever ever happened. He claims
he has all this money yet he has to beg
for an extra 150 a month and he begs for
drinks and weather spoons.
So read into that what you will. [ __ ]
left with 2500 a month. Oh you [ __ ]
left for 2500 a month.
Oh, you [ __ ] Anyways, you can get
yourself gone. Bye-bye now.
And then he's talking about Mr. Beast
who's going to make millions from
YouTube. And the difference is he's
putting advertisements on his channel.
He's not begging for money. You are
literally begging for money, which is
the difference. That's the big Yeah.
He is [ __ ] skin, bro.
Just like me. If I was getting free
grand a motor like Mr. B, I would do
Uber. You understand? I wouldn't do
Uber. You understand? It doesn't make
any sense. I wouldn't do any job. You
understand? It doesn't It doesn't make
any sense. People try to earn a bit of
extra money when they're lower money.
It doesn't make sense. Nothing he says
makes any sense. You understand? [ __ ]
can see me approach anyone they be. Yeah,
>> he's a [ __ ] fantasist. Absolute
Who the [ __ ] begs for drinks in [ __ ]
Weather Spoons, eh?
Doesn't make any sense. It don't make no
>> Doesn't make any sense, man.
>> I'll tell you what doesn't make sense.
You working 14 hours a day and making 80
quid. Does that make sense?
>> It wasn't 13 hours a day. It wasn't 13
hours a day. And well, yeah. And and
yeah, it would Well, it would make sense
to earn extra money. Yeah.
>> 15 hours a day for me.
>> You're begging.
>> It wasn't 15 hours. It wasn't It wasn't
>> It was like 9 hours. It wasn't 15 hours,
but bro, I'd rather work for 15 hours
and make£8 and beg. You're begging for money. You're begging.
>> You're But you're begging for money. I'm
not begging for money.
>> I'm riding a bike around. I'm not
begging for money.
>> I'm not begging for money.
>> You don't make no sense.
>> You're nearly 30.
>> You don't know where I live. So try 30
and you're moving.
>> You You don't know where I live. So try again.
>> You think your neighbor would never know where this
>> bro? Listen, you don't know where I
live. Keep guessing.
>> You think?
>> Well, you're getting the one out of Strawford.
>> Oh, really? Yeah. Yeah. Really?
>> Yeah. I know that.
>> So, um, are you getting a new F? Are you
get are you getting a new F seven?
>> No. You can't afford to get one. I got
more money than you. I don't beg for
drinks and weather spoons, bro. Look at
the evidence. Look at that. Okay. Why?
Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Why was
you begging? Why was you begging? Why
was you begging? Why was you begging for
drinks and web spoons? I've never I've
never I've never begged. I have never I
have never begged for anyone. I've never
begged anyone for anyone. Why you would do that?
>> I've never begged for money. Your dog
was in the money to PayPal. You begged
for money. You beg for money. No. Made
up stories. Made up stories. Made up
stories. Listen, you claim, this is what
doesn't. Look, he's talking over me
again. He's rattled. What doesn't make
any sense is how you claim that you get
£2,500 left every month after everything
is paid out. But then you'd beg for an
extra 150, 200 extra um um extra a
month. And then you try and say, "Oh,
well, Mr. Beast puts advertisement on
his videos." Well, I mean, there's two
things wrong with that. advertisement is
not begging for money and B he's going
to make millions off of that. You claim
that you get 2500 left after everything,
but you swallow up all your pride for an
extra 200 a month. Doesn't make any
sense. You don't make no sense. That's
why you resort to [ __ ] making up
stories about me begging for a drinking
uh McDonald's. And bro, I'd rather ride
a bike around and make my own money than
have to sit on YouTube and beg like you.
[ __ ] I've never begged anyone for
[ __ ] money. Why do you think the
whole Belfast thing never [ __ ] happened?
It all points to you being skinn.
Have you ever heard of a thing called
[ __ ] pride? Have you ever heard of a
thing called Have you ever heard of a
thing called pride?
Have you ever heard of a thing called pride?
>> Where was your pride when you got caught
out lying about going
out lying about going on
>> I think talking over me again because
you know everything that I say is the truth going to
say is the truth and that's why you're
talking over me. That's why you're
talking over me. You're just talking
over me. Talking over me again, bro.
Shut the [ __ ] up. You beg for money.
Nothing you say makes any sense. Shut
the [ __ ] up.
This guy is a [ __ ] He's a [ __ ]
[ __ ] isn't he, bro? He's a proper
[ __ ] I don't know how somebody can be so [ __ ]
Honestly, don't understand how someone
could be so [ __ ]
You're like a [ __ ] bro. It doesn't
make any sense. How can you be so [ __ ] [ __ ]
I shall never know. He's a [ __ ]
idiot, bro. He's
a [ __ ] absolute idiot, isn't he, man?
Who the [ __ ] begs for drinks and Weather Spoons?
How am I going to get by? It doesn't
matter how I'm going to get by. I've got
my own money. I get my own money. You
don't need to You don't need to worry
about that. Simple.
You don't need to worry about that. So yeah,
you don't need to worry about that, matey.
But who begs for drinks? And it all
points to you being skin. Literally,
that's all it points to. And when I ask
you about it, you just keep talking over
me. What the [ __ ]
You're on benefits. Just admit it.
You're on benefits just like everyone on
here admits it. I don't know why you
have to make up stories that you own
property and you have all this money.
Bro, you have nothing. You really,
really don't have anything at all.
Why do people here have to try and act
like they've got loads and loads of
money? I don't understand.
Virgin boy, LJ, when really they don't have anything.
Nothing at all. This is all weird. I'm
leaving anyways after today for a little
bit, bro. Gets weirder and weirder and
weirder and weirder and weirder.
So weird. It's creepy. It's starting to
give me the ick again.
It gives creepy vibes, bro. [ __ ] You
know what I'm saying?
He's an idiot, man. [ __ ] idiot.
Who the [ __ ] would beg for drinks in
Weather Spoons? He, Bro, I'm telling
you, he gets that £400 a month. He's
just too ashamed to admit it. That's
what it is, bro. It's He's too ashamed
to admit it.
I'm telling you. You know what I'm
saying? Everything points to you being
skinned. Literally everything.
If you was left with £2,500 a month, you
wouldn't be begging for money.
To be honest, you probably wouldn't even
find ways to make more money because you
you'd get enough money. It just don't
make sense. Nothing does. And then when
when you tell them it don't make sense,
they resort to talking over you. So,
this does not make any sense.
See how [ __ ] late that is, mate.
[ __ ] late, man. [ __ ] Yeah,
I'm going to leave you people to it as
well anyways after today.
I just don't understand. If he has all
of this money, why does he beg on YouTube?
I just I just want to know
cuz I just want to know why if you get
all this money, you would beg on YouTube
cuz people normally beg because they're
skimp or they're homeless or because
they have no money. So why would you beg
if you have money?
That doesn't make any sense.
That does not make no sense. He's a
skint bastard, bro. Just like Virgin
Boy. Just like the rest of them. And
I'll prove it when I'm gone tomorrow
when they're all stuck on YouTube and
can't get off it again.
I'll prove it again. You know,
I'm going to ask this person if they
want to meet up. Yeah.
Yeah. That Thompson, he's a proper stalker.
Yeah, I get emails from him. Yeah,
I think it's Yeah, like I was saying
earlier, bro, it's definitely definitely jealousy. Definitely jealousy. It is.
I can go on it right now. Let me go my
emails, bro. Look.
Yep. Email. See?
Yeah, they're definitely jealous of something, bro. Definitely jealous. Yeah.
I remember USA is he had a Kelvin Klein
bra. Steven Howard
Going to have more some going to have
some more pork soon. But
I worked on your mom. Yeah.
Oh, what color was it? I think it was black.
Yeah, it was black.
I don't think you could ever forget them
boobies coming out of that Calvin slime,
mate. But yeah, it was black.
That must been such a madness that her
dad Yeah. found out like all of the [ __ ]
that she done on holiday. Yeah.
I think it was black.
Oh, I'm going to have some more of that pork.
Yeah, talking about yourself, buddy.
You've got no money. You've got no bird.
Yeah, you're just talking about yourself, man.
All about yourself. And when I'm off of YouTube,
you know what I want you to do, Steven
Howard? Yeah. I know you don't like
getting involved in any of this [ __ ]
but you see how these people are saying
this stuff to me when I'm telling you
that they're speaking about themselves.
I want you to when I go tomorrow, I want
you to show me if these people are still
on YouTube every day so I can prove to
you that they're talking about themselves.
Uh cuz they say that people are skin,
they're this, they they're this, that,
and the other. Okay. Well, when these
people can't get off of YouTube and
they're still on it every day, then we
can safely say that these are the people
that are talking about themselves. These
are the ones with no money, no women, no
life. So, make sure you email me. Yeah,
these self projectors don't bother me,
bro, because we know that they're the
ones that sat on YouTube every day
and they've been doing it for years. So,
they don't bother me because we we all
know that they're just writing about themselves.
I've shown more money than anyone in
this community. Showed more women than
anyone in this community. Have more
money than people in this community. And
they still call me what they are themselves.
Sad, isn't it?
Yeah. Email me. You got my email. I want
you to do it daily
and we'll see who the real skin low
lives are. Yeah, we'll see it, bro.
We will see, bro. And that sub zero as well.
Yeah. I've got no money. I've got about 2K.
I got no money. Yeah.
meet this person. [ __ ]
How much do you think that LJ gets a
month? I think about £3400.
Yeah. Leon, you're noshing off [ __ ]
LJ daily. You sad. Yeah.
People keep saying he come he come on my
door and he done nothing. Like that's
not even a skip, bro. Like I don't don't
know why people bring that up. He come
on the door and he literally done nothing.
He literally done [ __ ] all. Was I hiding
behind the bed? Was I hiding? No. I open
the door, told him to [ __ ] off and I
stood in front of my mom
and then he had like two chances to kick
the door in my face. Like he looks
stupid every time he says that, right?
He literally looks so stupid
because A you open the door, B you stood
in front of your mom, C you had two chances
to [ __ ] kick the door in your face.
And then he said about how you
Yeah, bro. When you show me 10 grand,
come back to me.
Yep. Uh, when you show me uh 10 grand,
which I've been waiting for for [ __ ]
two years now, come back to me.
I'll be happy to show you some money.
And yeah, when you come back with that
10 grand I've been waiting for.
I'll happily play the money game. Yeah,
it's just the same old thing on here, is
it? Every day. Same old same old repeating people.
Yeah. And when you show me some of your
money, your 10 grand that I've been
waiting for, then I'll be more than
happy to show you money. Simple. Yeah.
These people are [ __ ] retards. Really are.
They're [ __ ] retards on here, bro. Absolute retards. Air bombs. One second. Yeah, bro.
Oh, these people are [ __ ] skinn.
These people are freaking skinn than the
[ __ ] skin flint. Steven Howard,
they're skinting skin flint. Let's kill it.
They're skinting skin flint.
And the fing skin flint. Yeah. Yeah man.
Do you think there's ways to to make
extra money nowadays, Steven Howard?
Nah, not really.
Not in terms of a self-employed job. Not really. No. Nah,
not really, matey.
Not really, buddy. Yeah.
Oh, shoplifted. Yeah, [ __ ] that.
It's cuz you buy too many takeaways.
Hey, Zippy. You buy too many takeaways,
Stephen Albert. That's what it is. Bro,
nah, not me. I'm not skin. Virgin boy
skin. Look at the amount of£10 notes
he's got. Steven Howard
trying to uh
trying to convince people that he's got money.
I've never known someone someone so
desperate to try to convince people that
they're not skin. Yeah. You bro [Music]
Yeah, it's funny, bro.
Yeah, you're boring as well. Go suck's
dick. You are a loser.
Yeah, you are loser. Go suck's dick. Oh [ __ ]
Yeah, he's such a skin bastard, bro.
It's a madness, isn't it?
I used to have a lot of money, matey.
Them casino times were good times,
weren't they, Stephen?
They were good times, bro. There.
Good, mate. I used to lose a load of
money on it. I just hope I can win some
money on the football in it.
Fingers crossed though.
You never know, one day I might be
begging for [ __ ] drinks and weather spoons. Oh, [ __ ] Yeah, man.
I hate just sitting around not being
able to do anything cuz there's no
opportunities. I need to make some more
money, bro. Somehow know that I need it.
I I have money.
I can do what I want. But now I want to
start like I used to like the Uber
because they used to pay you every Wednesday.
So like you do three days, it' be like
160 170 still money. Money is money in it. So
they used to pay every Wednesday in it. So
So I need to Yeah, I'm probably going to
put like 150 on two teams. I think
150 on a double team to score maybe if I
if I don't get anything by then. Oh, [ __ ]
I like all of them.
But you know they're vegan, don't you?
You know them pot noodles are vegan. Yeah.
You know, I actually fancy a pot noodle, you know.
Now people going to think I'm skinned.
Well, I'm not skinned. I did just start
saving money now.
Yeah, I actually fancy some of them pot
noodles. I've got some pork.
Yeah, they're vegan. They are. They're
vegan, bro. I like all of them. I like
the beef one, the black one, the the
blah blah. I like the Yeah, I like all of them
to be fair. Yeah.
Do you think there's Do you think
there's a way to make extra money these days, Jensen?
Nah. The Uber thing was good, man. And I
made like 160 in 3 days,
but two of the days weren't even proper hours. So,
so if you said 88 88, so that's like 170
in 2 days. So if you done like 9 10
hours, 2 days, you made like 170,
which is still quite good, isn't it? Really?
That's extra money. It's quite good, is it? Yeah.
Maybe 200. Probably. You can maybe make
200 in two days. Yeah.
It did used to get tired though. That's the thing.
But 88. So if you done two days, that's like one
76. It's still quite good, isn't it?
Really, for two days.
And it's not supposed to be a main job,
which is the whole point. I think you
could probably do 200 to be honest in two days.
Did it said? Yeah.
I don't care, bro.
I want I'm talking to one. By the way,
I'm talking to one actually.
I was going to go to a rave, but I
didn't end up going to Fabrics cuz they
were charging £35 to get in. I weren't
going to pay it. So, I got one that that
I'm talking to. Yeah. One reply out of
five numbers. Tragic, is it? I told you
Saturdays are [ __ ]
Saturdays are the worst.
had some pork, bro. I'm hungry again. I
might I might need to eat some more.
Yeah, I got one reply here.
I need a way to make money now, bro. [ __ ]
I think the only way is winning. Is it
witted money? Nico,
well, we'll wait a month anyways. If we
don't get anything in a month, then
we'll have to start slabing them
football bets on again. It's the only
way I can think of. [ __ ] sake.
Yeah, I got one reply out of five numbers.
But that's just England for you, is it?
It will never change here. So yeah.
Do you think the the Uber paid good?
Steen Howard? I think it paid all right.
Me in terms of a side hustle. I think so.
It's not like it's proper work. The only
bad thing was the [ __ ] Sunday,
but other than that, no,
I think I made 656 in 5 hours.
88 and 9 hours one time. Yeah, it's What
else can you do? There's nothing else
you can do.
So, say you done that every day.
So, it's better than nothing, is it?
It's better than nothing really. So,
it's better than nothing. It is better
than nothing, bro. If you done that,
right, say you wanted to go to America,
right? You could go to America like two
months. Even doing that, right? A couple
of times a day, you could.
No, but it was it was uh
it's not it's supposed to be extra
money. It's not supposed to be main
income. This is what even though people
do do it for main income.
So it's like
where else are you getting that kind of
money? If you made 170 in 3 days, where
else are you getting that kind of money?
So it is it is it is good to be honest.
I think it's I think it was good me.
I thought LJ said I couldn't do it cuz
I'm too anxious to go into people's
houses. Oh, that's self projection. He's
the only one that's got anxiety.
It depends. Get used to it, bro. Like 88
88 88 it adds up. You can easily make
£400 in a week.
We need to try and get with another
[ __ ] company now, bro. [ __ ]
But the only bad thing is you have to
buy into it. That's the only bad thing.
You have to buy into it.
Buy a phone. Buy a [ __ ] You know what
I'm saying? That's the only bad thing.
Don't think there is any ways to make
money nowadays, bro.
No, not really. Nah.
Sell your ass. Is it
sell your [ __ ] ass? Yeah.
Tell your [ __ ] it. Yeah.
Oh man, I'm trying to finish up something here.
That's Alien girl was such a [ __ ] I
need to remove her from my picture by
the way. I don't know why I've still got
that on there. She was a proper [ __ ]
Swear these women go on dates to pass time.
can't really go back to gambling because
with gambling comes risks and
I can't one day
your money and one day be skin. That's
the thing, bro. That's why you can't
gamble. You see, you'll end up like
[ __ ] virgin boy.
You end up like the virgin and red star.
So you can't do that. You can't do that.
I'm not used to doing this, you know. Nothing.
So I'm saying it is Sunday to be honest.
Why did she look odd? You didn't like
the way she looked.
And now she's saying she's moving back
to Italy. So why did you go out with me
for moving back to Italy? It doesn't make sense.
I think you need to stop this, bro.
this whole dating thing in this country.
I think you need to stop, bro. Really?
Nothing good comes out of this, you know.
It's just going to start [ __ ] with
your mental health and [ __ ] Yeah.
That's weird. She wanted to hold hands
and rub fingers, but she didn't want to
kiss. That's a bit strange.
Time waster, isn't it?
See, when you approach sober, right, the
bad experiences make you want to drink
because it will depress you. And where
you're out anyways, you will just start drinking.
You will just start drinking. That's the problem. [ __ ]
I want to work and earn some money, bro. [ __ ] sake.
That was a funny [ __ ] week, is it? Yeah.
[ __ ] get a job. Yeah. I [ __ ] just
do these football bets. I'll be sweet,
bro. I'll be [ __ ] sweet.
[ __ ] sake, man.
I'm just trying to think of things I
could do, bro.
I ain't sure, bro.
You got any suggestions?
It's not that I don't have money. I've
got money, bro. I have more than enough
money, but I want to kind of be earning
money now, you see.
Especially since I'm leaving again soon. Yeah.
But I like I like earning. You know what
I'm saying? That's the thing.
I don't like sitting on my ass all day,
bro. I don't sit on my ass all day. So, virgin boy. Um,
what the [ __ ] do I do? Hey. Um,
I have to buy another bag as well.
That's the thing. This is bad, bro. Really bad.
We're talking like I don't have 2K, but
[ __ ] I mean it ain't going to last
forever, is it?
It used to be nice getting that money
coming every Wednesday, bro.
Yeah, it was good.
Yeah, it was nice, bro.
Come to buy my car, bro. [ __ ] Um, [ __ ] sake. Yeah,
it' be good that, you know, get paid
every Wednesday, go out every Thursday.
It' be sick. I don't like Saturdays. So,
oh bro, that' be sick. We can get
something like that again. Get paid cuz
I was going to do the Friday to Saturday,
maybe like a Monday or Tuesday, then go
out the Thursday.
You know what I mean? Steven Howard,
I was my best when I was earning money, bro.
I didn't think about this women [ __ ] or anything.
Yeah, some madness.
Anything's got more body, Stephen. I
would be your virgin boy.
Me mate. [ __ ] me, son.
[ __ ] me, mate. Not [ __ ] virgin boy.
[ __ ] virgin boy. Yeah.
He has to convince
himself he's got money.
Yeah, it's good to get paid out
Wednesdays, isn't it?
Used to hit your car at midnight, eh?
I don't think Uber is that bad, to be
honest. I don't think it's that bad,
bro. You could easily make 400 in a
week. 350, 400. I think it's all right.
I think that's as good as it was going to get.
So he'd rent the bike, which was £12, but
you'd still make a lot of profit on it, you know.
I think it was good, man.
Wish I had my account back, bro. I'd be
doing it [ __ ] now.
It's [ __ ] cancellation. [ __ ] fraud, bro.
Even if you made £60 a day, bro, it's
still better than nothing. Really?
It's like a bill, is it? Like, [ __ ]
Yeah. I remember that Sunday. It took me
8 hours to make £55.
That Sunday was dead.
That Sunday was dead, bro. [ __ ] And it was dead.
It was really bad, bro. Uh
maybe I won't get this phone on contract.
I'd like to buy I don't think I could
buy it outright cuz I can't waste
[ __ ] two grand on a phone and I can't
justify it at the same time. So,
no, it's easy to pedal. It's an electric
bike. It's an e- pedal bike.
I obviously made money cuz I bought the
TV and then I was earning money. So,
you obviously must have earned money
bought the TV and still saved. You know
what I mean? Huh? Yeah.
Not sure what could be.
What are ways to get extra money
nowadays? Steen Howard.
Well, no. I bought it with some of the
rent money, but wish I made it back with
some of the grafting in it. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ] It's bad.
Well, I like the free time, but the
thing is when you got when you get free
time, you get depressed and [ __ ]
That's the thing.
So, where I was always busy, it was good.
It's not that bad. The hardest thing was
actually just going out doing it. But
once you do it, it's fine.
But I have to buy into so much even if I
started again. I need to get another
phone. I have to pop the SIM up. I have
to buy a bag. I just have to literally
do it for like a week straight, bro.
To even make a profit. How bad it is.
Yeah, the weather that's not a problem, bro.
The cooler it is, the easier it is.
It'll probably be easier to you probably
can make 120 in a day now. To be fair,
I reckon you can make 120 in a day. In
the summer, it's worse. No, no, no, no.
In the summer, it's worse.
The summer is the worst for it. The best
month is March. March, April,
maybe even September.
The summer is the worst cuz it gets hot.
It's hard to do it in the heat.
Constantly thirsty as well. That's a Uh,
get himself a little job. Get a job,
mate. Get a [ __ ] job.
You might finally lose your [ __ ]
virginity if you got yourself a job.
What I used to say.
Let me see if red star still stalking me.
Still stalking me. Wow.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Well, it's nice to know that you live in
some people's head, isn't it?
It's so bad, bro. Like they're never
going to get me insecure. I don't know
why they do this. They're never going to
make me insecure. They're never going to
get me mad. I don't know why they do
this every day. Like it's like earlier I
wasn't reacting to it. I was just trying
to figure out why they do it.
Like no one reacts to them.
They're [ __ ] weird, bro.
sitting on YouTube stalking every day.
It's mad, isn't it? That's what Pat Mage
used to do.
They are actually obsessed.
They are actually obsessed, bro. They
They don't even do stuff for reaction.
They are actually obsessed.
That's the difference, you know?
All right. Are they trying to get people
like insecure or
they're never going to make me insecure?
Cuz I always say to them, bro, like I
just say to them, "Show your face."
Like that's that's how you always beat
them. You just say to them, "Show your face."
Um, and they can't show their face.
Obviously, that's how you always win, is it?
I'd love to do it. I don't even have an
account. I would be doing it now, man. It's depressing.
I've got money, but I just want to be
earning money again.
And that's how you know Virgin by skin
as well because look at that money.
Yeah. You would not change that money up
which is his housing benefit. You would
not change all of that money up into
euros. You can just tell that he just
withdraws his housing benefit to make it
seem like he gets money.
Cuz when you got a council gap, they pay
you housing benefit. My sister gets it as well.
And obviously you you have to pay it
yourself whereas years ago you just pay
it. You can just tell he gets like 134500
withdraws it all to make it seem like
he's got money then puts it back in.
He literally is a fantasist.
Literally is a fantasist.
So, you withdraw all of your benefits
and somehow you're going to turn all of
that into euros
into [ __ ] euros for 3 days.
You really, really, really are desperate
to try to prove yourself to people on YouTube.
And you know what he said to them as
well, Stephen? You have some in 20s, but
most in tens. [ __ ] pathetic.
You can just tell, bro. You can just [ __ ] tell.
Yeah. Nothing screams more of a skin
than withdrawing your [ __ ] housing
benefit trying to make it seem like you
got [ __ ] money. That is sad, bro. To
the next level.
That really, really, really is sad.
Bastard, bro. I'm leaving anyways after
today. I won't be on for a long time.
Leave these weirdos to it. Weirdos.
weirdos on this community.
They're jealous. I don't understand how
they can do it for years. I don't
understand how they can do this for
years and years and years
every day. I think it's madness, man. I
think I don't know how people could do
it for years and years and years and
years and years and years and years and
years and years. It says a lot about
their shitty life, it really.
But yeah, bro. Who the [ __ ] has that
many 10 pound notes?
Yeah, he's [ __ ] skinned, bro.
He's got housing's
housing benefit. That's what he does.
Think of it, bro. If someone had all
this money, why have they got no bed?
Why are they living in a bedset? Why are
they wearing Trumpy clothes? Why have
they only ever been on a holiday when
they were 31?
You understand, bro?
Who the [ __ ] is that?
Yeah. Have you noticed? It doesn't make
sense, doesn't it?
desperately trying to convince people
that he's got money. That is madness,
bro. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, I need to cut down on the
takeaways, Greasy, cuz uh
Yeah, I really do need to start saving
money now, bro.
Yeah, they probably put their [ __ ]
money together to be honest.
[ __ ] Probably uh probably put their
[ __ ] money together.
Nah, bro. They It's housing benefit. I'm
telling you, it's that housing benefit.
See, the only reason I had money, right,
like I used to have cash is because I
used to win money from the casino. Cuz I
used to go casinos. Now I don't have
like any cash cuz I don't I don't gamble
the casinos anymore. But all my money is
in my account. So why do they have so many10 notes?
It's because it's housing benefits.
I don't care, bro. I've got more money
than them anyways. I'm just telling you
how it is, you know?
Like because I that's how I used to have
cash cuz I used to gamble the casinos.
So they used to pay me in cash
and people used to just get on at me
over it. But I've never known somebody
so skinn try to get people to think that
he's got money. I've never known it.
I've never never never never known it, bro. You know,
and he tried trying to say that he shown
14,000. He's never shown 14,000 pound
before. He's the kid is [ __ ] skinn
skinnier than anyone I've ever known, you know,
and all he wants people to do is start
going on the channel and arguing with
him so he can get the police involved.
They're just low lives. This is why I'm
coming off of it. They're just low lives.
That's what they are, bro. They're just
absolute lowife scumbags. They're not
even worth even talking to, talking to,
talking about. Let them be jealous. Let
them be on YouTube every day jealous of
you. You're obviously doing something
right, bro. You know what I'm saying?
So, what I count said earlier, they're
just low life scumbags.
They're not even worth talking about.
Same as at Triple H.
And you know why I didn't go Newcastle,
bro, again? Cuz I know what these people
are like. I know what these people are
like now, Grezy. Cuz it'd be a couple of
years ago, I would have went Newcastle
the next day, just like I went to
Manchester the next day, just like I
went to all these other places the next
day and people didn't come out. If I
didn't know any better, I would be I I
would have gone there.
But we all know what happens. You go
there, they don't come out, they all
stick up for each other, and then it
goes around in circles, and no one calls
this person out, and no one calls that.
It's not worth being on this disabled
place, bro. For real. For real.
For real. For real, bro. I'm telling you.
All the same on here, bro. They're all
the same on here.
These little mongos.
I don't like it, bro. It winds me up.
And if I can't get my hands on these
people, then there's no point me
watching them. You know what I mean?
But you shouldn't think like that. At
the end of the day, that's not the
that's not the right way to think
because they all do this because of jealousy.
Sorry, bro. So deep down. Sorry, brother.
So what I was saying is uh they do all of this.
They do this due to jealousy. So that's
why it's the wrong way to think. At the
same time, it's not a good way to think
cuz they do all of this [ __ ] cuz of
jealousy and [ __ ] And they ain't got a
life. They're low lives. That's the way
to describe them. Low lives. I'll go for YouTube.
Oh, wilder now.
What do I What do I I'm going to order something
my fresh start tomorrow.
Maybe some fish.
I've got pork, but I can have that
tomorrow, can't I? Um,
fancy some fish.
So, yeah. But do you understand what I
mean? Steven Howard, if I didn't know
like what these people are about, I
would have went to Newcastle tomorrow, bro.
Just like I used to do back in the day.
If I didn't know what all of these
people are about on here,
don't meet anyone. They all stick up for
each other. And you know what I'm saying, bro?
That's why I hate this place, bro.
This is like a triple H, but it's
winding me up today, bro. And I'm
thinking, bro, like the scenes on it,
like this guy is worse than Terry, cuz
I've actually been to Newcastle three
times and this little [ __ ] has not come
out. He's actually worse than Terry. You
know what I mean?
You know what I mean, bro?
No, they're not, bro. I don't even care
about Harry to be honest. But that No, I
don't even really care about that Harry
as much, bro. It's that Triple H. Yeah,
the guy does not come out when you go to
Newcastle. Then he's trying to [ __ ] stir
and I see what he's doing as well, bro.
And I don't like it. I don't find that
[ __ ] funny, especially when your [ __ ]
ass has not come out. Like, it's
annoying because he knows, right?
There's a few things. He knows what this
person is doing. He's continuously
trying to [ __ ] start on your channel,
right? He's continuously trying to [ __ ]
stir on your channel and
he knows what this person's about and
he's trying to [ __ ] stir on this channel
yet when you have gone to [ __ ]
Newcastle [ __ ] three times he has not come out
because bro like if if this was a few
years ago I'm not going to lie to you I
would have went there and started
talking about these kids like I'm I'm
not even joking bro if I didn't know any
about what these people do. I would have
went there and started talking about
these kids. I'm not even joking, bro. I
don't think that stuff funny. I think I
don't find that funny, bro. It's not
funny. It's annoying.
I'm going to order this fish and chips
now as well.
Well, I don't find that funny. Me? No.
cuz we don't see you doing it, Grezy.
Yeah, this all piss and shits. We don't
see you. He's trying to [ __ ] stir on my
channel knowing damn well what the
person is trying to do,
right? And then he is the same person
that does not come out when you have
gone to Newcastle three times.
Do you understand? I don't find any of
it funny, bro.
Cuz we all know if I went to Newcastle
again tomorrow, you wouldn't come out again. So,
it's just lucky I know what these people
are actually like, bro. So, I don't
waste my time and money again on these [ __ ] idiots.
Is that okay with you, boss?
That's why I don't approach sober
anymore. Greasy. It's depressing. It
gets you depressed.
It is depressing in it, bro.
Just want my [ __ ] Uber account back. Yeah.
Efficiency. Don't you greasy.
USA is a little Kelvin Klein bra.
What a lovely site we see.
I wish I could have that steak, bro.
Nah, it's [ __ ] It's all hella here,
bro. It's all hal here. You can't get
any English places.
Yeah, you can't you can't get any places
around here that's not allowed, which
obviously doesn't make a difference with
fish, but I like a savoy and I'm not
going to have a chicken sablo. That's disgusting. Sorry.
You're going to [ __ ] die one. You're
No, the fish and chips is nice.
Yeah, it doesn't taste The fish tastes
the same obviously cuz it's fish, but
not like a not savoy.
No, it's hard to get a pork sub now.
[ __ ] me, bro.
You're going to die one. You're going to
You'll die a virgin. You'll die one.
Is that right, Grizzly? You [ __ ] die
one. You, mate.
Joking, mate. I love you, man. Love you, Greasy.
I love you, bro. I know you're not a virgin.
He He will die when he will. He will
[ __ ] die when he walk.
I get 80 pound every week on top.
That's good, isn't it, Grezy? 80. That's
like what, a week shopping?
That's what I'm probably going to do. An
80 football bet. £80. Eh,
£80 on a double. Both teams to score
should return about 260.
That's why I was really trying to meet
someone before I run out of money. Grezy,
but nothing. I was trying to meet
someone before I could I run out of
[ __ ] money, bro. That's the thing. But uh not interested.
Just not interested in this country. Oh [ __ ]
Greasy, who do you think's better
looking, me or Virgin boy?
Right. No homo.
Definitely me, bro.
Definitely definitely definitely me.
I'm younger and I've had a better life
than that virgin. him. He
Go away. You're a keyboard warrior. So, yeah.
Listen, bro. You're a keyboard warrior.
[ __ ] Back to Large Asia. Boring.
Boring keyboard warrior.
Do I think do you know what? I might do
that video. Greasy. Do you want me to do
that, bro? go to Belfast and just
[ __ ] own this large.
Yeah. And you want to see that video of
me going there and just owning him.
I would [ __ ] this, bro.
I would [ __ ] him so hard, bro. You don't understand
or anything, but I [ __ ] him hard, bro.
intelligence used to say that.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, man. Bit of foster.
You know what? I could actually go
there. You know, I've never been to
Ireland before. I could actually go
there and I can officially say I've been
to all of
the countries in um the UK.
Go to the Guinness Factory, Grezy. That
would be a lovely site. I own that [ __ ]
and then do a video in the factory. Yeah. Any
new films you want to watch? Squeezy
got one on one, bro. I would slap him
up, bro. Easy,
easy. Slap him up.
Bless you crazy.
You need to watch what we did last summer.
Grezy. Oh, you actually want to do So,
you'd actually do Uber if you could, Greasy. Yeah,
you sound like a pretty good [ __ ] Grezy.
Yeah. Bless your grieving and your
little bicycle then. Bless you. Yeah.
Your back sweats. That is weird, bro. Yeah,
this guy said, "Oh, you need at least 2.5k
to earn the good life." And that
What do you mean only standard?
Nah, you can live easy off 1 [ __ ] 6K
2K a month without the outcomes. Nah. Yeah.
No, you can live off 1.6 two grand a
month easily if if you if you have no outgoings.
Trust me, bro. I was doing that on the
Uber for ages.
apparently I don't need to give rent
obviously I don't have it to give you
know what I'm saying greasy so if you
ain't got it
you ain't got it like I mean spare to
give it you know what I
Do you give Do you give your mom rent? Yeah.
>> Really? Your mom died when you were six?
Sorry to hear that, bro.
Well, at least your mom didn't starve you.
Yeah, my dad died when I was 12. But obviously,
yeah, sad. But well, at least your dad's
still alive, is it?
How did your mom die? [Music]
How did your mom die? What the [ __ ] Jeez.
Well, at least you know your mom died. I
don't know how my dad died. So,
I'm sure sometimes you think about your
mom, you know, probably
cuz you know these things kind of affect people
um and stuff.
Maybe even even it's not straight away.
Like virgin boy was abused by his mom
and that's where the hatred comes from
living with your mommy cuz his mom never wanted him.
But you know
it's past trauma you know
Yeah, I don't know how my [ __ ] back
died. That's a missy. [Music]
Yeah, there's always some fish and things. [Music]
Where the [ __ ] is this room?
Um, was it sudden? Um, he basically uh
went to sleep and then never woke up. I
mean, he wasn't alcoholic, so
maybe he died of carbon dioxide. I'm not
sure, but the death certificate was
inconclusive. So, just went to sleep and
didn't wake up
and the law the landlord found him like
decomposed and [ __ ] you know, in the
summer in it. So, yeah,
but obviously my mom brought me up and
[ __ ] so I didn't really know. Um, yeah. Yeah. All
right, man. Uh 0256. Yeah. >> 0256. >> Yeah.
Yeah. So that's how that happened. But I
didn't really know him. I didn't know
him like that. So obviously my mom
brought me up. So it was Yeah.
>> Yeah. Greasy. Um, we were speaking
yesterday before you, um,
basically comment that I used to have a
lot of people on Skype when I was a
child. This how [ __ ] up people are.
Yeah. Like when I was like 14, 15, and
they used to make fun out of my
relatives, my dead relatives. And now
they won't say nothing. They won't say
nothing to an adult because like when I
was like [ __ ] 14, 15, they were like
18, 17, 18 to 19. They were all Billy
big bollocks thinking they were smart.
But now, as soon as you're an adult, you
don't get nothing out of them. Yeah.
It's also like a virgin boy, right? Back
when I was like 16. Well, not 16, was 17 uh
17, right? He was always going on about
he's going to um do this and do that,
but like he would meet me, but now he
won't do nothing cuz he knows you're an adult.
Always have an adult. not
obviously I'm more intelligent than them
so they're not going to they're not
going to it's like there was this guy in
Canada called Chad right he commented on
some of the stuff that Jaden put out
he's somebody from years ago I used to
speak to when I was 14 but he won't
argue with me now
you're a [ __ ] adult he won't argue
with an adult argue with a kid but he
would argue with an adult
there people like that doesn't make any sense cuz
um and I If I messaged him a few months
ago, he would have none of it. I said,
"Listen, you Canadian [ __ ] French [ __ ] dickhead."
They don't They're only from hints.
That's what I'm saying. 14y old.
Yeah. But I think karma. Do you believe in karma?
Um, this guy used to talk about my dead
dad and [ __ ]
and then he had a baby that died in the
stomach. I think he
must have died in her stomach. We were
saying about how bullies always get what
they want. Turned out to be a bully, but
his child died. That's a karma.
So, in a way that is karma. All the [ __ ]
you used to do on Skype. All right. on kids on children.
Won't do anything now. You're going. Oh man.
Look at that. Oh [ __ ] Um yeah,
I remember they used to speak to Americans and stuff.
Yeah, I'm not sure what happened to my
dad. At least you know what happened to your mom. Um,
yeah, but at least you know what
happened to your mom.
Sorry to hear that.
But I said, I need your mom didn't
[ __ ] amuse you.
[ __ ] amuse you, man.
You [ __ ] know.
You can never stop Peter Benny.
It was spot up. Yeah.
Oh, do you want some chips? Sure. Some chips.
Some chips. Some chips. Yeah.
So, do you still do you still see your dad?
You still see your dad, bro?
Oh, I think you have told me this
before. They off.
>> Oh, wow. I feel bad.
So, did you get adopted or what?
Oh, that's sad, bro. What the [ __ ]
But you know when Virgin boy's dad dies,
I'm going to throw a party. I'm going to
throw a [ __ ] party cuz he used to
talk about my dad, which I didn't even
really even [ __ ] know who he was to be honest. Um, that's mad.
Sorry to hear that, bro.
I don't know you. You sound like you
seem like a good person. was not
uh dude in both her parents. I remember
before I had a friend in Nottingham
and u his mom died at a very age
and he still sometimes calls me and
talks about it and [ __ ] Yeah.
But yeah, when his dad dies, bro, I'm
going to throw a [ __ ] party.
I'm going to throw a [ __ ] party, bro.
He's a nasty little [ __ ] He nasty vile
mouth towards a child, but he would
never say anything to a [ __ ] man. You
know what I mean? He would never say
anything to a [ __ ] man.
[ __ ] runs through the [ __ ] boys in
[ __ ] blue. Don't need a [ __ ]
He's a nasty little [ __ ] he is.
You know [ __ ] he used to say. He's a
nasty nasty little version.
Yeah, I'm not even saying that as well.
I'm not even just saying that, bro. Yeah. Watch, bro.
He is such a little virgin. So when he
knows he can't bully a kid, he then gets
the pleased involved. You see what I
mean? Nasty, nasty little virgin. You
know, I would love to slap him up, you know.
Absolutely. Now we're talking about
this, bro. I'm actually remembering
these things. Yeah. I would love to slap
that [ __ ] up so much, bro. You You have no idea.
That's what you need. A good [ __ ] hiding.
That's what he is. A good [ __ ] old
fashioned hiding, mate. Mhm. So,
so who brought you up then? If if both
of your parents died, who bought you up?
You know, I would love to get my hands on that
come to think of it. Yeah.
So, who brought you up then if both your parents died? M
Yeah, it is [ __ ] up. That is
And it's probably even worse for you
because you lost both of your parents.
You lost both of your parents.
That's why I was so scared the other
day. I thought my mom died cuz she
wasn't uh messaging me back and [ __ ] I
thought she died. You know,
you know what I mean?
I got this whiff looking at me. Yeah.
He's a nasty [ __ ] virgin here, mate.
Horrible little virgin.
I would love to smash that under your
face, bro. You have no idea.
They're not big enough when they're
talking to an adult, though, are they?
That's what I love about them, bro.
You know what I mean? But he's a little
grass. That's what he is, Stephen. He's
a little [ __ ] grass, bro.
That's the That's the thing with a [ __ ]
He's a little grass.
He's a little [ __ ] grass and little
[ __ ] Little virgin. That's what he is.
He's nothing but a nasty little virgin.
That's what he is, bro. Yeah.
You know what I wouldn't even slap him
up. You know what I would do?
You know what I actually would do, bro?
I wouldn't even do that cuz obviously
he's a dirty little brass. I would get
up in his [ __ ] face. I'd slam my
camera in his face and say, "What you
saying now, you [ __ ] virgin? You
liter shit." That's what I need to admit.
And I'll keep hyping up and hyping up
and hyping up and hyping up because
obviously you got to be careful with
these grasses. These little dirty,
stinky little grasses. That's another
thing you got to be careful of. And I
would boy the [ __ ] off so much, bro,
that I would put it on YouTube. See,
with the prime finger,
this doesn't make sense cuz I was the
grass, you know? So, it made no sense
why he even done that. and then didn't
do anything. But this [ __ ] is a grass.
He's a certified grass. Yeah.
And yeah, you actually would get nicked,
but you would go to prison. They'd let you go.
That's what you do. Yeah. I think I
would do that, bro, if I had a chance.
I'm not even going to lie to you.
I hate that [ __ ] ugly version. You
You don't understand, bro? I hate that ugly [ __ ]
You really don't understand. I hate that
[ __ ] ugly [ __ ]
That really you don't you don't understand, bro.
That wor you might go to court, but you
go to prison. Like I said, you need to be careful
with what you do with grasses. You understand? Yeah. Oh [ __ ]
That's how you know like hungry for has
never been about that life
cuz he's talking about [ __ ] slapping
up grasses. Why would you slap up a
grass a known grass?
You understand Stephen? How that's how
you know he's never been about that life?
Cuz if you had you would know what
glasses do and exactly wine would do exactly that dirty stinky
bro. That's how you know how's never
been about that life bro. Trust me.
Never ever ever. There might be people
about [ __ ] in Liverpool, bro, but you
ain't about it.
You wouldn't be writing the [ __ ] you you
do if you was I mean I live.
Yeah. I hate that version.
But his dad will be dead soon anyways. Oh, suspicious,
man. I feel sorry for him.
He's a good [ __ ] bro.
Sorry for a pretty good [ __ ] Little virgin. It's off. Yes.
What do you think the triple H?
What do you think it should rate? Steen Howard
going to die like you're going to die.
Ste, who do you think's going to die a virgin, bro? [ __ ] one. Mhm.
That's it. No more.
No more [ __ ]
takeaways tomorrow. But I need to save
some money now.
I believe I was getting three grand a month.
Oh, Grezy. Three of the month I was getting, mate.
But the plan is Grezy. Save some of what
I've got left.
for like a month, another stop, be able
to to work maybe for two months. Just
lucky I have some [ __ ] savings in it.
I'm tired now, bro.
I want to [ __ ] that USA again, bro.
I want to touch her again, bro. 8 22.
I want to touch over.
What do you think's about that?
Is that okay with you, boss? I've
said I want to touch USA again. Welcome, bro.
No, but I need the I need the boobies. Greasy,
I'm going to play some Franklin in a bit.
I like Franklin. He's quite cute.
Greasy loves King. I don't know why
Grevy loves King. Grievy loves King, you know.
Grezy is obsessed with King It.
He's a cute little whiff.
That's Quezy. He's got no goals. He
won't even go Scotland.
Wait, so you're 27? Yeah. When's your
birthday again, Greavvesy? Not not the
exact date, but I'm 1997 October. So
what? What about you?
Well, it's Kingston. We call him
I'm October, so I'm guessing you're
older than me. Bless you.
Wait, you're older than me.
See, you're born in Yeah.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
And you haven't even been anywhere.
Bless you, Reevesy. You in your little ways.
You in your little nonoptimistic ways. Bless you.
I'm never going back to Scotland, bro. [ __ ] that.
Got no reason to.
You're obsessed with Scotland, you
obsessed with Scotland. I [ __ ] went
on like 24.
You like the Kilts? Yeah. [ __ ]
Bless you in life then.
Yeah, I remember Tom. He had a picture
on his WhatsApp of him wearing a kilt on
his graduate on his graduation.
Yeah, Tom was wearing a kilt in the graduation.
Tom's my dada BZY remember
he said I think you should talk some
things through with a psychiatrist a
psychologist he said
psychiatrist he said actually
he said I think you should talk some
things through he said gy
he said in good faith
he was a pretty good [ __ ] he doing that. Yeah.
No, but he was actually being weird,
though. He was actually being weird.
I'm not even joking, bro. He actually
was being weird.
I tell you how it started. Yeah. We was talking about like uh
I tell you what we was talking about
like they said they were from Glasgow.
Yeah. I said, "Oh, I've been to
Edinburgh." He said he went to
um he said he went to um
[ __ ] where was it? He said he went to
Ed uh uni in Edinburgh
or whatever was talking and then I said,
"Watch out here, lads. I'm going to do
this approach." cuz obviously they were
both taken. And then I think she said
she had a boyfriend. I remember m
they've always got bloody boyfriends but
they're never with them and [ __ ] And
his friend never said nothing but he did.
But I mean again I just feel like I'm
not in denial.
I don't feel like it's even a case for
needing help or not needing help. I just You understand?
Yeah. Just go to Scotland, Greezy. You
got nothing to lose. Why don't you just go there?
I hate having to sit around and wait
around for money, bro. I want to be
earning, man. [ __ ] hell, man. We
can't all be lazy like you, Grezy.
Just lazy, you know?
[ __ ] lazy, can't you? It's just lazy,
though, is it?
No, a lazy bastard.
Oh, look at Stitch. You love Stitch.
Oh, yeah. King woke me up in the morning
and he started licking my legs.
He started licking my legs, bro. What the [ __ ] Yeah.
Don't you get like a buzz off money,
Grezy? Like when I used to get the Uber
money and the rent and [ __ ] I used to
get like a buzz of getting money. It
used to give me like it used to motivate
me getting paid every Wednesday or
getting some of the rent money. Now I
don't have I don't have anything coming
in. So I'm just sort of sat, you know?
Anything you're spending, you're just spending now.
Oh, are you not asky?
Cuz I'm used to like frequent payments,
you know? So now I'm like just
just not. So don't know.
What do you think? Easy.
You don't care about money, do you?
Loads of things to spend it on.
Traveling, drinking, escorts.
There's loads of things to
to spend it on. See, I just like going
drinking with you. I like I just like
the people that I met on Thursday, you know.
I think they were cool. Um I think they
were cool guys, you know.
No, I just needed a drink the other day,
bro, cuz of stress.
I like the escort though, man. You can't
You'll never regret on your deathbed,
Grizzly, how many [ __ ] you got and
how much sex you had and how many boobs
you felt and stuff.
You'll never regret that on your deathbed. Yeah. Never. No.
Would you ever get with an escort greasy?
That's what happens when you're addicted
to [ __ ] isn't it?
Yeah, that's what happens when you're
addicted to jobs. Yeah.
[ __ ] hell, man.
I think me and you should meet up
grievously have a party.
But Grezy, you'd like it down here, son.
You'll never have to grow up.
But you'll like it that Grezy,
you like it down here, son. You'll never
have to grow up.
You like it down south, son. You never
have to grow up. One sec.
>> Have you ever been to Birmingham,
Greavvesy? Have you ever been to Birmingham, bro?
You've not been to Birmingham, have you?
I ain't been burning him in years, man.
Yeah. the same repeating people in it. I
said to Monty, man, why don't you come
on? I said to him, why don't you why I
said to him, "Why don't you come on
here?" He said, "It's the same repeating people."
Yeah. He said it's the same with PMV. No.
No. I think he's done with YouTube now.
I need to be done to be honest with you.
Community ruins lives, bro. What's Earth.
I don't take it personal because your
pro because your opinion doesn't mean anything.
I think my problem is women is there's
too many stuck [ __ ] in this country.
That's what I think my problem is.
No, that's the problem. Too many stuck
up [ __ ] in this country. We knew the
problem years ago.
They're [ __ ] all NPCs.
They're literally all stuck up in this
in this country, bro.
They're [ __ ] stuck up.
The one yesterday didn't seem stuck up.
They seemed all right, but no. Most of
them are stuck up in this country. Just
like Canada, just like Italy, just like [ __ ] America. Nah.
Like I said, I I only went out because I was bored.
If I could do Uber again, I would have
been doing that.
Yeah, it's just the same old [ __ ] bro.
You watch Hey, bro. Greasy. Yeah. You
know, you watch this black guy, bro.
uh do these approaches and it's always
the same scenario with different women.
I'm sorry. I have a boyfriend.
Oh my god. I'm just I'm I was just
watching it now, bro.
It's like they're they're all NPCs.
Grezy, how can you say they're not NPCs?
Nah, ugly birds all have boyfriends.
Bro, I don't even know why I'm
explaining this [ __ ] You've seen my
approaching videos. You've seen how
impossible it is. I don't even know why
I'm even having this conversation.
Oh my god, bro. What the [ __ ]
This is why I don't like watching these
things, bro. It's annoying. Even when
it's not happening to me, it's just the same old.
It's [ __ ] boring, bro. They're literally NPCs.
[ __ ] non-playing characters.
Same scenario with different women.
So, we have a boyfriend. What the [ __ ] bro?
No, they've all got boyfriends. And I
don't go for sevens and eights cuz
there's hardly are seven and eights in this country.
No, I don't think it's funny. Me. I
think it's annoying, bro.
We usually think it's funny, but I don't.
I hate that boyfriend [ __ ] bro. It's so
boring. This is why I had to stop
watching this black guy, bro.
It's annoying, bro.
Even when it's not happening to you,
it's so annoying.
[ __ ] boring, bro. [ __ ] boring.
Ah, it's boring, bro.
Shut it over. Boyfriend. Ah, boyfriend.
You remember the pub yesterday, Grezy?
It was packed out, wasn't it?
Everyone was looking at me, bro.
They all friends. I'll never forget the
way Adman said that.
Oh, bless you. Yeah,
it's pretty depressing, eh? Watching
that guy's videos. I hate it, bro. I hate it.
Why Steven Howard? I'm watching this
black guy do approaches and he keeps
getting the same. I've got a boyfriend.
I hate it, bro.
I hate it. It's annoying.
They've all got they've all got boyfriends.
I hate it, Gy. It's annoying, bro.
Everybody was shouting in the pub yesterday. Boyfriend.
They were all boyfriends. Squeezy.
I think they're all NPCs.
I'm playing characters. Yeah,
I'm in my little nesticles.
Do you ever play with your little Willy Wonka, Greasy?
Sometimes I think of USA is he and play
with my little wonky my little wonker.
I was saying to my mom on the phone
about like I wish I could be a porn
star. She said PJ too much information.
I said but ma I don't have a daddy. I've
only got a mama. So you have to be my
mom and my dad. So you have to have
conversations like this.
We have to have conversations like this.
And I said I was going to tell her about
the vintage p and that
I like vintage p
only vintage. I don't like watch I can't
watch Johnny Sins. It's too fake for me.
It has to be vintage, you know.
What do you think of when you when when
you do it, Grey? I'd just think of so
many different things, but normally it's
people that I've been with in the past.
Sometimes Sig, sometimes USA Izzy,
sometimes [ __ ] in the alleyway. I don't know. Yeah, same.
Sometimes I think of when USA Izzy come
on to me
and she started touching me and stuff. Yeah.
Oh, so you think of USA as well.
Yeah, I think of her boobs. Gre uh Grezy
her little voice.
I really want you,
but I don't think you want me.
I do, but everyone's looking.
She was finally happy when she had Peter
Belly's hecker in her mouth. Is it groovesy?
She gave me a [ __ ] in the alleyway.
What the [ __ ] Grezy?
That's crazy, isn't it?
It felt quite good. music.
That was mad time as well.
Thank you, C. One second.
But yeah, apply for the delivery jobs
anyways, Grevy. You should get accepted
quickly because you live in a in a less
busy area, bro.
Don't be a lazy [ __ ]
You're better than that, mate. You're
better than that.
Want to be that [ __ ]
[ __ ] virgin boy.
What a sight. Hey, Nicolo. Yeah.
Sometimes when I do, I think of USA
Izzy. When I when I have a little tug,
I think of her boobies.
How cute is that?
Oh, this woman said she wants to meet
me. I think I think we got a date here, bro.
She said, "Yeah, sure." She wants to
meet and that. I was speaking to her
yesterday. I was supposed to go to Fabrics.
Yeah, I think this one might actually
meet, bro. I think this one will mate.
I don't think I'll be able to save money. Oh, [ __ ]
But that's still bad though. out of five
numbers, you should have got more than
one reply to be honest.
Yeah, we've been talking all day, but I
should have You should have got more
replies than that to be honest with you.
That's really bad, bro.
This is how it should be, bro. People
replying back, people agreeing to meet
you. It should be this easy.
Nope, she's not fat at all.
Cuz I was going to go fabrics cuz she
went for a rave, but I didn't want to
pay the money in it. So,
she seemed all right when I met her as
well. But we'll see.
I think she's 21, but yeah.
a potential candidate. Yeah.
Remember there was one yesterday she was
wearing glasses. She was like a five out
of 10. Yeah. Her boobs are so big.
But she was just [ __ ] me around. So
she turns me on because of the little accent.
Yeah. But I do hate her though. She's a
[ __ ] Hate that [ __ ]
Yeah, I think she actually will meet
this one to be fair
cuz I was actually speaking to her
yesterday as well.
>> Yeah, man.
See, the thing is, Nicola, I was trying
to meet as many people as I possibly
could before I run out of money.
Yeah, that guy
He had a girl with glasses, bro. And he
was like a he was a decent looking guy.
He was speaking on a train and
everything like he he was sound and was
just talking. He said, "Oh, you" He
said, "So, what are you going to do,
mate?" He said, he said, "You need to
leave this country." Yeah. Mr. K and everything. Yeah.
But that just makes me feel better that
even the people that are in
relationships, they're not even with good-looking women.
There was American guy I start speaking
to him. He was with his girlfriend.
She wasn't even that good looking. But yeah.
Are you sure Tom's my dada?
So who's my mommy?
Yeah, this girl is sexy.
This one I'm meeting is sexy. But the
one that he's with has got glasses on.
That's strange, isn't it?
I just want to go back to earning money again.
No, she wasn't ugly ugly. She She was
just like she wouldn't have been good
enough for me. But that just goes to
show like you're not the only one
struggling, bro. Like even when you I've
seen some guys, right, with some
absolutely ugly women,
like really bad. and he just goes to
show you all you need to know.
I tell you a story. Yeah.
I have a friend, right? I think he's 31
and he always used to go gym, good job, everything,
right? Good job.
Um, and he always used to moan about
women not being interested in that. And
he had a good job, went to the gym, no
addictions, just earning good money, was
smart with his money. He ended up having
a child with a really fat ugly woman and
he used to go gym and everything.
Six-pack. Yeah. And then he ends up with
a fat woman.
See, I've never been with anyone bad really.
Not really really.
I mean, USA wasn't that bad.
I don't know where to take this woman.
She says, "Where should we go?" Uh, maybe
I've never been on a date in Liverpool
Street before, but yeah, Grey, a lot of
guys have had to actually lower their standards.
See, that 19year-old, she was
good-looking. There was nothing wrong with her. Yeah.
Yeah. I could have a date next week. We
think I might do Liverpool Street. You
know, I've never been on a date.
Liverpool Street, I think.
going to tell her about USA. Is he?
That's bad. One [ __ ] reply. And
did you believe that I'd done the
[ __ ] that I'd done the approach of
sober, Greavvesy? Yeah, I can do him sober.
Of course I can, bro. The [ __ ] How many
videos have I done?
This could be a potential.
But yeah, he with a 50-y old woman as well.
But yeah, like there's people that have
it worse than
like I said, it's like what Antman said,
there's people that go gym, six-packs,
everything. and and you should see some
of the women they're with.
So like trust me, there's people that
are better than me, mate, and they can't
even get anyone.
The only good thing about USA is it was
her boobies, and it
was her boobies.
She had big brown boobies. Nicolo
I remember squeezing them and that
squeezing them with my little hands. Nicolola. Yeah,
she likes a bit of bunk bad touch.
There were motherly kisses.
Sig is not your mama. I remember
grieving. Sign not Peter Belly's mama. [Music]
Sig not Peter Belly's mama.
Yeah. Nicolo Antman said unless you're
like a famous YouTuber or a big Tik
Tocker, they're not interested.
Is he right? Um Nicolo,
unless you're a big YouTuber or
he said they're not they're not interested. Yeah. Yeah,
Nicola. Imagine me and USA Izzy in the pictures together.
She told me, "Message me when you get back home."
And I messaged her. Then she she said
she had a great night, but then she
blocked me, Nicolo.
She said, "Let me know you get home safe."
I said, "You too, mama."
I said, "Get back to America safe."
Now I'll never know.
I wonder what would happen if I actually
stayed. Now I'll never know.
Now I'll never know. Greasy.
She seems all right. This one that I'm
messaging. She seems very laidback and um
I don't know, chill. She doesn't give
off any stuck up vibes or anything.
I tell you what, Liverpool Street is the
worst for stuck up women. Oh, mate.
Yeah, it's really bad. It's really bad them sides.
Yeah, even even worse than like
Leicester Square, Liverpool Street is bad.
It's bad for it, bro. Trust me.
Full of stuck up people, stuck up women,
hippies and that.
Now I'll never know.
Why the [ __ ] do you want me to message
you and [ __ ] if you was just going to
block me, mama?
Yeah. And it made me depressed, bro. It
got me on the drink.
Yeah, it got me on the drink. [ __ ]
depressing it is. And there's me
thinking I could do two weeks in a row
now, mate. It's depressing. Cuz when
you're drunk, yeah, you just don't care.
You're just drinking anyways. You're
having fun anyways. But when you're
sober, you have time to think about how
[ __ ] up it is.
Especially when you're not ugly as well. So, yeah.
Why do you think I was scared to do
sober approaches? I've done them before, bro.
Bro, I deserve it. I went out on
Thursday and I went out on Saturday. I
deserve to get a date, bro. I [ __ ] Do
you know how many approaches I done in
them two days? [ __ ] this. Yeah,
she was calling me stupid. I didn't hear
her say it.
No, I didn't see her. I don't watch that virgin.
He is so stupid, bro. He can get me
banned from as many places as he wants
and I'll still have more women in him.
Why do I want to block a number? I think
I might have found a new number. Oh, [ __ ]
I met some seat guys yesterday, Nicolo, from Nottingham.
They're really cool guys. So I said,
"I've been nutting in ages, man."
They really had a They really sounded
like that. That's how they sound in Nottingham.
They sound a bit like Derby,
like a bit like Robin Hood.
That's how they sound like.
And in the black country, they they talk
they talk a bit like dish in Birmingham.
That's how they sound.
No, they're right, bro.
They sounded like shake the tree.
A bless you. Yeah,
I found the name.
The name mama.
No one bs it up. She's my mama.
Look at her.
Look at my mommy.
It's a shame she's not as beautiful like
in real life. She's not as beautiful in
real life as she is there. My mama.
I was telling the Americans about her yesterday.
Yeah. I was telling my some Americans,
an American couple.
Sometimes I still tell them about my mama
and this is what I was wearing. Look
on the same day.
Virgin boy can't look like that.
Virgin boy can't look like that. [ __ ]
him. Now I just wear caps. Look how
young I was there. Nicolo
got my eyebrows done, my hair done. For
what? For what?
Exactly. Just for it to be the same as our ways. Yeah.
Yeah. They kept taking me there. Why did
the the Uber keep taking me there?
Why did the Uber keep taking me there, bro?
That boyfriend shove it up. Yeah,
boys got such a problem if people live
with their mom.
Must be some sort of trauma. Must be
some sort of past trauma.
That must be some sort of past trauma, Nicolo.
Yeah, that must be some sort of past trauma.
I had some delicious pork today. Cooked for me.
He doesn't like anyone else having a mama.
He is so boring, bro. Like you know that
whole you live with your mom. He is so
That is so boring. He goes,
he goes on. The thing is, bro, is that
No one else says it but him.
No one else says it but that virgin.
It's probably from past trauma with his
mom. It's like he doesn't like anyone
else having a mama.
Why does he care who if you live with
your bum or you live by yourself? I don't understand.
He's literally never worked a day in his
life ever. Like not even a day. Like
you've seen that I've worked.
Why does he do that, bro? It's weird.
She was supposed to meet me yesterday.
She was supposed to meet me today and
then she turned into an ignorer.
Yep. You're supposed to meet me today as well. virgin boy.
No, if she wants to meet me, I will meet her. Obviously,
if not then
he doesn't [ __ ] work. If he worked,
he wouldn't be skimp
[ __ ] work. He's what on benefits?
No, she will me. I reckon she will me.
This one will
I'm trying to think where I could take her. Uh,
he doesn't work. He's never worked. Why
do you think he's always skin virgin? Yeah, bro.
Yeah, but he he got kicked out of
college because people uh No, he didn't
get kicked out of college. He stopped
going to college because people used to
think he was gay.
That's why he started the whole She Cole thing.
Because uh people started to think he was gay.
That's why he started the whole I don't
wear pink. I don't wear pink. Oh, I like
Shel Cove because it was he didn't want
people to think he was gay. All [Music]
right, now she's typing.
[ __ ] hell, that shovel cult thing is so copying
Why do you always take the piss out of
me, Nicolola? You always mock me.
I said, "Why don't you want to meet?"
That was the one I was supposed to meet me today.
Why did the pigs there?
She said, "I'd rather get to know
somebody before I meet them." And I'm
going to reply back, "Well, you get to
know somebody by meeting them."
Oh, yeah. I'm waiting for the call from
them police by the way as well. I want
to tell them about themsel, bro, when I
go back to when I go to the police station.
This is someone else from the other day.
Not the person I met yesterday. And I'm
not going to reply anymore cuz she just wants attention.
Yeah, cuz she just wants attention. So
I'm not going to give her attention.
That's what they want, you see.
But yeah, them pigs do play two sides of a coin.
They do play two sides of a coin. Definitely.
Yeah. And and then they're like, "Oh,
you're not playing two sides of a coin."
I said, "Well, you literally are."
Yeah. You're telling me one thing, then
you're telling me another one. Make it make sense.
When you write negative things, they're
forced enough to reply to that though,
aren't they, Nicolo?
Yeah, they do pay two sides of a coin. Definitely.
They do pay two sides of a coin.
Yeah. Anyways, I'm not replying back to
this one, bro, from the other day on
Thursday because I'm not giving them attention.
Why do you say it won't change, Nicolo?
Joe said that your past don't dictate your future.
No, it doesn't change.
These people are dumb. But
No, honestly, bro, the reason I done
this whole thing is because I had
nothing better to do, bro.
That really is the reason why I went
out, cuz there was just nothing else to do.
Why is this Indonesian guy asking me to
go out when I've specifically told him
I'm trying to save money?
Is this I feel like this guy is actually
taking the piss sometimes.
I generally feel like this guy is
actually taking the piss.
It's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
That's what I used to have to tell people, bro.
That's what I had to tell people. Yeah. Yeah,
he's he's so scared to approach, bro.
He's so scared.
Why does he even go out? I don't understand. Like,
why does he actually go out if he's
scared to approach? [Music]
I won't be going out wasting money
unless a woman wants to meet me. Then
I ain't I'm I can't spend I can't waste
any money anymore, bro.
I used to like I'm going to miss the
[ __ ] from the escorts, bro. They're nice.
I used to like choking them with my willie. Yeah.
Yeah, it was fun.
They just ain't interested. Oh [ __ ]
So why do you say that it will never
change, Nicolo, when Joe says that your
past don't dictate your future?
But he told me that your pastor don't
dictate your future, Nicolo.
Yeah, it does with women. It does with women. Definitely.
Your past does dictate your future. Once
you've met one, you've met them all. Really?
Once you meet one woman, you've
basically met all of them.
Why do you think so many of them pretend
they got boyfriends in the same way to
so many different people? Because
they're all the same. They're all
brainwashed by Tik Tok. They're all
brainwashed by Instagram.
It's like you're not even speaking to
them. You're speaking to
a [ __ ] robot, bro. You're talking to
a robot. You're not even speaking to a [ __ ]
You're not even talking to a person. Yeah.
And man said, "The only place you're not
going to get I've got a boyfriend is Asia."
That's what he said.
He said, "That's the only place you're
not going to get it.
Yeah, pretty much.
Like, bro, honestly, if I was working
now, I wouldn't even be going out. Like
I said, I only went out cuz I had
nothing else to do.
Then I just acknowledge how [ __ ] up it
is again in this country.
Yeah. you would have had many wives, many girlfriends,
cuz it doesn't all of a sudden change.
That's the thing. It doesn't all of a
sudden just change like that. You know
what I mean?
No, you're not damned if you if you do.
Damned if you don't. Cuz I I I only went
out cuz I had nothing better to do.
Otherwise, I wouldn't I I'd probably go
out like every month, Maybe. Yep. Yeah, man.
Your time will come. Nicolai,
you take you just take the piss out of me.
Yeah, I know. It's It is. It is. [Music]
But yet you used to go casino and win thousands.
That's how you know this is [ __ ] up, bro.
Think of all the times when you used to
go casino, you'd win thousands and
thousands and thousands. But your metro
status never changed in any of them years.
Yeah, it's m
your muscle st
guy from America called Andy. Yeah, I
met him on Tinder and he started being
an ignor. And I messaged him the other
day. I said, "Andy, Pandy, you're still
being an ignorer."
I called him and then he uh he
uh he brought me Andy Pandy Yeah.
I wanted to go to Belfast and beat um LJ
up Nicolola. I think it would make good
content in it. Become the new king.
Like take over it. Like, wouldn't that
be such a good video just to go over
there and just take over the city?
Just completely take over.
That's what you call a lovely site, is it?
Just take over.
The package side goes back to ignoring again.
Yeah, he's a copycat. He's just like Virgin boy.
just like [ __ ] virgin boy. You [ __ ] virgin.
You're a [ __ ] virgin.
You can virgin.
Yeah. Why is he copying me, bro?
with them friends trolling women. Nicolola.
Oh, I've also started to uh
noticed that the Indians have started
saying they got boyfriends now as well.
I felt like really hurting someone
yesterday, bro. Like really felt like
I really felt like hurting someone yesterday, bro.
I'm not even lying, bro.
It's not even funny.
No, they No, they don't usually.
They say no or they never say they have
a boyfriend. That's how you know they
don't have boyfriends. Because most of
the time if you approach like um a
Muslim or a French or a Ukrainian even,
they never say they have boyfriends
ever. Like it's the same with Ukrainians. Um
who else? Brazilians.
That's how you also know they don't have boyfriends.
Ukrainian, you never get it. the
Pakistan, you never get it.
Um, there there's a few people that they
will never say they have one. Moroccan,
they will never say they have boyfriends.
That's how you know they don't have boyfriends.
Because you'll notice that none of these
women will ever say they have
boyfriends. So, if that's the truth,
right, why is it Ukrainians never say
it? Muslims never say it.
So that's how you know all of these
women that say they got boyfriends is
full of [ __ ]
cuz they they don't say it.
I don't think a French person has ever said it.
Don't think so. No.
They just troll you. They just play the
long game with you then [ __ ] you over. Uh
the French what they will do mate is
they'll give you their number and [ __ ] with you.
But it's so funny you can't even get mad at it.
They're [ __ ] trolling bastards.
You remember the one with the little
dress? Nicolo, I wanted to dress up for you.
Yeah, she was a [ __ ] proper troll, bro.
Yeah, you can't even get a combo.
But Joe wants us to believe that one day
we'll wake up and everything's perfect.
Everything's hunky dory. Nah.
Yeah. Ukrainian women never say it. They
never say they have a boyfriend. If you
if you if you even Asian people, like
even Chinese people, they never say it, bro.
Ukrainian women never say it. Maybe it's
against their culture to lie, but no.
No, you never you never get it from them.
I wonder why.
Who do you reckon the worst women are? I
think the worst women are are Indian
heritage British women. They are the
most stuck up you ever will come across.
They are the worst.
Like the brown skin westernized ones. Yeah.
>> Yeah. That's why I don't understand. I
don't understand with Australians is
that they always sit they'll always
speak to you. Um,
they'll always speak to you. They're
never rude, but then then they say they
got boyfriends. It's strange. It is very weird.
That's why I don't understand about them.
What makes me laugh is when they say
they're here for 3 months, right? But
then they've got a boyfriend back at
home. That's what makes me laugh. When Nah,
doesn't make sense.
But yeah, Ukrainian women never say they have boyfriends. Never.
If you notice, right,
you can actually generalize a nationality
cuz they're all the same. Like if you go
from like French people, they'll give
you their number, troll you. English,
pretend they got boyfriends. Ukrainian
women will just say no, but they will
never say they have a boyfriend. If you
go through every single nationality,
then you realize that all women are
actually the same depending on like what
where they're actually from.
That's how you know they're all the same.
Who else say they have boyfriends?
Muslim people don't usually say it, bro.
I'm trying to think.
But the worst for it is Americans, I
think, and uh English.
But they don't have boyfriends.
Trust me, boy. There's loads of
feminists out there that hate men. They
don't need men. They have their own [ __ ]
going on. Like basically what I was like
when I was at Uber, but you you expect
us to believe that they've all got
boyfriends. Someone said, "Oh, there's
millions of people in relationships."
But here's the thing, Nicolo. Most of
the men I know are single.
Most of the men that I know, one in
about four has a has a has a girlfriend
and they're all different. They're not
connected to each other from different
places. That doesn't make sense, does it?
If you actually think of it, actually
most men are actually single
and there's a lot of women that are
single as well. So
about one in four probably is in a relationship.
So that statistic don't make sense.
How many numbers? Oh, don't depress me.
Don't [ __ ] depress me, mate. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, I'm waving my white flag. You know
what that means? Greavvesy.
You remember when I was crying on the
train over USA? Is he Nicolo?
And uh Oh, I sent it to everyone.
How do you know what that means? Grezy,
I'm waving my white flag.
[ __ ] This isn't it.
I'm waving my white flag. Yeah.
Oh my gosh.
Why do you like that little voice that I do? Greasy.
Got that little voice. Yeah. Uh,
no. I'm not looking for a date. I surrender.
I want to know you, mate.
Do you think if this was the 1980s
I'd have problems with women, Greavesy?
I don't think so. Do you?
I don't think so. Do you? Nah.
I'm just looking at some I'm looking at
some Simpson stuff.
No wonder you've got anxiety, Greavves,
lad, after what you've been through in
your little life. Bless you.
Bless you, mate. Bless you.
Well, me, Laney, and King's always here for you.
If you ever if you ever wanted to visit,
we're here for you, matey.
I don't have anxiety. Me, bro. I don't
think I do.
I ain't got anxiety, matey. [Music]
It felt so nice when USA was kissing me.
It's so nice to be hugged and loved. No
wonder you felt bloody abandoned, Grievously.
for somebody to come on you, come on to
you in that way, right? And then just abandon you
and your mommy just abandoned you. Imagine that.
No one knows I [ __ ] up.
You know what I mean?
Do you like several cold grievy?
You like shower coy?
You're [ __ ] gay, mate. Gay. Gay.
Everybody, Greavves is gay. Greavves is
gay. Greavves is gay. Hey, Greavves is
Greavves is gay. Everyone.
Yeah, that's cuz you're homosexual,
mate. You don't like Cheryl Cole.
[ __ ] gay, mate. [ __ ] gay.
You're gay, mate. You need to get your
sexuality checked out.
How can you look like Shel Cole, man?
She's so hot.
You can't deny her attractiveness.
You don't like women, Grezy.
You're gay, mate.
You can't deny that she's attractive.
Nah, you're okay, mate.
You can't deny she's attractive, Grezy, can you
I want a massage.
I told the girl telling that I loved her, Grezy.
I said, "I want you to come and rub my
feet. I had a long day at work.
Oh, here's a card. She's French. D.
That's weird. Why do these French women
never have boyfriends?
That's just how you know women don't
have boyfriends. Most of them.
That's how you know it, is it?
Cuz don't you think it's a bit funny,
Grey, how none of these Ukrainian women
claim they got boyfriends. Most of these
Muslim women, these French women never
claim they got boyfriends. But as soon
as you speak to a British woman,
apparently they got a boyfriend.
[ __ ] off, mate.
I [ __ ] boy.
Oh, I found a stadium. that Huh?
She don't want to know.
I don't have a type.
You still there? Gy. Nope.
I like USA. Is he? Oh.
I like USA Izzy Grezy.
Yeah, I'm in my little nestles, too.
I want to stroke her little hair again.
We're supposed to get matching tattoos. Matching tattoos.
God bless you. Where is this?
That's the cause of your bed.
Bless your baby Peter.
Gy thinks I've got uh agrophobia. Don't be silly.
I don't have that matey. That's that guy
from Birmingham. Do you remember a
Birmingham? He's the one that had it.
Yeah, I like cuddles.
I like to be hugged.
Got to be hugged. Yep.
bit sleepy. I am. You know what I mean?
You should do Greasy. We should move to Birmingham
and live like a block of flaps.
You and you. Eh. [Music]
What do you think?
Me, you and King Greezy.
Can't believe you lost both your
parents. That's [ __ ] sad, bro.
You seem like a pretty good [ __ ] Greavesy.
I think we'll get on just fine. No, Greavesy.
Why don't you want to live for being king? Huh? Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, I almost shot myself the other
day. I don't know, bro. If it wasn't for
that cafe being open at 6:00 in the
morning, I would have had to gave in. Steven Howard.
Yeah, I almost shot myself, bro.
Oh, I thought you didn't care about women, Greavvesy.
All I can say is I uh
hope you had better luck than me.
You're not going to get a bird, bro.
Hopefully you Well, hopefully you do.
But if you if if it's anything like how
I had it,
good luck to you, mate.
Why do you want a bird? You don't want any babies.
Do you believe me, Greavvesy, when I
tell you that I do these approaches? Do
you believe me?
I do do them, Greavvesy.
Yeah, you used to like the ones live,
didn't you, Greasy?
I've done so many, bro.
hit that one.
See that one? Yeah.
You're sick and twisted [ __ ] Do
you remember that Grezy USA is your sick
and twisted [ __ ]
You've been stalking me for 2 years.
It's always the stalking card, isn't it?
With you [ __ ]
Always the stalking card when someone
stands up to array Grimsy.
You wanted to be a [ __ ] So I I was a
[ __ ] You know, Greavves had similar
experiences as well.
Where are you at?
You like pork, don't you? Greasy.
You're such a pork lover, Grezy. Oh, [ __ ]
You're such a pork lovery. Oh [ __ ]
Imagine USA Izzy was next to me now. She
take up all the room.
She would take up all the room. Yeah. Yeah,
good exchange, you know, steak and sex.
£40 was is cheaper than an escort.
I miss them steakhouse times. Sometimes
I lie in bed grooves and I'll just reminisce.
Just reminisce, you know.
Oh, I used to like them little steak mills.
Grezy, bless you.
You miss them little times. Groovsy,
bless you in life, Grooy.
I didn't even know you was older than me.
I'm 28 in October.
Grey, would you say that I've got more
life experience than you?
What do you mean? King will bring up a present.
But Grezy, would you say that I've got
more life experience than you?
You must be born in 98 like me though.
97. I'm born in 97. Uh yeah,
thank you [ __ ]
I've got more life experience than you though.
You can't deny that. Yeah.
Grezy. I think Grezy lives in Cheshure.
I think Grey lives in Chesure.
Yeah, that's where you live. You live in Chester, Grimsy.
You live in Chester, Grimy.
That's where you live.
>> I can't believe that Prime set me up,
man. Why would he do that? It's so
silly. He spoke to me for a whole year
to set me up
all over YouTube.
You know, if you actually think about
that, that is actually sad.
That is actually mad, bro.
Like that took some consistency as well.
Speaking on some speaking to somebody on
Snapchat for a whole year. Yeah.
Just to get a little video. It's mad,
ain't it? But
that is actually sad if you think about it.
This is mad. Like if I caught Virgin Boy,
he'd be saying more than [ __ ] sorry,
mate. Let me [ __ ] tell you that.
Trust me, mate. That's so mad, bro. That
took some [ __ ]
talking for a year and everything. He's
a sad bastard that prime. He really is sad.
I was even prepared for it, bro. I swear to God.
But it doesn't matter. That's sad, bro.
He's a Yeah.
Imagine me and USA as you had a baby.
Steven Howard. Would the baby be cute? Yeah.
be a cute bubba keep.
Maybe, maybe not. Bro, I don't want to
pay 1.7K for it.
I don't want to pay 1.7K for it. So,
probably really not.
Are you getting it?
I can't afford that, mate, on a phone. Not 1.7K.
I can't afford that. That's ridiculous.
They've always been expensive, bro. The
phones have always been that price
and I don't think I can get on contract
either. So, yeah, I just won't get it. I
can't pay that. But that's ridiculous.
Just like a holiday to America.
Yeah, they've always been expensive. So yeah, let's see.
Are you getting it, Daz?
I can't. I think it's like 1.8 1.9 actually.
I couldn't justify it, bro. I couldn't justify it.
I [ __ ] play. I ain't pay that.
Oh, [ __ ] man.
Guys, come and give me some cuddles.
Guys, come and give me a hug, man. Oh,
rest my little legs.
I won't be on YouTube tomorrow.
I'm off for a little bit.
I shouldn't even be on here when I'm
here to be honest.
uh really I don't want to
it's not my house and
I don't know I just want to respect
people's wishes sort of thing
like so yeah I won't be on there but I
don't want to be on there to be honest
so it's a good thing so Yeah.
No, no. 5:00 p.m.
should even be on there. This whole
YouTube has caused so much problems
in this household and [ __ ] and someone
let you stay, bro. You shouldn't even be on here.
Yeah, you might see me once in a few
weeks, bro. But
if I wasn't here, I'd be homeless.
But I mean,
why am I going to be on here, bro, after
all the [ __ ] that's happened?
No, I won't be on there tomorrow, bro.
Graves, I think you like USA Izzy, don't
you? I think you you fancy her.
When she was in London, she was mine.
She was all mine.
She was mine. My mama.
No one else's. And it looks
she was mama easy.
probably living his best life.
Yeah, he's probably living his best life, mate.
I don't get any vitamins either. Yeah. Oh, I'm sleeping.
She had some big boobs, man.
Do you reckon it was fat Greavesy or Nah?
I was squeezing them on the couch.
It was fun, man. It was really fun
with her little Calvin Klein bra.
Bless her then if she's using her little
body to get food and weed. Bless her.
Oh, bless her then. Greasy.
They all know about me. I just think
it's mad. Gregy, how the whole family
knows about me.
Grievy how the whole family knows all
about me. Guys,
this is hilarious, bro.
Her dad. Do you remember her dad, Scott?
That's [ __ ] mad. Looking back on it,
you can see how mad that is.
Yeah. Never [ __ ] ever forget me, you nasty bastard.
My dad said he was going to arrest me in it. No.
Grezy likes when I go live in the pub,
don't he? Cuz he knows I go mental.
Bless Greasy then. If he if he grew up
with no parents,
bless him. Bless him in life.
[ __ ] hell, man. That's crazy.
Cle, you've been watching Inet recently.
You used to love that
groovy. How come you don't go on Lord J's channel?
Was sure say Izzy was here so I could hold her.
Is that normal goose you wanting to hold her?
I feel special that you come on my channel Grezy.
I feel special. Yeah, same.
Anyways, I need to go sleep now. I'm
[ __ ] tired, right? So, catch your