I'm back. Sorry about that. Yeah, Yeah, man.
[ __ ] I don't think I'm going to bother
Thursday, man. It's too depressing. I
didn't realize I had eight [ __ ]
numbers, bro. What the [ __ ]
I didn't even count them, to be honest.
No, [ __ ] that.
No, I can't be bothered, man. Jeez,
that is really bad. [Music]
Yeah, it's [ __ ] depressing this life,
bro. [ __ ] hell.
Tomorrow I wake up at like 11.
Yeah, it's really really bad.
Yeah, I don't think I go out on
Thursday, bro. I could afford it. I was
going to go, but there's no point. It's
just the same old, you know.
Same old B in this country. I hold it.
high volume women. All women are the
[ __ ] same everywhere
cuz we didn't go there. But we we left
the country, bro. The [ __ ]
I notic that in life. Yeah. You go you
go backwards. You don't go forwards.
You go backwards. You don't go forwards.
And there are four out of 10 as well.
Oh, [ __ ] fed up. I am
fed up and bored.
Jesus. Twidden in our thumbs. Another
week. Twidden in our thumbs. No date.
But the past don't dictate the future.
Your past don't dictate your future.
So they say, huh? No replies. depressing.
I need a new life. That's what I need.
[ __ ] ain't numbers, bro.
I'm McDonald's. Grey,
I'm not going to do it though. We're not
all a fat [ __ ] like you, matey.
This life is Got it.
You're going to get hurt, bro. I'm going
to come to Newcastle and beat you up. You can't
N never got hurt me.
Yeah. Yeah. I got a bright future in the
coffin, bro. I want out of this [ __ ] life, mate.
Be taking some cocoon more again soon.
This life is depressing, bro. [ __ ] hell.
I'm going to move to Thailand for a better life, would you? Yeah, man.
Want to move for a better life, you know?
for anyone here, bro.
I was actually going to the gym, but I
just gave up with you cuz I moved. So,
I just want to drop dead me. I just like [ __ ] man. Yeah, man.
M I might as well be [ __ ] Timmy
with my experiences with women women. I
might as well look like Timmy.
I might as well [ __ ] look like
[ __ ] Timmy, to be honest.
There's no difference between me and
Timmy. Really, we might as well look the same.
Me and Timmy, we might as well look the
same. To be honest, you might as well be
to me. The way you get treated in life,
the way you're going to be sat this week
twinning your thumbs with no date.
Even though you got eight [ __ ]
numbers, you still have a date. You I
might as well be [ __ ] Timmy, to be honest.
pretty much, bro. But yeah, I was going,
but I just sort of gave up for now. So
yeah, it's depressing, bro. Yeah.
It's like what me and him was say. It's
like what me and Monty was saying
though. If they weren't skinned, they
wouldn't be on here every day. Richie, I
actually said that before him.
But to be fair, I was actually saying
that before him, that if these people
weren't skinned, they wouldn't be on it every day
cuz I was saying the same thing.
They would be out like living life. I
was saying that as well, bro. Funny enough.
They're all saying the same thing. Excuse me. [Music]
I'm feeling a bit hungry
even though I had a love sh
Yeah, I'm [ __ ] I'm actually back to
being depressed. Squeezy. Back to them depressed days.
Yeah, this is [ __ ] life.
[ __ ] life it is. Never changes. Ordering
food. I can't waste money.
I don't know how you buy takeaways and
you afford it on benefit squeezy. I
don't know how you afford it.
How do you afford it, man?
Just depressed. Giving up on life. Want
to die in my sleep.
I can't believe this week I'm going to
have no date. Eight numbers in two days
and not a single date this week. Well,
life truly never gets better, does it?
Same old England.
Yeah, the stoner.
This stoner guy said he moved to
Thailand for a better life.
Yeah, but what about sex? What about
relationships, Ghost? You can't even get
that. You can't even get anything in
your own country. I can't believe I got
eight numbers and only two replies and
no meats. That is disgusting. I might
not even go out on [ __ ] Wednesday, Thursday. So
yeah, but how can you buy takeaways and
save? That's what I mean. You crazy bastard.
And you save as well.
I just can't believe how I'm single
after all these years
ghosting all these years of trying. I'm
a good-looking fellow. I should have met
someone by now, man.
Well, when I go out, I spend about 6070.
I spend about 60 70 to be honest. on
stros now I spent about 70 which is not bad
I can't believe that all that trying
over the years nothing to show for it
I got nothing to show for my efforts
over the years how depressing is
Yeah, I get about 1,100 a month.
I got some savings. I got about 1.4k left
ghosting, but I paid everything off. So,
no 1.4 and one. So, actually about two grand. So,
doesn't matter if I've been laid a few
times. I should have been laid 100
I've been all over the country, bro.
I've tried more than anyone in the
world. I should still be getting laid now. So,
it's actually about 2K actually. But yeah,
should have been you should have been
getting more success than you did.
You should have been getting more
success than you did, man.
You should be getting laid every week
with the way you look, the way you go out.
By you, I mean me, cuz I don't know you.
It's [ __ ] disgusting.
I think it's disgusting me.
Yeah, I'm just trying to find another
side hustle nowadays. Ghosting. It's impossible.
Yeah, just just life sucks, bro.
Eight numbers and two replies. [ __ ] hell.
That is bad, bro. Really bad.
Yeah, I'm just like I said, ghost, I'm
just going to do the football bets when
the football starts again. My plan is to
do £100 on two teams, get 300, put the
300 on two teams and get 1,400.
So, I need to win two bets, which is possible, but
I'll only be starting with 100.
Yeah, making money is proper hardware.
It's not going to be guaranteed all the
time, but if I don't find a side hustle by then,
what else? What else are you going to do, bro?
No, I wouldn't sell puppies. If if if
the dog had puppies, I wouldn't sell them.
I wouldn't sell dogs, bro. You [ __ ]
No, I'm not doing anything illegal like that, bro.
I'll try and find something.
I don't know what I do.
>> Yeah, I still should have found someone
by now. Ghosting. Every week is the same [ __ ]
It's the same [ __ ] every week
with these women saying they got
boyfriends. It's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
It's [ __ ] so annoying. Someone's
like, "Oh, at least you're not Timmy or
L J. You might as well look like Timmy,
bro. The way you get treated by women,
you might as well be [ __ ] Timmy Eldridge,
the [ __ ] with glasses.
You may as well look like him cuz it
seems it doesn't matter what you look
like. It don't matter.
I can't get in with Uber cuz they
terminated my account.
So so I can't get with Uber.
I just want to die, bro. I'm I'm done
with life, bro. This is depressing, bro.
And I don't even go out for the dating.
I don't even go out for the women, but I
just acknowledge how [ __ ] up it is.
How you can get all them numbers and you
can't even get a [ __ ] date.
It's [ __ ] [ __ ]
bro. You can't It's not as easy as that
doing Just Dusty and Deliveroo, bro.
There's waiting lists. You're on a
waiting list for like 3 years. I applied
for Deliveroo 3 years ago and they've
still not accepting me. It's not as easy
as that. You can't just get into things.
It's like me. I'm homeless. Do you think
anyone will help me? No. Cuz I'm not
African. Unless you're [ __ ] African.
They don't give a [ __ ]
You do. You think it's is it's that
easy, bro. I applied 3 years ago when I
used my friend's account and they still
they're still saying there's too many
riders in your area. There's too many
riders in your area. That's all they ever say.
It's not as easy as that, bro.
I applied for another one. I'm still
waiting. I've applied for some. I'm
waiting. You can't get a [ __ ] house
unless you're African.
That's another thing as well. [ __ ]
you don't even get help in your own country.
You get treated by [ __ ] by women in your
own country. It just gets worse and
worse and worse. I need to go to
Thailand. I want to live there for a better life.
I think it will be a better life over
there to live.
Going to there for a better life, you know. Yeah.
Cuz this ain't no life here in England,
bro. This is no life here.
Yeah, but this this life in England is
it's not living. You're not living in England.
You're just existing here in England.
The women, the system,
you're just [ __ ]
You're not actually living in England.
You're just You're just existing. Really?
That's all you're doing? You're just existing.
I was speaking to these guys in
Birmingham at the pub. Yeah. They say
they work all over the country. They get
called out and [ __ ] and they get just
under 5k a month,
huh? They must do some mad hours, eh? Mad hours.
So, just under 5k a month. They must be
doing some crazy ass hours, isn't it?
But they go all over the country. Like,
wherever they get called out to, they go.
That's a madness, bro.
That's a madness product.
Yeah, I met him in a weather spoon.
We're all talking and [ __ ] That's a
madness, bro. [ __ ] But the only problem
with that is you ain't got a life. You
get all that money, but you ain't got a life.
But yeah, ghost. I
I know that if you ain't met anyone in 3
years, you're not going to meet anyone
now. That's just facts. It
That's just generally facts.
It's good though. Just under 5K a month, isn't it? Yeah. Imagine
that. You can't even get sex in your own
country. You can't even get laid in your own country.
There's nothing wrong with you. There's
nothing uh wrong with the way that you
look. And you still can't find anyone.
You sure can't find anyone.
Sad, isn't it? Sad life.
Just going backwards, eh?
Just going backwards. That's all you do
in life. You go backwards. You don't go
forwards. You go backwards.
This is sad life, ain't it, bro?
Eight [ __ ] numbers, bro, and two
repliers. How [ __ ] up is that?
How [ __ ] up is that, bro?
I don't have time for people anymore, bro.
I don't have time for people anymore.
No, I hate people, bro.
That's one thing I learned about that
whole like doing that Uber is I started hating people.
Nah, bro. I couldn't be dealing with that.
I just I started hating people even on
the roads, bro.
That was a self-employed job. So
um just because people are so [ __ ]
rude in London, they're entitled. And
like when I'd be riding my bike, yeah, I
had some women say, "Oh, uh oh, uh you
shouldn't be there." And I said, "I'll
go where I want." And then she starts
running up her [ __ ] mouth and I
parked the bike and I said, "If you got
anything to say, come back and say it."
And uh she was with a guy and then she
walked off. And I had other incidents
where there'd be people on the road.
Yeah. Like they just make random sly
comments because they're having a bad
day. I hate people.
But yeah, it made me start hating
people. The the job actually made me
start hating people. Not the customers,
the actual people on the roads.
I hate people, bro.
Yeah, that was a good thing about losing
the house is I never have to deal with
any people again, which was good. Eight people
can't stand them. Oh, yeah.
Oh yeah, it sucks, man. You should I
should be on a date this week, Ghost.
I should be on a date this week.
No, it was a place called Honest Burgers.
A place called Honest Burgers. Yeah. So yeah,
I won't be trying anymore though, bro. I
won't be trying anymore.
What is the point of trying? If
something was going to happen, it would
have happened by now.
You know, you're not ugly. There's
nothing wrong with you. you should have
met someone by now. That's another thing
people don't want to they're in denial about.
They always seem to think, right, that
oh, but the reality is if you was going
to meet someone, you would have met
someone by now.
That's my whole logic. That's what I think anyways.
I feel like if you would have met
someone, you would have met someone by now.
That's what I think. That's my opinion on it.
You got eight numbers on Thursday,
Friday, Thursday, Saturday. You only got
two replies. Why are the other people not replying? You know,
they also reply, right, and arrange to
meet and then ghost you. That's another
thing some of these people do. It's just
the same piss taking, the same stuck
upness, same [ __ ] every time.
But yeah, if you was going to meet
someone, you would have already.
You would have met someone. Of course
you would have, man. You went to [ __ ]
Wales two times in one week. What the [ __ ]
You would have met someone by now easily, bro.
That is facts, man. 100%.
So, it doesn't make any sense. You would
have met someone by now.
But you're still dealing with the same
boyfriend [ __ ] the same problem, the
same piss taken. You know, it doesn't
ever [ __ ] end. Never. ever end.
Never. Just like it would never end on
Thursday. It will be the same old. Yeah.
It's really bad, is it? Greasy. Really bad, bro.
This person I was, they said that they
wanted to meet on Thursday.
They said where where was you thinking?
I told them no reply. The [ __ ]
Never changes in this country, does it? Never.
Never ever changes in this [ __ ] country, bro.
Never. It's [ __ ] depressing, bro. Cuz [Music]
it's not like you're ugly. There's
nothing wrong with you. So why is it
continuously being like this?
That's another reason you need to give
up and leave this country. That's another reason
cuz they're the people that make people
lose their confidence.
They're the people that they're the ones
that make people feel [ __ ] ugly
because they base their [ __ ]
standards on of off of [ __ ] Tik Tok.
No one [ __ ] else,
you know? No one [ __ ] else, bro. You
know what I mean? That's another reason
why you need to move out of this country.
You're just going to escalate and
escalate and escalate.
You know, that's what's going to happen.
You know what I mean?
It is [ __ ] depressing as [ __ ] you
know? Nothing. There's nothing normal
about it at all. Nothing.
I've traveled more than Greasy.
Yeah, but do you know what position?
Yeah, but do you know what situation she
was referring to?
Yeah, but you don't know which situation
she was referring to, did did you?
Yeah, that was funny, isn't it? Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, it would. It would escalate.
Well, I messaged that [ __ ] a month and
a half ago. Yeah. I said, "Let me come
next week, Thursday, Friday. Let me come
and whip your ass in front of your
boyfriend." That's what I said. I said,
"Let me come and whip your ass in front
of your boyfriend." I might as well just
add him in there cuz I know
[ __ ] going to get involved.
Yeah. I said, "What day are you free in
it?" Uh, I was being serious, bro. I
kept I kept it all off YouTube as well.
Let me whip your ass in front of your
boyfriend. That's what I said. Give you
a good oldfashioned wallin.
Yeah, it was a madness, bro.
Cuz obviously I knew obviously get
involved in it. So So yeah.
So I had to kind of involve him.
Well, funny, bro.
They ask for it and then they play
victim. Don't they Grimsy? They ask for
it and then they play victim. And I said
to my mom, what do you think would have
happened the first time when I booked
her? I went, she said she said you
wouldn't be here now.
She said you would have been killed or
in jail. Yeah,
that's [ __ ] mad, bro.
Why do they start all that [ __ ] then get
the old bill involved? I don't get it, bro.
And then they get the old bill involved.
>> He's a [ __ ] coward.
People keep saying that there's there's
light at the end of the tunnel and
there's literally not.
You spent three and a half years of your
[ __ ] life trying, bro. Spending god
knows how much money and you're still in
the same position. How can anybody say that?
I think they're they're lying to
themselves. I think they're generally
lying to themselves.
I used to go through so much money spending [ __ ]
crazy amounts just spending spending.
Spending nothing ever changed.
Everything changed but your mal status. Mal status.
They must be lying to themselves, bro.
If anything was going to change, it
would have changed by now. 1 million%.
million% the kind of money you used to
go through as well.
But they still try to tell you that you
know there's light at the end of the tunnel.
The only thing you you can do is leave.
That's the only positive thing I I can
think with you is leaving this country.
Get out of this country. Leave and never
never come back. Just run away. Never
This ain't no life.
Say no [ __ ] life for anyone in this depressing function.
Yeah, you're an delusional man.
Nothing's changed in years.
And don't forget, I used to be I used to
be a crazy bastard. I used to be worse
than I am now. I'm more actually made back now.
Still nothing's changed.
Still nothing's changed. Nothing would ever change.
So you have all of this money for years, right?
Yeah. And you and you try and try for
years and you don't get anywhere and as
soon as you try one more time when you
when you get less money, all of a sudden
you you meet someone. How does that even make sense?
Let's look up the odds.
That would take
I traveled the world and greet if it
wasn't for this whole YouTube and me
trying I would have troubled. I would be like greasy.
I would literally be like busy.
But nothing ever changes. [ __ ] hell.
Nothing ever changes in this country.
It's [ __ ] aggravating.
I swear to God, it is so [ __ ]
aggravating this depressing country. You
know that? It's like it's just dying to
annoy you. You know, some things are
just designed to annoy you. Like this
shitty country that we live in.
It is a bad thing. It is a bad thing.
You should have met someone. You're
good-look. You've been trying for
[ __ ] 3 years. You You should not have
to be going out again.
Yeah. Most people have to work. You
didn't have to work for 3 years, mate.
For [ __ ] sake. You shouldn't be with
me. You should have met someone by [ __ ] now.
Yeah, but the whole point was I
traveled, right? So, I went to different
places. So, like women are supposed to
be different in Scotland. Yeah. They're
not. They're all the same.
They're all the [ __ ] same wherever
you [ __ ] go.
You should be bothered though. You
should have a goal in life. I've given
up in life. I admit I want to die. I'm
just I'm going to take two cocoon balls right now.
cuz it helps. But you should be
bothered, boy. Because what goals do you
have, man? You should have some goals,
bro. I'm I'm willing to die. I don't
give a [ __ ] mate.
You should be bothered.
You don't want to look back when you're
[ __ ] in your 40s thinking, "Oh, I
should have I wanted to go Scotland. Oh,
I wanted to go here. Oh, I wanted to go there."
You know, so you shouldn't be bothered, bro.
Really? You should have some goals, is it?
Well, if you end up like boy
don't like in your 30s, bro. You don't
want to be that [ __ ] virgin, do you?
I want to die.
I got these balls here.
They help. Yeah.
Oh, that is this [ __ ] Like
that's a long time. 3 years, bro. 3
years is a very, very, very long time.
Especially with all of that, honey.
You should have met someone by now.
You should be getting dates.
You should be getting dates. You should
have dates. You should be having dates.
Yeah, you should be having dates.
I should be having I should be on a date
this week, but I'm being sat home
twiddling my thumbs in bed.
Twiddling my fing swams thumbs. Yep.
You can't even get housed in your in
your own country unless you're an African.
Yep. That's the way it works.
Even if you're disabled,
you got foot problems. Don't give a [ __ ]
the [ __ ] bro.
You can be good-looking. You can't even
get a date in your own country.
What? What is this for life, bro?
This ain't no life here in England, bro.
It can't be.
It can't be no life here.
It can't be no life, you know? It can't be.
And you know the thing is, Nicolo, we
don't even go out for women, but then we
just acknowledge how [ __ ] up it is
because we're not in denial.
You understand? We're not in denial, bro.
So because we're not in denial, that's
why we voice our opinion. You see, you know,
I'm going to call these people up and
make them change their number. If they
don't reply to me tomorrow, bro,
I'm going to call them up and make them
change their number.
[ __ ] this, bro. That is a violation.
I'm telling you, bro, that is a
violation. I'm going to call every
single one of them and make them change
their [ __ ] number, bro. I swear to God.
It's [ __ ] up, bro.
So, I don't think I'll bother Thursday.
No, I don't think I'll be bothered, bro.
It's so [ __ ] annoying. That boyfriend
[ __ ] is so annoying, bro. You can't even
speak to someone without hearing it.
You can't even speak to somebody
normally without hearing it. It's so
[ __ ] annoying, bro.
But you you know you can leave the
country for good if you want you know
for a better life.
You will never stop hearing it. They're
too stuck up nowadays. Everything's Tik
Tok. Everything's in It's like what
Ant-Man just said to me. He said they're
not interested at all unless you've got
a million Tik Tok followers. Yeah,
things will never get better for me
ever. I know that for a fact.
Only because it's been happening for years.
It's been happening for years and years and years.
It doesn't ever change. Never. And it
still continues to happen.
It's really bad.
I agree, Grezy.
It was good. Yeah.
Is that the real uh Is that the real rice? Nah.
Well, it depends what your problem is, bro.
I don't think that's the real rice. But
most problems are you you can deal with,
but I'm completely [ __ ]
cuz I've been trying for years and nothing changes.
The only thing I can do is leave the
country and start a new life for myself.
That's the only thing I can do.
I mean, it depends what your what your
problem is, man. I don't know what your
problem is. I mean, it's okay to drink,
but I I would say if you drink, go
outside and drink.
I just go out and drink once a week now.
Well, I probably won't this week to be honest.
Why can't you go outside?
I'm starting to get these intrusive forks. Greasy.
They're quite well not anymore but
they're actually quite sick to be
honest. Won't get into them but
it's from um it happens when people are
depressed you see.
Yeah. It happens when people are depressed like me you know.
I'm not going to get into them.
Yeah. Yeah, I've got agrophobia, too.
I've got agro phobia, too.
You have gapia, matey.
I've been housebound for two years.
Yeah, I know you're taking a piss,
Nicolo. I love it, bro. I don't go out.
I've been housebound for 2 years.
Yeah, I don't go out, bro.
In a greavic. I don't go out. [Music]
Yeah, I just want to die here.
That man's living a life living in Thailand.
He doesn't have to deal with any of
these these the this these problems, you know.
Same old with women. Same old boring
[ __ ] You know, you know, you don't care
until you actually acknowledge how
[ __ ] up it is. You go from not caring
and then you just, you just realize how
mad it is.
I should have been born Timmy Eldridge.
Sometimes I think I I should have been
born like Timmy Eldridge.
You might as well just be a big [ __ ]
[ __ ] isn't it? Really?
I might as well just be Timmy, is it? Really?
Yeah, I should just be like Timmy
Eldridge. There'd be no difference.
Think of it, you know, Timmy Eldridge
approaching women and then me
approaching women. It's
uh it's exactly the same really, isn't it?
You know what Ant-Man said, Nicolo? He
said, "Yeah, the only He said the only
place you're not going to get I've got a
boyfriend is Thailand."
He said, "No." He said, "The only place
you're not going to get that is Asia."
That's what he said.
He said that's the only place you're not
going to get that. Yeah.
So, what do we have? Five one night
stands. That's terrible.
I know people with [ __ ]
body counts are [ __ ] 20.
What? So, I've got a body count of five.
That is disgusting, bro. You should have
got that in in the first six months.
Yeah, literally. Yeah,
my body count is five excluding escorts.
1 2 3 4 5. That is really bad.
Really, really, really bad.
You should have got that in the first
like 6 months of you trying. It goes to
show just how impossible it is to get laid.
Well, USA Izzy had a body count of 25. Yeah, 25.
So, she [ __ ] 25 men
and I've only [ __ ] people that weren't escorts. Five.
So, I've only done five.
Actually, it wasn't even five. I think
it's more like four.
Actually, it was four cuz obviously Yeah.
But don't forget, I went all around the country trying.
It's so bad, bro.
Well, I couldn't go the other way,
Grezy, cuz she had already come on
kissing me. So, I felt something in my toodger.
And now you got and you got people
nowadays Nicolo dating ugly girls.
Girls you wouldn't even look twice at.
It's bad, isn't it? It's really, really bad.
really bad. And then there was one guy,
right? He was dating a fat, ugly [ __ ] Yeah,
I think men just need to go to Asia.
That's what they need to do. They need
to start going to Asia.
And And it's not perfect there either.
It's not perfect there.
It's not perfect there, but that's what
people need to start doing. 200 rent,
[ __ ] you get people that actually
want relationships with you as well. If
you go Philippines, this ain't no life
here in England, bro.
I knowing him had a body count at 20 and she was
20. She was 20 and her body count was
like 15, I think. A 20.
Yeah, she had a large body count as well.
Do you remember that one in Nottingham, Nicolola? Yeah.
I've been knowing him for ages, man. I
said to them two turban them two seat
guys, I'll come to Nottingham and see you. But
[ __ ] that, bro.
Nottingham's a mission, is it?
They ain't interested in this country, mate.
Look at look.
It's [ __ ] annoying
because it's not like you're fat and
ugly. Do you know what I mean? Then then
it would make sense. Oh,
see if you was fat and ugly, it would make sense
why you'd have to start dating like a
lot below you or whatever, but you're
not. So, how people don't even give you
the chance is [ __ ] be That's what
makes it worse.
I think that's the thing that makes it worse.
That is the thing that makes it worse.
And obviously, you've tried for 3 years
as well. That's what makes it worse. So, yeah. Mom,
is that true though? The only place you
won't hear I've got a boyfriend is um Asia Nicolo.
That's what Ant-Man said. He said that's
the only place you're not going to get it.
The only place you're not going to get
it is Asia.
Yeah. They don't have boyfriends, bro.
Look at all the men around you. Isn't it
so mad how so many are single?
So many single men out there.
Doesn't matter. There's so many single
men out there. E,
so many single men.
So many feminist feminists.
So many independent women that don't
need men, but they've all got
boyfriends. Isn't that mad?
How all of these women that have got
boyfriends are never with them? Hey,
isn't that mad? You know what makes me
die, right? When like they're traveling
abroad and they're here for 3 months,
but then apparently they've got a
boyfriend back at home,
which doesn't even make any sense at all.
Makes no sense at all.
Some of them more funny in it.
I have a boyfriend. I have a boyfriend.
I have a boyfriend. Bro, if I if I
carried on doing him sober that day, I
would have ended up hurting someone.
Bro, I'm not even joking. I would have
ended up seriously hurting someone.
That's why I went on a drink.
I would have ended up seriously hurting
someone, bro. I don't know how I haven't
to be honest.
See, I'm more crazy than Ant-Man, but
I'm more smarter than Ant-Man because I
wouldn't go to prison for these [ __ ]
idiots. You know what I'm saying?
I'll never go to prison for these
uh [ __ ] [ __ ]
That's the thing. Nah,
I just walk away, bro.
I used to say, "I'll be your new boyfriend."
They ain't got [ __ ] boyfriends, mate.
No, no, they ain't got boyfriends.
They do not have boyfriends at all. It's
[ __ ] Most of the men I know are single.
Most of the people I know, bro, I swear
down they're single.
And I know a lot of people [Music]
They don't have boyfriends. No, that's cool.
I know. It's really [ __ ]
I want to die me.
I think if Laney wasn't alive, I think
I'd actually kill myself.
I think I'd actually do myself in
I think I would, bro. I'm not going to
lie to you. This is depressing.
Why do they reply saying they're going
to meet you if they're not?
They've literally said that they're
going to meet. Yeah. Why are they not meeting?
No one on it tells you that, do they?
I know where one of them works, you
know. I'm going to go to where one of
them works. [ __ ] this. I'm going to go
to where one of them works.
I know where they work. They work
somewhere in Stratford. I know. I know
where they work, but I'm going to go to
where they work. [ __ ] this. I've had
enough of it.
[ __ ] come and ignore me to my [ __ ]
face. That's what I'm going to do, bro.
I'm going there tomorrow. [ __ ] this. Yeah. Not for
And to be honest, money isn't even a
problem. We still got money. We might
not get as much now, but we still have money. But uh
but hey, I'm going to go to where they
work tomorrow. Anyways, bro, I'm going
to ask them to go and ignore me to my face.
They told me where they work and what
they work as where they work. So
no, I've had enough of it, mate. I've
had enough of it. I've had enough of it
to last me a [ __ ] lifetime, you know. You know,
I'm going to cause a [ __ ] scene.
Yeah, they do it on purpose as well, cuz
Nicolo, you know, you get all of these
people that say, "Oh, women might give
you their numbers because they're
scared." And no, no, no, no. But if
that's the case, bro, why are they
replying to you agreeing to meet you
then and then ignoring? No one mentions
that bit, is it? They all do that. They
all give false hope. They all do it.
They all [ __ ] do it.
Anyways, bro, I think I am going to go
there tomorrow, bro, and
cause a proper proper scene.
What the [ __ ] This person was like,
"Oh, you need fresh approaches." What?
To get rejected more and more and more
and more more and more.
Why would you do fresh approaches? It's
never ever going to change.
You're just going to get more and more
and more and more depressed. You see, if
you do this stuff sober, Nicolo, yeah,
it's going to really really really depress you.
It used to depress me. It used to get me
on the drink
like when I used to do it at the end. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. It would just get you depressed.
Press approaches to get rejected more.
I'm going to go to where she works.
Is that okay with you, grievy boss?
Come and ignore me to my [ __ ] face.
That's what I'll say to her. She's rude.
What? But it's okay for them to sit
there and ignore you, Grezy.
But it's okay for them to be. Yeah. It
Yeah. And And then And then you just
think to yourself that you're not ugly.
Why are you experiencing this?
Yeah, it it is depressing doing them sober, bro.
>> Oh, [ __ ]
>> I can't believe three years. I guess
there really is not someone for everyone. Okay.
I feel like I've lived my life, bro.
I've done what I've wanted to do. I've
traveled abroad. I've been on a plane.
I've [ __ ] You know what I'm saying?
I'd be happy to die right now, bro. I'm
being serious. I wouldn't give a [ __ ]
Had a good life, lived a high life,
didn't have to work for 3 years.
I don't think there's nothing else left
for me in this life, bro.
I'm not even joking. It's [ __ ] depressing.
It's not even really about the money. I
was even depressed when I was getting
three grand a month to be honest.
It is depressing. So depressing this life,
you know. Uh Yeah.
Okay. Anyway, Grey, but it's okay for
her to sit there and ignore people.
It's okay for her to sit there and ignore people.
That's not okay with me, boss.
No, that's not okay with me, boss. Okay.
Nope. I don't gamble anymore.
No, I don't gamble anymore.
All right, done.
This life is so depressing, bro.
How do I stop? Uh, so a waste of money.
though it has been rigged
and just stopped. Well, what else do you do, bro?
I'll be betting on the football again next month.
But maybe I won't. Depends. Uh,
I never had a problem with it. I never
made myself skint with it. I never had a
problem with gambling ever.
It used to just give me horrific mood
swings and I never ended up skinned from
it. Not for years.
So, no, I never
Not me. You got the wrong channel. I
used to just do it a lot and they would
just [ __ ] give me these horrendous
mood swings. That's why I stopped. So, yeah.
Yeah. I don't think I'd get the buzz
anymore from it. like I used to. I don't
care about gambling, bro.
We got bit bigger things to about how
we're going to be single for the rest of our life.
Nothing ever changes ever in this life.
bitch's workplace, bro.
[ __ ] I'm sick of these [ __ ] ignoring
me, bro. I'm sick of it, Nicolola. I'm
really, really sick of it.
And you know that guy that was on the
table with you? You can call him as well
and I'll do it in front of him
because I like to draw these [ __ ] men
out as well because they always try to
think they're gonna act big in front of
a woman, you know.
They always think they're going to act
big in front of a woman and they're not,
bro. They're really [ __ ] not. So,
make sure he's with you as well, bro. I
hate them people that try and look good for women.
It drives me mad.
[ __ ] hate them, bro. I [ __ ] hate
them. I do. Really? I do, bro. Swear down.
I won't be alive when I'm 50. Hopefully
not when I'm 30, to be honest. It's a depressing life.
It really is.
Really is a depressing life.
Being treated like you're ugly. It's not
a nice life. And all people tell you is,
"Oh, you don't know the future. You
can't predict the future.
Well, I've got a pretty good idea of
what it holds.
I've got a pretty good idea of what it holds.
The only thing you can do is leave the
country and start another life somewhere.
You'd have to go to another country and
start another life somewhere
and never come back to England. That's
literally the only thing I can think of now.
It's actually gotten that bad.
You should be with someone. You're 20.
You're 27. You've tried more than
anyone. You're better looking than a lot
of other people as well in England.
A lot better. You're better looking than
a lot of people in England as well. 27.
It's a depressing life, eh? Yeah,
it's a sad depressing life. Yeah.
No, I don't look older than 27. I look my age.
Gunachan stalking me on Reddit again.
Right. That's all right. Uh,
repeating again. No worries. I'll just delete that.
People stalking me on Reddit again. It's
not a problem. Just PM people.
Stalking to the max. Deleted.
Deleted. Not a problem. I just start
PMing people. There's no point you even
writing comments because as soon as I
find out one of you people are stalking
me on Reddit, I'm just going to start
PMing people and delete the whole post.
So, you're just wasting your time even commenting.
and no, I don't look anything like uh I
don't look anything I don't look
anything like my late 30s. So, yeah.
Yeah. There's no light at the end of I
think if it wasn't for Laney I probably
would end up doing myself in to be honest. Yeah.
To be honest with you. Yeah.
Imagine that. You have to lose a house,
lose income from the house,
still single, lose friends from the
house. It's not a normal life. I don't
see anything ever getting better.
Yeah. Anyways, make a new Reddit. One second.
These people are on YouTube. They're
still going about what you said about
kids. They're [ __ ] obsessed. They
don't change the record, do they,
Nicolo? They're so obsessed.
They're so obsessed. Do you know what?
Yeah. No one even talks about that [ __ ] anymore. Obsessed.
They're still going on about that kid [ __ ]
What the [ __ ] bro? They really, really,
really are obsessed. Anyways, thank you.
I just made a new Reddit.
So, wait, there's there's millions of
people on Reddit. You do realize that
these people are such [ __ ] autistic.
Bro, I'm literally going to have to
leave this this this this country, bro. Seriously. Seriously, bro.
There's literally going out on Thursday.
I didn't realize I got eight numbers in two days.
Still the same problem. Still the same
women. Still the same thing we've been
dealing with for [ __ ] years. Same old boring.
That's why I call it, the same old [ __ ] boring.
I'm going to go to this bitch's
workplace anyways, bro.
I'm going to go to this bitch's workplace.
No, they don't care, bro. They don't
give a [ __ ] They'll leave you on the
street. They don't care, bro.
Yeah, the council will leave you on the
street. They would. They don't care.
They don't give a [ __ ] Unless you're um
unless you're African, they don't give a [ __ ] Sadly,
that's how racist they are. [Music]
Yeah, I think the death is near, bro.
I'm not even joking.
That's how you know these people are
proper autistic. They still go on about
that kid [ __ ] That is mad, bro.
That's how you know they're proper disabled.
They live in the past, is it? These
people are living in the past. Yeah.
situation can get worse. Uh, not really.
depressing life, bro.
It is really the bro I think seriously I
need to start a life in another country,
bro. Seriously, all jokes aside, now
this is the only thing you need to leave
this country and get out of it cuz it's
just going to escalate and escalate and
escalate and escalate and escalate.
It is really really just going to keep
going on and on and on and on and on and
on and on.
It's not a life here in England.
You can have a [ __ ] foot condition.
You can be [ __ ] disabled, bro. They
don't even [ __ ] give you houses. Nope.
But yeah, you just go and start a new
life somewhere else.
Yeah, just start a new life somewhere
else. I think that's where we're at.
I'd even live off 50. I I would even I
would even live Yeah.
I would even live on £50 a week for 4
months if it meant leaving this [ __ ] off,
you know? I would even do it, bro. Even
if I had to do it to get out of here for
a better life, you know? Yeah.
Doesn't matter if they're [ __ ] bro. If
it means having a better life,
then I need a better life. This ain't no
life here, bro.
phobia one day. Nicolo,
what if one day I develop agriophobia?
You never know. I'll be like that guy in
Birmingham. Donna Birmingham, eh?
One day I will, bro.
You can't get anyone from your own
country, bro. They've all got
unrealistic standards. They base their
standards on Instagram and Tik Tok. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. You can't get someone in your
own country. E,
it is mad. It's all [ __ ] up. You
should just be able to go out and meet someone.
with the way that you look, the way that you dress,
the money you have, and the money the
money the money that you have had. You
know what I'm saying?
I just can't believe you can't get
anyone in your own country.
Well, I used to be rich.
I used to say I I pretty much used to be rich.
Really? I was [ __ ] well off.
I was [ __ ] well off, never made a difference.
Then a 19year-old started being a [ __ ]
I used to actually be rich.
I used to actually be [ __ ] rich.
Never made a [ __ ] difference.
Still not interested.
I used to have thousands and thousands
and thousands, bro.
Weren't even a joke.
I remember one time I had 6K in cash.
Imagine that. 6K in cash
just lying around, bro. [ __ ] madness.
It was a lot, bro. And no outgoings, nothing.
I used to have a lot of money, bro. [ __ ] hell.
I used to go on nights out and nights
out and nights out trying to get someone
but you would never find anyone.
Yeah, it used to be the same old every Thursday.
It's mad, bro. I used to literally I
just spend it on nights out. Nights out clothes,
[ __ ] all sorts of [ __ ]
[ __ ] good times, bro.
Lights out, clothes, escorts. Jesus Christ.
Yeah. A lot.
That's I used to do that a lot. A lot.
I used to have a lot of body, bro.
But all things go come to an end, right? So yeah.
Yeah, I had about 6K in cash. I think
the most I had was about seven grand.
About seven. It was
[ __ ] me, bro.
Not really, mate. I've got about 2K. That's it.
So, not really.
And I get less income now. Sorry. Nah,
I'm just normal. Just normal.
[ __ ] hell. It's at seven grand now,
mate. [ __ ] hell. But
I do with that.
I was living a life, bro. Literally. And
I still never met anyone. Oh, yeah.
So yeah, just life never changes.
Life never changes, bro. Yeah, man.
Yeah, that's what happened. I used to go
casino every Thursday. I used to always win
80 90% of the time.
Yeah, I'm bored as well. We're all bored. Oh yeah. Yeah.
I didn't know you was 27, but Wow. Yeah.
I remember I went in the P was 60 power.
probably went to a,000 6 days
like yeah about seven grand I had well
that was sick man
good days good is
I couldn't believe that I won four
grand, but that was a madness
in the casino. [ __ ] Imagine [ __ ] hell. Good times.
I have thousands.
I was always living the high life, bro.
It was fun, isn't it?
It has to end at some point, matey.
I'm going to lo some badness.
[ __ ] work place tomorrow.
Got to go to that bitch's workplace tomorrow.
There's no point, bro. There's not even
no point going out anymore.
Casino times for good times, bro.
[ __ ] All right, fair. [Music]