Yeah.
There we go.
What happened to that phone, bro? [ __ ] Yeah.
There we go. Yep.
Yeah. I was going to do video left
yesterday, but couldn't be bobbing, man.
Yeah, bro. These people are so obsessed
with me, bro. I had to I Cory, I had to
block like a million accounts off of
Virgin Boy yesterday. Madness, bro.
They're [ __ ] obsessed.
They're obsessed on here, bro. Obsessed
on here. They never stop, do they?
That's how you know they're just
jealous. They got nothing in life.
They're reacting to you.
That's what makes no sense. They say
that they do it for reaction, but
they're the ones that are reacting to
you being obsessed every day on YouTube.
They're the ones that are reacting to
you every day. So, that doesn't make any
sense. They're the ones on YouTube
obsessed reacting. What else? So yeah.
Not doing anything today. Just staying in bed.
There's nothing to do.
There's nothing to do, man. There's
nothing to do. Which day? Wednesday.
Yeah, there's nothing to do.
It's depressing, bro. Nothing to do.
Just stay in bed, I reckon.
Stay in bed.
Well, you know that there's not because
you know that it's the same old in this
country. So why are you asking when you
know it's the same old in this country?
Why are you asking that question?
I swear a lot of these people here have
got brain damage,
Cory. I'm actually I'm actually certain
that they've got brain damage cuz you'll
tell them something and then they'll
just completely forget and then just ask
you the same question.
I'm sure they've got brain damage on
this community, bro.
So yeah, cuz you you tell them stuff and
then they ask you the same question like
you've not already like you've not
already told them that the country is
dead and it's the same old [ __ ] in this
country and they just ask you the same thing.
It's a madness, isn't it?
Madness, isn't it?
>> Yeah, man.
They are disabled, bro. Definitely disabled.
Cuz they ask the same thing you've already answered,
but they know the country's dead and you
can't meet anyone. And they still ask
you the same thing. They're [ __ ]
They're proper. They are proper
disabled, aren't they, bro? Proper disabled.
Proper disabled, bro. Yeah.
Oh, it's a depressing country in it,
bro. Depressed. Depressing country.
Depressing depressing life.
Is that right, Cory?
Isn't that right, Cory?
Yeah, I haven't been gym in ages, man. I
still paid for it as well.
I hate life. It's boring. I hate life. I
hate this country.
[ __ ] man. Nothing ever changes in it.
So there's nothing There's nothing to
love about a life that don't ever change.
Life isn't that bad. It [ __ ] is. It
[ __ ] is that bad.
It [ __ ] is that bad. I'd rather be
dead than be here, mate. This country is
depressing. This life is depressing. I'd
rather be in a war country. I hate this life.
It's not normal for any 27y old. It is
really that bad. It really, really,
really is that bad.
It [ __ ] is that bad. I can't I can't
think of anything worse to be honest.
This country ain't it. It's depressing.
I wish I'd die in my sleep every [ __ ]
day. This This life never changes. I
want out of it. It's boring. It never
gets better. I want out of it. There's
no point living to be frustrated every
day of your life.
It [ __ ] is bad. It [ __ ] is. It is
really, really bad. burn mode
experiences with women for years. That's
horrible. No one should have to live by it.
It's like It's like tormenting. Being
alive is like tormenting. It's horrible.
I hate it. I hate this life. If I didn't
have my mom, I'd kill myself if I didn't
have my mom alive. Believe that. [ __ ] this.
Life is [ __ ] Nothing ever changes in it.
Like the piss taking women, the women
pretending that they got boyfriends is a
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] I don't even like
talking about it. It's [ __ ]
depressing. I hate it. I don't even want
to talk about it.
It's too depressing. I don't even want
to talk about it. It's [ __ ] depressing.
It's so [ __ ] depressing, bro. I want
out of this [ __ ] life. It's [ __ ]
Nothing ever ever changes. I don't know
why people sit there and say, "Oh, you
don't know what the future holds." When
we do know, cuz nothing ever changes.
So, I don't know why you get people like
why people say that. Because you do know
because it's literally always the same old. So
now these people don't win nothing, mate.
You don't know what the future holds.
But you do. You've got a pretty good idea, Greasy.
You got a pretty good idea of what the future holds.
I've got a pretty good idea of what the
future holds. I don't know about you.
I've got a pretty good idea.
I don't know about you, boss.
You will never ever change in this
depressing country. I'm never go I'm not
going out tomorrow as well. I said I was
going to go out Thursday, but there's no
point. It's too depressing. Yeah,
these people was on YouTube reacting to me. Grezy,
me. I was getting emails and all sorts yesterday.
I had to block about a million and one accounts.
Yeah, I had to block a million and one accounts.
sat there reacting to me. They react to
me every day,
man. They want a reaction, but then they
react to you. It's crazy, isn't it? Yeah,
it's [ __ ] depressing. This life,
this life is depressing. I ain't going
out tomorrow. [ __ ] that. I was going to
go out tomorrow, but I was like, "No, [ __ ] that.
No, I'm good, bro.
I'm good, Greasy. I'm all right, bro.
I'll stay here.
[ __ ] that. Same old [ __ ]
I already went out twice, did I?
This country will never change ever. Never.
I'm still hearing the same sayings as I
heard when I was 15.
They come on here every day wanting a reaction,
but they react to you every day.
That's the thing that does not make any
sense because they react to you. They
want a reaction but they react to you.
You know what I'm saying? But then
they're sat on YouTube reacting to you
every day. Being triggered over you
every day. That's why none of it makes sense.
Sorry. Just uh just um so this um just
the bad experiences with women they make
you negative. Uh
the bad experiences with women make you
negative. It's the same old cycle. It's
been happening for years
and it never changes ever. [ __ ] Sorry, bro.
Must have gone somewhere today, but I
couldn't be bothered.
But yeah, it's the depressing
experiences with women. It's the same
old. It never changes in this country
year after year after year after year
after year after year after year.
You know what's so weird the Greavves is
that people tell you you'll meet someone
but no one's interested in this country.
So I mean it kind of like contradicts
itself doesn't it?
No one's interested
interested in this country, right? But
um apparently we're going to meet someone.
The stats doesn't add up, does it, bro?
But apparently we're going to meet someone
yet no one in this country is
interested. Huh? That's a madness, isn't it?
See how that makes any sense?
This country will never change.
This country will never change. The
women in it, the people in it. I'm out
of here, bro. Adios.
Adios. Adios. Adios.
This country will never change with the
women in it, the people in it. It's been
going on for [ __ ] years. Greasy.
[ __ ] years. No wonder so many people killed himself.
But don't you think it's weird how
greasy people tell you on these forums,
right? Tell you, "Oh, you'll meet
someone. Oh, your time will come." Or
whatever it is, they say, and then when
you go and you speak to someone, they're
not interested. Isn't it Isn't it mad at
Do you find that mad?
Do you not find that strange? You know,
you should be able to just go out and
just meet someone.
No, suicide is for the smart.
Suicide is for the smart, man. Think of
it. We all die in the end anyways. This
country is [ __ ] This life is [ __ ]
Nothing's ever going to change. We all
die in the end anyways.
Suicide is for the smart. Think about
it. We all die in the end anyways. You
want to carry on living a [ __ ] life
where nothing's going to change? What's the point?
No. Suicide. People that do suicide are smart.
Why would you want to live in this world
and this country with these women in it
with these people in it when life's
never changing? You be you'd be smart to
just kill yourself.
I I don't think it's for the week at all.
Would you rather be living frustrated
and tormented every day? I wouldn't want to.
But yeah, I'll probably just go sleep, I
think, in a minute.
Still waiting for a reply, but for this
person, I'll probably just go back to
sleep in a minute.
Probably sleep all day.
It's depressing, bro.
It is depressing, isn't it? Very, very, very depressing.
And the depressing thing is it never
changes. That's the most That's the most
horriblest thing is it will never ever
change. You'll continue hearing people's
shitty advice, screamsy, and nothing
ever changes in this country. You're
just reliving it.
You're reliving the same life every day.
Same old boring. I called it same old
boring [ __ ] life.
Yeah, it's bad, bro. Really bad.
I'll probably go sleep again soon, to be honest. Yeah,
nothing else to do in this [ __ ] life.
Boring as [ __ ]
Yeah. That's really really bad.
Tell you how this is going to change.
No, no, no. Nothing would ever change.
If something was going to change, it
would have changed by now.
Nothing ever changes. This life is [ __ ] bro.
This life is bollocks.
And it's only going to get worse as well.
How do you meet people these days?
What? What a country, eh? You can't even meet people.
What? What is that all about, bro?
So, yeah, I just took some woke up.
I'm just going to go sleep today. All
It's [ __ ] depressing this [ __ ]
life, bro. I can't actually I can't
believe I was actually thinking of going
out yesterday. Um, sorry, yesterday. Thursday.
[ __ ] this depressing life.
Just tell people greasy that they're
[ __ ] Why don't they just tell people
that they're [ __ ]
Why do they give people false hope?
Oh, you you'll meet people no or even
things get better. Why do they give
these people false hope?
It will never change in this country. Never Never.
Just depressing life in this country
will never change. I'm going to come off
soon and play some GTA, I think, and
just fall asleep. Yeah.
Hopefully die in my sleep. That'll be
ideal. Yeah. This This life ain't
changing. It's clear as [ __ ]
You see my caps off today.
It's a depressing life, bro. It really, really is.
The cap should come either today or tomorrow.
So, it says on the tracking
It's really bad, is it, Cory? Really,
really bad. It's a sad life, isn't it?
We might as well been born Timmy Eldridge.
I was I should have been born Timmy Eldridge.
Man, I should have been born Timmy Eldridge.
You heard Timmy Eldridge? Yeah, that's
who I should have been born like. Timmy Eldridge, bro. Yeah,
I should have been born like him, bro.
Yeah. I wish I was born like Timmy Eldridge.
You know that? Yeah.
It would have made no difference after
all of these years.
After all of these years,
it makes it would have made no
difference if he was Timmy Aldridge.
How mad is that?
Yeah. Go tell the women that keep
rejecting me that. Don't tell me that.
Tell these women that keep rejecting me
that. Don't tell me that.
They're the ones that you need to
[ __ ] tell. These people that aren't
interested in this country.
Yeah, it's really bad.
Oh, just another time waster.
Just another time wastered like all of them.
Oh, just another time waster that went
on a date with me, held my hand and
everything. And then when I tried to
kiss, apparently it put them off. Just
another time waster.
Just another time waster. Like they
they're all time wasters.
Just like they're all time wasters. Just
another time waster. Like just like him.
All the same. Nothing changes in this country.
Same old in this country.
Just another time waster, bro.
from um where was it? Couple
what month and a half ago.
Yeah, I met them in a Weber spoons and
holding hands and everything talking and
then apparently it put them off that I
tried to kiss.
Just another one to add to knock your self-confidence.
I know. I couldn't believe in myself. If
I said, "What the [ __ ] How the [ __ ] you
holding a hand with someone and then you
hold a kiss?" I know. I can't believe it.
I've had weirder ones, bro. I've had
weirder ones. It literally never changes
in this country. Never. You'll be an old
man, bro. You'll be like 50, right?
You'll be like a 55 year old man, and
they'll still tell you the same thing.
Oh, well, you're still young. And that's
all they say, bro. They give you the
same advice, and it's only getting
worse. I know. I spent 200 pound that
day as well.
It never changes. Never. Never changes.
Yeah, I got about 2K, bro. And I'm not
wasting a single penny of it in this
country. So, there we go. I'll probably
get some pork chops today. Yeah.
Yeah. We're never changing this country,
boy. It's [ __ ] depressing.
It is really depressing.
All of them are. All of them are. But I
don't understand why people give you
advice saying that you're going to meet
someone when no one's interested in this
country. We should have like a debate
about this. Why do we get people right
that sit there and tell us things are
going to change when literally no one's
interested in this country? That's
that's that's what I want to know, bro.
Like no troll to the side. Like just a a
serious thing that I'm wondering. You know,
there are some people that you can go up
to on the street or like I don't know,
even when you're drinking and some
people will just straight up say they're not interested.
Sometimes they actually do, which if
hold on, but they said that they were
going to meet someone, so that doesn't
make any sense, you know? Yeah.
But you expect us to believe that we're
just going to one day go out and we're
going to meet someone? Yeah. Right.
Yep. And I'm actually 27. And yes, but
guess what? Things are only getting worse.
Things are only getting worse. Things
were worse than they were two years ago.
So, yeah. But it's only getting worse.
And if something was going to change, it
would have changed by now. That's the
That's the whole point I'm getting at. So yeah,
I'm 27 and nothing's changed in 10 years. So
nothing's just going to all of a sudden
get better when it's only getting worse
and worse and worse and worse and worse.
I was speaking to this person, right?
They actually replied back yesterday.
They said that they're going back
Thursday. They're flying out somewhere.
I said, "No worries. I've been good.
Thanks." They said, "He heading to
Moldova for Ukrainian rock concert. They
singing Russian. What are you going to
do on Thursday?" I wrote, "Oh, nice. I'm
going for some food and probably meet a
friend for a few beers. Guess we could
do something next week." No reply.
They actually reply back like a real
like paragraph. And then when it comes
to trying to meet these people, nothing.
And they told me when they were flying
and what day they're actually coming back. So,
cuz I wanted this person to meet and I
wanted to take things slow just to show
you that they're all time wasters. Just
to show you that they're literally all
time wasters. No holding hands, no
kissing, no any of this stuff.
Just to show you how they're all time
wasters once and for all like these time wasters. So yeah,
they're the same age as me as well. Same
age, same location. They're actually
more They're actually the same age as me. So,
and I'll prove to everyone how they're
just time wasters, just like that
Italian one was
trying to use you as trying to kiss as
why they wouldn't meet you again, which
doesn't even make any [ __ ] sense when
there's nothing wrong with kissing. So,
these people would even go on dates to
even waste your time.
They'll even go on dates with you just
to waste your time and their time.
But don't worry, one day you'll go out
and it will miraculously change.
Miraculously will change. Everything
changes. People won't say they got
boyfriends and suddenly in all of them
three years something will get better.
Will it? [ __ ]
I ain't going out on Thursday, bro. I
ain't wasting money.
No. [ __ ] that.
Well, she seemed right. She's from
Ukraine. But they're all the same, bro.
All the same.
I might as well be Timmy Eldridge.
The only difference between me and Timmy
Eldridge is he's addicted to gambling.
I might I might as well be Timmy Eldridge.
I literally might as well be Timmy
Eldridge. That's the whole point.
Yeah, I might as well be Timmy Aldridge
to be honest. There's literally no difference. If you
and she was sending like X's and everything, but
yeah, that's what they all do.
It will never change in this country. Never.
Also, it's going to be a lot harder to
make money now as well, Cory.
I won't get as much money now as well,
which ain't really
the main thing cuz just back to reality
now, is it? But yeah,
all you need to really do now is just
leave. I mean, anyone could save money
to leave, you know?
Yeah. Anyone can make money to leave,
you know. It's not money to leave.
Yeah, pretty much.
It's the only way. Leave the country and
start a new life somewhere. You know,
you know, start a new life somewhere. Is
that right, Grezy?
Isn't that right, Grezy?
Start a new life somewhere.
Start a new life. Eh, Peter Belly starts
a new life somewhere. There's got to be
more to life than this. There's got to be. Yeah.
Oh, that's bad.
But yeah, I love how these people are
obsessed with me every day on here. Cory
sat on YouTube reacting to me being
triggered every day. Joe couldn't answer
that one, could they? Could he? They
literally sit on YouTube every day
triggered over me.
It's mad, is it, bro?
Sat on YouTube every day triggered over me.
Yeah, it's it's lust, bro. It's nice, isn't it?
That's mad, bro.
That's how you know that that you're
better than them in every way. Better
Cuz they wouldn't be on here every day
doing reacting to you.
They do it for reaction. What? Reacting
to you? They react to me every day,
Cory. When they're sat on YouTube
stalking me, they're reacting.
[ __ ] got this [ __ ] fat [ __ ]
emailing me and all sorts. It just goes
to show that you have something they
want that they can never have.
Otherwise, they wouldn't waste their
precious time on you, would they, Richie?
Would they, Richie, bro? They wouldn't
waste their precious life if they were
truly better than you, right? They
wouldn't be on YouTube every day triggered.
They got nothing in their life. Exactly.
Just like Virgin boy coming on a million
and one accounts that [ __ ] the
[ __ ] virgin. They got nothing in
life, bro. Nothing.
They don't even have [ __ ] two grand.
Two grand. What I've got, they don't
even have two grand. Yeah.
I can't be bothered going out and spending, bro.
>> I'm all right, man.
It's the same old story in this country.
It's the same old story.
Same old boring story with the same old
women. There's no point even going out
and wasting it, wasting time, wasting money.
There's literally no point.
There's literally no point, bro.
Have you done Have you ever done escorts, Cory?
>> I used to do them all the time. I must
have done over a hundred now. Bust off.
There's no point because it's never
going to happen. So there's no point
saying it because it's not going to
happen cuz if it was going to happen, it
would have happened by now. Why is this
person stopped replying?
Messaging and all sorts.
Yeah, I just get a blow dub without a
condom to be honest.
So I don't really Yeah, you have to wear
condoms. It's [ __ ] in it. Yeah.
That is the only bad thing.
I usually just get the escort the
[ __ ] me. I never used to have this
probably because of that reason to be
honest. Keep down. [Music]
So yeah, it's bad though. Bad. But yeah,
you won't meet anyone because if you
would have met someone, you would have
met them by now. We would have met them last week.
So they replied back, said the exits and
everything. I said, "Oh, are you down to
meet next week?" Nothing.
So, we got three replies out of eight
and still no meats.
Just constant [ __ ] in this country.
It's really bad, bro. Really, really bad.
We'll never change in this country.
Never. Never. Cory. Never. Never.
I never had these problems in Newcastle.
No, I never had these problems with
women when I was in
I had them approach me.
It was so easy when I was in Newcastle
now. It's just impossible here. I don't
know if it's as easy as it used to be.
I've not been Newcastle for [ __ ]
years. But I know that when I went there,
it seemed to be easy, a lot easier than
it is here. I don't know if it's still
easy there, but it [ __ ] ain't easy here, mate.
I remember the last time I went to
Newcastle when I was staying in
Middlesbrough. It's got to be about 2
years ago now. I had [ __ ] one
approach me saying, "Oh, you're
handsome." She started kissing me and
everything. Nah, not here, mate.
No, never. You would never get out here. I've never
they just [ __ ]
I found it a lot easier. Me I liked it.
I like Newcastle. Me
even that time I got arrested the police
officers had like really good banter.
It was good, man. It was a good uh
no problems there. They were all really good,
but I don't know if it's still the same.
I don't know if it's still the same as it was.
It's always the same. You message them,
they don't reply, you message them
again, they come out with some excuse
turning down steak houses and
everything. It really doesn't look like
a bright future, does it? It doesn't
look like a bright future dating in this
country, I must say. Sorry. No.
Doesn't look like a bright future, does it?
I need to go get some pork chops. food.
I'm not wasting money on food today. Uh
quite afforded nowadays, matey. No m Yeah.
Yeah. Timmy tried to say they went on holiday it
red stars channel
reacting to it. Yeah.
They always react to me. This red star,
they react to me. Yeah.
This ain't no life for any young person, mate.
They moved to Thailand for a better life.
I'll be back to the old days, Cory. Not
as much money going to the gym.
Just like the good old days.
To be honest, I don't think I will, to
be honest. Bet on the football next
month. I don't think I'll ever gamble
again. To be honest with you,
life is hard enough without gambling, is it?
I don't think I will, bro. No, you still
haven't left YouTube.
No, you haven't left YouTube.
No, you haven't. You're on my live
stream right now. I I probably won't to
be honest with you, Cory, man. No.
No, no, you haven't left YouTube. You're
on live right now. Stop talking about yourself.
These people on YouTube are skin greasy.
Richie, they are [ __ ] skin. If they
weren't skin, they wouldn't be on
YouTube all day, would they?
You go on days, bro. It's the same
people every day.
All skin in it. Fat disabled people.
Fat disabled people ain't got a life.
But yeah, if this person does meet me,
I'm going to show you how they just go
and waste your time.
This person from the Ukraine.
From Ukraine. They're from the Ukraine.
never changes in this country. What do
you expect us to do, car? We go out
every week and spend money just in the
hopes that someone's interested when
then no one's interested in this country.
You know what I mean? Who the [ __ ] in
their right mind was is going to go do
that, bro? You know,
I know I had a haircut, but I went out
twice and I got eight numbers and I done
enough approaches, so I don't need to do anymore
than I've already done.
You've done more than enough
by you. I mean, me,
eight numbers is is a lot. God knows how
many approaches you've done to to have
got eight in two days. That's quite a
lot of numbers. You should be on a date.
I mean, if this person generally can't
make it cuz they're not in the country,
then fair enough. But it still counts.
When they do meet you, it still counts
even though it's not ne next week
because obviously they're not here. So,
obviously, but it would still count as
you go on a date. But you you should get
a date out of one of these numbers.
It's weird how women from Ukraine never
say they've got boyfriends.
Muslim women never say they've got
boyfriends. Isn't that a madness?
That's how you know most of them are
full of [ __ ] The ones that say they do,
Cory, cuz if you if you approach women
from like Russia or Ukraine or you never
ever get it. You never ever ever ever
get it. That's how you know they don't
Most of these people don't have boyfriends.
They don't need them. They get paid
higher [ __ ] wages than us. You know,
they're independent. How do they all
have boyfriends? It's [ __ ] That's
why they never say it. Cuz they don't
they don't have boyfriends. Why do you
think certain cultures never say it?
I've met people from Ukraine, Russia,
and I've never had it. I've never had
them say it.
That's how you know. And the French
never say it either. So that's funny, isn't it?
But yeah, all of these English people
have got boyfriends. Isn't that bad, eh?
She sent two X's as well. I just I just
don't like the leading on, bro. That's
the [ __ ] that annoys me is the leading
on. I hate it.
You need to accept at some point that
there's not there's not someone for
everyone and you need to move on. Simple.
Yeah. I got a number on Thursday in the
in the Weather Spoons when I was with
them Rommy lads.
They don't even give people a chance.
That's what makes me laugh with Grezy
that he says, "Oh, people just want sex
and that's [ __ ] That is absolute bollocks.
Why would someone need sex from people,
bro? You It doesn't make sense, you know?
They don't even give people a [ __ ] chance.
This person might as well be me. They
live in my area. They're the same age as me. So
It's bad, bro. It is bad. Well, at least
I got some [ __ ] numbers. Like I said,
I didn't realize it was that many, to be honest.
Yeah. Why does people from the Ukraine
never say they have boyfriends? Huh?
Are they a certain religion that that
prevents them from lying or what?
It's strange that isn't it?
I also met somebody from uh Yeah. same
kind of thing. Yeah.
Strange now, is it? That is strange.
That is strange. Why are they never Why
do they never seem to be in relationships?
That was such a nice message that they
sent back as well.
And obviously, I can't afford to be
spending loads and loads on dates
anymore, especially when it's not guaranteed.
Like I said, we're not living in La La
Land anymore, bro.
We're not living in La La Land anymore.
We're living in real life.
3 years was La La Land,
which again is shocking that you didn't
even meet anyone in 3 years. But that
was La La Land.
But it's not bad,
you know, being back to reality. It's
not the worst thing, you know. No. Oh, [ __ ] Um,
could I I'll probably just get a burger
from somewhere then.
I can't spend more than56 pound on food
today, bro. We should start saving.
Hopefully that person meets me when they come back.
Isn't that mad? That would be perfect.
Same age. They're born in April, which
is my favorite month.
USA Izzy was born in April as well. Uh,
but nah, that's what you're thinking, mate.
Hey, stop calling yourself a skid mon king.
That's not nice talking about yourself
like that, bro. Come on. It's only
[ __ ] 10. It's almost half 10 and
you're calling yourself a skint mter.
Well, let me ask you this question. If
you're not skint, why are you sat on
YouTube every day?
If you people weren't skin, you wouldn't
be sat on YouTube every day. All day,
If you weren't skin, you wouldn't be sat
on YouTube all day, every day.
You wouldn't be sat on YouTube all day
every day if you wasn't ski. That's all
I know, bro. You can say what you want,
but we all see you on YouTube every day, bro. starting
skin year in year out.
So yeah, you're just talking about yourself.
You're just talking about yourselves cuz
you wouldn't be on YouTube every day if
you weren't skin. Bye-bye.
Why does having savings trigger these people?
Cory, what's going on? Why does savings
trigger these people? Someone having
savings trigger these people?
These people never had savings before. [ __ ] hell.
I was making some good gains at the gym,
Cory, but where I had to move house and
all of that, I didn't and I had to work.
I didn't have time to go anymore. So, yeah.
I've still got the gym until the like
the 7th cuz obviously I paid for it, but
I can't be asked, bro. So yeah,
but yeah, it is strange, isn't it?
I think you should just go to the gym
and just live it just start a new life
in another country,
you know? Nothing else to do really.
There's got to be more to life than this. What's up?
Oh, [ __ ] sake, bro.
Yeah, it definitely was a right number
then, wasn't it?
I must have some bulls to do them
approaches in them web spoons.
I'm a I'm a crazy bastard, bro. I seriously am.
I'm going to make sure now that when you
go on these dates,
you don't try to kiss them for free dates
so I can prove to you that like they're
just all time wasters anyways. All of
this like taking it slow and
just like that one from Italy, it's all [ __ ]
It's all [ __ ]
What they try to do is they try to get
into your head
to make it seem like you've done
something wrong when in reality you
haven't. I mean, there's been people
that you kiss that they got and they
ghost you. So, this doesn't even make
sense. There's people you have sex with
and they'll ghost you. So,
they just meet you to pass time. A lot
of these people,
but I'll try this Ukrainian one. If they
actually want to meet, I I'll meet them
and it will prove to be the same.
It'll be proven to be the same again.
Still ain't been on a date to a cinema.
Never. Never have.
Never. Never ever have.
Never been on a date to a cinema in my
life. Don't see the point in it to be honest. Yeah. Same.
Now, when I go to the gym again, I'm
going to be [ __ ] for like three days. Yeah.
[ __ ] what? I buy it over there.
This we basically finished the sub it. Yeah.
Yeah, burger will cost. Yeah,
we can't be wasting money on takeaways anymore, Batty. No, Batty. Otherwise,
I'm going to be right later.