Sorry, fell asleep.
Better sleeper calls, mate. You're sorry.
That's [ __ ] bad. E, it seems like
when one wants to meet you, they all
want to meet you. It's weird. Oh, [ __ ] Oh [ __ ]
Just waiting for Griezy. Grieves. I'm going
take in my cat out today.
Yo, I just want to let J it popped up.
Yeah, I don't know why it pops up. Sub
to the full on YouTube again.
Goes the show every day. Who's the skid
ones? They are sat on your job every
day. I mean me, I'm saving money. I'm
I'm I mean, I'm taking a break. I mean,
I've done more in three years than these
people have ever done. Believe you me, I
skip mate. But still, you know,
that's just how you that's how you know
they're all skimp. They're sat on
YouTube every day. I can't get off it.
They'd be out if they weren't skim. Simple. Who's on
who's unfollowed Peter Belly? I don't like that.
has. Who is it? Um,
[ __ ] it. Don't for me.
No, don't tell us. Yeah.
Don't follow me.
Not me, mate. I've got two dates lined
up to be honest. But I'm I'm
disappointed, man. I wanted to actually
try and save some money. I don't know if
I want to be able to do it now, but it
could be worse. We could be skinned like
Virgin Boy. Is that right, Nicolo? We
could be skinned than a than a fing skin
and have no money to do anything.
But yeah, man.
I had someone else say they want to meet.
I hope they don't.
But we could be like Virgin boy. Nicolo.
Imagine we're like Virgin boy. Nicolo
have not popped [ __ ] piss in.
Imagine that. Nicolo, you're um you know [ __ ]
being [ __ ] spooking skin like him.
Yeah, I know it's the same old it bro.
But you got at least got one.
To be honest with you, I think I'll pick one.
I'm not going to, but I need to save
some money, bro. Like, really need to
save some money, especially if I'm
leaving here, you know? So, I mean,
it's a waste of time as well, bro. So,
at least we got more than Virgin by a N.
At least we got more than the Virgin.
You got more than the virgin.
So that's my little man. >> Yeah.
Yeah, bro. I went asleep. I was [ __ ]
watching some San Andreas and fell
asleep, bro. [ __ ]
Yeah, that [ __ ] virgin. That [ __ ]
skin flint. Ain't got nothing. [ __ ]
hell. Could be. He could be like him
a [ __ ] skin. L's on YouTube again. Is
it mad how LJ's got all and and like I
said, bro, I'm saving. Everyone knows
that I'm saving and I'm chilling for a
little bit. So, like, is it mad how they
got all this money, right? But they were
on YouTube every day. Isn't that so mad?
People that's not skin that's got all
this money would sit on YouTube continuously
every single day. Sounds like they're
the skinned ones. No one else.
Yeah, I need to go to gym tomorrow, bro,
cuz I've still got a month left and I
need to do some food shopping. But
he's a proper virgin.
You're a [ __ ] D one. You're a [ __ ]
D version, mate.
What about virgin boy? He's [ __ ] He
has to date [ __ ] Oh, [ __ ]
He has to date food [ __ ] disabled.
That's even worse.
Virgin boy has to date disabled. Virgin boy. Yeah, man.
I'm not doomed, mate. I'm going to
Thailand. It's your problem, not mine.
Yeah, it's your problem, not mine. [ __ ] Virgin Mary. Legendary. Yeah,
I believe my clown tomorrow anyways bro
today actually when I end the live stream.
Sorry, Nico. The stalking is so weird.
The stalking is weird by these little
Mongols. Sorry, bro.
Sorry, bro, man. I'm sorry. These
jealous people, they don't leave me alone.
They don't leave me alone. So, I'm going
to have to go, but I need to delete it. Sorry. They're
sat on YouTube stalking every day and
they've got a better life than me. Seriously, man.
Where is everyone? and man,
they're not interested unless you've got
a million Tik Tok followers
cuz you're right. [Music]
I can't move. [Music] Skinn fling skin Then
I was just talking about how like two
people want to meet me but kind of
trying to save money.
So this is the problem that you've got.
This is the problem that you've got mate.
I was saying how virgin boy skintlin
they're stalking me again. They were
stalking me again all day. Steven Howard
Jamie Fatson. Um, a fat boy.
Um, they were talking to me all day on
YouTube. Don't lie. They're giving me the griefs.
It's nice to know
that you've got something that they
want, but they try.
That's why they're obsessed over there with your
Yeah, they were sted all day, bro. All day.
But they call on people's skin. Hey, it's mad.
If you pop one of those days, I was on
there for about 10 seconds. Save people.
Save people. My life.
Yeah, they're the actual bloody victims of life.
I They're just sad, jealous people that
got nothing in their lives. We just laughing.
You're all obsessed on YouTube every day.
Nice know that you got something the day one. Yeah.
Yeah. We've got a date with this Ukrainian.
Where did my car do that?
Hey, where did boy do that? [ __ ]
give me that sponge.
Virgin boy can't do that.
[ __ ] virgin boy can't do that. Virgin Steven
boy can do it. [ __ ] do
never get laid.
We just keep showing these [ __ ] hours
and benefits. That's like he's got bodies.
That's like he's got [ __ ] money, bro.
And you got [ __ ] all. In reality, he's
he's got [ __ ] all, mate.
Cuz if you have something, you would be
living in a bedset. You would be living
in a bedit. No designer clothes, no bed.
Pick you the 31 to go on holiday. It all
points to being skin. You understand, bro?
It all points to literally being skin. Yeah. Oh.
Yeah. All points to being scoop mate.
Yeah. Most of them have because of that freedom.
Yeah. She's the same age as me as well.
But then I had somebody else say they
want to meet as well, which
is a madness.
I'm trying to save money, mate. And
obviously if I meet two of them, I can't
save. I just have money, but I won't be
able to save. That's
I'll have to meet one of them.
Well, you will be able to save, you know, like £300.
That's okay. That's okay with me, boss.
The virgin can't pull nothing.
Why you still
Why you still a virgin?
Yeah, still a virgin, mate. Yeah, I met
her in the Weather Spoon Steven that day
that I met them Brummy lads.
I came back in a good mood. They were
nice lads. They were them bra lads. They
made me want to visit Birmingham.
Birmingham again. It's been a long time.
But I don't want to go to Birmingham.
I'm scared of Timmy.
He might come and touch me up or
something. He's a weirdo. I don't like Timothy Eldridge.
So that's why I don't want to go to
Birmingham because he might abuse me.
Oh yeah, of course she is. Mate, I'm not
virgin boy. That [ __ ] dates [ __ ]
disabled and fat. [ __ ] anyone that
I'm speaking to, they're looking good.
Anyone I'm meeting is looking good.
Everyone I'm speaking to looks good.
Look at that 19-year-old.
The [ __ ] bro?
I'm not [ __ ] virgin boy.
I'm I'm not [ __ ] virgin boy, matey. You know
that's impressive, is it though, Stephen
Howard? Eight numbers in two days,
Thursday and Saturday. It's impressive, isn't it? Yeah.
Yeah. Virgin boy can do that. What the
[ __ ] Did the pillowcase come off the pillow?
Virgin boy can do that. Stephen Howard.
Virgin bike can do that.
Virgin bike can do that, bro. Virgin boy
couldn't even do it to [ __ ] up.
I would [ __ ] it up as usual. I never
[ __ ] it up. I didn't [ __ ] the last ones
They were [ __ ] time wasters, you
[ __ ] silly goose. No, mine.
Go out and make spend your own money
trying to meet women.
I didn't [ __ ] up the last one. She was a time waster.
Like most of them are time wasters.
I didn't [ __ ] it up, but she was a time
waster. She was holding my hand,
spending [ __ ] hours with me, and then
when I tried to kiss her, she didn't
want to kiss.
[ __ ] that's a time waster. So yeah,
this one could be as well.
Virgin boys that virgin boys.
I can't stop singing, bro. Virgin boy. Yeah.
Got to be careful with money nowadays,
Steven Howard, mate. I'm not raking it
in like I used to. But rest be assured,
I'm mowing his skin like that virgin. I
don't have to put out loads of tenders
to make it seem like I've got money,
son. You understand? I don't need to put out
money like, you know, like I've got money, mate.
Oh yeah, mate. Good boy.
Yeah, mate. Yeah. Do you see that little
10 pound? No. Steen Howard
trying to act like he's got money again.
Steven, we all know he's skinted in a
skintlin. The evidence is there. Steven
Howard, the evidence is literally there.
Bed sit, no bed, ain't been on holiday
till you 31.
It all points to you being skinn. You
know what I'm saying? Skinned in a
[ __ ] skin fle.
But I've actually got [ __ ] teeth in
my [ __ ] mouth. That's the difference, bro. You understand?
Nah, they're just [ __ ] retards,
aren't they, Stephen Howard? We've got
our own community, don't we, son? Yeah,
like I said, skin flip, mate.
Yeah, we shouldn't bother with these
jealous people. They've clearly got
demons. You know what I mean? Steen Howard.
Cuz let me just say this to you, Steven Howard. Right.
If these people aren't skin, why are
they on YouTube all day every day?
That that's just a question I've been
asking. If they're not skin, why are
they on YouTube every day? They not
there be out there living life. Proper skin.
Leave me alone.
It's the same people every day as well.
Have you noticed even Howard?
Same people every day, mate. Same people. Yeah,
they've got nothing. Like I said, I'm
starting the gym tomorrow, 100%.
I'm starting the gym. I'm doing food shopping,
but I'm not I'll be living life, but
I'll be doing stuff.
I say living life, but you know, mate. Yeah.
Scott Franklin as well, you know. Yeah, man. Um,
yeah. They ain't got no jobs. They ain't
got no money. They ain't got nothing. Bro,
I tell you what though, every year is
good though cuz January, February,
March, you can save for 3 months
straight, which is good.
You can just save for like 3 months
cuz they're not going out um days. I've
done it before. I saved for like 6 weeks.
I stayed in before. I stayed for 6 weeks, bro.
Oh, I had lots and lots of buddies. Yeah.
Yeah. They ain't got no They ain't got
no jobs, bro. I need to get to like
three grand. I need to get free grand
again. I'm like that too.
I don't get as much anymore, but matter
cuz I'm leaving anyways. So, doesn't
really matter, bro. Ski
to be honest with you, bro. I don't
think I will gamble when the football
starts again. To be honest, bro, I
started really hating it like the whole
gambling thing, bro. like this memories
and like flashbacks and [ __ ] you know?
I'm like [ __ ]
I don't think I will again, bro. I swear
to God. I don't think I don't I don't
see no point in it to be honest with
you, bro. I'd rather just [ __ ] save
what I have, you know? And pointless.
It's actually pointless, bro.
I don't think I ever will again to be fair man. Yeah,
I do like the 10 pound if I'm at the
pump very rarely, but
I don't think I ever will again, bro.
But I was thinking, Stephen, how I mean,
what's the chances of this coming in?
Yeah. Putting £100 on two games, winning
350 or 380 and then putting 350 380 on
the on another two teams and then it
coming in. I mean, what's the what's the chances?
Then you get like 1,500 from 100.
maybe like 40%.
But then you'd have to put a 350 380 on
two teams or something
might be that you won. You know what I mean?
But obviously you could put like 150 on
two teams and it come in. But
So risking it, that's the problem, right?
And it just doesn't make sense risking money.
Just doesn't make any sense risking
money, does it? Nah.
What do you think, Steven Allard? No. Yeah.
That's what I'm doing tomorrow. I'm
going to do some food shopping when I
come from the gym. And this state starts
saving hard, bro. Really hard.
What do you think, Stephen? I would do
you think it's Yeah.
You need to get laid.
What do you think's harder to win on the
roulette or the or the football? Steven Howard,
what do you think's harder?
Oh, he is the BS.
Probably football is it?
Football is probably harder. Yeah,
that's the thing. You can gamble all
your benefits to try and win more, but
[ __ ] it's a risk.
Obviously, if you lose, then you're [ __ ]
Then you're [ __ ]
I might just uh
then you'll be [ __ ] mate.
Are you going to be betting on the football?
I need to try and look good for when I
meet this woman next week.
I can make some [ __ ] gains, you know.
I still can't believe eight numbers in
two days. [ __ ] hell, bro. What the
Yeah. Football is hard to win on, isn't it?
Yeah, I will be doing sir. I've got it
until the um 7th. Obviously, I'm not
paying anymore cuz I don't know where
I'll be. So,
you might as well just try and save some
money now, you know, while you can. So, yeah.
Virgin boy ain't got no muscles. [ __ ] lanky [ __ ]
He's a [ __ ] lanky bastard.
[ __ ] lanky [ __ ] What damage could he
do to anyone? Lanky [ __ ] Lanky virgin. [ __ ] hell.
He was talking about USA again
yesterday. He's obsessed with her.
You know when he's like trying to like
when he's trying to [ __ ] his girlfriend
and it ain't going in. He he's probably
like trying to think of all of the like exf.
He's probably like desperately trying to
think of them and it doesn't go up. That
little disabled pecker don't go up, mate.
No, mate. Don't go up, mate.
No, it don't go. It don't go up, bro. Yeah.
So, will you be betting on the football
then if it will start throw?
Will you be betting on it? Nah. Yeah.
What? Small, but it's like what? £100,
you silly goose.
What? Like £100, you silly goose. Yeah.
What's the maximum you're going to put on one city? Oh,
yeah. I was thinking of putting like
£100 on two teams,
but I'm not sure if that's too much.
Why don't you tell us what you think, Sippy?
So, that's too much. £100 on two teams.
It's too much.
It's all too much, is it?
Well, you think it's too much really?
You actually think that's too much?
Why is that?
Why is that matey?
We think 100 pound on two teams is too much.
Why is it a bad gamble?
Why is it a bad gamble matey?
Want to do some food shopping tomorrow?
Maybe £40. Oh, [ __ ]
Why is it a bad gamble, bro? Why? No, bro.
I'll probably stick like 10 20 pound on it maximum. probably bro. Yeah, probably.
Will you ever play roulette again, Steven Howard?
Will you ever play roulette again? Yes. Yeah.
Remember that time I went in the casino
with 150 and then I won four grand. Oh mate,
that was lovely.
That was a lovely site, bro.
Oh, I've got a date with uh one of these
women. Ghost him.
And I think another one said they want
to meet me. But the thing is I'm trying
to I need to save some money, bro. Like
obviously I could spend the money. I can
spend money on dates. Not bullying, but
obviously I need to save now. I don't
get as much.
Obviously, one of them I'm definitely
meeting because I can spend like 50
pound, bro. I'm not skin. It's that I
need to save money. If I'm serious about
leaving, I've got to save money, bro. You know?
Yeah, we was just talking about the football ghost.
We're just talking about the football guy, but I'm um
Yeah, we're just talking about the
football like about what we're going to
bet on and stuff, but I don't think I
will gamble again.
I honestly don't think I will gamble again, bro. So, yeah. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, [ __ ] it. One second. Yeah, bro.
So we're saying it brother.
Yeah. One always lets you down, bro. Always.
Always let you down, bro. [ __ ]
I got a six before, bro. I put £1
and I got £75 off of a pound version.
£75 off of a pound, bro. The madness.
But I was thinking, bro, like, oh, just
put a pound on.
No, it's not going to come in. And it
did, bro. [ __ ] 16 was £1.
I wish I had £10 on it, bro.
Never mind. I was 19 back then as well.
So, I mean, [ __ ]
Yeah. No, I don't think £10's bad.£10
£10 is not bad, you know.
Yo, your boy was on. All right, listen.
Bro, listen. Listen
out, bro. I need to talk to you, man.
[ __ ] One second. Yeah.
These people on here, bro. One sec.
One second, bro.
Bro, these people. Yeah. Listen, bro.
You know that Triple H. Yeah. He He was
coming on my [ __ ] right? Yeah. I don't
know if you saw it the other day, bro.
Like purposely [ __ ] sterving. [ __ ]
stirring. [ __ ] stirring. [ __ ] stirring.
[ __ ] stirring. [ __ ] stirring. [ __ ]
[ __ ] stirring. Yeah.
Time and time again. Time and time
again, bro. like just [ __ ] storing non-stop
[ __ ] and then he's trying to like
he's doing what [ __ ] thing he used to
do like and the maddest thing about it
bro is that like these people you you
got to understand with these people on
here bro that they are literally all the same
for Triple H [ __ ] I don't know how
much money we've wasted I don't know how
much time we've spent yet traveling to
go meet these people and these people
don't show up.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Do you know what I'm saying, bro? Like,
they're [ __ ] They're all [ __ ] on
here, bro. Like that Smokeoky B and that like
if I didn't know any better. Yeah, I
would I would have went Newcastle on this Saturday.
I would have went Newcastle this
Saturday if I didn't know any better,
bro. And trust me, I would have said
some madness, bro. You don't understand. Yeah.
I hate these people on here, bro. I hate
these people on here.
Like you you laugh, right? You you can
laugh at it now cuz you're not on it,
but bro, you won't be laughing. You stay
a week on it, you won't be laughing,
bro. I hate these people. And the cheek
of it as well. I went there three times
and this cheeky [ __ ] is trying to [ __ ]
stir when, bro, the guy don't even come
out. Like, none of these people do. And
then they all come back on YouTube like
nothing's happened. That's what annoys
me, bro. That's what annoys me with these people.
It's like that Triple H, bro. Like trust
me, bro. If I didn't know any better, I
would have went there and shot and
violated him, bro. Trust me,
you know, but I I ain't got £4500 to be
wasting on spastics anymore. I've been
there, done it, won the t-shirt. I've
done it with I've done it a million
times with these people, you know. Terry
still coming on here trying to act hard
millions of times. He done it yesterday
as well. He's still on here. They're all
little [ __ ] begs, bro. They're not
about nothing. None of these people.
They're sad. Oh, they they still they
still stalk me to this day. So, I mean, yeah,
still stalk me, mate.
But that Triple H is very, very cheeky.
You know, I've seen him on your um yards
talking about [ __ ] Zane and stuff. Oh
yeah, I got stalkers, bro. I've actually
got Yeah, I was on Reddit earlier, bro.
They were stalking me all day. All day
these people stalk me. They've got
channels dedicated to me. They stalk me.
They do everything. Yeah, I've got about
four different people that just won't
leave me alone, bro.
I've got four different people that
won't leave me alone. Yeah,
won't leave me alone, lad. They're all
skin sad bastards. Yeah,
they don't leave people alone, mate.
They don't leave people alone. And the
reason I mention you, LT, is because
we've both done it to between us, you
know, gone to this place, gone to that
place. We've gone, we've tried meeting
different people and they never ever
show up and they all come on YouTube
like nothing happened again. It's the
same thing with that Triple H, bro. It
annoys me, bro. Like, it might not annoy
you, but it annoys me. You know,
you know what I'm saying, bro? No. No.
But here's the thing. It's not about
content, though, bro. Cuz they don't
stop. This is the thing with these
people. They don't stop. And it's not
that they do it for a reaction, because,
bro, there's two things that's wrong
with that. Yeah. A, even if you don't
react to them, they still do it. And B,
um, and B is that they are reacting to
you every day by what they're doing. Sat
on YouTube stalking every day, bro.
Like, look at look at these people on
YouTube every day stalking.
They are reacting to you. They're being
triggered by you. They're thinking of
you. Like, think of it, bro. That's
that's the reality of it. So,
but trust me, like I said, I admit it. I
ain't going anywhere, bro. Because I
ain't going anywhere, bro. Because like
I said, if if I didn't know any better,
I would have been I would be going to
[ __ ] Triple H and I would have been
going to that Smokeoky Me if I didn't
know what these people already do, bro.
I wouldn't I if I didn't know what they
already do, bro, I would I would have
done it all over again.
Trust me, my traveling days are done, matey.
We've seen the real you, mate. We've
seen the real Harry P. We've all We've
seen the real you little shitous. We've
all seen you, bro. Let's Let's list
them. Yeah. Terry, Mark Samson, Bomb,
Virgin Boy, [ __ ] Trevor Dawson.
[ __ ] It goes on and it goes on and it goes on.
Goes on and on and on and on and on and
on and on. They're all the same, bro.
What is wrong with them, bro? Why don't
they stop? I don't understand with these
people. Why don't they stop?
Yep. And I went to Middlesbr. He didn't
come out. Load of excuses.
Load of excuses, mate.
Load of [ __ ] excuses.
You know what I mean? They don't stop
LT. I don't think you understand that
they actually I've actually got people
that actually stalk me. I don't think
you actually realize it. They actually
want my ass, bro. They're [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] [ __ ] I swear to God,
they're absolute They're absolute [ __ ] bro.
Seriously, they are.
But yeah, I need to save money, bro, cuz
I go these dates.
They're [ __ ] weirdos, bro.
So, anyways, ghosting. Do you play that roulette?
Bro, do you know the only one I like on
here is that unworthy clock?
Yeah, they never Bro, they never Bro,
we've done more than Arnold Lane. We've
Trust me, bro. You don't know how badly
I want to go to Belfforce and smash the
[ __ ] out of that [ __ ] Like, you really don't understand.
I'm starting the gym again tomorrow.
Like, you really don't understand, bro.
But I know what it is because we've been
there, done it, worn the t-shirt.
Yeah. I don't gamble really anymore,
bro. I hate it. I actually learned to
start hating it. You know what I'm
saying? Yeah. I think the last time was
when I was in a pub maybe a week ago. I
like change. I was drinking some
Guinness. People were stressing me out
and I just put it in the machine. But I
don't [ __ ] with it, bro. It is a waste of money.
Yeah, I don't. I I actually went to
stop. See, a lot of people, right, they
when they stop, they get like um they
relapse and they get urges. I just went
to hating it. I just started hating it, bro.
Don't know if it's because I work for it
or I know like what it's caused and like
the stress and I don't [ __ ] with it,
bro. Trust me, I probably won't even do
the football to be fair. I keep saying
the football, but I probably won't. It's
there's no point in it, bro.
I don't like it, man.
So, some people go out of it. I guess
Timmy never will.
But yeah, they never show up anyways,
bro. And then they pretend like nothing's happened.
And LG, that L that L J annoys me, bro.
I would love to go and smash his face,
bro. Like, you have no idea. Like, I
don't think you have any idea, but I'd
love to, but back onto him. There's no
point because everyone's just going to
stick up for each other and it goes on
and it goes on and it goes on. So,
there's no point, bro.
So, there's no point, bro. There's
literally just no point.
Like I was telling my mom about this
yesterday the other day on the phone,
not yesterday on the phone the other
day. I hate these people, bro.
The only one I don't mind is worth the
clock. Unlike Grezy Grezy's a good [ __ ] No. No, bro.
I was getting pissed last week.
Actually, I was getting pissed.
Well, I don't know like that.
No worried about that, man.
Yeah, I bought a new TV, bro, cuz that's
to move and [ __ ] So, yeah. LTV and you
should play some Xbox. You should play some Franklin.
Like I said, I'm hitting the gym
tomorrow. I've got until the 7th. I need
to start saving some money. So, yeah, man. Wow.
He didn't die, did he?
I met some uh seek people from Nottingham uh
[ __ ] last week. L I can't stand that
Nottingham accent, bro. It's [ __ ]
horrible, is it?
I've not come back not long come back
from the gym. I mean we starting tomorrow. So yeah the madness
did he die then LT?
Did he die out?
Yeah, I almost had it with a [ __ ]
Polish bouncer [ __ ] uh two weeks ago. Ali,
I won't have none of it. I've got the video.
I weren't backing down, mate. I weren't
[ __ ] backing down. [ __ ] that. Yeah,
I weren't backing down from that [ __ ] lady.
I think me, Mark Samson, Terry, and LT
should all go out.
What do you think?
You know, you me LT dancing and then
Mark Samson and Trevor doing Coke Coke
off each other's noses.
I think that'd be a lovely site, isn't
it? Just like a little work stew, in it. Yeah.
Like a little works do it. Yeah, man.
No, you wouldn't, bro. I've turned up
before and they don't ever turn up. No,
no, no, no, no, no. I've turned up
before, mate. I know. I was thinking
about the other day when you went to
Nottingham. Yeah. for that shake the
tree and he said come in my garden and
let's watch football
gave me jokes man
you know to be honest with you've also
grown up on here as well yeah
you've kind of grown up on here as well
if you think about it bro you've kind of
grown up on here you've had some near fish's experiences
you know, you've kind of grown up on
here like I have as well. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Turn up, mate. Why would I turn up? Come on. Oops.
Yeah. New phone out. I can't afford it, mate.
Ah, I can't afford it out here. Can't
afford it, mate.
Did you get it yet? I'm poor nowadays, matey.
Man, poor me.
[ __ ] the new fold, bro. [ __ ] it. Yeah, I
went out on Thursday and Saturday out. I
had to really try and, you know, find
someone to find a candidate for baby Peter
before I go completely broke, you know.
But mate, it was seeming to be quite odd. Yeah.
No, seriously. RT matey
LT. Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ] I forgot to mention.
You know how much they're charging to go
into Fabrics nowadays? I I [ __ ] was
going to hit up fabrics on Saturday. I
got to fing station
out. I got to fing station and I was
walking. Done a little approach at the
train station. Got the number. She was
on some pills or something. Anyways,
bro, they were literally Yeah.
They're charging £35. I thought [ __ ]
that for a game of soldiers
LT. [ __ ] that for a game of soldiers.
35 [ __ ] quid there charging. I
haven't been in years,
you know. That's where I used to do my little boogieing,
how you can Yeah, you can vouch for me.
That's where I used to do my little boogieing. Yeah,
that's where I used to do my little boogieing, mate.
That's where I used to do my little boogie
when I used to go for a little
a little boogie.
You remember a little boogie?
You remember them summer times? Little
little boogie. You even went there a few
times to try and catch me. You remember
when you went to the swan?
You remember when you went to the swan?
You horrible [ __ ]
You went to the swan. You horrible [ __ ] Yeah.
You're not You're an horrible [ __ ] You
are, mate. Horrible [ __ ] You are.
No, you're noble [ __ ]
How's USA? Is he still trying to get in
her little knicknacks? LT
sure trying to get in her little panda nick.
Huh? Calvin Klein knickers.
LT, you know, it's just bad, isn't it?
Still trying to get Still trying to get
in her knickers.
Still trying to get in her little knick-knocks. Knicknocks. [Laughter]
knick-knocks, mate. Bless you. Bless you in life.
God loves a tribe, bro.
Nah, LT, you're never giving a bite
back, are you? You're a thief.
Oh, some [ __ ] stole my [ __ ] Dior S of
[ __ ] aftershave, man. Yeah,
I had a madness, bro.
Yeah, I had a madness. Me, man. [ __ ]
But it's stupid because where I had it
so long, it lost its smell. There was
only well there was quite a bit left but
it had lost its smell. So it was just
stupid to steal it to be honest. Yeah.
It was a madness. But I don't know you
know who done it. Yeah.
No racism here. No racism here.
No racism here. Not um [ __ ] Steven Howard. No,
you still been going out drinking.
I need to limit it nowadays out. I can't afford it.
I can't afford it. Mateies. No mateies.
I can't afford it. Mateies, we're not
all rich like you, matey.
We're not all rich like our team, matey.
I've got a whole load of dry cleaning to
that's going to cost me like 30 quid,
bro. Stonies, brow fees. [ __ ] a lot,
[ __ ] it up, bro. Hello matey.
Ah, so you haven't blocked him then.
LT's not blocked you.
Oh, you know Virgin boy still tries to
join my hangout. Do you know that?
Imagine that. Yeah. calling the police
on someone. Getting someone arrested. Yeah. Yeah.
Look at this. Hey, look at this troll. Yeah.
I look at this troll. Look at it. Yeah.
You have to laugh at it. Yeah.
Oh, he's on your side. You know, Rocky
LT, he's on your side. Yeah.
Oh, do you do you agree with me about
Triple H though? Do you agree with me
about that? Triple H. He is constantly
like [ __ ] stone, bro. Constantly [ __ ]
sting. Yeah. [ __ ] sting. [ __ ] sting.
[ __ ] sting. Yeah. And [ __ ]
He's constantly [ __ ] stoned, bro.
Um, about Virgin Boy knowing that, you
know, you're not going to meet anyone of
that. But when it's when you go there
and it's time to come out, he's nowhere
to be seen this [ __ ]
He's nowhere to be seen this [ __ ] bro. You know,
that's why I had to block him.
They made me come back to Newcastle next week.
But it won't be a lovely sight.
It will be really, really bad.
You understand? It will be really bad, man.
Don't make me [ __ ] come there and
[ __ ] you up, man.
Yeah, man. Welcome. So, what are you
doing anyways out to you? You smashing
all the poon's hand
whilst you're single. Why are you
single? You was in a lovely little relationship.
I don't get that.
You was in a lovely little relationship.
Doesn't matter if it's summer. What the
[ __ ] Well, it's better. Well, summer's
kind of finished now, but yeah.
I mean, yeah, but it's kind of finished
now, you know.
I mean, the weather's been [ __ ] Yeah, man.
So, what if it's summer? What the [ __ ]
What's that got to do with you being
single, you silly, you silly goose?
You really are a silly goose, aren't you?
You need to give me a call.
I've been waiting on you. I'm I'm I'm
here alone today. I'm [ __ ] bored, bro.
Give me a little call, man.
Give your boy a little call out.
Give your boy a little call.
Come on, give me a little call.
What are you waiting for?
[ __ ] hell, bro.
I've never seen
so many£10 notes in my life.
Why is Virgin Boy deleting [ __ ] when
I've literally got everything?
I've literally got everything this
Virgin has done.
So, I don't know why he's deleting
things when I literally have everything.
Everything, bro. Literally everything.
[ __ ] such a virgin.
Give us a little call.
It won't hurt to give us a little call out.
Want to play some Franklin in a bit.
Need a [ __ ] extension, bro.
Like a proper extension. [ __ ]
He is such a loser, man. The virgin boy
is such a loser.
He's an actual [ __ ] loser, bro.
He's a [ __ ] loser.
I've never known someone so skinn try
and make it seem like they got money. Never, bro. your skin.
20s and 20s and 20s then tens.
What a [ __ ] skin flint. Freaking hell.
Who's a [ __ ] skimp flint? Steven
Howard. A [ __ ] skimp flint, matey. Never mind.
Yeah, I don't want these haters. He's a [ __ ] virgin. [ __ ] off. Yeah.
I haven't heard anything, bro.
I haven't heard anything.
That's why he's trying to get reaction,
but I keep ignoring him. He's such a [ __ ] loser.
There is nothing, bro. They haven't said anything.
He is such a loser, bro. I've never come
across such a big a big loser in my life, man. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. So, they haven't said nothing.
He's such a loser in it, bro.
Virgin boy is such a loser.
I don't know why he keeps showing his housing benefit.
Why does he keep showing his [ __ ]
housing benefit? It's [ __ ] weird.
And man still in Thailand. Mollics. Bollocks.
[ __ ] bollocks, mate. What the [ __ ] Bollocks.
You still didn't ask my question about
that Triple H. He's a [ __ ] fanny, is
it, bro? A proper fanny.
You know what, bro? I might I might go
to Newcastle again, bro, cuz I want to
go anyways and show everyone how much of
a fan he is. Cuz I haven't been there in
a long time and I and I said I'd always
go again. Just don't really want to
waste £400, you know.
That's the only thing. And
yeah, but bro,
I can go again, bro, and just show you
how much of a fanny he is.
He's a fanny, bro. Proper fanny.
They're all the same on there, bro. Trust.
Trust me, bro. They're all the same now.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. You got the wrong
end of the stick, bro. I was dissing his
unborn because of what he kept doing on
here coming on my YouTube [ __ ] stirring
right when he knows damn well this
person's not going to meet me. Bro, I'm
not a victim. I'm saying that I will go
there and he will not turn up just like
he's not turned up the three times I've
been there. No one's playing the victim.
I said stuff about his kid. Yeah,
because bro, he was trolling me, you
idiot. That's why. And he's still doing
it. He is still doing it. I was on a
Hangouts the other day with him maybe
about maybe a few weeks ago and he was
normal talking about Yeah, I'm doing
this. Yeah, I'm doing that. Talking
normally. All of a sudden, this guy
comes on my [ __ ] Hangouts.
Oh yeah, nonslegs is is making posts
about you, which my eyes [ __ ] sting
because he knows that he's never going
to meet anyone.
Um, and he knows what he does and he
still shits on my channel. Then I
ignored it. Then he kept saying, "Oh
yeah, he's bullying you. He's bullying
you. He's bullying you." I was like,
"Bro, I've gone to both of your areas
three times and none of you come out.
Yes, I've been to Newcastle three times.
Yes, I've been to Kent three times and
you both don't come out." And you're
coming on my channel [ __ ] serving, bro.
Like I said, if I didn't know any
better, I'd be going Newcastle this
Saturday. Believe that. If I didn't know
any better what these people do.
Yeah. I don't find that [ __ ] funny, bro. It's annoying.
Is it? No, it is annoying, bro, with him
as well because he done it three
different times and he continuously does
it even more than Harry F as well. So, yeah.
So, yeah, bro.
But the difference is I'll back up my
talk. I'll say it to his face. He
doesn't meet anyone ever, bro. [ __ ] I
went three times he did not come out,
bro. Three times he did not come out.
Even in a normal way, he didn't come
out, bro. It's just a bit weird when
he's coming on here like [ __ ] stone.
Mark Samson is the same. You know, even
these people from London on here are the
same. Even if you think about it, yeah,
it's not even just these northerners.
It's also Londoners as well.
Uh Terry's the same, Mark Samson's the
same. There's someone else on here
that's the same. That [ __ ] guy that
claims he lives in Lambbeath that comes
on Hangouts. You know, it's even the
Londoners on here are the same.
Obviously not us, but even they are,
bro. It's, you know, it's not actually a
northern thing. They are all the same on here.
You do realize it is it is people from
London, too. Yeah.
They're all the same, bro. But when one
of these people get caught sipping,
they're not going to be laughing. That's
the thing. They're not going to be
They're not going to be laughing, bro.
They're not going to be laughing.
uh some guy that uh used to go Monty's.
But yeah, it's not just it's not uh just
northerners, it's Londoners as well,
bro. You've seen it yourself. I you
know, with Terry, with [ __ ] Arsenal
Mark, they're all the same [ __ ]
And actually, no, bro. Triple H actually
started it. Everyone that was watching
it will tell you. He keeps bringing up
this virgin knowing down low he's never
going to meet anyone and that he's just
a keyboard warrior and then he and you
can write on his [ __ ] right
oh you can go on his [ __ ] and he'll be
like oh manta m and I'm thinking bro I
can go to Newcastle right now and you
ain't coming out and saying nothing to
anyone's face just like the three times
you can do it
so it's like it's like what the [ __ ]
like at least with Fraser yeah
if it was Like even if it was like
Fraser, even Fraser met. Even Fraser
met, bro, in the end. That's the maddest
thing about it. Like even Fraser
actually come out.
Yeah, but some of the people on here are
black. That's the thing. They don't know
because some of the people on here are black.
That guy is definitely black, bro.
No, some of these people, well, at least
one of them on here are black, bro. Of
course they are.
That guy from Lambe is definitely black. So, yeah.
Oh, nice. Frank didn't go everywhere. Greasy.
Yeah. But yeah, like cuz
it's just like Belfast, bro. I'd go to
Belfast. I'm not scared of [ __ ]
flying to Belfast. Why would I? I've
already done it, but I've already been
on a plane before.
I ain't going to lie. I don't know who I
want the most on it, bro. I've got to say now
probably Virgin Boy and L J because you
know that L J he tries to portray like
he's something bro but he ain't nothing.
He tries to portray that he's this big
hard man. You know you know when you
were on here like two weeks ago I was
dead ass trying to meet this guy bro and
he weren't having none of it. He weren't
having none of it. Trust me. I went on
the hangouts and everything. I would say
Virgin Boy and [ __ ] him
to be honest with you. And who else?
Yeah, to be honest,
I hate going on that channel and he's
walking around like he ain't about
nothing, bro. He ain't about nothing at
all. Really ain't about [ __ ]
Cuz you keep saying about how you've
come here. Yeah, but bro, how many times
did you go for Timmy? Three times.
Don't you have you never heard of a rematch
two, three years later where people have
rematches? He would get [ __ ] up, bro.
I'm not even joking. He would. He generally would. So, yeah. Huh? Hurry.
Um yeah, they got him uh kicked out the hotel.
So they're not on here anymore. Yeah.
But bro, like like I said, is a snake,
bro. He definitely definitely is a snake.
He is definitely a snake, bro. 100%.
Who the [ __ ] is Chris?
[ __ ] madness, bro.
Yeah, my mama.
That's my mama. One second.
Do you see that count LT? People like LT
get what they want. He starts throwing it.
The Grezy is obsessed with women.
And man said, "That's the only place
you're not going to get that is is
Asia." He said, "The only place you're
not going to get that is Asia."
Is that funny, Grezy?
He said, "The only place you're not
going to get I've got a boyfriend is Asia.
That's the only place you're not going to get." Oh, really?
I agree with you. Why was you laughing
at the tenants being homeless? It's not funny.
Cuz I was laughing. He said, "What? You
think it's funny?" I don't think it's
funny. It's not funny. People being
homeless screams, is it? No. [Laughter]
Well, you think it's [ __ ] funny. Do
you agree people?
It's not funny people being homeless. Crazy.
You think it's funny, bro? It's not funny.
It's not funny, bro. Nah.
You think that's funny, Grezy? People
being homeless ain't funny, bro.
Oh, don't tell me.
No, not anymore, mate.
Nah, I don't live there anymore, bro.
They took the house.
When I told you they took the house,
bro, I was still living there, bro. I
was rack raking it in, bro.
raking it in. I've still got savings. I told you
that. But no, bro. But they actually
have now. Yeah, they actually have to
But every everyone knew that, bro.
Yeah, people knew where I was, bro.
People knew where I was.
People knew exactly where I was.
Just looking at this woman on Instagram.
She's got big boobies, Joe.
This Ukrainian one sexy man. Yeah.
Well, I still got some money from it and
[ __ ] But that's what I'm saying. I need
to start saving now, bro, cuz I don't
get that money anymore. So, I need to
find other things. But I'm chilling for
a little bit anyways, bro. Yeah.
Good times, isn't it?
[ __ ] stupid baiffs, bro. They're [ __ ] wankers.
They don't even [ __ ] help you, bro.
They don't even give you housing unless
you're [ __ ] Unless you're African,
bro. They're [ __ ] They're racist.
They're [ __ ] racist, bro.
I got an escort messaging me. You better
not say you're in Stratford, mate. Ain't
got no money for you.
Oh, you're in Wembley. [ __ ] that. You
can [ __ ] stay in Wembley, [ __ ]
Yeah, they're [ __ ] bro. It's so corrupt.
So, not really. I ain't got no outgoings.
Well, I got one a phone bill, but it's about it.
I think my PlayStation thing is about £10. So, no, man.
is what it is.
I used to live on like [ __ ] £700 a
month. [ __ ] hell, bro. That was bad.
Think it was like 700. So, yeah.
Then you can easy do it and still save
about £300 a month.
Save like £300 a month. Maybe
could save £500 a month
really. So hey,
you can still do it.
You can spend like 500 on like drinking
and eating out and [ __ ] Not eating out,
but like food and save 600 a month. So yeah.
Yeah. That [ __ ] uh Terry tried saying
that he pays £1,900
for rent and he was trying to say before
like how 3k is nothing and [ __ ]
uh whereas look at what the guy's wearing, bro.
Like look at what the guy's wearing.
He's wearing shitty trainers.
They're fantasists. They're complete fantasists, bro.
What do you mean? How do I get away with
paying no bills? Because I don't have it
to give. If I don't have it, I don't
have it. How can I pay when I don't have it?
It's simple, bro. Is it the [ __ ]
Yeah, you could save. You could probably
save about 600 a month.
Depends what you have in that. Uh,
but bro, he doesn't have money.
But that's what I'm saying. But the guy
does not have no money. So why does he
keep talking about money? Look at what
he's wearing. Bro,
this guy trying to say that he can't
live off three grand a month. Bro, the
guy's living in La La Land.
La La Luck land.
And he was like, "Oh, you're selling." I
said, "I was selling my stuff cuz I was
moving house, you spastic." And then
he's talking about money and people
being broke. But bro, I ain't rocking them trainers.
I ain't rocking them [ __ ] trainers
that he's [ __ ] rocking the [ __ ] and
he's talking about people [ __ ] having
money, not having money. Jeez. Have you
seen them trainers?
He's another one that goes on like he's
got money like Virgin by and in reality
they literally have nothing.
Yeah, you don't even have to live off
500. You could you could say 300 or 250.
But I mean, if you have no bills, you
can you can live off £1,100 a month if
you got no bills.
Obviously, bro, if you got no builds and
[ __ ] then obviously you can. Um, but yeah,
it's like even Ant-Man said he would
save he would live on 50 a week for 4
months if it meant going to Thailand. So, yeah.
Yeah, you can live off
you can live off £500 a month.
Yeah, but I've already had my summer,
bro. I've already sort of had my summer.
I've already had my summer. Do you know
what I mean? So yeah,
this country is dead, bro. Like, I don't
know why you'd waste so much money in
this country. I've got money. I've still
got [ __ ] savings and [ __ ]
But yeah, bro. Like I ain't [ __ ] got um
Yeah, I already done a lot this summer
as well, bro. Sort of thing. And I've
been there, done it. Worn the t-shirt.
I've had expensive food. I've gone on
nights out. I've banged their schools.
I've banged women. I've gone traveling.
It's not like I didn't have it. You know
what I mean? Sometimes people have to
wake up to reality, bro. And everyone
does eventually. So that's it.
Now I'm 27. Yeah. I'm kind of sort of
like uh it's kind of the time where you
need to save and leave anyways. So it's
not the worst position to be in, bro. But
it's still a bit [ __ ] but it is what it
is, isn't it? No one can do anything in
it. Oh well,
it is what it is, man.
actually be more than 1,100 but I owe
some money so
yeah I'll be living off like £40 a week probably
cuz I need to save I have money to spend
I can go on dates I just want to save
cuz I need to save to get in in into
stuff I don't mind living off 4050£50 a
week I'm going gym now anyway. So,
I've got like 2K. So, it's not a problem.
Got designer clothes. It is what it is, man.
40 50. Yeah. Food shopping.
Obviously, I'm still going on this date,
bro. I done it in the [ __ ] winter,
bro. I was living off like [ __ ]
nothing even when I still had the house.
No, it's not bad. You can easily live
off £40 a week, bro. You can live off
£40 a week food shopping. There's
nothing bad about it.
Like, you're talking like you're
millionaires again, bro. You're you're
talking to someone that's had it, been
there, never had it, don't have it, have
had it. £40 a week food shopping, bro.
What part of I'm not going out drinking
do not understand?
You're not millionaires. Trust me. I
used to have the money, bro. Even back
in [ __ ] last January, bro. Like, it's
not bad. It's easily doable.
You can easily live off 40 a week. And
I'm not getting into this conversation,
bro, about money again. It's [ __ ]
ridiculous. It's pointless. It's boring.
You can £40 and make the food last a [ __ ] week.
Yes, the [ __ ] you can, bro. What the
[ __ ] I was actually even cooking at an
old house actually. And to be fair, I
used to spend about4
to be fair
when I Well, I used to do about £50
shopping and it would probably last
about 11 days, 12 days.
So, yeah, you you can live off six pound. Yeah.
How much do you spend on a week?
Okay, but you can't live off £40 a week.
I don't know what I'm talking about.
Yes, you're right and I'm wrong. Okay,
bro. Are you happy? Like the [ __ ]
bro? I'll resist temptations, bro. If
I'm saving, I'm saving. Simple,
bro. I've done my own food shopping at
different supermarkets. I know how these things cost.
So, how are you telling me, bro? I used
to do my food chopping. I used to get
pork chops. I used to get steak. I know
what I'm talking about, bro.
Like, I literally know what I'm talking
about. I used to do like 4050 shops and
I would still have I would still have
um I would still have money left.
And I'm telling you, I've done my own
food chopping. I used to do it every
Saturday. I used to spend about £50 and
bro, it would last about 10 11 days. Pork, steak.
Very easy. Very easy. I'd have like
[ __ ] bacon. I'd have like bacon. I
don't eat three times a day. I eat two
times a day. You'd have bacon, right?
Which is is like a couple of quid that's
in the breakfast. Pork chops are like3
pound for a meal then maybe the burgers
are like two pound something. buy that
in bulk, bro. You can easily make 40
pound last a week.
And even when I had loads of money, I
would not spend. How much are you
spending a week, bro?
So, yeah. Paul Ch, it is a charge
because I've done it. I'm not asking for
your opinion, bro. I've done it.
So, I literally have done it. And I
don't eat three times a day. I eat two
So there is a chance because I've
literally done it even when I used to
pay the expense. Even when I used to buy
the expensive things, bro, you could
probably even add a [ __ ] steak in
there to be honest.
So, yep. I factored in a Coke. Yes, I have.
And trust me, bro.
Well, bro, you're getting ripped off if
you're spending £1,000. Well, I weren't
even spending that when I used to eat
out all the time. So,
I think a lot of you people here are
actual fantasists. Like, are you
forgetting that I've still got money and
I've had loads of money and I've spent
money and bro, what you're saying does
not make any sense. And yes, I have
factored in coke
and you're not spending more than £45.
£45 maximum for the week.
45 50 maximum maximum maximum. It does
not cost more than £50 a week to eat,
buff. No way. And that's not even [ __ ] food.
Yeah, but that's you, bro. I don't need
to eat five, six times a day. When I go
gym and I clean up my diet, right? When
I go gym and I clean up my diet, bro,
I'm already making gains. Like, I was
already making gains. But that's but
that's you, bro. I've never ate five,
six times in my life in a day. Yeah,
I've ate three times in a day, but not
five, six meals. What the [ __ ] bro?
I've never heard anything like it.
But yeah, you you you can easily easily
easily for a week. Easily, bro. 100%.
Like I said, I was doing my food shop at
the old house when I had the fridge. So
I I I know how much these things cost, bro.
I used to do food shopping and [ __ ]
pans and [ __ ] and [ __ ] So
you you can eat very cheap, bro.
And it's good food as well. It's not
[ __ ] food. I was shopping. The pork was
like you'd get some pork chops like £3.
Yeah, lamb is expensive. Yeah.
Yeah. We used to have lamb. I used to
have lamb cooked for me.
But you can live off £50 a week easy.
You can live off 50 a week easy, bro. you know,
but he uh
could be anything. You can get cheap
stakes as well, bro. Like, you can get
cheap stakes or what? Like, yeah.
So you're trying to save £700
a month, Grezy. Yeah.
[ __ ] hell. But no, even chicken like,
bro, [ __ ] Yeah, you can do it on
[ __ ] £50 a week. Easy, bro.
You can easy
live off that.
Don't forget you buy a bulk of chicken,
right? That's two meals. Steak, bro, you
can easily do it on £50 a week.
Rezy, you can easily do on £50 a week.
It's very easy to live off 40 a week,
mate. There are some people that live on
£10 a week. So, what what do you spend a
week for a single person? What? £150?
So, hold on. Hold on. Let's get this
straight. Right. So a normal person that
eats two times a day, which is what most
people eat two times a day or for my
what I eat is two times a day. So what
are you spending what 150 a week? Never
in a million years, bro. Never. Bro,
there is people Oh my god. This guy is
This guy is living in La La Land. You
can tell, right? He's he's never done a
food shop for himself. He has never ever
ever done a a a food shop for himself,
bro. You can tell, bro. £50 is not even
a small amount of money for the week.
50 £55. Yeah. Is is more than enough,
bro. You, bro, you buy a bulk of
chicken, that's two meals.
Then you buy steak, that's another meal.
Yeah. You, bro, you can easily easily
live off 50 a week on food. On food.
So, you know what I mean? Yeah.
It's not even basic food, bro.
So, how how much do you think? How much
do you think it is?
So, how much? Well, yeah, Joe, it does.
When you buy things in bulk, it does.
Yes, it does. It does go to about £3.
So, Well, yeah, it does go to about £3
when you're buying chicken in bolt in
your chicken in No, it's not £3. Coke is
not £3. It's £229.
Make it right. So, bro, it's like that.
I used to go gym all the time, bro. And
I I'll be real with you. The most I'd
ever spend is about 70. So, that is
[ __ ] bro. And I And I was And I was making gains. You know,
you're a fantasist, bro.
You've never done a food shop for yourself, Joe?
I did not grow. I did grow, bro. I was making gains.
I was making gains, bro. Yes, I [ __ ]
was. I was going to the gym recently and
I was making gains, but I just didn't
have the time with the moving and [ __ ]
And we're not even talking about the
gym. We're talking about normal One
second, bro. We're talking about normal shopping.
And yes, I [ __ ] did. I was going to
the gym recently as well and I was and I
was having a milkshake
um every um
every after every after the workout.
So you have not you have not ever done a
food chop. This Joe has never ever done
a food chop.
Never ever done a food shop, bro. 100%.
He never has.
Never ever ever has. I'm not saying you
ain't been doing it for years, bro. I'm
just telling you that I was making
games. It doesn't take me going to the
gym long to make games, bro.
You get a bit of chicken, you're
overthinking it. Yeah.
Get a bit of chicken, bit of broccoli.
Yeah. Protein shake. Clean up your diet,
bro. you're you're you're you're
um you're you're thinking into it too much.
But anyways, Joe, how much do you spend
a week on a How much does a normal
person spend a week on food chopping? Yeah.
Yeah. I can show you very easy as well.
And bear in mind, this guy's not going
to the gym either. So yeah,
it's 100 a week. Nah, it ain't 100 a
week, mate. I have never spent up, bro.
I've done my food shopping about a
million times and I've never spent £100
a week. No [ __ ] way. So that must
mean, right? That must mean you're spending
So you're spending what? £15 a day on food?
Doesn't even make any sense. So you're
spending, think about mints, right? How
much mints is and how much pork is.
Yeah. You're not spending £100 a week on
[ __ ] food. No [ __ ] way, bro. I
never The only time, right, I was
spending £100 a week is when I was going
butchers and eating big ass steaks.
You're talking absolute [ __ ] bro. I'll
prove you wrong. I'm going to do some
food chopping tomorrow. Yeah. And we'll see.
Nah, bro. You are actually talking utter
[ __ ] Like you are talking bollocks.
Absolute bollocks, mate.
You would spend that eating out every [ __ ] day.
Yeah, you would spend that eating out
every day. That makes no sense. If you
was to eat out every day, you'd be
spending about £100 a week. So that
doesn't make no sense. That does not
make no sense. If you if you spent a100
pound on food, Yeah. like a normal
person shopping, that would last you for
about two weeks. Yeah.
That would literally
But yeah, I was growing, bro.
Bear in mind, I wasn't really really
really really skinny. I can just go to
the gym and just build muscle.
But you don't make no sense because if
you was to eat out every day, you'd be
spending £100. So that doesn't make sense.
That does not make no sense what you're
saying because you're saying right £100
a week on food. You would that is how
much you'd spend eating out.
You really really have no life
experience at all. Like I know I'm 27,
but you really really have no life
experience. And how I know cuz I speak
to Adman and he tells me the same thing,
you know, like, you know, he would do
£40 and it would last him.
Nah, it's not £100, bro.
Bro, I've got I've bought salmon. I've
bought salmon myself.
I bought salmon myself, but
I spent a lot of money on it when I
started the gym, you know.
Have you not seen the kind of meals I've ate? So,
but bro, I can I can eat twice a day and
I'll still build muscle. I don't know
about you, bro, but I was building
muscle and I weren't eat I was eating
like twice. Yeah, twice a day.
you overthink it too much gym thing,
bro. You don't need to do that. I never
done it and I've gain muscle. So, but
it's not £100. There's no way it's £100 a week.
There's no way it's £100 a week, bro.
No way. There's no way. Cuz when you buy
things in bulk,
yeah, I'm not saying I was your size,
bro. But I was building muscle. I was
toning up. I was building muscle. I
don't want to be your size, bro. I'm
just saying I was building muscle, bro.
And I weren't spending no [ __ ] 100
pound a week on food.
Yeah. It ain't 100 pound. You are
talking [ __ ] mate. You are talking
Yeah, but I'm not skinny. As soon as I
go to the gym, I start making gains. My
arms start getting big. I go there for
like two weeks, it starts coming and
when I go, it goes down.
I'm not average, bro. I'm not scrawny
like Virgin boy.
Oh, thank you, man.
Yeah, Greavves, you answer the question.
But it ain't £100. No way. This guy is
talking [ __ ] bro. Never in a million
years has my shopping ever come to £100. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, but I ain't skinny, bro. I'm
average. That's what I'm saying.
But I'm going to go I'm starting a gym
again tomorrow, bro. And I'll and I'll
show you anyways. When I'm done, I'll
show you. When I'm done, I'll show you anyways. Yeah,
I gain muscle quickly, bro.
I'm like average, so but it doesn't
matter anyways. This Joe guy.
No, I'm not skinny fat, bro. No, I'm not skinny fat.
No, I'm not skinny fat, mate. Everyone
saw me when I was going to the gym when
you weren't on YouTube. I was making gains.
Skinny fat. Yeah, you wish, bro.
You wish. Anyways, I'm going to do this
two meals a day anyways and I'll come
back to you in a couple of weeks.
You wish I was skinny fat, bro. You wish I was.
And I was eat I was eating twice, but
now I've lost it now cuz I couldn't go
cuz I I didn't have time to go.
Yeah, I couldn't go. I didn't have time. So yeah,
but anyone would think these people are
millionaires the way they talk like Joe
and Nelly, but in reality they're all
skin. It's mad, is it?
Oh, bro, look.
This Joe guy is talking out of his ass, bro.
He really is talking out of his ass.
And the maddest thing is, you know,
these people that pay rent and that
they're probably left with about £1,100
at the end of the month anyways.
That's another thing. But you £100 for
the week, you are talking [ __ ]
You spend that, bro, when you're when
you're eating out every day like what I
used to do.
Yeah, he's full of [ __ ] bro.
He is full of [ __ ]
£100 for a single person.
He is full of [ __ ] bro.
Yes, that was eaten out every day, you
[ __ ] idiot. That's what I just said.
Anyways, how much do you spend, man?
Yeah, but bro, these people are in
poverty. People like Joe.
Yeah. 20. Yeah.
Yeah. I've got a picture of my muscles
here. My little muscles. Oh, my little
That's what I was saying about 40, but
apparently you can't do it on£40.
I think these people in here are actually fantasists.
I think they're actual fantasists, bro.
Nah, bro. There's no point, bro. I'm not
talking about it anymore. There's no
You're right and I'm wrong. End off.
So, yeah. 40. Yeah.
I probably won't even be getting a
takeaway to be honest.
I need to save money, matey.
Yeah, that's [ __ ]
That is [ __ ]
I can actually do an online shop right now.
Yeah, that's what I was basically
saying, Greavvesy. I was saying the same thing,
but apparently you can't do it. So, yeah,
I've got more money than Terry as well.
only talks like he's uh
it's not going to be really hard though
cuz I've got savings. I think I've told
you about a million times I've got money
and you're still acting like I've not got money.
So you're talking like I'm on about £200
a month when I'm not. It's more than
enough to live on. I have more than enough money. So yeah.
new people don't even have £1,000, let
alone £1,000 a month. [ __ ] some of
them people are Lord J's. That's what
makes me laugh. They can't live of that.
They can't live of this, but in reality
they're all skin. Like, have you seen
[ __ ] talking about [ __ ] money as
well? You know,
it's madness. You're obsessed with
money. It's mad.
And bro, let me tell you something,
[ __ ] If you're spending £1,000
a month on eating, then think about how
much money you're wasting in a year.
That's like more full you. £1,000 a
month on food, bro. That's more fool
you, bro. No one else.
That doesn't even sound believable. That's like,
hold on a minute. So that's like, hold
on, that's like £12,000 in in a year on food, bro.
What the [ __ ]
Imagine that. That is a madness, bro.
That is a [ __ ]
Nah, bro. You're You're talking [ __ ] So
you're saying that you spend £250 a
month on food?
You're talking [ __ ] wank.
Bro, I think you're living in La La Land.
Yeah. And you don't have no idea what I have.
So, mind your own [ __ ] business as
well. But, bro, £250,
what's it? Not a week. Sorry. Not a
month, a week. So, you spend £250 a week on shopping?
Do you see how it's not even believable,
bro? You know, the maddest thing is,
bro, is even if you have it or you don't
have it, think of all that money you're
wasting every single week.
That is a madness, bro. What the [ __ ]
But at the end of the day, bro, you I
mean, I have no idea what people earn or
what people live like, but I do. When
you're sat on YouTube every day, because
we all know if you weren't skinned, you
wouldn't be on YouTube every day.
You wouldn't be on YouTube every day.
That's how we know that you people are
skinned, cuz you're on YouTube every day.
But when I say that, you don't say
anything bad to it. So, it's pointless, bro. So, yeah.
But yeah, you're right, bro. You're all
millionaires. You've all got all of this
money. Yet you're sat on YouTube every
day and I'm poor. Yeah, man. Really?
Yeah. Really, bro?
So, yeah, bro.
Cuz if you've got all this money, why
are you people sat on YouTube every day?
This is a question me and Monty asked
and you couldn't answer it.
That's another thing that never got answered.
This Do you not see how it all points to
you being skinn? I be real. I just want
to chill. I'm just trying to save a bit
of money. Not that I even have to to be
honest, but I just want to, you know?
But like at the end of the day, it's like,
oh, you still showing the same bum
chains money. Jesus, is this virgin
still, bro? This Hey, bro. Honestly,
yeah, this virgin is so obsessed with me
out here, bro. It's like it's unreal.
Nobody cares about your little housing
benefit that you keep showing.
Like [ __ ] hell. What? It makes it
makes you feel good that someone's got
more money than you that's better
looking than you. That makes you feel
good about your life. No, I think what
it is is you people have got [ __ ] lives.
You ain't got nothing and you wreaking
jealousy and that's why you come on here
every day. Escapism from your [ __ ] life. Yeah.
Like that's what it is. How can you
laugh at someone that's better looking
than you, that's got more money than
you? It's not something to laugh at.
It's actually something to cry. And and
that is the truth. That generally
generally is the truth right here, right now.
And why does this virgin keep showing
his housing benefit? Oh, bro, do I need
to go to the Do I need to go to the bank
again and beat you at the money game for
the millionth, excuse me, for the
millionth time? No one cares about your
little housing benefit. It's peanuts,
mate. You show the same thing every four
months, the same benefit money, the same
benefits every We've been seeing the
same amount and the same benefits for
the m for the past two months.
You know what I'm saying? We No, no, no.
Do you know what I'm saying, brother? I
pulled out six grand and you all run away.
Why do you keep showing your housing
benefit? You're not. You ain't got
money. I don't know why he keeps
thinking that he's got money. Think of
it, bro. Let's look at the actual
evidence here. Bedsit, go bed, trampy clothes.
You're not going brawled until you're
30. But you claim you've got all this
money. It doesn't make sense, bro. I can
tell you my lifestyle, bro. And to be
honest with you, it's it's it's it's
because because he's doing it because I
can't, bro. I've already shown £6,000
and you couldn't double it. You can't.
No. No. No. No. No. Brother. You can't.
Yeah. You've been shown money and you
couldn't double it. Let's Let's get it
right, bro. You know what I'm saying?
Let's get it right. You have been shown
thousands and you can't show nothing
close to it. So, stop projecting.
You know what I'm saying, bro? I can
show it now. I've got more money than
Bro, I just told you I've got about I've
got realistically about 2.5K.
Yeah, but you don't show me nothing. So,
I'm not showing you anything, brother.
I've gone out two times last week. I
spent about £200 on them two outings,
bro. I don't need to [ __ ] keep
showing you people money that ain't got
no money that have to try to convince
people that you've got money. You
understand, bro? It doesn't make sense.
I have shown thousands and thousands and
thousands and you don't show nothing.
That's what I'm saying to you. That's
why people don't do it. You know what I'm saying?
That at the end of the day, bro. Like, [ __ ] me.
It's a madness. Like, you have been
shown thousands. No one cares about your
shitty, thousand skint broke boy in a
bedsit. Do you understand, bro? Yeah.
And that's the truth. No one cares about
who's got designer clothes, who's got a
bed, who's got more money. I do. How
many times do I have to keep showing you money?
Like, how many times do I have to keep
showing you people that ain't got no
money money? I have shown the most money
on here. End of story. Listen, listen,
listen, listen. Let's get this straight
as a rat, right? I have shown more money
than anyone on this community. That says
it all. And I showed it for like [ __ ]
months and months and months and months
and no one could show me nothing. So
then I stopped showing money. Then I
literally just stopped showing money. It
got to a point where I just stopped
showing money because none of you skin
fins can show anything.
You know what I'm saying?
You know, and this virgin is so jealous
of me. He does not leave me alone. Have
you gone on his channel? Show assets.
You've been shown money. You've been
shown assets. It's your turn. Listen,
listen, listen, listen. You can show
£500, 600, 700. You need to stop showing
me money now. But you can't. So, there's
no point playing this game. There's no
point playing this game that you always
lose, bro. Listen, honestly. Yeah.
There's no point playing this game. You
have lost the money game months and
months in a row. You have been shown
thousands and thousands and thousands.
And you know what, bro? Even if I had
zero pounds right now, I still beat you
at the money game. There's no taking it
back. Like, bro, it's it's that's the
whole thing. I want to see £10,000 cash.
I've literally been begging for the past
like last summer, show me money. Show me
money. Show me money. And no one can
show me it. This is what I'm saying. So,
bro, there's no point. There's no point
starting a game you can't finish. It's
ridiculous. It's a waste of all of our time.
I want to see $10,000 in cash. End of
show. And if you can't show it,
come back to you know what I'm saying?
And this little rat is saying that I'm
bolded. Have you seen his ugly face?
Have you seen that ugly rat face with no
hair? Thinking that he's got bunny.
thinking that he's got money, bro. With
me shitty little£1,000, bro. I do you
know what? I'm so tempted to go to the
bank now and pull out money. Well, not
right now, obviously, cuz it's 9:00 in
the morning. And do I have to own this
little [ __ ] ugly disabled ratfaced
[ __ ] again? This ugly little virgin that
sucks his dad's dick for a few quid like
again and again and again. And this is
what I was trying to say to my man
earlier, bro, is that they don't stop.
These jealous people of me never stop.
That's why I'm deleting my channel.
That's exactly why I'm deleting my
channel. What's the point of coming on
here entertainers? A b entertaining,
bro. A bunch of people that are jealous
of me. I'm already beating them. They're
jealous of me. They can't leave me
alone. It's It's the truth. They have to
keep coming on YouTube reacting to me
every day. I know you don't like it,
Joe, but you see what I say. Coming on
YouTube every day, reacting to me,
triggered by me, and me owning them
every single day cuz they're jealous of
me. That's that is the cold hard truth.
You know, let's look at the evidence
here. Somebody that actually is brave
enough to show their face. So, cuz you
say that people come here and they try
to laugh at other people. Well, let's
just say, let's just tell you about
somebody that not showing their face.
Jamie Thompson, fat, ugly. Is it no
wonder he's so jealous of you? Fat,
ugly. He's got about a million chins.
One wonder why he's so jealous of you.
It all comes down to jealousy. And I
don't know why you don't why you don't
seem to actually acknowledge that.
You're better looking than them. You've
got more money than them. And it kills
them. Just like that Ronald Pump said
time and time and time again. It is the
truth. Because all through last summer,
all through last summer, right,
no one on this community has left me alone
because they're jealous of you. Because
if they were, they'd leave you alone.
Normal people would leave people alone,
you know. They would leave, but they
don't leave people alone, bro. That's the thing.
I have finished it. When I showed you £6,000,
I finished it when you couldn't show me
anything. And we're just having the same
argument over and over again. This is
why I'm leaving. This is the act. This
is exactly why I'm leaving. You You
people never stop, bro. You know what
I'm saying? You people never stop. You
jealous people never stop. This is
exactly what I'm saying with you people, bro.
You never ever ever ever ever stop.
It's like what I was telling you about
that Triple H thing, bro. It's not a
joke thing. I would have went there this
week, but we know how the cookie
crumbles with you people. We know what
you people do. It's not even making
excuses. We know what you [ __ ] mongos
do. You know, I leave, they win. I They
win, bro. I'm already winning. They're
the ones that are obsessed with me every
day and they won't leave me alone. I'm
winning by them being obsessed with me
every day, reacting to me every single
day. Now, bro, you're already winning.
Like, bro, you're already winning.
They're jealous of you every single day.
They can't stop talking about you.
You're already you're winning by living
in their head.
Like, bro, you're you're you're winning
by living in their head. They're jealous
of you. They won't leave you alone.
And then you're trying to try to like,
bro, you're all the same on here, bro.
You are all the [ __ ] same on here.
Every single one of you, you're all the same.
They win, yet they're jealous of me and
won't leave me alone every day. But
they're the ones that win, bro. They're
already living in jealousy and complete in denial.
How are they winning? You literally got
something that they want that they're
jealous of. They won't leave you alone.
They will not leave you alone, bro.
You're better looking than them. You've
got more money than them. That's the
only thing it points to, bro.
Sorry, I've got to shout these things,
but it's the truth.
Yeah, I am. No, none of you people
trigger anyone. I'm just talking about
how obsessed, bro. Do you reckon that
little ugly [ __ ] with a disabled dad
could could trigger anyone, bro? You
reckon that [ __ ] virgin skinned boy
that could that literally got starved by
his mom, the ugly [ __ ] could ever ever
trigger anyone, bro? Do you think
anybody could ever come to my area, bro,
and put up posters of me? Are you
[ __ ] lad? Do you think that [ __ ]
ugly disabled skinned [ __ ] with the
disabled dad could could ever trigger
me, bro? Come on. I weren't staffed by
my mom. I weren't abused. Bro, listen.
But this is what I'm saying. They are
reacting to me. Brother, brother,
brother, listen. They are reacting to
me. So, what you're saying does not make
any sense. Listen, bro. They are
reacting to me every day. This is what I
was trying to expect. Listen, this Joe
guy, bro, has got something wrong with
him. Yeah, I tried to explain this to
you yesterday and as much as I tried to
explain it, but they are reacting to me.
Listen, bro, they have got a channel on
me every day reacting, reacting,
stalking, reacting, reacting, reacting,
jealous of me, reacting. So, what you're
saying does not make any sense.
What you're saying does not make any you
are reacting to them reacting to you
every single day. It doesn't make any sense.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Yeah. You
know what I'm saying? You are literally
doing exactly the same thing when you
are on Reddit every single [ __ ] day
like and they're stalking you or they're
posting about you or they're writing
things about you. They are literally
reacting to you. They are being
triggered by you. So what you're saying
does not make any sense. Do you know
what I'm saying, bro? What you're saying
does not make any sense
because you are owning them by living in
their head. So you're saying you saying
that you're reacting does not make
sense. You know,
I could put a stop to their channel. How
could I put a stop to their channel, bro?
You know what I'm saying?
So what you're saying does not make any
sense because you're sat on YouTube
reacting every day. So yeah,
I weren't starved by my [ __ ] mom. I
don't suck my dad's disabled dick for
£500 that like I've got money. Bro, the
reason people don't play the money game
with you anymore because you run away.
Every single time I have shown my money,
you all run away. Just like every single
time somebody comes to your area, you
all run away. We understand now. I
understand now how the cookie crumbles.
Brother, I wasn't joking the other day.
I did calm down and it is nothing to be
said and calm down. And I am not going
anywhere because we know what you people
do when people go to your area. Bro, I
told I'm telling you straight right now,
bro. If I did not already know what it
was, I would have went to Newcastle on
Saturday and I would have start speaking
about that guy's kids. Trust me, bro.
You don't know me, bro. Laugh all you
want. No one gives a [ __ ] We all know.
We know your history, bro. Listen,
listen, listen, listen, listen, bro. No,
there's no calling bluff. You call my
bluff. You have been shown £6,000 and I
want to see 10. Back onto that triple
eight thing, bro. I would have went
there and started talking about these
kids, bro. I would have went there and
started talking about these [ __ ] kids
if I didn't know any better about what
you people do. And like I said, it's not
even new nor it's not even new
normalist. It's all of you. Oh, I would
have done it. Look, mother's life. I
would have done it, bro. And embarrassed
the [ __ ] for the full time. But there
you go, bro. Full time. We know what you
people do. Why do you think no one meets
you? Because you will pretend it doesn't
happen. That's why no one waste their
time on you, bro.
Just like you get shown money and time
and time and time and time again, no one
has shown me 10 grand. I mean, bro, I'm
waiting for literally £10,000 and still
no one's shown it to me.
The whole point of the money game is Oh, shut
is someone shows money and then you
double the money that they shut.
Been going on for years. I don't know
who started it, but someone started it.
I have literally shown £6,000 in cash
and no one has shown me anything close
to it. So therefore, I'm not
participating in this money game
anymore. If people want to keep
uploading their benefits and pretending
that they've got money, crack on, bro. I
don't care. Let them show a,000 1,200.
Bro, I don't care. I've my my job is
done in the money game. I show 6,000 and
no one showed me 10. It's supposed to be
12, but I just said, "Fuck it. Just show
me 10." Bro, my job is done, bro. I
don't need to I don't need to play these
silly little games with you anymore. You
have been shown thousands and thousands
and thousands in 50s as well, and none
of you can show anything.
So, come back, bro. It's that's it.
Yeah. A normal person will not have
cash, but you're telling me to withdraw cash.
um you would have £10,000 in cash. So yeah.
Um so what what normal person and and
let me let okay let me well let me
explain this to you. Well the only
reason I had I used to have money in
cash is cuz I used to go to the casino.
Then when I got banned from the casino
I've been paid rent in my accounts which
is where my money is in my accounts. So
you want me to withdraw £2,000 again?
£2.5,000 again for what exactly?
For what? You've already lost the money
game. If you don't have cash, then show
your bank account or show some of your
assets, I guess, but you've already lost
the money game. It's It's not for me to
participate in anymore. You've been shown £6,000
and you can't show nothing. That's where
we're at going from last summer. It's
not, oh yeah, you go and show two grand
again. No, you need to show me 10 grand.
Well, I'm not the one playing these childish games.
I'm not the one playing them.
So yeah, bro. Like you're [ __ ] hell,
bro. They can't flex on anything. I just
can't believe not one person show me 10
grand to be honest.
But bro, like I said, I know I'm not
going because I know what you people do
on here. Otherwise, I would have been going.
I might not have the money to waste, but
I would have wasted £4500 easily. But we
know what you will do on here.
But it doesn't matter what they're doing
on here, bro. Like, it really doesn't
matter. Like, you're coming on YouTube
obsessed and jealous every day for
reaction. I obviously have a better life
than you. Simple. I obviously have a
better life than you.
So, yeah, I clearly have a better life than you.
That guy actually thinks he's got money.
He actually thinks he's got money. But
look at look at bro. But to be honest
with you, it's not even just about money
as such. I've got designer clothes, got
a [ __ ] phone, got TV, got more money
than him. You know, it doesn't even it
doesn't necessarily mean just about
money. Do you know that?
You do realize it. It's other things.
I've got a bed as well. I don't live in
a bedset. That's another thing. It's all
It's a lot of these uh different things, you know. You
know what I'm saying, bro?
Bro, my life. Because am I the one on
YouTube every day stalking for reaction?
Listen, listen. I'm not the one on
YouTube stalking people every day for reaction.
You're clearly jealous of something.
Otherwise, logically, you would just
stop doing what you're doing.
So you would just stop doing what you're
doing. And I never said I wanted to die
over women. I said I'm not in the Nile.
Yeah. Lives in a bed with no bed in it.
Be like I'm I'll be real with you. I'm
not rich. I've got about 2K
2 and a halfK something like that. I'm
not [ __ ] rich. But I don't come on
YouTube pretending that I'm rich, bro.
Like, that's the difference. I'm a
realist. Like, me and Rocky Roy will
tell you like the truth, lad.
Do you know what I'm saying? I don't
come on YouTube pretending I'm [ __ ]
rich, mate. Do you know what I'm saying?
And look at it, bro. I've And Oh, [ __ ]
is [ __ ] bro. I That's another thing.
I've been to more places and I've
actually been on holiday more times than
that virgin. But he's got all this
money. Isn't that a madness? All this
money but living in poverty.
Who does that Who does that remind you of, bro?
No, bro. Bro, you literally Let's put
yourself in these people's position,
right? Imagine waking up every day
obsessed with someone, doing videos of
someone, trying to get a reaction,
whether you get a reaction or not.
Imagine doing that
every single day of your life, bro.
You're not living the life, bro. You're
living your worst life.
Yeah. You're You're honestly living your
worst life. Anyone that has to do that,
bro, is is living their worst life. And
they're clearly jealous of something. No
matter how you want to like try to no no.
So yeah, like you do this [ __ ]
One second, bro. So yeah, you didn't
answer my question anyways.
Oh, [ __ ] One sec.
Nah, matey. Nah. Nah.
Not me, matey.
But yeah, like you're clearly Anyways,
bro, you're clearly and so what if I
wanted to die over women, bro? That's
not like you're you're stalking me every
single day on YouTube. like you're
actually stalking. Like I don't actually
think you realize that uh LT that
they're actually stalking.
Like they're actually stalking, bro.
That that's the difference. They're
actually like proper stalking. I don't
think you know the difference. Yeah. What's
No, they don't stalk you, mate. They
don't stalk you. They don't stalk you
like they stalk me, mate.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. Bro. No.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Bye-bye, Virgin.
Bye-bye, Virgin. Do you know what up? Do
you know what I had that you'll never
have? Oh, this is another thing he was
doing yesterday before he was he was on
his job. Do you know Do you know Do you
know what I have that you'll never have?
better look, better looks, more money,
and I've never had to resort to disabled
women. That's what I have that you'll
never have. That's why you you're still
obsessed with Morgan and all of these
other people. That's what I have. Some
things I've had and h have and had that
you'll never have.
Yeah. More money, better looks, and have
had better women than you. And I've
never had to resort to disabled ever.
And my mom never ever starved me. Which
is probably why you can't even gain
weight to be honest because you've been
starved by your mother so much. It just
[ __ ] your metabolism up. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Yeah. He was going on about it
yesterday, Joe. I had to keep banning
all the accounts, bro. He was putting up
like [ __ ] pictures of USA. Is he?
[ __ ] hell. He is [ __ ] obsessed
with my sloppy seconds. Yeah,
mate. Like, I told you, bro. If you
actually went to the dentist and you
sorted your ugly face out, you might
actually be able to get some of these people
saying that you are diagnosed autistic.
So, probably not.
Sort him out then. Good one, Joe. You're
not going to get a reaction, bro. Nice try.
Nice try, bro. It's not going to work.
See, me and LT already knows the the the
the the tricks of the trades. Nice try,
though, bro. It's not going to work.
I mean, I tell you who else does that,
Harry Fraud. And you know, the thing is,
we went we both went to Liverpool and
Harry F didn't come out. But bro, you
know, to be honest, yeah, I had only
went once and he doesn't do it
constantly where this Triple H was doing
it constantly, bro. And like I said,
I've been there three times and he
wouldn't come out. That's why I thought
it was a bit cheeky, even though you
shouldn't react to these people. Um,
nothing is going to happen. Joe, bro,
I'm not Monty Man or Timmy. You need to
you need to remember that
it's not going to work. It's not going
to work. Stop it. Stop it, bro. Stop it.
It's not going to work. I say the same
thing to Harry P. It's not going to
work. It ain't going to work, mate.
It's not going to work. Stop it.
Just stop it. It's not going to work,
bro. Just stop it.
It ain't going to work.
I know what all what you people do on here now.
You're not getting an explanation.
That's what they want, LT. Don't you
understand? They want this explanation. Yeah.
But like I said, Yeah. Like honestly,
yeah. Back to the [ __ ] But they don't
do it for reaction, bro. They don't do
it for reaction because even if you
don't react, they still do it.
Yeah. My word means nothing. Yeah, I
know, bro. I know. I'm going to I'm
going to get you get you into this as
well, Aliy. I know my word don't mean
nothing, bro. Of course, I'm I accept
it. Like, I didn't go to Manchester two
times trying to meet Bomb. I didn't try
to meet Terry. I didn't go Liverpool and
everyone shut up. I didn't go to Mark
Samson's area two times. I went by his
house. He didn't show up. Um, I didn't
go to Virgin's area three times and had
him run into the police. None of these
things happened, bro. Oh, I know. I
know. My word don't mean anything. And
what? I admit it. None of them things ever happened.
None of them things ever happened, bro.
Like, I I admit it. Move on. You know,
I did go to America and I did go to Thailand.
Uh Timmy. Uh yeah, Timmy's quite tall.
Yeah. You see what I mean? They're all
the same, LT. This is what I'm saying,
bro. This is what they do. They do they
do it to you as well.
I I'm telling you this, man. Don't ever
meet any of these people on here ever again.
Like, do not ever ever meet anyone on
here ever again.
Like, don't, bro. It doesn't matter what
they say, what they do.
Just don't, bro. Just just don't ever
meet any of them ever again. But yeah.
Yep. I'm not lying about anything, matey.
But I might go Newcastle maybe next
month or something. I don't really have
a reason to go there anymore, though.
Yeah, it's easier to get [ __ ] and
stuff, but [ __ ] hell, bro.
I don't really see the point, bro.
Yeah. So, but to be honest with you, I
can actually thank you people here
because if it weren't for you, you would
have made me travel to the places I've
traveled to, which is how we all know
your [ __ ] houses. It's like LT, right? I
bet you he wouldn't have never went to
Scotland if it wasn't for uh Shagger. I
know I [ __ ] never would. would have
went to Scotland. So, in a way, thank you.
But you did show yourselves up [ __ ] a
lot. A lot. A lot. A lot. You showed
yourselves up, bro. Time and time again. Yeah.
And what's your problem with um foreign
women as well, Joe?
Yeah. Yeah. That's another thing. Isn't
it funny how you remember that, don't
you? But you forget everything else.
But here's where you're all [ __ ] up on
here, though, because we all know that
if that was LT doing that to me, you
would have been like, "Oh, yeah, he
didn't hit him." No, no, no, no, no, no,
no. He didn't hit him. No, no, no, no.
Like, we all know what you do on it, bro.
Like, yeah, that's my whole point. It's
funny how you remember that, but you
don't um but you don't but you don't um
remember what I've done. Even though the
things I done LT was before that,
but it's funny how they remember that.
Like, let me tell you something, bro. Yeah.
I'm not saying, "Oh, that's not an L or
no, no, no, no." But bro, if I ever got
my hands on that nons legs, bro, it
wouldn't be a sorry. It would not be a
[ __ ] sorry, bro. He would be, bro, I
would lit, bro. You don't know what I
would do. Trust me. So, I mean, imagine
LT spent a year trying to lure me and
then he didn't even do anything. Like,
Prime didn't do anything. Okay, well, he
made you say sorry, whatever. But, you
know, like you you would say that's not
good enough. Like you've all got your
own little agendas.
That's all you do. You've got your own
little agendas on here. So
that's it, man.
Yeah. I mean, think about it. Uh uh LT,
right? When do we hear about when I went
to Bomb two times, when I went to Mark
Samson three times, when I went to
Nonss? When I went for Trevor Dawson?
Like there's other ones as well. There's
a few other ones as well, but they're
the main ones. When do we ever hear
about it? And Terry as well.
So, that's quite a few certified ones,
but we never hear about it.
So, it just doesn't make any sense.
Those are actual guaranteed W's right
there. Some of them even happened before
that whole prime thing, but we don't
hear about this.
And that Mark Samson one was the worst
one, bro. Like, no one could even say
anything. Like, no one no one could even
say, "Oh, like, oh yeah, well, he he
made you run away." Like, there was
nothing, bro. I went there twice on two
different occasions and I was live for
hours, bro. and they still don't
acknowledge it. He can come back on here
pretending to call people out and people
would just pretend like nothing's ever happened.
Nothing's ever happened. You know what
I'm saying, bro? Like they would just he
would come on here like say he does a
video right now calling me out,
pretending to call me out. Everyone
would would side with him, you know? Yeah.
And why is she not sustainable, Joe?
Well, this one's not meeting, which is
good. So, I've only got this one to
meet, which means I can obviously save
money now. So, yeah. Yep.
So, you're not going to go back home.
We're going to fall in love. So,
what makes you say fall so what? Just
because they're foreign, they're going
to go back home.
But but that but that's what I'm trying
to say out that he will come back on
here and he will start calling people
out and people will pretend like nothing
happened. That's that's what I'm trying
to say to you.
It's just like that little virgin. We
all know he doesn't meet anyone. We all
this is so mad about this and this is
how you know that this virgin doesn't do
it for reaction that he's called the
police many times, right? He's actually
got you in court, which doesn't make any
sense because if you went to prison,
then you would be no longer be able to
react. So then they've done that and
then they still come on YouTube doing
what they do. That is that is true
jealousy, bro. That is true true jealousy.
They tried to get me kicked out the pub
the other week as well. Oh, you didn't
see that? But yeah,
was it last Thursday.
Yeah, but it's never going to happen,
bro. But how many times though are you
going to keep No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Like, no
one's ever going to get hurt. You people
have tried your best for years and you
failed. That's the thing. Like, that's
that's what I'm saying.
Get hurt by who, bro? Who could possibly
hurt me on this community? Like,
you you It's mad.
Who could you any of you possibly hurt?
You're all little weasels. But it
doesn't matter the weasel anyways.
They're all biased on there. Uh
but yeah, anyways.
Yeah, Virgin Boy will never stop, bro.
My my best bet is just just leave
leave YouTube, bro.
But honestly, my best bet is just to leave YouTube.
I've only had a few hours. Yeah.
Yeah. Rick Mason has some proper L's.
Yeah. Proper LS.
But look at me. I'm still back living my best life.
Isn't it mad how all of the things
they've tried over the years, you you're
still you're still living a better life than them?
That's mad at, isn't it? Oh [ __ ] Yeah. Anyways,
well, I'm living a better life than them.
Nah, not even, bro. Listen, LG, I've
been off of here for weeks, mate.
Weeks and weeks and weeks, bro.
You should have come to Weather Spoons
last Thursday, LT. Man, you would have
loved it. Me and these grummy lads was
chatting up some birds, having baby Guinness. Ah,
no. No. I don't like Rick's mate. He's a [ __ ] stirer.
Yeah, he's a [ __ ] stirer. Like you and
that Morgan. You were [ __ ] stoned with
that Morgan. He was LT. [Laughter] [Music] Yeah.
Yeah. I was off here because I have
money. I do have money. I've literally
told you about a million times I've got
money and you're still saying I don't
have money. Okay, bro. I don't have
money. I'm skin.
>> No, I was off here because I was
actually living with people and I had
stuff to do.
So I can dull out now and live life.
I've got money. The [ __ ] you idiot.
And also look at that statement that
you've just said, bro. You've just said
that you was off here because you had
money and and enjoying your life.
So that must mean that you people are on
YouTube over there all skin [Music]
and you ain't got life.
There we go. all skin and ain't got a life.
You really think I can't go out tomorrow
and go in the piss? You really think I
going to go out Thursday, Friday,
Saturday and go out on the piss?
>> Bro, I could do it very easily.
>> Um, no. Because I'm saving for a little
bit. I'm just chilling out for a little
bit. So, no, not at all. Not at all.
Because I've already shown money. I've
already proven that I've got money. I've literally
got out Thursday and I've gone out Saturday,
which I spent about 150 160. So, how can
I be skinn? But I know all of you people
in large days are all skint
Oh, you're all relaxing and saving as
well. Well, that's not actually going to
wash because you're on here. So, what
you've just been relaxing and saving for years?
Oh, really? What? for years and years
and years. Well, all through the summer,
all through the spring.
Yeah. Really, really, really. Well, to
be honest with you, you wouldn't all be
saving because everyone is in everyone's
skin in your mind.
Yeah. So, what you're just saving?
>> I don't even know why I'm saving. I
don't use a saber. I can go out whenever I want.
But I don't know. I'm just I don't know,
man. I just got kind of got bored of it.
Virgin boy. Where's Virgin boy? Yeah. [ __ ] man.
And actually, I was actually busy
working. This is why I couldn't come on
YouTube. Also proves that you people
here don't work that s YouTube every day.
Sat on YouTube every day.
All this money.
But they're sat on YouTube every day.
Makes you wonder, doesn't it?
Makes me wonder. They work. They've got
all this money, but they're sat on
YouTube every day.
Yeah, that's why I'm doing it. But I
don't even necessarily need to do it.
You know, even when I was on three grand
a month, I was still saving
because my my biggest fear going broke.
I don't want to be like virgin legs.
[ __ ] Red Star, mate. [ __ ] skin on
YouTube every day.
I must have banged about 300 escorts in
my life. [ __ ] hell. I wasted a lot of
money on escorts.
That's for sure, bro. Huh?
That's what I think most of these people
are on that JSA. Like they don't even
get a grand a month. They don't even get
£1,100 a month. They do not even get
£1,100 a month because you know with
£1,100 if you got no outgoings. You can
still go out. You can still do things.
cuz you can still just do [ __ ] bro. Of
course you can. That's why that's what
makes me think, bro, that they are on
that £300 a month,
you know? That's what makes me think
they're on £300 a month. Yeah,
it's not 100 pound minimum. Where have
you got a 100 pound minimum?
Where have you got 100 pound minimum?
Some 60, some 70. 100 pound minimum. Uh yeah,
now I fancy some McDonald's now.
Yeah, my phone was like 31. [Music] Yeah.
28. I'm not 28. I didn't know I was 28.
That's news to me. [ __ ]
I didn't know I was [ __ ] 28, bro.
I'm I I kind of like this position
because now I need to find another way
to make money. So, it's actually um it's
actually quite exciting, you know.
Yes. Yes. I'm almost 30. If that makes
if that if that makes you feel better
about you being in your 30s. Yes. I'm
I'm almost 30. Yep. I'm almost 30, bro.
Yeah, I'm almost 30, bro. I'm 30
tomorrow. If that makes you feel better,
then let it make you feel better, bro.
I'm almost 30 and I'm getting old, just like you.
So, yeah, I've banged so many escorts,
bro. And this is what I mean, like,
people need to get rid of times, bro.
But I done this escort. I done this
AMSAM [ __ ] when I was like 23
and now Virgin Boy is just doing it. Jeez,
that's crazy, is it? Virgin Boy is
[ __ ] doing it.
That's mad. Who the [ __ ] would go to
Amsterdam of all places with with That's
how you know he's copying my holidays,
bro. It's getting weird.
Virgin boy's cop. He's also copying my
holidays. It's very rare that the first
place someone goes to is Amsterdam. Jeez, [ __ ]
That's not normally someone's first
holiday. Like, I legit know people that
ain't even gone there.
Have you ever gone to Amsterdam, Joe?
>> Yeah, I went by myself. I was a [ __ ]
Yeah, but it's not normally someone's
first holiday. Like he's even copied me
with my holidays.
Yeah, obviously can't go on a plane fear
flying in it.
No, not me.
I didn't comment.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ] Someone else said,
"Dudes." Oh, yeah. Do you know what? I
was speaking to some guy here. He said
he's going Blackpool for seven days. I
said, "Seven days is a bit too much."
You would have thought two or three days.
Uh, well, it was my first holiday. Bye-bye, Virgin.
But yeah, he he actually has talking
about yourself. Yep. I'm the skin loser,
yet you're the ones that sat on YouTube
all day, every day. So, the real skinned ones.
Yeah. All All you got to say, Yeah. You
don't need to say that. No, you're skin,
you're this, you're that. All you've got
to say is, "Okay, well, you're the ones
that are sat on YouTube every day. Can't
get off it. So, you must be the skid ones.
You must be the the well and truly
skinn." That's all you got to say to
them. And to that, they have no argument.
They have no argument to that cuz it's the truth.
But anyways, yeah. So,
yeah, I think I went there for three days, Amsterdam. Yeah,
I don't know if I think it was 3 days. I
can't remember. It was a long time.
Yeah, I can go and talk about myself.
I'm a big I'm a big strong Turkish man. [Music]
I saw that guy on Instagram who I met in a hostel.
It was a good experience, you know,
staying at a hostel, you know,
it's a good experience at least for one
night, you know.
Cost me about £800 that [ __ ]
Amsterdam thing. Yeah, it cost me about 800 quid.
I wasn't being suicidaly. I was just
saying that I'm not in denial about how
[ __ ] up the dating game is.
Answer your question, I should be
defending women. I've been with women.
I've had sex with them. But I can't
defend them. They're all stuck up.
They're all the same. And I've had more
women than these simps that defend them.
That's where it doesn't make any sense.
But they're in denial. Just like that
guy in Canada, I said I said to him at
the Weather Spooners the other day. I
said to him, "You can laugh, but you're
immature." Because in 10 years, you
won't be laughing when you can't find
someone. You have to go [ __ ]
Thailand. Oh, you'll be [ __ ] then
because in 10 years, Thailand won't even
be worth going to.
So, actually, you won't even be going
there. You will actually be you'd
actually be genuinely [ __ ] So, it's
like these people are just in denial,
man. They're really, really, really in denial.
They get no women or they've had no
women or they can't get women anymore
and they're always worse off than you
somehow, but they still defend women.
Like, there's not a problem. It's mad.
That's the bit I don't get. Honestly,
You you would have thought it'd be the
other way around, but again, I'm not in
the Nile. So, these people are in the
They defend. They defend women and [ __ ]
I said I was going to go out and jump in
tomorrow, but nah, I can't be asked.
No, I can't be [ __ ] bro.
I've got a gym tomorrow, baby.
I've got a gym tomorrow.
My friend said, "Do you prefer my life
working hard for 6 to800 a month?"
Bro, you know the thing is LT, I'll be
real with you. Yeah.
Yeah. Do you know when I went out on
Thursday, I just went out cuz I wanted
to go out like most times.
Like I just go out because I want to go
out. Like I had a lot of stress because
of the house and the tenants. And I just
needed to go out. I don't really go out
much anymore. I did not go out for
women, but obviously I done approaches
when I was out. And the thing that is
[ __ ] up is the whole dating thing. I
couldn't help but acknowledge how [ __ ]
up it is.
How [ __ ] up it was.
And I didn't go out there for that. But
I'm thinking I think it's mad how you
can be like decent looking and you can't
even find anyone. That's that's what I
was saying was [ __ ] up. I said you
might as well like be born Timmy Eldridge. Like
it's like unless you're a [ __ ]
big [ __ ] Tik Tocker nowadays or
and that's the only thing I tell you the
truth. Yeah. That's the only thing that
annoyed me with a house
is like having a house for all of them
years and getting the money is that you
didn't find anyone in them years. That's
when you should have you should have
found someone. That's the only thing I thought of.
It was only a little bit, 20% of it.
Like, but I still thought of it. I just
thought it was strange, lad.
But I I just thought I just think it was
strange how like you didn't get anyone
in them years.
And And what the thing is, LT is it
seems to have actually gotten worse. You
know, like, you know, 18 months ago, two
years ago, it was bad, but you'd still
get the odd thing, one night stand,
fingering, kissing, dates. It you'd
actually get you'd actually get some
things. It was just hard back then like
it's supposed to be, but now it's gotten
worse. Now, it seems that it has
actually gotten worse.
Now, I'm not saying it's like that for everyone, but
it's obviously like it for more people
than not. Clearly,
it doesn't matter, bro. You get my
point. It could be anything. Do you
remember that Sig that USA Izzy, that
[ __ ] other one that stand? You can't
get anyone anymore.
You can't even get nothing. You can't
even get a conversation out of the [ __ ]
you know? You can't even get a
conversation out of them.
Um, I'll be 28 in October. Yeah.
It seems definitely that it's gotten worse.
It seems that it has gotten worse though.
Do you remember when I said I was going
to paint myself black to get all the
women out here? Paint yourself black.
That was funny, isn't it? Yeah.
That's funny, isn't it?
That is drugs.
That's drugs, isn't it?
No, you don't have Oh, you don't have cuz you're
a big strong black man, bro.
But if I look like Mon [ __ ] money
Mike M, whatever the [ __ ] he calls
himself or Timmy, I could accept it. But
you shouldn't have to accept it. You
know, you you can be decent looking, you
can [ __ ] live by yourself, whatever,
bro. You can't get nothing. What the [ __ ]
Do you know? Oh, man.
So, what you're telling me you wouldn't
bang that USA, is he?
You really wouldn't bang her? I'd bang
the [ __ ] again
if I had the chance.
Yeah, I I [ __ ] would, bro.
I'd give it a whirl. Wouldn't you?
Yeah, I would, bro. [ __ ] damn, I [ __ ] would.
Wouldn't you, Joe?
But listen, LT on a on a on a all jokes
aside, yeah, we need to shut down this
[ __ ] law J, bro.
Like, listen to me, bro. I I'll tell you
something. Yeah. If you if you book me
the flights, I will go. I will go. I've
already proven that I've flown before
and stuff. Why Why would I want you to
waste your money? It doesn't make any
sense. Like, why would I want you to
waste 60 70 80?
You I I I will I will schedule it, bro.
You know, you can bring your little
popcorn. I really want to [ __ ] own
that [ __ ] bro. Like, you don't
understand. You really don't, bro.
I I want to be the new king.
You know what I'm saying? I want to go
there and run the city, bro. I ain't
trolling as well. I'm being deadly serious, bro.
I want to go there and run the city. Do
you know what I mean? Take over.
Take that crap, bro. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
You know, the maddest thing is, bro, is
you do all of that [ __ ] Yeah.
And then you come back live and two of
them will be like, "Oh, uh, yeah, man.
Big up you. Big up you." And then what
would happen next week is he'd come back
live and it was if nothing ever happened. So yeah,
I think I would just be embarrassing,
bro. No, seriously, I couldn't do that,
bro. I'd be it'd be an embarrassment to
my mom and [ __ ] family and that. Like
you're still dealing with this with this
[ __ ] on YouTube.
>> A bro that is embarrassing. I I couldn't do seriously.
>> Yeah, I couldn't do it, bro. You have Yep.
Yeah, I'm still here, bro.
Do you want to join it? join. Bro,
call me before you go bed, bro. I just I
need to talk to you quickly, bro. I'm
going to play some GTA and that
I need to actually talk to you, bro.
So, can you call me so I can end this
live stream? I need to play some GTA, bro.
Yeah, call me man
before you go bed.
waiting for this [ __ ] thing, bro.
Yeah, give us a bell, LT, bro. Give us a little bell.
I miss our little late night chat.
I'll hook you up with Shasha.
You love Shasha, don't you?
>> You love Shasha.
She's I still don't speak to my other
sister, you know, bro.
Just some siblings just get better than
others, you know. I don't talk to them,
but as obviously I speak to my mom and
my other sister and [ __ ] Um, yeah.
Oh, bless you.
That's how I always knew you wanted that
Morgan. You always wanted to get in
there little knickknacks.
You always wanted to get in there little knick-knocks.
Bless you. Do you remember when you say
you was going America it
when I used to
message you in the morning pissing you
off for that, bro? Yeah. Bless you. So yeah. Oh [ __ ]
No, he's my little friend.
Oh, I want to [ __ ] me, man. I want to [ __ ] [ __ ]
Oh, that Jane was messaging me as well.
I just ignore her now.
Well, I've been for years. I know your
little tricks. It's not going to work.
You just want me to start flirting with
you so you can put it all over YouTube.
It's not going to work, mate. [ __ ] off, old woman. Yeah.
It's not going to work, mate. It's not
going to work.
You know, and sometimes we get hoy and
stuff and Yeah, it's not going to work,
mate. You're just trying to feel wanted
and feel loved
so you and Mark can have your little
laughs. It ain't going to work, mate. It
ain't going to work. Yeah.
You need to call me, bro. One sec.
Hold on. I'm doing something, bro.
He works and he gets £800 a month.
Steven already gets £800 a month. Jeez.
Yeah, but he's foreign in it. So what
they do is they get money and then
[ __ ] they they get money and then
once they pay rent and send money back
home they have nothing and it's every month
And then they just go and then they just
do it in circles. Yeah.
London's expensive, right? It Yeah.
So if you get like a delivery job, you
can get like one point well you can make
like three four you can make like £400 a week
which you could probably get like 1.7
1.8 which is more than enough for a
single person with no outgoings.
But obviously without something like
that there's nothing you really can do.
star, bro. But is what it is, man.
You need to be.
Oh yeah. Why did you steal the bike,
Eli? That weren't nice. Why?
Why did you do that? You [ __ ]
Yeah, this woman I meet, bro, I need to
Yeah, I need to try and find a
self-employed job, bro.
Oh [ __ ] This is going to be hard, bro.
[ __ ] hell, man. But to be honest with
you, I I didn't like the responsibility
from the house. I didn't like the
responsibility of it all. And
it was a lot of stress, even though
people didn't know, but it was. So yeah. Yep.
If I get another self-employed job
again, I'll never do that. [ __ ] that, bro.
The other man's thing. I had to sleep.
The other day before the bay come, I had
to sleep. Yeah, I had to sleep in a
house by myself. You would have been
scared to do that, wouldn't you, LT? You
silly sausage. You would have been
scared to do that alone, would you?
You would have been scared, would it?
Yeah, you would have been scared, isn't it?
Yeah, LG would have been scared, bro.
Just a couple.
You know the how are they even going to
help you, bro? Cuz you're not African.
You can't even get help in your own [ __ ] country.
Like you can't even get
m I was in sub. I don't know what you're
talking about, bro. Nah, I don't know
what you're on about. Not me.
Not me, matey.
Not me. I don't know what you're talking about.
Well, I don't know what the [ __ ] you're
talking about, man,
but they're [ __ ] idiots.
You got to cut the ground out the wankers.
At least I got to cut the ground out,
mate. And my designer clothes and [ __ ] No. Nah, bro. Nah.
How would they catch me, bro? I told
everyone to go. I told everyone to leave
before they came like a couple of days before.
actually owe one of their money like 250
but someone stole my afterge after shave.
Um obviously it lost its smell and
everything like it was dumb. So
obviously I'm not going to give them the money back.
They were trying to like take the TV and
they oh yeah like we're going to hold
your TV and that. I like you're not
going to hold my TV cuz I was smashing
in front of you. Um but I sold
everything anyways cuz I had to leave. I
had to leave because I didn't want to
take everything with me. And obviously
now they've took the fake Dior t-shirt
and the Dior after shave. I'm just
saying my [ __ ] has gone missing. One of
you people took it. So which that after
shave is probably worth around £20 now
cuz it loses its smell.
I've had I must have had about a year
that after shave it loses its smell. So
it's pointless really stealing it. But yeah,
nonetheless someone did. So,
someone did [ __ ] steal it, bro. I
might actually buy one for this date.
It's going to cost like what?
Maybe 90. I might buy a new after shave
to go on this date.
Yeah. No, because most of them they they
paid up until the date. Yeah, I only
owed one of them money,
but I I'm I'm not giving them it back. So, yeah. So, yeah,
it's [ __ ] isn't it?
So, yeah, bro.
But um yeah, the afterlate I'm not even
going to get a big after save now
because it just loses its smell. I don't
even know why they would steal it, bro.
It's so stupid.
Yeah. And then then I was knocking on
the door. They were going they thought I
was going to beat them up and that in
it. I like, "Oh, we're not opening the
door." I said, "Open the [ __ ] door."
That's what I said. Yeah. It was a madness.
It was special then, but it's over now.
So, ain't no one can try and tell me
they've ever had more stress than me.
Imagine losing a house, right? Having to
move, losing your income from the house,
and also happen to lose friends from the
house as well, cuz I was living there.
Ain't no one can tell me about stress, bro.
I'm surprised I'm still alive, to be
honest with you. So,
so no one can actually tell you about
stress. It's not like you lost like 2,3400.
You lost most of your income.
So, as well, and there's no other ways
to make money, so you're basically
[ __ ] for now. I need to answer the
phone to some. Yeah, I knew it was going
to happen, which is why I was doing the Uber.
Who caused all of this? Um, well, the
cancel because I offered to pay the rent
and they wouldn't let me. They wouldn't
let me. They wouldn't put the name of my teny.
Oh, who caused it? No one. Nothing to do
with people on YouTube. They were trying
to get the house back for years. It
wasn't anything to do with anyone on YouTube,
but I mean, I offered to pay them and
they just wouldn't have it. So now it's
all been boarded up now and know now no
one will have it.
I I would have paid the rent every every
week as well.
It wasn't anything to do with anyone on
YouTube. They were trying to get a house
back for years and years and years, you
know, and got a couple of grand out of
it anyway. So [ __ ] them.
Nah, mate. I had more stress.
I had to lose income.
I had to lose a house. I had to move.
And then I also ruined other people's
life in the process because they
they were used to being there. We were
like all like [ __ ] a family because
we would see each other every day. So
then I we was getting withdrawal
symptoms from each other. I've lost a
house and I've lost income.
And obviously they were [ __ ] in
different ways than I was [ __ ] So I
just said put to put it bluntly to put
it bluntly we're all [ __ ] really we're
and now even being here I can actually
see my mental health is actually bad
when I didn't have any mental med I
didn't have really any problems when I
was in Stratford
I was good bro I was normal like yeah
now I'm just sort of isolated but bro
that's stress that's stress and you lost
most your income as well you didn't lose
like £500 pound. You lost most of it.
And it's not like you said you weren't
going to pay for the house as well, you know.
So, it's not like they weren't going to get money.
Yeah. You can't live on your own
anyways. We've already been over this.
The council don't help you unless you're
African. Not even Jamaican. No, no, just
African, bro. They're straight up
racist. They don't even help like
[ __ ] Pakistani people. They're all
[ __ ] as well. So yeah,
I remember when Bomb Bomb used to come
in here and he he used to think right
that you you can just live by yourself.
It's not as easy as that. You know,
there's a lot of people in London that
they live they either live with their
parents or they live in a box room.
No, it's not even being racist. It is
the truth. It is literally the truth.
Like I'm a British citizen, right? you
know, I'm down of having like foot
conditions and [ __ ] and they just don't
care. They don't care, bro. But, you
know, a lot of people in London, they
still live with their parents or they
live like in a box room. A lot of people
live like that. A lot of people live in
shared accommodation because they can't
afford to live.
But, you know, like Virgin Boy, he's
never had to work. He's been he's just
been put in a bedsit,
you know, been put in a bedsit, right?
Never worked a day in his life. been put
in a bedsit and he seems to think that's being independent
whereas I was actually independent
because I was actually working and I had
a house to run. So yeah,
so that's the problem you got.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] up. That [ __ ] needs to
be made to work, bro. At least once in
his life. Can't believe he's never
worked in his life. I've worked a few times.
>> I always say to him, man, I don't even
live with my mom, but I I used to say to him,
I'd rather live with my mom than live in
that [ __ ] [ __ ] bed that you're in.
And he would never ever have anything to
say to that. I'd rather live with my mom
than live in a shitty bed like you, [ __ ]
hole. See, that house was actually a
good [ __ ] house.
It had like four bedrooms, but it was at
to be fair it was falling apart to be honest.
And you know, to be fair, I wouldn't
live alone. I would live with a [ __ ]
I would actually live with a dog.
It's not good living by yourself either,
really, cuz that's how you can have
mental health and [ __ ]
Like cuz I was living with them, I could
never go mad. I could never go mad cuz
we was always like
I don't know, man. It felt like they
were family cuz we lived like for with
each other for so long.
And I knew some of them for years and
we'd all have laughs and jokes. And then
when like when I was living like that, I
was like, I don't think it's a good idea
I ever live alone because, you know,
there'd be some times where they'd have
seconds of you being like depressed and
[ __ ] but then you'd always laughing and
making jokes with each other. So that's
why I never really had any mental health
when I was there. But if you live by yourself,
you would get mental health 100% unless
you had a dog. So,
I would have stayed in that house
forever to be honest with you if I could. But
probably just bought a dog to be honest
with you. Yeah.
Yeah. They get everything, bro. They get everything.
Especially them Africans. They get
everything, bro. They do. Yeah.
They definitely definitely do. It's [ __ ]
I hate this country.
Yeah, they get everything.
Why do you think there's so many people
sending [ __ ] weed nowadays
and [ __ ] [ __ ] You know what I mean?
>> No, bro. It is Africans. It is a Listen,
bro. Listen, listen, listen. Let me ask
you this question. Yeah.
It's not people from my side, bro.
Because people from Pakistan don't even
get houses. So, how how do you work that
one out? Like, I know one guy. He hasn't
even found a room yet. So, how can it be
them? Think of it, bro. Why do you never
see homeless African people and you only
see homeless British people? That tells
you all you need to know, bro.
That tells you all you need to know cuz
why do you never ever see any homeless
people but British? You know
that's dodgy, bro. That is [ __ ] proper dodgy.
I always used to say to the like, "What
do you get from being here?" Cuz
what do you get from being here, bro?
Like cuz it seems like you they would be
working to be skimp every month. It's mad. Yeah.
It is mad, isn't it? But yeah,
it is disgusting, bro. It is disgusting.
And you're saying that it's my people,
but bro, I'm I'm theoretically white.
I'm theoretically English. Yeah, you
might be quarter Turkish, but bro,
you're white. Simple. I've got Scottish.
I've got Irish. I've got German. Like,
you're less than half Turkish, brother.
You're white. Simple. And that's another
thing, bro. It doesn't really matter
what you look. It's actually what you
are. You're white. You might as well not
even be any Turkish. You're basically white.
English like there's that's literally
it. Yeah, you might look more than you
are because [ __ ] sometimes that
happens, you know, but you you are theoretically white,
you know. Most these people that you
meet from Pakistani, what are they?
They're full Pakistan. Rarely are they
half and they are never quarter. So
theoretically, you actually are white.
You actually are English. Yeah. You know,
I am I am co I am Caucasian. I'm quarter
Turkish, which is less than half. I'm
more white than I am Turkish. Do you not
understand what quarter means?
So yeah, actually you are white because
you're quarter Turkish.
You're mixed race, which means you're
half black. I'm literally the smallest
bit Turkish. That's all I am.
Yeah, but I might not look Caucasian,
but I am Caucasian. That's what I'm
trying to say to you. I could look fully
Turkish, but I'm caught. That's the
whole point I'm trying to make.
Listen, my grandma was was was Scottish.
My granddad was Turkish. He come here
when he was 16. They both spoke English.
My dad was fully white and then my mom
was half Turkish. They both spoke
English. All only English was spoken in
the household. I'm caught Turkish, so
you're basically a white,
you know. But yeah, like what? You know
what I'm saying? Yeah, but you're Yeah,
but you're full black. That's the
difference. You're fully black.
That's what I'm saying. But you're fully
black. You're not caught a black.
That's what I'm saying. But
either way, bro, like you're a British
citizen. You born here. Your family's
from here. Your your grandparents are
from here. It's irrelevant. Like
that's what I'm saying, bro.
So, your parents weren't born here. My
parents were born here.
That's what I'm saying. Your parents
weren't born here, bro. My parents
weren't born here.
And my my grandparents may as well been
been born here as well. That's what I'm
That's what I'm saying.
Do you know what I'm saying, Captain?
Yeah, but it doesn't matter whether your
mom is more British than me. Your
parents weren't born here. Mine was. So,
do you know what I'm saying, Captain?
Bro, it's like a Right, listen, bro.
It's like a Pakistani guy, right? Being
born here and being westernized. The
ones that like to say they're Muslim,
but they're they're actually not Muslim,
are they? But, and then we'll ask them
where they're from, bro. Bro, it could
be like even a Romanian person. They
would they would say that they're from
here, but their parents weren't born
here and they and they don't even speak
English, so therefore they're not from
here. You know, that's that's that's my
that's my whole like judgment on that.
If someone for example is from Pakistan
and their family have come over here,
even though they sound English and they
speak Pakistan, they're Pakistan,
they're not English. No, that's that
that's my whole thing on it
because you told me that your dad wasn't born here.
But either way, bro, we're British
citizens. It doesn't matter. [ __ ] me,
bro. [ __ ] You know, I've got, you know,
I've got a foot condition and I'm I'm a
British citizen and they don't care.
It's as simple as that. Like, so yeah,
but that that would I would then say
that that person is not English cuz they
can't be. How could they? You know, so
them black cockney make me die, bro. I
come across one the other day.
Them black cockneys are funny, bro. Is
it? Them black cockneys. Is it?
Yeah, it's funny, mate. Yeah,
it's looking a bit dodge.
It's a bit dodge.
But yeah, either way, like it's [ __ ]
It is [ __ ] bro. It is [ __ ] The country's [ __ ]
The dating, the [ __ ] you know.
Yeah. Do you know there's a scrap guy?
He's from the Caribbean. I used to pay
him to clear the garden out of that. He
We called him the scrap guy. And we
always used to say, "You all right, Captain?
All right, captain."
He kept coming on the door for money.
Yeah. I made him a burger.
You'd like it in that house, LT, when
everybody was there. Bro, you would have
liked it in that house. You'd never have
to grow up
when everybody was there. Bro, I should
have invited you, man. You'd like it
though. You'd like it in that house, LT.
You'd never have to grow up anymore.
Do you get it? Oh, that house used to be
rammed, bro. Yeah.
That Why do you think I was trying to
invite you for the barbecue and that,
bro? We had it all planned out, mate.
You weren't going to come out of the
house, mate. You weren't going to come
out of that house. You never have to
grow up. All your all your stresses
would go away.
All your stresses would go away, bro.
That's why I kept telling you to come to
the barbecue, man.
We was going to bad you up, bro. You
don't understand. We was going to bad
you up, bro.
No, I'm joking, bro. Well, you should
you should have actually come to the
barbecue, man. It was tasty.
It was quite tasty. You know,
you'd like it down here, son. You never
have to grow up. I love that little catchphrase.
When they're night, yeah.
No, I'm joking, bro. But you should have
come to the barbecue, man. It was an
actual invitation. Why do you come?
Why do you come, brother? Instagram user.
One second, bro. Yeah, bro. Can you call
me quickly anyways, bro? I need to speak to you
quickly, bro, for like 10 minutes.
We need your assistance. We need your
assistance right away.
I need to be quiet, bro.
No. LT, don't go.
What do you think, Steven? £1,100 a
month, no bills. Can you live off it? Yeah.
I used to live off Les and I used to go gym. Yeah.
[ __ ] it up, bro. Yeah.
really you need about 1.6 six, but you know.
No. What do you think, Nicolo? 1100
pound a month, no bills. I think I think
you could live off it.
Yeah, of course you could.
Yeah, it was funny, bro. Yeah,
but they always run to the boys in blue.
Yeah, you could you could live off it. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm not even used to living a high
life anymore, bro.
Been there, done it, worn a t-shirt.
I'm just happy to have 2K to be honest. So,
but it is hard. Yeah,
I ain't going back to gambling, bro. I
can't I can't go back to gambling, bro.
There's no way.
I need to find a job within the next month, honestly.
Grand a month, mate. Grand a month.
Yeah. Well, it's actually more than
that. It's actually a bit over 11. But yeah,
there's nothing I can do about it, bro.
There's nothing I can do. Still got my
stonies and that. Still got my designer
clothes. I can't do anything, bro.
So, you can't do Gambling Nicolo because
obviously if it goes the other way,
you're [ __ ] That's the problem.
Say you get £700 now. Yeah. Say you got
640 650. Yeah. And then you go and then
you go and you gamble, bro. If you lose, you're [ __ ]
So you're [ __ ] for a month.
So you can't you can't do that, bro.
It's not a good life.
[ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that. Imagine that.
Nah, bro. Give me nightmares.
Saying I actually fancy a McDonald's now. Yeah.
How much is a couple of grand though?
Yeah, but you can't risk it. You can't
I've got a couple of grand now, but still.
See, I'm being very careful with money.
Even though I don't need to. Like, I can
get McDonald's right now. I just don't want to.
I need to try and readjust, you know?
But yeah, you're set for a couple of Oh, [ __ ]
I need to really start like I'm trying
to save just for like a rainy day sort of thing. Um,
yeah. It's hard, isn't it? No, man.
Just need to get another delivery job.
If I can get a delivery job, I'll be
set. I will be set then, bro.
cuz I can earn anything back that I just
spend. So, I'll be good.
See, that Uber thing was good, bro.
Like, cuz it's like free money, you
know, and they used to pay every week. Yeah.
But I can't go I'm not going McDonald's.
I am craving a McDonald's, but nah, bro.
I love one in a couple of days. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, he's a fantasy. The most I ever
spent on the night out was £700,
but I was like
£700, but I was [ __ ] um
Oh, I spent about £700 once and that was
pushing it. But it was good cuz I want
all that money back. Yeah.
And I used to like get it back cuz I
wanted a car. That was good. Yeah. That
was that that was that time of that
19year-old. Was it was it when I met her?
I used to take the gambling losses out
on her. Yeah. I remember that. But no,
the first time I met her, I think it was
the first time I met her as well. I was
living a life, bro.
I put £300 in, I got 900 out. I spent
£700 that day, bro. Madness. I swear down.
But again, we can't live the high life
forever, bro. We need to kind of just
settle down now. Anyways,
yeah, I was living that high life. So,
yeah, Nicolo, the whole thing about
going out Thursday, Saturday is like
going out as much as possible, trying to meet someone
before obviously it all stops, you see,
trying to find a prime candidate for baby Peter.
No, it wasn't Stratford. It was central London.
Yeah, we me and him have a lovehate
relationship, bro. Like the amount of
times I used to clean them casinos out. Oh, mate.
I used to clean them out, bro.
So, I had a life, you know. I'm not
there's no regrets, you know, like
I wouldn't live that life now, bro. Even
if I had loads and loads of money
because it would be like I would just
leave the country.
That's what I'd be doing. So, it kind of
happened at the right time.
We're talking like a couple of years ago, bro.
I'll never forget that. That one I went
on a date with from Ukraine, bro. I was
like, I went gambling with her, bro. And
I walked her home
and then I walked her home. No, I walked
her to a train station. I was like, I'm
going I'm going back to that casino,
bro. And that's when I got that £1,600.
Remember, bro, I was like, I'm not
taking those [ __ ] L's, bro. I'm
cleaning them out. Trust me. H. Oh, it's
good times, bro. Used to go back to the
old neester calls. It was good times,
bro. It was good times. It was get
making good money, you know. So, yeah.
They're just something to look back on,
you know, them times.
So, like, they were good. They're good
times to look back on, bro. But we can
never live that life again cuz
it wouldn't have the same buzz cuz we're
older now anyways. Like so Mr. B, I used
to rinse them, bro. I used to [ __ ]
rinse them bastards.
And I went out and then the funniest
thing is the guy would let me in the
front door cuz he used to say, "Oh,
you're not coming in. You're on sense."
So then I went the other door, the other
way. And imagine that. And then I walked
out the same door with the £1,600 where
he wouldn't let me in. He must have been
[ __ ] Oh, he must have hated me, bro.
And obviously they can't take the money
off you if you want it. He must have
hated me, bro. But yeah, we saw each
other again um few weeks ago. We shook
hands like we'll never forget each other, man.
the guy that
the guy that would let me in the casino
happened to try and avoid him.
They I used to clean them every
Thursday, bro. I used I used to take
them to the cleaners like
same thing. Win money, goals,
try to get w women come back with money.
It was just living the life nonstop
living their life, bro. You know,
I actually was living a life, bro, if
you think about it. Yeah. But the funny
thing is your mortal status never changed,
which was strange. Your mortal status
never changed in any of them years, Mr.
B, which I found quite strange. Yeah,
but I don't give a [ __ ] I'm lucky to
have 2K, bro. [ __ ] [ __ ] them, you know.
But it was constant, bro. Like constant
and constant and constant. Just going to
them casinos winning.
Oh, I can't believe it, bro. Then I used
to just go and use escorts. [ __ ] bro.
And like I said, they're just something
to look back on. I wouldn't go back to
that life. I wouldn't relive that life
cuz it would have the same feel to it now.
I hate gambling now. So, you know,
and that four grand as well. Oh, [ __ ]
hell, bro. I'll never forget that.
That was a day I was supposed to go to
America as well. I had some really good
times. Like really good times
cuz uh my friend from the army,
oh, do you want to come out, man? Do you
want to come out?
I said, bro, it's a Wednesday. I don't
really want to go out, but I had nothing
better to do. I was like, okay, let's go out.
went out approaching these women. Then
we went to Burger King. I was, "Oh, do
you want to you want to come to casino?"
But I just like to gamble, man, before I uh
before I go home sort of thing. Gambled
[ __ ] got one [ __ ] 50 to four
grand. I couldn't believe it, bro. I
bro, I swear. I couldn't believe it.
I couldn't believe it, bro. That was a madness.
They paid it in cash as well. I I had to
walk out the casino with £4 grand cash.
Gave my mom £200.
We were living the life, bro. Trust me.
So I I had a good life, you know, like.
Oh [ __ ] I just popped this bubble.
Water come out. [ __ ]
Yeah, man. To be honest, we had a very
good life out that house. Do you know
what I mean?
I just want to travel now before I'm too
old. Obviously, I'm not going to have as
much money to do it, but obviously he's saving it.
All the restaurants, Nicolo.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Miss those days, you know.
Really do miss those days.
I miss them days, bro. Oh, [ __ ] Well, I
don't miss them cuz like I said, I
wouldn't relive there anyways if I could. Madness.
Madness. I was a mad bastard, bro. Yeah.
So, where do you go from now, Nicolo?
I was living the life, bro.
But my income has took quite a uh decline.
Wasn't TGIs. I haven't had TGIs, bro.
I've only had them one that once in my
life, but [ __ ] I was living that life, bro.
USA Izzy, who paid for USA Izzy's little stakes?
But trust me, one day you'll look back
on it, bro, and you think like you
actually really had some good times, bro.
Really, really had some good times, man.
Madness, isn't it?
Like I said, I'm still happy to have
money, you know? Two grand is still a lot. [ __ ]
still get money and [ __ ] but
what do you do? Madness. [Music]
It was good times. But it was good Yeah.
Uh nice garments.
If you actually look back on it, it's is
actually something to It's good, bro. To
look back on it.
6K before Justin Cash.
Yes. Angus steakhouse.
Oh, mate. I was living the life.
Living that life, bro. Living that life.
You reckon I could ever live that life again?
I wouldn't want to, bro. To be honest,
that sounds mad to say I wouldn't want
to, but like
all I want to do now is just work and
then just go out once a week
and then just leave the country. Bro,
I'm not I wouldn't do all that [ __ ] all over again,
you know? I wouldn't do all of that all
over again, bro.
I don't even do the cyber approaches anymore.
Me and USA had some good food that day, bro. Good food.
You have been paying the Somalian £250
for a blow up anyway.
[ __ ] hell. We were so We had so much
money going up. We were just like stupid with it.
We were just stupid with it, you know.
Even what my mom said.
It's not going to work. She's got her own house. Oh [ __ ]
How's that going to work when when they
both got their own house?
Doesn't make sense, bro.
No. Hopefully I get another delivery job
soon, so I'll be able to make money on that. Um, [ __ ]
Don't worry. We'll find a way out.
We'll find a way, bro. Don't you worry about that. Yeah.
Yeah, you see Triple H.
Yeah, that Triple H is still going at it
again. There we go.
Oh, he's going.
Yeah, I want your opinion. Uh-huh.
Yeah. I want your opinion, bro. Yeah.
So, I've just been trying to meet someone.
Have a baby with a woman. Move in with
your mom and then sublet that house. But
then you'd have to look after baby
Peter. [ __ ] that.
But yeah, my mom was right. She said
that like one day you'll look back on it
like all the good times that you didn't have.
Then you'll think, "Wow, that's mad."
Good times, bro. But yeah, I want your opinion.
Do you want my opinion?
They're all [ __ ] Yeah, bro.
Why does Virgin Boy keep trying to act
like he's got money? Nicolo
is obsessed with me.
Why does he keep showing the same
£1,000, bro? I don't understand.
It's embarrassing. Why does he keep
showing his housing benefit? You know,
one day, right, they're going to try and
take that housing benefit out and it's
going to be too late and he's going to
have to put it all back in and explain
why the money's not in there to pay the housing benefit. Jesus Christ.
I've never known someone so skin to
think they've got money. E N
thinking that they've got money. E it's a mad
I mean Nikolai listen bro. Have you ever
seen so many10 notes in your life?
I've never seen so many10 pound notes in my life. He literally
tries to act like he's got money.
It's really weird. It's very strange.
It's It's It's so weird,
isn't it, bro?
I could pull out probably over 2K right
now, bro. But I ain't doing it. I don't
need to do it. I've already beat I've
already won the money game, bro. Yeah,
these people never ever ever stop, do
they, bro? I'm coming off of this
YouTuber. I'm going to have to come off
this YouTube, matey.
They never ever stopped, did they? It's unbelievable.
I don't know how they how they like do
this year in year out.
I don't know how, bro. Do Do you not Do
you not think it's weird how they do
this year in year out?
They've got to be skinned virgins
to do this year in year out. They've got
to be uh of course you can, bro. They've
got to be skinned virgins.
It's like what Monty man said. They
wouldn't be on it. It's to save atmosphere.
Do you remember? It's to save atmosphere.
No, no, no.
It's sing my mommy. Hello.
How long do you reckon 2K can last? Even Howard,
maybe two months, 3 months.
Maybe two months, two and a half months. Oh, probably. Uh,
no more £300 or nights out, matey.
Ah, USA Izzy.
USA Izzy has nice boobies.
Virgin boy would never know what nice
boobs feel like. Will he Nicolola?
Cera ain't got none.
That [ __ ] the wolf ain't got none.
Nah, you will never know. You will never
know what it's like to be with a normal woman. Really? Nah.
I can't believe I'm younger than him and
I have a better life than him.
Been more places, got more money, had
more women. Do you think that's where
the jealousy comes from? cuz obviously
we're quite like we're quite different
uh ages as well.
Yeah. Do you know what that's also where
I've I've thought about this. You know,
cuz obviously I'm already 27, I Virgin
Boy is 31.
Maybe that's where the jealousy comes from actually.
The age is quite a difference as well.
Hm. That's something to think of. Just
think about it, bro.
Think of lives. Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ] YouTube
for a second. Think of lives, right?
I've got teeth. I don't look like a rat.
I'm not a virgin. I don't live in a bedsit.
I've got more money.
And I've been more places, had a better
life. Now, even though for three years,
been with more women and then look at
that virgin's life.
Think about it, bro. Just and tell me
what you what conclusion that you come to. H,
what conclusion did you come to?
Huh. Strange, isn't it?
I'm not sure.
Better clothes, more money, better looking.
Seems like jealousy to me. What about you? Yeah, man.
What does it come down to to you? I
think it is jealousy. Me,
I generally think it is jealousy. Like,
am I delusional, bro? Like, if I do
sound delusional, bro, tell me like I and
you know what I'm saying? Like,
I might do a video on this, bro.
Like if I am if I do sound delusional,
let me know I sound delusional.
We need to actually put our lives
together, bro. Someone we actually know, you know?
I'm not sure.
Oh my god. You've got crippling anxiety t-shirts.
What the [ __ ] is that? What law is selling now?
Well, the only one that's got anxiety is
you. But I didn't know that you made
merch on it. I have crippling anxiety.
That's you and your followers.
Jesus Christ. You should be giving it to
them for free, bro. What the [ __ ] Yeah,
I think Joe doesn't actually uh get my
point. You know that I don't think Joe
actually understands my point.
It's that like he's telling you that
you're reacting to them, but they're the
ones that are reacting to you every day,
which is the whole point he uh didn't
really understand is that they're
reacting to get a reaction, which could
only show what they've got in their life. Nothing.
I'm actually going to do a video on
this. You know, this needs to be addressed
cuz we go round and round and round and
round in circles, bro.
doesn't really get anywhere.
You You don't understand that your life
is revolving around someone every single
day, which is worse than a reaction,
you know? That's what I'm This is what I
was trying to explain,
you know. And he says that when you're
explaining these things, you're
reacting. But you're not reacting.
You're you're you're telling the truth
what they are.
reacted is going mad and smashing things
and punching. They are jealous of me.
It's it's that's it. And then when you
say that I say these things, you're
saying that I'm [ __ ] reacting.
I'm going to do a video on this, bro.
Yeah, I'm going to do a video on this. I think
you better give me thumbs up, bro.
Yeah, bro. You better give me a thumbs
up, bro. I'm going to come down and I'm
going to [ __ ] do you in, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm going to do you in, bro. If you don't,
you [ __ ] Yeah, [ __ ]