Well, you got to put over there and you
need to put it down the road cuz you're
a bit soft. Yeah.
Yeah. I need I need to start like
[ __ ] charging for this sick content.
Me, bro. Train approaches and everything, bro.
You know, a certain person's over. We
never allow him to do it. I need to
start charging for this content. Mark this.
I need to start
for the good old content, M. [ __ ] man.
Yesterday was a long one.
Let's see. Um uh
yeah, man. I actually got it on the
train so [ __ ] mad bast didn't I [ __ ]
Let me see if my little temps are coming. Say,
you know what?
This whole time,
it's not having a plan B. And that's
what everybody needs is a plan B.
There's no point you doing this and your
and you doing that if you ain't got a
plan B, matey.
Let me see. Where the [ __ ] are these coming?
Yeah, you need a [ __ ]
You need a plan B, mate. If you ain't
got a plan B,
then it's all pointless.
Yeah, he Hey, bro. She should have said
that to my friend. They should have
called me over. I would have told her to
mind her own [ __ ] business.
Yesterday I was with that [ __ ] Indonesian guy. Yeah, ma'am.
Not really, bro. Um I don't want one
approach on the street sober on the
train sober one train station one on the street
um three sober I got one number then I
just got five numbers in total I have to
text them yet
um yeah not really bro but I don't I
don't I don't need to that's the risk
you take when you go out at the end of
the day you know what it is and you need
a plan B that's the I was lying in bed
just yesterday playing a bit of Franklin
and I'm thinking, bro, you need you need
a plan B. That's your problem. You ain't
got no plan B.
And that's where you're going wrong.
Either, you know, leaving the country or
leave, you know, use medical. There's no
plan B. This is why you'll keep going
around in circles until you have a plan B.
And I'm free sober. Anyways, I recorded
two of them. I recorded a train one, but
then I'm like, bro, you can't really
moan because it's it you you play it at
your own risk, you know? You know that
it's to be honest with you, bro. I do
this [ __ ] cuz I'm not working anymore.
So like I have literally nothing better
to do. Otherwise, I wouldn't even be
doing doing this [ __ ] It's like what
Antman it's like it's like when Ant-Man
done this, it was a temporary temporary
thing cuz where is he now? He's
Thailand. If he really thought he had
hope here, he would he wouldn't have
left. He wouldn't have moved to a third
world country because he knows deep down
there is there is no hope here. But it
is something to do and that's that's it.
There is no hope here, bro.
You're playing like mad lottery odds now
that it's it's literally gotten that
bad. But I did get five numbers, so I'll
text them in a bit and see. I got like
two in in the first hour. Then it sort
of died down. But
no, it won't never change.
Really? That's like [ __ ] what? 13
numbers in three days. >> Jesus.
One sec. I need to listen to his voice
though. It doesn't play when I'm on
here. One sec. Two seconds, man.
I'm sorry about that. I was just
listening to something.
Yeah, man. [ __ ]
That's the story about Mory, matey.
Wouldn't you like to [ __ ] know?
Kind of scared to text these five
numbers, man. Cuz like if they don't
reply, they don't go anywhere. I'm kind
of [ __ ] [ __ ] basically. And know
must have spent about £100 yesterday,
man. [ __ ] Cuz a round cost like £24.
But you know, you can't take money with
you when you die. So,
but yeah, you need you need a plan B,
bro. This is supposed to be a temporary
this is supposed to be a temporary thing. Cuz
I lie in bed thinking that you can't do
this forever, bro. You can't do this for
the rest of your life. You know, going
out expecting things to change them and
not changing and then there's no plan B
and then there's nothing to look forward
to because then it's just all pointless.
Your life is in a you're like you're living
you're living in a loop.
If you have something booked for two
months, go out every week, count the
count the weeks down and then you know
you're gone. That's what you should do.
Something like that.
That's why it's a cycle really.
But it's all good, man.
We had on three approaches yesterday. I
mean to get one number three approaches
over was pretty good to be honest.
Then I put the [ __ ] drunk and it
started [ __ ] raining. Oh [ __ ]
I'm a bad bastard.
I'm actually a bad [ __ ] bastard.
Where are you, boss?
Just some food.
How about some nice piggies?
I told it
these piggies, baby. Da
da da da da da da da da da da. Ta
in your [ __ ] up. [Laughter] Oh [ __ ] Oh, man. Let's take this.
So the power is [ __ ] [ __ ] Uh
yeah, it could be the weekend all at
once, but I went out yesterday.
need to go get some n.
I am giving up though. I'm just waiting
so I can work again so we can do plan B.
It's all right going out in England, but
you need a plan B. If you ain't got a
plan B, you you're completely [ __ ] screwed.
Unless you um unless you have a plan B,
you're in a loop. So,
What? What do you really really want to do? [Music]
>> What happened to my savings? I've still
got my savings.
Why you Why are you asking that anyways?
Does it matter what happened to my
savings? I've got savings, bro. I've got
plenty of money. Yeah.
No, you don't have to get out of London.
You have to get out of England.
It's not London. You have to get out of England.
There's some nice [ __ ] Asian women as
well, bro. I really know. You need to
get out of England. That's what you need
to do. But if you ain't got a plan B,
then you're [ __ ] There's no point. No
one's forcing you to stay here.
It doesn't, bro. Don't worry about me
and what I've got. Worry about yourself.
Don't you worry about me and what I've
got. Worry about yourself.
We're not talking about money. Why are
you talking about money?
You don't need to worry about what I've got.
No offense, matey. Why are you so
worried about what happened to my
savings and how much I've got and why
I'm working this and why I'm working
that? What the [ __ ]
No, I just said I went out on Thursday.
I don't need to go out on the weekend.
You got brain damage.
But yeah, we No, we basically need a
plan B, but not a plan. And then after
like the second approach and I got a
number on the third one, but then I was
like the approach on the third one, but
and then I was kind of but then I was
like, but there's no point like even
trying to moan because you're risking
when you're going out. You know, you
know this. And yeah, we know it's [ __ ]
up that like a good-looking person
shouldn't be be struggling today, but
you are and it is like that and it's
never going to change. So, I mean, you
can moan about it all day long,
but you ain't even got a plan B.
Yep, I've got two approaching videos,
but I'm not putting them up. I don't entertain bongos.
Yeah, I actually did record two
yesterday, actually, funny enough. Well,
I don't even record them anymore, but
not putting them up. Don't entertain mongos. Yeah.
Um, so unless you got a plan B, bro,
then it's pointless, you know?
You need a plan. Actually, you need a
plan B and then you need a plan C.
But like I said, I do this [ __ ] cuz I'm
bored. I I'm not working at a minute.
So, you're just bored. That's the reason
I do this [ __ ]
you know? That's the reason I do it. Me,
I got these five numbers. I need to text them.
Still ain't text him yet. I will do though.
You asking McFry cookook still your life.
You asking otherwise you wouldn't be on
YouTube all day.
That's all you need to say to these
people. Yeah. If they had money, they
wouldn't be on YouTube all day.
But yeah, I'm not putting any
approaching videos up for you. Bug guys.
Go ask your lost Go ask your Lord
Savior. Savior to do it. The one that
claims he doesn't have anxiety. Go tell
your Lord Savior to do it. These
approaches and put them up, bro. >> Yeah.
But anyways, yeah, without a plan B,
you're completely [ __ ]
Well, actually, I think a bit
differently now to be honest with you, Joe.
So, actually, actually, well, actually,
it was almost how you predicted
actually, but I mean, I got five
numbers. I mean, you said six numbers.
That's a bit much. I got five. I done
three approaches. So, bro, I actually
recorded two of them. I done one on the
train. I know I'm a crazy bastard.
So, I got five. And after the second
one, I was kind of thinking, oh, like
this is [ __ ] up. But then I thought,
hold on a minute, right? You you take
this risk every time you go out. You
know that this is going to happen. And
then you know this is I was like, you
know, this is going to happen. So you
can't really moan. I mean, yeah, we know
it is [ __ ] up that you're good-looking
and you can't find someone in your own
country, but it's not it's only getting
worse. So what? Unless you've got a plan
B, we can go around in circles all day
and think, "Yeah, it's [ __ ] up." But
at the end of the day, you don't even
have a plan B. So if you ain't got a plan B,
um then it's pointless you even moaning.
This is supposed to be a temporary
thing. I was lying in bed yesterday
thinking about this long
long and long and long and long and long
a long long a long time. I was thinking about this
and I'm thinking, look at this, right?
you and I've come to the conclusion of
the I was trying to figure this [ __ ] out
and I'm thinking look listen yeah
Ant-Man's not even tried nearly 10% as
you have and he's in Thailand so at the
end of the day he must have known that
there's no hope here and I'm thinking
hold on a minute why do you why have you
why do you do this
and it actually comes down to boredom
I was home by midnight yeah I went out
at 1:00 Um, yeah, I went out at 1:00
p.m. and I come out at midnight. Yeah.
Anyways, stop coming on my channel
trying to troll, bro. You've done this a
few times. [ __ ] off. So, anyways, Joe,
as I was saying, as unless you have a
Unless you uh No one's out at that time,
lots of people out at that time.
Anyways, bye-bye now. So, unless you've
got a plan B, it's pointless.
That's where I was going wrong all this
time. You need a plan B.
I think that's right, isn't it, Joe? You
need a you need a plan B otherwise
I mean there's nothing to really moan about.
It's no I I you should see like I was
saying you need to see these people
nowadays bro what these women are what
what these guys are with. I see this
black guy he was with an absolute ma
like even now that tells you like even
the the people that you see now with the
with women right and you look at these
women you're thinking bro this is [ __ ]
Well, actually, there's a plan B and
there's a plan C. So, the plan B is to
work and use escorts and go Thailand.
Simple. That's the plan B. If there's no
plan B, it's relentless.
It doesn't make sense. This is supposed
to be a temporary thing, something to
look forward to before you leave. You're
not leaving. So, if you're not leaving,
then it's going to continuously be the
same thing for years. So, you got no one
to blame but yourself, really.
That's what I basically that's the
conclusion that I've come come to. Like
you want to stay here and not leave and
it's only going to get worse. It's going
to get worse and worse and worse and
worse and worse and worse and worse. So
leave. You need a you need a you need a
you need um
so yeah that's and I think that I think
that's actually good to be honest.
So yeah, there's no point moaning about
this bro. It's never going to change.
So why moan about it, bro? It is what it is.
It is [ __ ] up, but it is never going
to change. So you get used to it or
leave. I don't think you can get used to
it, though. It's not normal. It ain't
But um so yeah, you need to leave
literally leave the country. So I need
to get some piggies in a bit.
Yeah, I recorded two approaching videos.
I don't I don't want on a train. I don't
want a train station job. But I don't
really want to entertain Mongos.
Let your Lord save you do that.
Well, nowadays a lot more people are
going to Thailand. A lot more people are
going to Thailand. Like that's why when
I was working, I barely went out cuz I
know that there's no hope in this
country. Truth be told, I only do it
because I'm bored. I do it out of
[ __ ] boredom to be honest with you. I
ain't got nothing to do. If I can't work
at the minute, I can't work. So that's
the thing. Like I I I you generally do
it out of boredom.
That's that that is what it is.
If you think in your in your head,
you'll find out these answers. So
it will never change.
It won't ever it will it will never change.
I'll mess these numbers later and we'll
see, but it will never change.
it it has no chance of changing
because of the amount you've tried and
[ __ ] and the amount of places you've
been. You see, it's not like a normal
person that goes on and off dating apps.
Um, you've tried more than anyone in the
world. That's what separates you. Um,
yeah, you've never had a girl. You're
still a virgin. That's why you resort to sing.
I know, bro. But you've never had a
girl. You You ain't got the balls to approach.
You ain't got the balls.
Again, somebody that doesn't want to
accept the truth that there's too many
stuck up [ __ ] in this country. We
know the truth. We just don't moan about it.
You know, all of these people like, you
this guy right now, they're all in
denial. They all don't think there's
problems. But there is problems. Look at
[ __ ] Belg. Look at all of the these
people with women nowadays. [ __ ] mters.
Like black guys resorting to that now.
Jesus Christ. You know what I'm saying?
It tells you all you need to know.
They're dating down down. I know men
always have dated down, but bro, that is next level.
And then you'll see the odd thing with
like a good-looking woman, but that's
how you know it's [ __ ] bro.
That's what actually makes me feel bad.
That's how you know it's [ __ ] up.
I got five yesterday. I haven't text them yet.
Nah, mate. Nah, it's not take what you
can get. Well, yeah. Yeah. Well, to be
true. Well, that is the truth actually.
Yeah, you do. You can take what you can.
And obviously, they're desperate and
that's all they can get. You know, some
white people, some black people, because
they wouldn't be with them if they could
get better. That's how you know they're
down there, bro. That's how you know
that there's a problem in this country
when you're seeing it. You're seeing it everywhere now.
That's how you know they're down, man. Bro,
I was um with the Indonesian guy
yesterday. He's so scared. Bro,
you five numbers got to be 1 million to me.
Well, considering you've been all over
the country and there's no point trying
to explain it to you brain damage
people. You'll never understand anyways.
you just nothing processes in your
brain. Anyways, I I met this Indonesian
guy yesterday. I bought us a round of
drinks. It cost £24 and the [ __ ] was
still scared to approach. He's such a
[ __ ] And then obviously where where I
was approaching in the club, right? I
didn't realize this person had black
boyfriend. And then she Okay. Then I
approach I was approaching other people.
He then called my friend over, which I
didn't even know what it was about. I'm
ordering a drink. school my friend over
said, "Oh yeah, your friend's
approaching people." No, no, no. Some
random person in the club. It weren't
staff or security or anything. I said,
"Bro, you should have told me to come
over. I would have told them to mind
their own [ __ ] business in front of a
black boyfriend." I would have said,
"Hold on a minute, bro. You're you're
Hold on. You're in a relationship.
That's your boyfriend.
Mind your own [ __ ] business. Carry on
with your own [ __ ] night having a
drink and [ __ ] mind your own [ __ ] business.
Do you know what I'm saying? Mind your
own [ __ ] business. That's what I
would have [ __ ] said if they if he
[ __ ] called me over and I would have
said it in front of a boyfriend as well. Yeah.
What is it with people in London not
being able to mind their own business?
That's another thing you won't get in
Asia. See, you you think like when
people leave the country, it's solely
because of women. It's a better life.
It's a better life all around, you know.
But yeah, anyways.
But no, five numbers. You're not willing
to get one to me? I've had nine numbers
before and none of them have replied.
I've had three numbers. I've had all of
them reply and one meet me. Nah.
Nah. Not one willing to meet at all. Not
at all at all. I've got one saying that
they're meeting me next week. We'll see.
Hopefully I don't have to ever do this ever again.
Well, I won't be cuz I'll be leaving.
But, you know,
yeah, this this this applies to normal
people on and off of dating apps for
years and years and years. Like, like I
said, if you was going to meet someone,
you would have met someone by now. It's
it's end off. You go out, you try, it's
the same old in reality. Like, we're
talking about reality. We're not moaning
again cuz it's not going to change. So,
you need a plan B, bro. You need to
leave. End up. If you're not doing plan
B, then you're the more fool is you.
You're the more fool really. Which by
you, I mean me. So, you've really got no
one to blame but yourself.
Really, if you think about it, you want
to stay here all your life. You want to
keep dealing with this all your life.
That's on you. You know what it's like.
You know it's in the shambles. You know,
you know it's only going to get worse.
Um, so you only have yourself to blame.
and that's where we're at, bro.
And it's like this person right here,
five numbers, one should be willing to
meet. Why would one be willing to meet?
I've been to Wales, I've been to
Scotland, I've been all over. And again,
you that's the thing you really need to
think about as well. So
if something was going to happen, it
would have happened by now. And cuz
you're like the 1% of people that's
tried more than anyone.
Bro, there is more to life than this.
Which is why I'm saying you leave a plan
B. You need to leave this country.
Yeah, there is more to life than this.
But I'm I'm just I'm just stating like
it's it is weird.
I still think it is weird how you can't
meet someone, but you know, it is what
it is, man.
But there is more to life. I'm going to
go on holiday soon, 100%.
I'm going to go on holiday soon.
So, yeah, I'm going to go on holiday soon.
Defa 100%. I still got some money and [ __ ] So, yep.
Um, yeah, F was good, bro. But yeah, it
is strange how it is like this. But
again, we can go on about it all day,
but at the end of the day, there is one
thing you can change is leave the country.
You can leave. That's the thing. Yeah,
you can't control these people. They're
not interested in this country. You
can't control what people like, but you
can control what you do. You can leave.
You can technically make a life better
for yourself. Do you know what I'm
saying? Like Ant-Man um um so yeah,
[ __ ] anywhere out of here. It could
be anywhere. It doesn't even need to be
Thailand. Yeah, it could be anywhere.
Like you could book to go, for example,
Miami or whatever, say in 2 months. So
say for example for argument sake as
example 2 months right say you you book
to go for like say you book to go for
like 2 months or any any sort of holiday. Yeah.
So you got two months in advance and you
go out drinking every week. Oh
2 weeks and I'm gone. Four weeks and I'm
gone. You know you you're counting down
the days because you know you're out of
here. Doesn't matter where it is.
Philippines, Thailand, anywhere you want to go.
So, you know, once you have that, you
know that the the joke is on them
because you're out of here. You're out
of here in a couple of weeks.
So, you know that after that, you're out.
You know, you don't have to keep putting
up cuz if you keep doing this in this
country for the rest of your life,
you're just a fool really.
If it ain't changing now, it ain't never changing.
Yeah, I like going out Thursdays though.
>> Yeah, if you send me £50, I put the
approaches up, John. I done it. I done
one on the train. So, man, it was funny.
Oh, yeah. That's where we're at anyways.
What's that? Living the life, man. Hi, Jeff.
Nowhere near as me. Um
he has been like big off this guy right
here. He has put up with nowhere near as
much as [ __ ] as you put up for with and
he's already been Thailand three times.
That tells you know and when he did come
back to England he was booking to go again.
So you need to really he's actually
really putting you to shame here if you
think about it. This guy has not put up
with nowhere near as much [ __ ] as you
have. He has gone three times. Bear in
mind, this guy hated flying, bro. And he
hated it with I'm not scared of flying.
So, you know, you don't really you don't
really have an excuse anymore.
You you need to wake up, bro. Seriously.
And and he's done it three times and now
he's living there like this guy is is
really putting you to shame. Like he is
he is motivation. He is motivating. You
know, you know that guy actually right
there is actually motivated. Think of
it. He's come whether you like him or
not. Yeah. He come on YouTube. Yeah. As
like a [ __ ] loser t and I I will
never go on a plane ever again. I hate
flying. He said you would never get on a
plane again. He saw the country for what
it is. They didn't put up with nowhere
near as much [ __ ] as you have. And he's
living in Thailand. He's been three
times in a year.
So I mean that's what you need to
understand and he's no one in this world
has tried as much as you have. So it's
about time you start looking for a plan
B bro or this is going to just keep
happening and happening and happening.
So you need and you don't need to live
somewhere. You could just go there for a
month, two months.
You know what I'm saying? I'm not
complaining. I don't complain anymore. I
stopped myself complaining yesterday.
What's there to complain about? I It's
like what Antband says, you best get
used to it. You want to stay here, you
best get used to it. And it's only going
to get worse as well. There's nothing to
complain about. You need to get used to
it if you want to stay. If you want to stay here, so
no, I'm just not in denial, Joe. I'm not
complaining at all. I'm just not in denial
like these simps.
So, and what I was saying is
I think it was good. Yeah.
And man's not loaded, man. I've got more
money than him. But yeah,
and what you're saying is the definition
of saying he's doing the same [ __ ] every
day, but that's the only thing you can
do other than leave. So you're sat there
saying, "Oh, you're you're doing the
same thing expecting a different result,
but whilst you're here, that is all you
can do. There's nothing else you can do
whilst you're in this country, which is
the whole point of leaving the country.
Just like if you if you if say you
booked Thailand for 2 months, you would
go out every week drinking once a week
and um you you'd have that to look
forward to in in 2 months or however
long you booked it for. When you're in
this country, there is nothing else you
can do but what you already doing
until you get out of here. Simple. So
that's it. So you best get used to it.
I think it's it's time we actually grow
up now. I think I've actually grown up
that um you best get used to it if you
stay here cuz it's only going to get
worse. You don't want to wait you don't
want to waste your life complaining
every [ __ ] day, do you? That's ridiculous, bro.
It's not It's not going to change. So
what? Get used to it.
Get used to good old England. There's
even people that are better looking than
me. They've got good jobs, got good
bodies, and they can't even get anything.
And the people you do see with [ __ ] women,
[ __ ] you you've seen the kind of
people the women that people are with
nowadays. You know that you're not alone
in it. There is people that are way
better than me.
So you either stay here and get used to
or you um But to be honest though, I had
a right to be pissed off more than
Ant-Man cuz I tried more than him. But
then the but then it's like yeah you
tried more than him and he's the one
leaving and he's the one that's left. So
you're it's the more fool is you really
the more fool is you no one else. You
got no one else but but to blame. Like I
said I done two approaches yesterday
sober saying oh I've got m I've got a
boyfriend and just before I done the
third one I was just about to complain
and I'm like bro you this is your whole
you're this when you go out in this
country you're playing at your own risk.
Just like when you're gambling, you're
playing it at your own risk. That's This
is why I don't gamble anymore. I hate
gambling. I hate everything about
gambling and I wish I never have to
gamble again to be honest. I hope I get
a job before [ __ ] the football
starts. That's why I started It's like
the gambling. I started actually hating
it. Not even like, "Oh, I hate gambling
now." which is mad cuz most people when
they've been gambling for many many
years they um
yeah you just wake up eventually and you
see what it is which is what I don't
with gambling which is why I don't
gamble I hate gambling I hate everything
about it which is mad when when someone
used to love it so much as I did
I don't even think I'd even enjoy it now
like the winning money and that hate it here.
A check shirt. I've tried everything, mate.
Check, turtleneck, blazer.
You stay here, bro. You might as well
get used to it and stop moaning.
Yeah, like I said, I was lying in bed
yesterday for 4 hours. So, I had a lot
of think I had a lot of thinking to do.
I had a lot a lot a lot of thinking to do.
And bear in mind, all of these people
that say, "Oh, yeah, you don't know
what's around the corner. You never know
who you're going to meet." It applies to
normal people. It doesn't apply to you.
Normal people that haven't tried like
you. They didn't have the time and the
money to try like you. You're in the 1% of people.
You're not in a natural normal position.
you you was able to go out and get 3K a
month. So you you know you've met loads
and loads and loads of people. But that
advice doesn't even apply to you. It
applies to people on and off dating apps
for years and not really trying. But
with you, no, there's no one for you in this country.
You know, every week we never get proven
wrong. But hey man, you know,
but it doesn't matter anyways, bro.
How's the roulette anyways, Joe? You've been winning.
You've been winning, matey, huh? Oh,
you've been winning, matey.
I'm trying to think. Now I need to find
ways to make money as well. I need to become rich.
Ah, all of this stress for one person.
Eh, surprised you ain't got a mental
breakdown to be honest. Had a mental
God bless you.
Yeah, I'll be doing some both teams to
score if I can't make [ __ ] money by
then, to be honest.
So, I played an online roulette in a
couple weeks if if there was no way to
make money, but there's no point playing
it because it's rigged.
So, there's just no [ __ ] point even
playing it. 100 150. It's just all
rigged. You can't even win on it.
You just can't even [ __ ] win on the bastard.
I think that's going to be my thing now.
I just put like £80 on two teams. If I
can't make money by then and just spend
the money on just going out in escorts,
that' be the only buzz I get now.
I've already got both teams to score
lined up to be honest with you. But
then you get £300, you can just spend on
drinking an escort.
Be a fun life, eh?
I didn't do escorts yesterday. I don't
really do them anymore.
Six numbers. Joe, you almost I got five.
Don't know why you said six. That's a
lot. Even five is a lot. I don't know
how I got five numbers.
[ __ ] six numbers, bro. What the [ __ ]
But it doesn't really matter anyways.
It's all the same. Once you've got three or four,
you know, it's the same.
Like I said, you can get nine numbers,
no one replies. You get three numbers,
they all reply, and one meets you.
So, it's really quant. It's really
quality over quantity really.
That's why I used to go to the clubs and
come back at like 8:00 in the morning
and none of the numbers would would
reply whereas the ones on the street
would reply more any anyways. Yeah. [ __ ]
Yeah, I just have money now, but I'm not
really able to save unless I stop going
out. But I'm not saving for anything.
Like long as I can stay at 2K, but more than enough.
So, I don't know, man. [ __ ] I want to
go out and earn some money again, man. I
like going out and earning money. It's
just not good.
Going out and earning money.
It was good feeling, eh? But you can't
work. You can't work. Simple, simple, matey.
Right. I might just go to university.
Get go to university. Get loads of loans
out. I'm rich. Nah.
We'll figure out something.
It's hard it
travel cost me a lot of money as well.
It's going to deduct it
in a yesterday. um Joe and nothing got
me going but USA is he I done it once
and I tried to do it again after other things
and then um
only thing that seemed to work
yeah oh I can't always seem to do it to
Paul you know doesn't really always [ __ ]
8 95. Oh, it wasn't too bad then.
Hello, notorious boss. Done some
approaches yesterday. I got five
numbers. I done one on the train. Is
that okay with you, boss? I done one on
the train, one at the train station,
then I done one outside. I got a number
and I'm three sober. I got one number,
but then I got [ __ ] by the rain. But
bro, I got uh I didn't I didn't record
the last one
cuz I just My friend said, "Oh, can you
do some sober approaches?"
Um I said, "I'll record some for you."
Yeah. Don't just record it, too. Nah,
bro. You can't even get that nowadays.
It's too hard, bro. And I don't give a
[ __ ] about kisses. I'm trying to
actually meet someone, bro. I'm not in a
rush to get [ __ ] kisses from [ __ ]
people that's probably sucked dick
before kissing you.
No, but it's gotten harder, notorious. I
I don't know if you've noticed this or
is it just me, but
I've noticed that it's just gotten harder.
Have you noticed it's gotten harder? I
reckon it's gotten definitely gotten harder, bro.
I don't care about kisses, bro. I
couldn't wait the next day for that. I'm
not really asked about that. I'm just
trying to I'm only focused on trying to
get somebody to actually come out and meet.
I really like the clubs as well. So
yeah, I go around in like central
London. So you got no chance of getting kisses there.
Yeah, man. You want to see the one on
the You want to see the the train
approach the tourist? I'll send it to
you if you like, boss.
You don't send me yours anymore. No,
my little hair. Notorious.
I wear my little cap. My little special
Yeah, they've all got an ego. And yeah,
it's hard, bro. Definitely. Now, I'm not
going to send it to you, bro, cuz I
don't want these people seeing it.
Yeah. The only reason I do it, bro, is
I've got nothing else to do. I can't
work at the minute. So, that's the only
reason I'm doing it. You want to see it? Okay, boss.
One second. Let me upload it.
One second. I'm uploading it. Yeah.
You ever done one on the train, boss?
Oh, she did indeed, boss.
You betcha, cobber. You betcha.
One second. Are you still there,
Victoria? Sorry, brother. The internet
is not as fast here.
You still there? I'm going to send it to
you, but I'm just uploading it.
So, the internet is not as fast.
You have to wait a minute, bro. One second.
And And I just come back and I was
playing some Franklin. Oh, I got a little message.
Oh, that's cute, isn't it? I still I got
five numbers. I've still not text them
yet, but I will do.
What's it? It's uploading, bro.
Virgin boy can't do that. Hey, Virgin
boy can't do that. I'm serious. Virgin
You're the [ __ ] virgin.
One second, bro. I'm going to send it to
you now. Yeah.
[ __ ] internet, bro. One sec.
There you go. That's one of them. [Laughter] Yeah, bro.
Never change is Notorious. I'm going to
come and tickle you. I am
I'm going to I'm going to come and tickle you.
They've all got my friends. Yeah.
Oh, I love that.
Do you like it? It's quite sweet, isn't Yeah.
Don't put this on this, bro.
[ __ ] you. Yeah,
that was before I shot again on the the old alcohol. Holy.
Thank you, boss.
I can't get anyone. Pet can't get no loving.
Did you like it?
Did you like it? Notorious.
Tell me what you thought, boss.
Did you like it? Thanks for the thumbs up.
Everybody was looking. Ah, cheers, boss.
I did try though. Did Did you like the
approach? What do you rate the approach
out of 10?
Give us some feedback.
I need to go get some bacon and [ __ ]
bro. Honestly, real. I'm starving. I
actually went on the run calls last night,
which I know is a bit naughty. My body's
getting [ __ ] again. I need to go back to the gym.
Oh, did you like it? Thank you, boss.
And then I done another one and then
Did you hear it though on Notorious? Did
Did you hear the interaction?
Yeah. See, Lar and Virgin Boy can't do
that. Their anxiety wouldn't allow it.
Right. I need to go, bro. I need to go
and get some um food and [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah, I tried, bro. I done another one
as well. I'll show it later, but I need
to go, bro. I'll be back later. Yeah. Peace.