I think I forgot just how bad it was cuz
it's been 2 months.
Wow. That doesn't seem to change either.
[ __ ] hell, bro. That doesn't even
seem to change. Nope. Oh,
[ __ ] know how you can do 100 pound
spin when you do put 150 in. Yeah. Yeah.
Gambling's the same old gambling.
Uh, yeah. I just thought I'd try 150. I
bought out my [ __ ] head. Same old
boring. Same old misses everything that you bet.
Same old boring.
The worst thing is the [ __ ]
connection was keep lagging, lagging,
lagging. It's mad how you can miss
continuously when you've got 189 numbers
covered. And this is coming from like an
actual um um
what how do you say this? Um an unbiased
an an unbi an unbiased point of view.
Like there's no triggering, there's no
smashing things, there's no going skin.
This is just straight how it literally
is. It's like there's no way if you're
covering 1890 numbers, how you can
continuously miss. But but here's the
thing. We actually done something about
it. We stopped gambling because of this
reason. We literally stopped because of
this reason. So it you know some it's
not a bad thing every 2 3 months or
whenever you rarely do it to think, oh
that's why I stopped now because it was
the same old boring. But the difference
is we actually done something about it.
We stopped doing it. That's the whole
thing which is doing as well
cuz it was same old.
Oh, that's why.
Yeah. At least we we're reminded of why
we stopped gambling. Damn. It's nice to be reminded
because it's the same old boring come out
from my side. It's straight straight
straight the truth.
You get these people that say
house. It's not house bro. You had half
the ball covered. We learn like 108
spin. It ain't nothing to do with our
house. Leave the [ __ ] alone, mate.
He's getting old. That poor house head.
Stop blaming him.
No way. Again. I'm not even an hour. I'm
all good, bro.
Oh, just now, bro. I just put 150 on,
man. I just thought I'd give one give it
a try. 150. I ain't done it for like two
two three bucks. No, I think it was like
two bucks. I thought give it a while.
Same old boring, same old zero section.
It's nice to be reminded why you don't
um keep these cuts in business.
It defo is do you know what it is yet?
It's it's when you start putting more
money on the numbers. You just see how
[ __ ] rigged it is. Like next door to 11.
Next door to 11. No, I'm not muted. No, I'm not.
It's nice to be reminded, bro. I'm glad
to be reminded. I tell my mom about this
later on the phone, actually.
Don't do it anymore.
Like another L for me. What? Being
better looking than you and having more
money than you. You are the ones that
sat on YouTube every day, bro. No life.
Yeah, you're talking about yourself.
Life is great. You're sat on YouTube
every day waiting for your little
benefits. Let's not be in denial now.
Sorry I'm not a uh [ __ ] stop and bro,
but guess what? I got more money than
you, better looking than you, and I'm
not sat on YouTube every day like you.
So, yeah. Bye-bye. Self-reflect on
another channel. So, yeah. Can you hear
it now? Yeah, bro. I just thought I'd
give roulette a little try. One Well,
actually, it was 155 cuz I took5 for
some reason. But yeah, man.
It's all good, isn't it?
It's nice to be reminded of why I
stopped doing it. Nice to be reminded.
Oh, it was a nightmare as well. I had to
find a roulette table that would accept [ __ ] England.
[ __ ] there were a lot of them were
banning it in England and it was laggy.
And at least I know why I stopped. So
that's a good thing.
Yeah, at least at least I know why I stopped.
So I can't get addicted to it. here cuz
I know it's rigged. So I I can't get
like addicted like put more and more
because I know it's rigged and I'm the
fool if I keep putting money on these
rigged things because it is rigged. It's
rigged as a [ __ ] because there's
no way you with the amount of numbers
you covered with the money that you put
on it. You can keep missing that many times.
Um I think I got to 180 then I was doing
like four but I just done like a 80
pound spin or something. Well same old
ball then anyways.
Same old boring. But I'll never be like
these losers on YouTube or skin. Never
be like them. These little skin losers.
[ __ ] hell. These little skin losers
sat on YouTube every day. I can never be like them.
But yeah, it's nice to get a reality. It
is good a reality check, you know, in
three months, two, three months.
It's exactly why I stopped doing it.
That is exactly why I stopped doing it.
Think of how much money I saved in like
three months as well.
>> Yeah. I just I don't I don't I'm not I
don't really do it anymore. It's the
first time in months. I can't be asked.
just that to be fair.
Thought I'd give it a wall. What?
One second. Hold up. [ __ ]
150 now. 150 is
nothing to me. I've still got some
money, so I'm all good, man. Nice to be
reminded, though. It is nice to be reminded. Yep.
So yeah, that's why. Oh [ __ ]
Yeah, I couldn't justify 200. 100 was
too little. So I thought 150 was just
right to try with.
Yeah, I won't be doing that again.
will not be doing that again, mate. [ __ ] that.
Imagine you just kept doing it. Yeah.
And you lost all your money. [ __ ] that.
Could you imagine now?
I don't know how I used to do that, bro.
I was mad. I was a crazy bastard.
I never go back to that. Um,
I don't know.
Maybe like £2,000 maybe.
Yeah, I guess. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't I just wanted to
try and put me in a better mood, but it
never worked anyway. So,
nothing lost, nothing gained.
Like 1,200 in that account. Sepate accounts. Yeah.
I'm all good, bro. But everything paid off anyways.
More than enough, in it.
I'm not really saving for anything.
It's bad though. Oh,
and it has me thinking that would be a
chance or something to get back to. No
way. But [ __ ] that. No way.
Never going back to that [ __ ]
Never going back to that [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] that.
Hung over as well. [ __ ]
Yeah, that's called having a life. It's
called living your life. if you should
try it, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, man. And actually, it was 150 last
week as well, but apparently I'm a skin. So, yeah.
But the thing is, we done something with
the gambling. We done something about
the gambling. We stopped the gambling to
be fair. So, I'm not even asked to be
honest. So, I don't really care about
that. I've got no reason to be a sore
loser, bro. I've still got money. I
rarely I can't even gamble anymore
except from you know like rarely. So I
have no reason to be a sore loser. If I
genuinely didn't think it was rigged,
I'd keep doing it. I'd be I'd be doing
it right now. But we all know that it is
rigged. So that's been done in the football anyways.
Yeah, I'm eating beans on toast, bro. Yeah, man.
You want to join the hangouts, Timmy? I
just gambled, by the way, on roulette.
Same old same old balling. Reminds me
why I quit to me. I don't know how you
do this [ __ ] every day. You You're
[ __ ] How you can gamble every day?
You're mad, bro. I learned that [ __ ]
27. Today was a oneoff, bro. I only done
it today cuz I was in a bit of a bad
mood trying to get my spirits. I ain't
gambled in like 3 months the way you've done.
So, I don't know like how you still do
that [ __ ] bro. Like that. [ __ ] that,
No way. And to be honest with you, it
reminded me why I don't do it anymore.
So it was actually a good thing today.
Yeah. It reminded me
what I mean. Yeah.
You want to join the hangouts to me?
Yeah. Reminding me why I don't do it anymore, mate.
Just reminded me why I don't do it anymore.
[ __ ] you do, mate.
You just stop this gambling [ __ ] I just
told you I just lost 150, bro. What the [ __ ]
Well, I have like I have money. I have
savings. I'm not really saving for anything.
So obviously I would need to stop going
out now. I've proved my point enough.
I've already been out like four [ __ ]
times anyway. So it is what it is.
do over again, man. [ __ ]
[ __ ] sake, man.
70 in the draw as well. It's bad.
It's bad, bro. I'm back.
Is that how much you have left? 170.
So, I basically won't wouldn't have
saved anything this month.
Yeah, I lost 150 on roulette grievy.
No, that's wrong. Hold on. 80.
Yeah, I just lost 150 on roulette, man.
And it reminded me why I quit. So, yeah,
I wouldn't have saved anything this
month, but the whole point is still
having the same amount of money until I
can find another way to make money is
the is the whole point. But yeah, I lost
150 on roulette. That's why I don't do
it anymore, bro. First time in two months.
It's so bad, ain't it? [ __ ] hell,
man. But we done something about that
because we don't do it anymore.
I mean, except from today, but you know,
like that's the whole point of why we
don't do it anymore. Yep.
Not for me, mate. I've still got money.
See, I can't adjust my lifestyle. This
is why I can't I can't save because I
like to go out and [ __ ] So, I'll just
continuously just keep having
the same amount of money
every week, uh, every month because I
can't save. I like to spend it. I like
to go out and [ __ ] So,
but like I said, as long as you, you know, you have
Yeah. money and and it's all good, in it.
Maybe I'll save
maybe maybe I'll save like a £100 maybe. So,
yeah, it's not an issue, but it's one
it's one of the reasons why I stopped
doing it because it's just rigged. You
can't even [ __ ] win on it. So maybe
this month maybe I'll be able to save
maybe a £100.
Well, you can't save on benefits. M you
can, but you'd have to live a very bad life
and I'm not disciplined for that. So I
mean even if you saved you could save
£200 a month, you know,
it's still something, is it?
Yeah, pretty much. So I I didn't do it
for 2 months. So
[ __ ] [ __ ] it
pass come out as well.
You can live on benefits. You just can't save.
I can't live the way you do, Grezy.
I can't live the way you do, mate. I'm
not used to it.
I like going out approaching. I like
going out drinking. So, I mean,
but I'm getting old, so I shouldn't have
to, to be fair, I don't I shouldn't You
shouldn't have to go out. Yeah. Yeah. you know.
[ __ ] I don't know, bro.
Yeah, that's been one 11 one yesterday as well.
You could do that, mate, but I won't be doing it.
But I won't do that because I know it's
rigged, so why would I do that?
I got five numbers. No replies yet.
It's not looking good, is it? I actually
recorded some approaches, Nicolola.
I put one up earlier of doing I done it
on the train and uh I done three
numbers. I done three approaches so far,
but yeah, no replies yet. I'm sure one will reply.
You would have think so, but it can
happen, bro. Sometimes you can go out
and get 10 numbers, you don't get a
reply. Sometimes you get three numbers,
they all reply.
It's bad in this country, bro. It is
really bad. But again, we need a plan B.
There's no point moaning. There's no
point complaining. We need a plan B.
Without a plan B, it's pointless
talking. It's pointless to It's
pointless [ __ ] complaining if you're
not going to do anything about it. Like,
leave. So, it's simple as that.
But you be mad sticking any more of your
money in? Especially when you know it's
[ __ ] rigged. [ __ ] that.
It's [ __ ] rigged as [ __ ]
But this should have this week. next week.
But it will never change. Yeah, but
that's why I said you need a plan B.
Without a plan B, mate, it's pointless.
I got so many numbers, bro. [ __ ] In
them three days, I got 13 numbers.
I tell you, I'm [ __ ] bro. I swear
down. Got 13 numbers. And I think we
might just about get a date if we're
lucky. But can't do it in this country, bro.
It's too hard.
But to be fair, I probably won't be out
now for two weeks. I can't afford it if
I'm trying to save at least something. So,
who knows? Eh,
maybe I will, though. I'm a crazy
bastard, bro. I should stop living like
this. I can't afford to live like this
anymore. I don't know why I keep trying
to live I can't live like this, bro.
Can't afford to live like this anymore, you know?
But I still do it
cuz I feel like you know you only live
once in it. But
it's [ __ ] it.
But even if you save 150 this month, you
still save it.
That's all I see it.
But know I probably will need to stop
for a little bit now.
feel like you can stop now for a month.
I feel like you can stop for a month,
bro. You got 13. What did you get? 13
numbers them times you went out. So,
and that's not including including the
people that you've you already
approached. So, I feel like you can
stop. You're in a position now. You can
I feel like you are in a position where
you can stop now for at least a month,
two weeks, even two weeks. Where are we?
when you can. Bro, my body is looking
[ __ ] now as well from all the drinking
cuz I stopped going to the [ __ ] gym
and that is it. Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ] Nicolo. I
remember that Indonesian fella
yesterday. He's a proper [ __ ] house. He
is. He's a proper [ __ ] out of him. Yeah.
Yeah. I bought him a [ __ ] round of
drinks. I bought him a round of drinks.
I bought him a [ __ ] round of drinks,
mate. £24, two Guinnesses, two baby
Guinnesses, and he's stole a [ __ ] ass,
bro. He won't do it. He won't talk to anyone.
I can still taste the baby Guinness in me.
That ain't good, is it? [ __ ] Yeah.
See, if I save now,
if I stop going out now,
I could probably save about 150,
which is a smart thing to do really.
You rather said you save something than save nothing.
That's a good idea. I reckon
if I had the delivery jobs, I would just
be working two day two weeks straight if
I could work. But I can't work. though.
You still got the gym until that time. I
think that's a good shout, bro.
I think we should pack it in for two
weeks. Obviously, well, I mean, we can't
say this person wants to meet, but
obviously if this person wants to meet,
then obviously that's different, you
know. We have to go. Yeah.
I want to start the gym tomorrow. I
think I need to start the gym
cuz 17. So if you're back to 18, you
must have saved some money. You spent a
lot as well. So
But then at the same time is that even
if but then the way I see it as well if
you're a single person right and you've
got 13400 pound in your account it's
more than enough if you're a single
person with no outgoings what's the
difference between saving a little and
then not saving a little really if you
think about it. So you're a single
person it's quite a lot you know think
of how many times people have to how
many days people have to work and [ __ ]
So obviously you've got that side, but
then the other side of it is like it's
not going to change. So why can't you
just stop for like 2 weeks? You know
what I'm saying?
Some people go out once a month. You've
already been out four times, three, four times.
See, you could just learn that 150, but
that doesn't matter. You've been out
enough times. So you can't think of it like that. Um,
yeah, I'll have to pack it in, I think,
for a couple of weeks, man.
I'm going to have to pack it in for a
couple of weeks, I think. that far
back here for a couple of weeks.
See, we're not all rich like greasy. You see,
I think it's still good.
So that's it, bro.
So I feel like you should just stop now
for 2 weeks
cuz it's better to have saved 150 160
for the month. What? Like Yeah. You can
keep going out and trying and you'll
still be all right with money, but it
just doesn't make any sense. You've
already done you've already got 30
numbers. You've done enough approaches
this month. You've got a gym membership.
So, it's like you've had your fun with
the [ __ ] gambling and [ __ ]
drinking this month. So, I feel like
feel like we got it made, bro.
Think we should just wait until the
football and then just go from there. Really?
30s? That's a lot of numbers. Some
people can't even get [ __ ] one. My
whole phone book is filled up with all
these different women greasy
that just full of them, mate. All like
different kinds of [ __ ] people. But
and you know, it's the same result as well. Uh
no, it's it's the truth, don't it?
It is the truth.
What? What's the reality, bro?
And you got a TV, man. You got a nice
bed here. You got a TV. You got a gym
membership. Just [ __ ] pack it in
for a couple for a couple of weeks, man. Jeez.
Got a nice telly. You got a nice Franklin.
Try and save like 150, man. You know, be good.
But to be fair, I've had a lot of fun,
you know, in the past few weeks.
Surprised I still have any money left to
be honest. [ __ ] hell.
But yeah, the only thing I'll be betting
on now is the football. Yeah.
Yeah. I I hadn't gambled for two weeks.
I haven't gambled for two months. So
basically I don't gamble. I hadn't
gambled for two
I hadn't gambled for two months, man.
What the [ __ ]
I thought I'm bored. I'm in a bad mood.
So no, but this Yeah, bro. But that
wasn't going to just approach. It's
because I wanted to go out anyways.
It's not about approaching anymore. It's
But yeah, I need to stop now for two
weeks cuz I do want to kind of try and
save some money this month. So
good. You know, we're not rich anymore.
So, we don't get as much money anymore.
So, we need to
we need to start saving slowly. Think if
you slave save slowly all the way to the
end of the end of the thing, you know,
it's good for you need a detox anyways.
I think a detox is good as well. Save a
bit of money and you have a break.
You've proved your point, but
it does make sense. Okay. So, am I
addicted to gambling? No.
It doesn't really matter anyways, bro,
does it? Because I'm not addicted to gambling.
Clearly, you're not addicted to gambling,
which I'm surprised Timmy never learned.
I'm 27 and I [ __ ] learned. I'm
surprised he doesn't. Do you know how
many times I go to Weather Spoons and I
never touch them machines? I must have
been Weather Spoons about [ __ ] 30
times the past two weeks and I never
touch their machines. I don't go to no
bookies. So, it's irrelevant what you
say because it's not
it's not uh you're not addicted. It's
not affecting you financially.
So, it doesn't really matter whether you
say you do or you don't. Doesn't really
matter, does it, man?
You know, I just done it because I just
wanted to cuz I was bored.
And let's put it this way, right? If you
gambled every two months, you basically don't gamble.
Think of people that do the lottery.
They're not classed as gamblers. So,
I just thought I'd try 150. I wanted to
try to think I can't justify 200. That's
too much. 250 is too much. 100 is a bit
I want a little tiny bit more stuff for
150 is just perfect. So
well I didn't want to lose it but still
[ __ ] first time in two months maybe a
bit over two months
maybe. Don't even touch any of it anymore.
No, I'm not addicted and I'm not your mate either.
Um, no, you're not addicted. It's like
someone, right? If they smoked every two
months, they're not a smoker. If someone
drunk every two months,
they're not an alcoholic. They're not
even a social drinker. So, you're not a
gambler. Simple. It's just straight as that.
It's straight. You know, I used to go
through like smoking periods when I do it socially. So, Yeah, man.
I don't I'm not even classed as a
gambler, I don't think, to be honest.
Until the football start again. So, yeah,
everyone has something that they do.
So, I'm not addicted. If I was addicted,
if you was addicted, you wouldn't have
no money there. Simple. You would I
would be broke if I had no money left.
I'd be broke if I was addicted. So
I was just in a bad mood and thought, "Fuck it."
Okay. So you you think Okay, so let's
let's let's so let's get this straight.
So I'm I'm addicted to gambling.
I just thought maybe the magnet man
might have been on the toilet. The
magnet man might have been on the toilet.
So, I'm I'm addicted to gambling. I
don't think so, bro.
It's not about controlling it. I rarely
do it. It's not like we we should we we
might as well just not even have the conversation
because it's not about controlling it or
not. You barely do it. like it's not
even worth talking about.
I don't I don't I don't control it
because I don't do it. Simple.
But yeah, you're not going to win. That
is a But I was just thinking that maybe
there was a small chance. Bear in mind I
hadn't done it for 2 months. So,
but yeah. Why do bro Why do you think
I'm not doing it now?
I've got like 12 in one account. I could
easily lose, 1200 pound right now if I
wanted to, but obviously I'm not going
to do it because I'm not stupid and I
know that it's rigged. So, it's simple as that
cuz it [ __ ] is. It [ __ ] is, mate.
Live two weeks ago.
What? And I put £10 in.
Oh, what? when I put £10 in a in a in in
a fishing frenzy machine and it wasn't
two weeks ago. Did I've not been to that
pub for more than two weeks. So it
wasn't two weeks ago. Yeah, I went I I I
went to a pub two weeks ago that you
didn't see and Yeah, I put £7 in the slot machine.
Yeah, I'm I'm addicted, bro. Yeah. Yeah,
I'm addicted, bro. Yeah, I'm very addicted.
Yeah, I'm I'm addicted.
You're right, bro. You caught me, man.
Damn, I'm addicted. I'll be homeless soon.
But yeah, I'm just going to I'm I need
to do some food shopping tomorrow. You
know what I fancy today, Grievy? I fancy
a savoy and chips.
Yep. I'm completely addicted, bro. Yep.
Yeah, I'm completely addicted, man.
Uber man. [ __ ] Wow.
Five numbers yesterday
approaching on the train. I'm a mad
bastard I am.
So what's the plan? It's like what the
guy said right on the train. What are
you going to do?
So realistically what I'm doing is
next month cuz I got some stuff to do.
I'm I'm I'm I am actually booking this
one way ticket.
Um, and I'm going to go on holiday for 2 months.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ] Joe, I forgot to tell
you. Yeah, you know that woman I told
you that I met in New Zealand, right?
She wrote me a paragraph and I thought,
okay, well, she wrote me a paragraph.
So, uh, let me reply back to her. Yeah,
she didn't even give me a chance to
reply. She just blocked me. Now, that's
a bit unfair because at least let me
defend myself if you're going to write
something. And I literally, bro, gave
her like a big onage, bro. That's why
she blocked me because she knew. Yeah, I
didn't book it, but I was I was joking.
I lied, bro. But I might book it next
month. For real. We need We need a plan,
bro. If you ain't got a plan, then
you're pointless, bro. If you ain't got
a plan, then it's pointless. But listen,
listen to what I'm saying. Yeah.
Yeah, I was just joking, but I haven't I
haven't yet. But I am I am going. But listen listen.
You know what? She turned around and
said Grezy. Now I feel like I've got
I've got a point with this one. Yeah.
I'm going to ask Grezy because Greavves is impartial.
Can I tell you what it is?
And I actually sent her a 5 minute voice
note and she didn't even listen to it.
So she's just another [ __ ] She replied days later.
So, what I'm saying is I want to make
sure Greavves is here.
I think that I'm right on this one.
I'm not talking to any of them except
one that says they're going to meet me
to next week, but to be fair, they've
not replied today. Nah, you can't even
get I got five numbers yesterday. I got no replies.
I mean, you don't need to ask, bro. It's
always going to be the same old in this country.
So, it's there's no point asking because
it's always going to be the same old here. So,
there's no point um asking to be fair.
You know, I got five numbers yesterday.
None of them replied yet, which is strange.
You're the ones supposed to be meeting
me next week. didn't reply to my message today. So,
your guess is is as good as mine.
But that's just the reality of the
dating game in this country. It's [ __ ]
It is [ __ ]
So, yeah, it's [ __ ] up, bro. Oh [ __ ]
But yeah, it will never change in this
country. That's why you need a plan B.
You need a plan B. Cuz
if you ain't got a plan B, then you're
just existing in this country.
You need a plan B.
What if you realize, right, something is
a cycle? You need to break the cycle
with the gambling, right? Do you
remember how we kept going around in
circles? This is riggeda
and then we used to moan and moan and
moan. What do you do?
You stop gambling.
Like for the most part, you stop
gambling. Yeah. So it cut all the
problems. The only the only thing that's
going to change in this country is you
either use that school for the rest of
your life, or you leave. If you're not
going to do any of them things, then you
want to stick to plan A without a plan
B, a plan C, then you're [ __ ] cuz it's
it's it's only going to get worse here.
So, I mean, that's it.
Nope. None of them is texted back so
far. Anyone would think I look like Timmy Eldridge.
I know. It's a madness, isn't it? No.
No. None of them.
Strange for Thursday.
I'm hoping one will and some of them are
just busy cuz that's very strange.
Um, and that's the reality of dating in
this country. So there you go. And I I
done an approach on a train, recorded
it. Done on a street, recorded it. It
will never change. It's been going on
for years. You know better than most
people. You know more. Yeah. You know
what I mean? So by you I mean me. So
yeah, that's that
greasy. Right. Let me ask you this qu.
So this do you know this woman in New
Zealand? Do you want to know what she
said and do you want to know what I said back?
which I think I won this argument if she
was actually to listen
which I always take on board what other
people say cuz but she doesn't
understand it right
do you know what she said
she was like you don't understand you're
not listening from a woman's point of
view this is why you can't get women
from a woman's point of view that women
do not like being approached on the
street where and then she went on a rant
about how women don't like to be
approached on the
Then I was thinking, here's the thing,
right? There's a few problems with what
you're saying. Yeah. Firstly, you're
only seeing it from your point of view,
right? Try being a guy where dating apps
don't work. You don't meet anyone
through friends. You don't meet anyone
through hobbies. What else are you
supposed to do in London? And it's not
like we live in a town or we live in a
village. We live in London now. We live
in London now. Pretty much people expect
it in London. You know, it's a big city.
A B we're not talking about street
approaches. It doesn't matter where you
approach someone. Bar, club, mall, cinema, [ __ ]
concert, [ __ ] a festival.
They're still going to say that they
have got a boyfriend. It's not about
where you're approaching someone.
So I I said, "Well, it's got nothing to
do with approaching on the street." See,
there are some women that do like being
approached on the street. Yeah. Not
every woman is scared of men. So if
you're going by your logic, you're
speaking on behalf of all women. And
it's and it's and and to be honest with
you, it doesn't even matter because it's
not a street that's the problem. We're
not talking about we're talking about
approaching genuinely. It could be anywhere.
And in London, people pretty much expect
it nowadays. It's a [ __ ] big city,
bro. People do it all the time, you
know? So, and then she just blocked me.
I responded to her and she didn't even
listen to anything I said
because she knew that like I would have
I've got a valid point with what I'm
saying. Stop only seeing it from your
point of view.
You're only seeing it from your point of
view. You're not seeing it from another
guy's point of view. That's the problem.
You see what I'm saying? You're only
seeing it from your point of view.
You understand what I'm saying?
So, and I think and then she just turned
out to be a [ __ ] as well because what
she's writing doesn't make no sense
cuz you clearly wasn't scared.
So, what is that? Okay. Okay. And I said
to her, I don't even approach on the
street most of the time. And even if I
did approach on the street, what else am
I supposed to [ __ ] do?
What else am I supposed to do?
And stop speaking on behalf of all
women. Not all women, believe it or not,
are scared of being approached on the
street. To stop speaking on behalf of
all women, even if 30% don't. Yeah,
there's still a percentage that don't.
So, you're [ __ ] wrong. And we're not
even talking about approaching on the
street. Why are you even talking about
that? That's how we met. But it doesn't
matter what where. And I said to her,
basically, you could have the same
interest as someone and you would still get rejected.
You can legitimately have the same
interests as someone and you would still
get rejected. So what you're saying
don't make sense.
Bro, can you stop calling me mate? I'm
not your mate. I don't know who you are,
so stop calling me mate. But there's
more than there's more than a percentage
that don't mind being approached on the street. So it's like
it's [ __ ] what she's what she's
saying and she's just a [ __ ] as well. So
do you know what I'll be honest with
you. Do you know why I always used to
think I was like different than Ant-Man?
I never used to think I would end up in
Thailand. Like not better than him but
maybe like he was giving off strange
vibes and you know not not better than
him but different to him. So, two
different people can't get the same
result. But I think I I think for many
years I was in denial thinking that I
weren't going to end up in Thailand like
or Philippines as well. And she said,
"Oh," she said, "Oh, you can go to any
other country, it's the same." No, it's
not the same. No, it's not the same
because you go Philippines, you have
people wanting to be your girlfriend.
You know, you have people wanting
wanting to be your um girlfriend um in
in the Philippines. So that doesn't and
they don't want money off of anyone. So
what you're saying don't make sense.
Doesn't matter, mate. It's not about the
street. They do the same in bars. They
do the same in clubs. They're not
interested. It doesn't matter what
they're doing on the street, bars,
clubs. They're not interested. This is
is what I was trying to explain to her
that they're not. It's just they're not
interested in this country in me and
what it seems like 80% of other people
clearly by what I've seen people be
ending up with nowadays.
So it doesn't matter you're a
good-looking guy, you should easily be
able to find someone. That's the way I
see it. See, they they're seeing it from
their again, you're seeing it from their
point of view, but you're not seeing it
from anyone else's point of view. I see
it as you're a decent looking person. Oh
[ __ ] You got normal amount of money.
You should be able to find someone. That
That's the way I see it with the amount
of effort that I put in. I was ly I was
lying in bed yesterday,
4 hours playing Franklin, just driving
around thinking about this wheezy. I
didn't get to bed till like 6:00 in the
morning. Right. But then I thought,
okay, so we know there's a problem. We
know that you're decent looking. You
still can't find anyone? We Okay, we're
aware of this. Sorry. What are you going
to do about this? Like, hold on, hold
on, hold on. So, wait. So, is there a
plan B? And that's where you was going
wrong long. Plan B. So, yeah.
Strange guys. I'm not a strange guy.
Stop talking about yourself. I'm a
normal guy. And I don't say I saw you
from over there, bro. Stop being jealous
because you can't approach. Stop being a
s. Sing never ever got anyone laid.
Remember that, bro.
Um, sing never ever got anyone laid.
I've never said I've seen you from over
there for like 2 years. Like, bro, you
probably can't even approach. Stop being jealous.
You know, stop being a s. Sing never got anyone laid.
Believe that, bro. So,
yeah. So, no, I'm not strange. cuz I'm
actually a normal person. So, uh yeah,
sing never got anyone labor
and what you're doing is coming across as sing.
Um it's coming across No, no, no, that's
the wrong word. You're coming across as
a white knight.
Oh, you've got a girl, dude. Oh, yeah.
You're all in relationships on it. Isn't
that mad? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You're all in relationships, aren't you?
Yeah. Cool. Bro, stop being a white
knight. It never got anyone laid.
Ask all of these people that have ended
up with all of these muners.
I don't know why so many guys are in
denial, Greasy. Why do you think so many
guys are in denial?
What? What? Do you think it's some sort
of condition or what? What is it? Do you
think it's some sort of mental health
that they don't accept the reality? Like
I could sit here and say, "Oh, I've had
USA. I've had I've had all of these
women I've had these women that women
don't do no wrong. Like you would think
in my position I'd be the one sticking
up for them. I mean, yeah, it's [ __ ]
now, but you know, think of it like
this, right? I've had women I I go out
and get numbers even if they don't
reply. You would think that I would be
the one defending them. Do you
understand? You would think that it's
people in my position, right?
Um would would be defending them. You
understand, Grezy? You you you'd think
that I would be the one defending them.
And 86% of guys are not in
relationships. Um, actually, most people
are single, so you don't know anything.
What you don't know what you're talking
about. I've got friends that are not
connected to each other in any way, and
most of them are single. Yeah, I know
people that are in relationships. So,
that is that is bollocks, mate. Absolute
[ __ ] There's no way 86% of people
in relationships you I would say it's
not one in five. I'd say one in four
um uh no statistically they're not
actually one in four in relationships.
You don't know [ __ ] And if you did know
[ __ ] you wouldn't have to resort to white knighting.
You wouldn't have to white knight. If
you knew [ __ ] you wouldn't be sat here
white knighting. So anyone would think
that I would be in a position to start
defending these women. I don't defend
them. I know they're [ __ ] I go out for
a drink anyways. What will I get by
defending them? It's not 86%. It ain't
86%, bro. Most of my friends, yeah, are single.
They're not It's not 86%. This guy
doesn't know anything, bro. It's not 86
86% of men are in relationships.
The guy, he doesn't know anything, mate.
And you know the thing is, right, right?
Even the people that are in
relationships, have you seen the people
that they're in relationships with? It
proves my point even more.
So, no, you don't know what you're
talking about, bro. You literally don't
have no life experience. You don't know
what you're talking about. And stop
trying to troll on my channel. Um,
because I'm not Timmy or Monty. So,
yeah. And no, you're completely
completely wrong. So, yeah.
Anyways, you're banned, buddy. Bye-bye.
>> Oh, [ __ ]
>> Oh, that's the one. [ __ ]
Stop talking [ __ ] on my channel, bro.
But yeah, there's no way 86% of See,
this is what I'm saying. Like, you would
think that I would be the simp.
Like, if you This is how in denial these
people are, right? You would think,
right, that I would be the simp with the
amount of women that I've been with and
dates and [ __ ] even the fact that you
can just go up and get numbers. Doesn't
matter where they lead. Yeah. You would think
that you you would think that you would
be the simp.
You would actually think that you would
be the simp. Not these people that can't
get women that's that's never had a
woman or they don't get women
and they've got no history. You would
you would think it's the other way
around. It's so wild. They sit there and
defend women and they must know like
after year and year and year it ain't
going to get them laid. But they still
they still whitelight them. I don't
understand it. If I was them, I would be
going [ __ ] mad if I got to their age
and I hadn't been with anyone or um
I'm not with anyone now or whatever it
is and I can't approach. I'd be going
[ __ ] mad. But they defend them. It's
[ __ ] weird. It doesn't It makes no sense.
It makes no sense whatsoever.
You know, it's mad.
But they still defend him. It's a madness.
They still defend him.
Strange, isn't it? It is strange. It is
very very strange
cuz think of it right. Say you went on
there now and you started slagging off um
slanging off women. Yeah. One second.
Hold on. Where the [ __ ] is this video going, bro?
Say you started slanging off women. Yeah. They can't um
There it is. Yeah. They can't call you an incel
because obviously you've been with
women, you've had sex. So they they
can't actually call you an incel. You're
just not in denial like they are. That's
that's the only thing. You're just not in denial.
You will get these people that just will
get no women, never had women, and
they'll sit there and defend them all
day. And then there's people like me
that's actually had women and been with
women. And I I tell you the straits, the [ __ ]
Do not do not think that's weird how it
should be the other way around.
I can sit there and say, "Oh yeah, women
are perfect. I had this woman in
America. I [ __ ] her. I sucked on her
tits. I had a New Zealander. I had a
[ __ ] I've kissed women. Oh, women
are so perfect. I used to come I used to
have somebody around coming to suck my
dick. You know, like I'm not in denial,
bro. It's [ __ ] up. But at the same
time, it's never going to change." Which
is why we need a plan B. If you ain't
got a plan B, you're doomed. So that's it. I'm sorry.
Yeah. What you going to do, bro?
So, do you understand like Greavves is
not a s. He just
he just doesn't understand
and he doesn't really stick up for
people either. But these people actually
stick up for women and they don't get
women and they never have had women.
It's it's so weird. Like you get like
Virgin Boy, right, for example, like him
saying, "Oh, women don't know you this.
Women don't know." But I've had more
women than him. Like as as immature as
it sounds. Yeah. Like we use that as an
example. the virgin. I've had literally
had more women than him. I've been with
more women than him. I've got more
experience. But I don't sit there and offend them.
I say like, "Yeah, they're stuck up.
They're this. They're that." Whatever.
Cuz they are. Cuz I'm not in denial.
But yeah, you need a plan B. So like I
was saying, if you ain't got a plan B,
you're [ __ ] So
you know what I mean?
You understand what I'm saying, Grezy? Like
they defend them, but I don't know why
they they continuously defend them.
It's strange. You would think I'd be the
one defending them. Do you know what I
mean? I can actually go up sober and get
a woman's number, whereas most of these
people can't even do that, but they're
the ones defending them. It's weird.
It It's strange.
So, who had a fair point? Me with the
New Zealander. Is it Greasy?
Yeah, I think I had a point because they
do only see it from their point of view.
You think I had points with what I was saying?
I think I had some points in what I was saying. Yeah,
I think so.
Yeah, I I think I did because they only
like I said, they only see it from their
their point of view. I think that is a
ma that that is that is a main thing, you know.
I think so as well. It's like if you
want to go by that logic, right? Every
woman's scared to be approached. Look at
USA is she wanted to be approached. She
would have probably [ __ ] me there and then.
So, it's like
that doesn't really ring right, you know.
But she's just a [ __ ] anyways, so [ __ ] her. But yeah.
Yeah. 86% of people in relationships. Yeah, right.
Yeah, [ __ ] right.
All the people you meet are [ __ ] single. single, man.
All the people I meet are single.
I'm not I'm not that I'm not really that
I'm actually all right with life. Me,
Greavves. You got some money, got a nice
TV, got a bed. What more could you want?
We just obviously have to do plan B.
That's the only thing. If there's no
plan B, there's nothing. So,
it's clearly not going to change in this
country. I don't know why it's so hard
to date in this country, but it is. So, yeah.
I think you need to be pretty thick skin
to do this to be honest. Um,
yeah, I was thinking about USA is his
boobs yesterday. greasy.
I was trying to [ __ ] wank, but I
couldn't wank. But then I just thought
of her again and it come out. Yeah,
it's cute. Is it Grezy?
Must have been the boobs all along. Is it Grezy? Yeah.
I think I've gotten into sex, you know,
more now than [ __ ] Greasy, do you know that
since [ __ ] these escorts? I think
I've got the sex now. Well, someone message me.
No, I thought I got a little message there. Crazy. >> Yeah.
Yeah, Grezy, man. What's your what
what's your plan, mate? What are you
going to do?
I'm actually booking Thailand next month.
I've got a whole month for this [ __ ] to
change. We're enough numbers. I'm
booking it next month, bro. I have to
It's never going to change, bro.
It's never going to change ever.
I can't believe I do these approaches
sober, but I'm [ __ ]
I can't believe I don't want on the train. Jeez.
I really am crazy, aren't I?
But yeah, you need to think of
something, mate, because you can't keep
doing this for the rest of your life,
you know? That's the that's the thing
you need to you need to really think of.
And you ain't got an excuse cuz I'm not
even I'm not scared of flying. So you
don't even have that as an excuse.
You need to think about what you're
really going to going to do.
And I'm saying that to you as well, Grezy, you know.
Oh, Gre, I forgot to tell you. I had a
nugget meal yesterday in McDonald's. I
had a nine nugget meal. I went to
McDonald's and I had a nine nugget meal.
Yeah, cuz I was doing the washing and I
didn't really have time. So, I just I
just popped to McDonald's. I felt like
being a kid again.
I felt like I was a kid again.
Yeah, I felt like a [ __ ] kid again, bro.
Why is your telly packed up?
Why is your telly packed up, mate?
Do you like my little approaches, Steven Howard?
Well, we're on a break now anyways, so
But yeah, year in year out nothing
changes. So you need to do something.
150 Steven on roulette.
Nothing. [ __ ] nothing, mate.
Can't even [ __ ] win on that now. Jeez.
There we go.
Do you think the roulette rigged Steven Howard?
Well, I'm in a good position, bro. I
know. I've tried.
I know I've got these numbers. So,
I know I done my bit for the month.
Yeah, I know. I done my bit for the month, [ __ ] One sec. Yeah. Yeah. Exactly. Yeah, bro.
is if she wanted a one night stand. Steven Howard.
Yeah, I miss touching her body, man.
I almost touched nobody.
It was fun.
You and your little Calvin Klein bra.
See, I've had enough experiences that
the rank bank is always full, but you
don't see me [ __ ] defending them. It's weird.
God bless you. Yeah.
Yeah. Would you like it? Yeah.
She had big boobs. Steven Howard,
it was fun sucking on those tits, man.
It was fun. No.
I love this.
I just got some food back.
Anyways, I'll be back later. Yeah,
probably. Yeah, I'll be back later. Yeah. Yeah.