LJ sing again on the tubes
on the good old fashioned cubicles.
He is such a projector, bro.
[ __ ] such a projector.
Oh my god. Let more people join. He is
such a projector.
Me and Kitty. People like me and Kitty.
Oh man. Bro, you can't even take one day
off of YouTube.
Look at you singing over a [ __ ] woman again.
We can't take Listen, listen, listen.
Let's talk about you. Yeah. You claim
that you have £25,000 a month after
outgoings. You have all this money. You
can live without YouTube, yet you're sat
on YouTube begging every day, begging
for money, talking to a bunch of losers,
sing over women.
See how none of it makes any sense? Uh,
I heard about it. Yeah, someone typed
about it. Yeah.
Yeah, I heard about it, bro.
Well, not on the channel, but I see
someone type it on L J.
Look at look at how desperate can you be
to start trying to flirt with that Jane.
Let me tell you something, K. That Jane
has been emailing me and guess what I
do? I ignore it.
Yeah, cuz we all know what she's about.
I don't need to simp over any woman on
YouTube. I can go out and meet my own
women, get numbers. I got 30 numbers in
a couple of days. I'm speaking to one now.
Whether they meet me or not, it's not
the point. He's the one that sits on
YouTube all day talking to losers,
begging for money. Yeah, apparently he's
got all this money. [ __ ] off, man.
Guy's a [ __ ] joke. Literally, bro,
without YouTube, Ly's followers would be
[ __ ] They would have nothing without
YouTube. Me, I've been off of YouTube
for weeks, days.
They literally can't live without
YouTube. YouTube is literally all they
have. Why are you singing over that Jay,
man? She's [ __ ] stinking. A B.
Everyone knows what she [ __ ] does on
here. He's a s. Classic simple What? Yeah.
Yeah. He's But yeah, I heard
it's all about Ky
and L Simple Belfast. Can can't live without YouTube.
Lord simp Belfast can't
live without YouTube and talking to
losers. Literally bro,
you're probably more YouTube dependent
than [ __ ] pity to be honest. S
Lord simple go fast.
I feel [ __ ] I feel slow in that, bro.
I was drinking that white rum in that, would I?
Oh [ __ ] I feel like [ __ ] bro.
Yeah. L Simper Belfast talks about himself. Ler Belfast.
You sit on YouTube claiming you got
money. No, no, no, no, no. Yet you're
sat on YouTube begging
sing on YouTube over Jane. Do you you
think you'd ever catch me sing over a
woman on YouTube?
[ __ ] no, bro.
Why? What is it? I've been hearing some
things. I don't even know they still on YouTube.
I didn't even know they were still on
YouTube to be fair. What are they saying?
What's going on, bro?
What's going on?
Yeah. So, what channel was this all on?
What channel was this all on then?
That LJ is such a stimp. He was like to
uh Jane. Oh, let me get your number. Why
would you want Jane's number?
Why would you want Jane's number? You simp?
complete another S.
You complete a lot of simp stimpy, bro.
That is so stimpy. Yeah.
Little Franklin Grezy. You love
Franklin, don't you, Grezy?
Oh, have you seen them GTA clips? Gy
them little glitches on GTA.
I need to send you one, bro. Like the
San Andreas little clips. You'll laugh at it.
Uh, can I show you it, bro? It's funny as [ __ ]
I'm always hungry the next day. Grezy,
I'm always [ __ ] hungry the next day, man.
I just fancy you like Coke from McDonald's.
I had a Chinese earlier.
I feel [ __ ] bro.
Can I send you a GZ?
I feel [ __ ] bro. I feel [ __ ]
Swear, man. I want to send you this
thing. You're going to piss yourself
laughing. Bless you.
No, I'm going to send you anyways.
You can't get Jane. And why would you
care? Why would you care about um a
woman on YouTube as well? Everything
points in being a being a skin loser.
Literally everything, bro. All this [ __ ]
He says he gets all this money, but he's
sat on YouTube every day begging. Says
he gets all these women. He has to
resort to simp women on YouTube. See how
none of it makes any sense. He doesn't
make no sense whatsoever.
The guy's on [ __ ] job seekers
allowance, man. Come on.
Send, [ __ ] There we go. He's on
job seekers. He don't get no money. He
has no money. [ __ ] Be real with
yourself. I think we're all real and
here what we get. You know what I'm saying?
He's a sin.
There we go, bro.
Jane is not fit. She's a [ __ ] ma.
You know, when she was emailing me, I
was ignoring it.
I was ignoring it, bro. She She emails
me sometimes. I ignore it.
And that's how you know the difference
between someone that has a life and
don't have a life. Y doesn't have a
life. That's why he simps over women on YouTube.
Uh, did you watch it, Grezy?
I like these little videos. I like these
I like these little uh these little
these little clips. They're very cute,
aren't they? The little characters. Little characters.
There's another one. You know, that little video
that's making me want to play DJ San
Andreas, you know, bro.
I'm going with my [Music]
Yeah, this woman says she's seeing
someone, but that didn't stop her giving
her a little number to baby Peter Grezy,
texting me, sending me all of these X's.
We're going to try and get into the [ __ ]
Oh, what a lovely site.
I'm going to reel her in like Frankie.
rules the fishing leure. Yeah.
But yeah, that Lord J is the biggest
loser I've ever come across.
Oh, I'd love to go to Belf and just slap
that on, bro. But that would be very
silly of me, Grezy, isn't it? That'd be
a very silly thing to do cuz we all know
what these people are like on YouTube
and what they do. But that would just be
a waste of time, waste of money.
Everyone would just pretend like it
never happened. So be just just a silly thing.
[ __ ] I hate that [ __ ] bro. I really do.
Him and Virgin Boy. Him and [ __ ]
Virgin Boy, bro. I hate them. Yeah,
you like it greasy. Stop this.
I fancy McDonald's.
I fancy McDonald's. Oh my god, bro.
I already spent £10 on Chinese, but I
actually fancy a McDonald's.
[ __ ] me, bro. Did you have a McDonald's
today? This is bad, bro. Really bad.
This is really bad, bro.
Nah, I'm I'm going off coming. I had a Chinese earlier.
I just fancy a [ __ ] I just eat when I've ate.
I just eat when I've drunk all the time.
I just eat non-stop. I spent I had a
Chinese yesterday as well. Had a burger
from Weber Spoons.
Have you ever had two takeaways in a
day? I have.
I've had two takeaways.
I had a I don't really like curry in the
in the summer.
I do, but
I fancy a McDonald's. Me, bro.
Yeah, I'm never going to be able to save
money, am I?
Jerry, stop trying to troll me, bro. I'm
not Monty Man or Timmy.
I don't know how many times I have to
tell you this.
Right, let's look on the McDonald's menu.
I told you, stop trying to troll me, bro.
It's not going to work.
I'm not wanting man or Timmy.
I'm [ __ ] hung over as [ __ ] bro.
What burger do I like the look of
cheese crispy? No, cuz that's chicken.
Stay fresh tomorrow. Yeah,
I love pork chops.
No, it's not lovely, bro, cuz it's chicken. Uh uh
I think I might just get a big Mac meal.
Is that okay with you, boss?
Is that okay with you? Greasy boss.
No big mac sauce. No pickles slices. No lettuce.
And I just want cheese.
I'm going to have to go to buy greensy
first. Is that Is that okay with you, boss?
I can't believe how many [ __ ] women I approach, bro.
13 numbers in three days. I'm [ __ ] losing it.
But again, I ain't the virgin. I'm not
the virgin from Ken.
You understand? I ain't I ain't the
virgin from Ken. £11. So that would be
No, I spent more than 20 cuz I bought
some bacon today. So that would be like
roughly breakfast. Yeah, like 20 I spent
on food. Need to pack this in, Greasy.
We need to pack this in, mate.
We'll be skip like a virgin boy soon. If
if we carry this up,
we'll be skip like the the [ __ ] virgin, mate.
It's not funny. We'll be skip like the
virgin. You know what I mean? No,
I've got like no [ __ ] selfawareness, mate. None.
We're not going to We need to start
saving from tomorrow, bro.
I need to start saving from tomorrow, man.
No, I'm serious. Yes, I do. Bro, I need
to do some food chopping tomorrow, bro,
cuz I will go broke if I keep doing this.
I will be [ __ ]
I will be [ __ ] up. Yeah,
think I've already spent about 700.
Yeah. Is that a little GTA thing? Greasy. Da
just ordered some McDonald's. But yeah,
I'm going to have some pork chops
tomorrow. I'm going to do a 40 food shop tomorrow, Grey.
And it's going to have to last a week.
That would be
I want to end up like that skin virgin from Kent. [ __ ] hell.
I just don't want to end up like that
skin virgin groovy.
I lost one [ __ ] 50 today
which was silly but I don't want to end
up like that skin virgin.
So he's the wow and benefit of what I'm
saying. Don't worry, mate.
They need to be I don't know why L J and
this Virgin don't just be real.
But I do have to come online and act
like they've got money when they
literally have nothing.
They literally have [ __ ] all.
I don't need to lie about anything, bro.
I tell you how much I get,
how much I get, how much I have.
They have to lie. Lord J says that he gets25,000
a month after outgoings. That's [ __ ]
At least with me, bro. I was living in
[ __ ] London, so the rent is [ __ ] expensive.
That Lord J
is on carers allowance. Not car is
allowed. He is on job seekers
that £350 a month. 100% [ __ ]
That's what he's on.
Nothing more. Bro,
think a bit greasy. Let's be realistic
about this here. If you was getting all
of this money, would you be sat on
YouTube begging every day?
You wouldn't. Would you be on YouTube
begging for money every day? You got all
this money, bro. Let's face facts.
It's cuz he's skint. He needs money for
survival cuz he's skint just like the virgin.
You need to see people's lifestyles,
bro. You understand? Yeah. He's skinting.
Flynn, you like it when I say that.
Don't you agree, boss?
You greasy boss
skint. than the food and skin. Yeah.
Yeah. This woman replied back,
"I think she likes Peter Belly."
Yeah. Incredibly skinn skin like Lord J, bro. Yeah.
Nah, the only people that are skinn is
you people sat on YouTube every day.
Sat on you. These people's YouTube
activity gives them away. It gives their
whole life away.
Cuz if they weren't skinned, they would
be sat on YouTube every day. Look what I
was doing yesterday, bro.
I'm only just calming it. Think of it.
These people, all this money, right,
that sat on YouTube every day.
[ __ ] that, bro. You know,
they won't be s on YouTube every day if
they want to skip.
You got my car.
But honestly, that large skin, what's
your opinion, Stephen Howard? It all
points to what somebody would do on £300
a month coming online begging for money.
I don't I would never take any money
from any of you [ __ ] on YouTube.
That's like a last resort sort of thing
just to try to get a bit of extra money.
So that's how you know he's he is generally
skinned as [ __ ] You know what I'm saying?
But yeah, [ __ ] skin, bro. You think you
would do all of that extra last resort
[ __ ] for a tiny bit of extra money if
you had all this money? Come on, bro.
Please. Just like the virgin skint.
They all live skint lives. Look at what
I was doing and look what I'm still doing.
Virgin boy ain't even got a bed.
Virgin boy ain't even got a [ __ ] bed, bro.
You're very skinn
trying to say that he says that I can't
live without YouTube. Steven Howard when
he he's the one that's on it all day
every day and can't take a day off of
it. He has to flirt with women on
YouTube. Him and his [ __ ] followers.
I would love to go there and smash his
face in. You know, bro,
if I didn't know any better about what
these people are like, I'd be there now,
bro. I'm not even joking.
But I said I'll never meet anyone on
here ever again cuz of like what they do
and [ __ ] So yeah, bro, [ __ ] that.
He's never off YouTube. [ __ ]
followers never I've took weeks off of
YouTube, bro. Weeks.
Basically, what what you got to
understand is Yeah. Basically with this uh
with this place, whatever they say about
you, they're really just talking about themselves
because it takes one to no one. So they
say you're skin, they're skin. They say
you are bored and they're bored. They
say you're ugly, they're ugly.
Everything is about themselves.
Basically what they say about you is is
just about their own lives.
You get me?
And Jane's a [ __ ]
She's a [ __ ] troll, man. She emails
me. I ignore the [ __ ]
I ignore the [ __ ] Yeah,
I ignore that [ __ ] bro. What the [ __ ]
I can meet women off of YouTube me.
Even though they're [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, for real, man.
Bro, to be honest, I don't even think
they're on pip.
I think they're on that job seekers. I
don't even think they're on pip, bro.
Cuz I was actually thinking of it
because obviously I was so used to three
grand a month. Yeah. Like £1,100 [ __ ]
But you know if you got out no outgoings
and [ __ ] £1,100 you could easily just go out and
do stuff and
no no no and [ __ ] So that's how you
know they want job seekers. I don't even
think they get that cuz that is still
quite a lot for a single person.
you can still go out and do stuff with
$1,100 a month, you know,
but um yeah, they they want that universal credit
£300 a month. They've got to be, bro.
That [ __ ] crazy.
She don't want you.
She don't want to know you. Steven Howard
Yeah. So, what are you thinking about
saving anyway, Grezy?
You got to pack this [ __ ] in. You do, mate.
You got to pack this [ __ ] spending
money [ __ ] You know,
I've got to pack it in.
I just got nothing to lose. I'm a single
person. I got no outgoings. So yeah,
except my phone.
I used to get seven underpowered a
month. What do you think of that a
month, Grezy? 700 pound. That is [ __ ]
isn't it? Yeah.
What I'm going to probably do is try
with a football bet like £80
to try and get like £300 and probably
spend a£300 on nights out
through nights out and then obviously
save the rest of the money.
Probably what I'll end up doing to be fair.
Yeah, smart idea.
That'll get you like two nights out. Maybe £300.
Obviously, you just save your rest of
the money in it. So,
I'm happy, bro. Like I said, I got a TV,
got a place, they got Xbox. uh laughing.
Everyone's got Tik Tok planes now. Yep.
I can't believe how many women's numbers
I got. I'm [ __ ] mad I am.
All right. Do you think there's too many
stuck up [ __ ] in this country, Grezy?
I think so.
I I think so. Yeah.
You like Antman? Um, Steven Howard,
I think he's a pretty good [ __ ]
I think he's a pretty good company. Oh [ __ ]
Grezy, they're just not interested in this country.
Simple as that. I don't know why you cry
about it, Greavvesy, man. [ __ ] sake.
They're just not interested in this
country. Simple as that. Why do you cry
about it? I don't know why you always
cry about it, Grezy.
My eyes are [ __ ] bro. All that rum in it.
Greasy. They're just not interested in
this country. Simple as that. What's the problem? Huh?
You always cry and stuff.
Simple as that. You're supposed to cry, baby. Oh,
I'm on the same money as Grezy now, basically.
I'm going to make some money on a
football. You watch? Yeah.
They just aren't interested in this country.
Do you like England Grezy? Huh?
Imagine me and USA is having McDonald's.
Oh, she would eat it all.
She would eat it all. She's a fat pig.
How did she get so fat?
She got really fat in it.
She got fat in it.
I can't believe that Ronald Pump
account. I'll never forget what he said
to me, bro. I wonder where he is nowadays.
He said people like Red Star and Virgin
Boy and all of these people
He's like, "Oh, you're better looking
than them. You got a better life than
them, and you got more money than them,
and it kills them." He told me to get
off of YouTube and live my life.
That's what he told me. And his name is Ronald Pump.
I think it's true, isn't it?
Ronald Pump with a green avatar. That's
what he told me. He said he told me to
get off YouTube and live my life.
Yeah, it's true that is it? Yeah.
Yeah, obviously it is, bro.
How long can one be obsessed for? Do you
know what I mean?
And it kills them.
I'm just on my little mobile.
What the DC though,
they just aren't interested in this country. Grey,
I made loads of new friends recently. Grey.
Yep. Made lots of new friends.
Is that cute?
Peter Bell in his little cap.
Oh, speaking of caps, when when are my
caps coming? One sec.
My little caps.
Where was it?
Oh, bugs money. One second.
Package is on its way to your country. Huh?
Well, that ain't good, is it?
I bought myself some caps from Timmy.
Cost me £11.
Yeah, cost me £11. Some bugs bunny ones. etc. Onwards. Yeah.
My little caps. Yeah. I've got a Bugs
Bunny one. I got a Mickey Mouse one.
And a Donald Duck one.
should be here soon, bro. Franklin.
Everybody loves Franklin.
He looks clean with that new cut, isn't it?
No, I'm not joking. I'm being serious.
There's so many caps to choose from. I
had to get three. Grievy.
I got a panda one and Mickey. Yeah.
Panda, Mickey Mouse, and Bugs Bunny. And um Donald Duck.
Yeah, I got Donald Duck, Mickey Mouse,
and a panda one. £11.
Yeah, there was so many.
And they're so cheap. I tried to get
three of them. Still got more to be honest.
There's a Mickey Mouse one, too.
Py's little cap.
There's a Tweety Pie one as well. It's 189.
Yeah, there's a Tweety Pie one.
I just end up buying like 50 of them,
bro. There's so many of them.
No fall apart. My little caps. Franklin.
Do you like Franklin Greaves? He's a
nice little character.
He's a nice little character.
He cost me £15 a month. Yep. Yeah.
No, CJ is quite nice, too.
Come on, Mackey's. I'm waiting on you.
I'm waiting on you, Mackey's. Come on.
Oh, yeah. Yeah,
I'll wear a Bug's bunny cap with a pink
t-shirt. I don't I don't give a [ __ ] me.
I don't care.
I don't care what this I quote society
deems as socialable socially be social socially acceptable.
I'll do the very opposite of what they
deem as socially acceptable. I don't
give a [ __ ]
if you feel me, Grevy.
[ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] what they deem
as socially acceptable. What? looking at
Tik Tok all day and [ __ ] Instagram is
socially acceptable to [ __ ] with what
they deem socially acceptable. These [ __ ]
you know what I'm saying?
Who's with me?
Yeah, I'm waiting for it. I remember
when I used to meet Virgin Boy, he used
to say, "Oh, that's not socially
acceptable." I said, "I don't give a
fuck." I used to say to him on the train
as well, I don't care what's socially
acceptable or not. I don't give a [ __ ]
I said, "Your [ __ ] your [ __ ] self
ain't [ __ ] socially acceptable, you silly cunt." Yeah.
You know what I mean, Grezy? What What
is socially acceptable? Being on TikTok
all day, having a bad day, and trying to
ruin other people's day. Is that socially acceptable?
Is that socially acceptable? Grezy
The only place you're not going to get
I've got a boyfriend is Asia.
I've already told you this, Grey. The
only place you're not going to get it is Asia.
Yeah, I do remember.
But Grezy doesn't listen. And I've told
Greg this about a million times. The
only place you're not going to get it is Asia,
but he doesn't listen. The only the only
place you're the only place you're not
going to get it, that's what Antman said to me.
He said, "The only place you're not
going to get a boyfriend."
Well, my Maki should be here.
You hear me?
Give me my McDonald's right now.
Can't believe I lost 150 on roulette today.
[ __ ] [ __ ] It
I'm waiting on it. Where is it?
Shame it's here.
Where the [ __ ] are these [ __ ]
Where the [ __ ] are these [ __ ] Remember
that one, Grezy?
Where are my boxes?
That's nice. I can give you a number if
you want her back. I can give you a
number if you want.
Yeah, if you want a number, I'll give
you a number, man. 0258. >> 0258.
>> No, no. 0285.
>> Thank you.
Did you hear what I said? Crazy.
Did you hear what I said? It
Thank you, C.
I got myself a Big Mac meal.
Big M. I want some Franklin.
Thank you, C.
Thank you. What did you say?
That's what he said to the supervisor,
one of the tenants where I kept saying,
"Cunt." He picked it up and he said to
the super supervisor by accident, "Thank you, cunt."
Supervisor like, "What did you just
say?" He said, "Oh, it's just a slip of
the tongue." He said, "Yeah, watch your
tongue." Thank you, gun.
I was dead.
Oh, I was dead when I first heard that
heard that, bro. I can imagine that must
have been so awkward.
It's a nice coke.
Oh, I got a cheeseburger. Franklin,
was you there when I went on door?
You know when I went on Isabelle's door?
I was going to give her a [ __ ] good
that day, mate. [ __ ] trolling me on YouTube.
>> Yeah, I was going to [ __ ] give her a
[ __ ] good eye then. Enough of you Mhm.
Yeah, it was quite a few years ago, mate.
M. The chips are lovely.
M You remember who used to do that? I
thought they didn't put cheese on that
for a minute. They [ __ ] did. They [ __ ] do.
Do you remember who used to do that? Yeah, Mark.
I love what s is repetitive.
I remember when I used to meet the
virgin, Stephen Howard.
Yeah. Remember when I used to used to
meet the virgin? Must
be a big version.
I had an argument. I had an argument
with one of the attendant today, bro.
Oh, a madness. But I put him in his place. Oh yeah.
No, he's a big virgin. But he's a big
I knew Eddie was a virgin.
I I knew from that day he was going to die once. M. Oh, nice. Nice burger.
Wow, it's nice.
I'm not from Kent, lads. I'm not a Kent virgin. Say Virgin, mate.
You say is his boobs were tasty.
I got withdrawal symptoms.
Yeah, you got withdrawal symptoms, you guys.
That's why you take a piss.
But that's why I say it's like taking a
baby away from its mama.
Taking a baby away from its mama
to be learning to be attached and to be dropped.
Oh, that's cruel.
And then after that when my mommy um put
me up and they had to I went into care grezy
I went into care I I went into care
because I was abandoned
cuz obly I was supposed to go back
to America you see with her and
obviously this didn't happen I got put into care you see
and since that Hey, I've not been right.
Yeah, I got put into care. The sound of it.
You remember she called me a
[ __ ] She said, "You
You're sick and Christmasy motherfucker." Remember?
You like that, didn't you?
You should. You're sick and twisted, [ __ ]
I got took away from my mama.
She'll have a baby soon, I reckon. What
do you think, Grezy?
I got the feeling.
Yeah, I am on it. I'm on the McDonald's.
That was a good one. I am on it. I'm on Ronald McDonald. Yeah,
I'm on the Ronald McDonald. Yeah, thanks.
What are you up to, you [ __ ]
I'm not drinking now for two weeks. I
need a rest. I need a rest.
That goodness is a killer.
You ever had goodness squeezy?
You about to [ __ ] y'all. What? Quite strong though.
Would you go out with virgin boy?
I wouldn't go out with virgin boy.
Yes. Probably smell the virginity on him
and then probably want away the virgin.
They probably smelled a virgin on him
and run away.
A [ __ ] virgin.
What is that or something? N.
Thank you, son.
Oh, that was nice music.
Tummy is full now.
Well, at least I [ __ ] eat good, don't I? M
Can't be a McDonald's coke.
It's like crack. You know what I mean?
Grievous. It's like crack. I don't know
what they put in it. Oh, lovely.
I wish USA Izzy was here right now.
Oh, it'd be nice, man.
Maybe with her big boobs again.
Isn't that right, Grezy? Yeah.
Like the good old days.
That was lovely, man. No, I want to drink it.
But that that McDonald's Coke is nice.
USA is got big boobs, man.
They're all mine.
They were all mine. Remember,
Grezy, that's the most funniest saying.
You're my mommy, no one else's.
You're my mama, nobody else's.
That's funny, is it? I thought that was
one of the best sayingings, me.
I think it's cute, bro.
What picture should I put up?
Oh, I like him. He's cute.
Do you like that little character?
Do you like that little character? He's
cute, isn't he? Yeah.
Why do you love King so much, Grezy?
You love King, don't you? You love I
think King loves I think Grezy loves
King the most.
You love King, don't you? What is it
with you and King?
That's king. That was king the other day. Yeah, Kingston.
That was him the other day. Yeah. Baters.
We called him bats. Yeah.
It's funny, isn't it?
Yeah, he's fat now.
But everyone loves King, don't they? Yeah.
Do you think he's got a cute face, Grezy?
It is him.
Yeah, he likes McDonald's. He likes the
burgers. He used to We used I used to
get him one every day and he used to wait patiently.
Yeah, King loves McDonald's.
He's a good dog.
Your eyes are not
One second, bro. No.
Where's the camera?
One second, bro.
Do you want me to do a zoom in? What?
I don't know.
You ready, king? I'm greasy. I mean,
that is funny as [ __ ] Oh,
that is [ __ ]
That's like That's like That's like the
Franklin Zoom in, bro. Yeah.
But it is, please.
I love him, bro. He's cute. He looks like Stitch.
Yeah, he's a
he's he looks like Stits, doesn't he? Grezy.
Oh, he's cute, man.
Would you, if someone said you could,
would you would you look after King Grezy?
Would you would you take him on if he
had nowhere else to go? Yeah.
You would, wouldn't you? Yeah.
Yeah, I think he would.
No, he's too cute.
Who's this [ __ ]
Who the [ __ ] is that [ __ ]
King's cute. Kingston.
He come in, bro, one morning when I was
staying around. Yeah. And he was licking
my legs. Greavvesy.
He [ __ ] woke me up.
What's going down? [ __ ] all. Just
had a McDonald's. I went out yesterday
to do some approaches.
Same old I've got a boyfriend. Same old England.
Got some numbers. Usually don't go
anywhere. Now just sat chilling, bro.
Lost 150 on roulette today. Yep.
I don't gamble really anymore. That was
the first time I gambled for like 2 months. So yeah,
I don't play it. That was the first time
in two months. I don't play it.
I don't play it, bro. That was the first
time in two months.
[ __ ] You gamble once, people think
you're addicted, Grezy.
Nah, they weren't funny, man. Yeah.
Uh, nothing new. Same old [ __ ] Go out
every week, get rejected,
go home, chill.
Nothing new really. Same old [ __ ]
Oh yeah, man. Same old
same old life in England, isn't it?
Depressed, isn't it?
Who the [ __ ] is that? Is that bomb? Bomb.
Where the [ __ ] is that up, bro?
Don't know why you email me, Jane. I'm
not playing your silly little games.
I don't know why you still email me, love.
Go to [ __ ] Lord J the S.
I don't know why you email me.
You emailed me.
You was emailing me.
Well, I don't give a [ __ ] about YouTube, mate.
Do you want my opinion? You're all [ __ ]
Why do you think you don't see me on
here for a couple of weeks? I think
you're all a bunch of [ __ ]
You ask me.
Got someone messaging me. Yeah.
So, what you been up to anyways, Jane,
except from lurking on YouTube,
I was thinking of actually going Cardiff
next week to be honest. Yeah.
Don't know. Maybe not. Maybe somewhere else.
Nah, I'm not meeting you, mate. Don't
meet people from YouTube.
You can meet nonsexs.
I ain't meeting you, mate. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that, mate. You and Bson's caused
a lot of trouble.
Is that actually the real you, Jane?
You can't suck me in. I go out and eat
my own women.
I don't need you. Really, Jake?
So, why did you um why did you split up with Mark? Huh?
Do you know where that place is in
Cardiff? The square bit where there's the club
in the square
uh by the five guys. You know Cardiff?
There's like a square.
I don't know if you know what I'm
talking about. There's like a square
and there's like stairs that it's like a
sort of bar thing.
There was a big fight that happened
there last time I went with a bouncer.
It was quite scary.
It was quite scary. Remember that one,
Grezy? It was quite a vicious attack.
It was quite vicious.
When did you last go to Cardiff City Center, Jane?
I remember the first time I went to
Cardiff. It was so good. The first time
I went, good hotel,
got some [ __ ] Those
were good days. No plans. I was just
like, "Fuck it. I'm just going to go Wales. [ __ ] it."
I kissed three [ __ ] that day as well.
That was a mad bastard, bro.
I was back when I used to go gym.
Why? Why don't you like the club life?
Yeah, I never been to Wales before. I'd
only been to Scotland twice, so I
thought, "Fuck it. Let me just go Wales."
Yeah, it was good, man.
What? You want to go clubbing, Jane?
You want to go clubbing? We should We
could go clubbing. Yeah, I prefer pubs
nowadays. I prefer Weather Spoons.
I prefer [ __ ] Weather Spoons me to be fair.
Less [ __ ] Uh
they don't tell you what you can and can't wear. Yeah.
No, you're never too old. [ __ ] up, Jesus.
You're never too old. Yeah.
So, why did you you I heard you speak
about LT, how he [ __ ] his girl.
Yeah. So what, bro?
Come in the hangouts.
Yeah, I only knew about that. That's old news.
Yeah, that's old news, man.
That is old news.
But to be fair, Fraser was trolling him.
That's why he done it.
He was speaking to some girl that I got
with from America. But I don't care.
He's American. Yeah. But he done that
because of what [ __ ] Fraser done. You know understand?
Yeah. I knew that ages ago, man.
The one that tries to stiff around all
the women on here is Tiger and LJ. L is
the ultimate simp. I got 13 women's
numbers in 3 days.
I got 13 women's numbers in 3 days.
Yeah. But it doesn't matter. But that
will never happen to me because he
doesn't know what women I speak to. So
if you if he doesn't know
Yeah. Think about it. Yeah, I I I I women's numbers.
He doesn't know any of the women that I
know. So, it it doesn't matter. As long
as he doesn't know anyone I know, then
you don't need to worry about it, do you?
By Nicolo. Yeah. I tried to get that
Indonesian fella to approach yesterday.
He wouldn't do it. I bought him two
Guinnesses and I got us two Guinnesses
and two baby Guinnesses and he wouldn't do it.
He said that. He said, "Oh, there's too
many of them." I said, "I'll [ __ ] do it.
There was [ __ ] five of the [ __ ] went
that went there, got the number.
I'm flirting with this woman right now. So,
uh, that's him, bro. It
said to him, you can have that one in
America. Go to America and have her. I don't care.
Yeah, but he doesn't know because it doesn't happen
cuz he doesn't if he does that, he
doesn't do it, bro. He's too scared to
even do that now.
What's the point of coming out if you're scared?
He's scared, bro. This guy is proper
Yeah, I got five numbers yesterday. me.
I don't [ __ ] I do it sober, bro. I
don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah, it is cowardly though. But he
doesn't try with anyone I do it with cuz
he uh he's too scared. Like he didn't go
up to any of them.
He's scared. He is actually pure scared.
Whereas one of the tenants, he doesn't
drink cuz he's Muslim, but he used to do
it in the clubs, just not on the street.
I'm not loyal. I don't care.
Are you going to come in the hangouts?
I'll put the link up.
I'm not loyal to him. I don't even speak
to him. You [ __ ] silly case. What woman?
What woman was she bragging about?
So he's talking about
which one, bro? I don't know who you on about.
Which one was he bragging about? Do you?
Well, the American one that I got with
I don't know what short you on that, man.
The one that I met, she had big boobies, Jane.
She had big boobies.
He had really big groupies. [Music]
There's a lot that you don't know about
that Arsenal Mark as well.
You don't know that I went to his area
two times and he didn't come out. And I
was live on YouTube and he didn't come out.
That Mark Samson's a fraud. He is a big
and he's never been on my door.
He's He just wants attention.
That Mark Samson is what you call a
fraud. I've been to his area two times.
He didn't show up and he started
sniffing around Izzy and [ __ ] So I
thought, "Fuck this. The [ __ ] didn't
come. The [ __ ] didn't come out.
He ain't a good man. He's a [ __ ] He's
a weirdo, mate. That Mark Samson is a [ __ ] weirdo.
How old are you, Jane?
See, I would come to Cardiff, but the thing is
you're um you're going to put me all over YouTube.
I know what your game is,
but I'm not Samson a proper [ __ ]
All of this like him trying to call
people out, it's just for attention.
All of this calling out people is just for attention,
Jane. It's all for attention.
All of it's for attention, you know.
So, anyways, what else about this LT? What else?
I knew that phrase is girl thing ages ago.
No, he is a bad man.
Well, we'll have our different opinions, won't we? Yep.
So, join the hangouts. Yeah.
These friends scared my mommy.
Bless Laney. Lane is a good soul.
Are you are you going to come on the hangouts?
You going to come and give it a whirl?
You still there, Greg? I'm waiting on my 80. Okie do.
Yeah, I get 80 pound on mid at midnight,
Grezy. I get 80 a week.
Isn't that lush? £80 a week, Grezy.
It's quite nice, isn't it? £80.
I pay for the McDonald's and stuff. Oh, [ __ ]
Jane wants me to come Cardiff.
Jane, I can't come to Cardiff. People
will start talking.
People will start talking. You know this, Jane.
People will start talking, mate.
will start talking matey. Isn't that right? All
right, let's see what James got to say for herself.
Okie dokie. I'll be here.
I'll be waiting patiently. Is that cute?
Do you like lady greavesy? Laney.
Yeah. Lenny's old.
I'm [ __ ] so tired. But can you
imagine I tried going out today drinking? Nah. Nah,
I wouldn't be able to
No, mate. [ __ ] that. What would happen
if I tried today, Grezy? I think I would
have died, bro.
What do you think? Listen.
How long is it? The little
virgin boy couldn't do that.
Hurry up, Jane.
Nah, he's never bit me. No,
he's called me though.
And I've had to say [ __ ] claw me, you
He's clawed me.
And it ain't nice. It ain't nice and
you're not expecting it, you [ __ ]
It's not nice and you're not expecting
it. It's horrible, man. Yeah. You
[ __ ] bite me, you [ __ ]
You me [ __ ]
Laney said that to the dog. I got up
from Laney. She he clawed Laney and
she's like, "How you claw me, you cunt?"
I said, "Oh, you know, fuck."
I said, "She don't call the dog a cunt."
She I weren't expecting it. Yeah,
[ __ ] copy. We [ __ ] How could a dog
be a [ __ ]
I can't do with these two [ __ ]
I can't do with these two [ __ ] mate.
Yeah. No KFC.
Bless him. He's a lovely little water though.
So is that Natalie G pregnant? Yeah.
He's a fat one. Yeah.
No, I'm waiting for this train. How many One second.
Damn man. Oh. Oh, [ __ ]
She coming back.
Are you coming or what, man?
Sorry, I'm I'm watching I'm watching GTA.
Can you hear me? Hello. Hey y'all. One second.
>> Hello. Can't hear. Can't hear you. What?
>> Hello. I'm trying to I'm trying to flip the camera.
>> Can you hear me? >> Yeah.
>> How are you, CL?
>> Hang on. Wait there. Hang on.
>> The mic's a bit [ __ ]
>> I know. Hang on. Um,
>> am I on? >> Yeah.
>> Oh, okay.
>> What's the story?
>> Hang on. Wait there. I'm going to come
out and come back. I'm going to come out
and come back in. >> Okay.
>> Hang on.
I will be right back.
>> I think it's my my thing to be honest. Yeah. Yo,
show you what he left. Yeah. Jade. Oh, Jade. You good? Hello. You're muted. >> Hello.
>> Yeah. Can you hear me? Yeah.
>> Yeah. What's up?
>> Nothing. What are you doing?
Just chilling, man. Just still hung over from yesterday.
>> Oh, hang on.
Is um is my camera facing front or back? >> Front.
>> Okay, hang on.
>> My god, my hair is a mess.
>> Yeah, I think that L wants you.
>> I don't blame him.
He's a [ __ ] ugly [ __ ] isn't he?
>> Well, what's going on?
>> Nothing, mate. He's just an ugly
bastard, isn't he?
>> I think he's good looking.
>> Yeah, you must be [ __ ] blind.
>> Hang on.
>> Yeah, I know. So, um I saw all the
comments calling me a fat [ __ ] and everything. >> Who?
>> No, on here.
>> Yeah. Who said that?
>> All the time.
>> Yeah. People say you should see what
people say about me. I don't give a [ __ ] man.
>> Yeah, I know. But
it's not very nice, is it? Bless
>> you. You and you and your little Welsh accent, eh?
So, what's going on?
>> Nothing. Just chilling.
Say while she it
>> look at Jane like putting herself out
there like not trying to hide her
identity and that.
>> So, what's going on with this LT then?
>> Ah, he's a wrong.
>> What's he done? I already knew about
that phrase I think ages ago. You're late, man.
>> Did um
did you see the pictures of me that he put online? >> No,
>> you did. I sent you the link.
>> Yeah, I didn't click on it. >> Why?
>> Cuz it's just all [ __ ] is it? This
whole YouTube thing is is bollocks, isn't it?
So, how how old are you now?
>> Uh, 25. >> Really?
>> No, that can't be right.
>> Am I lying? >> Yeah.
>> Hang on.
>> You remember when you was on the phone talking dirty? >> No. >> Yeah.
You was talking dirty. You was.
>> You wish. Mate,
>> mate, it's recorded. Everyone heard it.
>> Oh, when you fre me.
>> No, you was on the phone talking absolute filth.
>> Yeah. And you and you lied.
>> No, I didn't say. How did I lie?
>> Cuz you never said like, Anyway, I'm I'm
not interested now. What are we talking about?
Um, we're talking about LT. >> Yeah.
Have you actually met him in real life? >> Nope.
>> No, absolutely not. Total fraud.
>> Yeah, but so is that Mark Samson? >> No,
>> he is.
>> How? No, I I've
I've dated him for five years. Like, no.
He comes on YouTube, right, calling
people out for attention when he's been
on the sniff and then when someone and
then he doesn't finish it. He's a
[ __ ] He's a fraud, man.
>> But do you know do you know you and LT
how disrespectful you two have been to
me is like crazy.
>> I don't even speak to you or talk about
you. So, how's that?
>> No, but look at the things you say about me. But
>> I didn't say anything.
You got the wrong person. I didn't say nothing. Me?
>> Wow. I think uh
I think people on here are deluded. >> Why?
I see myself as a normal woman and
people like just want to be disrespectful and hang on.
Oh, I don't know. Why is this so
complicated? Oh, there we go. Am I front
or back camera?
>> The front. >> Front. >> Yeah.
>> Why can't I see it?
>> What? Are you just showing everyone what
you look like?
>> There's nothing wrong with me.
>> That's good then, isn't it? At least
you're not insecure.
>> I I don't have anything
to Yeah, exactly that. I don't have
anything to be insecure about.
Can I come to your house for a sleepover? >> No. >> Why?
>> Cuz you more than anyone have been so
disrespectful to me.
>> No way.
>> And do you know what? Like you and your mates.
>> Dane, stop being such a silly goose. How
dare he put my private images up
and like think that's okay.
>> Probably such as a silly goose.
>> Anyway, what's new?
>> Um, I'm going to go to Cardiff tomorrow. >> Yeah.
>> Want to meet up?
>> No, I'm busy tomorrow.
Want to meet up for a Welsh reb?
>> A what?
>> A W A Welsh rebby.
>> I thought you were Muslim. >> Nah.
>> I thought you was halal.
>> Yeah, I'm Well, I'm Muslim. Yeah,
>> you're halal.
>> I'm Muslim. Yes.
>> Oh, I don't like Muslims.
>> Why? What have we ever done to you?
I I don't agree with that.
>> What? So, but that's my religion.
>> Yeah, I don't agree with that.
>> So, what religion are you? >> Pardon?
>> What religion are you?
>> I'm a Christian.
>> Oh, I don't believe in Christians.
You don't Well,
you don't need to, but I I'm a Christian.
>> No, I'm joking. I'm atheist.
>> Are you? >> Yeah.
I thought you didn't I thought when you
had your barbecue, it was Hello.
>> No, I was taking a piss. I'm atheist.
>> Okay. I believe in God.
I don't believe in anything. I like
pigs. I like piggies. I like bacon. >> Okay. Well,
anyway, so do you know your weird mate? >> Yeah.
>> You've never met him in real life, have you? >> No. Uh,
very very dodgy, sinister man.
>> I think he's quite a cool guy. Me. >> Really? >> Yeah.
>> After he broke into your house. >> Yeah.
>> I think you two staged that.
>> So, what would have happened if I was in
the house that day?
>> I I think you two staged it. It wasn't.
It was. Are you okay?
>> There's no way.
>> Staged it. The whole window got broken.
You [ __ ] idiot. How could it have been staged?
>> There's no way you would ever be okay
with someone that did that to your home,
>> bro. He broke the whole window. Why
would it be staged?
>> Oh, I But he probably got what? Like
some little youth to do that. Yeah, cuz
I told somebody to come break into my
house and steal an electric bike and I
never got back. Yeah, that's staged. Yeah. Okay.
>> Yeah, of course it is.
>> No, he he he takes advantage of you and
he takes advantage like
>> he never gave the bike back. It wasn't
my bike. It was one of the tenants and
he still hasn't given it back.
>> I understand that. But what I'm saying
is he never broke no window. He never
broke into your home. The man is an absolute [ __ ]
>> So who done it then?
>> He probably got he probably gave like
some little hoodrat a tenner to do it.
It wasn't him. Absolutely not.
He is the poshest gangster
and nothing he says is true. Nothing. I
I can promise you that. I've got no
reason to lie to you. Really?
>> In fact, if if if I'm lying, it's an
open platform. Let him come on and call me out. [Music]
>> Do you speak to Chase? >> No.
>> He lives in your city.
>> Yeah. I don't speak to him. I don't know
>> But you must know him because you knew
who I was talking about.
>> I know. I knew what
>> I said. I didn't get my house, Rob. He
didn't take nothing from me. That bike
wasn't mine. He didn't he he didn't take
my house. It wasn't my house.
>> No, but you you show loyalty to him. If
you if if somebody broke into my home, I
wouldn't show loyalty to them. I
wouldn't speak to them. I wouldn't
entertain it for a second. >> Yeah.
>> It's a fit up. It was it it didn't happen like >> Yeah.
>> Do you know I will say one thing for you.
People can say whatever they want
but like you are true to yourself and I
know and you know he didn't break into your home.
>> Well, whoever done well someone did
>> but it wasn't him.
>> Yeah. It doesn't. I know. But it
summoned it, didn't it?
>> Yeah. It wasn't him. >> Maybe.
>> Like I said, he might have got a little
hood raft, do it, but it wasn't him.
>> He two had had a thing going on for ages now.
>> He doesn't even live in London.
>> Yeah. Not anymore. He moved. He He told
everyone he moved.
>> Absolute madness. It's like you're
inferior of this guy and he is nothing
that he says he is. Literally nothing.
>> Have you been on the drink, Jane? >> Then
>> have you been on the drink?
>> No, I'm just on so stream. >> Yeah,
>> you know I'm not lying. That's why
you're trying to
>> That L is a fraud as well though. I
don't know why you speak to him.
I've only spoke to him tonight for the first time.
>> He is the biggest fraud going. >> Why?
>> Because he claims that he gets all this
money. Yeah. He's on YouTube begging
every [ __ ] day. He talks to all of
these [ __ ] losers. He begs for money.
He's a fraud.
>> But in the same way as I see you with
him, what you see is where you get.
>> I don't come on YouTube begging for money.
I don't see him do it. Well, I I don't
>> Yes, he does. Yes, he does.
>> Well, I I I don't know. I don't watch it.
But I'm I'm just saying that the guy
you're so loyal to
like literally posted my body over his
channel in revenge porn
and it It's wrong. >> Yeah.
Yeah, but you've come on here and you've
trolled before, Jade. >> Who?
>> You've trolled me.
>> You wish.
>> You have trolled. >> Who?
>> You've trolled me.
>> Anything I've ever had to say to anyone,
I would say
directly to them or I would let that
person know I've said it about them. I I
don't hide behind accounts. I I've never
ever needed to do that.
>> I think you think it's all a laugh, me. >> Wow.
>> You do, don't you? >> What?
>> Think it's all a laugh. >> Yeah,
>> you do, don't you? >> Absolutely.
Isn't it funny how all you people
made like trolled me in the worst way
saying I was fat and [ __ ] and then like now
what has anyone got to say?
>> I agree you fat.
>> Yeah, you did. >> Nah.
>> Yeah, you did. Numerous occasions.
>> That was LT.
>> No. No. Yeah. >> No,
>> it was.
>> You're a liar. >> No,
these people try to hate on me every
day, but I I ignore it because I know
they're just talking about themselves.
>> I mean, I'm going to be honest. I am the
elite of the community.
>> What do you mean?
Like I am the bollocks.
>> Yeah, but you're on your last legs.
>> What do you mean?
>> Like you're getting really old, Jane. >> Really? >> Yeah. [Laughter]
You're a troll. [ __ ] off, man. You're a
>> I'm on my last leg, so I'm in my coffin. >> Yeah. Yep.
You're getting on though, aren't you?
>> Yeah, I'm 37 next week. >> Really? >> Yeah.
>> Know how time flies, eh?
>> Doesn't it just But do you know what you
like you people on here like you are disrespectful? >> Yeah. >> Um So yeah, [Music]
>> you're a troll. You're a troll.
>> I am a troll.
>> I might have to come to come to Cardiff
and slap you. >> Yeah.
>> I'm a troll. Okay. Yeah.
>> Okay. But anyway,
go back to the original discussion.
>> How your ex is a complete [ __ ] >> Pardon?
>> He's actually like No,
>> he actually is.
>> No. No.
>> Yes, he is. I went live right by his
house two times and the [ __ ] did not come out.
>> Absolutely. Listen,
>> everyone saw it. Everyone saw it.
>> Okay, listen. I I was sent from your
partner in crime
a photo last a couple of weeks ago where
apparently he spray painted Mark's
garden wall. Mark is a non >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. That wasn't Mark's wall. Nobody's
wall was spray painted. It's all for
show. Like I should be
>> He's still there. Ghosted. It's funny
though, isn't it?
>> You and him are as wack as each other.
>> Yeah, but guess what? Your man comes on
YouTube calling people out then shits it
when someone tries to meet him. So, you know,
>> I'm in my own lane. I speak for me
myself and I. I'm not affiliated to
anyone. But I am telling you, you and LT are literally
>> And I'm telling you, your ex-boyfriend
has never been on my [ __ ] door ever
because he would have got a [ __ ] good
iding, mate. Let me tell you that.
>> Because I stopped him,
>> mate. Stopped him. But he ain't got the balls.
>> I stopped him many, many.
>> You stopped him? Yeah. How could a How
could a How can an old woman stop him? Come on.
>> An old woman? >> Yeah. Really?
>> Stopped him. The guy would get [ __ ]
hurt. Please. He's a [ __ ]
>> How many years has he done this on
YouTube now? Huh?
>> Very old, battered, you know.
Blah blah blah.
>> Let me
>> If you don't stop, if you don't stop,
Dane, I'm going to have to come on your
door. Let me let me guess. You've had a
text from your boyfriend LT saying,
"Mate, rinser, blah, blah, blah." I I
know exactly how this [ __ ] works. >> No,
>> Jane, if you don't stop, I might have to
come in your door,
>> mate. There's cameras and Ring
doorbells. Like, I'd have you tasered.
>> I'll come and do a welfare check.
>> You'd be tasered, >> huh?
Like I I would take like
taser knives and [ __ ] to you. >> Really?
>> I'm sorry. I'm an old woman obviously. [Music]
>> See, see how when you run with the
narrative and you try to show off and be
a smart [ __ ] but you run your mouth,
but actually that's not what you think
because you're trying to impress people. H >> really
>> really am I right?
>> You should Why don't you tell everybody
how much of a wronging you are when you
you was playing Craig Goodston? You horrible [ __ ]
>> No, no, that's fine. What? What
happened? What was then wrong to Craig?
>> You made Craig Goodston cry. You horrible camp.
>> Yeah, but what was done to Craig? You
led him on.
>> No. In what way did that happen?
>> You led him on. You played him. >> How?
>> You gave him false hope and then you blocked him. >> No. See? >> Yes.
>> Now th this is where I know. See, now
this is what this is the part of you I
don't like because instead of being true
to yourself, you run with the crowd.
>> That is That is the truth. That is the
truth. No, no. The the truth is I got to
know Craig. I decided I wasn't
interested romantically, but I would like >> Okay.
>> I would like to be a friend. Craig took
offense to that and threatened me. And
as much as you might like to
>> No, you're a horrible old cut.
>> You You could bring the GV and Mrs.
Brown on here and they would both tell
you when that happened. They both joined
a call with me and told me that Craig
had asked them to threaten me.
>> Pack of lies. Pack of lies. >> Okay.
>> Is a pack of lies.
>> Okay. Drop drop your link.
>> A pack of lies.
>> Drop your link in the chat and throw it
open to go and Mrs. Brown and come in
and tell me I'm a liar.
>> What are you talking about?
>> You You made an accusation and I told
you the truth. I just told you how to
prove it, but you don't want to hear that.
>> You was needing Crayon.
>> Yeah, I'm going to have to kick you, J.
Anyways, ghosting. I got five numbers
yesterday and only one of them replied.
Um, the past three times I went out in
the past week, I got 13 numbers and only
a few of them replied. But yeah,
[ __ ] yeah, I got one reply. [ __ ]
It's mad ghosted. They're just not
interested in this country.
Oh, my back is there.
Sorry, bro. I couldn't tell you cuz this [ __ ]
get the [ __ ]
I got five last night. Yeah,
I've got a lot of I've got boyfriends, bro.
I lost 150 on roulette today. Ghosted.
It's a cycle that you go out, drink, get rejected.
Oh, same old in this country, is it? Hey, lad.
I hope you had a good night.
Yeah, same old England, is it?
Same old England, lad.
Same old England.
Would never change, would it?
I don't gamble, bro. I don't gamble.
That was the first time in two months.
First time in two months, bro.
Oh, I don't gamble.
Yeah, I lost 150. I have like 1.2 left
in one account. 1.2,000. So, not too bad. Is Yeah.
But yeah, I don't think ghostly I don't
think the dating game will ever change here, bro.
It will ever change in this country. I don't think.
Yeah, I don't think so, bro. What do you think?
Yeah, I was chatting this thing up, bro.
You know, I said to her, I was like,
"Hi, it was nice meeting you yesterday.
I was going to say, let's meet up on
Saturday and go for a few drinks. It
would be nice to get to know each other
more." X, she replied, "Hey, it was nice
to meet you, too. As I said, I'm seeing
someone, but if that changes, I'll let
you know. How old are you by the way? I
said, "Oh, this is my age." She said,
"Oh, yeah, casual, but she said she was
casually dating someone." She said,
"Yeah, casual, but I don't have the
capacity to date multiple people cuz I
thought you might be in your 20s. I'm 32."
I said, "Nice, nice age. Nice age gap.
Ain't bad then."
Well, we went from you not wanting to
give your number to you giving it a
reply and it must be a good start. Hey, joke X
and uh no reply.
Yeah, I don't think you can meet anyone
in this country, bro.
But the thing the reason why I go out
ghosting is cuz I want to No, she she
said, "Oh, I'm seeing someone." Uh
there was a sexy woman I got yesterday,
but I got her. I don't know approach on
the train as well. I'll send it to you
if you want.
But um she said you see something. I
Okay, well give me your number. I'll
message you. If you reply, you reply. If
you don't, you don't. Then I messaged
and then she replied. So cuz she said
she was casually dating, so I thought
[ __ ] it. But either way, bro, it's the
same [ __ ] Um back to what I was saying,
the only reason I go out in this country
cuz there's nothing else to do.
It will never never change in this country ever. Um,
so that's where that goes, bro.
So, yeah, man.
Yeah. Did you die yesterday or [ __ ] what?
Did I come home? Yeah.
Yeah. On three approaches sober, bro.
And I got this one number. She was sexy,
bro. I got her number, but she didn't even reply.
It's impossible in this country, bro.
Well, nowadays, everyone's got Tik Tok brains.
Terry, go away. You're boring, bro.
You're boring, Terry. Terrible trainers.
You're another nons legs. You're boring,
mate. Go buy yourself some new trainers,
you boring bastard.
Boring. Coming on YouTube for men's
reaction again. You're boring.
You are boring.
Listen, bro. I'm skin. I'm this. I'm
that. I'm this. Stop wasting your time
talking to me. Get off of YouTube.
Get off of YouTube. It's pointless now.
It's boring now, bro. Ban anyone that's
a a Yes, man. Bro, you get banned
because the last time I went to your
area, your [ __ ] ass didn't come out.
Why am I going to sit here and argue
with a [ __ ] [ __ ]
with shitty trainers? We all saw you,
man. You don't show up anywhere
and you're [ __ ] emailing people.
Oh, I'm not the one. Oh, I'm not the
one. Oh, I'm not the one, bro. I went to
your area. You didn't show up. Everybody
saw it. You can't be took seriously,
Terry. Terrible trainers. You're a
boring now, bro. You're a bore. You're banned.
[ __ ] off, weirdo. Yeah,
these people are sad, man. [ __ ] sad individuals
met alive terrible trainers.
A [ __ ] idiot. But yeah, anyways guys
on on uh back to that, bro. Yeah,
but I think it is a uh bro.
So yeah, I think it is hot impossible in
this country nowadays, bro. But if
you're starting off, seems that way. Anyways, yeah.
still there, bud. Yeah.
Everyone's got Tik Tok brains.
I must be the only one that's not on
that Tik Tok in it.
[ __ ] Tik Tok, man.
for the [ __ ] And yeah, bro.
But yeah, it won't ever change in this country, brother.
So, I'm a bit slaggy, bro.
I'm [ __ ] bro, from the drinking on my bad, bro.
I can't be bothered listening to you,
Jay. And you're a [ __ ] idiot.
It is. It is impossible now. [ __ ] mad.
I'd say it is. Is it possible now, bro?
It would never change in England.
We even got some pressure I can show you as well.
That run, bro. Jesus.
Yeah. So, we're just all about dating as [ __ ] bro.
Everyone's got Tik Tok brains. me.
Yeah, it seems impossible dating in this
country, but can't lie to you.
Jeez, I'm so tired, mate.
I don't You should date Jane. Why not? I
can't date me. I can't get a
conversation out of anyone. And when I
do, it's got a boyfriend.
I don't really bother nowadays. Me, Joe. Jane. [ __ ] Jane.
Everyone's got boyfriends, mate. So, I
don't I just leave them to it.
I'm wasting [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. I'm wasting B [ __ ]
Yeah. But you need sex, Jade. Can I
I tell you what, I don't like Jay. That
[ __ ] Triple H. I [ __ ] can't stand
that little [ __ ]
That Triple H. Yeah,
that little [ __ ] man.
He's not my mate.
I see what he does. I'm not stupid, bro. Yeah.
No, he's not my mate. I see what he
does, mate. I'm not stupid. Yeah.
Um, so you know how Virgin Boy NES is
obsessed with me and how he does all
these posts knowing that the cow will
never ever meet me. Triple H will like
bring it over onto my channel. Even
though I said I don't want to hear it. I
don't want to hear about the coward.
He'll continuously bring it up and join
in knowing that I don't like the [ __ ]
being mentioned because the Virgin's
never going to meet me. He never never
going to say anything to my face. And
then he comes on trying to [ __ ] stir
which I think is cheeky because when I
went to Newcastle three times, he never
come out. So I'm thinking, what the
[ __ ] You you you're on my channel, [ __ ]
stone, right? And then when I was in
Newcastle, them three times you didn't
come out. What the [ __ ] bro?
And I was like, [ __ ] you people were
the same on there, man.
I just swerved him, bro. I just him
so [ __ ] My eyes are [ __ ] bro.
Swear down. Never drinking again.
No, I don't think he's a laugh me. I
don't find it funny. Me,
I don't find that [ __ ] funny.
No, I don't find that funny. me.
Yeah. I remember when I used to speak to
you on the phone, Jane, you used to find everything funny.
Like me losing the house. You think
that's funny? It's not funny.
It's not funny, is it? It's like
Yeah, it's like it's like it like
I don't know. It kind of like ruin people's lives.
Do you think that's funny? Me losing the
house. It's not funny.
Yeah, it's not funny. What? Losing a
house. Why is that funny?
It's not funny.
No, that ain't funny.
Hey, you wanted to give me a [ __ ]
didn't you, Jane?
Then I exposed a little hallways
and everyone started laughing at you. Right.
Yeah. You dirty [ __ ] Oh [ __ ]
No, they were laughing at you, mate. Not
me. They were laughing at you. You think it's funny?
Why do you think people getting evicted
from a house is funny? Yeah.
Well, mate, I'd rather be single than
[ __ ] date that bald-headed [ __ ]
freak. And you're so in denial as well.
Like, you speak about LT and LT. Have
you seen that Mark Samson? He is the
biggest embarrassment ever.
Like you've got no you've got like no
room to talk.
You got no room to talk, mate. He is the
biggest embarrassment ever.
That Mark Samson. Oh, you are so in
denial. So in denial.
You are so in denial, mate. You really, really are.
You think someone getting evicted is
funny? A what? You think it's funny? Yeah.
Yeah, it's funny. Yeah. [Music]
Yeah. I do remember when he wanted to
give me a [ __ ] Sir, nah,
you're too much of a troll, James. Sorry.
It's the same that one on WhatsApp
didn't reply, man. She was sexy, bro. Shame it.
Fame people aren't interested in this
country in it. No,
you need a ice tested.
You need your eyes tested. [Music]
Yeah, he could be. Yeah.
Let me see what I look like right now.
See what I look like.
[ __ ] I'm over to [ __ ]
That's what I don't [ __ ] [ __ ] over [ __ ] hair. Who's
had a haircut
a few days ago?
I had a haircut a few days ago.
Oh [ __ ] I'm [ __ ] man.
I'm so tired.
Yeah, I'm Muslim. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm I'm a I'm a Muslim J. I told you this. Yeah.
Oh, I'm so tired.
Oh, Jane, I'm so tired, man.
I need to go to sleep soon.
They just aren't interested in this country. Oh,
it's all about drinking. It's all about drinking yesterday. Aging.
Yeah, Jade. It's all that drinking, huh?
I am [ __ ]
I am so [ __ ]
Bye-bye, keyboard warrior. Go make another account.
Terry, terrible trainers.
You know, I should have stopped. I
should have stopped reacting to you.
As soon as you didn't meet me,
you should see this. She's [ __ ] sexy, bro.
number I got.
Yeah, he's a little [ __ ] but I got
this number completely sober as well.
It's like what Ant-Man said, Jane,
unless you've got a million subscribers
on Tik Tok, they're not interested.
Oh, a million followers.
You told me that it's all social media
nowadays, you see.
No, they used to they used to email each
other, but they don't email each other anymore cuz
LT told Terry to [ __ ] off. Terry tries
to betray that he's some sort of
gangster and [ __ ] LT clocked on to it.
I knew he was full of [ __ ] that time
when I went and he didn't come out. But
even since then, I should have stopped
entertaining a fool.
I might actually go to Wales again soon. being serious
talking about yourself.
Stop talking about yourself.
Not a pot to piss. Stop talking about yourselves.
You are the ones sat on YouTube all day
every day talking about yourselves.
We you, which is you, are the skinned
ones. That's why you're s on YouTube
every day because you're talking about yourselves.
That's why you're all on law all day
every day. You see, the thing is, Jane,
you got to look at people's YouTube activity.
These people sit on here every day
calling people skin. Yeah. They're the
ones that are sat on YouTube every day.
They wouldn't be sat on YouTube every
day if they weren't skin. I mean, yeah,
that hits a nerve cuz it's the truth.
So, I don't need to I don't need to
betray betray something I'm not. I get
about £1,100 a month and I've got about 2K.
Ah, that's real, bro. I don't need to
portray that I'm something I'm not like
L J Virgin boy. I don't need to portray
something and make up the story.
Just like when I lost the house. I lost
the house. There you go. So, I don't
need to lie like people like Lord Jay
and Virgin Boy and all these other
people on here that self project every
day. Like, that's not that's not me,
bro. I ain't about that life. Yeah,
I got this [ __ ] Um,
it's like LJ
says he gets all this money, but yet
he's on YouTube every day begging. It just doesn't
make make any sense. You're on YouTube
every day begging,
but you got all this money.
But you got all this money, but you're
sat on YouTube every day begging.
It's very easy for these people to get
caught out, you know.
Yeah. [ __ ] is what it is, man. I
don't pretend I have, you know what I mean?
And on that and, you know, Yeah.
And that's what it is with this
community. They're mongos. That's all
they are is self-p projecting low lives.
They're just they're just fat ugly
people that you're giving entertainment
to. because they're fat, ugly, and
disabled. So, they don't even leave
their house. So,
they they tried to get entertainment out
of other people's lives because they're [ __ ] mongos.
That's what they are here.
So, I don't know why they have to lie
about their life. I don't lie about my
Uh I don't lie about my life, bro.
This LJ he doesn't he ain't know about
man you think mate
you got properties in Belfast and you
get over so you get over three grand a
month but you got property in Belfast.
Uh makes sense that
yeah that makes a lot of sense.
Yet you come on YouTube and you beg every day. Uh,
see the thing is Jane, you know, all of
these people on here, they simp over you
like LJ and all of these. It's because
they ain't got a life. People that have
a life wouldn't care about you. Doesn't
matter what you look like. That's also
how you know who have who has a life on
who don't have a life. Cuz I would I I I
got 30 numbers in three days. I've got
my own women's numbers. I was speaking
to my own own women regardless.
So they they're going about you because they uh
cuz they ain't got a life. You see, they
don't meet anyone. That's it.
There's a sad little mongos. Ain't got a life.
I'll be in Thailand in the next two months, Jade.
So yeah, I'm in Thailand loving life.
I'm I'm going to I'm going to move there
for 2 months.
2 months. What a better life. 2 months. [ __ ] good.
Oh, I'll try the Philippines next time.
Imagine that going somewhere where
you're actually wanted by women and
actually women are interested.
They're not interested in this country.
You go Philippines. Yeah.
You get people wanting to [ __ ] date
you. They don't even ask you for money. Yeah.
Yeah. Oh, this one is sexy, bro. She's
my age as well.
Shame they don't even give you a chance
to [ __ ] up. It's a madness.
No one if I'm lucky.
This one's good looking as well. I can't
believe I actually got a number so I'm
[ __ ] You know, it's mad how they
don't give you a chance. Not Not that I
care because I accepted England now.
It will never change. Yeah. But it is
what it is.
Been happening for years. Get used to it.
So it's what I had to do. Yeah.
Yeah. I got 13. But uh
they're all different ones.
But the point is I can go out and speak
to women. I don't need to simp women
over women on YouTube is is my whole
point. Whether they meet me, they don't
whether you got a number, whether they
reply, whether they don't reply. The
point is I don't need to s over women on YouTube.
And I actually do have one that's meeting me.
Well, they're saying they're going to
meet me next week. We'll see if they
actually do, but that's not really the
point. Whether they do or they don't, I
don't need to simp over no women on no
[ __ ] YouTube or no [ __ ] any social [ __ ] media. So
whether they meet me or [ __ ] not to
be honest. So it's [ __ ] beat [ __ ] So Yeah.
Yeah, there we go, bro. Sorry, I got DC.
but anyways, the point is you see LJ
sing over you, that's how you know he
ain't got a life. Just like most of
these people there ain't got a life
but calling people what they are themselves. So
yeah, you're in denial about that Mark.
I went to his area twice live
and he didn't show up and you still deny it.
You're in denial, mate. You're in denial
about that, Mark.
And they shouldn't even be giving you
their number to [ __ ] get rid of you.
They should be giving you a chance. Oh,
[ __ ] my nose, bro. Someone should be
giving you a chance. That's how [ __ ]
up it is. But again, we can go on about
how [ __ ] up it is. We know how [ __ ]
up it is, but it's never going to
change. So, you get used to it or leave.
There is one thing you can change. What
you do, leave the country. Simple.
That's what I said to myself yesterday
and I felt fine again.
We we know that it's [ __ ] up. We know
that it's there's nothing normal about
it. But no, no one's stopping you leaving.
And then that's what I said to myself.
And it it makes logical sense, you know.
So I'm good, man.
I'm happy in my own.
So you're in and about that Arsenal Mark. Anyways,
he's a big [ __ ] He is. Yeah,
he's a s as well, just like Lord J.
Yeah, he's a s. Just like Lord J. [Music]
But it is it is it is weird. It is
It is weird.
But like I said, it's never going to
change. So get used to it or leave. Simple.
Yeah. Yeah. Whatever, bro. End of
conversation. It's not my problem
anymore. I know what I'm doing. I know
what I'm doing. It's not my problem anymore.
It's not my problem anymore, bro.
enough for all go places by yourself.
And I'm not having this conversation
again. Anyways, we've been through this
a million times. I'm leaving. End of.
I found a solution. End of. Done, man.
It doesn't matter.
You hear excuse after excuse after
excuse after excuse. I'm not getting
into it, bro. I'm not talking about it. End off.
End the story.
Not not not not doing this again, bro.
Not talking about this again. So yeah,
I'm not talking about this self
projecting [ __ ] again where you're going
to try and say I don't have friends when
you're the one sat on YouTube all day.
It's boring, bro. It's boring. Like [ __ ]
what was you saying 10 months ago?
Oh, you can't find a girl cuz you live
with your mom. You don't work. Guess
what? [ __ ] like lived by himself
and I was working and I still had the
same problems. So, whatever excuse you
make, it's laughable, bro. No one cares
what any of you think. Imagine that. I
was working and I was living by myself.
So, it's just another excuse.
No one cares about your silly excuses, bro.
No one cares about your silly little excuses.
You know, you used to love You used to
love using them excuses.
Work and living with your mom was the
biggest excuses you used to love. You
used to love using mommy not working the
[ __ ] said it all the [ __ ] time,
bro. I live by myself. I [ __ ] worked.
You had nothing to say about me. You
know what I'm saying? So
anyways, end of conversation.
Now you're going to talk about the job I
was doing and how it's not proper work
and well it's working. I could have been
making 50p an hour. I'd still be
working. I was I I lived by myself at
the same time as I was working and it
was for a very long time. So all of
these things like you live with your mom
or you don't work, it's all excuses.
Just like you go out approaching by
yourself, it's all excuses, bro. No
one's interested in them.
Who was paying my I had to go ages
without money, bro? Who was living? Who
was paying for my [ __ ] bro?
Me. The money that I was working for,
who was living by themselves? Me.
That's not independent. That's independent. You know,
there used to be weeks I didn't get rent
because it would all come at the same
time. How was I getting money? The money
that I was working for. So, like so yeah.
No. So, and I was going to gym as well.
[ __ ] I was actually going to the gym as
well. So I was actually building a
decent body as well. Slacking now
though. But yeah, I was also going to
the gym. I was going gym. I was working
and I live by myself. Well, I didn't
live for my mom. So
yeah, and we didn't do it for women as
well and nothing changed. We've heard
these excuses a million times.
I'm sure when you finally get to the
[ __ ] Philippines, it will be exactly
the same as it is here. No, it won't.
That's what I think it is. I think you
need to have like [ __ ] millions of
[ __ ] followers, bro,
to get anyone interested in this
country. As as stupid as it sounds,
bro, you need to worry about yourself.
You need to do that. You need to work on
yourself and get off benefits. You need
to give that advice to yourself and stop
being sat on YouTube every day cuz it's
not the first time and it won't be the last time.
The same advice goes to you. Get off of
benefits and get a real job because if
any of you people worked, you would be
sat on YouTube every day. You would not
have the time to do it.
So yeah, take your own advice.
No, I'm not getting Tik Tok. And it's
got worse because
you hear more about Tik Tok now. Even
though Tik Tok was made years ago,
even when I met that [ __ ] America,
[ __ ] American [ __ ] what's four or
five years ago, but you never really
heard about people. No, you didn't hear
about it as you hear about it now.
Before it was just Instagram and
uh dating apps and [ __ ] and it was hard,
but not like this. Now it is actually impossible
unless you've got like a million
followers on Tik Tok because before it
wasn't like this. People wasn't using
top Tik Tok like they were now 2 years
ago cuz I noticed that it's it has gotten worse.
Honestly, it's like now Yeah.
Sorry, bro. It's like now you there's no
point you even going out and drinking
and approaching unless you just want to
go out anyways, which is what I do. Um,
yeah, another fantasyist.
Yeah, bro. Well, then you don't need to
worry about them, do you? You work, you
get all this money apparently. So, you
don't need to worry about how people
live off benefits cuz you're rich, you
get all this money. So, you don't need
to worry about that, do you?
And do you think that's something to be
proud of that you're saying that your
sniff bill is too much? That's
embarrassing. I think anyone that You
know what? Honest truth. Yeah. I've got
friends that do it. Anyone that does cocaine
like continuously does it at this age,
they're [ __ ] losers.
That's like one of the lostest thing you
could do, bro.
I got friends that do it. It's It's what losers do.
I tried it twice years ago just to see
what it was like. You think that's
anything to be proud of, bro?
That is a I mean I meet sniffs all the
[ __ ] time and [ __ ] trying to
tell me that I need to work on myself.
That's not something to brag about, bro. Yeah,
that's [ __ ] madness.
But yeah, it has gotten worse here cuz
it's all t it's all Tik Tok now whereas
before people didn't really use it. So
the dating game is kind of dead because of that.
But you you get used to it. Yeah,
it is strange though. It is. But you get
used to it. Sorry, I have to some
sometimes get stop myself going in a
[ __ ] uh loop
cuz we can't say anything that's not
already been said. Do you know what I'm saying? So,
I'm so tired.
What's going on, Mr. B? Man,
I'll be waking up late tomorrow. Me thinks
I went on TikTok with my friend to try
it out, but I don't like it, bro.
Yep. Okay, bro. Whatever you say. If
that helps you sleep at night. Yep.
Whatever you say.
Yep. Whatever you say.
Uh-huh. Just like we're all skin
and you are the ones sat on YouTube
every day. Uh-huh. Yep.
Yeah. Yeah. I've got no friends.
You've got all of these friends. I'm
skinn. You're not.
But you're the one sat on YouTube every
day, not me. Huh? Isn't that a madness?
You know, it's funny when you say that
because there's not anything they can
say to that because there's evidence
that they sit on YouTube all day every day.
So, I mean, there's nothing that they
they can actually say because
think of it, right? We're skint, we've
got no friends, we're [ __ ] ugly,
we're [ __ ] this, we're [ __ ] that.
But they're the ones that sat on YouTube
every day and can't get off it. So,
it is it is funny in a way. You know,
I'm not on YouTube every day and I've
come off of YouTube for weeks and weeks
and weeks. I was out all day yesterday.
Did I was out all day
yesterday? No, day before yesterday. I
was out all day on Thursday. I have come
off YouTube for weeks. So,
yeah. Yeah. And like I said, you you
call people skint, but you're the ones
that sat on YouTube every day. So I
think the old saying goes, make it make
sense because we all know that if you
people was not skin, you wouldn't be on
here. End of that just cuts the whole
conversation. That just cuts the whole
conversation cuz think of it, Friday, Saturday,
why is LJ on YouTube live all day and
why is people on his channel all day if
they've got all this money? Why are they
not out with their friends? Why are they
not out with their misses? Because it
will explain that they're talking about themselves.
They don't have any of these things.
They sit on YouTube every single day.
You s you sit on YouTube every day, all
day, every day, even on a Friday,
Saturday, no life. Sat on YouTube.
Will you be living your life, living the
dream? I can tell you what I done in
three in in in in three weeks. Oh, so
you don't even have a grant to your
name. I've got more money than you,
mate. That's the funny thing about it is
you're talking about a K a month, but
guess what? I've got more money than
you, no matter how you look at it, and
I'll continue to always have more money
than you. So, you don't even have
£1,000. So, try again. There's no point
you even talking about a grand a month.
You ain't even got a [ __ ] grand.
Yeah, of course he's definitely on benefits.
And of course he's on benefits. Does it
make sense? Of course he is on benefits.
Of I could have told you that.
Listen, I'll tell you how you know that
he's on benefits. Just like I know how
you people talk about yourself when you
call people skin cuz you're on YouTube
all day every day. because he claims
that he gets over three grand a month
because he owns property. Now, Belfast
property doesn't pay that much. What is
your actual job? Did he ever say what
his actual job is?
Did he ever say how what his job
actually is? No. So, apparently he gets
all of this money. Yeah. He sat on
YouTube every day begging begging in the
Weather Spoons and begging on YouTube.
It don't make sense. It's more like he's
on £300 a month doing anything he can to
make more money. But just own it.
You should just own what what what
you're on and what you have, bro. I do it, you know?
So, yeah. And I find it strange how you
also, most of you on here don't work cuz
you won't be on YouTube every day.
That's another thing. If you all worked,
you wouldn't be on YouTube every day.
You wouldn't have the time to do it.
That's how you know you don't work
because you're on YouTube every day, all
day, every day.
So, how what? You all work. You've got
all of this money. You've got this great
life, but you'd waste it all on YouTube.
It doesn't add up.
But yeah, with that, L J, that's how
you know that it it doesn't add up to anything. Okay, you skin.
Who the [ __ ] would beg for drink?
Listen, listen, bro. Listen. Who would beg
for drinks and Weber spoons if they had
loads of money? Who would beg on YouTube
if they had loads of money? Answer me
this question. Who would do it?
Who would do it for an extra100 pound a
month? It don't make sense.
I know him better than he knows himself,
man. You know what I'm saying? It don't make sense.
If you was making loads and loads and
loads and loads and loads and loads of
money, then it does make sense.
If you was making loads and loads and
loads and loads and loads and loads, cuz
why not? You're making tons of extra
money, but you're on all of this money
and you're what? Swallowing up pride for
what, an extra £100 a month? It doesn't make sense
cuz all of these followers are skin. No,
it just doesn't make any sense. I don't
beg it for money from anyone on here.
It just doesn't make sense at all. It
don't make no sense. And he always
betrays like, "Oh, I've got money." Cuz
a lot of people on here will just tell
you straight, "I've got no money. I'm
scared." A lot of them will own it. Like
they'll be like, "Oh, I ain't got no
money right now. I d my balls in." or um
yeah, you get a few people that tell
you, "Oh, I'm on this amount. Oh, I've
got no money. I've only got this certain
amount of money." But he will betray
like he's actually got money.
Just like virgin nonslegs when they
don't. So, I don't know why they betray
a life that they don't have. It's ridiculous.
Just own it, bro.
Just [ __ ] own it.
You know what I mean?
No point trying to pretend. Own it, bro.
Just own it. I own what you get. Own
what you have, man.
And I'm not jealous of anyone, bro. I I
want people to succeed.
UK claim benefits yourself. So, you need
to ask yourself that question.
No, you bro, you're not embarrassed.
and you claim benefits yourself
just like all the LJ followers all benefit claimants.
Um, so I don't know, ask yourself that.
You're the one that's claiming benefits.
So you should ask yourself that.
Again, listen, bro. I know, you know, we
all have mental health and we're not
perfect. I'm not perfect.
But here's the thing, man. You people
seem to have a tendency of getting
yourselves confused with other people.
I don't know like what the disability is
you suffer with, but you seem to be
getting yourselves confused with other
people like myself.
You you you are on benefits yourself.
So I mean ask yourself that question.
Don't ask me. So yeah.
Anyways, moving on.
How much do you get with a How much do
you get a month then? Let me ask this
question for the LS.
Let me let me ask you this. How much do
you get a month?
It's a shame you don't even know how life works
since you're probably older than me.
Let's hear this for the lows. How much
do you get a month?
This is going to be funny, but yeah,
this is going to be really funny.
But do you know what makes me laugh with
you people on here? Yeah.
Is that you come on here every day jobless
telling other people to get a job. Then
if somebody was to get a job, you would
try to make them lose their job. So I
mean what what is that all about? Same
[ __ ] that's been happening for years. So
which one is it?
Uh, so which one is it?
It's funny, bro. Oh, [ __ ] Yeah. Strange. Very strange.
It is very strange. I must say
I think you people will benefit yourself.
You must get sick of working, eh?
Working [ __ ] If you actually do work,
that is, which you probably don't.
You must hate working, eh? If you
actually do work,
yeah, but think of all that time you
miss out on. There's so many things to
do in life. enough.
Yeah, RJ is definitely on benefits. Definitely. Definitely. Bro, [ __ ] defo.
And he doesn't understand that I can
live without YouTube.
Him and his followers can't. That's why
they're sat on YouTube every day and
they can't take one day off it. Like, we
need to see the evidence. I've been off
of YouTube for weeks before. Weeks. He
can't take a day off of YouTube.
He was even on YouTube when he was in
Vegas. Now, bro, he's talking about himself.
If YouTube shut down tomorrow, him and
his little lowife little scummy scumbag
[ __ ] followers would be [ __ ]
They would be [ __ ] This is actually
their life, bro.
For real. It's actually their life. They
would be [ __ ] without YouTube.
Man, I can easy come off YouTube, bro. Easily.
I'll prove it to you. You're
You don't need to worry about my life.
Worry about your own life. If your life
was that perfect and you work, you
wouldn't care about anyone else's life.
So, it just goes to show that you're the
one who's on benefits
cuz you're saying that you're working
and you got this and you got that. You
wouldn't care about anyone below you on benefits.
So, it seems that you're just talking
about yourself. Really,
you're talking about you. You people
come here. If if I'm wrong, right,
get off of YouTube. Don't come back on
here. I'll do it. I I've I've bro I've
done these experiments before, bro. I'll
come off of YouTube one week. When I
come back, I don't want to see any of
you people on here. Why is it when I
come back and I come back on here,
you've still been on here every day?
It goes to show that you ain't got a
life. What's the day today? Right. I can
say, right, I'm not going to go on
YouTube now until next Saturday. No
posting, no live streams, no YouTube.
And I'm going to come back on Saturday
and I'm going to rescroll every single
day and you people will be on YouTube.
So at the end of the day it's you're
showing yourselves up.
Yeah, but it's not entertainment. It's weird.
No, no, no, no. It's not entertainment. It's weird.
It's [ __ ] weird.