Oh, I'm going to play some Black Ops.
Remote on, controller on.
I can bloody
th that bloody body bag. You know, going
be back on here with these little mongos. Seriously,
I told him the whole point of it yesterday. You know,
the whole point is, right, these people
come, they come come on here a name call
every single day. But how you prove who
the real who it really is is the ones
that can't get off of YouTube. And if these people
can't get off of YouTube, then it's
obviously them. They're talking about themselves skin.
They must be talking about themselves
because they can't get off of YouTube.
So I don't even need to name call. I
just come off and then come back on.
I can't be bothered with it anymore.
Yeah, it's Friday night. I can stay
Friday night. I booked Skyline yesterday
as well. 7 7 7
the flight's cost me. So I have no time
or any more money to be wasted in this
country. I think I made the right
decision as well to be honest with you. So,
>> cuz you need to realize a bit like some
of these people that your life is
is a cycle, right? And especially when I
was watching that guy in America doing
these approaches and it's like, "Oh
[ __ ] he's getting the same [ __ ] in
America." And it was it was it seems
even worse over there than it is here. I
was like, "Fuck this. I'm leaving, bro.
[ __ ] this. I ain't doing this no more."
So, that's how I broke the cycle. You
know, it's quite simple. So yeah,
you don't spend £700 in a weekend, but
yeah, it's like, you know, you're not
going to get any of that [ __ ] in
Thailand or Philippines or anywhere. So,
I just thought it was the most logical
thing to do. Keep wasting my time here.
I got 13 numbers last week. I didn't
even get one date.
But yeah, I get your point. Anyways,
four or 500, whatever. Yeah,
because it's like
but I just went by the logic that
you know people say things changes but
if something was going to change it
would have changed by now. It happens.
It's still happening and it's getting
worse. So, we can't [ __ ] spend um you know,
I never spend £700. When I used to do
Manchester, I used to spend about 400.
Don't know where you get 700 from, bro.
When I used to do my [ __ ] Manchester
weekends, it was nowhere near 700,
but each their own. Either way, the
country's dead. So, I just thought I
made a logical decision as well. So,
and if it's not changed now, it's never
going to change.
And I think that's logical. So, yeah.
Yeah. You can ask what you want, you know. Nope.
Because I don't need to show videos when
I go away, bro. Just like I do loads of
approaching videos. What I did, I don't
put it on this channel. I don't I don't
show I don't see the point. I just come
on here to see if it's the same people.
And it always is. So same people that
ain't got a life. Well, I only went on
here yesterday cuz Monty told me to. He
was suicidal. So yeah.
No, I don't need to show these people anything.
Why would I want to show them anything?
These little dirty grasses.
The [ __ ] glasses on here as well.
Oh, and another thing I don't bother
with this anymore is because they don't
leave people alone as well. Like they
you'll notice with these little mongos,
they never ever stop their [ __ ] So,
it's just best to just leave them to it.
The little low lives. I don't need to
shut Bob up. I already shut Bob up when
I went on the plane and he's still quite
blank and eyes. I don't need to shut him
up. He's he's a he's a he's a bedbound
little loser. I don't need to prove
myself to anyone, bro. I already done
that [ __ ] years ago and you still talk [ __ ]
Even if someone proved you wrong, you
would still say it never happened.
Shut bum up. Bum's a bedit [ __ ]
bedbound ridden [ __ ] [ __ ] that got
run off of YouTube. Who cares what the
[ __ ] he thinks? You know what I'm
saying? He's never even been on a plane
in his life. Anyways, we're not getting
into this. Ah, so yeah. Yeah, man.
You somehow seem to think that people
need to prove stuff to you on this community,
which is strange.
I wouldn't I don't know why he was
getting like that over Natalie G. I said
that to him yesterday. I would never get
like that over women because I know what
they do. I would be more surprised if
they did do that. This is what I was
saying to him yesterday. I got [ __ ]
around with this week. I was someone was
supposed to meet me and I was meeting
someone several times. I said, "Douches,
Addios. I don't give a [ __ ] me because I
know what they're like. You see, they're
all the same. So there's not one
different than the other. I wouldn't get
like that, bro. It's already happened
before. It will never happen again. Not
like that, but yeah, cuz you cuz you get
to a point when as you get older, you
know what they're like. So everything
that they do is just similar to each
other cuz they're all the same.
So how how how could you get that? Cuz
they're all the same. They do all the
same [ __ ] 27 and yet to be proven
wrong. still waiting for somebody to
prove me wrong.
Which is part of the reason I don't even
go out anymore because it's just [ __ ] pointless
hearing the same excuses, the same Tik
Tok brains. It's pointless. Everyone's
got Tik Tok brains. Everyone stuck up.
It's just no point.
So, I know what they're like. I know
what they do, bro. Once you've met one,
you've met them all.
Once you've met one, you've met them all.
I was watching this guy in America on
Instagram. He keeps doing these
approaches and it's like they're like
they are honestly bro like I know we've
made jokes about this. They are actually
non-playing characters. It's like it's
the only word they know is I have a
boyfriend. They must have got that [ __ ]
from Tik Tok. I'm watching the dude
right and they act exactly the same.
Every single woman he approaches it's
either you're too old for me, you're too
young for me. I have a boyfriend. It's
just the same. They are exactly the same
now because of Tik Tok.
It's why I don't go out. I I just chill
based on Call of Duty.
Black Ops 2 is the best game now.
Should have. Yeah.
So he said, "Yeah, I bought Black Ops 2
yesterday. It was £11.99 down from £35.
It was £35 in the store for some reason.
Black Ops 2 is the is the best."
Yeah, you my man tried sexing himself. No.
Bless Nelly G if she broke your hearty
clause. No [ __ ] can do that to me, bro.
You [ __ ] mad. No way could a [ __ ] do
that to me.
Oh, Greavves. I thought I let you know I
told the tenants about themsel yesterday.
Yeah, it wasn't very nice cuz obviously
I had to buy a new office to show you. I
told them all about themselves and no
one said anything back, but I really dug
in deep. They were pissing me off, bro.
So, I was like, "Oh, okay. Let's go down
this route then."
Yeah. I said, "You can still after shave
behind people's back, but you can never
do it to my face. You dirty little
cunt." That's why I said to him, "You
dirty little thief." I don't even think
it's it's bad. It's not even the worst
thing necessarily being a thief because
it's it's when they don't own up to it.
There's nothing worse than there being
like three, four people, something goes
missing. It could be any situation and
no one owns up to it. It just makes me
want to [ __ ] every single one of them up. Yeah.
Like it make I hate that me, bro. I hate that me.
Has to buy a new after shave. [ __ ]
hell. You know, it's not the point
anyways, bro. It's just annoying. I hate
that, you know. Dirty thieves
from people. Anyways,
what do you think we
uh maybe he was in love? Maybe that was
his true first love. Bless him. Yeah.
And I was like, well, someone took it
and someone also told like something one
of my business to someone and I said, is
anyone going to admit it or not?
Cuz I said, when I see you again, I'm
going to [ __ ] one of you. That's what I
said to agree with. I said, but when I
see you again, I'm going to [ __ ] one of you hard.
I said that to them as well. So, I'm
going to [ __ ] you really hard. Yeah.
So yeah, and it's like they told my
business, which I didn't really care
about, but I did care about it because
like, who are they to be start [ __ ]
telling people's [ __ ] business?
And then this girl was trying to say
she's going to get her ex. I said, "Get
your ex. I'll give you my address right
now." Like they would start [ __ ] I was
like, "Bro, I I'll come and meet you right now."
And then they stopped. So it's like,
"What's the point, bro?" So I just
blocked them all. You know, in many ways, I'm
I'm very I'm glad they took the house.
In many ways, I'm glad they took the house.
Yeah. Okay. You might have lost some
money. I've still got money. I have
enough money. I can do what I want, you
know. I just had bacon and egg.
Bacon and egg. Bacon sandwiches and egg.
Just made myself something.
Oh, I tell you what I had the other day.
Pepe's chicken. It was very nice.
I went to go to the bagel shop that I
took king, but it was too packed.
And then it's like I said to her, she
was trying to be funny and I told her
about herself. I was like, "Listen, bro." Yeah.
Yeah. I basically said to her, "Well,
guess what? Somebody does want to suck
my dick. Remember that girl that was in
the house? The one that was 100 times
better looking than you. She sucked my
dick and she was 100 times better
looking than you. I stuck on all of them
though. Every single one of them. There
was only two of them that I don't have a
problem with. I said I ain't got a
problem with with with you two.
But um with the rest pretty much the
rest of them I kind of do. Oh no. You
took my bloody after save. I had to buy
a brand new after shave. [ __ ] 72
[ __ ] quid. What the [ __ ]
[ __ ] wankers, bro.
I told her about herself, bro. So, do
your ex, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] Yeah.
And I was like, listen, you wasn't even
staying there for like 4 months. You
wasn't ever coming back.
like you was never coming back to that
room ever that you was paying for. So
stop trying to make out like you you're
still not even in the country. She was
[ __ ] pissing me off, bro. Yeah,
she was proper pissing me off, bro.
I And and I said in the voice yesterday
to them, I wish I [ __ ] them all over.
You know what? I wish I I'd done Grezy.
Just never told them. Yeah. And then
they just come in the door and then
chuck him out. I wish I'd done that, you
know? I I actually fully wish I'd done that.
Yeah. I actually fully wish I'd done that. Yeah.
Yeah. That' be [ __ ] jokes, isn't it?
Like they're sleeping. Yeah. On the door now.
Yeah. A bless you.
[ __ ] football better come in tomorrow, bro.
Do a [ __ ] near 300 quid extra. Wish I
won't be like to skip Virgin if it
doesn't, but still.
Yeah, I was tired as well. I fell
asleep, bro. I was [ __ ] knacking.
It will never change. Never. One sec. Uh
oh gosh darn it.
What the [ __ ]
So, I've got a question. Stephen,
is this right? I let these people call
me what they want on YouTube.
And I don't say that you're it back.
Your skin, you're this. You're that. I
don't say anything to them. I go by the
evidence that they're on YouTube every
day. They can't get off it. I love it
when they all come on YouTube
and they can't get off YouTube. That
must means they're the skinned ones. You
know what I'm saying? That's that's the
logic I go by. You know, that must be
they're the skin ones cuz they can't get
off YouTube. Not even for one single day.
Oh, wasn't that so nice watching that
lose yesterday? Oh, I actually did see
that. I watched it back and he was going
mad at losing what was it £100
and he said, "Oh, I don't mind losing on
the horses." Yeah, I was saying exactly
the same thing. I don't like losing on
them machines. It's [ __ ] annoying. It
doesn't matter how much money it is.
Yeah, cuz it's annoying.
Which is why you don't play them.
[ __ ] is. It is. It is [ __ ]
annoying, bro. Losing on them machines.
It is annoying. But it's funny what
happens to him.
Proper [ __ ] You got proper triggered.
Did you watch it yesterday?
So yeah, no one's going to admit who
stole you after shave. No one's going to
admit who told my business.
But then what makes me laugh is these
Muslim people going on about black
people. They'll go on about black people
and then they'll go on about white
people. But the fact of the matter is,
I'm sure in their religion they're not
allowed to do that.
[ __ ] shy [ __ ] Yeah, man.
Cuz you know, in school it was always
known as, "Oh, the black person tells
the lies." Well, this is what they try
to make you believe. The black person
tells the lies, but the Muslim person never does.
But obviously that's not true because
where's that after shave gone? Greasy,
where's the after shave gone? Summons took it. So So
obviously took it, bro. So nah nah.
You still doing good on,200 pound a month, Grezy?
I don't think I saved anything this
month. It's too [ __ ] hard.
It's too [ __ ] hard. I've just been
staying in chilling, bro.
My [ __ ] bones are hurting me, bro. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. I booked the flight yesterday. degrees 770
Bangkok. I was like, we need a change,
bro. This is We're not going to be doing this forever.
forever, bro. This is ridiculous.
I was watching this guy in America doing
these approaches, greasy, and he was
getting the same old. I must have
watched about 500 of his approaches.
He was a black guy, right? And he was it
was the same old. Hey, bon.
[ __ ] off. [ __ ] annoying it is. But
once you met one, you vet them all.
Once you've met one, you met them all.
That's first person was supposed to be
meeting me first. [ __ ] me around. So
that's 30 numbers, four replies, and two time wasters.
It will never change here in good old England.
So, I think you get to that point where
you realize and it's like, "Oh [ __ ] we
need to do something now."
Yeah, I think I made a good decision, bro. Yeah. Boyfriend Remember
Greezy, it's not funny. It's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
I don't know how you laugh at it. It's
[ __ ] annoying. I hate it, man. I
don't find that funny. I hate it, bro.
It's even worse when it happens to other
people. I don't like watching it.
So yeah, if you're thinking of going to America, right,
um, don't even bother because from my
from what it's looking like to me, it's
even worse. And this guy was going to
Florida, Miami, [ __ ] New York. Like,
he went to a few different states. I'd
say he was probably more confident than
me as well. And it was just the same. It
was like I was watching a golf
Yeah, I got I think I got about three
off. No, I got four or five replies.
This Ukrainian woman was supposed to
meet me, then she just ghosted. Someone
else was supposed to meet me, they just
[ __ ] me around. And then the other two
they were seeing someone. It's just the
same [ __ ] It's just you just expect the
same [ __ ] when you go out.
Maybe if I win this football bet
tomorrow, I might go out for a few
drinks, but I probably won't to be honest.
Like, so can't be asked anymore.
And they don't give their number because
they're uncomfortable either because
they reply. They actually they actively
sometimes set up dates with you. So it's
not because they're uncomfortable. So
they can't even use that anymore
cuz they they reply, don't they? So
I don't know why they do it.
I've already done the football bet.
Warsaw versus Swindon and Colchester
versus Tre. I mean, I don't even like
gambling. I hate gambling, but you know,
it's there's no other ways to make some
sort of money now. So I just went down
that avenue which is as soon as I can
stop working again when I come back I
will just quit again. So
[ __ ] hate damning bro. I hate damn
going to lie but yeah 80 return is 285. So
I just stuck 80 quid on it.
It's basically £300, isn't it? So
that'll pay for like two nights out. How
much 285? Two nights out. So
there's no ways to make extra money.
The only way you're able to save her is
if you just stayed in,
which ain't bad because think about it,
people go prison, right? And time flies.
So, you could still go places, but you'd
have to save and not go out and [ __ ] really.
Um, it's quite boring, isn't it? But
there's no other ways to make money.
So, this that's what we're left with, basically.
But it's not a good thing
cuz of the mood swings and just hate
gambling, bro. So
yeah, 30 numbers.
I remember asked Grezy before, how long
would it take you to save up to go
America? You said four months. I think
it's about four months. Yeah.
Yeah, I'd say roughly about four months.
It's hard though because say you say you
book flights in hotels, right? Yeah. And
it's like 2,000. Then you need to
somehow find another £2,000 spending
money. Where you finding that kind of
money, you know? So that's the thing you
got with that. But I'd say, yeah, 3 4 months probably.
Yeah, these four months. [ __ ] hell, bro.
I'll never g one roulette ever again.
I was just thinking of the good times,
Stephen Howard, when I used to go to the
casino and used to get all them£50 notes.
Sometimes I just sit back and think of
the good old days.
Yeah, that's never happened again, matey.
Good times there.
The times partic hunt now.
Even McDonald's gy bloody hell.
I don't have money to be wasted on
takeaways nowadays. I think I get one
like every four days. Nah,
I mean I can buy takeaways every day and
still have money, but it's like I won't
be able to save anything. the spin. But
me, Greasy King, me, Greasy King, and
Ronald McDonald all sat at a table.
Yeah, I don't get it once a day, bro. I
don't want to waste my money on it.
Like I said, we're back to reality now.
We're not We're not living in La La
Land. We're back to reality.
So, I don't want to be wasting money,
bro. But I could still have money, you
know? It's just I'd rather trying to
save a little bit.
I hope that football bet comes in, mate. [ __ ] hell.
You can't even play a fair game of
roulette nowadays. Bomb boy bicycle.
I wish I could get back in them casinos, bro. Yep.
I was watching Seven Neighbors. Yeah. He
was playing Lucky Lady Charm roulette,
which is the roulette that I was
playing, which was the roulette I won
the four grand on.
Yeah, that's the roulette I played. Yeah. Just
do a food shop there. No. Bless you.
I felt sorry for Monty man, you know.
Bless him then.
Bless him then if he's flying over
women. Bless his little son.
I knew after the USA is he they were all
evil. Easy. Yeah. I knew after the USA
is he bro. Look at that [ __ ] um
20year-old I was meeting
you know [ __ ] looking at 19 that 19
20 year olds. I didn't give a [ __ ] when
she went. I told her d I said told her
[ __ ] off. Bye bye bye now.
But she was good-looking as well. I
don't give a [ __ ] I got no time for no
[ __ ] woman, bro. [ __ ] that.
So, it must have been his first time in
love, I'm guessing, bro. Cuz if you had
experience, you would know what to
expect from them and you wouldn't expect
any less from them.
It's like me with the 30 numbers greasen
all over it.
Same old England. You wouldn't expect
any less, would you?
Yeah, I still don't have a care in the
world really, but I mean
I just can't just spend loads and loads
and loads and loads and loads.
I can't even get into them casinos now
to be honest with you.
Yeah, I booked it yesterday, bro. 770
and I probably need about two grand
spending money. I'm only going for two weeks.
Yeah, I'm not [ __ ] staying here
forever, bro. It just ain't this ain't a lie.
I said to I said to Adman, "You found it
funny, is it?" He said, "I didn't find
it funny. I found it depressing, which
is why I left." Yeah.
cuz I know it doesn't matter what anyone
tells me. I've been trying more than
anyone for years. It's the same old.
It's been the same old and it's
continuously being the same old and it's
getting worse cuz of Tik Tok. So people
are telling me things will change.
They're living in La La Land.
Cuz my whole logic is greasy. Yeah.
I then I then turn around and say to
him, "Okay, think it's going to change.
So why hasn't it changed already? It's
been three and a half years.
So why hasn't it changed? If if this has
been happening for three and a half
years, three years, I know long it's
been happening, but why did nothing
changed when you was constantly trying
in 3 and 1/2 years? It's not 6 months,
it's not 8 months, it's not a year, it's years.
So that tells you all you need to know,
bro. You need to leave.
There's nothing else to be said about
it, bro. Yeah.
I can't. You know what made me laugh
about Ant-Man? He's f my favorite saying yet is
he's not been all over the world. He
hasn't even been to Asia and he's not
even been to Australia. He's been nowhere.
Just like you little mongos that come
from his channel. You've been nowhere.
[ __ ] 42 and never even been to Asia. [ __ ] pathetic.
That is pathetic, mate. Pathetic.
You know, you know some of these people,
right, that that used to come on here
like bombing that bomb even L that and
then they say that the places that
they've been to is basically nowhere.
Like if you if you watch like travel
traveling vlogs. Yeah. People go to
[ __ ] Asia. They go [ __ ] every
continent. Not every country, but they
go to every continent. That's what made
me used to laugh about bomb
is even though he's been anyways, but he
used to list places that bro you could
have done in like 6 months,
a year, 6 months maybe. [ __ ] if you
watch actual traveling YouTubers, you
you will see they've
been literally everywhere. Every
continent. Not every country. You don't
have to go to every country. That's
that's a bit excessive, but every continent.
I've been to more places than both of
them. Believe that. Oh [ __ ] that bad. One second. All right, bro.
Yeah. So, uh I wouldn't say anything to
him cuz I wouldn't let him on. But, um
yeah, the games don't stop. Yeah. I was
supposed to meet someone on Thursday,
which was yesterday, and then they just ghosted.
Yeah, I don't Yeah, I really expect
anything now from them. They just This
will never change.
They don't even change when they're 40.
There's some 40year-old that messages me
on Instagram trying to get my attention.
So, they they they don't the games never
ever stop ever. So, yeah.
You think I couldn't go out today and
send it, bro? We could do, but I'll be
honest. Can't be bothered.
Can't be [ __ ]
Can't be ass, mate. Boring, is it?
Yeah. And it's never going to change either.
So that's why I booked the the the Thailand thing
cuz it's just never ever going to change. Yeah.
It's all about breaking the cycle, D
lad. That can be said about anything.
Pisses me off, bro.
This guy in America approaching and him
keep getting I've got a boyfriend. Oh,
it was annoying as [ __ ] bro.
It was so annoying, bro. I must have
been watching for like an hour. It's so annoying.
Just goes to show how impossible dating
is. It's [ __ ] another guy in another
[ __ ] country doing it, you know. Yep. November. Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. Me.
Cuz it doesn't change this life
in this country. Greasy.
I'm going for a better life. How cute is that? Yeah.
He said that's the only place you're not
going to get it. And man says the only
place you're not going to get I've got a
boyfriend is Asia.
Sounds exciting then is it.
That's the only place you're not going
to get it.
Oh, these batteries are dodgy on this
controller, bro, man.
[ __ ] these [ __ ] batteries, man.
Yeah, you always get weapon. It's Thailand.
These batteries are proper [ __ ] dodgy greasy, man.
We're supposed to batteries. Yeah,
I have a boyfriend.
I can't believe I not even got a date,
bro, this week. That is disgusting.
Just a date. Like, even a date. Not even
a date this week. [ __ ] How many people
I approached last week, Grezy?
Not even a date. Jesus Christ,
that is madness, bro.
I could easily go on a date, spend £300.
It's not a problem. She can't even go on
a [ __ ] date.
I just wish I could work again, bro.
Nice self-employed job. Yeah.
[ __ ] die boarding. I don't know how
Greasy sits around all day and he's fat ass.
Yeah, but it was it was reminding me of
them USA days when Monty was going mad
over Natalie. Oh, bless him. He learned
the hard way.
Getting a date is a hard thing. Getting
a conversation is a hard thing. You
can't even get a conversation out of
them. And when you do, it's out of a
boyfriend. That's all you ever get.
That's all you ever get, mate.
You can't even get a conversation out of
them, let alone a [ __ ] date, let
alone a relationship.
Is that right, Grezy?
Why are these batteries like this? [ __ ] off.
Yeah, I haven't tried that yet. I still
need to try it, but I haven't tried it yet. Batteries
These batteries are useless, bro.
But yeah, I got 30 numbers and I got
four repliers. But the good thing about
having loads of numbers is you can
message them again in a month and
sometimes they might meet you. One of
them might meet you. That's the good
thing about having all of these numbers.
I would never have stayed with that
20-year-old because she turned out to be a [ __ ]
She turned out to be a nasty [ __ ] Like
entitled and [ __ ] That's why I just
didn't give a [ __ ]
But she used to come around and suck my
willie greasy in the old house. Yeah.
She used to come around meet all the
tenants and suck my willie in the room.
It was quite cute to be honest. But
do you know why she was like she always
used to come back to me grievy? Cuz it
was always it was because of the money.
Cuz obviously I used to always have
[ __ ] 50s. I used to have so much
money, bro. Even to people our age, right?
And then obviously to someone that's
like 18, they've grown up with and and
you're all they basically know. So
they basically got attached with you
because of the money. They know that
they're not going to get that lifestyle anywhere else.
I spent £700 in one day, you know, on on
that day. £700, bro. It's a lot
Um, no I didn't pay her.
I just used to go for drinks with her and stuff. Yeah.
So obviously I used to like go casino, win money,
go for drinks. It was good times, bro.
So that's probably my best chance, but I
couldn't be dealing with her attitude.
So that's why I just swerved her. She
come around a few times and she had like
a I was getting the entitlement grievy.
So I just looked at her. I was like, I
thought it would go away and then it kept happening.
Yeah, she is after me for money.
Going out money. Of course she is. So, nope.
Not interested in beers. Not interested
in drinking. All I'm interested in
leaving. I need to save now. So,
I'm not interested in going on beers or
beers for what, bro?
But that 19-year-old was good, bro. She
was actually good-looking, too.
Yeah. And I was saying to the guy, I was
like, "No one wants to suck my dick." I
was like, "Listen, when you was in the
house, that girl that is 100 times
better looking than you, and all of the
tenants would agree was sucking my
dick." Oh, [ __ ] you. [ __ ] your mom.
That's what I said to her as well.
She was trying to be funny in it.
She was trying to be funny.
You remember when I got an STD test
squeeze? You had to go to the sex clinic
all by myself? Oh,
bless you. Hey, Nicolo, it's your
problem, not mine. I booked Thailand
last night. 770.
I didn't even put it up, bro.
I booked these flights, bro. So, it's
not my problem.
It's your problem. Where is it?
Not going to show the airline, but here we go.
I get I still got money. I might get 1k
a month. I still get I still have money.
I still get money. So, and I get more
than 1K actually, but not 2K. But yeah.
So, yeah. And I get more than 1K.
Slightly more. But doesn't even matter.
It's enough anyways really.
It's enough. Let me let me let me let me
let me let me explain it like this. It's
enough for somebody that's already lived
the life. I've already lived the life,
bro, for years. So, I didn't really feel
like I lost anything.
So, they don't know what Yeah, but they
don't know what flight it is. They don't
know what terminal it is. But yeah,
Nicolo, it's your problem now. It's not my problem.
Yeah. money. Come to London, bro. You
can you can come around, bro.
Yeah. 1K. No, it's a bit more than that.
But yeah, it doesn't matter. It's enough anyways.
I've already lived the life, bro. Like I
said, I've already lived the life. More
than enough. The only thing I'm doing in
my age now is I'm leaving. So, yeah. One sec.
Should have about I still have about 2K.
I think I've still got about two grand. So
you want you come to hang out? She like it here. Listen then
I remember I remember when N wanted to uh
meet me. Nah, not for good. Mighty man
lives there. Not money man. Sorry.
Antman lives there. But I I lose good. I
don't think so.
No, man. Just holiday. I'm not I'm not
moving there. [ __ ] that. That's what But
maybe I might. It depends how bad it
gets in England. If I can't find a job
or anything, then maybe I will go there
and start teaching English. So, yeah, maybe.
Who knows? But I don't think so, bro.
You know, England would be perfect,
right? If there weren't
so many [ __ ] the women weren't
[ __ ] You didn't have to wait
around for everything. It would actually
be a good country.
No, you'd have to come off benefits. Obviously,
they they'd stop you benefits, but you'd
get like 78 £800 a month, but it's a lot
of money over there. 7800 pound a month
is worth more over there than it is here. So
if I can't find a job, then I'll have to do that. So
there'd be no choice. I'd have to
fake money, man. I think
>> Yeah. I'm not saying no, no, nothing.
I'm going to jump back just I'm done
with YouTube PJ. I'm done with it. I'm
literally done with YouTube. So, like
>> I'm done with the money. But you Hold
on. You got me back on it. You [ __ ]
[ __ ] You can't just leave me.
>> I told you to go live this morning. Not now.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I wasn't going to come back
on it, bro.
>> That's your job. It's not mine to come
back on now. Like, this is your choice.
I haven't for
>> So, so you get So, you get me back on it
and you [ __ ] off. You can
>> Yeah. It's a part of being a troll,
ain't it, PJ?
>> I swear to God, Monty, I'm going to [ __ ]
you really hard when I see you again.
>> Yeah. No, I'm only joking. No,
>> no, but seriously, Monty, we should we
should we should meet up. Honestly,
>> no, you're too small for me, PJ.
>> Your your behavior was very concerning yesterday, Monty.
>> What do you mean?
>> You he was behaving a bit erratic.
What do you mean erratic?
>> You can't go around trying to get
sectioned. Monty, that's silly.
>> No, I was looking I weren't looking to
get sectioned. I was looking for help.
That's it. Because I I was feeling Yeah.
Like that's all what we're doing.
>> That's what Peter's here for.
>> My mom told me to go. >> Yeah.
So you came you came crying back to
Peter Belly. That's cute, isn't it?
>> My mom loves Natalie. My mom my mom's
not blaming Natalie
>> or any she's not blaming her for what
I'm doing or nothing like that. My mom
loves Natalie and that.
>> Well, I think we're I think we're
friends to the end, is it?
>> Friends to the end.
>> Yeah, bro. [ __ ] no. because you always I
think you always have like a little um
soft spot for me, you know.
>> Not in a gay way. No, not in a gay way.
Like obviously, but yeah.
>> No, I don't think
>> Yeah, but you can't stay You know how
you can stay mad at like Virgin and
that? You never stay mad at me. You see
what I mean? >> What?
>> You know how you stay mad at Virgin and
you never want to be his friend again.
>> What? I
>> know that Virgin. No nonsense.
>> No, he's not suitable for my [ __ ] IQ
with that [ __ ]
>> But but you never stay mad at
Peterbelly. Do you know what I mean?
>> I can do if you want me to.
>> No, Monty. We're friends. We got Wait,
Monty, we used to stay on PlayStation
till 5 in the morning talking.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Did we? Did we?
>> We should meet up again, man.
>> Okay. You know, you want to meet up so
bad with me, don't you, PJ?
>> Yeah, we go for some Guinnesses. >> What?
>> We can We can go for some Guinnesses.
>> I don't drink. Ask Mate if he's still
in. No, I'm not still in hospital. What
the [ __ ] Yeah, I can read I can read
your comments, you [ __ ]
I can read your comments. I can read
PJ can read your comments.
>> Yeah, I might come up to you at some
point. I know where you are. I'm not
going to tell these where you are
anyways. So, I know where you are.
>> But the thing is is that I'm moving
again. I'm moving again. But this time,
I've got me I hope Natalie is watching.
I hope she is watching cuz I've just got
off the phone to an outing place.
I've got three choices. I can rather get
get a flat. I can ether get a
one-bedroom flat or I can get a twobedroom flat
>> or I can get another one of these
places. One of these. I've just rung up
the other one of these places now.
looking for two
>> looking for a twobedroom
>> and me and that
>> are you speaking you back together?
>> I'm I'm trying to [ __ ] get back in a
good box. He's still in Bless you then.
>> I just want to get back in a good book.
>> Bless you.
That's cute. Is it Monty?
You'll always be in my good books.
>> The two bedrooms going to cost me 850 a month.
>> It's expensive, isn't it?
>> Yeah, it is expensive. 8 [ __ ] 50 a month.
>> So, you'll have hardly anything to live
on, isn't it?
No, I guess we have something to live
on, but it's [ __ ] expensive. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, there's another one. The onebedroom
flat is 800. The twobedroom flat is [ __ ] 850. >> Yeah.
>> The other place at least is
deepest chips. So, I go just go for the
cheap place. I'm [ __ ] tired now. I'm
going to sleep. I haven't been asleep
for five 4 days.
>> Well, bless you in life.
>> No, I'm going to be sick because of it.
>> Don't be sick. Come down here. You can
we can we can go to the pictures.
>> I'm not even I think there is not to
worry. If you come down here, I'll make
you a piggy sandwich. I
>> know. This is why >> what
is a good [ __ ] man? >> Uh,
have you been sick, Monty?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Oh my god,
that's quite concerning. Bless you.
Do you remember USA? Izzy Grezy,
she she's Oh, she's moved to Miami now,
by the way. Um, Grezy, I was on her
Facebook. She's moved to Miami.
I was thinking of going there some point.
lot cheaper. I knew I had something to tell you.
Might go there and cause a scene. Can you see? Bless you. Oh, cars.
Oh, bless Monty if he's being sick.
Bless you in life.
Is it your mama? Are you sure it's my mama? Greasy?
Yeah, it is my mama.
>> I think I'm just [ __ ] loves sick or
something. Me? I don't [ __ ] know.
>> You're just a fall in love.
>> You know, I've never felt like this for
anyone in my ent life. I can't even say [ __ ] man.
>> Oh, bless. Bless you.
>> Bless you.
I've never ever ever cried over a woman
in my entire life. Never.
>> Yeah, cuz he was too busy crying over
men. Only joking.
>> When have you ever seen me cry over a
woman or have you seen me [ __ ] like
start laughing at him? I saw you cry yesterday.
>> Yeah. Yeah, yesterday. Yeah, that's
tickering. That's [ __ ] tapering.
You know what you need to do? You need
to get some nice food, Monty, and get on
the Guinness. It will help you forget
all about it.
Hell doesn't wash you to array. It's not
you get pissed, you'd be happy for a
minute, then next morning, they'd be there again.
>> Yeah, but if you did, you should be all right.
>> Even with any kind of alcohol, it [ __ ]
you up. I've quit the weed, man. Because
the weed's [ __ ] me head up as well.
I've quit the weed. I haven't
>> I haven't had no weed. What? What? Since
yesterday I even yesterday I didn't even
have a job. I tipped all my
>> I tipped all my [ __ ] I tipped about I
said half an ounce an ounce down the toilet. >> Really?
>> Yeah. An ounce of weave down the toilet.
So, what do you like about Natalie the most? Like,
>> I'm not talking about Natalie to be
honest with you.
>> Okay, bro. No worries.
>> I don't want to say
>> Yeah, fine.
Me and you should go to a nice little pub.
>> I should even be [ __ ] back here. So,
I'm going to jump off PJ.
>> Okay. Just message me on Facebook. Yeah, whatever.
>> Yeah. Yeah, we'll do we'll do it. It's
not that I don't
>> see [ __ ] being here. You know what I
mean? Cuz I don't I don't want to be here. I
>> I don't know why I went on and when when
we was at the hotel. I don't know why I
went live be honest with you when I went there. They
>> Yeah, they are.
>> They're repeaters, isn't it?
>> Yeah. When I went live in the hotel, I
didn't go live for the idiots. I won't
lie to the good people who do want the
actual content. Actual [ __ ]
Well, these people here put you off the
content. They're not even [ __ ] proper
trolls. I I will offer any of these out
in this community. Who would show up?
>> none of them
>> exactly that lad that lad look um he was
he was um taking you know
but to join two places
you do this one sec what's
you do Yes. PJ,
can you see me? Can you check that? Anyway,
PJ, I'm going to jump off. Yeah.
A lot of love, Peter. A lot of love.
Yeah. What I was saying is basically the
difference is when I cried, my mommy
didn't care. My mommy abandoned me.
But I think Natalie G will care.
No one cared when I cried. and poured
out my little feelings.
No one cared grievy. I was mocked and
taunted and laughed at.
You know, my mom didn't give a [ __ ]
My mommy didn't care. She abandoned me.
I've come a long way since being
abandoned, haven't I, Grezy? By my mama. Yeah.
Why do you troll me, Gregy? Why do you
troll me? Why? Because it's a Black Ops.
I love Black Ops, bro.
Black Ops 2 is the best.
Right here, bro.
You must be signed into Xbox Live.
That doesn't make any sense. I'm logged
in. What did he show me?
Oh, here we go. One second. Here
we go. Look,
Black Ops team. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, me and me and Bonnie going to be
this probably my mommy abandoned me. Grezy,
she didn't care. She literally didn't
give a [ __ ]
How can you abandon your baby, bro?
That's so That's really horrible.
What's the point of having a baby if you
don't want them, huh?
just going to abandon them?
Doesn't make sense, does it? You know,
I can't believe she actually abandoned
me the way she actually abandoned me. That's horrible. You know,
don't you think that's just horrible to
just abandon someone like that? Just left left wondering.
I don't know how you do the gaming
streams on Xbox.
Oh, I want to get o you know GTA San
Andreas Grezy. There's this thing that I
follow on YouTube and they're still
showing like glitches.
They're still rinsing that game. You
know, 21 years later, that game is in my
opinion is the best GTA, but a lot of
people prefer four.
Yeah, I think San Andreas is the best,
bro. There's so many glitches in that
game that you don't even know.
I love San Andreas, bro.
No, I don't know how you do it.
You want you wanted me to do a little um
little GTA game through with Mr. Mcoo's
voice, didn't you? Greavvesy Franklin. Yeah.
You wanted me to do like a little
gaming videos. Yeah. With Mr. Mcoo's
voice, isn't it?
Okay, I'll give it a while. My favorite
character is Franklin.
Yeah, my favorite character is Franklin.
How big is your telly, Grezy?
Yeah, I like Franklin. Oh, Franklin.
How big's your telly?
I like when Franklin sticks his middle finger up.
He he sticks his middle finger out the car.
Franklin's got me through some tough
times, you know. Grey, he got me through
some tough depressing times.
Oh, it's a bit small, isn't it? Mine's
55 in. But
uh Oh, I booked Thailand yesterday.
Yep, there we go. I booked Thailand yesterday. £770 for November.
I just figured I can't keep living like
this. Going round and round and round
and round and round in circles.
This just ain't no life for anyone, Joe.
You know, it's no life for anyone in
this country. So I figured, listen,
Ant-Man's done it
right four times,
you know, keep getting the [ __ ] and I
got and I got to the point where I just
use logic, Joe. I realized that people
told me, you know, it will change. Then
I tell you what, Joe,
I got 30 numbers last week. Didn't even
get a date, which I was supposed to go
on two dates. They ghosted. Then I
stumbled across this guy's um channel in
America when he was going around
approaching women and he was more
confident than me and he was getting the
same old I have a boyfriend, you're too
old for me, you're too young for me. And
it just got annoying. It was just
annoying watching it and I was like this
this is life is too short, bro. I'm not
doing this [ __ ] anymore. I'm not in this cycle anymore,
you know? This is ridiculous, bro. This
has got to stop. This has been happening
for years now. It's only continuous to
get worse. And yeah, I shouldn't be on a
date. I should be on a date this week.
I should There's no reason I shouldn't
be on a date this week with the amount
of trying I done them them them days.
So, I didn't go out last week. I'm not
going out this week either. Oh, I got a
football bet. Joe, would you like to see
it? I have booked it, bro. I swear it's
good. I booked it. I'm going in November.
This time I'm going to do videos just to
just to show Grezy. I'm going to put
some videos on my channel just to show Grezy
because this is ridiculous, bro. Like if
something was going to change, it would
have changed in three and a half years.
And it hasn't. So I mean it's the same
old I should be on a date this week.
I've done enough trying last you know
that stupid foreign woman goes to me.
So it's like you were supposed to meet
me. We arranged to meet and then Yeah.
So it's never going to change. So I
think I done the right thing.
All right. Do you want to see this
football? I done I'll show you it.
Actually, I kind of need this football
bet to come in now. I don't I don't get
as much money now. So, I mean, I don't
need it to come in, but I'd like it to
come in. I could go out today, spend
£400 if I wanted to,
but I need Yeah, I'll show you it if you want.
I ain't got I need I I'd like it to come
in because I do have an extra almost £300.
But if it doesn't then
yeah what what do you do by
there it is
war and spending both teams to score and
coldchester and tramier both teams to score.
This is only because I can't [ __ ]
Yeah, I put 80 pound on it. 285, which
is basically 300 pound it. So,
but who is he going to win? Eh.
>> Yeah, because they always used to win,
you know. I won four in a row before. What?
Yeah, cuz Colchester Colchester wins.
We swing both teams to score. So I need
300. It's almost £300 285. It will pay
for like two nights out. If if it
doesn't win then it doesn't win. But
listen, did you watch um LJ's live
stream yesterday? Lord uh LJ's live
stream yesterday. He was going mad at losing £100
and he said, "Oh, I don't I just don't
like losing on them machines. I don't
mind losing £100 on the horses, but I
don't like losing on them machines."
Oh, so now you finally understand now
how [ __ ] annoying it is.
Yeah, it is annoying losing on them
machines, [ __ ] And you used to call
me [ __ ] skip because of it. No. Why
would I be ski? I just don't like losing
on them [ __ ] shitty ass machines.
So you're like,
but he needs to be real with himself,
but I don't need to lie, bro.
I get [ __ ] £1,100 a month. I don't
need to lie. Rocky Roy will tell you the
same [ __ ] He seems to go on that he's
got more money than he does, but in
reality, he he doesn't have anything. I
don't know why he needs to lie. Just be truthful.
Don't know why people need to lie on here.
Yeah, it is both teams to score. Yeah. So,
don't know why he needs to lie, bro. But
I don't really like gambling. I hate
gambling. As soon as I can do a
self-employed job again, I'm going to
get on it and quit again like I was. So,
yeah. But he goes on like he's rich when
he really has nothing.
Like he really doesn't have anything
more than a normal person. But he seems
to go on like he's rich.
It's strange when we all know that he's on benefits.
It's very weird, you know, very very weird.
But I'm Yeah. Once I get a self-employed
job again, I'm not I'm quitting the gambling again.
I just don't like the whole you're not
guaranteed to win. I can't I don't like that.
I just don't see the point in gambling
to be honest.
I only done it because uh nice win it if it wins.
Probably won't win. I'll probably just
get an escort to be honest. Few lights
out on the desk over there. Yeah.
Well, I didn't like that. Actually, I do
cuz when I was a child, there was this
Tai American that I used to find good-look
actually. And um the Australian one was also Thai.
I tell you what, I don't like these
[ __ ] westernized [ __ ] here.
Yeah, there used to be one on
Nickelodeon that I used to like. I was a
child as well and she was she was tie as
well. So, yeah.
But if if it means not getting that I've
got a boyfriend [ __ ]
then so be it, bro. Like this. That's
why I'm not going out today. There's lit
there's little to no point in even me
going out trying to speak to anyone cuz
they all they've all got Tik Tok brains.
So, it's just a complete waste of time
just even even doing it
barbers getting the same [ __ ] hearing
the same boyfriend [ __ ] Got I got 30
numbers. I don't even have a date
replies. It's just pointless, bro. This
just is really just pointless.
The only way this is ever going to
change is what I said to Antman yesterday. Yeah.
Is if they ban social media, which is
never going to happen. You go to South
America or you go to Asia. That's the
only way this is possibly going to change.
And the first thing is never going to happen.
So it's like that's the only way this is
going to stop
just the same as like cuz like I said I
was watching that guy in America and in
if anything it's even worse over there.
I'd say it's even worse in America than
it is here which I didn't think it would
have been but watching them videos.
[ __ ] Jesus Christ bro. Like
what am I going to do longterm? probably
just use just use escorts.
Go Tai, use escorts. Go back to
Thailand. Something like that. South
America. You also go South America
because this is
ridiculous. Just stay there for 3 months time. Yeah.
He's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
Does anyone watch that Billy Moore? I
watch Billy Moore and then I see that
Charlie belts. I've known about that for ages.
But yeah, that's what Yeah, if it was
back in the If this was M if this was
MSN days again Yeah. MSN days, then
[ __ ] hell, bro. You'd be pulling
You can't even get kisses anymore. I I
noticed that in the past 18 months
there's been a change. You can't even
get kisses. You can't get anything from
anyone. You can't even get a
conversation out of anyone.
I don't like that Charlie Beach, bro.
He's a coward.
Funny. I've never seen him in Manchester
all the times I've been. He's a coward,
bro. He's a proper coward. He has like
security now as well.
He's a proper coward. He is. Yeah. So,
yeah, escort. Yeah. I can go, like I
said, I could go out today if I wanted
to, but just pointless.
It's not change all them other times. It
ain't going to change now.
So, yeah, I can't be after it.
[ __ ] Billy Mo.
Jesus. He goes all around England. I
watch him. He It's like what I used to
do. Go all around England. But he
doesn't go abroad.
Does anybody watch that Wendle?
I was watching his Benador video
yesterday the other day. I watch a lot
of these people, man.
Oh, what's Wendle? You might not know
about Wendell, but I What's that? Billy Moore.
Yeah, it reminds me when I used to go
all around England.
Just chilling, man. I got no plans. Just
chilling. Playing Call of Duty.
Yeah, bro. Just chilling.
glass is there.
I know I know the side men, Joe. Do you
know who they are? I used to see the
side men all the time.
Yeah, I know about him.
I know about that walk on the wild side.
But I know the side men, you know. I I
used to see them
in in Westfield all the time. I've seen
the sign, man.
I saw that [ __ ] um Cal Freezy. I've
seen that Cal Freezy two times. Tall
[ __ ] he is. Yeah, he's a he's a tall
[ __ ] he is, mate. That Cal Freezy.
He's [ __ ] tall [ __ ]
Don't know if anyone know who that is.
Yeah, that Tree is a tall [ __ ] bro. I
used to see him in Westfield all the
time. Cool [ __ ]
Yeah, he's tall, bro. Yeah, man.
Well, I am traveling, bro. I'm going to
[ __ ] Asia in [ __ ] November,
but I'm not traveling around this country.
And like I said, I'm in the 1% when they
It's like I was saying to this guy in
Wales. Yeah. When I met in the pub, I
was like, you might think I'm being a
bit awkward, but it it's not going to
change cuz I've probably traveled more
than anybody my age around England. And
when I traveled, I would approach women.
Yeah, I'm still single. So, how is it
suddenly? It's like what Adman said,
it's never going to change. Like I said,
it's not like this has been going on for
6 months, 8 months, a year. A year is
nothing. You might not meet someone
trying in a year, but three and a half years, bro.
Come on now. It will never change. Never. Never change. [Music]
I'm going to be poor now. I'm going to be poor. No.
How do you not know who the side men
are, Joe? I don't know how you don't
know who the side men are.
You must know who the sidemen are.
They're bunch of [ __ ] They are. Grey
knows who they are. They He must know
You don't know who they are? I know who they are.
They're rich [ __ ] That's what they are.
Oh my god, bro. [ __ ]
Oh, there's this guy that I watch. Yeah.
Oh, his name is Kings Cleans. And at
first, yeah, he he annoyed me like his
face. And then I seen like what he does.
Yeah. And he actually transforms
trainers. So he catch he gets people's
dirty trainers and he makes them look
brand new. And I can't lie, I rate it,
bro. Like I I like that. I think it's he
has like all these different tools. He
brings it back to like his apartment, I
guess, and he refurbishes transforms the trainers.
I was like, bro, I can't lie. I actually
I actually rate that, bro.
That's actually pretty good.
He actually like transforms people's
trainers. He does a good job at it, bro.
So, I was like, "Yeah, that's
Yeah. See him on uh on Instagram."
Yeah, it is. But
that's his Instagram.
He does a good job, bro. That's like hard grafted. Yeah.
I rate him, bro. I can't lie. Does a good job.
If I had a million followers, I'd have
people interested all the time. I think
that's the only way you can get a
girlfriend in this country is have loads
of followers on Instagram.
Um, I showed it before I booked it, you [ __ ] idiot.
Yeah, I'm going to need it. I'm going to
need Good luck.
You need like followers and [ __ ] If you
ain't got followers, they're not interested. Simple.
Which is sad cuz there is people out
there that actually want children. I
think it's sad. Me
say that like you you always wanted
children, which I don't, but and
obviously you can't have children
because you can't find anyone.
It's bad, isn't it?
It's really bad.
That's really sad to be honest. No, it's not him.
Yeah, just like you and just like many
others. Well, you will.
You will. If you stay in this country,
you be single forever.
But not if you leave. If you stay in
this country, you will be single forever. Yeah.
Huh? No, you won't have success, Joe.
Because women don't even change when
they're 40. I'd say they change when they're 60.
Look at that Jane. She's 40. She still
does the same [ __ ] There's this woman
on Instagram. She's 40. Nah, even when
you're 40, they don't change.
I'd say more 60. Me. Look at Jane. Look
at what Jane does. She's she's a
Yeah, I did see it. It was funny.
Now, I don't even think in 40 I don't
even think when they're 40 they they they stop.
I think more 60 me. Yeah.
Yeah. Maybe. You never know. But I
didn't know. I don't think America would
be worse than here, but it is. It was
pissing me off, Joe. This black guy was
approaching these women. Boyfriend,
boyfriend, boyfriend. [ __ ] annoying
it is. It's like they don't know any other word.
They're literally NPCs.
I was watching them do it as well.
They're literally non-playing characters.
You'd have the same problem in America.
They're not going to think, "Oh, you're
from England." Nah, trust me, bro. I was
watching this guy and he was doing it in
Florida. He was doing it in New York. He
was doing it in Chicago. And it was it
it seemed worse than it was here.
All [ __ ] And the thing with them as
well is they think their country is
better than anyone else's. So there it
would be even worse because they they
they've got even more egos there cuz
they seem to think their country is
better than everyone else's. I mean look
all the [ __ ] come from there. USA Izz
is a [ __ ] She come from there
you know. So yeah,
they're all [ __ ] bro.
They're all [ __ ] Um, so Yeah, bro.
Same with Canada.
They're all [ __ ] Every woman you're
going to meet is going to be a [ __ ] So,
what's the [ __ ] point even trying?
It's mad how they all use social media.
I don't even use Tik Tok.
Strange, isn't it?
And then even if it is, it's it feels
like you're begging, which you shouldn't
be like that. Not begging, but like when
someone's like, "Oh, like they're seeing
someone and they're playing hard to
get." Like even that shouldn't happen
because you realistically you're better
than them. You're they're not above you.
You shouldn't be begging them. You
They're not above you. That's all wrong
in itself. You know, there was one
playing game saying that she's still
seeing someone, then they reply back
like it shouldn't be. They're not better
than you. Well, obviously simps on
social media make them feel like they're
better than people. This is where these
problems happen, you know? So,
they're not better than anyone.
But it's the simp. So,
yeah, sometimes I use Reddit sometimes. Yeah.
you know. Yeah. There's so many simps,
bro. So many. And the thing that don't
make sense is it's always the ones that
don't get women or never had women that
that defend them.
It's not even like people that's had
women. That's the weirdest thing about
it is that they just sit there and
they're just like I said, they're just
lying to themselves.
They're just lying lying to themselves, bro.
They're just lying to themselves,
trying to think that there's not a
problem. And I've had women I've had
more women than them. I don't defend
them because there's nothing to defend.
They are just generally [ __ ] That's
what they are more than any of these
simps. And they're [ __ ]
Like any anyone would think the way that
I complain is I've never had one.
They're just they are [ __ ]
But people don't think these simps
defend them. It's weird.
And I tr truly believe a lot of them are
evil as well. So
you see when Monty man was crying over
Natalie, do you think anyone gave a [ __ ]
when I was like that?
That's how I know that it was Monty's
first love. Because if it wasn't his
first love, trust me, you would never
get attached again. When you actually
realize what they're like, you can't
even get attached to them because even
if you got attached to them, sorry, you
would know what they do. You would
expect what they do.
Don't you expect what they do, bro?
But sometimes I get I get caught up in
it sometimes as well. Like this one from
Ukraine, I was like, "They're going to
meet. they're going to meet. I was
hoping that they were, but then deep
down I was like, you got to kind of
expect that they're just going to [ __ ]
you over like they always do.
No, I just been chilling, man. Playing
GTA, playing COD. There's nothing to get up to. Nope.
Nothing really to go up to really is
that it's [ __ ] boring, bro.
It's boring, man. Yeah.
Yeah, he did.
Like I said, like I was saying earlier,
when that 20-year-old [ __ ] went, I
didn't give a [ __ ] Yep.
We were supposed to meet on Thursday.
She came back to England. Then she just
blocked me. Strange. We arranged to
meet. Just the same old. It will never
change. Same old England. Well, I don't
go out anymore.
It's [ __ ] very rare. I go out now.
Same old [ __ ] England, is it? Never
change. Never ever ever ever never
change in this country. Matey, look.
It's It makes me laugh when people think it will.
How could it?
I still playing slots, bro. The [ __ ]
I'm not playing slots for [ __ ] ages.
What are you on about?
You got brain damage, matey.
Yeah, we'll never change. So, yeah.
Anyway, she was supposed to meet me and
then she never. So, she was coming back
from the country she was at and it was
one tick, but I didn't think anything of
it. I didn't think anything of it of it
because sometimes it is one tick when
she has no signal. Then I woke up and it
was still one tick and I'm thinking,
"What the [ __ ]
Then I messaged on my mom's phone and
then I've been blocked. So
yeah, it will never change, bro. Never.
Cuz it sometimes is one tick and then it
would go two ticks where she never had signal.
Why? Because they're sick in the head.
You know, she didn't have a picture.
So that's the funny thing is she never
had a picture.
But they do it to [ __ ] with your head
because they're sick in the head. That's
why they do it. Well, it's self-explanatory.
So then I messaged on my mom's phone
just to see and then it was two ticks. I
was like, "Oh, the [ __ ] got me. It's mad."
They are all the same.
They are all the same. Entitled,
westernized. I can actually read you the conversation actually
if you want. Where is it?
Her name was Tanya.
She was like, "Hi, sorry. I saw your
message, but then someone interrupted me
and I forgot to reply." Bit strange,
isn't it? It's been so busy at work. No,
I don't live with my mom. I was around my mom's.
I don't get hangovers because I only
drink low alcohol stuff. I'm fine
tomorrow. We'll be back on Sunday night.
How are you? Have a great Thursday. I
said, "Oh, that's fine." But I said,
"Oh, no worries." Yeah, been good,
thanks. Where are you heading to?
Heading to Moldova for a Ukrainian rock
concert in brackets day. Singing
Russian, though. What are you going to
do Thursday? I said, "Oh, nice. I'm
going for some food and meet a friend
for a few beers. Guess we could do
something next Thursday if you're down.
What day do you want to meet?" She said,
"Oh, why not? When?" I work Monday and
Tuesday. I said, "Oh." I said, "Let's do
Thursdays. Thursdays are good." Thumbs
up. Okay. And
then she asked me what I was doing. Told
her what I was doing. Then I messaged
her 2 days after nothing.
So yeah, same old. Never change.
Never ever ever change, bro.
Never changing good old England.
Good old England. So yeah,
I just told her I was meeting a friend.
It will never change in good old
England. Richard, help me. Help me.
So yeah, it will never change.
So that's why I booked the whole
Thailand thing, bro, cuz I want to
change cuz this ain't changing in this
country anytime soon. So yeah, man.
Anyone would think you're fat and ugly.
No, I think they all like it, B.
Unless they're in their 60s, I think
they all like it. I think they're all the same.
Personally, bro, nah, there's no good
ones. They're all the same. If there was
good ones, you would have found one by
now. Three and a half years counting. If
there was good ones, you would have
stumbled across them with the amount of
approaches that you've done, I've done.
That's what I mean. Hold on. N there's
no good ones. They all They've all got
Tik Tok brains.
Yep. Well, you get people from New York
and London. So, and yeah, of course it
would be IA because it's full of English people
that go over there. [ __ ]
any westernized country is bad.
There's no good ones. They're literally
all they they're all the same. They say
the same stuff. I have a boyfriend. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no.
I have a boyfriend.
I was hearing it, bro. I hate I hate
hearing that, bro. It [ __ ] annoys me,
I'll give you this black guy's Instagram
channel. Yeah, it's so annoying hearing it.
Just change the record. Just [ __ ] off
with it, man. It's annoying.
I have to turn it off. I have to I have
to turn it off, bro. Yeah,
it is annoying.
I have a boyfriend.
Oh my god, they're all They're all the same.
So all the bugings I maintain.
No, why would they find it annoying?
That's what that's how people used to
be. Why would it be annoying? It's
actually quite a brave masculine thing
to do to be able to approach someone. I
don't think it's annoying. It's all you
can do since dating apps don't work.
Again, when you only see things from your perspective, right,
that's the thing that you come up with,
but you don't see it from anyone else's
perspective. Which is what I was trying
to say to that woman from Australia
is that you're only seeing it from your
perspective. Oh, it might make some
people feel unsafe. Oh, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Stop talking
about yourself. Um, no self projecting
on my channel. Um, but you don't see it
from Yeah, you asking. Stop talking
about yourself again. You are the ones.
Um, you are the ones that can't get off
of YouTube, not me. So, you must be
talking about yourselves. My approach to
my approaches sound nervous. No, they
don't. Never been never ever ever been
nervous to approach.
No, they don't. And yeah, anyways, I was
saying that if you see it from some if
you see it from someone else's point of
view, you know, and she then and she
didn't know what to say to that cuz they
only see it from their point of view.
That's the thing.
You know, there's two POVs.
And even if I did sound nervous, you're
scared to approach. Like most people are
scared to approach. I'm not scared to
approach, bro. The [ __ ]
No, I don't sound nervous. Never been
You're probably just saying that cuz
you're scared to do it yourself.
Just like most people. So,
so you probably can't even approach
yourself. That's why you're saying that
I sound nervous. Never sound nervous.
And it's normal to be nervous as well.
Anyways, even if you was nervous,
you probably can't even do approaches.
a worker with money. You keep telling yourself that.
And let me guess, they don't want they
want someone to
uh not live with their mom, right? They
want somebody that uh works, don't live
with their mom, and goes to a gym. Uh
yeah. Yeah. That's just, you know, the
things that you're using there is just excuses.
That's just a load of [ __ ] because
we all know even from other people's
experiences when someone tries to speak
to a woman what you get. So all of that
simp excuse [ __ ] is bollocks cuz it's
been proven wrong time and time and time
again. I live by myself. I went to the
gym. I worked. I had money. Never changed.
But I lived by myself for 2 years when I
went. Nothing changed. [ __ ] And I
was working two times. So you're talking
out your ass. No, they don't. They want
people with loads and loads and loads of
Instagram followers. Million Instagram
So yeah. No, they really, really, really
don't because most people work.
Most people live by themselves. So all
of these people that struggle, so it's
not that they want a worker. That's
[ __ ] because they you don't you
can't even get a conversation out of
them. So how would they know whether you
work? Anyways, I'm not going through
this. Anyways, these are just silly
excuses. If you're too brain damaged to
think that that's on you, bro. We're not
going over this again. I don't need to
talk about this. I'm going to Thailand.
It's not my problem anymore.
You keep being a s. See where that gets
you in life, bro. It's not my problem.
It wasn't my problem.
from the day I booked that flight which
was yesterday. It then become not my problem anymore.
Anyways, [ __ ] you know you people. Yeah.
The one I just banned. You say that I'm
skint. You say that I'm this. You say
that I'm that.
But you're the ones that can't get off
YouTube. You're the ones that on YouTube
all day. This money man got me back on
this YouTube yesterday. He kept telling
me to go live and live and live and
live. Let's look at the bigger picture.
You can't even take a day off of
YouTube. People that wasn't skint would
be spending all their life on YouTube.
It just goes to show that you are the
skin ones without being called it
because you wouldn't be on here.
That's that's you can't argue with
facts. the day you people stop coming on
coming on YouTube and projecting is the
I'll say okay you're not skin think
about it bro what what does calling
someone skid mean you've got all of this money
why are you on YouTube every day no life
no one no one can answer it you know
uh cuz that's what people do they book
things in advance. Uh,
so let me ask you this question. I'm
Skin. I'm this. I'm that. Okay. So, how
comes I can come off of YouTube, but you
people can't come off of YouTube without
name calling because you must be skin.
You literally must be skin yourselves
sat indoors on you. I mean, I've been
sat in a couple of days, bro, cuz I've
just been chilling. I'm on a detox, but
I ain't been on YouTube.
I've been I've done a lot the past two
well I haven't even been s actually I
was out the [ __ ] I was out doing
other things but yeah so it must mean
that you are skin that literally that
must mean you asking yourselves November Uh,
okay, bro. But yeah, Richard, why are
they on YouTube every day with everyone else's skin?
Did you hear what Did you hear what Lord
J said the other day? If YouTube closed
down, me and Kitty would be [ __ ] Me
and Kitty would be [ __ ] bro. We don't
care about YouTube. I only went on
YouTube yesterday because Monty wanted
me to come on YouTube. Huh?
So why are you use on YouTube every day
if you got all of this money and your
lives are so better?
See, evidence catches you out, doesn't
it? Because you got no life. Think about
it. You've been sat on this [ __ ]
shitty platform for [ __ ] years
calling other people what you are
yourselves, but you claim that your life
is better than everyone else's and
everyone else's skin and everyone else's
this. Yet you prove to be the favorite
thing when you can't get off of YouTube.
Sat on YouTube every [ __ ] day of your [ __ ] life.
On your [ __ ] life on [ __ ] YouTube.
You know what I'm saying? Come on, bro.
It doesn't look right.
If you go on that Lord Jay's Richard or
anyone, you will see it's the same
people every [ __ ] day. the same
people, same atmosphere. This is why I
don't go on it anymore, bro. Only
because this Monty man was just begging
me to come back on it. I was like, "Fuck
it. Okay, cool. Whatever, bro." He He
was in a bad place. I said, "Okay, let
me talk to him." He was begging me to go
live, bro. I said, "Bro, I don't want
anything to do with this [ __ ] whole place anymore." You know, simple.
I'm just mad.
These people will prove to me one day
when they stop commenting on YouTube
that they were right about me and not themselves.
It's like that Subzero. Have you ever
seen that Subzero account on YouTube
every [ __ ] day? Every everywhere you
you go, you see him on YouTube, but
they've got all this money. Their lives
are better than everyone else's, but
they're sat online every day.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Come on.
Yeah, they're all projectors, bro.
They're all projectors.
Doesn't matter what I will do. Well,
worry about your own life,
you know. That's it, man.
And then they give you [ __ ] when you
moan about women, which I don't really
understand to be honest because none of
you have ever been showed with a woman.
And then you still call me for it. Like,
think about it, bro. I can sit here and
say that women are [ __ ] They're
stuck up. They're [ __ ] And I've
probably had more women than most of you
people, but yet you still try and call
me for it. It's funny, bro, isn't it? It
really is funny. You know,
I'm not going out today cuz I can't be [ __ ]
Germany just can't be bothered to go out
today. It's just pointless.
Oh, they're all strange. They all
They're all obsessed with me, bro. Jamie
Thompson, Virgin Boy. They're all obsessed.
Yeah, they're all They're all obsessed.
They're all obsessed. Jealous people
that waste their life on me, bro.
They've been doing it for years. So, yeah.
Yeah. He stalks me every day, bro. He He
emails me as well.
But again, he's got everything in life
that I want.
Yeah, bro. You have everything that I
want, yet you're the one stalking me every day. Uh, yeah, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. You have everything I want, bro. Really? Uh,
why am I on this morning? To speak to Monty, man.
Why are you on YouTube? Why are you
people on YouTube every day? Okay, you
Okay, I answered your question. I was on
YouTube to speak to Monty Man cuz he
kept telling me to go on YouTube.
Yeah. Why are you people on YouTube
every day can't get off it?
No, no, no. So, let me rephrase that.
Why can't you take a single day off of YouTube?
I'm skinn. I got no money, bro. I'm
dying. I'm I'm [ __ ] Like really
[ __ ] Your lives are so perfect. Why
do you waste your precious life on
YouTube every day
stalking? Your life is so much better
than everyone else that you call. Then
it just doesn't really make any sense.
And then you just realize that you're
actually talking about yourselves cuz
you wouldn't be on here, you know. So
I told you why I'm on there.
Why do they target me? Oh, [ __ ] My
arm's hurting, man. Um, jealousy.
They target me because they're jealous. Um,
that's that's the only thing it can be
why they would waste their life every
day doing this. It's cuz it's jealousy.
Or they want to [ __ ] you or both. That's
the only reason they target me, bro.
Got more money than them. I'm better
looking than them. You know, people
don't like that, you know.
Yeah. Because they don't have a life.
Like Red Star, bro.
How long has this guy been doing this?
And I don't even go on his channel. He
just wastes his life away on me. He just
wastes his life every day stalking me,
bullying himself. It's quite sad to be honest.
And the thing is I don't even go on the
channel but since you want to even bring
it up like they don't realize that they
just they just embarrass themselves.
That's all they do. They just embarrass
themselves on YouTube.
They're fat ugly mters. They got no
money. That's why they do this [ __ ]
every every day, bro.
So yeah, man.
Yeah, he's been doing it for years as
well. That red star, bro. It's sad, isn't it? Yeah.
He doesn't show his face because he's too ugly.
That red star doesn't show his face cuz
he's he's too ugly. But everyone knows
he's a coward anyways. So fat coward.
Yeah. He's just some fat little little victim.
Little bully victim coward.
That's what he is. Yeah.
That reacts to me every day. Doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter what I would do.
He would never leave his keyboard.
So, nothing anyone can do. Eh, and then
even that when I'm And then even then
you got Jane messaging me. I don't know
how many times, right?
They ain't messed my life up.
They ain't messed my [ __ ] life up, mate.
They ain't messed my life up at all.
They're just They're just harassing
stalkers. That's all they are.
Yeah. Messed my life up, mate. All I was
living by myself. But yeah. Yeah.
That red star is a [ __ ] proper
coward. Everyone knows. And then if it's
not them, [ __ ] then you got Jane emailing you.
That's fake Monty. No woman would ever
make me [ __ ] cry. [ __ ] that.
No. [ __ ] that, bro.
After that USA is [ __ ] [ __ ] that. I
knew then they were like evil, bro.
I knew then they were evil [ __ ] even from then.
That's why I don't um
[ __ ] with that, bro. Oh [ __ ]
I got a feeling that uh Richard is that rocky ride.
Little Rocky one. Sorry. What's his name? Um,
what's that motherfucker's name again?
Yeah, but he has all this money, doesn't
he? Nikki, but he begs for donations.
What's his name again? Dusty Shers.
Yeah, that Richard is Dusty Shoes, not
Rocky Road. Why? Rocky Road. >> Yeah.
Yeah, that's dusty. Uh,
that's dusty [ __ ] showers. That is
Yep. Hey, that Richard is a
Is that show is that show?
Why don't you just come on your real account, bro?
Oh, [ __ ] me.
Yeah, I'd go out for a drink today, but
it's utterly pointless
just to hear a boyfriend. They've all got boyfriends.
They've all got boyfriends, matey.
I need a haircut, matey.
Why do I eat pork? Uh, because I can.
What a stupid question. Why do I eat pork?
Why do you drink water?
[ __ ] hell. What a stupid question.
Why do you come on YouTube every day and
can't get off it?
Yeah, I am Muslim.
Yeah, I am Muslim. So what?
I am a Muslim.
What do you think? I want you crying
over that energy.
Bless him. Bless him in life.
Will it all the same?
When does he re when would he realize this? >> Yeah. [ __ ]
Nah, I love piggies, bro. Yeah, that uh
Richard is um Dusty Showbiz.
He makes it too obvious.
This is what I mean, bro. None of you
have got lives on there in it. You do
this year in year out, year in year out,
and then you come on different accounts.
You really ain't got a life, do you?
You know, it's it's to this point now,
right? I just feel sorry for you. Right?
I know you come on here and you try to
bully people and whatever, but I just
feel sorry for you. I actually, you know
what? It's to a point that I actually
feel sorry for you,
you know, and it just goes to show that
you really are the skid ones cuz you
want it every day. So yeah.
Yeah, that's definitely that dusty
showbiz that uh Richard. Yeah, 100%.
>> I told you. I told you, bro. I can smell
them like a like a dead fox.
Yes, I know, bro. I have literally
nothing, bro. I'm going to be on the street soon.
I know, bro. I'm lonely, depressed. I
have no money. Uh-huh. I know. But you
can't get off of YouTube.
You're under fake accounts trolling on YouTube.
So, it doesn't look good, does it? I'm
lonely, depressed. I've got no money.
I'm about to die. Yeah, but guess what?
I can come off of YouTube. You can't.
So, it says more about your life than it
does my life. You can write whatever you
want, say whatever you want. That
doesn't mean anything. We know that you
can't come off of YouTube. So, it must
be about yourself you're talking about. Simple.
So, I don't need to sit here and say,
"You're this, you're that, you're you
don't know where I live and you would
never know where I live." Um, there's no
point name calling because without
evidence is pointless. We know that you
can't come off of YouTube.
You're so much of a [ __ ] I just
realized who you was. You're so
disabled, you don't even know how to
cover yourself up. But anyways,
you're still on YouTube. I told you why
I'm on YouTube. Cuz Monty man kept
[ __ ] harassing me to come back. You
can't take one day off of YouTube.
Why is that? I'm lonely. I'm depressed.
I don't know anything about uh You don't
know anything? I do know stuff about you.
One second. One second. I I do know
stuff about you. You can't get off
YouTube. You sit on YouTube every day self-projecting.
Every time one of you people's faces get
put out there, you're always fat and
ugly. So, yes, I can actually I I can
actually um I'm not even I'm not
So, uh, yeah. So, we know that you can't
come off of YouTube. So, uh, yeah, we
know that you can't come off YouTube
because the evidence is there. The
evidence is there that you can't come
off of YouTube, which is ridiculous
because if you wasn't lonely, depressed,
and skint, and every and everything that
you call other people, why are you on
YouTube every day?
I've still not I've still not got the
answer to this.
I've literally still not got the answer
to this. You keep deflecting. If you are
not lonely, bored, and skint, why can't
you come off of YouTube?
Why are you on YouTube every day? I'm
not on YouTube every day. I've come off
of YouTube for days, weeks, two weeks.
But you people can't come off of
YouTube, which paints a quite worrying
picture because hold on a minute. If
someone has all this money and they're
not lonely and depressed, they wouldn't
be on here. That's that's the logic that
I go by and it's quite accurate. Why are
you making fake accounts every single
day, spending all of your life on
YouTube, wasting it if your life is so
perfect? And it goes about your own
lives. Yep. You are no life. You are
scared. Yep. Again, you're the ones that
are on YouTube every single day, not me.
You're the ones that haven't shown me 10
grand talking about yourselves. You can
talk about yourselves
and try to say it's other people every
day, but guess what, bro? It's not going
to change the fact that you're talking about yourself.
It's not going to change the fact that
you're talking about your own virgin
skin lives on YouTube every day. I
noticed how like when I said about how
you you can't come off of YouTube, it it
it triggered you because it's the truth.
You little sad little virgins have never
even been with a woman. And you ain't
even got a penny to your name. All of
this self projection. I love it because
it's all about your own skin ugly lives
cuz you're on YouTube every day. I know
that I pulled the trigger. Bam. You
can't get off of YouTube. It pulls the
trigger because they can't argue with it
because these spastics are on YouTube
every day. Okay, listen.
I calling this typeman [ __ ] anyways.
How about you come and join the
hangouts, bro? So, before I ban these
little cowards, right, the dusty
showers, little bongo,
let me put the link up.
I'm going to show you how ugly these
people are. If they've got the balls to
join the hangouts, I'm going to show you
how ugly and skint they are, but they
ain't got the balls to join. They ain't
got the balls to join these little sados.
I will show you about these ugly [ __ ]
These ugly, insecure [ __ ] that will not
join my hangouts cuz I control them.
They can't join my hangouts, bro. Cuz I
[ __ ] control them.
Yeah, you're talking about yourselves
on. Let's see if any of them can come on
the Hangouts and say anything to me. I'm
ignoring the comments now from these
little virgins. Let's see if any of
these can join the hangouts. Anyone's welcome.
Yeah, you're calling yourself a ba on
YouTube every day. Never had a woman.
You are the ma. Every time you leave
your house, you get bullied, mate. You
are the ma. The m of all time. The skint
one at that. Hiding behind a YouTube
account on a Friday all by himself. Oh,
that's funny. That is, bro. Sat on
YouTube. The ma. No money. Waiting for
his little benefits behind his little
account. You are the ma. The biggest
one. the biggest bud to go in. Listen,
mate. Have you Have you shown
You sure hasn't shown Okay, let let's
let's let's go by the evidence here.
I've been shown with women. I've been
shown with money. These little bongos
have been shown to be on YouTube every
day projecting. The evidence is there.
Bongo man, the evidence is there. The
evidence is literally there. You
skimplints ain't shown a penny. You
skint little YouTube keyboard warbies.
I've never been with a woman. The
evidence is there. The evidence is
there. Anyways, I'm locking these little
bongos now. Anyways, these little
spackers. See, they're so disabled.
Like, listen, Stephen Albert. They're so
disabled that they can't even troll.
That's the maddest thing about it is
they can't even troll because you sus
them out straight away. Bro, I told you
straight away that little [ __ ] was
that. And this is exactly why I don't
come on here anymore with these little
self-reflectors. It's pointless. It's a
waste of time. It's the same 40-year-old
virgins waiting on their benefit money
coming on YouTube every day. And and
they've been doing it for years, bro.
They've been doing it so long. I even
know who's who.
I I literally know who is who, bro, cuz
they're so disabled that they give themselves away.
Anyways, now we're not typing over each
other. Let's go buy the evidence. Skin.
These people are on YouTube every day.
They can't get off it. They've been on
it for years. They've never been seen
with a woman. They've never been seen
with any money. It doesn't look good, does it?
[ __ ] they they've got a proper proper
addiction, bro. These people are
addicted. They're addicted to talking
about themselves every day.
They're literally addicted
to talking about themselves.
Yeah, I knew it was these disabled
bongos straight away.
>> Yeah, they're [ __ ] spastics. This why
I don't come on him anymore, bro. I
spotted that dusty show of mind off,
bro. As soon as you were saying the West is finished,
right, with a tick, I knew it was that
bongo straight. And this is what I'm
saying, bro. Like him that what's the
count again? Lewisville Sa. They're all
little rejects. That's is this is why
they spend their life on YouTube doing
this because they're rejected. They're
little rejects. They can't come off of
YouTube, bro. They ain't got no bird.
They got no family. They got no money.
They got nothing, bro. They talk about
themselves. They're life's biggest losers.
That's why they're on YouTube and they
can't get off it.
Literally, bro, they're life's [ __ ]
bully victims. They're rejects.
Absolute re rejected self projectors.
That's what they are, bro.
Yeah, I knew it was that bongo straight
away, bro. They ain't got a life.
They're disabled. I'm telling you, bro.
They're [ __ ] spastics. You know what
they do, bro? Yeah. They sit in, they
get that £300 a month universal credit
and as soon as they get that money, bro,
they just [ __ ] lose it and then it's
come on YouTube.
Like they they're they're [ __ ]
disabled. Like how many more years are
they going to keep coming on here call
trying to call you what they are
themselves every day? Like how many years
like how many years are they going to be
doing this for? It's so weird, isn't it?
These absolute bully victims. And guess
what, bro? They're just like the tenants
because if they saw anyone in real life,
they would, you know, the most cheekiest
thing about these little rejects on here
is that they would never say anything to
anyone's face. But like, you know them
tenants like the fe and that like that's
that's the most funniest thing about it.
Like they never say anything to anyone's face. Never.
Well, of course they would. They're too
scared to leave their [ __ ] house to [ __ ] bombs.
They sit there and wait, bro. It's bad, isn't it?
I feel sorry for them sat on YouTube
projecting negativity every day because
their lives are [ __ ] Cuz they failed.
They're in their 40s. They've got no
money. They've got no life. They're
ugly. This is all what it's because of, bro.
They've been bullied from a very young
age. I'm telling you. Yeah. Mhm. One second. Anyways,
everything everything applies to
themselves. That's why they want YouTube
every day. No money, no friends, Mr.
Lonely. That's all them. That's why
they're on YouTube every day. Not for
any other reason, bro. That's why
they're on YouTube every day behind fake
accounts. They hate the fact that
they're bully victims. Like, listen,
bro. Let me tell you something, bro.
They hate the fact that they're complete
and utter bully victims, but there's
nothing that they can do about it.
So, what they do is they come on YouTube
and take and and try to hate on other people.
Think about it. Who's been seen with
money? Me. Who's been seen with women?
Me. Who's been seen on YouTube every day
ain't got a life? Them. So, I mean, that's it.
Yeah. I don't find any of this community
funny. I think they're all spathic. I
think they need to get a life and get laid,
you know? They need to get a life and
get laid. They would never say anything
to anyone's face. How can they sit
online behind a keyboard for years and
years and years, doing this for years
and years and years? You know what I'm
saying? Because the thing is, like I was
saying, the funny thing is is they would
never say anything to anyone's face.
Like, not any of them. They're just
keyboard warriors. Like, I tell thinking
about this all the time.
Like that little Dusty Show, that little
puppet, that little bongo man. Do you
think that [ __ ] would ever say
anything to my face?
Bro, I'd slap him and I'd slap his mom,
bro. He's [ __ ] old mom. would never
say anything to anyone's face. Never.
They're all little [ __ ] keyboard
warriors, little [ __ ]
little spindle benefit self-reflectors.
Yeah, get off of YouTube. If I'm wrong,
If I'm wrong, get off of YouTube
if I'm wrong. Get off of YouTube with
all of your money. Stop coming on
YouTube, you little [ __ ] [ __ ]
Simple. This is why I said the same
thing to Monty. Yes, everyone's all of
this. So, get off of YouTube. But you
can't cuz it's your life. That's the
whole point. It is your life. You are
nothing without YouTube,
you know? Like, and I don't Do you know
what? I don't even really call them
repeaters because they're not actually
repeaters to be honest with you. It's
not even that they're repeaters. They're
just they're just describing what they
see in the mirror every day. Skint, bun,
[ __ ] no friends. It's everything that
they see in the mirror every day. They
they feel the need to type out what they
see. What you see is what they what you
get. And it's literally their own lives
that they are talking about skin on
YouTube year in year out. You know what?
You would have thought, right, that in
three years, one of these people would
have got a life by now. Oh, I was born over [ __ ]
I lost my job. You would have thought
that one of these bongo disabled people
would have actually got a life by now,
but they ain't got a life. That's the
funniest thing. They ain't got a life.
They literally have not got any life at all.
this bad, bro.
But I guess that's what happens when you
get bullied your whole life. That's what
happens when you get bullied your whole
life. Like, bro, these people probably
tried to go to the corner shop. Yeah.
For like a pint of milk. Yeah. Like the
smallest pint of milk because they're so
skinn they can't get anything else. And
they probably get bullied every time
they try to go to the corner shop, bro.
They probably get bullied. They probably
get dragged by their ear
every time they try to leave the house,
bro. They probably get [ __ ] bullied
by the whole street. Yeah.
But hey, I didn't I didn't No one
answered my question anyways.
Like, think of it, bro.
How much money do I have right now? Oh,
actually, you don't know how much money
I have right now. How would you know how
much money people have? You don't. You
don't know the exact amount of money
what people have, but you're coming on
YouTube claiming that they're skin. So,
you must be getting yourself confused
with other people.
Where the [ __ ] do they get this skin
thing from as well?
Think about it, bro. If they weren't
talking about themselves,
where do they get it from? Where the
[ __ ] do they get this whole your skin?
Where? Like where does it even come
from? Like I don't know where it even comes from.
I do. Actually, I do know where it comes
from. It comes from their own life.
It comes from their own life cuz they're scared.
[ __ ] you, Monty. You got me on here,
bro. Yeah. And now you don't even want
to like help me, bro. Like these little
[ __ ] mongos just self-projecting
every time. They ain't got a life.
They're all bully victims, you know?
[ __ ] hell, Monty. You're going to
You got me back on here. Now you won't
even [ __ ] come in and speak to me
about these little mongos on YouTube.
Bro, I come off of YouTube because of
these little mongos. And now you've got
me back on here. And now you won't even
join. Bro, I didn't want to come back on
this [ __ ] community. You know,
these little [ __ ] disabled little
bongos, you know, same self projectors.
And now you got me back on it. What the [ __ ] bro?
[ __ ] hell, buddy. Bro, the [ __ ] up
this [ __ ] [ __ ] whole place with these [ __ ] bongos.
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
>> PJ, you doing all this wrong now? Yeah,
don't react to these [ __ ] idiots.
Yeah, ignore them. Just ignore the
[ __ ] I'm not being funny, PJ. Yeah,
but you look at the state of them. Look
at them. Just look at them.
>> They are.
>> Yeah. Just look at them. They can sit
low and say they got this, they got
that, they got these. But it's [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] And that's only what
these are in this community. [ __ ]
All they want to do is cut out videos.
Cut out make you look like you're the
prick. But these are the pricks in this
community. There's no point entertaining
pricks. talk about something totally
different instead of bringing how much
of [ __ ] weirdos these people are.
>> No, you know, Monty, I said it, Monty, I
said it because they kept coming up my
channel and I had to block them. That's
why I just
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. They will do. They
will do. Just leave them to let let them
keep writing. Don't read their comments
and read all the good comments. [ __ ]
Claymore off. Don't block them. Just let
let them keep writing. Let them
embarrass theirelves for where they at.
>> Do you know what I mean?
>> I'm coming back on. I thought I'd come
up and tell you, "Stop reacting. Stop
bringing them up. Stop talking."
>> Think of it. Think of it, Monty. Yeah.
Think of it, Monty. Yeah. How can me and
you, how how could we be skinn? It's impossible.
>> I'm I'm not skin.
>> That's what I'm saying. But they say
that we are, but we can't be.
>> A person who calls another person skinn is skinn.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Yeah.
Funny. Yeah. I'm ignoring them now. I'm
ignoring them. You had a soft night
though, Monty. You had us up all night
worried about you.
>> I'm worried about Nat to be honest with you. Like
literally I'm I'm just worried about
now. I [ __ ] I've never I've never
felt like this for a woman in my entire
life. Never ever ever felt like this for
a woman in my life. You know what I used to
>> I used to laugh at a woman. I used to
[ __ ] laugh at him. >> Yeah.
>> But now I can't stop [ __ ] crying.
I've been crying for 4 days. Self armed
myself. [ __ ] try getting myself
[ __ ] sent into rehab.
>> Yeah, but she's going to get back with you.
>> I hope she does. I hope I hope she does
because I've planned a lot of [ __ ] out.
>> You should have just You should have You
should have just got off YouTube.
>> I'm looking. Yeah, I should have. I did.
I did. I I was already off YouTube. It
was my [ __ ] head. when we get in the
hotel when when Natalie kicked me out
the hotel room and that it just brought
it all back. Me getting kicked out of
Kay's house, getting kicked out of the
hotel in Blackpool. So I [ __ ] know
what if I'm getting kicked out of all
these places. [ __ ] it. I'm going to go
live and start talking about a hotel.
But I didn't mention the hotel what we
was in. I mentioned that we was in
Manchester. So I didn't give out no
information or whatever else like that. Yeah,
>> it's not even that. [ __ ] I was I woke
up I woke up and that [ __ ] I've been
waking up since 4 to 5. Yeah. And it's
been like it's been like I'm back in my
tent, do you know? When I'm back in my
tent, I'm [ __ ] waking up at half the
clock, you know? >> Yeah.
>> That's what it that's what it's been
like for these last [ __ ] couple of
days. Like I've been [ __ ] homeless, obviously.
>> Yeah. When I used to when I used to tell
you about my women problems, you used to laugh.
>> Yeah. Obviously me and obviously we're
not homeless. It was just a [ __ ] It's
just a speech. Just a new new word for
me, you know.
>> Yeah. But you used to laugh though. You
used to laugh in it.
>> Laugh at women.
>> No, but I used to tell you about like
about the why problems I used to have
with women and stuff. You used to laugh in it. >> Huh?
>> But I don't know. like having PJ
>> and when you first come on this
community you found it funny the first
time is it
>> to be honest with you I thought this
this was all banter at first I thought
it was all games and jokes I thought it
was just a little a little community who
sits there and call calls people and
that's how it stays but it's not it is
so [ __ ] toxic these people if I ever
meet these in real life please ask swear
to God how they be put underground I
swear to God, these talk to God they
don't get docked themselves. >> Yeah.
>> I swear to God, I'd be the first person
to knock on their [ __ ] door.
>> Same, bro. Same. I would as well 100%.
>> The house walk to the houses. They only
giving it out lies because you're behind
the [ __ ] computer. If it was real,
they'd be [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] The [ __ ]
[ __ ] PG and it will always be [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Yeah.
But I am not letting this community ruin
the rest of my life what I've got now. >> Yeah,
>> I can I can probably mend it with now.
Probably I can't mend it with now. It's
not up to me.
>> But don't you think it's all [ __ ] how
this is like the same website you can
watch Spongebob and like look how much
it affected you is it?
It's not that when I left PlayStation 3
PJ when I left PlayStation all the
trolling behind and you got me back into list.
I didn't want to troll. I I don't I
don't want to troll now. I don't want to
call anyone names.
>> Same website you can watch Spongebob on,
>> you know, cuz I'm not a troll PJ.
This is a trolling community. In fact,
it's not even a trolling community. It's
just full of [ __ ] weirdos to be
honest with you.
You know, like I [ __ ]
There's only one person who I've always
liked in this community and I [ __ ] it
up and that's Natalie. I've always liked
Natalie. I've always had a thing for
Natalie, but I didn't know that I
fancied Natalie this bad.
I [ __ ] love her, man. I love the
[ __ ] shoes she walks in, man.
And this is why I'm getting off YouTube
because I don't want to [ __ ] what I've
got left with Natalie up.
And I don't want you [ __ ] your short
PG ether entertaining these [ __ ]
clowns. He's left now. He's ended his
life as she pushed the wrong button. You
all [ __ ] clowns in this community
anyway. So I'm going to jump off now.
Anyways, you're all clowns. Literally
you you all know nothing because she
even give you anything.
Like you will not get nothing. Only what
you people know is that I [ __ ] gone
downhill big time. That's it. That's
only what you people know. But I'm a
strong [ __ ] lad.
I find my shoes again. I get back on my
feet. I'm sorting myself out. I'm
getting back on my medication. I'm
getting back on my tablets. I need my medication.
I need to start thinking more straight
instead of [ __ ] doing what I'm doing
on YouTube. I need to start using my [ __ ] nogy
because I am a brainy bastard. I'm not
exactly what you call me, a [ __ ] I'm
actually actually a brainy brainy
bastard in in real life. This is all
[ __ ] All all make believe [ __ ]
But you make it real
and I'm done. I'm I'm just completely done. So,
and you people will be always on
YouTube. You people will always be stuck
on YouTube with no live, no nothing, no
[ __ ] all. You people will just be sat
here wrinkling up like old farts you
already are with nothing going for
yourselves or nothing like that. You
already know I can get girlfriends,
peeps, plenty easy. But I don't want no
other bird. I don't want anyone else but
Natalie. But Natalie.
That's it. You know, I can go out right
now and just go and get myself a new
girlfriend this second, but I'm not. I
don't want a new girlfriend. I'm happy
with Natalie. And obviously, you all
think if Kaye clicks her fingers, I'm
going to go running back to that [ __ ]
ugly Shrek lookalike [ __ ] Obviously,
not people. I don't go near Shrek. I
don't fancy Shrek. I've never even
fancied Shrek. I'm calling Kayie Shrek,
by the way, peeps. I've never fancied
her. I've never had any feelings for
her. Yeah, I've got kids with with her.
I've got children with her. But she sits
there and calls someone a [ __ ] and
bullies a partner. I've been I've been
abused by that woman. I being completely
abused by that woman. She she says, "So,
she's not not abused. I'm not being
funny. But you kick the you keep [ __ ]
out your own kids." And that's not
[ __ ] You kick [ __ ] out your own two.
Oh yeah, even my dog you k [ __ ] out of.
And that's no [ __ ] And I'm not
sitting on YouTube entertaining weirdos
like Kayie and yourselves in this
community. Kayie, you can sit there and
call me a [ __ ] all you like. At least
I'm not a child abuser or a partner
abuser. You can sit there and that's all
innocent and all or whatever you [ __ ]
want. I can show people the scar on my
head when you smash the cup over my
head. I think half of the community know
about the cup either way. what you put
off my head. At the end of the day, I
will never ever go back with her abuser.
I have been abused,
you know. And this is what probably
makes me and Natalie strong together
is because we're both the same. It's
because we're both the [ __ ] same.
We both got the same kind of moms. Not
in that kind of way, obviously. You know,
my mom would never ever choke me under
the [ __ ] bus like Natalie did, but in
the same kind of way. Like,
my mom's been through what Natalie's
mom's been through and [ __ ] Like, I'm
not talking about this either way. But
literally, me and Natalie are more like
than what anyone thinks. Like, this is why
I probably got feelings for Natalie. And because
me and Natalie, we're suited. We are a
couple. We are suited.
And a lot of you already know that me
and Natalie are proper suited. That me
and Natalie do make a perfect good good
couple. We do. It's just that I'm just a [ __ ] And
I don't really mean to be a [ __ ]
I don't mean to be. is just
like this is why I need to get back on
my medication because I need to start
using my brain more instead of letting
my brain rule me.
So, I need to do a lot for Natalie now.
I need to put my [ __ ] feet under the
table and say, "Listen, I'm a man. I'm
not a child. I'm a man." And I need to
start acting like a man instead of
sitting on YouTube all my life calling
people I don't know. That's play
pathetic to tell you the truth. That's
[ __ ] getting a bit It's childish. Too
childish on my behalf to be honest with
you. So if you if you people think it is
so clever clapping your hands, calling
people out, calling people mongos,
calling people whatever, whatever,
whatever, whatever. Calling people
pedophiles when you even got proper
proof on people.
Like literally proper ass proof. You
don't have [ __ ] on me. You don't have
[ __ ] on anyone. What? You can bring up
the teen dating app. He can bring up Pat
Most kids. I don't give a [ __ ] about any
of that. Never went on him. Posters
kids. I don't give a [ __ ] what I said
about them. He's been going around
putting pictures up of children up. Not
bringing that subject or people way.
Let's get off that subject. At the end
of the day, you're all weirdos and I'm
completely done. Yeah.
I [ __ ] my life up being in this
community and I am not [ __ ] up anymore.
I've already lost my children through
this community. I've already lost one
relationship. Losing another
relationship through this. Am I [ __ ]
losing anything else? I've lost too much
in this community. And if you all think
it's funny and clever, then then you go
ahead and be childish. Just like the
pricks is that the end of the day, you
people s on YouTube say you got this,
you got that, you got this. So why the
[ __ ] are you not at work? Why the [ __ ]
are you calling everybody skin [ __ ]
mongos and virgins every day? You people
talk about yourselves daily. [ __ ]
daily. And then you sit there learn and
then you judge other people. Why don't
you people jump on camera, switch your
camera on, show your face. I've seen
most of you and most of you are [ __ ]
ugly, ugly, ugly, ugly bastards. Can't
say that because you you know you are.
And this is why you people do what you
do to me, to PJ, to people who are 10
times better. And you people
listen, you haven't trolled me. You
haven't [ __ ] ruined me. I've ruined
myself. You've not done that. I've done that myself
for not using my brain. So now I'm going
to start using my brain. PJ, stop asking
me to come up on a panel. I just quit
YouTube. PJ just get off it like you
already. I already asked you to go live
so for that that video for Natalie to
see that video because I haven't give
these people nothing. No nothing.
So if I give you people anything about
Natalie or myself, can you all explain
what I give you to use about me and
Natalie like that day at the hotel? What
did I say?
What did I give you about me and
Natalie? does the hotel that that Nat
kicked me out the hotel. That's it.
What else was I talking about? I was
talking about a dead bird saying that I
was talking about um obviously Natalie
were talking about Natalie about kicking
me out the hotel.
Um obviously saying that we was in Manchester
saying that only why she kicked me out
is cuz I woke her up. Um, you know,
obviously I don't blame her. I don't
blame her why she kicked me out to be
honest with you, you know, but I should
have used my noggin and not went live.
But I know everything I said that day
and I know everything I said. This is
what what I said. Yeah, this is what I
Went live, mentioned about the hotel.
Nat kicking me out again. Um, then they
started mentioning about the dead bird,
what what was on the floor. Then then
what was it?
Then then I mentioned that I couldn't
sleep. I'm waking up at daplock in the
morning like 4 to 5:00 in the morning
like I was back in the tent back when I
was homeless at that time. When I was
homeless and I was waking up at that
time I started waking up and and that's
only what I said. That's only what I
said. I didn't say anything else. I
didn't say anything about Natalie or
nothing. I just said that that Natalie
kicked me out of the hotel and started
saying that I want I should have stayed up [ __ ]
WhatsApp up with with Diesel and all
that. Look, I shouldn't have said any of
that. I shouldn't have said that. At the
end of the day, N has been there for me
and I need to be there for her.
Like literally, I need to be there for
her. I'm not a bad man. I'm a [ __ ]
I make I make the wrong choices like you
know people do. Like now I'm making the
wrong choice by being on here by talking
to now on here. This is the wrong choice
what I'm doing now. So don't think I
don't know that because I do. I'm just
explaining to myself and to you people
what the [ __ ] are you people doing on
YouTube? If you people say you got a
life, what you doing on YouTube?
What are you really all doing on YouTube?
That's none of your business to be
honest with you. That's none of your
business. And this is what's happening
from now on. People, you're not getting [ __ ]
I done what I did is because I was
hurting. I'm still hurting now.
I'm still hurting now. Yeah. I've never
felt like this for a woman in my entire life.
Never. I didn't even do [ __ ] Kaye. I
laughed every time she kicked me out.
Obviously, I sat there in bed and bleed,
please, please, please, please.
I can put videos up now where I'm proper
in tears. Proper in tears. Tears rolling
down me eyes and everything. I can put
all them videos up, but I'm not doing.
Yeah, people, I cried off in that. Yes,
people. I'm still kind of crying off in Natalie,
you know. And that's love. And that's
what love is.
When people say, "Do you know what love
is?" Yeah. It's when you cry over a
woman. When you feel things for a woman
inside and it hurts and
you just want to sort yourself out,
but at the end of the day,
I've treated that woman good, very good,
but I've also treated her like [ __ ] by
going on wife,
you know, but she's also, you know, I'm
not giving [ __ ] Anyway, evil. Well, I'm
not giving [ __ ] But she's a good woman.
She's a [ __ ] fantastic woman.
But you told us, bro. told you what what
what what have I told you? Like I would
like like to know. Obviously, I'm noting
starting, but I would like to know what
I exactly told you.
that literally I would like to know that.
You know what I mean? I've quit weed
now. I don't even smoke weed anymore,
peeps. I quit weed yesterday. Well, no.
I think it was three days ago when it
all this happened. I t a full house of
weed down the toilet.
I done can't be asked anymore with weed.
I want to sort myself out. I want to
sort my head out and be the perfect man for Natalie.
I don't want to keep doing this and
being a prick and
calling people and [ __ ]
trying to make people feel small or
trying to put people as things what they
know. I'm not that person. I would never
do that that to anybody.
So, I don't know why I'm doing it now.
I'm not a troll. I'm just a normal
[ __ ] regular [ __ ] guy trying to
get sort his [ __ ] life out because I
do need to sort my life out. Like
literally sort out back how I used to be before
I joined YouTube. Before I joined
YouTube, he had a [ __ ] straight on a
[ __ ] straight arrow. I was never
calling no one, never trolling. I never
felt down. I was always happy, [ __ ]
always joying life until I come on
[ __ ] lock down and I come into this
community on YouTube.
I'm happy because I met a lovely woman,
Natalie. I met Natalie, man. She's got
me She [ __ ] got me some shorts and
t-shirts and all that. Look, I've got
the shorts on now,
you know. I've got her shorts on. I've
even she even got me le peeps.
She even got me start
that here now even got me le
it's like a panther or something you
know she got me these shorts one what
I've got on she got me these shorts for
what I've got on she got me like three p
she's even got me lad this coat
she even got me lad this co it's not you go boss I've decided
You know, I'm going to let Natalie choose
now. Literally, the best thing for me to
do is anyway, is get off YouTube
is just to get off YouTube and PJ do the
same. Just get off YouTube.
To be honest with you, I'm not bother
Natalie doesn't love me or not. Yeah,
that's up to Natalie if she loves me or
not. That's not exactly up to me now, is
it? You know, but I'm not bothered if
she does or doesn't. I'm sick of crying,
but I do love N.
If Natalie did have any feelings or
whatever for me, then then, you know,
but I'm not getting involved with this
anymore. Anyway, so I'm going to jump
off now. Anyways, PJ, I'm jumping off.
Stop asking me to come up now, PJ. Yeah, I'm done.
Done with these like sad. I got no life.
I'm done. Dusted.
See you later.
Yeah, sorry about that, bro.
Had to uh I was I went to the shop.
Oh, smuggling the tire and self
projecting again. I'm going to do what
Monty man says. Just ignore the little self projectors.
Yeah, just ignore the little self-reflectors
that tell people to get jobs and stuff.
Yeah, just ignore them now.
You think that's so mad though? Like
greeny that money man could have got
sectioned over the same website you can
watch Cyp. That's scary, bro. the same
website you can watch the Simpsons and
Cip on. It's very worrying, isn't it?
Yeah, we need to like ignore these
self-reflectors now like Newville
Slugger and um show Biz. They're just
fives. Don't give them no attention. Let
them be sat on YouTube their whole life.
It's all they have. Bless them. Same
website you can watch Sippy on. That's
kind of scary. Grievously, I don't think
this is a website we we should be on.
And I always said it from day one
someone's going to get hurt or sectioned.
Yeah. I just keep thinking about that USA now
because of this Monty thing with
Natalie. It's just it just keeps
reminding me of USA. Nommy
didn't care about me. My mommy just abandoned me.
She literally just abandoned me.
That's so cruel to abandon your
something that you gave birth to, you
know. Horrible. Horrible.
Monty needs to get off YouTube, don't
he, Grezy? He needs to get off of YouTube.
Yeah, he needs to get off of YouTube. Definitely.
Definitely needs to get off YouTube. Franklin.
Franklin, stop sticking up your middle finger.
He's sticking up his middle finger. Franklin,
stop it, Frankie. Bless.
Bless you. That's what I was saying to
Monty last night. Bless you in life. Bless you.
The less young I
did. My mommy abandon me. Greasy.
Probably she doesn't apologize. She's
such a [ __ ] She's such an entitled
[ __ ] And you say easy, bro.
She should say sorry to me.
She should say sorry to me. What do you think, Grezy?
She should say sorry.
Do you think she should grieve? Say sorry. Bless you.
Bless you. Bless you. Bless you.
Come on, Franklin. Get out of the car.
Oh, Franklin died.
Franklin died. He's dead now.
Frank's dead died.
>> Yeah, I told that girl tell it about
herself, Greasy. I told her go [ __ ]
herself, bro. Yeah, sitt
Yeah. One step. Jesus Christ. [ __ ]
So, how much have you put on your bets
then, Steven Howard, for tomorrow?
Why do I keep going? I I wasn't going
off. I went to the shop. I I run out of
milk. Grezy, I run out of milk.
It's a shame USA Izzy wasn't here cuz
then we could just use her boobs or milk,
but she's not. So, I had to go to the shop.
Yeah. So, I had to go shop.
So, we don't have Yeah.
How much are you going to spend on the
football every week?
How much are you going to put on the
football every week? Like 100.
I hope this bet wins, bro. I could do
with an extra [ __ ] £300.
Again, I don't need it, but uh who who's
going to turn down the three 285, bro? You know,
I might do this one then do one more
then just give up with him. Yeah.
You doing a football bet this week,
Grezy? You should do a football bet with
the Bros. I'll go live Saturday. We can
all watch the scores come in and we can
all laugh at each other lose.
What a lovely site.
That is a lovely site. E
yeah, I don't really bet. I hate
betting. I hate gambling. I'm only doing
it because of like I said,
there's not really any ways at the minute. So
to make money. There we go.
We can all laugh at each other lose
and feel better about our crap lives. Ah,
me, Greavvesy, USA, Izzy, King in the
casino, all holding hands playing roulette.
Ah, what a lovely site.
Oh, that would be a lovely sight. No,
all holding hands together.
I think Greavvesy trolls me, you know. I
think deep down like Greavves is a troll.
Grezy, you troll me.
You told me, don't Huh?
Why are you such a troll, Grezy? I
thought we were mates.
I've been watching that OAB gambling channel recently.
Yeah, you're a nasty troll. You are
Did you like USA Izzy's boobs?
Did you like them?
They were really fun to play with.
Did you like them, Greasy?
You need to watch out for this Joe guy.
This Joe F's a troll.
This Joe F guy is a [ __ ] troll, bro.
Yeah, this Joe F is a troll, bro. He's a
He's a proper troll.
Yeah, that Joe's a troll, isn't he? Um, Grezy.
No, he definitely is a troll, bro. He
definitely is a troll.
He's a troll. That's your
So, Greg, did you like USA's boobs?
Did you like them? Wow.
Going on holiday to Miami in search for your mama.
Can't believe she's gone all the way there.
And there was stinky.
What the hell, Gizzy? How can they be stinky?
Well, cuz she's fat.
What? Because she's fatty. Yeah.
Yeah. Miami is quite far from Boston, bro. Jesus.
Bless you, Greavvesy. Greavves got no
goals in life.
He's got no goals whatsoever.
You should make some goals. Greavvesy.
Why don't you just Oh, you can't do that
because all I was going to say you
should go to different places to see
what McDonald's is the best, but all the
McDonald's in England tastes the same to
be honest. All the McDonald's taste the
same. McDonald's is McDonald's in it.
God bless you, Grezy.
God bless you.
I'm getting old, me. I'm getting [ __ ] old, man.
really getting old.
We'll be [ __ ] Virgin boy by his age
before we know it. Gre. Yeah, man.
I can't believe Monty.
Mony's a cool [ __ ]
I agree with you. I just want to come on
YouTube one day bro and not see these
people on here. So then I can say, "Oh,
they're not skin. They're not talking
about themselves." But if every time I
come on here and they're on here, then
they must be skin. It's like what man
says, someone that's that call someone
skin must be skin.
It's funny the way money says it. Yeah.
Here's the truth.
These people asking
these people asking
do you think LJ a skin um Steven Howard
definitely he is definitely skin he
didn't make no [ __ ] £500 from YouTube
that's his benefit money
bro that is literally his benefit money
is skinting skintlin
Yeah, he's skin.
He's [ __ ] skinned, mate.
I'm going to go and play some fishing
frenzy. £150 versus fish and frenzy.
Grezy, is that okay with you, boss?
I have to run it by Grezy first.
If he says no, then I can't do it.
He says if he gives me the green light
then I can
nah my [ __ ] Oh, you're a bad influence.
Grievy. You were supposed to say no.
I'm [ __ ] putting [ __ ] I might [ __ ]
putting 150 on [ __ ] that [ __ ]
I'd rather go out drinking and spend
[ __ ] 80 quid.
You're a bad influence. You greasy boss.
Is is uh Yeah, he is. I was worried
about him last night.
I wonder if Virgin Boy posted anything about it. Nah
[ __ ] virgin mall.
Anyways, just counting a few thousand quid.
Oh, bro, this virgin legs is is is
[ __ ] You're counting a few thousand quid.
Why does he keep going on like he's got
money when he literally has nothing?
I just read that. A few thousand quid.
Who the [ __ ] turns a few thousand quid
into euros when they're going to Amsterdam?
You know what I think he does, Stephen Hour? Yeah.
I think he I don't want to sound nasty.
Yeah. I think he sucks his dad's dick.
And every single time he sucks his dad's
dick, his dad gives him some money to
like show on YouTube.
Yeah, that's what I think he does. I
think his his dad gives him money to
suck his dick. That's what I think, bro.
That's why he thinks he's lost his
virginity. No, that doesn't count, mate.
That doesn't count. That don't count.
He's definitely a [ __ ] fantasist. He
ain't got no few thousand quid, bro.
He's [ __ ] skinn as [ __ ] just like LJ skin.
What do you think, George?
I don't know why they have to lie on
here and pretend.
I tell everyone what I have. I tell
everyone what I get.
Don't know why people have to lie on here.
You just don't get me.
I don't get it.
Yeah. I've got about 2K and I get £,100
a month. I don't need to lie about
anything, bro. Yeah.
Virgin boy don't have a couple of thousand pound.
He's [ __ ] skinning skin. Flint.
Do you gamble, George?
I don't really gamble anymore, but I've
got a football bet for Saturday.
I just hope it [ __ ] wins.
I just hope it wins to be honest, bro.
I could do with that 280 £300. I could
do with it, mate. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't really do it anymore, bro.
I gambled on roulette a few days ago.
First time like two months. Yeah.
And it's only to make some extra money
at the minute, George, because I'm I
can't I'm struggling to find a number to
make to make extra cash at the minute.
So, it's it's quite difficult.
I used to like doing the Uber, man. It
was quite fun.
But I don't really like gambling, bro.
like you know [ __ ]
Yeah, it should be, mate. I hope
hopefully that [ __ ] bet wins.
How much is that £300? That's like two
nights out, isn't it? Two or three nights out.
Well, how much do you spend on a night out? Maybe £80.
Maybe spend 80,
80, maybe 90, 100, 120.
Two nights out, maybe. Who knows? Two, three, whatever.
Quite a few in it.
You can get quite a few drinks with it.
I might just go on a night out and just
get an escort, bro. With the money, if I win,
probably just get
I don't know how people spend 150. I
spend about 80 90 I just drink beer.
I normally just [ __ ] spend like 80 90. Yeah,
I got 30 numbers last week, George. I
got no date this week. Shocker, isn't
it? I'm going Thailand in uh in November.
Yeah, I booked the flights to go Thailand 770.
The dating game is dead in this country
now because of social media. So yeah,
I should have went [ __ ]
[ __ ] like years ago, bro.
Like Well, no, not really, cuz I still
had hope I was going to meet someone here.
It's ridiculous here, George. You try to
chop up a bird and they just say they
got boyfriends, just not interested
and it never ever ends. It's just the
same old. That's why I I I decided to
like make a change, lad.
They all stuck up.
Um, American, English stuck up [ __ ] So,
and Canadians as well. They're all the
same. They're all the same. Western
eyes. No good.
Yeah, I didn't go out last week. Didn't
go out this week, bro, either. Just
can't be asked with it, bro.
It's always I have a boyfriend. It's
[ __ ] horrible, bro. It's [ __ ] depressing.
I take it you go out a lot, don't you? Yeah.
And I said about the football bet
winning, but I don't see, you know, you
like I said, bro, you get to a point
where you think like
there is actually no point even going
out anymore in this country. Like you
actually get to that point.
Maybe it's because I've tried more than
anyone in the world. But I don't see
like it's good that this house stopped
when I was 27 cuz I wasn't going out as
much anyway. So it's not like I'm
missing anything being on a lower income now
to be it doesn't feel like much has changed because
like I said I was living the life for 3
4 years anyways
when I was going out more. Now I just
I'm not even going to go out as much now
anyways. I just don't see the point in
this country and even going out
drinking and that I don't see the point
in it, bro. Maybe I'm getting older.
You can't even pull. You can't even get
laid. You can't even get a girlfriend.
[ __ ] pointless. What's the [ __ ]
point of it, bro?
Think about that, George. 13 numbers I
got um not last week, the week before,
not even a single date this week, not
even one single date with a woman. That
opened up my eyes, bro.
I was like, "Yeah, Thailand. Bye." Adios, [ __ ]
But then I was thinking of maybe going
to Miami with some last money I had
left. But then I realized after watching
that guy's video in America that it's
even worse there. Not even no point in going there. So
yeah, it's bad, bro. Very bad.
Do you think I'll win this? Do you
reckon I'll win a football bet this season?
I [ __ ] hope. I [ __ ] do, mate.
I'm going to put I think I'm going to
end up put like 150 on two teams, bro.
Like not I don't know.
Not this week or next week, but maybe
like a couple of weeks I might just put
like 150 on two teams.
Should get like six on the back. [ __ ]
I don't know. Uh,
yo, I'm only gambling because I can't
find a thingy right now. You still doing them fobies,
bro? You still playing them [ __ ] FBT?
I haven't played one of them in ages. Frankie, thank
you're going to end up homeless one day.
You are. You can't. You're going to end
up homeless one day.
You're going to end up homeless.
You really are going to end up homeless
one day, mate.
I think I grew out the gambling, bro.
You know what I think it is with me?
Yeah. I think this is going to sound mad
cuz I'm a lot younger than you people,
but I feel like I've done it more than
anyone, bro. Like, I'm just bored of it.
Done the gambling, done the drinking,
done the women. I think you just get
bored of it, which the only thing that
was left to do was go on holiday.
I think I've done it so much. Like the
gambling, the I'm bored of the drinking
now and going out anyways. I where I've
done it so much. I think I'm just bored of it.
Like that's what it is. I just don't
like the stress of the gambling. That's
what I don't like about it.
You never know if you're going to win,
lose, then you have to lose. I just
don't like the stress of it.
That's the main reason I don't [ __ ] with
it anymore. Oh, [ __ ]
Like, say you win. Okay, you win. Yeah.
Say you won, but then the next day you
can go skin.
So, it's like it just doesn't make
sense. One day you can win, okay, but
then the next day you go skin
or have a lot less money. It's just not
worth it. It's just to me it's just not
So, that's why I don't do that [ __ ] anymore, mate.
So, even when you're talking about it,
it doesn't even tempt me anymore.
I'm just going to get some escorts. With
that money, I win. I think if I win,
just going to get some escorts and drinks.
Don't know what I'm doing.
Yeah, I done I done my football bet. I
think I done it on Tuesday. Didn't play
the machines. Weren't tempted to play
It doesn't even like tempt me. The
stories don't even tempt me anymore.
No, it hasn't. No, it hasn't. Because I
was getting 3K a month, even over at
some point. So, not really cuz I've also
lost a lot of money from gambling as well.
No, cuz I've I've I've always I've also
lost money gambling as well.
It doesn't matter if you could afford to
lose it. I hate losing just like L J. I
hate losing well on on the machines. But
it's not the best times cuz I also lost
a lot of money as well.
And it's not even that to be honest with
you. If I could get into casinos again,
I probably would still gamble to be
honest. If I could get into casinos again,
maybe I would. Maybe I would. But I
don't know, man. I doubt it. But you
can't even play a fair game of roulette.
You can't uh you can't even play a fair
game of roulette anymore. So, it's all
rigged online. I was playing it the
other day. So,
like watching people lose. Yeah.
I like watching LJ lose because he's a loser.
You know that time I won £75 off of a
pound. Um Joe, I wish I had £100 on it.
I never thought them six teams was going
to come in. Oh, let me just put one
pound on six teams and they all come in
as well. £75 off of a pound. I think
that was my first football bet I won.
I wish I had like [ __ ] 50 quid on it, bro.
Oh, I wish I had more on it.
But even to be fair, even like
20 pound on it back then when you're 19
like almost £1,500. Oh,
I hate 16.
But you can't even play a fair game of brunette anymore.
online. It's all rigged.
Online is rigged, isn't it, Joe? So,
£75 I won off of a pound. [ __ ] me.
Imagine having 50 quid on that
16. They all won.
That was insane, bro.
£75 off of a pound. Do you This was
before I was on YouTube, I think.
You always wish you had more in it
though. That's the thing.
Ant-Man won a lucky
31 with £11. He won4 grand.
Yeah, online is definitely rigged
though. Definitely rigged.
It is rigged cuz you cover half the ball
then you miss like three, four times in
a row. It is rigged. Definitely rigged.
How does seven neighbors get all that money?
money, bro? Jeez.
He's a rich [ __ ]
He's a rich boy.
I could go to a casino, but I'd probably
have to go to Nottingham to be fair, but
then it's trying to get the money out
and then they ask for ID and all of this [ __ ]
That's what happened. I can get into one
in Nottingham probably. There's like a
private one, but imagine going all the
way to Nottingham to gamble. That's
something Timmy would do.
That's something Timmy would do, isn't it?
Yeah, I remember winning that four
grand, bro. I've got the buddy. I still
got the money, bro. The muddy picture. Oh, [ __ ]
Look at that, bro. Imagine waking up to that. Jesus.
Imagine waking up to that. [ __ ] hell.
That was mad, bro. On a nice Wednesday
night, eh? Nice Wednesday night.
Those were the good days, matey. Yeah, matey.
It's fun days, good days, eh?
They were the good times, bro.
I was the first one to get them not I
was the first one to get them um
new 50 notes
with the man on it. I was the first one.
That was sick, bro.
Yeah, but all good things come to an
end, in it, matey.
Don't they matey? That just reminds me
of that 19year-old. I always used to
meet the 19year-old. I wonder why she
wanted to meet so much. Hey, I wonder
why she wanted to meet so much.
I wonder why.
I wonder [ __ ] why.
That's the day I was supposed to go
America the first time as well.
She was like, "Oh, don't go. Don't go. Don't go."
That [ __ ] would have [ __ ] lod you,
mate. She would have [ __ ] loded you.
She would have loded you, mate. Yeah.
Yeah. There were good times, man. Good times.
I'm still better off than most than a
lot of people though.
But it's just [ __ ] in it.
I knew was getting 3k a month as well.
But it's not bad though. It's not bad
being back to reality at 27.
The only thing we're doing now is
leaving. So I mean Yeah.
Just good thing we're not 23 again. 24
again, is it?
I had like 5.7 in cash actually in the end.
That can never happen again, man.
It can never happen again cuz I can't
get in the casinos.
So therefore, it can never happen again,
can it? Nope. No,
but it was there to be spent. And to be
fair, like I said, I wouldn't be doing
it anymore anyways, going out every week
cuz I've been there, done it, worn the
t-shirt, which is how I know about how
nothing will change in this country when
it comes to women. Like
that's how I knew, you know,
cuz obviously they're going out and [ __ ]
I was [ __ ] buying escorts, [ __ ] garments, [ __ ]
[ __ ] everything, bro.
Garments, escorts, the lot.
The [ __ ] lot, bro.
The lot, matey.
Think I went to Wales again, matey. Yes, matey.
See, I can't even get tempted on the
online roulette anymore cuz you can't
even hit big on it. It's just next door.
Next door, next door. It's pointless.
So yeah, if I went to Nottingham,
they'll be like, "Oh yeah, have you got
anything with your name on it?" And then
they're going to find a way to not pay
you out. And
unless you can [ __ ] find Unless them
500 machines are working.
Unless them£500 machines are working,
then maybe we can. But if they're not
working, I'm not doing it.
Cuz I'm not willing money to not be paid
out. Then I'll just smash the whole
casino up. So it's like it's pointless.
It's called uh what's it called? All
casino. I went there with Ant-Man. So if
the 500 machines are working, you could
do it. But
if not, then don't know.
Every casino matey. Every casino matey.
So obviously if the machines Yeah.
Then then I can
then maybe I'll take a trip to
Nottingham at some point.
Obviously I'll go for a drink there as
well. Like I've been there for ages.
Could do that. But
it's what if they don't pay you out? Um,
that's the thing.
Have you ever been Nottingham Casino,
Joe? There's one in Nottingham. It's
like a private casino.
Yeah, I would give it a while.
But then what if they don't pay you out?
I remember when I went with Ant-Man, I
think I was 200 in. And it was there for
like an hour and in the end I got it to
350 and they were trying so hard not to
give that money and it was only 150
profit and I thought, "Oh, 150 is
enough. It'll pay for some drinks and a
hotel and shit." Yeah, I remember that.
It was funny. Yeah.
Time I got a [ __ ] Oh,
what a lovely sight.
So, but then the thing is it's like they
were saying, "Oh, have you got anything
with your name on it?" Nah, bro.
That's what happens, bro.
Yeah, that was from last year. I won four grand.
I love that Ronald Pump guy, bro. He's a legend.
He said, "You've got more money than
them and you're better looking than them
and it kills them." He wasn't wrong back
then, was he, Joe? He wasn't wrong back
then. What he means by better life is
you're going out [ __ ] banging women,
going on dates. You got more money and
it kills them. It is true though.
Of course it kills them, bro. Why do you
think they've been stalking you for [ __ ]
Yeah, you can't win anything, bro. This
was last year.
This was last year, Mark.
This was like last year, mate.
Oh, [ __ ] Yeah, I put 150 in the
roulette. I took out 4K. I hit a
multiplier. Yeah, it is hard to win nowadays.
Might try Nottingham, bro.
Maybe I'll go Nottingham today, Joe.
There's a casino in Nottingham,
but it's getting paid out. That's the problem.
It's getting paid out.
Yeah, I don't really gamble anymore anyways, Mark.
On one condition, am I going to get the
I've got a boyfriend, Joe? You know,
I don't want to hear boyfriend though. Yeah, boyfriend.
They've all got boyfriends. I don't want
to hear that [ __ ] if I go there. I don't
want to hear [ __ ] stuck up women.
Yeah, but no, it depends. Like, if
there's if there's like a cash out
machine, I can do it.
If there's not a cash out machine, I
can't do it.
cuz obviously they're going to ask me
to [ __ ] prove who I am and [ __ ]
So, and then obviously when they find
out who I am, they're not going to pay me.
So, yeah, you can't win nowadays, bro.
Online roulette rigged. The casinos are
dodgy trying to pay people.
Yeah, it's [ __ ]
I don't know, bro.
I didn't know.
Have you ever been to a Manchester
casino, Joe? I've always wanted to go to
the Manchester casinos, but they would
never let me in.
Yeah, they'd never let me in.
Nah, man. Online's rigged.
Nah. Oh, by the way, Joe, that uh that
USA Izzy is in Miami now. She moved to Miami.
I was thinking of [ __ ] um going Miami
at some point actually.
Yeah, I was actually thinking of going
to Miami, bro. Not like soon, but like
months away and that before I booked the
Thailand thing. I was actually thinking
of going on my birthday before I even
knew that. Remember we spoke about it before?
Oh, bless you then.
Yeah, there's only one in Newcastle.
It's the Aspers.
Yeah, online's online's rigged, isn't it, George? George George.
Yeah, I told that girl turning about
herself, Joe. She was trying to be funny
about the house and [ __ ] I told her
about herself. She shut up.
Yeah. She was trying to be a [ __ ] Nah, bro.
All as [ __ ] Oh man.
Yeah, I told her about herself, bro. And
and the other and the other tenants. Yeah.
So, you think I was bad, Joe? Money man
was cutting himself over a woman.
Oh, she was basically trying to say
about how um yeah, like you need to give
me 150. And bear in mind, she wasn't
staying in that room for 4 months. You
weren't even in the country. I said,
"Hold on a minute, right? You weren't
even staying in that room you was paying
for. You're not even in the country. I'm
not giving you nothing." And then she
was trying to say like, she's trying to
be funny and that. And I said, "Oh, all
the other tenants can suck my dick." She
said, "No one wants to suck your dick."
I said, "Listen." Yeah. You remember
that girl in that house that's 100 times
better looking than you? She sucked my
dick several times. Yeah. While she was
in that house and saying like you you're
saying you're going to get your ex. Get
your ex, man. No one's scared of your ex.
No one's scared of you or your ex. You
wasn't even in the country. You're still
not in the country. So,
I said, "Let's start talking about
things that don't make sense. You're
paying for a room that you're not even staying in.
Like when everyone was going to end up
homeless, you weren't even in this
situation cuz you're not even [ __ ] here.
Yeah. I sent them back and then I told
them all that they're dirty, stinky
little thiefs and that. I told them all
about themselves. Only there's only two
of them that I don't have a problem
with. I said, "Obviously, I don't have a
problem with you and that, but I had to
say about them three obviously
out of the six because Yeah, man. They
were pissing me off in it. So yeah, madness.
I hate people, bro. I'm so glad they're
out of my hair now.
Really hate people. Me.
But yeah, she shut her mouth after that. Anyways,
cuz I said to her, "Stop being an opportunist."
Like, if you if she tried to come back
in the house and and and the locks had
been changed and she had just paid, right?
Then obviously I would have gave the
money back. Of course I would have gave
you money back and I was going to take
your stuff to put somewhere safe to give to you.
Like I I said to her as well, like
here's the thing, right? you're you're
not um what was I saying to her?
Um that and he was like, "Oh, so what?
You just going to have me keep paying?"
I was like, "Well, well, yeah. You're
not staying in a room. No one knows when
you're going to keep coming back. Of
course, I'm going to keep taking your
money." Who wouldn't do that? You're in
a different country. What am I going to
do? Say, "Oh, yeah. Um they're coming to
uh take the house. Can you come back
from whatever country you're in?" Nah.
What's the point in that? I'm just going
to take your stuff, store it somewhere
safe, and then when you come back, I'll
meet you with your stuff, just like I
was going to do anyways. Who Who is
going to do that? If someone's been if
someone's been gone for four or five
months and you're paying the rent
anyways, then we're going to keep it as
that. Like, it doesn't matter.
And obviously, if you paid and then you
come back like 3 4 days, then obviously
you'd get the money back. Of course.
Like, I'm not just going to take your
money, but like, you're an idiot, man.
You don't make sense. Who the [ __ ]
refurbishes a room? Yeah. [ __ ] off for
5 months and pays almost £400 a month.
You don't make sense. That's what I
said. You don't make sense.
I said, "Do you think I give a [ __ ]
about your 350,400 a month? I can get
money out right now."
What? No. And I said you was never
coming back. When was you going to come
back? You was never going to come back.
You're not the one homeless. They are.
So, I don't know why you're You got
people stealing your after shave and
[ __ ] [ __ ] off, man.
I said to them in a voice, I wish I
[ __ ] you all over. Like, I wish I
actually really [ __ ] them all over
now. I wish I never told them when they
were coming. And I wish I just took as
much as I could from them and [ __ ]
them over. I wish I did now, you know,
cuz you realize in this life, yeah, do I
thought I was doing the the normal
thing, right? Giving weeks and weeks notice
then they they act all weird
and then the problem I had is someone
stole my after shave and someone's and
someone told my business. So yeah.
So she it's not like she was ever going
to come back anytime soon.
You know what I'm saying? Because then
obviously I would have obviously gave
your money back
which she didn't pay. She didn't even
pay for the month. So she didn't even
pay. Talking like she was staying in the
room. She wasn't even staying in the
room. Who does that? Who who refurbishes
a room and pays almost £400 a month for
a room and doesn't stay in that room for
five months? That doesn't make no sense.
That don't know that does not make no
sense at all.
That doesn't make any sense, bro.
So yeah, she was trying to be like funny
about it and that it and yeah, and I was
like, "Oh, so you so you people want to
tell people's business and you want to
steal people's after shave. Why don't
you admit it?
But they can't admit it. They're little
[ __ ] That's what I'm saying. They're
all little [ __ ] [ __ ]
And then I had one trying to threaten
me. Yeah. Like was it a week ago?
I had one trying to threaten me a week
ago as well. I said, "Why don't you come
now? Why don't you come now?" That's
what I said to him. Yeah. And then he
shut up. [ __ ] [ __ ]
I'm so in glad. I am glad in ways that
they that they donate to the house. But
in ways I am glad
cuz I don't want to deal with them
again, bro. [ __ ] Hey, Notorious. I
got 30 numbers week before last. Not one
single date. I was supposed to go on a
date this Thursday and last Thursday.
Both mucked me around.
How you getting on? Hope you're killing
it. Hope you're out there killing it.
But everything's hard nowadays. It's
hard to get a job. It's hard to win
money. It's hard to make money. But
it is hard nowadays, matey.
Yeah, it was funny, isn't it?
And that guy with the half rent, I was
going to give him some money back. But
when my after shave started going
missing and no one admitted to it, then
I was like, I'm not giving you [ __ ] Simple.
Had to buy a new after shave. It cost me £72.
Yeah. Notorious, bro. I was watching um
this guy in America. He was doing loads
of approaches and he was getting the
same I've got a boyfriend. I've got a
boyfriend. You like it though? Is it Notorious?
I don't like it. Me. I think it's [ __ ] depressing.
Yeah. I was watching it. I have a
boyfriend. I have a boyfriend. It's
[ __ ] depressing, isn't it?
It's depressing watching it.
It's some black guy in America. Bro, I
had to stop watching it. It's annoying, isn't it?
I said to Antman, "You found it funny,
is it?" He said, "No, I didn't. It's depressing." Yeah.
They're all NPCs. They're non-playing characters. Yeah. So,
anyway, Thailand in November. Yay.
Yeah, I booked Thailand for November
770. It cost me Notorious £770. Yeah.
It's not going to change in this
country, is it? Yeah.
Yeah. That Ukrainian woman mugged me off though.
[ __ ] hate these [ __ ] I do, bro.
Was going for two weeks.
Ntorious, did you?
Ntorious, did you used to find it funny?
I have a boyfriend. I have a boyfriend.
I don't find it funny. Me?
No, I don't find it funny. Me?
Nah, you found it. You used to find it
funny, isn't it?
You find it funny, is it? It's not funny, bro.
Yeah, nice little bet, Joe. Nice little
win. £1,000 off 20 quid. I bet you wish
you had £200 on it.
That's the way it goes. You wish you had
more on it when you win.
bit hungry today.
I might get some grilled chicken from
somewhere. I'm not sure.
Going to be hard to save money now,
isn't it, Joe? I'm just a lot less. I
need to try and find something, bro, to
to to make money. What the [ __ ] I need help.
Maybe I'll gamble at some point again. I don't know.
Nah, I'm not gambling again.
Sorry, bro. I can't.
I can't afford to gamble.
How do you £1,000 with a 20 bet? [ __ ] hell, man.
Yeah, but I don't have money anymore,
bro, to to to be wasting on that [ __ ] you know?
Yeah, like 150 get bonus pays another
bookies. Yeah, you could do it.
But I just don't really want to get into
the whole gambling thing again.
And how much would you start with? Like 150?
I mean, yeah.
I don't know, bro.
It's quite risky. It's quite dangerous.
150 to like 2,000 would be good in it.
I can do it. How much do you want me to
start off with?
You put 150, you won't even get a [ __ ] bonus.
Yeah, there's a place in East London.
There's loads of loads of bookies. I can
go to them. Um, [Music]
no, you're not there to take away.
Yeah. So, what do you think, bro?
I'm asking you a question. Stop ignoring me.
even have takeaways anymore, Joe.
I can't even have [ __ ] takeaways
every day now. Oh no.
What's today? We
get a takeaway like every four days.
I'm scared of going broke. I don't want
to end up like [ __ ] nonslegs and
living like [ __ ] nonslegs and [ __ ]
Lord. I don't want to be skin like them.
You know what I'm saying?
No, I I can get a I can get a takeaway.
I can eat.
I can get a takeaway, but I just don't
want to waste money, you know?
I've got money. I just don't want to
waste it. Does that make sense, Greenly?
I'm looking at some meatballs today, I reckon.
Yeah, I get takeaway every 3, four days.
It tastes better when you don't have it
for a while. Have you noticed that
greasy? The longer you go without a
takeaway, the better it tastes.
Just like the longer you go without drinking. Um,
the better you the more you enjoy it. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, I had Peppy's grilled chicken.
That was very tasty.
I need to start to get some sort of job soon, bro. Really?
I can't be that virgin, boy. sound his
lanky ass all [ __ ] day.
I don't know how these people do it. Sit
sit around all day. Greasy.
I haven't had a [ __ ] in ages.
Can't be asked of it. No.
To be fair, there was days I I stayed in
for 6 weeks before.
Well, just to make some [ __ ]
money and just go to different places
now. That's mine.
That's my That's mine. Go gym. Try and
find somewhere way to make some money
and just [ __ ]
leave here as much as I can.
But yeah, I don't know.
But in the winter, last winter, I stayed
in for like 6 weeks. I didn't go out for
6 weeks, bro. 6 weeks. I didn't go out for
That's almost 2 months. That's impressive, man.
Yeah. I said to Greasy like, "You got no
goals. You're older than me. You haven't
even been anywhere.
You haven't even been anywhere.
Mine is to [ __ ] as many escorts as possible
and go to as many places as I can. Now, I think
Oh, my [ __ ] arms are hurting me, bro.
My back is [ __ ]
Grey's barely left where he lives. Bless him.
I've been all over the UK.
A bless you.
Yeah, at least you don't have distress
from these shitty women anymore.
[ __ ] evil bastards.
They never change.
Black Ops 2 time, I think.
Oh, [ __ ] So, how much do I need to
start with the bookie crawl then, Joe?
How much starting balance? 150.
No, I really I'm scared of wast I'm
scared now, bro.
I'm scared of wasting money.
I'm scared of wasting money and losing money.
It's It's too hard, bro, to uh
I mean, you could do £100.
I ain't doing 150, though.
100 pound is how many spins? 100 100
150 is too much in it. Yeah, 150 is too much matey.
What do you think, Grezy?
Too much, matey.
What? £100 and four bookies?
I'm not [ __ ] gambling for £100, you
[ __ ] idiot. I ain't gambling £400.
What the [ __ ]
You mean £100 and then go to four bookies?
No, I can't gamble [ __ ] £400, bro. be
mad. What the [ __ ] Nah.
Who the [ __ ] would do that, bro? £400.
Jesus Christ. [ __ ] that. Frankie.
No, I'm not doing it, bro. I don't want
to ever play that Frankie again.
You remember Frankie Greavesy? No. [ __ ] that
no no no no no no. Sorry, matey.
I can't be doing them things. I'll go to
Nottingham. I'll play the roulette in
Imagine that Greavves. You're going to
Nottingham for a quick gamble and then coming back.
Oh, what a lovely site. I tell you where
I could go and they'd never find me.
Paris. I could just go to Paris, go for
a gamble, go for an approach, go for a
go for a night out, and go for a gamble,
then come straight back to England.
That doesn't even seem like a bad idea.
You know, bro, that doesn't even seem
like a bad idea.
We've got to have casinos in Paris.
[ __ ] uh [ __ ] then go and [ __ ]
Belgium again. That doesn't even seem
like a bad idea. Go Paris,
do some approaches, get [ __ ]
go casino, and come back.
Yeah, I know they do. I'm not going
Amsterdam again, bro.
[ __ ] I ain't going there again.
I've already been there. Another place
Greavvesy hasn't been.
Yeah, but their casinos are weird. The
roulette works a lot different.
Hey, what have I told you about self projecting?
Just ignore these people. Let them
embarrass themselves like what Monty man said.
What do you think, Joe Paris?
be be a laugh, wouldn't it? No.
Nah, [ __ ] that. I went to the casino in
Belgium. I went to the casino in Amsterdam, too.
Imagine going all the way to France to
gamble. That's mad, is it? That's like
Timmy level, is it? Grezy.
Ah, bless you.
Is that right, Greavvesy? Bless you.
Ah, bless. Cuz obviously
cuz what if what if I win in Nottingham
and they and they try not to pay pay me, Joe?
And what if they don't pay me? So what
if they don't pay me? Then what?
Then I would be
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
Yeah. What if they don't pay me?
They won't pay me, matey.
Would they don't pay me, matey?
That must be that would be so fun. Yeah.
All right, say you was just traveling
around England, winning in casinos,
going drinking. That'd be [ __ ] fun as
[ __ ] is it? Imagine just going casinos,
winning, another city, drinking, winning.
Imagine that. That would be sick.
That' be really good, would it?
That would be a good life. Oh,
I need a better life at the minute, matey.
See Joe, the thing is you're actually
addicted to gambling.
You're addicted to gambling. You matey.
I'm not addicted matey. You're addicted
You're actually addicted matey.
You're addicted matey. Yes, matey.
My bones are aching, bro.
I think that's depression
where I've been lying down too long. [ __ ] knows
who's been messaging me.
No, it does. When I was working and
doing Uber, I didn't give a [ __ ] about gambling, bro.
It It will. It does.
I don't even get a buzz from it anymore
really, which is why I don't really do it.
Do you get takeaways often?
But you must be addicted cuz I ain't as
bad as you, bro. Like I said, it's
probably where I've done it so much.
where I've probably gambled so much and
drunk so much, it just bores me now, bro.
So, like even when I've lost the house,
I feel like
like the only reason I'll be honest with
you, man. Like I keep saying, you don't
believe me, lad.
I I'm only doing this football thing because of
there's literally no extra way to make
money now at the minute. That's the only
reason I bet on the football, bro. I
don't give a [ __ ] about gambling.
I got I went moms about gambling, bro. I
don't It doesn't You do it when you do
it so much the way I have, you just
realize that it's bad and you just get
bored of it. Like drinking, I probably
still will go out drinking, but just not
every week. Just when I when I want to, you know?
That's what happens when you when you go
three years without working and you've
done it so many times,
you know. But the only reason I probably
I might do it now is cuz I will actually
need extra money.
It doesn't seem like there's any other way. So,
I might put 150 on two teams next week.
Yeah, but them savings will go.
£2,000. I have Well, I have £2,000.
It will go. If I gamble, it will go. Simple. So,
if you got 2K, it will easy go. You
gamble, it's pointless.
And then if it goes, how am I going to
get it back?
I'd have to stay in for like a month or something.
You'd have to literally stay in for like
a month and then you'd be back to like 1,600
maybe. I'd have to live on like £50 a
week for like a month.
Well, you think two grand's going to
last forever if you if you keep dam
[ __ ] hell, man. Come on.
So yeah, 2K e Nope.
Not at all.
Oh, you got run over. So what? You think
2K is going to last forever?
Is that what you think?
Like I said, this football bet wins. I'm
going to go on a night out and then get an escort.
I'll probably go out. Not this week.
I'll probably go out next week.
Uh escort. Go out the week after
Then I'll be done for a month.
280 will be enough. Uh
well, it doesn't matter if it'll be
enough. It's it's extra money. So, after
the world to save,
yeah, well, I'm booking another holiday.
I might do the Miami thing when I come
back from Thailand. I might do the Miami thing.
So that there is a point because I'm
going I'm going to go Miami
which is to be fair is only like 1.3k.
Yeah. You see like even when you're
talking about wins and stuff it don't
even trigger me. This is that that's the
that's the concerning thing because you
know when people stop,
right? I don't know if you're trolling
or you're actually up, but it doesn't tr
it doesn't it doesn't trigger me.
How am I going to lose it, bro? And I
don't even gamble.
How can I lose it? How can I lose it?
How can I lose it, bro?
So obviously if the football bet wins,
like I said, I'll go out next week, get
my haircut next week, go out, escort,
week after, go out, escort, done. I
might even add a third day in there.
Then I can still save cuz I got extra
money. So like that's what it's come
down to now. So yeah, [ __ ] hoping it
does [ __ ] win.
But it's not though. But it isn't cuz I gambled 150
into Yeah, it's like £80
80 160 hecka. Yeah, it's still
even if I spend 350 on them like I will
still have 280 extra. So not much of my
own money would be spent.
I always get an escort after I go out drinking.
No, because I'm going when I get paid. So,
and I'm going for 2 weeks. So, yeah.
And I'm not saying I am because USA is
there. I was always talking about that
even before that.
I'm taking my bank. I'm taking my bank
card with me.
So the only thing you can do with money
is is holidays.
At my age now, I've got all the designer
clothes and stuff, so it's only really
holidays you can really you can really do.
I wish I could do Uber again. I'll be
doing Uber today, bro. Oh, I think I
could make about 120 today. [ __ ] sake.
So yeah, even if it winds tomorrow, I'm
not going out tomorrow.
I'm going out tomorrow. No way.
The detox ain't finished. So,
so yeah, Miami is about 800 to about 1.3
everything. Obviously, you got your
spend, you need spending money as well. So,
Oh, it's [ __ ] hard, isn't it? Trying
to save for things now, is it matey? Yes, matey.
You remember the little Uber, Joe?
Oh, Uber. I remember Uber.
Uber was quite good.
No, I'm going to do both.
Then I lose the football bet, don't I?
And then I'm fat.
What else is there?
Then I'll probably go out next week anyways.
Uh hopefully it doesn't, but it probably
will to be honest. Football bets are
hard to win.
I just like to think it will win because
it's not really a big chance, is it? Yeah,
I might just never approach again here.
I don't know. [ __ ] knows. I hope it does win, but
because it's not even like it's they're
not like really they're not unrealistic odds.
I might start putting more on the
football though. I might start putting
like 150 on two teams. I'll have nothing
to lose. I'm always going to be at
[ __ ] two grand by the time I get my money again.
I mean, you could do that because by the
time you keep getting your money every
month, you're just going to be back at
the same amount. Uh,
if that makes sense.
As long as you've got like 1.4
1.3 1.4 1.5 in your account as a single person,
it's it's enough, you know.
Well, you get good returns if you put
150 on two teams. You get good returns.
You get like you do get quite good returns.
You get like 600 sometimes 500.
But this if it comes in isn't it?
What do you think?
Is there any playing Tuesday?
I do look into the teams. Yeah.
Let me see what
what if I put £300 on
two teams. Joe,
that's like £1,200, isn't it?
Let me see who's playing. Yeah.
What do you think the chance is my
football bet's going to win though?
Probably won't win, will it?
Probably won't win, eh?
I was going to do Aquinon and
Chillington and Colchester and T but the
odds were looking more
I don't I One second.
I just want my football bet to win.
I need £285.
Do you think it will win?
Yeah, they're [ __ ] I actually do
remember that Tremier trying to score.
They're [ __ ] But I think Oxford is
playing Swindon next week and I'm
definitely putting a bet on them cuz
that is they're definitely both going to
score. I always bet on Oxford. They
always both to score and Swindon as well. Oh [ __ ]
What do you think?
Well, I'll be back later.