Oh, sorry. Won't you mind? One of me. She alive.
Yeah. Morning man. Will to go live.
This one is going to get me in serious trouble. on
you all day mean serious [ __ ] boy.
They're on YouTube again. They can't get off it.
Yeah, you know YouTube.
>> Oh my gosh. My YouTube. >> Yeah. >> Yes.
>> Yeah, man.
>> Same people. Same people in it.
>> Yeah. I can't be asked anymore to be
honest with anything or anyone now.
Can't be asked anymore.
Like what are you doing?
>> Just playing this. Yeah.
>> That's why I told you to go live because
I'm not sitting in the house all [ __ ]
bored not talking to no one.
Yeah, they're just mongos on here.
>> You agree?
>> The yellow mongos, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Yes. I I just got Natalie her new TV.
>> Really? How much?
I tried getting a 45 um but they didn't
have um thingy. It cost him like 300. >> Nice.
>> That was already being ordered.
>> So that's what I'm doing.
>> Why you asking where diesel is?
>> Cuz they think that I'm asked about
that. I'm more asked about Nal and about diesel. Okay, now
>> let me turn my camera off.
>> Yeah, I'm all about these.
>> I'm just off home anyway. So,
>> where did you where did you buy the TV from?
>> I'm not saying [ __ ] mate.
I'm not giving nothing to these people.
Nothing. All the noise that I'm getting
Natalie a new TV.
>> The [ __ ] mongos.
I got a new TV.
>> Have you?
>> Yeah. 55 in.
>> Nice. Nice.
>> Yeah. 400. It was £429.
>> I think um I was going to get the 43 in,
but they didn't have any of them left in
stock. You already had that 30 34 35 in
or something whatever
one of them.
>> So I just got one of them for
I'm trying to show her that I'm sorry.
Okay, now I should have come live. I
should even be on YouTube now. But
what's the point? I don't have no one to
talk to. I'm not sitting in my house all
all alone [ __ ] swinging my fingers
around. Natalie's gone out somewhere.
What are you doing, PG? Why?
Why does PJ leave
KJ? Man, I'm not talking to Le on my
own. I just [ __ ] off, man. If you're not here.
>> Sorry about that.
>> Yeah, man. I'm not entertaining cuz I'm
not entertaining these. I'm entertaining you, PJ.
>> I'm not entertaining. >> PJ,
>> can you hear me?
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's just the car going past
me. I'm near the old now anyway, so
>> Monty, you like these people?
>> I don't. I don't
there's only one person who I like in this community. One person
you know what I've never felt like this
for anyone in my life you never ever
you know when people said you know what
love is and he's like no I don't know
what love is when I [ __ ] do its [ __ ] hurts.
I'm hurting, man. It's not not funny, >> I >> What?
>> You like it, is it?
>> I don't like it. I really don't like it.
I've never felt like this for any [ __ ]
>> Any [ __ ]
>> I don't like this really. Really? I
I don't know why.
I don't I don't know where these
feelings coming from,
>> you know,
>> cuz every time a woman every time a
woman has broke up with me or whatever,
I sit there and laugh at him. I can't do
that with Natalie and I don't know why.
>> I can Monty.
>> Well, you can laugh.
>> Yeah. If it happened, if Matthew said it to me,
um I could just laugh and pay it.
>> I tried it. I tried it. It's just
>> So, how come how comes I can do it then?
>> Because I'm different than you where
I've been in where I've been in a 10
year relationship and I've come out of a
10 year relationship.
You know what I mean?
I'm going to come out of a 10 years
relationship. Natalie was L for me. She >> and
I would love for her
but I [ __ ] up on her last last.
>> I remember I remember I remember I
remember when Nat wanted to meet me at
first. I just said no.
>> Yeah. No, to be honest with you PJ that
was a joke. She were joking on that.
>> No, she [ __ ] wasn't. She was giving
you a fake hotel and all that lot.
>> No, she [ __ ] wasn't. Was she [ __ ]
>> No, she [ __ ] wasn't. No, she was not.
>> You don't ask her.
>> So, I was going to go all the way to
Birmingham. I was going to go all the
way to Birmingham. Bro, that's that's a
story that she made up cuz I didn't go.
>> Yeah. No. Yeah. No kidding.
>> I don't care anyways, bro. Like, [ __ ] it.
>> That's what she was saying.
>> Yeah. She's lying, bro.
Doesn't matter anyways.
>> No, no. This your fault.
>> She's your She's your She's your lady.
>> Is that your lady? Money.
>> I [ __ ] know.
I don't know what she wants from me. I
don't know what I'm trying my hard is.
I'm getting a all I'm getting a I'm
getting a lot of [ __ ] Not saying
>> what you trying. Are you trying to get
back in a nickn?
>> I'm trying to get just back in a good
box. That's it.
>> What about Nicknox?
>> No, I'm not trying to get in a nickn your mama.
She is my mama.
>> Yeah, I have a mama, too. But my mama abandoned me.
>> She's a [ __ ] She's my angel. I'm And
I'm just a [ __ ] up.
>> She's my angel and I'm just a [ __ ] up.
>> Do you still get grief of that money
Mike anymore? Nah.
>> Money man will never meet me. As you
said to me, they never meet on your He
was on your case for a while, wasn't he?
>> Yeah. Ch is because of Natalie and me.
>> You know what I mean by on your case?
getting shameless about me.
>> I don't know what to do with myself, buddy.
>> Just have a wank in it.
>> Just have a wank. I don't I don't I
don't need I don't do that [ __ ] man.
It's not even I don't have a pair of Natalie Nik.
>> Oh, bless you.
>> I'm joking. I'm joking. That was a joke.
Don't bless you in life, won't he?
>> No, man. I just I'm too in love, man.
And I'm a [ __ ] up. I'm not
>> just going for a beer with long legs.
>> Why do you want to meet up anywhere, PJ?
Do you want me to beat your [ __ ] pulling buddy?
>> No, I'm going I'm going to beat you in a sword fight.
>> PJ, come to Birmingham today.
>> Yeah, but I'll beat you in a sword fight.
>> What? I feel a sword fight.
>> What a sword fight. You want fight?
>> I'm all right. No,
>> man. W PJ over and over and over.
>> Do you want a sword? Do you want a sword fight? Um,
where is he?
>> So weird, man. You know when you first
come on YouTube? Yeah. Do you think it's
so weird now? When you first come on
years ago, it's still the same [ __ ] all
them years later.
>> Yeah. It's still the same shitty ass
people. And that's why
>> you know PlayStation. You know PlayStation?
>> Yeah. Yeah. You know, you know,
PlayStation, don't you think it's weird
that everyone left?
Everyone moved, didn't it? Everyone left.
>> Yeah, I left it first. I was a
>> Yeah, but eventually everyone left. But
this is the same, isn't it? And here.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I was PlayStation 3. I had
enough of it. Me too. I don't want to
sit on YouTube and be a prick. I don't
want to sit on YouTube and call
everybody spastics, retards, [ __ ]
ugly little mongos. You know what I mean?
>> That's what they do. Is it? That's what
>> Yeah, that's what they do. And
you just do what you're doing like just
like a normal chitchat like this. They
hate it when you ignore them. They
That's what I'm doing. If Natalie can't
forgive me, who am I going to talk to?
No one. So, I might as well just start
going back live. I don't want to.
You know what I mean? I don't want to
start going back live. But if now they
can't forgive me for something they
haven't really done,
>> you know,
I will never tell anybody what is
actually happened. No one actually knows what's
said [ __ ] lost everything over an app
on your phone.
>> Over a app on my phone? No, not over the
app on my phone. It's cuz I can't keep
my mouth shut. That's why.
That's totally different. I can't keep
my mouth shut. And that's one thing I
need to start learning is keeping my mouth shut.
I'm keeping off YouTube. I'm not coming
on YouTube. I don't want to be back here
to be honest with you.
>> Remember whole.
>> Yeah, he's died.
Yeah, as well.
>> How do you know these things?
>> I don't know these things. Anyways, does
anyone know how to get this [ __ ] 50
quid back in my bank? Yeah.
>> Do you remember? Do you remember WWF Grevy?
>> Yeah. Go on, Monty. Sorry. I just wanted
to ask Grey something.
>> No. Yeah. Well, I've got 20. I mean,
I've got 50 coin in my bank yet. And I
left my bank card at my mom's house and
I placed cash now to go to cash machine
where you put the code in the cash
machine but it didn't let me put the code in.
So I [ __ ] ended up going to the 50 quid.
It's saying that the 50 quid is pending
but the the 50 quid in my bank.
So here I show you that's funny how you knew about
Where did you hear?
>> Yeah, I can hear you.
>> No. Where did you hear about that whole?
>> It's all over. It was all over Facebook.
Do you remember WWF?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> What did What did you watch?
>> Does anyone know about this? I need Py.
I need help. I need a 50 quid back. It's
pending and I need to stop it from pending.
>> Look, I need to get that back in my bank.
How do I do it? So, what I've done is
that I've left my bank card at my mom's
house. I've gone to the bank machine on
my online banking
place cash now. So, I can get cash out
the bank by just using that.
And uh [ __ ]
it didn't draw my money out. It just put
my money as pending. Now I can't get
back to that cord. You get a code to get
the money out. And now I can't get back
to that [ __ ] cord.
>> How was you able to buy that TV for £300? >> What?
>> How was you able to spend £34? You're rich.
>> I can get more [ __ ]
Yeah, you're rich in it.
>> I got that TV for Natalie. It's not even
my TV. It's Natalie's TV. >> It
could afford it easy.
>> It's coming soon.
Coming soon. I don't want it TV cuz it's Samsung.
>> But I think it's a 3D TV or something. I
think it's a 3D one. >> Yeah.
>> Like a 3D TV.
>> You should be getting You should be in a
liquor by the end of today, man.
>> I don't want to go in the knickers. I
just want to have to [ __ ]
if Roro [ __ ] go back out with her or
[ __ ] do what? I'm not even I'm not
even chatting [ __ ] when I say this. I'm
not even [ __ ] I swear I'm doing my
kids. I'm not even chatting [ __ ]
[ __ ] you haven't even at for five
days. Four days. Five days. >> What?
>> Oh, bless you.
>> Yeah. No, I've not even been eating
nothing. I haven't I haven't
[ __ ] Look at that, PJ. >> What?
>> I haven't been eating me.
>> You're proper. You are
>> skinny now. Look at that. I'm [ __ ]
proper skinny. SC starting to look like fairly 420.
>> Starting to look like him now. I'm
losing my [ __ ] belly weight.
>> I've lo you meet me.
>> Yeah, I'll meet you. I'll meet you. You
ain't got no one else to meet now, have I?
>> You're mad. You're a mad [ __ ] You are.
>> Why do you meet Timmy? We friends. You
don't meet me.
How about me and Timmy?
>> Remember Timmy? You think money?
I know Timmy makes you laugh. Timmy
makes you laugh in it.
>> Jimmy don't make me laugh. No, his voice
actually goes through me.
Only what makes me laugh about Timmy is
when he makes a laughing noises. That's about it.
No, you me.
You like Timmy, bro. He's your friend.
>> I'm not being funny. That person who
said Kay's trolling him, Kayie can't
even troll anyone. Have you seen the
state of that woman?
>> You look like a dude with a wig on.
>> That's not what that says.
>> Look like a dude with a wig on and a
hairy [ __ ] ass. That's not what that says, bro.
>> What did it say?
>> They're trying to say I'm trolling you.
Why am I Why would I be trolling you,
bro? How am I trolling you? In what way?
Well, I'm [ __ ] not.
I don't troll anyone, bro.
Why are they asking for your new
address? That's weird. Why would you
give me know my new address? Why are
they asking for your address? Me and
>> Natalie moved for reasons.
We still live in the same house
together. We just moved into a different property.
Just it's because of all these little on
YouTube. The council wanted to move us
because of all these. Look
>> all over YouTube again.
>> Yeah. So the council moved me and
Natalie a different
>> That's USA is he to a different property. Huh?
Money mike has shown text. Money mic has
shown text with N. No, he hasn't.
Natalie won't go back with Money Mike or
anything like that cuz what Money Mike's
done to her.
>> They're trying these people said they're
trying to say they'll find you.
>> You can't find me. You can't look for me
all you [ __ ] want, peeps.
Hide and seek. They said
hide and seek.
>> No, they can find me all they want. They
can look for me all they want. They
won't find me either way.
They won't find me.
>> Well, she does get back with that mic though.
>> She won't go back out with Mike. He's a
ugly man. Natalie can do much better and
money mic. Much better. She's not
[ __ ] ugly. She's She's
She's a [ __ ] lovely woman.
>> What would you do if she love Timmy?
>> No, she goes to Timmy. That ain't no
standards, is it?
>> You'd laugh at it. No, that's weird.
>> Would I would I would I would laugh.
>> Franklin. I'm playing some Franklin.
Who's a bit of a whale? >> Kayie.
>> Yeah. You go left, you go right, you go
down the middle, and you find the ass
crack. And it's right [ __ ] there. >> Yeah.
>> You go left, you go right, you go down
the middle, and you find the ass crack.
>> Yeah. Birmingham's Birmingham is near
Blackpool anyways. It's not too far.
>> Nowhere near Blackpool.
>> It's like 20 minutes.
It's in full 20 minutes.
>> Kind of 30 minutes.
>> I don't like his is a [ __ ]
He's a lag. Is he?
Um, so what is it like 30 minutes?
>> No, it's not even 30 minutes. like two
to two to three hours.
>> That's too long, is it? >> Mhm.
>> You're from Blackpool.
>> I want to know I get this [ __ ] 50
quid back in my bank.
It's just pending. It's just pending.
How do I
>> Explain it again and I'll tell you
>> what's the problem. >> Right.
>> Explain it.
>> Right. I left my bank card at my mom's house. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> So, I can't draw no money out only with
my online banking. So, what I have to do
is go on to quick cash well cash out.
>> Go to a bank and then put a code in.
tried doing that
and it just like completely wouldn't
give me the fe like
it just puts up and it wouldn't [ __ ]
give me the 50 quid. So now the 50 quid is pending
>> waiting out
and I need to get that 50 quid back in my bank.
>> Are you skinn?
No, I'm not skinned.
>> Well, I am skinned. Look, it's pending.
I show you.
>> Are you almost skinn? Yeah.
I ain't even being able to draw no money
out or nothing. I ain't even been able
to do nothing.
>> N you're rich, bro.
>> Look, pending. That's what I need to try
and get back in my bank. Pending. See? Yeah. [Music]
So, I need to try and get that back in
my bank, but I don't know how.
>> Oh, here we go.
>> Let me try and give my mom this 50 quid. Who's there? Franklin's gone flying.
I'm gone. She
>> have you, Shagger. Have you found that
Tam yet from Glasggo? The one with the
glasses that we was looking for? I still
ain't found him. Yeah, Tam.
I'm looking for a Tam from Glasgow
who I met two years ago. Yeah, the old
one. I can't find him. All I know is he
wears glasses and he went to
uni in Edinburgh.
and we wear a kil he wore a kilt to his graduation. Scott's prick
want you still there?
>> Yeah, I'm still here. >> Oh,
>> you can see me. I'm just trying to get
this 50 quid back.
>> I [ __ ] hate myself, man. God bless you.
>> I don't know what to do with myself
anymore, mate. I really don't.
Just have a lunch.
>> No, don't do that [ __ ] man.
No, I don't. No,
don't need to do that [ __ ] You know,
I've got Natalie.
I should have Natalie. Yeah.
>> Let me bring my mom.
>> This is [ __ ] up.
>> You like it though?
>> I like what?
>> That is [ __ ] up, isn't it?
>> No, I don't like it, PJ. I really don't
[ __ ] like it.
I don't like feeling I don't like
feeling like this. I've never felt like
this in my entire [ __ ] life.
>> It's not funny though.
>> Monty is very serious. Monty never
laughs at anything in it. Franklin.
>> Yeah. No, no. I am a serious guy. I
can't be ass [ __ ] with these clowns
on this community. That's why I don't do
what I used to do. I haven't I [ __ ]
since I've been in this community, I've lost myself.
Literally lost myself.
>> Why don't you laugh at anything though?
>> Because what is to laugh at when you
just lost [ __ ] the woman of your life?
>> Come on. Do you think everything's funny?
>> Do you think everything's funny?
>> I don't think nothing's funny, buddy.
There's nothing to be funny about,
>> buddy. I I don't laugh at a lot of
things, do I?
>> Do you?
>> What? You laugh at a lot of things.
>> No, I don't laugh at a lot, do I?
Okay, I'm getting a take away.
>> I already had a take away. I had a whole
chicken meal from Peppies. >> Yeah.
>> Might get a Subway, you know.
>> Well, bless you.
You should start saving money.
>> No, no. Believe it or not, I don't smoke
weed no more. I've actually quit weed.
>> M. All right. So, I don't smoke weed
anymore. So, I am saving money now
because I've literally quit weed.
Obviously, I can go out and get weed
now, but I'm not doing I rather [ __ ]
>> just quit.
>> I want to put weight on, but I'm not
putting weight on when I'm not eating. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, this looks gorgeous.
Can I get a kebab from me? No. That one.
It's expensive for that place.
>> Not much.
>> It's [ __ ]
>> She's not that good. Bomb base. She's
>> Yeah. What? Monty,
>> it's one of these places, you know, with
like um kebab shop. >> Yeah.
>> Kebab shop or one of them expensive [ __ ] places.
>> But I had one from there. Abs are not
that very good actually until I tell you the truth.
KFC. No, I don't want KFC.
>> Monty has a lot of money.
>> Oh, just on date I went on, she turned
out to be a time waster.
was holding hands and everything. H
holding hands and everything, flirting.
And then when I went to when I went to
kiss, she didn't want to. And then she
was just being just wasting my time.
Sorry, Monty. Go on. But
I can't be honest
with you. If women if women do this, if
women do this and don't give you a
chance to talk or give you a chance to
explain yourself or anything like that and then
>> stop asking weird questions, not you, Monty, but
like if a woman said like if you have an
argument with a woman. Yeah. Yeah,
>> obviously it's just the argument. That's
how how they should stay as arguments.
If you [ __ ] up, it's just as argument.
You should finish each other over
absolutely [ __ ] off. You know what I mean?
>> B. Yeah.
>> Women's Women [ __ ] men's heads either
way. They They think that
>> I'll say that to you. I'll say that to
>> Yeah. They think that men are
strongarted, but women don't know they
that most men think about one woman
where most women think about different men.
>> Money, why are these people asking weird
questions? They're asking me if I've
seen someone naked. That's some weird, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. What? Don't Don't read the
comments. Don't read them. Leave them to
look weird, PJ. You're looking weirder
by reading them comments.
>> That's [ __ ] weird when they're
asking, is it?
>> Yeah, you're [ __ ] idiots. These actual mongos
money someone said, "Hey, Lisa said,
"Tell Monty the workers asked for his
channel. The landlord I gave I've gave it." Huh?
>> Yeah, that's fine.
I'm at a new address.
So that's fine.
>> Get that. But yeah,
>> we've got a new landlord.
>> Yeah, women are time wasters though, man.
>> I got other account. I got other YouTube account people.
>> I got other YouTube accounts
watching. Yeah, but why? Why? Yeah. So
what if the landlords watching? So what?
>> Yeah. So
>> no, the download's not watching PD yet.
>> That's what Lisa said.
Tell him I sent sent Vince this morning to him.
>> Why you doing that, Lisa? >> Because
Lisa is a [ __ ] and she doctor wrong
daughter. That's what it is.
Come on, Lisa. And Lisa, you need to
stop going on that L's channel as well.
>> Leave her to a PGA. She's all into the
trolls. She likes the trolls. She's
[ __ ] her own daughter up for the trolls.
>> Yeah. Is that funny?
>> No, it's not funny. Is it [ __ ] funny?
What mom would chuck her own daughter
under under a bus by giving her giving
her a dress out by doxing her address?
So if the landlord is watching, it's
Lisa who's docked this address. It's
Lisa who's g everybody this address on YouTube.
>> You know what I mean? It's Lisa who's
done that. So Lisa, everyone even knows
about that either way. And Lisa, look at
this. This is probably going to piss
Lisa off. Mother, I'm not being funny,
Lisa, but look at this. Lisa, that Lisa,
all your clothes,
all in bags
getting ready. Getting ready is getting
sent to the charity shop.
>> Look, Lisa, so you know the words or
getting sent to this charity shop,
please, sir. Look, so you know that he said, "Look, [ __ ]
[ __ ] they all going."
>> I think you two need to pack it in.
>> I'm not a
PJ box for Lisa, you s. I'm not a [ __ ] s.
If Lisa wants them close, she needs to
come and pick them up
literally because they are going um the
thing is coming picking them up. Um
the sport workers come and picking them up.
Don't know when she's picking them up,
but she's only giving um Lisa a week or
so to come and get them close. That's
why they pack like that now and left downstairs.
No one's told Lisa about it, but I am
cuz I'm not a cruel bastard. But Lisa,
if you went any closer there, you don't
want him, that's fine. But I'll let you
know anyways cuz I'm not a tight hunter.
>> There's nothing funny about this.
>> No, it isn't. There's nothing funny
about this. Nothing at all. Absolutely nothing.
There's me. You fought your daughter's
head up. Yeah.
Oh [ __ ] What's up?
>> They're proper bongos. They
buddy. They're proper mongos on this community. Yeah. >> Yeah. Mongos.
>> Yeah. No, I'm done with Lisa B. I'm not
done with Natalie. I'm a [ __ ] I will
never be done with Natalie. Lisa, I'm
completely done with her.
Completely done with her. I will never
open up to her ever again about anything or anything.
I opened up to her in the bedroom and that
you know since all this with Lisa
in this address me and Natalie haven't
been the same. Me and you know
we're just looking being at each other
and that's not good. And that's not
So, what are you going to do if she says
she doesn't want to get back with you,
for example, then what? You've had it in it.
>> If she doesn't want to get back with me,
then she doesn't want to get back with
me. That's completely fine. I'm going to
have to take it. >> Yeah.
>> At the moment, I'm not giving up on
Natalie. If I give up on Natalie, then
it shows that I don't love her. If I
give up on it, I'm not I will never give
up on that.
>> Why do these people want to know? Why do
these people want to know where you
live? That's weird, bro.
[ __ ] idiots. That's why I idiot.
>> That's [ __ ] weird, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. That Captain America be crazy,
>> you know. So, it's all these fault. All
of this why [ __ ] all this has
happened with me and now. >> Yeah.
>> Because if I dress, it didn't get
dodged. Yeah. And then
that that day in that hotel when it
kicked off in that hotel, Natalie wanted [ __ ]
>> Just go to where she just go to where
she um lives, Monty.
>> Go where? Who lives?
>> Natalie and just talk in it.
>> Natalie lives with me. Natalie lives
here. She's going out for a bit.
>> Yeah. So just talk to her when she's
going back in it.
>> Yeah. I wouldn't know. I'm leaving a be.
I'm not getting on the net.
>> How did I lose? I didn't do anything to that America.
>> Stop going live. [ __ ] >> Lisa,
you're in your 50s and you're going on
live calling people mongos. You [ __ ] crackhead.
>> Who the [ __ ] is this?
What's going on?
>> What's going on? >> Nothing.
>> How's day going, mate? >> What? >> Huh?
>> How's your day going, man?
>> Good, man.
>> Can you Can you talk normal?
>> What the [ __ ] man? >> Weird.
>> What? Left it.
>> Yeah. Weird. No.
>> Yeah. That's That's all they said. Can
you not talk normal?
>> That's what
>> Yeah, that's why you're not talking.
>> Yeah, they're weirdos on here. Is it
>> money? Will this community ever change?
[ __ ] keep up you.
Why money? Will this community ever change?
So Lisa, what are you trying to do with
Are you trying to help me out or like
take the piss?
Are you trying to tell me to get off
YouTube to help me out or tell me to
>> leave YouTube like just taking a piss?
>> Same website you can watch the bear in
the big blue house on. Eh, madness that
this [ __ ] community has ruined money.
You know, Benny's life has been ruined
over this site.
>> Everyone's life's been ruined for this
YouTube. Everyone's everyone's everybody bullied.
You do you.
>> You do any of these? Yeah. >> Huh?
>> Probably on big.
>> You do these PJ.
>> Your camera's froz Oh no. There you go. Yeah.
Yes. Can you do any of that peep? Yeah.
>> Yeah, but not now.
>> Yeah, peeps. I can do it with one hand,
too. I do it with one hand. Yeah.
What is it? Second, bro.
>> Don't get on one hand.
>> One hand. I got
>> Oh, you dirty [ __ ]
What a dirty [ __ ] you are. Yeah, dirty
What are you? Yeah, you're dirt you're a
dirty [ __ ] mate.
>> That's what I call a body.
>> You're a dirty [ __ ] bro. I'm a
money. What does the movie ever change? >> No. >> Monty,
one second. I'm in.
Yeah, I trust Monty to not put nudes up.
Yeah, they're weirdos, isn't it? Monty
Lisa, this ain't your bedroom.
You've never paid rent on this property. [Music]
>> You give up this bedroom cuz you didn't
want to live for your normal. smog going
to try and get a job. B I will one
second Monty listen to what I'm saying
here Monty. Yeah. I'm just going to say
one thing. I'll get a job when you get a
job. That's all I'm saying back to them. Monty,
what do you think? Monty. [ __ ] no.
>> Yeah, I'll get a job when you get one.
>> Lisa, I don't even sleep in this bedroom
anyway. I just do me exciting this room. That's it.
I share the same room as Natalie. I
don't sleep in that room, Lisa. That
room's always been left alone.
What's Lisa like in real life? I've
never met her.
I thought she was all right in real
life. To be honest with you, PJ,
I thought she was actually all right.
When I first met Lisa, but I only met Lisa once,
>> but when I first saw I thought she were
decent. I thought I thought she was actually decent.
I didn't expect her to go on to
other people's YouTube channels and slag
me off to them cuz that's what she did.
That's where the issue is. It's Lisa
slagging me off to people and she's
supposed to like me.
We're supposed to sort everything out
and then she's lagging me off to um
what's his name now?
>> Lord J.
>> What? Lord J.
>> No, not Lord J. Yeah, Lord J and someone
else. Yeah. No, no, she still caught for
Lord J. Lord J were going for N
calleding Natalie and I was sticking up
for Natalie and Lisa jumped on and
started sticking up for Lord J.
I know that lot and Lisa slagging me
off. I know that lot. And um someone
else's channel forgot his name now. Sky
Parker or something
taking the piss up with Sky Parker in that
>> [ __ ] the skeleton. Why do you people
just do this [ __ ] Keep calling people
to it cuz let them think that I'm
skinny. It's not it's not very skinny.
It's basically more muscle and skinny.
So I'm not ass.
>> There's people calling themselves in it.
>> I'm happy to be like that, but I'm not
as skinny as belly. I need to start
eating now. I've quit weed anyways, so
I'm going to start gaining weight now.
>> Money, have you ever
have you ever used the steering wheel in GTA? >> No.
>> No. Like PlayStation, you like buy the
steering wheel, you connect it. It's
good, isn't it?
Natalie used [ __ ] for money. Definitely
not. Natalie's never used me for money.
Never ever ever ever used me for money.
I've always give Natalie money. I never
wanted money back off her. Natalie's
always give me money. I've always gifted
it back to her.
Natalie's got her own money as well.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Me and Natalie, we're not
even going out.
>> So, you're not in a relationship anymore technically.
>> I don't know what's going on to be
honest. It's all what Natalie wants in
it, not what I want. I know what I want.
I want Natalie, but it's all it's what she wants.
I'm not going to force or push Natalie
or nothing. I just I just want Natalie
to know I will always be there for her.
Always be there.
>> No matter what.
>> I make the biggest mistake and I'm not
willing to make a mistake again.
Obviously, I'm making a mistake now by
being on YouTube, but I ain't got [ __ ] else.
>> I ain't got no one else to talk to. I'm
here swiggling my fingers. Don't know
what to do.
[ __ ] don't know what to do.
You know, with with Natalie,
she actually kept me on the straight.
She actually kept me off YouTube. She
>> No, she was she kept me off YouTube. It
was just that one day I [ __ ] up at the
hotel. When we was at the hotel, I told
everyone we was at the hotel and [ __ ]
like that. She knew I went live. She she
went angry at me for it, but she didn't
know what what I was saying. If she
wanted to know what what we're saying, I
would have told her. >> Yeah.
>> You know,
>> because it's not weren't going to be a
secret. I went live,
but I didn't tell anything to these
people. Only what I said to the le I
repeat what I said. Now, I said this,
okay, Natalie kicked me out the hotel again. [ __ ]
getting sick a bit. I shouldn't have got
rid of my dog and should have stayed in um Mansfield.
Um I should have said that because I
[ __ ] I do love Natalie and I do want
to live with N. I do want to spend the
rest of my life with that woman.
It's just when I get pissed off with
women shouting at me because of Kay. I
don't like shouting.
>> You know what I mean? I just don't like shouting. And
>> you remember do you remember when you
first do you remember when you first met
Natalie tent like you was live. It was
funny isn't it?
>> No no no being it's not funny being almost PJ
no I'm not laughing at that bit. I'm
laughing at when you was in the tent and
you met her like when she shook like you
shook her hand. Do you remember the
first time you hugged her? >> Yeah.
>> When you met her the first time? Yeah. >> Yeah.
And that's what I mean. Natalie and
[ __ ] she's been there for me and I
just [ __ ] everything up.
>> Is she Is that the real Natalie G?
>> No. No. It's a fake.
>> You know, I will always be left.
>> Was it that bad in the tender? >> What?
>> Was it that bad in the tent?
>> Yeah, I were freezing. Natalie were
freezing and my dog was freezing. All
three of those worse than you. I was
sleeping on the stairs before. I was
homeless. I was sleep I was sleeping on
the stairs. I was I was homeless. Well,
I had that room, but I had no bed or no
room, so I had to sleep on the stairs.
>> It was bad.
>> I would never ever wish homeless on
anybody. I wouldn't even wish homeless
on Natalie or [ __ ] anyone.
>> The enemy being homeless.
>> It is [ __ ] hanging. I've only been
homeless once in my life. Only only
slept rough once in my life.
>> Yeah, I was sleeping on the stairs.
Monty, listen. Listen. Uh, one second,
Monty. I was sleeping on the stairs
because the house that I went back to
had rented all the rooms out and they
had paid the rent. So, I'd had to sleep
on the stairs. And then, um, when I was
cold, I had to go to the bathroom and
sleep in the b in the like a bathroom to
to to heat I had to heat the shower up
cuz it was cold. It was bad, bro. It was
in the winter as well. It's bad.
>> Lisa, that is a fake account. Oh,
Natalie is not the real Natalie. Lisa,
>> so I'm a survivor. I'm a warrior. Ever
since that day, I knew I was a warrior. Monty.
Yeah, but sleeping in a tent ain't that bad, man.
It just goes on and on and on and on.
No, it's it's not. It is. It's bad, PJ.
It's not good, man. You're getting bit
by You're getting bit by mosquitoes. You
get bit by flies.
Did anyone ever come? >> What?
>> Did anyone ever come from where?
>> Like the like um the tent like when you
were sleeping. Did anyone ever come? and
like knock the tent off.
>> No, no, cuz you had diesel. Yeah, people
come and that but make sure it was all
right and stuff like I had people
checking on me around.
>> That's funny, is it?
>> No, we could. It's respect, isn't it? I
would never ever w Natalie homeless. I
would never ever wish anybody homeless.
Lucky enough, Natalie still lives here.
She Okay, but she's just gone out. That's
>> That's not the real Natalie.
>> No, it's not a real Natalie. It's a fake.
>> It's KJ. It's a fake nut.
>> No. Yeah. Yeah. No, it's not a real N.
100%. They just spot the sauce up, don't
you? Where he's going. Yeah. No, it's
not the real N.
Everybody knows about Natalie. So,
all right then. All right then. I ask
you something then. All right then.
Fair enough. You want me to ask you something? >> Yeah.
>> Okay then, Natalie. What did you do?
Oh, wait. I can't. No. In fact, I'm not
saying [ __ ] because
No, I'm not saying nothing. I'm not
saying nothing. Keep my mouth shut.
You know, no, it is a fake. Go on. It's
a fake nar PJ. It's not even a real one.
>> Why do they make fake accounts?
>> Cuz she [ __ ] idiots on YouTube.
Natalie will never come back on YouTube.
She's quit cuz of all the [ __ ] I've
quit as well. I'm not back on YouTube.
I'm only here cuz I [ __ ]
how [ __ ] up. You know what I mean? How
[ __ ] up be?
I've got Natalie a new TV. I [ __ ] pay
300 for it.
I've seen I've seen um a single one seater
set as well. the same one as the ones in
the bedroom or she's got a bedroom nice
set and it's like I'm getting her one of
them as well like a single one
that's shagger still on YouTube.
>> They all still on YouTube.
I'm surprised one of them is dead. What? Oh [ __ ]
PJ, kick out Natalie account, please.
Man, it's a fake account. You're just
leaving it there to go on and on and on.
All right, then. If it is the real
Natalie, text, send me a text. Yeah,
text me. If it's the real Natalie, say
it is me. So, send me a text if it's the real Natalie.
And I believe you. So send me a text on
on my phone number on text messenger
>> or whatever the internet cut off again.
>> Yeah. TJ, it's not real by the way, buddy.
>> No. Okay.
>> No kick. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. No, it's not Lisa. [Music]
Yeah. Put the link in for Natalie PJ cuz
it it isn't Natalie. >> Yeah.
[ __ ] miss woman, man.
>> No, I do. I do. I [ __ ] miss her.
>> I miss you.
>> I would do anything for her, man. I get
her anything. I will do anything for
her. [ __ ] you.
>> Would you have a sword?
>> Even if she wanted a Ferrari, man, I get
her a [ __ ] Ferrari, mate. If she
wants a Porsche, I get her a Porsche.
She wants a Lamborghini, I get her a
Lamborghini. If she wants a [ __ ]
limo, I get her a [ __ ] limo.
Monty, you're you're you're Monty,
you're a s.
>> I'm a s. What do you mean?
>> Oh, it's hard to explain it.
>> [ __ ] you don't even have 50 in your bank.
>> Who doesn't?
>> I got 50 quid pending. I'm trying to get
that 50 quid back.
I need help mates with this order
[ __ ] [ __ ] I can't read [ __ ] orders. EJ,
see I told you it's not the old knack.
Oh, she would have text me or she would have [ __ ]
come up on a hangout. told you
the TV is
I mean 89 or will
Okay. Okay. TV will be here next week or
something. So now this not this TV I
just got a text now.
Now, this TV will be here next week.
I got a nice [ __ ] TV. A [ __ ] smart ass TV.
About 300 for it. I paid 300.
Not that I'm paying um another 300 as
well. So, that's like 600 quid on
spending. Maybe a little bit more here, man.
I got really bad internet here.
When will she be back? Monty.
Huh? Because what? What? When will she be back?
>> It's up to her when she'll be back. It's
up to her.
It's gone down or something
clear in a red.
>> God bless.
I've got Yeah, but Steven Howard, I've
got a £429 TV.
>> Yeah, King. My TV at [ __ ] Knob's
house cost me a grand and I want that [ __ ] back.
What a Have you ever owed anyone money? >> What?
>> Have you ever owed anyone money?
>> Of course I've owed people money.
Obviously. Of course I have. Yeah, but
you know when you owe people money, they
come on the door and it
>> No, not really. Cuz I always pay my
bills. Never say you didn't pay.
>> No. No.
Whatever I've had out of people, I've
always given it back. I've never
>> Yeah. But if you don't give it back, do
they do they try get Would they try and
get it back? [ __ ]
>> knows. And I've never tried it.
You know what I mean? Is it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I know what you mean.
By [ __ ] lending money or someone and
not giving them back for years or >> Yeah.
No, that's not me. I'm not that person.
If I lend 20 quid or someone and I end
up just getting 20 quid put back in my
bank and I ow that 20 quid to someone, I
will give that 20 quid to someone and
leave myself skinn. >> Yeah.
Taking man. I need to be more active. My
body's aching. You know what that means?
When your body's aching. >> Yeah.
>> Horrible. Have you ever had it?
>> Billy Moore. I know Billy Moore.
You know Billy Moore, Monty?
>> Billy Moore? >> Yeah.
>> Billy Moore. Who's he? Liverpool.
He's from Liverpool. Oh,
>> okay. No, I don't know.
Send Monty a few quid.
Monty's got money, don't you?
>> You got money, don't you, bro?
>> Me? I've got money.
>> Know [ __ ] Barack brassic.
spent my last bit of money on [ __ ]
Natalie and I try getting my last 50
quid out and it won't come out. >> Seriously?
>> Yeah, I got Natalie on TV and I It's coming.
>> Yes. How you going to How you going to eat?
>> I'm just going to [ __ ] I'm not I
haven't been eating PGF for 5 days, buddy.
>> How you going to eat now?
>> I'm not eating. I'm not eating.
I'm I'm looking at takeaways, but I I
just can't be out ordering nothing. I'm not eating.
>> How can you afford it if you got no money?
>> What do you mean?
>> You said you got no money, so how could
you buy a takeaway anyways?
>> No. What do you want me to pay for a takeaway, dear?
>> No, I'm just wondering how how cuz you
said you got no money in it.
What? What did Lo say? Multi if it's what?
What did L?
>> If it over, just go Lady Se. She's the
fittest on here.
>> No, believe me, I'm happy. I'm happy
with Natalie. I don't want no other
woman off YouTube. Literally, I'm happy
with Natalie. Now they
like I'm not getting with anybody else.
Literally nobody else.
I would never ever sleep.
>> Someone said someone said put your
camera on and show £5.
>> Put my camera on and show £5. I don't carry cash.
>> I sure change
>> the money.
The the money game. The money game again, Monty.
>> There you go, peeps. I show you all
loose chains in there. There's some
loose change for you, peeps. I show you
some loose change here. There's loose
change everywhere in this house.
>> Hi, Monty. Why Monty? Monty, why does
>> change in this house? Everywhere.
>> Hi, Monty. Why does Nons legs try to
call me skin? >> John. >> Yeah,
>> I think it's skin.
It's projected in
it's like a reverse in it. It's like
reverse every time. Is it bro?
>> I am rich. I got more money.
>> It's like what they say is about them in it.
>> Okay. Let me order some food. PJ
>> that's just like
skin. Yeah. This projection.
Did it? Huh?
>> How do I get a woman to forgive me? Man,
>> get your [ __ ] out.
>> No, no, man.
I don't know. She I don't know why I
thought I was okay,
>> you know. I know. She probably won't go
back. She will come back to me either
way. I know.
>> Did she give you Did she give you Did
she give you Did she give you good [ __ ]
I'm not talking about my sex life, PJ.
>> No, it's just I It was just one
question, is it?
>> Yeah, but it's a question. Am I a good lick out?
>> You know what I mean? Question. It's
like, is it? Is she any good at giving
[ __ ] Am I any good at licking a woman out?
>> Well, yeah, you can answer, is it?
>> Oh, no. I'm not answering.
>> Maybe you didn't get a [ __ ] is it?
Yeah, of course. I got a [ __ ]
PJ, stop. Stop. Just stop.
>> Okay. Stop it now. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Because he is skin. Do you remember that
money? Because of your skin. It's true
though, is it?
>> I want to know how to [ __ ] work. I
can't even work this app.
But you trying to order food?
>> Yeah, I'm trying to order myself a [ __ ] kebab.
>> I thought you had no money. >> What?
>> [ __ ] it. I get mac and it
big mac. You go for it. I get a big mac meal. Um,
I got a large. Okay, I got a large.
I got chips. What's this?
>> No, I'm not putting my words this. I'm
not weirdos like you people in a Monty.
>> I'm I'm looking for the milkshake.
>> Cheese slice.
>> Cheese slices.
drink. Old drink. Uh,
I'm looking for the milkshakes. Me, lad.
There we go. Milkshakes.
Give myself a chocolate milkshake. Now
there see my trolley. I've done it.
There you go peeps.
Not showing you my Oh [ __ ] Not showing
me my location.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Come on. Come on.
>> I can't hold down a job. You've never
had a job. Stop talking about yourself.
You've been on benefits your whole life.
You've never had a job.
>> Looking good. Looking good.
She doesn't want you. Of course she wants money.
Yeah. Talking about yourself, buddy. You
never had a job.
Talking about yourself. [Music]
These people love talking about themselves.
I got fired. Bro, you never you've never
even had a job. You've been on benefit
your whole life.
>> Monty, I'm having problems with these projectors again.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yeah. They keep self-reflecting.
>> Oh, [ __ ] up, man. I sent my mom a takeaway.
It's not funny.
>> What the [ __ ]
>> Yeah, that's one month more than you.
>> Yeah, but
one sec. Huh?
>> Can you cancel it?
>> Uh, I don't think What What app is it on?
>> Just eat. >> Uh,
get refund. Yeah, you can. Yeah, you can
play and get a refund and then order it again.
How do I do that? >> Um,
let me see.
>> Hey, Jimmy. Hey. Hey, Dizzy. That's 1K a
month more than you. You're on 300 a
month, Skin Flint. It's 1K a month more than you.
Um, show me the app.
>> I'm on this bit.
>> Oh, [ __ ] hell. You're an idiot, man.
How the [ __ ] did you manage to do that?
>> Because I [ __ ] got my mom some
flowers from forward and I didn't
[ __ ] change my I'm I'm done. I'm
done. I'm not eating today again.
Just moving my mom up. One second. Just
tell her [ __ ] I [ __ ] up.
>> Just get a refund and then just order it.
>> You have to request a refund.
My mom. Oh, what the [ __ ]
To be fair, I've done it as well before.
>> Yeah, but I was thinking a [ __ ] pitch tick.
>> Jizzy, you don't even have £1,000 to
your name. That's how bad it is.
J, you don't even have a,000 quid to
your name, lad. Self reflector.
>> For [ __ ] sake, PJ, I'll be right back,
m. All right,
>> I [ __ ] up. You've got McDonald's on it way.
>> What's going on?
>> I [ __ ] ordered myself um ordered
myself um a McDonald's that >> Yeah.
But he's saying to No, I'm not saying
you got more money than you ever
>> I've got more money than you'd ever
have. So [ __ ]
>> more money than you'll ever have, mate.
I get more than 1K a month. And that's
1K a month. More than you. And I got
more money than you.
>> You don't even [ __ ] mean to do that.
>> You £300 a month.
>> It's when I sent you when they sent you flowers.
>> How can I cancel it? Counsel it? Well,
I'll have them delivered and I'll have
to send you all me this German.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I know. I know. This is
[ __ ] [ __ ] This
>> ow me
like 200 quid.
>> No, 200 sparing. Yeah, 200 quid
sparring. This is [ __ ] [ __ ] man. Mom,
just take your time and let me all over
the place, Mom. It's [ __ ] a mess. It's time right.
This is [ __ ] up. So yeah, just give
the kids some McDonald's or something
when he comes. I'll [ __ ] do what? For [ __ ] sake.
>> It's a big M chick and a [ __ ] chocolate milkshake.
>> It's all right. I'll get eaten. All
>> No, that's fine.
Then I ordered it and then then it says
you're checking on your delivery. Your
delivery has been completed getting sent
to number 19. >> Yeah. Did
>> No. No. I don't want Yeah. No [ __ ]
I'm going to do it on just [ __ ] Yeah.
Just wait till the McDonald's turns up
first. Yeah. Just wait till the
McDonald's turns up cuz I know it's
going to turn up to you.
>> Yep. And and I'll enjoy more money than
I have than you as well.
>> You own £300 a month.
>> Thank you. I'm I'm never doing this [ __ ] again.
I'm just going to go on [ __ ] change
the address now. It's when they sent you
that them flowers and um like
screaming. It's all right. >> Yeah.
>> When sent the kids that anyways, um I've
been spending um 20 quid over as well
for the kids spent as well. They got 20 quid each.
So, I'm going to give them 20 quid each
for spending money as well.
No, no, that's fine. So, I do that. So,
So, I'm going to give you one out of one
payment. 20 quid out of one payment
tomorrow. Sort it out sometime. Don't
worry about it.
>> Relax tonight.
>> Yeah, we'll do it. >> Chill.
>> Yeah, I will do. I've not for [ __ ] five days.
>> Yeah, I will do. I'll probably go out or
something for a walk or something. Don't
know what to do, Mom. To be honest,
>> gems of walls are something. It's good.
game is a wall.
>> Is it?
>> Yeah. Sheldon plays it. >> Okay.
You got to build up your characters and
that lot to win.
>> Start playing it. Come on.
>> Write this code down because you're
going to need this code.
>> Oh, for God's sake. Not this again.
>> Just write it down cuz he asked you for the cord.
>> The code is four.
>> So it's 43 or six. I tell you again. 436. >> Yeah.
>> Got it. That's the code.
Oh, in fact,
it's a woman
with Yeah. a skinny ass woman.
He's coming. I can see the picture of her now.
All right. Go on, Mom. I let you go.
Wait. It's on its way to you now. Oh,
hang on. All right.
Let me see where this is.
>> Jeremy, just delete my address off it, please.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I am. Yeah, I am. It's
coming to you. Yeah, I am. 4 minutes away.
I'm so sorry, Mom. You got a McDonald way.
>> Me too. I'll see you later. I'm so sorry.
>> It's all right. Stop.
>> I'm going to stay here. It's nearly to
you. It's on that. Um, it's just coming.
It's just turning the corner down.
>> See you later. Yeah.
>> Anyways, see you in a bit. Byebye.
>> See you later. Byebye.
>> Where's PJ got off to?
Yo, peeps. Can all you stop talking
about N of the Yeah.
And that is including Lisa as well.
Go back onto McDonald's. Hey, where are you?
Let's see if this is going back in my
bank cuz my mom says she's going to put
some money in my bank again. We're unlock.
It just said takeaways arrived being delivered.
Right. Right. Okay.
Time to go again.
Right. Go on to that.
How do you make a woman forgive you,
man? That's what I want to know, man.
How do you make a woman forgive me, man?
I'm trying everything, peeps. Literally,
you know, I'm [ __ ] trying everything.
I'm a good lad. I am I am actually a
good lad. I'm not a prick,
but I can be a prick. But sometimes I
don't mean to be a prick.
Sometimes I don't mean to do things.
Sometimes I react without thinking.
And that's just [ __ ] thick as [ __ ] on my behalf.
That's something what I need to stop
doing as well.
But just to let you all know that
Natalie, she's my [ __ ] angel, peep.
She's my angel. I will never ever ever
troll or call Natalie ever again. Never
again like I did like like I used to do
back in the day. I will never do that [ __ ] again.
cuz I found out what kind of woman that
is and she's a [ __ ] I need to stop
myself to stop Jimmy Stingle Burger.
Where's PJ got off to? Anyways,
I'm just looking for the big max. I
can't even find it.
Okay, I just got one of these
>> large fries.
>> Yeah, I want large fries.
>> Own side salad 77 kilo jewels, 18 kilo calories.
>> Cucumber bag. Cucumber bag.
>> Melon chunks. 73 kiloj 17 kilo calories.
O green apple egg Sprite.
Mango passion fruit X Sprite.
Organic semi-kmmed milk 524 kilojoules
125 kilo calories.
Let's just go back on state and change the address.
This is just hanging peeps hanging.
You must have got the wrong address, you [ __ ]
This is why I need help, peeps.
This is why I need a good woman in my
life, cuz I'm just a fake bastard.
How do I change addresses?
You know what I mean? I don't even know,
>> bro. [ __ ] DCD.
>> What do you mean? He
>> My internet's [ __ ] bro.
>> Is it?
>> Yeah. Do you know? Do you owe your mom 200?
>> Yeah, I 200 quid. Yeah.
>> Oh, okay.
>> Not bad. I've got the money anyways.
How much do you have?
>> You know, Natalie knows how much I come out with.
>> No, no, no. But how much do you have
like right now?
>> All right. Not a lot on me now. Okay.
I'll do a work PG Big Mac meal. >> Huh?
>> I'm just going to do this. [ __ ] it. Grab that.
Let's see what these are.
>> Fries. Yeah.
Get a last fries. What's this?
>> Apple X Sprite. 27 kiloj 6 kilo calories.
>> Where's the CX man?
>> Upgrade large vanilla.
>> Upgrade large banana milkshake. What the
[ __ ] are you on? >> McDonald's.
>> You're a mad [ __ ] You
>> upgrade. Large chocolate milkshake.
>> Yeah, large chocolate milkshake. >> 828. >> Bless kilo.
>> Hey again.
>> Bless you.
>> I'll just pie.
Why do these people keep saying skin? It's boring. Just skin.
>> Yeah, they need to stop saying it. We
know they're skin, bro. I'm saying. >> Huh? >> What?
know they're skin. Is it? >> Yeah.
>> Cuz why are they watching us on a Monty?
Listen. Listen. What's the day today? Friday.
>> Friday. Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, think about it. If they
weren't skin, they would be out, wouldn't they?
>> They'd be out. Yeah, they'd be out.
>> Yay. Finally, we got us some work.
>> That must mean these people are skinned, isn't it?
It says skin.
Yeah, I'm not out because I'm chilling
today, bro. I'm taking a break and I'm
saving for my holiday that book. So, I
mean, [ __ ] that's why I'm not out.
I'll just kill him.
>> There you go. My order is being sorted.
>> Done. Dusted. Dusted. Done and dusted.
Just waiting for that now.
>> Monty man's rich.
>> Oh, it's the McDonald's me and Natalie
went to his around the corner with that
one as well.
Monty watches KSI. >> KSI?
>> No, I want speed. I watch speed.
>> No, you watch KSI. >> Speed.
>> Yeah, same thing.
>> PSI is not the same thing.
KSI is a different person. K's
eye is uh
he's got a big big massive forehead.
He's got a big forehead.
>> Yeah. You watch him in it?
>> Yeah, I watch him. Yeah.
He had Paul the fight in the boxing.
>> Yeah. KSI's skin, isn't it?
>> KSI is not skin. You're mad.
>> Yeah, he is.
>> Is he [ __ ] skin? None of these. Listen,
they're proper ass YouTubers. They are
they are proper prop they like we're
like me. I I can be like a proper
YouTuber cuz like them only what you do
is ignore the comments and just do what you're doing
and that's what you do. You ignore the comments.
>> Yeah. These people obsessed with skin.
These people this community are obsessed
with skin is in it. Yeah. Yeah.
>> That's all they say in it, bro.
>> You're scared.
>> Yeah. Get a job.
>> Will they ever stop saying it? Like,
Monty, not to be not to be rude. Yeah.
I'm asking a serious question. Are they disabled?
>> Yeah, they are dis
they just got bullied in school. >> Yeah.
It just makes perfect sense. So I would
be on YouTube doing it. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. But you like YouTube. >> No.
>> Franklin's on his little phone.
I like Franklin on GTA Monty. It's good, is it?
>> You don't like Trevor? No,
>> I like Franklin.
You like Uncle Lester? You
>> You all right? Franklin.
>> Not Uncle Le. No. >> Nah.
>> Why not?
>> No. You have an old man at the cinema.
I want to take Natalie out for a meal somewhere.
I want to take you out for a meal. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Birmingham must have some nice
curry houses. We can go to a nice curry house.
>> The worst thing is I'm sick of look
walking out me and seeing all the
Asians. Man, there's too many Asians.
>> I swear we can fool you. I
>> [ __ ] spot the white over here. Spot
the white man. What the mean?
>> Yeah, Manchester is the same.
>> No, not not not as worse as Birmingham.
>> No, Bing is bad for it, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> You've never been to Sheffield, is it? >> What?
>> You've never been to Sheffield, have you?
>> Yeah, I've been I've been I've been all over PGA. Shepherd PGA.
>> I'll fit in. No. Why would I fit in? I'm white.
>> You can't eat.
>> Well, you know you're not allowed to.
You're not supposed to be eating
McDonald's, Monty. You know that. >> Why?
>> Because it's not um It's not halal.
>> Well, I'm not allowed.
>> It's not allowed, bro.
>> I'm not a pedo. I'm not allah. I'm not a pedo, mate.
>> You're [ __ ] Yo. Oh, [ __ ] son.
>> You remember that old man in love with you, Monty?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I remember that old man who
was in love with me.
>> You never forget it, is it?
>> No, I never forget it. It never never
[ __ ] that were weird. That was your
fault. Like you introduced Yeah, but you
know, you liked it.
No, it's not. It's not even that. Yeah.
I don't I don't know. But PJ, every time
I go out or something Yeah. or if I go
live on any kind of social media, I
always get fooled by gay men.
>> Yeah. Cuz you're good-looking. They they
think you're good-looking, is it? I I
was I was like I was like I think it was
not yesterday the day before because I
was angry and that cuz me and Natalie
what happened with me and I went on meet
not not to [ __ ] meet anyone or not
today I never do that on that again but
I went on there next minute this gay man
this gay man joined my house I let him
up for talking that and he was like
proper flirting with me and all that.
Look, he's asking me for my WhatsApp and
that. I said I'm not I'm not gay.
>> All right, let's everyone Yeah. Hold on.
Let's everyone vote. What's the best
GTA? I'm going San Andreas. What? What?
What is everyone saying?
>> I might as well go get PJ want to be my boyfriend.
>> Nah, that's GTA. I think San Andreas.
What do you think, everyone?
I'm going San Andreas.
>> No, but and when me and Natalie had the
hotel. Yeah. In Birmingham. Me and
Natalie got the hotel in Birmingham. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Lots of people say four. Lots of
That's with Nico, is it? A lot of people
say four is good. Money.
>> Me and Natalie got a hotel in Birmingham
when we first met each other. Yeah.
Okay. And I went down the elevator to go
and get some of them little cans of milk
so we could have a brew. Went down in
the ele. This man was asking me bare
questions. I mean you on my own. What am
I doing? I know.
>> I ain't played Vice City in [ __ ]
years, man. I used to play on PSP, but I
think San Andreas is the best because
there's some good glitches on that game.
I watch some shorts. Even to this day,
they're still milking that game. It's
just a funny game. or GTA.
>> Yeah, San Andreas is my favorite, but a
lot of people for
>> I know every single glitch on GTA 5.
>> You don't know any of the San Andreas?
>> Yes, I do.
>> Okay, which one then?
>> Which one is San Andreas?
>> Is that number five?
>> No, it's just called San Andreas.
I need to find out which one that one is
and I can tell you then one sec is a old school man.
>> So is that a old school one? Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, okay. So
this is Have you done the car glitch?
>> Could done. Could one second. I'll show
you one. Hold on.
One second. One here. You like it
though, is it? I like
>> you like YouTube.
>> You like YouTube? >> Yeah.
>> I don't like YouTube. I'm already here
cuz I don't have no one talk to and I
don't want to
keep harassing Natalie. You know what?
>> Do you like Monty? Do you like Ed Sheeran?
>> Ed Sheeran's all right.
>> How do you know who he is?
>> Ginger. He was armless in Manchester or
London or whatever one where was homeless. >> Cheering. >> Yeah.
And she was homeless.
>> You remind me of Frank G. You remind me
of Frank Gallagher, bro.
One second, bro.
Ask him where that is. She's not in
Lisa. She's She must be in Muhammad's shop. O.
>> Yo, start kicking people if you start
taking a pitch like that, PJ. Yeah. >> Okay.
>> I'm not being funny, but Natalie does
not like Asians anymore. She [ __ ]
can't stand them. She hates Asians.
They can't She can't stand them.
Absolutely can't stand them anymore. >> Really?
>> Yeah. No. No. Yeah. No. She don't like
them anymore. She looking at them.
>> She's been with some it.
It's got nothing to do with me. you now
he's dated or whatever. I don't [ __ ]
been with or dated.
>> All what I know is that she's playing
and that say I'm good. >> Yeah.
You know that one that I met that was
from America. Did you think she was good-looking?
>> I've never saw her.
>> I think you did. No.
I think the women don't like blocks over
there to be honest.
>> Yeah, they're [ __ ] fat it.
>> We don't like blocks in America. That's
why all American women fancy the British men. >> Yeah,
>> a British man can pull American bird
like [ __ ] cheese on [ __ ] butter.
>> America's so big though, Monty, ain't
it? Yeah, it's massive.
>> Where would you even start?
Think about where would you even start
if there's 51 states? Yeah, some of the
states are bigger than the whole of
Europe. Where would you even start? You know, madness.
I remember when I used to speak to you
on PlayStation, Monty, your plan was
always to go to America, wasn't it?
>> Yeah. No, not America.
Um, it was go to [ __ ] Australia to
make that Australian.
>> No, you wanted to go to America to see
all the states.
>> No, no, I've never I don't want to
>> I don't want to go to America. It's just
It's another [ __ ] England.
>> All westernized, isn't it? No good, bro.
It's no good. Oh,
>> you get shot over there.
>> Yeah, but you always wanted to go there. Right.
I'm going to stop talking about that in a way. Me too.
>> Do you know what you should do today, Monty?
>> I'll tell you what to do, Monty. Yeah.
Do you know how you really get her back?
I'll be honest with you.
>> Go out today in Birmingham, right? Have
a few drinks, right? Pull another bird
and show her. That will show her who's
boss. Trust me,
>> listen to me.
>> I'm not that kind of man to go out to
[ __ ] a woman over like
>> No, not [ __ ] her. Not [ __ ] her, but not
[ __ ] No, no, not [ __ ] another woman.
Just go out and socialize and just like
meet someone else. Like, not not [ __ ]
I'm not saying
>> I'm not even I'm not even meeting anyone
else. I don't need anyone else. I don't
need to talk to anyone else. I don't
need anyone else.
You know, only one person. I do need is
>> that would show her who's boss though is it?
>> It's not whose boss.
>> There's no boss.
>> There's no boss in this relationship.
I'm not the boss. She's not the boss.
That's where arguments start coming into
place by over controlling each other.
You There's no bosses in relationship.
You're both equal in a relationship.
>> If I if I what if I come to Birmingham
tonight, will you come out with me?
>> Yeah, I'll come out with you. Yeah. What? Drinking?
>> Yeah. If you come out tonight, I come
drinking with you. Of course I would. >> Really?
>> Yeah. Really? Of course I would. If you Of course.
I go out drinking with you. I ain't got
nothing else to do.
>> Would you do it tomorrow as well?
>> Come on. Come then. Come now. You're in
my bed. Let's go out.
>> Would you come? Would you come tomorrow as well?
>> Yeah, we go out tonight and tomorrow.
It's Friday night. Let's go, PJ. Let's
go, man. I get Where where where where
am I going to stay? >> Here.
>> Well, with you. >> Yeah.
>> Well, at your house.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Okay. I'll come tomorrow 100%. Yeah.
>> Oh, okay. Okay.
>> Okay. I'll come tomorrow cuz I I'll get
my haircut tomorrow. And I'll come tomorrow then.
>> Why not tonight?
>> Because, bro, I need to get my haircut
and [ __ ] bro. It's [ __ ] almost 20 tonight.
>> Yeah. You look better with your hair,
PJ. You look better with it.
>> No, I got a long beard, bro. I'll come tomorrow% off.
>> Shave your beard off and get get down here now.
>> Yeah, I'm coming tomorrow 100%. Hold me
to it. Yeah.
>> Hold you to it. Yeah. Okay. My takeway
so you know. Anyways.
>> Yeah. There you go.
>> We'll show them who's boss. Monty in it. >> What?
>> We'll show them who's boss. I'll take
you to a place. money. Yeah. I'll take
you to a place where there's loads of
18y olds and stuff. 19y olds.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no. I'm out. I'm
out. You can stay in [ __ ] You can
stay where you are.
>> No. They're like students.
>> No. Too young for me, man. Too young. I
don't know. [ __ ] 18y olds. [ __ ] off, man.
>> No, I'm only joking. I'm only joking. >> Yeah.
Oh, Franklin got Franklin's got his
little phone out. >> Franklin died.
>> Thank you, buddy.
>> Yeah, I was I in Birmingham in ages, man.
I went on a date with someone from
Birmingham. She was the right m though. Right m
Got my mack meat buddy.
>> God bless you then.
>> I paid I paid for getting my mom
McDonald's as well. >> Yeah,
>> I got my mom a mad as well.
>> Oh, bless.
>> Bless your Monte.
>> I might get Natalie one now. I might
send Natalie a take away.
>> Send me one. Then you
>> send me one, man. >> Yeah. >> No.
>> Too much, PJ. Too much.
>> Imagine me, you and Timmy out on the pool tomorrow.
>> No, we're not meeting Timmy, bro. We're
not meeting Timmy.
>> Listen, Greavves. You I'm I'm Frank's on
his little phone. He's in the fan on his
little mobile. Bless him. Little Franklin. Franklin's cute.
Yeah, Franklin's a cute [ __ ]
Little Franklin with his little black
hands. Bless him. Huh?
[ __ ] it. No. Now.
money. It's now or never. You know what that means?
>> Yeah, it's now or never.
>> It means we rather do something now or
never do it. >> Basically. >> Yeah.
>> It's rather let's go and rob like car or
not rob it.
>> Give it a while it. I would. [ __ ] it.
Yeah, I'm on Xbox Live. I'm on Xbox
>> I had to get myself a large, man.
>> I tell you what though, Xbox controller
is better than the PS um the PlayStation
one. 100%. The Xbox controller is
better. I think
>> you have to agree on that one, Rick
Grey. And I've always been PlayStation.
I don't even know why I bought Xbox. I
just was uh Yeah.
>> Natalie likes his TV. I got her, man.
It's not my TV. I don't want to
>> Monty likes it.
>> Yeah. She might give you some loving.
>> No, I've actually got a brand new ass
TV. No second line, no [ __ ] no [ __ ] all that.
>> You're not asked about You're not asked
about sex anymore, are you? >> Nah.
>> No, not really. Why?
>> Just wondering.
I've kind of lost my sex drive. Don't forget,
>> don't forget I've been with loads of
women and I saw
>> Yeah. Get boring, is it?
>> No, it don't get boring. Sex doesn't get
>> But you just you just prefer [ __ ] is it? No,
it's not mine. Whatever. No,
>> we usually likes a [ __ ]
>> You like your blood jokes, KJS?
>> Yeah, I used to love them, but now I'm
getting more into sex again.
>> I used to just get [ __ ] I never
used to bother with the sex.
I'm [ __ ] in bed, mate.
>> I'm proper [ __ ] in bed.
>> Oh, just Black Ops 2 is full of camping [ __ ]
>> But what you playing on Xbox?
>> Yeah, man.
[ __ ] full of camping [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> Guess what I'm getting? Have a guess. >> What?
>> I'm getting a PlayStation 3. >> Why?
What the [ __ ] They've just spawned me
somewhere where someone just killed me.
Ruby, that doesn't make any sense, does it?
>> What do you play with with Green Speed?
>> I'm playing with Xbox One, but it's Xbox
360 version cuz I bought on the store
and I love Black Ops 2. It brings back
like memories, you know. >> Yeah,
>> I love Black Ops 2, man. I used to play
it all the time
when I was a child. Look, they've just
spawned me somewhere and I just got killed again.
>> I'm missing Natalie, man.
>> I'm missing you.
>> I always think to myself, does anybody
ever miss me? And he like, you know what
I mean? Like, [ __ ] no.
>> No one misses. Oh, some [ __ ] just tried
to shoot me from behind. Dirty [ __ ]
[ __ ] so many campers on this game, is it? >> Yep.
Why? Campers, isn't it?
N is your mama.
>> Okay, I'm going to ask my mom if I can
go back up there.
>> So, is it full of tampers?
>> Well, can ask my mom if there is. >> Why?
because I've got nobody in Birmingham.
Give me a second in Minga. [ __ ]
>> Oh [ __ ]
>> I'm I'm bad at Call of Duty. I can't
lie. Well, actually, I'm I'm not too bad.
You know what game I used to hate? FIFA.
Oh, mate. I used to hate that FIFA, bro.
I used to hate that FIFA. I can't lie,
bro. That used to trigger the [ __ ] out of me.
go on WhatsApp.
>> I need to go back there anyways because
I I ain't got nobody in Birmingham anymore. So,
>> I'm trying to kill this [ __ ] bro.
>> One sec.
>> Someone's going to go up there and try
and kill me in it. >> Hello.
>> I go back [ __ ] where I went before.
do it all without and everybody knowing
Jeremy that's the thing I Oh that's
that's fine that's fine not that I've
got nobody in Birmingham and not getting
the help I need either so
>> I come back
>> did you [ __ ] tell
>> no I'm I'm getting I get that I get that and anybody.
>> Yeah. No, that's fine.
What she say?
This YouTube has caused a lot of [ __ ]
for you. Is it Ronnie? [ __ ] camping.
You camping [ __ ]
So many camping [ __ ] on here, Grezy.
So many camping [ __ ] on this game. What the [ __ ]
There's some people in here. They They
haven't even got one kill yet.
Why do they keep spawning me somewhere?
I'm just getting killed as soon as I respawned. Dirty cab.
Oh, by myself now.
The worst game is FIFA, though. For
real. For real.
I hate FIFA, bro.
[ __ ] This game is annoying, bro. I hate it.
They keep respawning me places and I
just keep dying.
Yes, cuz I've got four of the [ __ ] on
me, bro. I got four of the [ __ ] on me.
Greaves his favorite DJ San Andreas.
Look, there's one of me. Yeah, there's
two of me and there's like six of them.
Nah, GTA San Andreas. I can I send you
something quickly, Grezy? Second. What's Nothing.
This makes me laugh, bro. What's this music? What's that?
>> That is so funny, bro.
>> I love San Andreas.
>> Yeah, I'm
I'm allowed to go back up. So, I'm going
to go back up north back near my
>> What did your mother say? Just don't go
on YouTube. Is it?
>> Yeah. And she said, "If you're going to
come back up here and and live up back
back up here again, just don't go back
on YouTube." I ain't got no one.
You know what I do? >> What?
>> You got Timmy? >> No.
So, yeah. So, I know now I'm going back.
>> Well, you living with your mom?
>> No, I'm not going to go living with my mom. No. >> Okay.
I'm not going yet though. So you still
can come tomorrow.
>> I'm coming. Yeah, I'm coming tomorrow.
>> Oh yeah, I'm going back.
>> It's funny. It agrees. He He hit him
with a bat and then he tried to save him.
>> What? Watch you with a bat.
>> I'll send it. Can you watch it on I'm
going to send it to you on Facebook
here, Monty? I'm going to make you laugh.
Yeah. I'm going Birmingham tomorrow to
meet Monty. We got to go in the pool together.
>> Well, I'm I'm moving again, peeps. I'm
going to be moving again now. I'm not
going to be I'm not going to be living
in Birmingham nor.
I'm going to go back up.
Well, I used to live, but I'm not
qu Facebook, bro. It's like 20 seconds
and tell me tell me what you think.
>> Wait, is Facebook did you send it? Me got two.
>> Both of them. Both. Both both of them.
>> On both of them. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> You have got two [ __ ] Facebooks, my
>> Yeah, I got I sent it to both.
>> I'm watching it. I don't watch sometimes the gear.
>> We [ __ ] hit him and then saved him.
Greasy. Does that make sense? Does it? No.
I love the little characters, me.
>> Oh, yeah. I've seen it. I've seen it.
>> So, what is it then?
>> It's a [ __ ] It's the oldest GT where
you can go out to drive drive the
ambulances and then survive. Who have a
bat? Let me watch the video. Keep watching it.
Yeah, pimp. You won't have my address anymore.
What? What? What's
revived the victims and drove off, but
just a few seconds later, they parked
next to a random house. The doctor got
out and just started walking down the
street. Okay, so I tried again. This
time, the ambulance drove in circles
like crazy, crashing into everything.
Then it stopped at a red light and hit a
random car. The doctor grabbed a
baseball bat and went after the
pedestrian. He beat the guy down,
casually got back into the ambulance,
then immediately got out again just to
revive him like it was part of the
treatment. And after all that, he stuck
at the red light forever. Would you try
following one in your game? Let me know
what happened when you tried. What
happens if you
>> funny? Did that make you laugh?
>> No, not really. Did you get it? Did you
>> Yeah, I bet you I can make you laugh, PJ.
>> Yeah, but did you get it though?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I got it. W the baseball
bat, jump back into the ambulance, jump
back out and find him.
>> I mean, that makes sense, does it? >> No. It doesn't.
>> So, we got to go on the pool tomorrow.
I'm not going on no pull. I help you get
pulled. I'm not pulling.
>> I'll help you. I'll help you as well.
>> I've been telling the woman to [ __ ] off.
Trust me, there's only one woman I [ __ ] love.
And you know what? I've never felt like
this for any woman in my life. Even
though I was with Kaye for 10 years, I
felt nothing for her.
>> Literally nothing. I'm being
>> you just you just liked Kaye for the sex isn't it?
>> I I think no to be honest with you it
will play. I just wanted to go live by the sea.
>> So that's why I got with with Kay
because I wanted to go by the seaside.
>> God bless you.
>> So that's why I got with Kay. I didn't
even fancy it to be honest with you.
>> Well, you had kids with her so you must have.
>> I always wanted kids law. PG. That's why. >> Yeah.
>> No, we got him.
Franklin, stop putting your middle
finger up. It's rude. >> Yeah.
You still there? >> Yeah.
It is weird though, is it?
>> It is. Yeah.
>> This community is weird.
>> So why did you always want kids then?
I've never wanted them. Me.
>> Always wanted them. Every woman I've sp
with, I've never got pregnant. I've
always thought I had something wrong
with me until I got
>> PJ. PJ Monty. Dumb and dumber. Oh, just
talking about yourself. I'm not even
going to block them. I'm not even
blocking I'm not even blocking them.
>> No blocking. Leave them to write [ __ ]
>> Let them embarrass themselves in it.
>> Let them embarrass themselves.
>> Yeah, let them talk about themselves.
>> they just talk about themselves.
>> Well, you do realize it's like the same
three people. You do realize that behind
like different accounts.
>> Yeah, of course. [ __ ] idiots got
nothing going for themselves when they
on YouTube calling people and they don't know.
Yeah, I'm going to come and see you tomorrow.
>> I need a friend, PJ. I need a friend.
>> Yeah, man.
>> Are you a friend who does everybody
over, you [ __ ]
>> No, you don't me over, you bastard. with that traumador. >> When? >> Huh?
>> Couple years back.
>> What did you do?
>> You know what you done?
>> You know what you done, bro? Joining Discord.
>> I'm not a troll. TJ,
>> you [ __ ] are.
>> I'm not at all. >> Yeah,
>> I'm a good
You live near the train station? Yeah,
you you come and meet me at the train
station. No, I'll just be at the Weather
Spoons. I'll meet you in the Weather
Spoons. I'll tell you which Weather
Spoons I'm at. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that's fine.
>> I'll be in the city center.
>> You might as well come where I am. This
Weather Spoons here where I am. Yeah,
>> You're you're in a [ __ ] black
country. [ __ ] that.
>> It's all that.
>> No, we're going we're going to city
center of Birmingham, isn't it?
>> Yeah, city center is still basically that.
Oh, but Birmingham's like that, you mad.
>> No, but we're going to go out of the city center.
Wait, how far you from the city center?
How far am I from the city center? >> Yeah.
>> How far?
>> Don't know.
I can't believe I quit. Weed, man.
>> We can get an Uber back. It's fine.
>> Lad's night out tomorrow. It's It's PJ
>> and Tim Timmy's welcome to join if he
wants as well. Timmy can join.
But in the where he sits.
>> Yeah. Yeah. If he tries Hey, Monty. If
he tries to p up tomorrow, we'll [ __ ] him up.
>> Simple. Yeah. We will [ __ ] him all up if
they if they stop. Yeah. >> Burger.
Look at that sexy burger. PJ,
>> we won't take no L's. And I'll be
calling that prime as well. He tries.
>> Look at that. That's banging.
>> We end up getting battered, won't he?
Let's put it in a light. Look at how
[ __ ] fat that is. >> Yeah.
>> Burger in it. It's got some
>> part two. Return of the spastics. I am more [ __ ]
>> Stop calling yourselves.
Oh, where we meet? So, hey, Timmy, don't
try to get involved. I'll I'll beat you up
like last time.
That means the battery is >> Yeah.
If I go out tomorrow, we can go out
Saturday and Sunday, Monty. And I'll
just go home on a Monday. It's fine, is it?
>> You want?
>> Yeah, if you want.
>> We can just spend a weekend together.
>> Timmy. Timmy wants a link. Okay.
>> Give him a link.
>> Yeah. He's a [ __ ] idiot, isn't it?
But he's I don't know how you laugh at Timmy.
>> He's irrelevant to me this lad. [Laughter]
>> He doesn't stop, does he? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I need to ring some places up
tomorrow to try and get back to
Nottingham to I need to try and ring
some places up to see if we can get a a
route over my head.
>> Okay. All right. No talking over each
other, please. Yeah. No talking over, right?
>> Go on.
>> I'm going to Birmingham tomorrow.
>> Good. What part? So I can meet you.
>> I'm going to beat the crap out of you. Mongol
Mongol. I'm going to meet you, >> Timmy.
>> Why can't everybody just play nice?
>> Why are you going to McDonald's? I can
meet you. What? Why are you going?
>> Why can't we all just play nice? Everyone
>> in it McDonald's.
>> Why doesn't everybody just play nice?
>> I hate a nons.
You give [ __ ] alcohol to kids on a
bus, Jimmy. What the [ __ ]
>> Nobody wants to play nice. Bring out teenagers
picking lad. You're the one. Okay.
I'll meet you now. I will meet you now.
>> Meeting you now. [ __ ]
>> Exactly. Exactly. You have a [ __ ]
>> The camera with your mouth. Timmy. Look.
>> Come to Rusty. You [ __ ] [ __ ] bad.
Come to Rusty. You piece of [ __ ]
What the [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> You are a
>> piece of [ __ ] That doesn't even make sense. Timothy,
>> go do some press ups, nonstop.
>> Go do some press ups, you [ __ ] nons.
See what I mean?
>> PJ, why are you having this [ __ ] nons
in your life?
>> He's my mate.
Nobody likes him apart from
everyone that there's
>> see any press ups you can dark you
[ __ ] clumsy [ __ ]
>> [ __ ] you you fat [ __ ]
>> Why don't you meet me in Worcester right
now at the
>> Why don't you meet me now? Where's Ro?
>> I'm going to meet you cuz you're a
[ __ ] little [ __ ] back.
>> Is that in Birmingham? Is it in
>> Scared, aren't you, [ __ ]
>> No. Is it in Birmingham? So why didn't
you answer the door when I come around your flats?
>> You've never been to this house. You
>> come around your flat, Mongol. I've got
the evidence. Monging up.
>> I don't want to put it up now. Mongol
cuz it's giving you got the evidence.
I have got it. Mongol
panic Mongol. So I can catch panicking his voice.
>> I'm not panicking. Mongol can't tell the
truth. Can you Mongol?
>> I am telling the truth. So, where are
you now, Timmy?
>> I've got the evidence, [ __ ] I've got
>> All right, then. Listen,
>> listen. You just offered me out a fight. Yeah,
>> I knocked your door and you
>> So, where do you want me to go to?
>> Where do you want me to go meet you now? >> Buster,
>> where's that Timmy? Timmy, do you know
what? One second. One second. Yeah.
Timmy, do you know why
>> you go? You get out train station, go
left, you go past McDonald's
straight up, then you take a voice.
There's a few shots. Is it in
Birmingham? Is it Is it in Birmingham? >> No.
>> This is why I stopped talking to Timmy
because he thinks everything's not in
Birmingham. Timmy, get in Birmingham.
You suck yourself.
>> Why can't you
wait? Wait till I meet you. Money m
>> scared of me, aren't you?
>> Oh my god.
>> Jimmy, you've been up everybody on
YouTube. Why don't you come here? You [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> I'll see you tomorrow.
What the [ __ ] He doesn't even talk properly. It
>> [ __ ] big his bastard going.
>> Yeah. I stop talking to um himo cuz he
finds the gambling thing funny.
That's why I don't He He thinks it's all
funny. He's immature.
>> He's [ __ ] telling him he'd go and
meet him when he's in Birmingham in
totally different towns and
is some sad man or something.
>> [ __ ] hell tomorrow anyways.
>> No, he won't turn up anyways. He's a [ __ ] bag. Yeah, it's sh.
>> I don't know why I don't know why
everyone just can't play nice.
>> It's not a nice community, is it?
>> It's full of spastics, is it?
>> I don't even want to come live anymore
to be honest with you.
>> Why is I don't have no one to talk to. I'm alone.
What's the main reason you don't What's
the main reason you don't want to um go
live anymore? Same people in it.
>> Yeah, it's same people. And it's just to
respect Natalie in it as well. >> Yeah.
>> I want to respect Natalie. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? That's what I want
to do. I want to at least respect that woman.
The respect she deserves.
>> Oh, [ __ ]
You like her, don't you, Monty? >> Yeah.
When was you last in the city center of Birmingham? >> What?
>> When was you last in the city center of Birmingham?
>> Last time. I don't know when the last
time I went to city center
last time I went there is when I met
Natalie and that in Birmingham. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, okay. Yeah. Then in and out on
trains and that to go up back up country.
>> These batteries I put is dodgy. I have
to use batteries for the Xbox
controller. Um, they're [ __ ] dodgy
these ones. I need to buy new ones. They
keep putting out every [ __ ] 6 hours
having to change them.
>> I don't get I don't get that. Like with
the PS4 controllers, the PS3
controllers, you always just put them on charge.
>> But you can charge this one as well. If
you get an adapter, you can you can charge them.
>> I hate it. It's annoying.
>> I really can't eat. I'm picking. I'm pick eating.
>> God bless you.
>> Literally pick eating. Look, I [ __ ]
>> That's what happens when you're in the bar.
>> Oh, they took like a little bite of my
burger. [ __ ] left it. My chips are swips as well.
>> That's unlike me. I don't I don't do
that. I've always at a full meal. Always.
>> Yeah. You
That's because you're in love. Bless you.
>> I am in love, man. I [ __ ] am. But if
they haven't got anyone in Birmingham,
I'm going to have to go back to workshop.
I'm going to have to go back up there.
>> I just I just prefer KFC, Greasy, to be
honest, the McDonald's, I have to say.
>> So, I might as well go back to workshop
if you ain't got no one in Birmingham.
I'm never ever coming back to Birmingham
if I go if I go back up north
cuz I need I need people, PG. I need people.
>> You've got me. I'm your friend.
>> No, no. You dead.
You're always in like with me kind of thing. >> Yeah.
>> I've never been alone before, buddy.
I've never been alone. I've never ever
ever been alone alive.
>> To be honest though, can I ask you a serious question?
>> Who? Me?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Go for it.
>> Was K good in bed?
>> Yeah, there was [ __ ] in bed.
>> Fair enough.
>> No, it's w that good in bed.
>> You like to?
>> No, not really. Not when not when they
just lie there like ironing board.
>> What the [ __ ] What?
>> You I remember on PlayStation you used
to do anything to get your little pecker wet it.
>> I'm not like that anymore though.
>> No, not anymore. But you used to it.
>> Uh yeah, I was only young back then. Low
was only young. >> Yeah.
>> About as you in my 20ies.
>> Yeah. You do anything for bit. You do
anything for a bit of puss it. But I was
younger than you. How old are you now? 28?
>> No, 27.
>> Oh, yeah. I was 25 when I first met
Kelly and that I was only
You know, the funny thing is Yeah. is that uh
when I messaged that Aaron Cox, he he
blocks me, you know.
>> He blocks Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> What? On Facebook or YouTube?
>> Everything. Facebook, Instagram.
Aaron C. I remember he was he was an it.
>> Yeah. I remember that birdie we we went out with.
>> Yeah. She come from Spain is it?
>> Come from Spain. He robbed all the money
off her. Robbed every single bit of her
money and [ __ ] [ __ ] her off. >> Yeah.
>> Then she ended up getting with one of
his mates and getting pregnant.
>> And he used to he he used to lie that he
worked. Do you remember
>> what? He used to lie. He never worked.
You know that he was just lying.
>> Yeah, I know. I know. He's never worked. No,
>> he was a He was an online key gangster in it.
>> Yeah. I thought he were a gangster.
>> You know what? I'm not calling money a
nons. Why am I doing that?
>> You people are nons. All what you people
do is talk about nons. And you people
actually fancy pedophiles.
You people actually fancy the [ __ ] out
of pedos cuz only what you talk about is pedophiles.
I am nowhere near near a [ __ ] a
pedophile. I have never dated anybody
younger than me. Only the person I've
dated younger than me is actually Kaye
and that's it.
No one else. That's the youngest person
about Ollie being out with Kayie. And I
got with Kay when she was 17.
These people that call you a nonst
project in it.
>> Yeah. Tell them to Google me. Google me you [ __ ]
>> Ain't it you calling me a nunch? Google
me. If I be if I was a nunch I'd be all
over the Google by the police. I'll be
all over the police websites. Not
YouTube or Facebook. It
>> would never stop there, would it? No, >> never [Music] to fat.
>> You know what?
>> You know what, PJ? I need a woman who
don't run off when it gets hard. >> Yeah,
>> that's what I need. I need a woman who
doesn't run off when [ __ ] gets hard.
>> Good luck with that because they're all cowards.
>> It's funny cuz men are different to
women. Men always forgive a woman. A man
will always forgive a woman. Always.
But a woman will never forgive a man.
I agree with you. Are you still there?
So, when I'm plugging my char my
controller in the charger, the Samson
charger, it seems to stay on. >> Um,
>> this [ __ ] man.
>> When I use my Samsung charger, it
doesn't seem to die when I use a Samsung
charger on the controller. Um, Grezy,
interesting, isn't it?
Maybe that works, huh? Who knows?
What time you going live? Um, you cook.
Why would K call him an N? I don't know.
>> Because she's a [ __ ] prick.
Hay is a pedophile lover.
Kayie fancies the [ __ ] out of the
pedophiles who targeted her kids. Pretty
funny that ain't it?
Now she talks to Fel 420, a man who had
pictures up on a wall saying, "Oh,
I never forget, but I never forgive
him." But you and then putting it like,
"Fuck off. I will never forgive anybody
putting pictures up my kids and never
talk to him again. Never."
Obviously PJ has done it, but that's
different. DJ's apologized.
>> These people are just repeated.
>> Yeah, of course. Cuz they're repeaters.
That's what they do is repeat. They
bring people up like Kick
because they single themselves. These
people had a [ __ ] bird. This is why
they put people as pedophiles cuz they
these people who talk about pedophiles
and put people up as pedophiles. They
are the pedophiles.
They're the ones who are probably all
over the [ __ ] Google and they're
sitting there calling you the N. >> Yeah.
>> I want I want to know what makes me a N. >> Yeah.
>> Kay bullies me. Kayie bullies me.
That's what Kayie does. Kayie
She bullies the [ __ ] out of me. She
calls me to [ __ ]
And that's what Kayie does.
If a woman loves a man like Natalie, I
think Natalie does love me because
Natalie doesn't call me anything. She
only called me once when she were pissed
off and that's when we were pissed on a
drink. But Kaye
Kay calls me every [ __ ] day when I
was in a relationship with her, calling
me a [ __ ] calling me everything what
everyone else did online. And that's
what she does. I I don't love Kelly. I
will never ever get back with that
[ __ ] monstrosity of a man. I I don't
know why I went out with her in the
first place. I don't even know why he
had kids with her because only what she
is is a child abuser. >> Yeah.
>> And you notice people, why the [ __ ] am I
allowed to move back up near my mom? If
I was an abuser,
if I abused my kids, why the [ __ ] am I
allowed to go back up there?
>> Sure. Don't make sense to me, peeps, does it?
Why am I allowed to see my children,
peeps? Don't make sense to me. But was
the n allowed to see them?
You are [ __ ] weirdos.
>> I can't believe they do this every day.
>> Yeah, they ain't got no [ __ ] life.
It's all me. But yeah, I've had a DBS
check because they use people and this is where
I've had a DBS check as well.
[ __ ] hanging, man.
I weren't even allowed near my daughter
until they had my DBS jet done. >> Really?
>> Yeah. I weren't even allowed near LA to
[ __ ] monet me. >> Madness.
>> I weren't even allowed to take Cla to
the shop or anything until my DBS jet
come through. When my DBS check through,
social services told me I can start
taking my kids out now.
>> [ __ ] hell. I've had a DBS check.
Nothing come up on mine. Did anything
come up on yours? >> What?
>> Did anything come up on your DBS check?
>> Nothing. Nothing come up on my DBS check.
I haven't got a record. Yep.
>> Yeah. I just let these people type what
they want. I'm ignoring them.
>> No, you're being reading the questions.
>> No, they're wring more stuff. I just
ignore them. I just let them embarrass
themselves in it.
>> Yeah, that's it, PJ. They don't do it.
just let them keep embarrassing themselves.
>> Do you know the fact you know the madest
thing is none of these people money
would ever say anything to your face?
>> No, they won't. They won't.
I don't know what to do with myself. I
really [ __ ] don't.
>> Well, we're going out tomorrow for some beers. >> Yeah,
>> that should cheer you up, didn't it?
>> Yeah, it should. It should.
>> It's not that. I need Natalie to cheer
me up. No one else. Natalie, I need her.
No one else. [ __ ] hell. If you had
Natalie, I stay in Birmingham. This is
why I come to Birmingham for Natalie.
You know what I mean? This is why I have
here for her.
Ah [ __ ] But now I'm going to have to go
back up north now
cuz I'm not staying here when I don't
have nobody here. Do you know what I
mean? So what? There's nothing here for
me now. Nothing. So go back up north. I
don't think now.
>> Oh yeah. I'll buy you a baby goodness.
>> That is a baby goodness.
>> Yeah, man.
PJ has a better life than [ __ ] but
[ __ ] get more money. You don't know who
has money or doesn't have money.
The only thing we know is that your skin.
That's the only thing we know.
>> And I get laid more times than PJ.
>> Not anymore. You want to be?
>> I still can get laid if I want to. PJ.
>> Yeah, but you're not going to.
>> I know I'm not going to because I don't
want anyone else. But no.
>> Why do these people always talk about money?
>> Because they ain't got money.
Guess what, Jizzy? I get more sex than
you and I've got more money than you and
I get more money than you.
Will these people ever get a life? >> What?
>> Will these people ever get a life?
>> They haven't got a life.
>> Will they ever get one?
>> I don't know, PG. I really don't know.
Okay, I'm going to get
I might go get some [ __ ] beer.
Won't get pissed.
Okay, I'm going to go shop.
Get some beer in it, PJ. Have a drink.
>> I'm only getting
I'm getting a monster. Oh man,
if I can't get back with Natalie, I'm
completely done with women. I am. I
can't be harsh with women anymore, mate.
I was going to be done with women after
Kay, but then then Natalie come along
and I fell in completely in love. You
know what I mean?
fell completely in love.
I don't think I can do this again. Like you PJ.
>> Yeah. What about Hold on. Hold on. Yeah,
I'm here, bro. >> PJ. Yeah. EJ
thing about me. who I fall in love too
easy. Too easy. But Natalie, these
feelings what I'm getting for her. I've
never had these feelings for anybody in
my life. Nobody. I've even I even got
myself barely sectioned last night.
I even got myself nearly sexed.
My mom My mom don't blame Natalie for
the way I'm going what I'm going
through. My mom blames me. It's my
fault. My My mom actually loves Natalie.
My mom loves her to pieces. Like it's
her own daughter. Obviously, not like
that. But yeah,
my mom thought I found the right woman
and that my mom was were bossing with me
cuz he had a perfect woman.
My lovely. Yeah, I'm good. You
Yeah, just one item. See if I got it.
Are you in?
>> Thank you. Thank you. See you.
>> Keep the change. Keep it up.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> Yeah. No, it's all right.
>> Keep the change. Keep the change.
>> You very much.
>> No. No. You're all right, my love. I'll
see you later, sis.
>> Yeah. Sorry about that, Bob. >> DJ.
>> Yo, can you hear me?
>> Yeah, I can hear you.
>> Yeah, bro. You good?
Yeah, I'm good. I'm good.
>> Yeah. So, will you go to buy alcohol? >> No.
>> Just messing
I just got a monster.
>> I'm not I'm not going down that path.
I'm If I start drinking,
I start harassing Natalie and I don't want to.
>> Dy Jazz, why don't you come in the
hangouts? You little coward. Why don't
some of these come in the hangouts? Why don't you
>> want to come on the hangouts? The idiots
PJ who don't forget these people are
ugly as sin on YouTube. They want to
come on your hang out and they want to
talk to you.
>> Right. I need to ask Timmy something.
Yeah. One second. Stop talking over each other.
>> Timmy Timmy. Timmy. Yeah. The reason I
stopped talking to you is because you
find the gambling funny.
>> What are you on about, PJ? Can you say
that in English, lads?
>> Like you think the gambling industry is
funny. like losing money.
>> I hate the G PJ. I fight against the the
gambling industry every day. You haven't
seen the work I've done yet.
>> No, you think it's funny.
>> No, I think YouTube's funny. And I'll
explain why I think YouTube's funny. Cuz
you're all [ __ ] on here right now.
[ __ ] you could discuss. You every
day. You sad mate. Thinking you've got a brain.
>> Oh my word.
>> Thinking you got
>> Okay, Mongol. Calm PJ, tell him to calm
down or kick him out the box. PJ, I mean
Timmy, you don't know how to calm down.
He's [ __ ] over me, PJ. He's overalking me.
>> I'm not over talking.
>> Yes, you are. I was talking to PJ, not
you. And you overspoke us.
>> Beat you up. Okay,
>> Jimmy, you can't even open a packet if you can.
>> God, PJ, why are you scared? This
[ __ ] clunk cucumber.
What are you on about? Monty man's a
cucumber. Boy, you scared of the cucumber,
>> right? Okay, Timmy. Timmy, listen to me.
>> You not a cucumber?
>> Why can't you meet me now then? Timmy,
>> why can't you meet me in Wor got to meet
you? I'm in wherever the [ __ ] it is.
>> [ __ ] coward.
>> You know where you [ __ ] You're in
Birmingham. So pretend to location. So
why don't you
Hey, I tell you what, Timmy. I do you a
favor. Yeah. No,
>> I will go I will go to the train station
now. Yeah. I'll meet you at the train station. You're
>> coming to Birmingham.
>> I'll meet you I'll meet you at
Birmingham train station now.
>> No, I'm in Worcester. Meet train station now.
>> There you go peeps.
>> Why are you too scared to come to
Worester Mongol? It's580 out of your
money return from New Street. >> [ __ ]
why why are you scared to spend 580 m on
gold? Go on, Timmy. See, I'm not in
Birmingham. You can come to me. Well,
I'm not where you at, Timmy. So, you can
come to me.
>> I'm ready for a fight and I've had some
cocaine. So, what about give yourself a
clap to me?
>> You think you're clever because you're taking out
taking look dickfest.
>> I still b you even
James. I can meet you and beat you up.
You can't even open a packet of crisp.
>> Oh, come on. You can't do one plus four.
>> One. So, what's four?
>> I know what oneplus 4 is. You tell me.
>> Oh, go on then, Jimmy. What is oneplus 4?
>> It's easy. Okay, it's your turn now. 2 plus 7.
>> All right, Timmy. Can you do the alphabet?
>> You can't. I know that.
>> Yeah, I Yeah, I can.
>> You want to do it then?
>> You want me to do it? >> Yes.
>> Yeah, I I do it now then. Yeah, I need
my mic for you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, no, no. Not mute it.
You're doing Why is he ming his mic and
doing the alphabet? PJ, isn't he a cucumber?
>> Stop being scared of him, bro. You could beat
>> Can you hear me? Can you hear me?
>> I can hear you find Mongol.
>> Timmy, what? Timmy, why do you keep
laughing at the gambling?
>> What do you mean laugh at the gambling?
What do you want about PJ?
>> You think it's all funny?
>> No, PJ, I find it funny you lose. And
I'll explain why. because of the stuff
you've said online.
>> Oh, that's your autism to me.
>> Here we go.
>> PJ PJ, you have said some stuff.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that's that's your autism.
>> PJ is to say you're Oh, it's PJ. You
kicked me out when I'm Timmy. Do you
know Timmy? Do you know Timmy? Do you
know? One second. One second. One
second. Do you know Do you know Charlie V?
>> Charlie who?
>> Charlie Vel, the guy in Manchester.
>> No. You don't know who that is?
>> Jimmy, Jazz, the only one that's got
anxiety is you. Have you noticed that
we're on the hangout? Me, Monty,
>> me, Monty, Me, Monty, and Timmy's in the
hangouts and you're scared to join. So, I mean,
>> just let me do the
>> You must
PJ, right? You've got to understand
this, lad. Right. And put in this nons
for five minutes cuz I'm trying to have
a serious conversation.
>> Hang on. Hang on. angle who's normally
in this community the longest to me. PJ
has known me longer than anybody in this
community. The only people we is you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. The people is you.
>> Why won't you come to us?
>> I'll meet you now. Why tomorrow? Come
tomorrow and you won't meet me tomorrow.
>> Why are you scared to pay £58?
>> Oh my god, man. I will batter you. Money
m and [ __ ] tiger together, you [ __ ] clown.
>> I'm not coming to Birmingham. I've got
booze. I've got chicks. Exactly. You're
not coming to Birmingham because we're
already in Birmingham. Timmy, you're a virgin.
>> Only Timmy, you're a virgin. Only what
you can do is kiss me. >> I
like it. It tastes so [ __ ]
what a [ __ ] man.
Anyway, I did the alphabet. I did the
alphabet for you. Yeah. [ __ ] I want
you to come to give you a good idea. >> F
H I J K L M N O P
>> Timmy. There's nothing funny about roulette.
>> S T U V alphabet, please.
>> Yeah, I've done it. X. Timmy. Timmy. Timmy,
>> you haven't done it. Pour. One second.
One second. Timmy, Timmy, why are you so immature?
>> That's coming from you.
You know why you get trolled and why
people laugh at your gun? Do you want to
know the truth? It's cuz the [ __ ] [ __ ]
sick [ __ ] you said on here saying that
you're going to rape women.
>> Yeah. Really? Well, then
>> people like said it.
>> One second. One second. Hang on. Timmy,
didn't you Didn't you come on my and say rape claw?
>> No, I didn't. Mongol.
>> Yes, you did. Yes, you did. I've got a
[ __ ] video of that. You [ __ ] tag
man. You you upload
>> Timmy. Stop sitting there like you
[ __ ] Mr. Cler. You talk about my kids every
make yourself look like a clown. Well,
you are the clown. You are the You are a
clown. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Me. I'm a
clown. I am a clown. Have you got you
got the VPN? Have you got the IP? [ __ ]
Have you got the evidence?
>> I said yeah. You probably ever done
something like yourself where you sat on
the bus talking to kids asking telling
kids you got a beer in them.
>> Very simple question. Have you got very
>> Tik Tok mustard?
Oh, come on. Pat mustard. Do I give a
[ __ ] on what I said about Pat Mustard's
kids? Really? A man who went piss up on
my kids? Come on, man.
biggest people in this community.
Are you sure about that
right here? I can lean on one month cuz he's [ __ ]
>> right. What is out for? Why you kicking?
>> When are you coming to Birmingham?
>> Why don't on Lord Jay Mongol? You
couldn't beat yourself. Why don't
>> you beat yourself out of wet paper bag,
lad? You're too scared to meet me in the >> Jimmy
Mongol. Why are you afraid to come to
Birmingham? I don't want to impress. Oh
my god. Banger just come back in.
>> Why Timmy? When are you going to lose
that V card? >> Huh?
>> This is [ __ ] gold. Yeah.
>> Listen. Okay. One second. One second.
Monty, hold on a minute. One second.
Normal chat. Yeah. Monty. Um, not Monty.
Why do you find the gambling industry funny?
>> I find it funny you lose, PJ. [ __ ] harm on.
>> I don't gamble. I don't lose.
>> That's why I find it funny, PJ. Cuz he
wasn't a nasty bastard. I wouldn't laugh at actually.
>> No, not me. You just find the whole
gambling funny. I don't find it funny. Me?
>> What do you mean I find the old gambling
funny? What the [ __ ] are you on about, lad?
You think it's all a laugh?
>> No, I don't, PJ. Banger lost money
yesterday and I supported him.
>> Yeah, it was funny. It was funny him losing.
>> No, it wasn't funny, PJ. Cuz Banger's a
good guy, even though he's an [ __ ] at
>> No, he's not. He's a [ __ ] beggar.
>> Lose like you do.
>> No, I I like it when he loses.
>> You deserve to lose, lad.
>> I like it when he loses. Me,
>> Banger, do you get hard on, do you? >> Mhm.
>> Yeah. When he loses, I love it.
>> Did you get hard on when Banger loses
his money? Yeah. >> Yeah.
So you did get that hard that it's
satisfactional that banger lost £100
which is [ __ ] all
>> it's a lot of money to him. No, it's
not. [ __ ] a grand is, but not 100 quid. P,
>> he's [ __ ] Yeah, but he's Yeah, but
Yeah, but Timmy, he's skinned.
>> Doesn't matter. Still can lose 100 quid.
It's not It's not a lot of money, PJ.
>> You've been gambling recently.
>> Yeah, I lose a lot more than 100 quid,
PJ. Put it that way. You know how much
I've lost today, PJ?
>> How much? >> 9,320. >> PJ,
>> no you haven't.
>> No, I haven't gambled today. PJ, I'm
warning you up.
>> Yeah, but you need to stop laughing at
this this whole thing, Timmy. You need
to grow up.
>> I laugh at life, PJ. Why should I take
life seriously? We live in a [ __ ] world.
The world's a [ __ ] horrible place.
What? So why should
>> That's why I stopped That's why I
stopped um meeting you cuz you just find everything funny.
>> But why? Why should I find everything sad, PJ?
>> No, you find everything. How do you want
to live life, PJ? Sad or happy?
>> But why do you laugh at everything?
Because I can't be asked to cry anymore,
PJ. What's the point in getting upset on
[ __ ] you can't solve? The human race is
[ __ ] The world's [ __ ] There's too
many nons like Mongol in the world.
>> You know,
>> where is where is Mongol?
>> He left.
>> Oh, has he not? Is it because he's a So,
what's your opinion then, PJ? As you are
an adult and you call yourself an adult
with no autism, what's your opinion
about Monty Man having a teenage dating
app on his phone? >> Sing.
So, it's funny that kids get [ __ ]
stalked by grown men. Yeah.
>> No, it was you didn't have a teap.
>> That's not funny, PJ.
>> You don't have a TJ app. You're being silly.
>> Okay. This ain't funny. You're talking
to someone who's been speaking to Lance
on a teenage dating app at the age of
[ __ ] late 20s, 30s. You saying that's acceptable.
>> It's made up though. It never happened.
It's made up.
>> It's not made up, PJ. The evidence is
out there. And he admitted it on
keyboard. Even though the evidence is
out there that he had one.
>> Pack of lies. Pack of lies.
>> PJ, it's not lies. He know you know how
we know he had one. Can I explain? When
he did a video, which I've got it
somewhere, he [ __ ] he forgot to [ __ ]
turn on his turn off his screen. He
showed his whole dashboard on his phone
and he come up with a teenage dating app.
>> So you I mean PJ, have you got a teenage dating app? >> No.
>> Nor have I. So why would he have it on
the first place? Don't know.
You can't say Lola's using it. She was
only [ __ ] zero at the time. >> Really? >> Yes.
>> You think it's
>> I don't think you realize how serious
this is, do you, PJ?
>> You think it's funny?
>> Certain things you laugh at, PJ, and
there's certain things you don't. And
that's one thing you don't laugh at.
>> You think it's funny?
PJ you can't hear me laughing PJ
>> certain things are funny PJ certain
things are not and that's not a thing
what's not funny PJ
PJ when you meet your Monty man so I can
meet you and beat you both up tomorrow
>> mate you can never beat me up matey
>> okay so what part what time you coming
to Birmingham PJ
>> um probably around live.
>> Yeah, go live and I'll meet you.
>> Yeah, I'm going to go live in the
Weather Spoons. I'll find a Weather Spoon.
I wouldn't go live in Weather Spoons
because you'll get absolutely exterminated.
>> I'm going to defeat you.
>> Yeah. Okay, PJ. But I'll see you soon,
>> Yeah, bring whoever. Bring Bring that
Prime with you as well.
>> He ain't going to come out. He's got too
much to lose, bud.
>> Oh, yeah. Of course he does, mate.
You're a pair of [ __ ] [ __ ] >> Yeah,
>> you are. You are. Oh, here he is. Hello, N boy.
>> Timmy, shut the [ __ ] up, you [ __ ]
Yeah, listen. I will meet you tomorrow.
I will meet you tomorrow. Stop repeating
yourself. I'm not repeating. I'm not
even answering that question.
>> I am not answering questions what I've
already questioned. Yeah.
>> Why did you have a
>> Why are you bringing up questions what
I've already answered to me?
>> Oh, I can't be asked with this. It's like,
>> yeah, you can't be asked cuz you repeat
yourself, mate. You can't Jimmy, Jimmy,
>> don't let me Don't let me ring your
auntie up. Don't let me ring up your
>> Why are you on YouTube anyway? Your
mommy don't want youimmy.
Your mommy don't want you, does she?
You're the only one who has.
>> Timmy, you're repeating yourself.
>> I'm going to kick [ __ ] out of
you coming tomorrow.
>> Yes, I am coming. Perfect. Perfect.
>> 100%. Yeah. I I'll put you any in money.
Yeah. When PJ turns up tomorrow. See me
once you're up.
>> See me. I'm not PJ. Just kick him. Kick him. Just
>> the question.
>> See you later. Can't answer the
question. I've answered that question times.
>> Yeah. I'm not answering it over and over again.
Yeah. Over each other. Is it?
>> Yeah. And plus, it's repeating as well.
I'm not repeating the same [ __ ] what
you do in this community. [ __ ] hell.
I've explained myself over and over and
over again. I'm not explaining myself anymore anymore.
So, move on. Talk about something
different. Or don't
>> He's shouting, isn't he?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Just trying to talk for me
and that makes me shout.
>> Yeah, it's true now.
>> Yeah. I swear my kids live share. Watch
me snap to Mr. Jaw tomorrow if he turns
up. I'm not as
>> I'm going to restart my thing. Hold on,
hold on, hold on.