[Laughter]
You find funny. [Laughter]
Oh my god.
Stop laughing, bro. I need to get off
this [ __ ] bro.
People don't want to hear it. [ __ ] dead.
What should we charge now?
Yeah, YouTube needs to stop shouting,
bro. You got people on here trying to
[ __ ] sleep and [ __ ] man.
I'm coming off this YouTube [ __ ] I'm
having to I have to come off, bro.
Just [ __ ] pack it in. All right. Yeah. >> Yeah. >> Yo,
>> you good? Yeah.
>> Yeah, I'm good. I'm good.
>> Well, I don't [ __ ] know or not.
I'm just missing that, mate. I'm just missing Natalie.
Completely missing her.
I'm not chasing her no more. I can't be
ass chasing after women anymore, mate. >> Yeah.
>> Done now.
>> Can you Can you hear me? Yeah.
>> Yeah, I can hear you.
Yeah, I just text her anyway saying I'm
going back to Nottingham.
>> What's that?
>> I can hear you, PJ.
Where the [ __ ] are these headphones?
>> Sorry about that, bro.
>> No, there's two of us in here.
>> Can you hear me?
>> Yeah, I can hear you. I can hear you.
Why is it that you're you're either very
loud or you're very quiet, bro? There's
something wrong with my phone.
>> Can you hear me? >> Yo,
>> you What did you say?
>> I said you're either very quiet or
you're [ __ ] or you're loud. There's
something wrong with my phone, bro.
>> No, no, your phone's right. It's my I'm
low. I'm low. There you go. I just bet myself up.
I was just looking.
>> Yeah, it's weird, bro. It's This
community is just too weird.
>> I want to talk about the community, PJ.
Just do your own thing. Forget about
them. They're just [ __ ] idiots.
>> Yeah, true.
>> Just kick them. Just keep kicking them
>> and just keep talking about your own
[ __ ] thing. What you want to talk
about, not what they want to talk about,
>> cuz that's what they do. That's what
they do is bring up what they want you
to bring up. So they will write comment
about something because they know you
will read it then you know what I mean
here pigs. Anyways I'm going to show you
all a little bit of survival gear now. Yeah.
>> You what?
>> So you want
survival stuff? I've got more I've got a
hell of a lot more [ __ ]
So do you know what? Do you know if I
ever go homeless again?
>> If I ever go homeless again. Yeah. We have got outdoor shower.
So it's a shower for out like outdoor camping.
>> Yeah. Why? Why would you be home again?
>> Why would you be homeless again?
>> Why? because I'm scared to go homeless
again. I've only been homeless once.
So, I' I've been collecting all my
survival gear type.
>> I think you should I think you should
call Natalie and ask her what the score is.
>> She's not answering me. She's not
answering me one little bit.
I'm just leaving her alone. I don't know
what the score is. I'm just leaving her
now. I'm leaving Natalie B. I'm not I'm
not bothering with her. I'll let her
come to me when she's ready. But she
hasn't got along cuz I'm going to go
back to Nottingham workshop and I'm not
coming back to man. I'm not coming back to Birmingham.
>> If Natalie talks to me and we can sort
things out, then I will stay. I will
stay in Birmingham.
Not no issue with that at all. But if
she's not going to talk to me, I've just
chucked away everything for absolutely nothing.
>> You know what I mean?
>> No, it's not funny. It's not funny. I
blame myself for it to be honest with
you. I do. I blame myself.
>> I should have gone. You know, it's not
funny, PJ. It's really not funny. I'm a
prick, man. I shouldn't have gone live.
I shouldn't have gone live that day at
the hotel. I shouldn't have any channel.
I shouldn't even be live now. But I want
to get Natalie's attention.
That's what I'm doing. I want to get her attention.
>> Does she have WhatsApp on here?
>> Yeah, it's got WhatsApp. Yeah.
>> Try and speak to her for you. >> No.
>> Okay. No,
>> you're not coming in. Uh, Timmy, cuz you
just shout. You just shout over each other.
>> He's done it.
Only what he brings up. He says he he
repeats. Only me and
>> I'll let you in, but no repeating and
no, oh, I'm just going to kick you, bro. Straight.
No talking over and no repeating.
Have a civil chat. [ __ ] [ __ ] up.
on your [ __ ] Go on.
OP [ __ ] [ __ ] Go on. Go and clap her.
Bing Pingu. Go clap.
Who's that? That's Kayie, is it? That is. Hey,
>> Pingu. No, this
>> what was that Kay? I
>> think it is.
>> That one K on her Timmy account were it?
>> No, this is Katie though calling you [ __ ]
>> Oh yeah, she look like a dude with a
[ __ ] hairy ass.
She can call me a [ __ ] At least I
don't look like a dude. In fact, I am a
dude. A good looking one. about that.
That's the thing about K. She's just a [ __ ] bully.
And that's why I will never love Kayie
because she's a bully just like a mom and dad.
>> Yeah, it is Kayie. Yeah, definitely is.
>> she's a [ __ ] bully.
She bullied me and she bullied.
>> What you been up to? Uh, what you been
up to anyways, Kaye?
You've been sniffing around rice again.
>> I think you and Rice are made for each other.
>> Is it? I was about to serve out two ugly
peas in a [ __ ] pot. Perfect couple.
Kay and [ __ ] rice. Best couple on YouTube.
But the man's ugly. Oh, he's [ __ ]
ugly as [ __ ]
Ah, whoever goes out there rice has got
to be [ __ ] so [ __ ] desperate. So
>> True. Is it? >> Yeah.
>> Kay's desperate.
I would never ever go back out with Kayie. Never.
>> All right, Timmy. I just you have the link. Join,
>> but he just shouts over people.
Yeah, I was trolling you, Kaye, and
Monty heard it. Yeah, when I was sending
you to come to London. Yeah, I was
trolling you, you idiot.
>> Get in there, PJ. Get in there.
>> No, I was trolling. I actually was trolling, bro.
>> I never go back there anyways. I learned
my lesson. Keep getting kicked out. Keep
getting stressed out for nothing. Keep getting attacked. King
[ __ ] I stole from my head. I'm all
right, mate. I'm good. I'm all right.
I would never go back there. I learned
my I learned my lesson.
>> God bless you
>> over and over again.
So, okay, when you were saying I can
click my fingers and get Jerry back, you
can. Natalie can. Natalie can click her
fingers. I will go running straight back
to her every single time. Every time
Natalie clicks her fingers, I will be back. You
My mom actually loves Natalie. My mom
adors Natalie. You My mom [ __ ] hates
you. She cannot stand you. She cannot
even stick you. My mom can't care. She
[ __ ] can't stand you. And you know
that yourself. And my mom [ __ ] loves Natalie.
It just shows that Natalie is a better
woman than what you will ever be.
4K in space red ahead as in now.
Go and stay red ahead
early. Come on. Speak early. earlier. >> Yeah.
>> Easy. Go right you [ __ ] lemon.
>> He's not even talking. No.
>> Oh man, [ __ ] happens. Oh, here we go.
Who the hell is that in that picture? Does
No, that is what
>> in a picture.
>> I can't see a picture >> there.
What? Have you sent me a picture or something? [Music]
I'm going to sing Natalie a song with
me, I think.
>> Should I sing her a song? Yeah.
>> So, sing Natalie a song, PJ.
>> Yeah. Go on. Do you know what you should
do? No. No. No. Monty, do you know what
you should do? You should write her a poem.
>> Write her a poem. No. No. That [ __ ]
works. I've wr about 50,000 poems and
they don't work.
>> I' I've wrote poems before.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I've got a good one. Roses
are red, violet blue. PJ picks his nose
and eats his groies.
>> No, I used to write poems.
>> Did you? >> Yep.
There's a nice buffet in um Birmingham
we'll go to tomorrow. It's called Jimmy
Spices if it's still there. It's a nice
buffet. We'll go there. >> Okay.
>> It's by Chinatown.
>> Yeah. I sing that song, shall we?
>> Oh, bless you.
>> I will I sing it on your live stream.
Yeah. Tell you what, give me a second.
I'll be right back.
I didn't get these kids strip searched
at all. At all. Stop talking [ __ ] Kaye.
It's not going to work. Stop talking [ __ ]
Yeah, exactly those. You tell them
no matter what women do to me now, I
wouldn't care, bro. I expect everything they do.
I wouldn't care. I wouldn't cry. I don't
give a [ __ ] I don't care about them.
I'm only going out tomorrow to meet Monty. Yeah,
cuz I don't give a [ __ ] about these women, bro.
I got 13 numbers like two weeks ago and
I didn't get one date.
ignoring, stuck up, ignorant. I don't
give a [ __ ] bro.
I don't give a [ __ ] I'd be more
surprised if they didn't do this [ __ ]
That's saying something.
I've been [ __ ] over more times in
worse ways than Monty has. That's for sure, man.
And that 20-year-old, I knew that
20-year-old longer than he knew Natalie.
He's only known her for like what, a few
months? Two months or two months, 3
months. And then when she was given
attitude, I just [ __ ] her off. Didn't
care. Literally didn't care.
Cuz I I I expected from these [ __ ]
So that's why I didn't bother me, bro.
I knew her for like over a year.
Over a year. Two years maybe. Didn't care. Adios.
They don't care about us. We shouldn't
care about them. Anyways, so yeah.
>> Yeah, man.
>> Yeah. sing your song for then high and
low. Yeah, high and low.
>> Oh, bless you.
>> Do you know what high and low song is? Yeah.
>> Never heard of it.
>> Okay, I'll sing it then. You probably have
full of highs and lows. If you mind, if
your heart gets broke by your side, if
you're alone, God bless you.
>> I was going to buy USA some flowers with some weedke.
>> I will be
I will I'll be there for the highs and lows.
top when you haul yourself in road.
>> Yeah, nature g I was going to buy I was
going to buy um USA is I was going to go
America and buy her some flowers
>> and some weed
but don't worry me and you me and you
will go out tomorrow and we'll show her who's boss
>> we'll be on the baby Guinnesses me and
you show her who's boss in it. Yes.
>> Who's boss? >> E.
Finish the song up in that there. Finish
it off for probably two seconds.
>> Buy some flowers.
>> I don't I don't get I don't get women flowers.
>> I was going to buy you a sazy flowers.
How cute is that?
>> I've got I've got a brand new TV.
[ __ ] do I need to get flowers
when I got a brand new TV?
>> Oh bless you.
>> Bless you.
>> Bless you in life.
>> We'll be on the baby sister.
If you mind if your heart gets broke by your side.
Well, I'll be left and loses.
You're talking about yourself in this lonely road.
>> Well, listen. If she doesn't reply, if
she doesn't reply by tomorrow, we're
getting you a new bird.
give you my
girl. I'm waiting for Natalie. I don't
want no one else, buddy. I just need I
just need Natalie.
That is it. That's it. That's all he would need. >> Bos. Yeah.
>> I've known Natalie for seven years. I
mean, not seven years.
>> You know what I would do if I if I was
in your position, bro? I'm not even
joking. Yeah. I would just I would ignore her.
and and go out and meet other people
because you know that 20-year-old I was
meeting, I used to ignore her. She
always used to come back like texting
and [ __ ] You know, do you you realize
they always come back? You do realize
that when you ignore them, they always
come back, bro. >> Yeah,
>> I wanted to I wanted to come back, but
>> when you ignore them, they always come
back. Trust me.
>> Yeah, but I'm not ignoring it. I'm going
to go back up to [ __ ] workshop. I'm
going to go back to [ __ ] the only
shelter. Got cl me. That's what I'm
going to be doing
cuz I ain't got no one in Birmingham. If
>> I' I'd ignore her and try and meet other
people for now. I'm not even joking,
bro. I swear to God I'm not even playing.
>> Just don't just don't write her and just
try and meet Yeah, I would.
>> That's not to I told her anyway. But I
text her. I text her that I'm going back to war.
>> Yeah, you're not in a relationship anyway. So,
>> I just hope she understands I'm not messing around.
I'm not messing around. This ain't no
game. I don't want to play games. I'm
done playing games with women.
>> I was I was done I was done I was done
years ago with that. Monty, bro, you're
new to this.
>> I'm not new to this [ __ ] Like I've
never been. This is [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but Monty, listen.
Listen, bro. You're older than me. You
should know what they do.
>> Yeah, I do know what they do.
>> I've never loved anybody like Natalie.
This is what I'm saying to you.
Natalie is like literally my first first
ever ever true love.
>> No, I'm not even on
I've only been in love once in my entire
life. Once. And and and that was Natalie.
>> I've been in love three times, I think.
>> Well, no. No.
>> Two times. Two times. Two times. Two
>> Two times. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I've been
in love for two times with my ex
ex-girlfriend. That's when I come on
PlayStation and met you. I come out of a
really bad relationship.
>> That was twice. Definitely twice.
>> But I did love her. Then I met Kay. special.
>> Then I met Kayie, but I didn't love
Kayie. I just, you know, I don't know. I
don't know. I never
>> We're not doing Monty. We're not doing
any drugs tomorrow.
>> Drugs? I don't do drugs anymore. PG.
I've quit the weed. I've quit.
>> We're only doing drinking. We were only
doing drinking and a lot of it.
>> A lot of it. Yeah.
>> Yeah, man.
Do you remember? Do you remember when
you met me?
>> Man, you people are pedos in this
community. Did not [ __ ] me and Kayie
when she was 13. You people are
>> Monty. Listen, Monty, we Monty, we we
met years ago, ain't it?
>> Yeah, we met years and years and years
ago. I knew you when you was a [ __ ] teenager.
>> No, no, but I'm saying I'm saying when
we met in person was years ago as well.
Really? Is it? It was a few years ago. Yeah,
>> a few years ago. Yeah, about five years
ago. Four year ago. Three. No, maybe
like three. Yeah.
>> How was I in person? >> Huh?
>> What? How was that in person? Cuz I met
you in in [ __ ] London.
>> Yeah. How was I in real life?
>> Yeah. Small [ __ ]
>> A what?
>> You're small.
>> [ __ ] off you [ __ ] Not even am I am I small?
>> Are we [ __ ] you [ __ ]
>> Are we? >> Yeah.
>> I didn't know that. I thought you were
small. Me, PJ,
>> I thought you was the size of [ __ ] tiger.
All you've got to say to Kaye is, "Shut
the [ __ ] up, [ __ ] You sucked my dick
and I came in your mouth." That's all
you got to say to [ __ ]
>> Yeah, exactly. Shut the [ __ ] up. Yeah,
because you sucked on this mongol dick. >> Yeah.
>> You [ __ ] sucked on my mongol dick.
>> Did she ever swallow? Did she ever >> Once.
>> Yeah. There you go. So you you can say,
"Aha, you swallow my babies." That's
what it means. You know, when someone
swallows your gum, that's what people say.
That's what I used to say to people. [ __ ] them.
>> No, really. It's on about me saying I
should say to you, you suck my dick and
you have suck my dick.
>> Yeah. And you swallowed as well.
>> Hello Jamie. We meet again.
>> Why are you lying?
>> Look at you on that. You sadly
ugly. Ugly man.
>> Created two gifts in the world. Well, you know
>> Jimmy, you're a virgin. Get
>> what? Why? Why? Why am I not watching me?
>> You love Kayie. You're lying.
>> I don't love Kayie.
>> Yes, you did.
USA is Steven Howard.
>> You did
not level two level a long time ago.
>> Listen. Listen. I loved Kay once until
she started [ __ ] abusing it. You did
>> until she started abusing me. Kicking me out.
>> Kicking me out. I only wanted to go back
to Kish to get my dog. to get my dog.
So, why did you say
>> I didn't love her? I didn't love her
like I love Natalie. I love Natalie a
lot more than I've ever loved.
>> He was only with her for two months.
Loved her a lot more. He was with Kylie
for 20 years. It's a massive difference.
>> I was longer. It was I've been with Natalie longer.
>> So, how can you be in love with someone
that short a period of time, Mongol? >> No,
>> that because I you
You've never even been laid.
>> Never had a girlfriend. I have had a
>> No, you've never had a girlfriend, PJ.
You're a virgin.
>> Yes, I have to. But you've never even had sex.
>> Okay, PJ.
>> One second. One second. One second. One
second. Monty, you Sorry, Monty. One
second. Timmy, you've never even had
sex. You're still a virgin.
>> PJ, more times I've had sex this week,
PJ. I had sex last week.
>> I listened to this. PJ, you wouldn't
even know what to do. You You'd be too nervous.
>> Monty, you're still a virgin. That's not
not Monty. Timmy, you're still a virgin.
>> Yes. Okay. I'm a virgin. PJ, you satisfied now? >> Yeah.
>> I stick up for Kaye on this one. I will
stick up for Kaye on this one. Kay's
never put a cup over Laura's head. She's
put a cup over my head. Not L's head.
Over my head.
>> She did put a cup over Mongol's head. It
wasn't the kids. It was Mongols cuz I've
seen the clip.
>> Yeah. Cup over his head. How did How did
it feel anyway Mongol that you had a cup
over your head?
>> Well, I've got a scar across me head obviously, Timmy.
>> Oh, are you got a boner over that?
>> No, I get a boner over now. They're whipping me. [Applause] >> Really?
You've got some bad tasting women, mate.
I'd choose Kayie any day that one.
>> Timmy, you don't know what Samsung is. >> What?
>> You don't know what Samsung is.
>> Choose Kay. Go with Kayie.
>> I can't, mate. I'm old enough to be a
dad. I'm not a non
>> Timmy. Timmy, you don't know what I've
got back now.
>> I'm not a nons like you, Mongol.
>> I've got my old phone number back now.
My triple triple 7 phone number.
>> Timmy, you don't know. Timmy, how come
you don't know? Timmy, how come you
don't know what Samsung is? phone
number. Oh no. Oh no. >> Timmy.
>> Oh no. Yes.
>> Why don't you know what Samsung is?
>> What the [ __ ] are you on about PJ?
>> Samsung the brand
>> killed. I don't want to talk about
Samsung. We're talking about why Jamie
lying that he that he didn't said he
didn't love Kaye. But he did.
>> I didn't love Kaye.
>> Yes, you did.
>> My love went my love went a long time
ago for that woman. Right. I'm not being
funny to me. If I'm listen >> Yeah.
>> So if I put
it's going to come out 100% positive
that one sec.
>> Timmy. Timmy. Hold on a minute. >> Positive.
>> One second. Timmy, you actually went on
holiday, ain't it?
>> Yeah. And your point is,
>> how did you Was you scared of the flying this time?
>> You knew I was scared of the flying, PJ.
I missed it several [ __ ] times.
>> Well, you still Yeah, but you still
went. Yeah, cuz I I had to, PJ, because
you know what it is with me, PJ, I have
got the gift of holding it in. Do you
know what I mean by that? What I mean by
that, if we got to do something, it
doesn't matter how much I'm scared, PJ,
I overcome my fears.
>> I don't I don't have no one to talk to. I'm talking
>> that was the Timmy, that was the first
time you went abroad in like 10 years, isn't it?
>> You actually are spot on, actually. Yes, it was.
>> So, what made you all of a sudden 10
years later just want to go again?
That's mad. Because I just wanted to get
out of this country, PJ, because I'm
bored of this country.
>> Kay, you are right. You didn't give a [ __ ]
>> Correctly, Kayie. You didn't give a [ __ ]
because you don't give a [ __ ]
>> If I paid £200 to do a lie protector,
you're telling me you're going to come
back clear that you never love Kaye.
>> Listen. Okay, let me explain one thing.
Would you love a woman? Yeah. Right.
Listen. Yeah. Kay's being abused other
mom and dad being left dumped whatever
24/7 every time of her [ __ ] life.
Yeah. And I've been there with Kayie
through all that. Yeah. When Kayie let
her mom move into the house, I said to
Kay, I don't want her mom living with
us. She didn't let me finish my
sentence. I was going to say I don't
mind her staying with us for now, but I
didn't want her living with us. Then he
said, I'm telling my mom you don't want
her here. Go and [ __ ] tell her. The
woman who abused you.
>> But the thing is, [ __ ] you did love
her. It's like with me and my ex because
even if we had a bad break in
>> I don't love my ex
she chose her mom a woman who's never
chose her in her life of her own
boyfriend who who's a father to her children
>> Mongol this is getting off
here to catch you out that you are lying
out of your face that you did love
>> okay I'm lying out my face because I'm
not lying on my face I do not love you.
Yeah. Just get that through your head.
>> Talking about now, Mongol, but we're
talking about when you had a
relationship with her, you did love her
or you wouldn't have been with her.
>> Oh my god, Timmy.
>> I love her. Listen to me, Timmy. Yeah, I
loved her before she started abusing me.
Yeah, I did. Yeah.
>> So, you did love her. So, why you lied on YouTube
>> when she started abusing me?
>> When she started abusing me.
>> The fact of the character is that you
did love her.
>> Yeah, I did. I did. Yeah, of course I
did. Of course I did. But I didn't I
don't love her like
I've got feelings for nothing.
>> But you you said you never So that was a
lie, wasn't it, Mongol?
>> Listen listen. You know what love is?
Yeah. I've never felt anything really
for Kaye. Kayie is the mother to my
children. Yeah. Right. But I've never
really Why do you have 10 years in your
life with her? She meant nothing to you.
He calls I thought Kay was nice when I
first met her. I thought she wasn't right.
>> So you love her. So you you've just
basically admitted you sentence that you
loved her. That's when I found out why
she was actually wanted. So don't lie.
You could just
listen. You did love each other at the
time. So let me just stop talking.
He did love you. He's a bullshitter.
>> I'm not a bullshitter.
10 mil. Both of you two notches.
Shut the [ __ ] up, Lord. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Come to Birmingham.
Hit me up.
>> One second. I'm going to own this clown.
>> Yeah, he's not even
still begging for money. You're still
begging for money. Skim boy scent. more
money than you would ever have £1,000 a
month. Bro, you're on £300 a month. Look
at your traders. Your skin,
>> bro. You don't even have £1,000. That's
why you're begging for money.
>> Jesus [ __ ]
>> You don't have £1,000. That's why you're
begging for money, skin boy. That's why
you're crying over losing £100, skin boy.
>> You do not get £3,000 a month. You do.
You get Are you going to let me talk?
You're going to keep talking over me.
Okay. You're going to keep talking over
me. Listen, £300 a month, boy. You don't
even have £1,000 to your name, let alone
£1,000 a month. That's why you're on
YouTube constantly begging for money.
You don't have money. I don't know why
you keep coming on YouTube. One second,
Monty. Like you've got money. You don't
have money because you wouldn't be
begging on YouTube. Skint flint. Yeah,
you're the one who's wearing True
Religion. You're skint. You don't even
have £1,000 in your name. Look at you
crying over [ __ ] £100, bro. [ __ ] me.
[ __ ] pathetic, bro.
>> What the [ __ ] is true true religion?
>> Oh, just some cheap brand, bro.
>> Bro, the guy's on £300 a month and he
acts like he's got money, bro. He's
living he's living his life on YouTube
every [ __ ] Who beg Monty? Who begs
for money? Who begs for money? This guy
trying saying that he get £3,000 a
month, bro. He gets nothing a month. He
is skint flint. That's why he's on
YouTube Friday, Saturday. >> Let me
get you know,
>> you're not trying to come on, bro.
>> Is she not?
>> Why? Let Let me ask you this question.
If he if he doesn't keep talking to other people,
>> why do you try to convince people you
have money? You have nothing.
>> You have nothing. Why do you keep acting
like you've got money?
>> Answer if every time I say anything, you
overlay me. Yeah. Go on,
>> PJ. You're It's not my fault you're a skint,
>> bro. I've got more money than you would
ever have. I've shown more money than
you ever have.
>> What are you talking about? I'm not
begging for money on YouTube. You are.
>> You've been shown money time and time
and time again.
>> You can't show nothing. You get Bro, you
don't even get £1,000.
>> Okay. How much do you get a month again?
>> Okay. So after I pay all my bills and
put money in the savings, I probably
left about three and a half grand.
>> You do not get three and a half grand a
month. You don't. Listen, mate. I was
ready to No, you do not get three and a
half grand a month. Stop lying to
yourself. Stop lying to yourself.
Listen, listen, listen, listen. This guy
does not get three and a half grand a
month, bro. Benefits does not pay 32
grand a month, which is what you're on a
B. Even when you're renting, one second.
Let me let me scream. One sec. One sec.
One sec. One sec. One second. Let me let
me kick Monty out a second. Yeah. Let me
tell you something. Yeah, I'll kick them
both out. But brother, people in London
do not even get three and a half grand a
month. Like even chefs that work [ __ ]
a million hours a week does not get
three half grand a month. Even if you
rent property in London, you don't get
three 1/2 grand a month. You do not get
no 32 1/2 grand a month. Oh, and he's a
liar as well, cuz last week he said how
he gets 2 and 1/2, now he gets three and
a half. Bro, if somebody was getting 22
1/2 grand,£32 grand a month, they
wouldn't be begging on YouTube for £200
a month. The guy is [ __ ] skint. Look
how he acted when he lost £100. Uh, when
was it? Yesterday, bro. The guy doesn't
even make any sense. First it was 22
grand, then it was three in in in
[ __ ] Ireland, bro. Come on. It
doesn't look right. Just admit what
you're on, bro. Just admit what you're
on. I don't understand why you don't
just admit what you're on. Me, Monty
does it. [ __ ] Rocky Roy does it. We
all admit. Oh, the internet's gone
again. Same old internet here. Same old internet. Mm-
It's the same old internet again. It's [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] it. Yeah.
Oh, here we go. No, it's better now. So,
just admit what you get. Basically, just
admit what you get. You don't get no
fucking£3 half grand a month. You don't
get no 22 grand a month. You get nothing
per month, but your [ __ ] £300
benefits, £400 max, which is your
[ __ ] universal [ __ ] credentials.
You get nothing. Literally, bro,
chefs get paid more than you think. I
know how much they get paid, bro. I know chefs. So, anyways,
32 grand a month, but he's begging on
YouTube. He wishes he got three and a
half grand a month, bro. If somebody if
somebody in Ireland legitimately got
three half grand a month, they wouldn't
be sat on YouTube every day. They
literally would not be sat on YouTube
every day. Especially in somewhere,
especially somewhere like Ireland where
everything's a lot cheaper. Bro, you are
lying to yourself. You're skint. Look
how long it [ __ ] took you to [ __ ]
save up to go to [ __ ] Vegas.
>> Why people have to lie? Why? I don't
know why people have to lie on here. Money.
>> I don't know either. To be honest with you,
>> just be honest. Like we're honest, bro.
Do you know what I'm saying?
>> Anyway, Kayie, why are you a pedo lover
any lying, bro?
I want to know why Kay's appeared all over me
sitting there entertaining.
>> First it was two and a half then it's
three and a half. Which one is it?
>> Yo. Anyway, K, I'm going to send that
picture to my mom where you said that [ __ ] bullshitter.
>> I'm going to be sending that [ __ ]
absolute bullshitter, bro.
>> He is an absolute bullshitter.
someone. It wouldn't be in anyone's
interests if they were getting all that
money a month to start begging on
YouTube. That would only happen to [ __ ]
it so I can call you.
>> That would only happen if someone's skin
that would only happen if someone's skin
you understand. Unless obviously you was
getting a lot more then [ __ ] So
you're saying you get all of this money
yet you're sat begging on YouTube and
you're on YouTube every day, bro. You get nothing?
will do. Don't you worry. You know, my
mom, you know, my mom will see like >> you
>> and you know what you do on social
media. So, you're It's right. It's getting done.
>> He's a proper liar, bro. He's a proper bullshitter.
>> Like, even when I was renting them
rooms, even when I was renting them
rooms, I think the most I got a month
was about 3.2.
>> Like, maybe about 3.2K
>> after bills and stuff. Maybe three. And
that was London. He does not get no
[ __ ] three and a half grand a month
for what's sitting on your ass.
Sitting on your ass title.
>> I'm done with it. I'm done PJ because
only what you're doing is reacting to
him. You're making me s you react back
to these with you. What the [ __ ] are you
doing? You're sitting there letting them
in, letting him call.
>> I didn't know who it was. I didn't know
who it was. I didn't know who it was. I
I didn't know who the [ __ ] it was. No,
I'm just I'm just I'm just telling
people, bro, what what they do. They're liars.
I'm telling I'm not reacting to them.
I'm telling you how the guy is a
bullshitter. Just in case people go on
his channel and believe him. I'm not
reacting to him. I didn't even know it
was him, otherwise I wouldn't let him in.
Let's just go by logic here, bro. Yeah, simple.
Oh, [ __ ] Middle finger.
He's making me react to them now, bro. I
swear to God. Yeah.
He does not get no money a month. Think
of it. Why am I the only one,
Steven, that shown the most money on
here? Why am I the only one that shown
the most money on here
and none of these people can show
anything? Why are they on YouTube all
day, every day? Why does nothing they
say make any sense? Because they're [ __ ] skin.
See, people like Monty, people like
Rocky Ride, I don't mind them because
they don't lie. But these certain people
here feel they need to lie. And I don't
know why they need to to lie about their life.
It's madness. Anyways, I'm done talking
about them now. So
>> don't do it. That's why they [ __ ]
>> Oh, we just Oh, sorry. One second, Joe.
I was just I was just telling everyone
that just just LJ is full of [ __ ] with
how much money he gets and he's just a
projector. That's all. We just finished
up that anyways.
>> Yeah. So, oh,
>> I didn't know who it was, Marty. I
didn't know it was him, bro. Otherwise,
I wouldn't have let him in that. But he
got me into it. I did. He did come in
his real account.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I know. They come on fake account.
>> Scared the [ __ ] out of her. That was all
right. But like I was trying to say, but
you won't let me finish cuz you'll get on talking.
I'm going to say this one thing to her
now. Kayie, my mom has told me to
collect every single bit of evidence of
you bullying and doing whatever on
social media and then she can stop you
from seeing the kids. Bob's your [ __ ]
uncle. So, thank you, Kaye. You fought
yourself right up. >> Listen,
one second. Not not to react. Yeah. not
to react. Um, but Hammed, people have
tried that a million times and it's not
even a police matter. So, yeah, crack on
anyways. Uh, it's a civil matter, but
yeah, I mean, crack on.
>> I'm not letting my kids snare Kayie
who's a [ __ ] bully.
>> He's getting done. I'm sending my mom
the picture of the screenshot she's been
saying and calling and whatever.
>> Yeah, Kay's [ __ ]
>> I've got it. I've got it now.
Yeah, my mom's
helping the kids. Oh, Kayley and we
already know you you wrong social
services up on my mom saying that Scots.
We already know that you already know
go please then. And you're banned for
just talking about grassing. Anyways,
bye-bye little [ __ ] Anyone that
talks about grassing gets banned on my
channel. So yeah, I just I was just
telling everyone about him, Joe.
Anyways, like I don't know what this guy
is telling you.
But he's full of absolute [ __ ]
So I just had to bring the subleting
thing up. There's no way someone in
island sitting on their ass all day is
getting all that money a month. Bro,
>> see you're reacting to him again. Just
stop talking about him.
>> Am I Am I lying over here?
>> Am I lying?
>> No, you're not lying. Buddy's making no
point sitting there reacting to a
[ __ ] fat only man from Ireland.
>> Yeah. This is why this is why I'm done.
>> I'm done with all of this. This is just
bollocks. YouTube's bollocks. I've done
five years of this [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's ruined my life.
>> I know. I know. I know.
>> Bro, listen. You're the one that got me
back on it. You're the one that got me
back on it, bro.
>> Yeah, I didn't get you back on it. I
only got you back on it last night, not today.
>> Yeah, but still, bro, I weren't going to
come back on it. I swear to God, bro.
>> My belly is hurting me, man. [ __ ]
>> just like when I come to Birmingham
tomorrow. We're not put We're actually
not going to put it on YouTube, bro.
[ __ ] it. Yeah.
>> Oh, cuz you ruined it.
>> No, I just don't want to put it on
YouTube. [ __ ] them. Is it
>> Kayie? I will do what I want to do and I
will do it.
>> Yeah, because money if you got that
pregnant. Obviously not.
Kayie thinks that her mom can get the
the the kids off my mom. No, no, no.
Kayie, do you not remember? I've been
caught with you. Weren't your mom on
social services herself by neglecting you? Yeah.
Your mom never even took you to any of
your courses when you were younger. Why
the [ __ ] is your mom going to get the
kids? And you're not even going to get
them either. Cuz I will put a stop to
that. I will tell social services
everything what they don't know
cuz don't forget K I stood by you told
everybody the lies about what what you
done the full system by sticking up for
you by saying you've never smack you
never done that you never done that I
lied to you but
our kids man your abuser
[ __ ] I hope you don't believe You think
he's a [ __ ] absolute compulsive liar?
>> What's your baby?
>> I've got a baby. Natalie's not pregnant.
What's it? What's this with everyone
thinking Natalie's pregnant?
I've only got two kids and that's with
you. To be honest with you, I wish I
never had kids with you.
>> Sorry, PJ.
>> You think someone
>> You know what? I'm going to sell this Natalie.
Yeah, man. If I marry Natalie, yeah,
then Natalie will be the stepmother to
them children. In fact, Natalie is the
stepmom to them children. She is a
stepmom to them kids. She's in my kids'
lives, Charlie. She is the stepmother to
them kids. She's a better mom than you.
She is a better mom than you, Natalie.
[ __ ] Lola and Prim Adora. Natalie,
they both love Natalie.
>> Yeah. What if she doesn't get back with
you, Monty? Then what are you going to do?
>> If she don't get me back, she don't get
me back. Now what I can do?
>> Jo, do you know what I was saying to
Monty? Yeah. I was saying, do you know
how you um when like a woman does this
to you? Yeah. like she needs space now.
I was just basically saying to him like
the best thing to do is to go out and
meet another woman to show them who's
boss. That's what I was telling Monty earlier.
>> Yeah, I was telling him, bro, cuz I know
how like what they do and [ __ ]
So, yeah, that's what I was telling him.
>> I'm just going to let Natalie calm down.
I'm just going to leave her and let her
calm down. That's what I'm going to do.
She does love me. We're going to go on a
drink tomorrow. I'm going to meet Monty
tomorrow. So, we're going to go for some drinks. So yeah.
>> Yo, PJ, do you like my phone? Have you
seen my new phone?
>> Um, yeah. It's nice, bro. You show me. Yeah.
>> It doesn't matter if he's in love. The
thing is you What am I What was I saying
again? Bro, you should expect this. Look
at that 20-year-old who I who I know I
knew for over a year. I knew eventually
she was going to come back. I just went
and met other people and I knew
eventually she was going to come back.
>> I love Natalie does come back.
>> I know what they do. So I can't be in
love now cuz I know what they do. I I
wouldn't expect anything less from them.
That's what I was trying to tell Monty.
>> Check this out. It's [ __ ] mean.
>> Monty's a simp.
>> I do want Natalie back.
>> Here. Look. Look. Yeah. Reminds me of
the USA days. Joe, let me see. Yeah,
I've seen it, bro. I've seen it before.
I've seen it yesterday. >> It
remember when I was in love, Joe?
I am in love. Complete love, man.
>> She's breaking me, man. She's breaking me.
>> She's literally breaking me out, man.
>> You remember when I was in love? I was
going to get her I was going to get her
flowers and weed. Remember, Joe,
>> your flowers and weed?
>> Yeah, I was in love once upon a time. Oh,
>> special then. But it's over now.
>> Try your eyes, mate.
>> I know to see her mind. >> Yeah,
>> there's plenty of fish in the sea.
>> Are you in it?
>> I can get me.
>> Nah, I've got too much experience in this, Joe.
I've got too much experience with the
women and too much experience with the >> Huh? Is it?
It's this song.
Do you know this song? Oh [ __ ]
>> Do you know this song?
Isn't that right, Joe?
>> Stand there for a minute.
>> Yeah, that's an old song, bro. It's very old.
>> Yeah. Good.
>> What does mean? Yeah, that guy's from um >> where?
>> He's from Birmingham. Well, he's from
London. Maybe it's Birmingham.
>> His name is Mike Skinner, I believe.
>> That was [ __ ] roing.
>> Oh, yeah. Jo, we're definitely going on
a piss tomorrow.
>> [ __ ] I need a new [ __ ] I don't
need a new woman. I don't need a new
woman. I only need the one woman. I
don't need no one else.
>> Yeah, but that's because I Yeah, but
that's cuz I've got experience with
them, Joe. Um, Bobby, I've done this
with these women before. Like I said, I
would be more surprised if they didn't do this.
That's what would be the surprising
thing. I know what they do. So, how
>> my belly is hurting me, man. I haven't
ate it for days. I can't even eat
anything. What's wrong with me?
>> This has got to be your first love. I
think this is actually your first I
think this is actually your first love, Monty. Bro,
>> I can't [ __ ] eat. I've been taking
out of his burger.
>> That reminds me of the days, you know.
You know the first Izzy Joe? This is
what I used to be. I couldn't eat. I
couldn't sleep. When I woke up, I
thought I'm talking about the first one.
That's the first first one.
Bear down. You Monty, we're going out tomorrow.
>> Yeah, I know. But
>> I hope Never mind. Izzy, the first one
just knew what they were like. Yeah,
>> I even I PJ I even put an initial on my
man. I let a N on my
>> God bless you.
>> Oh, bless you.
>> Bless you in life, Monty. We'll find you a bird.
I'll put an L there for now.
>> I'm going to come to Birmingham tomorrow
and meet you. We're going to go on a drink.
>> I loved I loved UK Izzy and I loved USA Izzy.
>> But then I just stopped when I knew what
they done and how they move and [ __ ]
Then I just like [ __ ] this. Like even
that Ukraine one, it didn't piss me off
cuz I was like oh I knew what they were
going to do anyways. Sorry. >> What?
>> I've actually I actually have been in
love three times actually. Actually has
been three times
when I was like 12 as well actually. Maybe.
>> Yeah. that she loved me by blocking me
and make up stories about me and stuff. Yeah. >> Huh?
>> No. I think you said that Kayie was my
first love. Kay is not my first love.
I've never really had feelings for Kaye.
Never really had feelings for not the
feelings I'm getting now. Okay. Now
I I've got more feelings for Natalie and
they have for and I did for Kayie.
I got more.
>> I didn't even like that USA easy at
first. She actually drew me in. She
actually like drew me in, bro. I didn't even like
>> I'm done anyways. I'm done with women.
I'm I'm I'm done now. Anyways, I can't be asked.
I can't be asked. It's been nearly a
week. It's going on too long. So, I
really can't be asked. I'm done with
women. I'm done. I'm done. I'm not
chasing after no one no more.
Yeah, we'll find We're going to find you
one tomorrow as well.
>> I can't wait tomorrow.
>> Can't [ __ ] even eat it.
>> I can't wait to see you tomorrow, man.
>> Tell you not. Let me chop this burger
out. I'll punch my burger up.
>> I can't find her. She's in Miami.
Like I said, you know, you know, you
know the you know the 20-year-old Joe,
you know when she kept like [ __ ] off
and that I didn't give a [ __ ] I said,
"Okay, bye. See you later."
She wasn't ugly and stuff and she was I
[ __ ] her a few times. I didn't give a
[ __ ] I said, "Bye. See you later." Adios.
Don't give a [ __ ] about them, bro.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
Just like Jane, you know, she's emailing
me trying to get my attention. I just
ignore the [ __ ]
I do the opposite of what they want me
to do. I love it, bro.
Dude, I used to be like Monty. I used to
think poems would work and songs would
work. And I used to be silly, you know?
I used to think this [ __ ]
But then I learn.
>> You know what?
You know what, PJ? I might go and make
some videos or some artable content
helping some homeless people out. That's
what I might start doing. >> Yeah.
>> Do you reckon that' be good content? Yeah. >> What?
>> Going helping homeless people out.
>> Yeah. But you're going to get some hate
cuz I used to do that. If you record it,
you're gonna get hate because I used to do it.
>> No, not record it.
>> Yeah, I gave a I gave a homeless guy
Five Guys before and I got
>> come back. I'm not coming back on
YouTube. I'm done with YouTube. I'm I'm
only here now on YouTube. It's because I
don't have no one to talk to.
>> Yeah, I'm going Birmingham tomorrow to
meet the [ __ ] out of my burger. I just
had to chop my burger out.
I'm coming to Birmingham tomorrow to see you.
>> Well, it's basically today.
>> No, it's basically tomorrow.
>> Please, Natalie. I go up to Texas me.
Natalie, if you're watching, meet me in PJ tomorrow.
>> Yeah, you'll get a prize.
I've never met Natalie before. I've met
Timmy. I've met you. I've met Mike. I've met Tiger.
>> I do want Natalie, man. I've only
[ __ ] one of that. I'm not doing this
no more. I'm looking at [ __ ] money,
Mike. I'm not as ugly as him.
>> I'm a goodlook [ __ ] man. She's
>> me, me, you, Natalie in USA. Izzy,
imagine that, Joe.
Internet's going to get
>> Yeah, they get the five stars hotels for free.
They get the [ __ ] for free. It comes
talking about actually
hopefully this football bet comes in
tomorrow as well.
Yeah, [ __ ] that. You after that USA
[ __ ] I knew what they were about, bro. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that, bro.
Oh, I want to know. Anyways, what is it
with Kay and Rice for?
>> Yeah, she made me torment stuff. What I
what I do?
>> She made me torment her.
>> Go on. What? PJ.
>> No, I just saying something to
>> I need to go out on a walk or something.
>> I've already done both teams to score. I
remember being in love like Monty. Do
you remember when I was in love with
Izzy? The first one. money.
>> Yeah. You went somewhere else
when you come to England.
>> I couldn't eat. I couldn't sleep. I was
sending voice messages. I was sending voicemails.
>> And that's what I'm doing. That's what
exactly I'm doing with N.
>> Yeah. I [ __ ] love it, man. I really
[ __ ] do. You know, I [ __ ] up. I
won't [ __ ] up again.
>> Comes back to me. I get off YouTube now.
I'll be ending these live and saying,
"See you later, PJ."
But I'm all here. Like I said, cuz I
don't have no one to talk to. I'm all
[ __ ] all alone here, man.
It's weird cuz I'm charging this Xbox
controller with my Samsung charger and
it doesn't die. It's fine because of the
batteries, but when I plug it into my
Samsung charger, it doesn't die. That's
strange, isn't it?
>> Very strange, isn't it, Monty?
>> Need to find some shots.
What time is it, Pia?
>> It's 10 to uh 11.
>> It's fine. I've got some crisp so I can
eat my crisp.
You probably just missed the sex.
>> No, I'm missing Natalie. It's not the
sex. I'm missing her in person. I'm
missing waking up, saying good morning,
giving her a cuddle, giving her a kiss.
>> I miss USA Izzy's kisses. Um Joe, I miss the kisses.
>> It's just the odd words what I miss with it. like
um love you love you more or
stuff like that or you know it's just
>> I miss I miss the kisses and the little voice
>> I miss a little quite a cute little voice >> huh
>> I just miss everything about her I miss
a company I miss I just miss I'm missing
her completely I I'm not seen in
Birmingham. If not,
>> I miss eating. I miss eating the steak.
Greasy. I miss eating the steak. I miss
the kisses. I missed the little accent.
I missed a little false hope. Oh,
>> if if if she is giving me false hope and
this is just [ __ ]
I don't know.
She lost my tongue. She [ __ ] lost my
>> No bless. And she lost my dick. She lost
my tongue and she lost my dick. So I
don't know what's up with her.
>> She loves your what?
>> Well, she lost my tongue and she lost my dick.
>> What do you mean she loves your dick?
>> Well, my neck. She likes it.
>> How do you know?
>> How do I know? Cuz I don't last 5
seconds in bed.
>> I'm one of these PJ. Even she tell
yourself I'm one of these.
I I [ __ ] I can go on after even when
I've come I still can I still can have
sex. Even when I've come I still can go. >> Nah. >> Yeah.
I still can shag when I've finished.
Even when I finish I still can go for
another 10 hours.
>> Y you've never you never had a [ __ ]
and come in someone's mouth in it.
>> Yeah. cause a ped in someone's mouth. I
come in Kay's mouth.
>> Was it fun?
>> I rather come up apparently instead of a
mouth to be honest.
My goal is getting
>> I used to like coming in now. It used to be fun.
>> That's my goal. Getting every single
woman who was think we're pregnant.
That's my goal. Well,
>> bless you. What?
>> I said I bless you.
It is is my goal. Any woman you want to
sleep with, I want to get them pregnant. No money.
>> I can't get a [ __ ] money, unless I
come in their mouth. I can't. I can't.
Unless I come in her mouth, you know.
>> Unless you come.
>> You like getting a money.
>> I like Nats. I love nuts.
>> I love everything.
>> I paid £200 for a [ __ ] before if I
came in the mouth. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> I used to have a lot. Well, you don't
care when you got a lot of money in it. Yeah.
A not can't have children. Yes, she can
have children. This is what you don't
understand. Natalie can have kids, you [ __ ] It's just
>> I've never had somebody kiss me like that before,
>> G. I've never had someone kiss me like
that before. It was cute.
>> It was full of love.
>> It was just full of so much love. >> Huh?
>> I'm trying to relax.
>> Yeah, you need to relax. You don't want
You don't have a panic attack.
I'm not going to have a panic attack.
>> Cuz you used to suffer from them, didn't you?
>> No, I've never. I'm panic attacking now.
This is the first time I've ever had them. >> Yeah.
>> You should have just got off YouTube, mate.
>> Yeah. How the [ __ ] have I be ending up
with 60 quid in my bank?
>> How much? >> 60.
>> What's wrong with that?
>> What's wrong with that? I didn't have 60
quid. I had it less than 60 quid.
>> Well, that's good then, isn't it?
>> Let me see you with that sauce.
Yeah, I should go and find her.
>> How the [ __ ] have I got 60 quid end up
in my bank?
>> Is that how much you have left?
>> No, I had nothing in my bank. I had
literally four all in my bank. [ __ ]
>> At least you got something, can it?
>> Yeah. 60 [ __ ] quid.
>> It's a lot of money, isn't it?
>> It is. One second. I'll be right back. Yeah.
60 quid is not a lot of money, [ __ ] >> Yeah,
>> I'll be gone in a second.
>> 60. Give me a second. I'll be right
back. I'll be right back.
Okay. Give me one minute.
I don't have grands, mate. I [ __ ]
don't. I have about two grand. That's it. I'm [ __ ] Really?
That's what I'm doing, matey.
Yeah, it's not expensive. Go Miami. I
mean, it's like 1.1K, 1.2K. Obviously,
you need to spend the money as well.
It's hard to save money just on benefits, matey.
It's hard, isn't it? just for benefits
to save, bro. Even if you have no out
guns, it's [ __ ]
I'm going to have to start my own
business of something, bro.
He bellies pork chops
or something. I need to do something, bro.
Cuz I'm going to end up like L skin and
virgin boy. I don't want to end up like
them skin on YouTube.
No skin, mate. [ __ ] skin. The skin
the [ __ ] skin flint.
I mean, you could save. You just have to
just live off 50 60 pound a week or even
£80 a week.
You could you could save, but you would
just have to stay in
saying the worst thing. I've already
lived the life anyways, but still like yeah,
yeah, I don't have grands. I wish I did
have grands, matey.
You could gamble and try and win, but
that's not going to work.
If you got paid 7800, you can try and
win money, but it's not going to work. So
you just get rinsed.
So you're [ __ ]
Yeah. It's not really the bare minimum.
If you got if you get £,100 a month, you
got no outgoings. You can still go out and [ __ ] do [ __ ]
You can still go out and [ __ ] You
know what I mean?
It's nowhere near as bad as these people make out.
Nowhere near as as as bad as these
people make out.
Oh, Hulk Hogan died, by the way, Joe. I
don't know if you knew that Hulk Hogan died. Yep.
Yeah, Hulk Hogan died.
Don't know if you do.
Did you know
who was your favorite WWE wrestler? I
think I liked
I like giant
like Andre the Giant, but he died at a
very young age.
He died at [ __ ] 46.
Yeah, I do remember that. Andre the
Giant. He was French. I actually do
remember him. Yeah, I didn't know he
died though. She died years and years
and years ago, but I was just looking into wrestlers.
I used to like Stone Cold and The Rock.
They were my favorite.
I like John Cena. Well,
yeah. So, I just basically said,
you know, I could gamble grands if I
want to, but I just don't want to gamble
grands and lose.
Um, but yeah, Monty, I told Monty like
the best way is to try and meet other
women and just forget about the [ __ ]
cuz I know cuz I've done this [ __ ] with
these women many times before. So, yeah.
I could gamble grands, but why would I
do that, bro? And then lose.
Why would I want to gamble? Yep.
Hope I win this football bet tomorrow,
man. It's [ __ ]
I'll just pay for the whole [ __ ] Birmingham thing.
Doge of gambling.
I'm kind of stuck, bro.
I'm actually kind of stuck. What I'm
going to do, bro? I'm stuck.
Like I said, I'm not that ass about the
house cuz like I said, I lived the life
for 3 years. I'm not going to be going
out drinking every week now anyways. I'm
older now. But I still would like maybe
1.6K, 6K 1.7,
but there's just no ways to make money
now. It's sad. Oh, [ __ ]
All the delivery companies try and
saying that they're [ __ ] full when
they can't be all full. You know,
my back is hurting from like lying in
bed most of the day cuz Yeah.
And that's not from like not going out
drinking cuz I don't want to do that [ __ ] anyways. Yeah,
there's just no ways to make money at all
unless you somehow get enough money to
start a new business. It's [ __ ] up,
bro. It is [ __ ] up.
That's the frustrating part about it. I think
I used to get some hobbies and work cuz
I'm lying in bed all day. My back stop
hurting and [ __ ] cuz I'm used to being
proactive, you see. So
>> yeah, I want you. >> Yeah.
Yeah. I can't even be [ __ ] chasing
after her no more. I'm I'm done.
>> Yeah. [ __ ] her. We'll get you a bird tomorrow.
>> I am [ __ ] her. I'm [ __ ] her off. I
can't be asked. It's I'm done there now
anyways. I've been trying and trying.
I'm trying. It's
you know I'm done. I'm done. I'm I'm
just going to go back where I for to be
honest. Okay. It can't be asked. I just
told her then I just text her. I said I
am in love with you but it's okay if if
you don't want me. It's done
basically. So I'm done. I can't be asked
anymore. I'm sick of feeling like this.
I'm sick of not eating. My belly is
[ __ ] hurting the [ __ ] out of me.
>> I'm not chang.
I'm not even going to go. I'm not even [ __ ]
if a woman comes on me or hanging with
me. I'm not going there. I'm just going
to tell you to [ __ ] off or suck on your
dick, not mine.
>> Yeah, but just do it for the laws, is it?
It's not the law PJ. I'm not that kind
of person to go out to go and sh I'm not a slide.
I'm committed. I'm a I'm a dad. I'm not a [ __ ]
>> Inet. What the [ __ ] is the Inbetweeners, Mike?
>> In Between Urs. Have you never watched
In Between Us?
>> No, I don't know what that is, man.
>> You don't know what that is?
Wow. It it's J and [ __ ] Simon and
thingy. It's where they where they at
school then they talk about having sex
and the in the yellow car. It's a comedy.
>> No, I never watched it, man.
>> Yeah, I sure I showed you now. Can't
believe you never watched it.
>> No, I never, mate.
Well, like with Mr. Gilbert.
>> King Patrinos.
>> Mr. Gilbert.
>> King Petrinos.
>> I don't Of course I know what it is,
bro. I was [ __ ] with you, man.
>> Yeah, I used to like Mr. Gilbert.
>> No, Mr. Gilbert was the funniest.
>> Who's that? The the teacher.
>> The [ __ ]
>> the tall the tall one.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Not the pedo one who touches the legs.
>> Nah, no. Mr. Gilbert, he was the funniest.
>> I've I've lost a lot of weight. I need
to get my weight back up, man. I need to
sort myself out. I'm never going down
this road again.
>> Yeah, but Monty, do you know Mr. Monty?
Do you know
>> Monty? Do you know Mr. Gilbert?
>> Mr. Gilbert? Yeah. It's all gray.
>> Did you find him funny?
No, not really.
>> I thought he was funny.
>> Jay's the funniest.
>> No, I like Gilbert.
>> I like Gilbert. And there was another one.
>> Neil. Neil.
>> No, I like I like I like um Will. I like
Will and Gilbert.
Will the one with the glasses on? >> Yeah.
>> What about Neil?
>> Yeah, he was funny as well.
J I thought J was a little bit childish on it. >> Yeah,
>> he J weren't even funny. J I don't think
J were funny.
Not like [ __ ] >> um
>> Oh, no. No. I told you who I like, bro.
No, no, no. You know Jay's dad. Jay's
dad was funny.
>> Yeah. In a car fan, you know.
>> Oh, he was funny as [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
Jay's dad was funny.
>> He takes piss out of his son. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. when he's talking about having sex
with all these women and his dad's comes
and only what you've had sex with a [ __ ]
>> At least you've got 60 left in it. >> Yeah.
>> Loving life, aren't you?
>> I don't know. I got like 60. It's
probably like 50 quid. He ended up back
in my bank.
>> Why are you acting like£60 is not a lot?
Yeah, it is.
>> It's not a lot.
>> How is it not a lot?
60 quid's not a lot. >> Why?
>> Because how many 20 quids are in a in um this what?
>> Four. Three. Sorry. Three.
>> Yeah. Three. 20 quid.
>> I used to gamble £80 every week. Yeah.
To try to get to 300. >> Yeah.
And sometimes I'd win like 300. It's
good, isn't it? 300. That's not bad, is
>> No, it's not bad. No.
>> Yeah. I used to gamble when I used to
get No, 60. I used to get 60 every week
and I used to try and gamble it to 250
300 and then just buy myself some stuff with the
money. I guess >> I [Music]
give you mine is broke. I am done with
[ __ ] women. Yes, I am.
>> Monty, why do these people try to take
the piss out of how much money I I get?
>> Because they don't come out with money.
I've not on YouTube every day. >> Yeah.
Yeah, I get £1,100 a month. So what? At
least I don't lie, you know.
I'm leaving Birmingham.
I get paid. Once I get paired, I'm
going. I'm not staying here. I'm going.
I've been trying to
>> Monty. I used to get £700 a month. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. It was [ __ ] I used to get £700 a
month. It was bad.
>> I get two of that. >> Yeah.
>> I get 790
on both of my money.
I've come out with quite a bit of money, but
I've got Natalie quite a lot of [ __ ] to
be honest coming. I've already ordered
Natalie a TV, a new set. Obviously,
she's already got a set in the bedroom,
but I've ordered a
she's got the set in the bedroom, but
it's just like one that is like it's
just a single set
>> and that's got a collection. It's like a blue
um old set. So I got one of them as
well. I spent like what?
>> 300 plus 300. That's basically 67.
I was doing the delivery job. Yeah. And
I made £88 in 9 hours. >> £88.
>> In 9 hours.
>> That [ __ ]
>> Yeah. But if you done it Yeah. Say you
done it 4 days a week,
you'd make money in it.
>> No, not really. Then
>> how wouldn't you?
>> If you done four days, you'd probably
make like [ __ ] over £300.
>> So why did you keep it?
>> Yeah, cuz it was hard, bro.
>> What? What? What did you do after pedal toes? >> Yeah.
>> Well, on Have you got a bet pedal bike, have you? >> Huh?
>> What? Have you got a pedal bike?
>> No, I was renting one.
>> Okay. So, that cost more money just to rent one.
>> Yeah, but no, it was like £12 a day
though, so it weren't that much
cuz you can make £100 in a day easy.
So, like you'd still be making money.
You know what I'm saying?
>> I just get your own bike and do it.
>> No, because then you have to worry about
it getting stolen and then the battery
running out cuz it was an ebike. It was
like an electric pedal bike. You see,
>> I've been offered a job. Literally, I've
been offered a job if these
>> money. Say you done it Monday to Sunday.
How much money do you think you'd make?
>> You'd make easily £500 a week. Easy
job in Birmingham. I think it was Yeah,
I got offered a job today,
but I'm not doing it. I'm not doing it.
I'm a [ __ ]
>> I thought um of one of these people that
we were talking to today, they offered
me a job
>> kind of thing to get me out of the house
and to do things and that, but I said no to it.
>> Do you think Do you think the Uber job
was good, Bobby? I think it was good me.
Yeah, I think it was good me.
It's just [ __ ] long.
>> I me smelling this belly button, man. >> Really?
>> Yeah. She's got the most cutest belly button ever.
>> This is who I was in love with. This
person. This person from America. Look,
Monty. She was cute, isn't it?
I'm in love with Natalie, man.
>> No, she's cute.
>> I think she understands how much I love her, man.
>> Don't you like this one in my picture? >> Anyway,
>> you like the one in my picture?
>> Oh, no. It's too skinny for me. >> No.
What do you think of the Uber thing,
Bobby? It's good, isn't it? What? He
couldn't do it. He's too lazy.
We need to try to find ways to make
money, Bobby. It's impossible, lad.
I'm trying this [ __ ] deliver roofing,
but they keep saying that they've got
too many drivers, which is impossible
cuz I applied 3 years ago.
See, if you get accepted with that, you
can make 150 a day. 100%. You can make
you can make 15 to 20 an hour. the SG
camera. They just don't give new accounts anymore
for some reason. I tried changing the
address and they're just not having none of it.
They just weren't having none of it at all.
So, we're pretty much [ __ ]
Unless you [ __ ] I don't know what you
could do. There's nothing you can do.
[ __ ] shoplift. Sell your [ __ ] ass.
No, it's not about the rules. They just
don't give new accounts anymore.
And trust me, with that, you could
probably make about £1,000 a week on
that. You can do
um but they just don't give new
accounts. I mean, I applied 3 years ago.
I still chase them up, nothing. So, yeah.
You're [ __ ] unless you can start your
own business of some kind restaurant or
but it's very hard nowadays.
You go through the route of trying to
win money but obviously you can lose money.
>> Yeah, I've just text now saying I am
done but I told her I've just got a new
TV and a new set on its way.
>> Yeah, you could do that. You could do
that. People do do it, but it's a risk.
Are you going to get your money? Um,
people do do it. Yeah. But they put a
verification thing on it now where you
need to verify yourself. >> Um,
>> yeah, it's very hard. But then you got
to obviously take into account what if
you don't if they don't give you your
money. See, I'd pay £130 a week to rent
an account. But the thing is is um
is obviously are they going to give you your money?
So it's bad, bro. I don't know.
>> PJ just to show that I'm not ass. Look,
look. It hasn't been crying over woman
peeps. Oh, it won't let me put it on.
>> Did I?
No, we're going to change how you don't
know how you can do it.
>> Do what?
>> Just talking about saving money, trying
to get money and that.
>> See, it's not it's hard, but it's also easy.
>> How's it easy?
And another thing is you can get SIA
badge. You can get a CI what's called SI
badge. You can get a security badge.
Yeah. and not even get shifts.
That's the thing. You can get you can
get a security badge and and not even get shifts.
That's the thing. So, there's nothing
you really can do really. So,
but yeah, I was thinking of an account.
>> I'm just going to go the same as you.
I'm just going to have my time on like
this as well. Okay. Off myself.
You can rent a couch. Yeah,
I don't really trust anyone.
>> What do you not trust?
>> They won't pay me. Do you like that
picture of me, Monty?
>> Keep it on.
>> You like it?
>> It's all right. Oh,
>> I can't I can't I can't keep looking at
that picture of Natalie and myself. I
just can't keep looking. I I'm never
ever going to delete my pictures. Never.
>> Oh, bless you. >> Keeping
I need to stop with her now. I do. I do.
I just need to stop with her. I need to
stop. I thought so. You never seen
You've never seen my mom, have you, Monty?
>> Yeah, I've seen your mom. Yeah, [Music]
>> this is my mom.
No, it's not your mom.
>> Yeah, it is.
>> No, it's not.
>> This is my mom.
>> The one in the black.
>> Okay, P. Yeah. Okay. Yeah, that's your
mom in the black. Yeah,
>> that's my mom.
>> Do you still see your mom, do you, Pidge?
>> Nope. She abandoned me.
>> It's YouTube, is it? YouTube.
>> She abandoned me. She's now in Florida. >> What?
>> She's in Florida.
>> What's she doing in Florida?
>> That's where she she moved to.
>> Why she left you? >> Because
she abandoned me.
>> Wow. You know what? I will never ever
ever abandon my kids. Not like that. I
would never. Obviously, they live with
my mom. Yeah. But I would never leave
countries. Never. Don't care how old they are.
>> Yeah. I I got abandoned.
>> You know what? I need to start putting
my my family first before anyone.
>> Maybe maybe you can maybe you can be my
foster parent, Monty.
>> Well, you want me to be your daddy, do you? PJ,
>> because obviously my dad died and my mom
abandoned me, so
>> Oh, okay then. PG. Yeah. Um, send me the
[ __ ] adopted papers over there. Fill
them in. Yeah.
>> Well, you'll adopt me.
>> I adopt you. Yeah. Go on, PJ. Yeah. You
can start calling me daddy now.
>> Okay. Okay then. Cuz at the moment, I'm an orphan. >> You're
an orphan? Yeah.
>> What do you think? Do you think my mommy
looks like me?
That's not your mom.
>> Yeah, it is.
>> Isn't it? Your mom wrinkly.
>> You want to smoke?
>> That's my mommy.
>> Oh, that's my mom.
>> [ __ ] I don't know what I'm going to
do now with [ __ ] everything. What?
Natalie's got me
like with the shorts and t-shirts and
[ __ ] like that. She's got me. I'm
keeping them, but it's hard to look at
them. You know, when a woman gets you
something, who you being with? >> Yeah.
>> And you know what? She's actually
teached me a lot about clothes. You
don't need branded clothes. And she's
taught me that
you can only
>> Bobby, can you find new ways to make
money, please? Puppy.
>> That's my mama.
>> These are be fuming.
>> That's my mommy. Is it? >> Yep.
It's my mama. We look like each other in
it. Same hair.
>> If a woman If a woman who's got children
is called a mil,
what is a man called who's got kids?
>> How do I get paid, Bobby? I don't get paid.
I'm on £1,100 a month. How am I going to
get How do I get paid, bro? I'm [ __ ] People
>> if if a woman has got children, she's
called a mil. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> So if a man has got children,
what what is he called?
>> I can't.
>> No, but it needs to be a self-employed
job because I need flexible hours.
I need I I I need flexible hours. You
know what that means?
>> Some balls.
What am I going to do, peeps? Only what
I can say is now Natalie, if you're
watching, yeah, meet me. But she won't
meet me, so there's no point in me saying that.
>> Bobby, can you help me?
Well, I'm going to be skinned soon, man.
>> I've been going on about Natalie all
day, Anna. I need to shut the [ __ ] up now.
>> You just want her to suck your willie again.
>> No, I just want her to talk to me for 5
minutes. I only want 5 minutes. Five
[ __ ] minutes and then I let it go.
Let it go now. Anyway,
>> what's five minutes? Do you know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> What? What is 5 minutes? Nothing.
Absolutely nothing. And if she ever
loved me, then she would give me 5
minutes to esplain and then she can go
do whatever she wants. Then
>> I will be one day, bro.
I will be skipped one day.
>> Trust me.
>> [ __ ] depressed.
>> Give you five minutes.
>> Do you know what PJ I might end up do?
I'm I'm just going to play a woman back
at her own games now. [ __ ] it. A woman.
>> That's what I was telling That's what
I've been telling you all [ __ ] day.
>> [ __ ] it. I can't be asked. I've noticed
with women, they think about all
different men where one man where man
only thinks about one woman.
>> I was trying to tell you this all day, DBY.
>> If I knew that Natalie would have done
this, I would have moved to Ria. I would have [ __ ]
>> This is what I was telling you all [ __ ] day.
>> I would have even got rid of my [ __ ] dad
if I knew that this [ __ ] was going to
happen. I told you this place.
>> I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done.
I'm completely done. I am never ever
ever doing anything for a woman again
like I've done with women.
>> My story is worse. That my story is
worse though. I bought my mommy a nice
steak and then she abandoned me and left the country. No,
>> mine's worse. I had to get rid of my dog. My dog.
>> I got [ __ ] abandoned.
Only what I've got left of my [ __ ]
dog peeps is this.
Only what I got left of Diesel is that
his [ __ ] dog born and his [ __ ] thing.
So I still got his toys and there
is the dog now.
>> He's still alive. He's in Birmingham.
>> Let me tell you know the maddest thing
about this as well. Um, the maddest
thing about this as well, Monty, is you
know your dog, your dog, you know your
dog, right? Any any dog, they stay with
you forever and they don't betray you. A
[ __ ] I know. I know. A woman does
betray you. A woman does
>> a dog will love you forever.
>> Yeah, I know. But no matter what
mistakes you make, that dog will still
stand by your side.
>> Yep. Should have stuck with a dog, buddy.
>> I should have. I [ __ ] should have. I
really should have. I'm not saying it in
a nasty way because I love Natalie.
You know what I mean? But I I shouldn't
have got rid of my dog. I should have
stayed where I if I knew all this was
going to happen. If I knew this is all
Lisa's fault. I blame Lisa for all this [ __ ]
Because if Lisa didn't give out her address.
>> Yeah. Then then Natalie would have been in trouble.
You trying back?
>> I told my mom I'm going to try and get
Diesel back from the dog shelters, but
my mom said just leave him. Leave him
just because there's no point. Just leave him.
I do want him back, but my mom just said
leave him. It's not It's not fair. Just
Just leave him.
>> Yeah, women are nasty, bro.
>> They are. They are. They don't. Women
don't understand men at all. Obviously,
women are being abused by men, you know,
but women don't understand how men feel
or what they go through or
>> and you know the maddest thing is
they're the evil one. They they're the
one they're the ones that's supposed to
have feelings and stuff. They don't.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, no, they don't. They
don't. If they had feelings, they've
been ringing you up straight away trying
to sort it out. But it's always a man.
I've noticed that. I bet she's probably
she's probably sucking on some she's
probably sucking on some other guy's knob now.
>> Yeah, PJ.
>> Yeah, but you never know.
>> No, just knowing that it hurts me. I
don't want her to do that. I don't want
her to [ __ ] around like that,
you know. It's not like she did have
feelings for me, man. And then she won't
be doing this. I don't even think she
has got feelings for me. It's not like,
yeah, I've been there for her and she's
been there for me. We both been there
for each other. We both been through the same [ __ ]
>> We both strong. We both are strong together.
It's just when one of us [ __ ] up and
goes on to YouTube. It's the same when
Natalie went went live. I told her not
to in Blackpool because I knew that that
they were going to ring up the hotel. I
told her not to. I said, "Wait till we
go on and then go live." But she didn't.
She went live straight up in the pool
room playing pool.
>> That would annoy me if you say Izzy here
was sucking someone else's dick whilst I
was like [ __ ] mad and [ __ ] That
would piss me off, bro. Would it piss you off?
>> It is pissing me off. This is pissing me
>> It is completely pissing me off. It's
getting ignored for one.
Getting ignored off a woman for one.
That's something. What I don't want is
not to ignore me. I want her to at least
be my friend.
That's it. She don't have to go out with
me. She don't want to go out with me
again because I [ __ ] up on YouTube. I
just need her. I just need her. I
haven't got nobody.
I need Natalie as a friend or a girlfriend.
I need her.
>> How old are you, Monty?
>> I'm 35.
>> So, you're 36 this year? Yeah.
>> Yeah, I'm 36 this year. Yeah.
>> You're getting [ __ ] old, son.
>> Oh, yeah. I'm getting there, aren't I?
Yeah, you'll be 40 in four years.
That's mad, bro.
>> Yeah, I'm 36 this year. My same age as
Natalie. Natalie is already 36. I'm 35,
but when Natalie is still 36, I be 36.
So, me and Natalie, we're both the same.
You know, I've never died.
>> Did she ever mention me?
Now Natalie's not in her 20s. Natalie's
36. She's older than me. Nalie,
Natalie doesn't even know what older old daughter is.
Does Natalie have anxiety, Monty?
>> I'm not talking about Natalie's issues or problems. >> Okay,
Monty, why does Lord J say people have anxiety?
>> Because Lord J's got anxiety.
>> It's the truth though, is it? Every It's
like a reverse, isn't it, Monty?
Everything they say is definite. >> Yeah.
>> I love it when you do that, bro. It's so
funny. It's like a reverse. Yeah. >> What? >> Huh?
>> What? Like I I refresh it all back on to them.
>> Yeah. Cuz it's Yeah. Cuz it's true, isn't it?
>> Yeah. They call them skin cuz they skin.
They call you a fing. It's cuz they're a [ __ ] Yeah.
>> You you even said they get themselves
confused, didn't it, with us?
>> Yeah, they do. They do. They completely
get themselves confused with us.
>> So, how long is that 60 going to last you?
>> Not long.
>> Maybe talk like 3 days.
>> She's probably dead.
Well, how long?
>> Not long.
>> It's not that.
>> I can't eat. So, this my money's basically
being stalker for ages. But Natalie has
taught me how to save money, how to put
money to a side and all that. But she's
Natalie taught me that and that's what
what I've been doing. I get paid what in
16 to 15 days.
Do you know what I mean? So, and I've
still got kind of 60 quid there from last month.
How much you got left for 15 days? >> Yeah.
>> So, what are you going to do? You're
[ __ ] in it.
>> Yeah, I'm [ __ ] Really?
>> Yeah. I'm put completely foot.
>> So what are you going to do? [ __ ] buy
money off your mom.
>> If I need to. I need to.
>> You went through a lot of money. Jeez.
You went through a lot, bro.
Yeah, because I've got Natalie. I got
Natalie a new TV
like brand new TV.
I've got a one. It's coming soon. And if
you don't believe me, I'll [ __ ] pull
it up on YouTube when it gets here.
Um, I've also got Natalie a new seti as
well and the same ones that she's got in
the room like a blue one, but it's a
single one to go with them both.
So, I've got all that for Natalie. I'm trying to
>> So, you must have had like three So, you
had £300 in your bank and you bought a TV
>> basically. Yeah.
>> You're [ __ ] mad. You, man.
>> Yeah. I got that TV for Natalie Lo. It's
Natalie's TV. Not my TV. It's her TV. I
got it for her.
You're crazy, bro.
>> Because the TV what she's got is a
[ __ ] It's a [ __ ] old [ __ ] one. So,
I've got a actual one with a [ __ ] TV
remote. A [ __ ]
smart ass T. It's smart. It's a proper smart TV. Proper smart.
Obviously, if I can Yeah.
>> How am I getting back to Manchester with
no money? I'll walk I will walk back to Manchester.
How am I getting back to Manchester?
>> You need to start saving some money in it.
>> And that's what I'm doing now. Saving my
money up. I've quit weed. Soon as I have more money
now this month anyways.
>> Yeah. I've quit weed.
>> Would you walk? PJ going to meet
halfway? Yeah. Start walking now. >> Nah.
>> No. Fine. Don't Don't walk.
Why are you going to Birmingham tomorrow? Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, man.
>> I know. We're going to get a drink.
>> Yeah, we go for a drink in it.
I'm not I'm not I'm not picking up no
women page yet.
>> Well, can you drink?
>> Yeah, I can drink. Yeah, I drink, but
I'm not picking up no women.
How much do you reckon we'll spend
tomorrow on drinks? 100 quid. >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] knows. I've only got 60. So, I need
to save that then for tomorrow.
>> £60 is enough.
>> Yeah, I know. I need to go in that West
Bank and get that out.
>> I'll probably spend about maybe 100. Yeah.
>> Oh, God.
>> But I can stay with you.
Yeah. Yeah, you can stay here.
Yeah, that's not bad then. Yeah,
PJ is loaded. No, I'm not loaded, mate.
I wish I was.
I'm [ __ ] just like everyone else now.
>> I'm not loaded, bro. I'm [ __ ]
>> PJ, I can get you a [ __ ] room here.
You know, you'd be rich then. You only
pay 40 quid a month. Really?
>> Yeah. I can get you a room here.
>> How much is loaded to you, Lo?
How much do you class as loaded?
I remember when I had this money, bro. It's good.
I remember when I had this money. I won
in the casino. Monty. Yeah. This
>> This is a lot of money, is it? Monty,
this is a lot, is it?
Money's money is just [ __ ] paper or a
tree. I don't know why people get
excited over it.
Just let me teach you something about
>> Okay. Just say this here, PJ. Right. If
I had a book, just say like marble book. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> A complete
>> And no, just say you had the marble
book. You had the marble book and you
were selling that marble book for 30 quid. Yeah.
I give you 30 quid for that marble book.
Yeah. You're going to spend that 30
quid. That that 30 quid is going to be gone. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Now I will still have that marble book
and that marble book each year will go
up in price.
Each year I'm coming making more money.
I'm coming I'm coming to
>> I'm coming to Birmingham tomorrow and
I'm going to do you.
>> You [ __ ] not doing me? Are you [ __ ]
>> I'm going to come and do you?
>> I'm not PJ.
>> That's what that means.
>> I'm going to do you. That was that's
what it means. I'm going to do you up the ass.
>> No, bro.
>> Man, I've had
I've had women ask me out for these last
couple of days and that when I've been
on [ __ ] trying to socialize with
people and that and like meet me and
[ __ ] like that, but I've been saying no.
I'm not I'm not I don't want anyone. I
don't want I don't want a relationship
anymore to be honest. I'm done. It's
only one woman I want and she's just
completely ignoring me. If that's the
case, I am done with women.
>> I nearly got myself [ __ ] sexed
yesterday. I was going to be
>> I was going to be another cosmate Kitty. >> Yeah.
>> Did you [ __ ] That were meant last
night's chat though, was it?
>> Last night's chat with me last night.
Oh, [ __ ] up.
>> I'm coming to see you tomorrow.
>> No, that's fine, PJ. That's fine.
>> So, what we We're not going to put on
YouTube, are we? >> No.
>> Do you know why?
>> Because the girl's kicked out the
>> Yeah. And Timmy will come here.
>> A not really.
>> We'll go live. life over in your house.
>> Yes, he has fought me off because of my
mistakes coming on YouTube. It's my
fault. It were my fault I shouldn't have
come on YouTube like they had the hotel.
But I'm sick of getting kicked out of
[ __ ] hotels. I'm sick of getting
kicked out of [ __ ] houses. What does
she want me to do? Sit there and be
quiet and not do nothing. I went on
YouTube because I was just angry and
that's why she's ended it with me.
[ __ ] stupidness or what? Not me. It's
[ __ ] stupid that just ended it all
for something so pathetic.
It's not like I've cheated on her. It's
>> No, I think No, I think it's pathetic
that these people get you kicked out of places.
>> Yeah. Yeah. But that's why she didn't
want me going on YouTube because of
that. But the hotel, the hotel was
already finished. It was already going home.
>> We was already going home.
So the hotel was already done. I I went
live is cuz I was angry. I'm ang I was
angry of a matter of fact is that every
single woman keeps kicking me out of
hotel rooms. Last time I got kicked out
of a hotel room was in black [ __ ]
pool. I was out all night. All [ __ ]
I was all night was out all night. I had
to sleep on a [ __ ] balcony for [ __ ] sake.
Then then [ __ ] the hotel
what we went to a couple of days ago.
I woke her up by accident. I went
toilet, come back out, picked my can up
just check if there was any in it cuz we
dehydrated a little bit. There was
nothing in it. So, I was about to go
back to sleep, but I woke Natalie up.
Natalie started stressing out at me and
then told me to get out of the hotel.
So, so I did. I [ __ ] off out the hotel,
>> you know what I mean? But she she But
she's going to expect me to stay alert
and not be angry at that. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? I'm sick of
getting kicked out of places off women
like with K with with Kaye. I kept on
getting kicked out of the house. If I
didn't leave the house, she kicked the
dog out the house.
>> Natalie Natalie tells me to go. I leave.
I just leave. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? But it's so I
don't hate Natalie. I do not hate her. I
love her. And the son be like do this to
>> Monty, you Monty, you live off£50 a week. >> [ __ ] >> huh?
>> My money comes and goes, PJ
comes and goes. It comes.
>> I'm just a big spender.
>> Yeah, cuz you're rich.
>> Have you even seen my survival [ __ ]
What? What? I spend my money on. >> No,
>> I show you now. Right. First thing we got
is this. We've had this for ages. You
know what this is, peeps? This is my [ __ ] torch.
What? This is my survival torch.
Obviously, it's got light bulbs on it.
This has got a light bulb, PJ. I show
you the light bulb. Lightbulb.
So there's the light bulb PJ.
So that's So there's the light bulb.
It's connected to this.
So that's my light bulb.
Turn that off.
>> Take that out of there. So that's my
light bulb. So that comes with that.
Yeah. I'll show you what else I've got.
Turn the camera off. Okay. This
this comes with that.
So all these come together. So that's a
son panel to charge that up. Sonal panel.
Um we come here.
>> Someone said no wonder Natalie [ __ ] you off. >> Why?
Trust me. You don't even understand me, peeps.
Survival phone charger.
That's a phone charger. And we got more
[ __ ] peeps. We've got this PJ.
>> We've got this.
>> So, it's a So, so it's a plug so you can
watch like TV.
Um, you can charge your phones up on this.
>> Do Do you know Do you know Ant-Man, Bobby?
>> One second. Hey, did you go Ant-Man? >> Antman?
>> Antman said even if he didn't do the
shoplifting, yeah, he would still go
Thailand. It would just take him 4
months. He would just live off £50 a
week and then go in 4 months
on benefits. Yeah.
Monty's a big spender.
See, I've even got these people. You
know how expensive these are? You know
how expensive these are? It's not a 10,
by the way.
>> Yeah, he he loved he loves he loves he
loves Thailand, Bobby, because he went
to Thailand because he said the women
just aren't interested in this country.
So, he went to Thailand and then he's he
loves it there.
>> He loves Thailand. this country, PJ, the
women in this country, the thing is is
us man men are too soft with these
[ __ ] British women. That's why these
British women run circles around us British men.
You know what I mean?
>> He said they're just not interested in this country.
You know what that means?
>> That there's no women interested in a British man.
You look, you're all looking in the wrong places.
>> We're going to find some to my mat out of me.
Natalie, she's in my head.
>> Yeah, it's hard. It's hard to Did you
used to watch my approaching videos,
Bobby? Did you used to watch them?
>> Well, here we go. And this PJ,
do you know what this is?
It's a paddle. She PJ look.
>> They're not
boyfriends. Bobby, it's boring.
>> Yeah, I'm watching, bro.
>> Yeah. So, this
>> I'm only I'm only I'm only trying
tomorrow cuz I'm meeting Monty in
Birmingham. That's the only reason.
>> Yeah. This is a phone charger as well, PJ
M. There's nothing there, but yeah, this
is a phone charger. You put your wire in there
and you stand out in sun and it charges
your phone up.
So, all this is my survival [ __ ] What
I've got to show you it all in one.
[ __ ] quite a bit. I don't need
anything else, mate. I'm I'm already set
for the apocalypse.
>> I hate it, Bobby. I hate it, mate. This
[ __ ] bors me, bro.
I hate it.
Monty thinks it's funny.
Right. Here we go. PJ.
All right. So, we got the son panel
there. That's a phone charger.
This basically charges up anything and
you can watch TV or whatever with that.
And that was just me ass talking.
Yeah, you got the all this is like okay
all expensive, man.
>> They're not interested, Bobby. I got 30
numbers two weeks ago and I didn't even
get one date. They just play games with
me every time.
>> Yeah, that's why I turn my camera off
cuz no one cares.
>> I do care, bro. Sorry.
>> No, no, no, you don't.
>> Yeah, I do. People would care when they
care when they when they when they run
out of electric and when the [ __ ]
power cuts start happening and they be
like, "I wish I [ __ ] I was with [ __ ]
this second cuz he can charge up my phone."
>> Monty, so you got to buy some food tomorrow?
>> Uh, no. I'm not eating, PG. I'm not eating.
>> Are you taking a piss? You've actually
got £60 to last you two weeks. >> Yeah.
>> You're [ __ ] then.
>> If you don't believe If you don't
believe I can screenshot that and show you that,
>> then you'll be [ __ ] up then. Is it?
>> I have [ __ ] up. I haven't [ __ ] You
just see me smash my burger up in the
kitchen. I ain't had nothing to eat.
I've only been nibbling [ __ ] Look, I've
even left I've even left my chips. Look,
that's unlike me to leave my chips on a
McDonald's and punch my burger through.
I've even [ __ ]
I've even ch my milkshake away.
I ain't even been eating, drinking, or
nothing. Do you know
>> how he doing drinking is paying for
everything? Nah, £60 enough for a night
out. Is it Monty?
It should be.
>> Yeah, it is. We'll get some food and
weather spoons, won't we?
>> Yeah. I just said that we [ __ ] get
some food and [ __ ] go and get some
beer in the house. Have a drink in the
>> Nah, I need to get some [ __ ]
>> Yeah. No, you want to go out. You want
to go out and get some birds in it?
Yeah, man. I want to listen to some I
want I want to go to a club and I want
to I want to listen to some music as
well. Some good music in the club, you know.
Now I can talk about birds now. No, I'm
only investing. I'm only talking about
Natalie. PJ, if you pull a woman. Yeah.
>> Literally. Yeah. I'm not pulling nobody. Just [ __ ]
if if a woman comes up to me, I'm just
going to say, "Listen, I've got a
girlfriend. I'm with somebody." That's
only what I'm going to be saying all
night. I'm going to be pointing
>> and I'm going to tell them that you're single.
No, don't be telling them that I'm single.
Don't tell any. No, cuz I don't want I
don't I don't [ __ ] want to go out and
[ __ ] start pulling women. I'm I'm not like that.
One woman know I love his nicely actually.
PJ, would you have this phone?
>> Huh? Would you have one board?
>> Yeah, it's nice one. I saw it yesterday.
>> Would you have it? Yeah.
>> The back of it.
>> Do you know what phone this is?
>> I forget the name.
>> It's a nothing phone. It's called of
nothing. Monty, you're lying. You don't
only have £60. Don't be silly.
>> Oh my god.
You know what? We do have to prove it to
you. For [ __ ] sake. Let me back in.
>> Yeah, but how But how is that even possible?
>> Put a link up.
I show you how much you'll come out with
if you're really that interested, people.
>> No, not I don't care how much you come
out with, but how how are you going to
live off the 60? Yeah.
>> 60 pound. >> Yeah.
>> Put a link up. >> PG
and I show you. >> Yeah.
>> What link?
>> Chat link. Chat link so I can come back in.
>> Okay. I can't. What? [Music]
There you go, Con. 60.
That's mad, bro.
I just got 80 in one account.
I just got 80. I just got paid £80 in one account. Yeah. [Music]
What are you going to do, Monty? I'm sure [Music]
he's getting anything on my bank. I saw
you. I saw you.
I was going else.
There you go. £605.
Jesus. Yeah. Told you. Show you how much
money I rarely come out with though.
There's the 700. Oh [ __ ] One sec.
>> Oh yeah. >> There. >> Yeah. >> 498.
Right. That's one payment.
Go to my second payment.
Oh [ __ ] One sec. 7 9 0 07.
>> Yeah, there you go.
That's one payment.
Look at all these transactions come through.
>> You should still have money, Monty. >> What?
>> You should still have money.
>> You should have still have money. No,
>> look. Seven. There's another one.
>> Yeah, you should still have money.
See how bird I'm
not skin but I am skin now
you see peeps I'm not skin I've got good
money me peeps come out with good money
you want to come out with good money PJ
>> yeah for not working yeah definitely bro
you should still have money now. What
the [ __ ] How the [ __ ] have you gone
through [ __ ] 15 over £1,500? Taxes, takeaways, taxes, takeaways.
All my shit's been takeaways and [ __ ] like that. >> Huh?
>> Nah, bro. Not You must have been doing
more than that.
>> N rinsed him. N didn't rinse me rinsed
me at all.
N's never [ __ ] took money off me.
Never. I've always given N money, but
she's always give money back to me.
>> It wasn't 500 for TV. It was 300.
>> The TV is 300.
Look what I've still got with me. I took
it off last night. Lord,
that was around me. The hospital [ __ ] thing.
Yeah, look what what I found on my legs
as well yesterday.
I didn't even know I had them on my
legs. Come on, put my pants off. I've
seen that these on my legs
of the doctors. They left them on my legs. >> Mad
doctors left them on my legs yesterday.
Bless you, Monty.
>> Oh yeah, he was cutting yourself long.
You know, peeps, that's not funny. Me
cutting myself, you know. I only wanted
to do myself.
>> It's not funny. I wanted to do a Nerf for that,
like a tattoo kind of thing for that.
Like a N. I've done a no literally I've
done a letter no on me hand but it won't
sky all you look look
can't even hardly see I've done
>> you can't
>> nerfing that
you can't even hardly see it but it's there scrapes down m you
Never do it.
>> I just got paid. I just got paid. I just
got paid £80. Bobby, what should I do with £80?
>> Get a train up here now.
>> Yeah, I'm coming. I'm coming. No, not
now. I'm coming later, you idiot.
>> Later. What time?
>> Uh 4 5.
Come earlier you nap, man. [ __ ] hell.
Spend a day with me, man. >> 1.
>> Yeah. Come at one. >> Okay.
>> Yeah. Go get your haircut. Get your
haircut and just come.
>> Yeah, I will.
>> I'm missing Natalie, man.
I need to stop with her. I don't stop
bringing her up. I just can't help it.
>> Monty, [ __ ] are so good in it.
>> What is it with your own [ __ ]
>> I don't know. I just like them.
>> L you come here then. Yeah, I give you a
[ __ ] then. Yeah.
>> How do you explain what they feel like?
They feel like wet in it. It's like
warm, isn't it?
>> No pedia. I just need a woman to love me
to to love me for who I am for you know
to begin with for what I do.
>> That's what I want. I want a woman to
understand me for who I am.
But obviously no woman will understand
me for who I you know they won't
I'm done with women. I'm done now
anyway. I can't be
if Natalie rings me I'll pick the phone
up straight away to her. Obviously,
cause if Natalie says, "Sort yourself
out and give and we give it another go."
That's fine. I will cook and I'm sorting myself out.
You know, I need to This is why I've
quit the weed. I haven't had a joint for two days.
>> Money, £80 a week ain't bad, is it? >> What?
>> £80 extra a week ain't bad, is it?
>> It depends. Yeah,
>> it still money, isn't it?
>> Yeah, it's still money, but it depends
if you got food in because if you need a
food shop, then that £8 is just going to
go on a food truck. So, that's not even
going to last you.
>> No, like you you can do you can do food
shopping with like 50
>> what? Microwave meals? Yeah.
>> No, like if you went to the supermarket,
>> you know, I'm on about to last you the
week. 15 quid won't last a week.
>> I said 50.
>> Oh, 50.
>> Yeah, you could. 50 would. 100. Yeah.
Would 50 wood
for a single person?
>> For a single person.
>> So listen, Bobby, listen to me. Yeah. If
you were saving to go on holiday, right?
One second, Monty. Yeah. Say you were
saving to go to America and you got
11200 a month. Yeah. So you'd have to
live off like £80 a week for like 4
months in it
to be able to go in it.
You'd have to be able to live off for 80 pound for like
four months and you could go I guess it >> Yeah.
>> I might get a hair implant me PJ
save like just spend just live off £80 a
week in it.
>> Yeah. [ __ ] off. We can't live off £80.
Well, yeah, you can actually.
>> You can live off 80 a week. I mean, if
you didn't go out drinking, just food
and that. You could live off 80 week.
>> Yo, PJ, I'm done me getting you go boss
now. Me, I don't get you go boss no more, man.
>> Wait, but listen. How much do you spend
a week? Like a 100. Is it >> me? >> You
me? No, no, no. I don't spend 100. I
spend more than 100 in a week. >> How?
>> My money doesn't even last me a week.
>> Well, your benefits.
>> But both my money, my money don't even
last me. It will ship my 700 what I get.
Natalie will even tell you. It doesn't
last me a week.
>> That's crazy, boy.
>> It does not last me a week. Now, Natalie
will tell you herself.
Because I got paid my first payment,
spent all that in a second. Yeah. I get
paid a week after each other. The week
after that, I got paid my disability
money. That all went. This is only what
I got left. Out my disability money. 60 quid.
>> You spend it under. It can't just be
takeaways and [ __ ]
>> Takeaways and taxes.
So what? You spent um almost £800 in a
week in in in less than a week?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Taxes take taxes take away. Taxes take
away taxi takeaway. Taxi take away taxi
takeaway. Taxi take away taxes take Literally.
>> So did you struggle last month as well?
struggle. I strugg we I struggle. I I
didn't even talk myself out was like
trying to quit the weed. It's not that I
see things and I want it and when I live
I see it, I want it. >> Yeah.
I get you.
>> You know what I mean?
>> I'm just more careful with money
nowadays cuz it's so hard to get. I just
try to be careful with it, you know? >> Yeah.
Money is money to me. I don't give a
[ __ ] about money. I rather not have
>> to be honest with you. That's why I
spend it all in one >> really.
>> Yeah. Do you know how much I give my
kids spense every month? I don't know if
Gibson spent or not, but I get I give my
kids money every single month.
>> Someone said that's why you live in a tent. Live
>> in a tent. I don't live in a tent.
>> You big massive tent then.
>> Come through back today. Um, Bobby, it
returns 285. Fingers crossed. E.
>> 285 return.
It's a good return, isn't it? Monty. >> Yeah.
>> Monty likes Cole. Does
>> Kerry me mate?
>> No. You like Sher Cole. Kerry.
Why do you think it's going to come in
Bobby? No, you don't know who Jerel Cole is.
>> Call of course, mate. She got She's done
a [ __ ] expat.
Gra's got talent judge.
>> Yeah, she's [ __ ] ugly, is it?
>> Yeah, she's a judge on X Factor.
>> She's ugly. Uh,
>> my my celebrity crush is a [ __ ]
>> Oh, you know who it is. I've already told you.
>> Yeah. K in it.
>> What's the second one? >> What?
>> No one. Oh. do this.
>> I'm on you. You did.
>> So, this is manipulation or manipulation someone.
>> Do you remember that Bobby Sher?
Everyone used to copy each other with that one.
>> That's how we manipulating someone.
>> That's how you know. That's how you know
Monty's a real one
>> cuz he he likes Katy Perry. No one else
really does. You see with that Beyonce
>> people used they used to copy each
other. Do you remember Bobby?
>> They used to say if you don't find
shovel co attractive you're gay. They
used to copy each other. Do you remember?
>> So what do you mean I'm normal?
>> Like you're not a copycat?
>> Cuz I Cuz
>> yeah because I like Katy Perry. Yeah. >> [ __ ] pyram.
>> It's just a figure. It's just a full
It's just how she is. >> Really?
>> I've had a te a jumper over with a naked
sat on the toilet. Knickers down to her ankles. M
Do you remember Big Bang Theory? >> Yeah.
>> You used like the blonde, didn't it?
>> I went to uh No, Kat Perry's got brown dark hair.
>> No, but you like the blonde and Big
Bangu in it.
>> I've never gone for blondes. Who you
about Penny? Is it Penny?
>> Yeah. How do you know? >> What?
>> How do you know? Oh yeah.
>> How do I know Penny? >> Yeah.
>> I do. Do you know that she's Do you know
that that she's the one who actually
makes Big Bang Theory? >> No.
>> Yeah. She's the one who created it.
Big Bang Theory. But she put the elder.
>> She's old now. Oh,
>> she's not that old. 40s.
>> Her 40s, probably late 30s.
>> She's not that good looking, is she?
>> She's not bad. Natalie's better.
>> You like Taylor Swift. You don't even
know who that is.
>> Taylor Swift. >> Yeah.
Do you know who it is?
I know there
>> Taylor Swift. >> Yeah.
He doesn't know who it is.
>> Not my cup of tea. Not my cup of tea.
>> You don't know her, is it?
>> Yeah. Is it a finger?
>> Yeah, but you just looked it up in it.
>> No, I looked nothing up. How can I lock
>> How do you know who it is then?
>> EG, I'm not stupid, man. >> Really?
>> It's his blonde, green eyes.
His blonde and green eyes. >> Yeah.
I don't like my blondies even though I'm blonde.
>> I like I like brunette me.
>> I like brunettes. I like my dark
>> I like brunette with big boobs.
>> I like darkhaired women. Brown women.
I've never really blonde women. I've
never really gone for a blond woman.
>> Yeah, I wouldn't say no to one though.
No way. I wouldn't I wouldn't say no to
one myself, but I wouldn't I wouldn't
date one. I wouldn't go out with one.
>> I'm blonde. I'm dopey as [ __ ] Do you
know what I mean? You seen how dopey I
am. I'm [ __ ] blonde myself. >> Yeah.
>> I mean,
>> well, dark blonde. Well, yeah.
Obviously, my girl, my daughters have
got more blonder than what I've got. >> Yeah.
But yeah, I'm blonde
blond and brown.
I'm looking getting I'm going to get um
a hair implant PJ.
>> It's going to cost me like five I think
it's 500 quid. >> Really?
>> Yeah. Do you know that we real her
one of them kind of things? That's what
I'm getting. I want to see what he
actually look like with her.
>> See if I look see if I look good with
her. You reckon a suit it with a head forever?
>> Yeah, I think you'd look a [ __ ] as well.
>> Think I look a [ __ ] as well. I got to go
and get a wig in it.
>> Get one of them twops on my head. >> Yeah,
you should do it.
>> I would. Yeah.
It's going to cost me 500 to 600 quid. No,
>> you have the money, don't you?
>> Yeah, I've got the money,
>> but that's kind of expensive just for a
[ __ ] air implant kind of thing.
>> You should gamble your money away.
>> I do it. I do it. I get it done. keen.
>> Yeah, but you've only got £60.
>> Yeah, you've already read that comment, Pete. Yeah.
>> No, but seriously. >> Yeah.
>> I don't mean this. Well, I get paid this month anyways.
Getting paid in like two to two weeks anyways.
>> Yeah, it's fine. Yeah.
Two weeks is nothing, is it?
>> Yo, PJ, get yourself some of this, man.
This is [ __ ] delicious, mate. In
fact, I'll let you l
>> It's more than £500 for a hair transplant.
>> Do you want some of this? Do you want
some of this on tomorrow, PJ?
>> No, I got my own one. I got Dior Sage. I
bought a new one.
>> [ __ ] banging this. This is lovely.
Lovely. That is It's a lovely
Mr. B, how how much money does Timmy have?
>> Timmy, he's on [ __ ] top rate. Aim for clapping.
He's on top rate for being a [ __ ] top
rate that kid is. He probably comes out
with the same out as me to be honest
with you. About 700 and odd to be honest. >> Yeah,
>> that was [ __ ] Timmy don't come out
of it nowhere near like it's always skin.
>> Yeah. Virgin boys skin as well.
>> So now you know peeps I'm not exactly
skin. I do come out with quite a bit of money.
>> Yeah. You just need to be more careful with it.
>> Yeah I do. I do.
I come out with like nearly two grand.
Just under two grand.
It's not just under.
>> What is it?
>> It's quite a bit under, but it's still good. Still good.
>> I'm happy with the amount of money I
come out with. I'm happy with it. I'm
not greedy with money.
>> I'm happy.
>> I'm greedy. I'm I'm greedy in it. Yeah.
>> Yeah. People I don't like money. I
really do not like money. Natalie will
even tell you, "Okay, I give anybody
anything. I'm kind. I'm a kind-hearted
man. Maybe I'm a prick by doing things."
Well, what I shouldn't be doing like
now. I'm a prick by being on YouTube
now. But I'm not being funny. I don't
have no one to talk to. What
>> did Listen, Monty, did uh Did Natalie
have a lot of money?
>> I'm not talking about Natalie's finances. Oh [ __ ]
whatsoever. I talk about mine. I'm not
asked about mine. But Natalie, no, I'm
not talking about Nances.
Am I [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> I never bring up Natalie yet again.
>> See, if we put mine and money, if we put
mine and your money together, it'd be a
lot in it. Yeah. Like say we live
together, not that we will, and we put
our money together, be quite a lot, would it?
>> That was a lot of money. If me and Natalie
>> me and Natalie was coming out with quite
a bit of money,
>> it's just that >> Yeah,
we had money. We get paid. The best
thing This is This was This was the best
thing with me and Nat. Yeah, me and Nat
gets paid so close to each other. Like
literally so close. So when I spent my
money, Natalie gets paid. >> Yeah.
Sorry. So, so we was never without, but
now we are.
>> I love that woman, man. [ __ ] love her.
>> I love you.
>> She loves me. She [ __ ] She won't do
this to me.
Do you know what I mean?
>> So, you don't think she loves you?
No, I don't think she did love me.
>> So why did she why do you think she got
with you then?
>> I don't know. I don't know. To be
honest, I just think about it. If a
woman loves you, Yeah.
they give you a chance to at least
explain yourself or they won't finish
you on the spot
>> for absolutely nothing. Do you know what I mean? >> Yeah.
or if it is over, at least give me a
chance to explain myself and you know,
but they don't. That's how that's why I
think Natalie doesn't love me or or
[ __ ] whatever. I'm not asked anyways
to be honest with you.
>> Yeah. So, why would you think she got
with you then if she didn't love you?
>> I don't know. I don't know. I don't know
if she did me or if she didn't love me.
But if I love somebody,
I wouldn't leave him. It doesn't matter
what they've done.
It don't matter. Like
even if she cheated on me, I still give
her a chance. I still give her a chance.
You know what I mean? That's the kind of
man I am.
>> Somebody was saying Yeah.
Somebody was saying that she got with
you to get back at Kaye.
What you got with me? Did you get back at Kelly? >> Yeah. >> What
>> do you think that's that's the Do you
reckon that's a possibility or
>> I don't know to be honest with you.
If that is the case then then that's
just spite from me
giving me false hopes giving me
but if it is I can just say at least I
[ __ ] give the one but it's not about that.
>> Yeah obviously it's not you know what I mean
>> cuz you obviously got hurt in the
process is it so
>> yeah yeah again of another woman again. Yeah.
>> My My mom likes Natalie. My mom likes
her. My mom knows it's my fault.
>> My mom's never ever ever ever
likes any of my girlfriends. None of
them. My mom hates Kay. She cannot stand
her. One love.
>> She cannot stand her. Natalie,
she she likes Natalie. She She don't
want me and Natalie breaking up. This is
hurting my mom more than it's a [ __ ]
me because only what my mom wants from
me is a good woman who understands my disabilities
and who understands me
and take me for who I am
>> not for what I do
>> or not for what I've not I make mistakes
like I said to Natalie I'm not perfect.
I am not perfect,
but I am still a good man. I will never
hurt her in any form of way. Maybe I get
her like coming on to YouTube, but
that's basically for all. I've never
smacked her. I've never hit her. I've
never really shouted at her. >> Yeah.
>> I've never done anything to her, to hurt her.
Only the way I have hurt her is by
coming on YouTube telling everybody that
I'm at the hotel and calling Nat that
that I'm sick of her and all that lot
kicking me out of hotels and that I
should have stayed up [ __ ] Mansfield
with my dog. I can't believe I got rid
of my dog. Only why I said that is
because I keep getting kicked out of
places. Understand? I was angry
and that's what women don't understand.
Men do get angry. Men Men said things not meaning.
And that's what I did. I didn't mean to
do it. It just happened.
>> God bless you.
>> Not bless me, PJ. Just put up on it.
At least you got some good sex, I guess.
good sex. It's not about the sex or PJ.
It's not about that. It's about [ __ ]
trust about love. Obviously, I put the
the trust up by going back onto YouTube
that day when I shouldn't have I
shouldn't have even done it. I weren't thinking.
I just was not thinking. But in at the
same time, Monty, right, like
she should um either take you have she
should if she if she can't have you at
your worst, you don't deserve you at
your best, you know.
>> No, no, she don't. She don't. You're
right on that one, P. Yeah, you are
right on that one.
If she can't handle what what I've done,
she can't handle me when I'm good.
I do need to be a man. I need to start [ __ ]
doing what I do on YouTube by giving you
people [ __ ] about me and Natalie,
talking about man and Natalie's business. >> Yeah,
>> that's why Natalie's done what she's
done is cuz I keep putting every her
business and my business up on YouTube.
That's why she's sick of me.
>> You know, I understand that.
You know what I mean? That's something I do understand.
I don't want to do what I want to do
because what I want to do, it [ __ ] up
the relationship. I just I want to get my head
back how I used to be before I come onto this community.
It's this community is what's done all
this and put my head up. >> Yeah,
>> it is. It [ __ ] is. And I've let
YouTube [ __ ] my relationship up with Natalie.
>> And I don't know and I don't know why
I've done that.
Not like Natalie,
I've got her a new TV. I've got a new
set coming. That set is expensive. That
cost more than a [ __ ] TV.
>> Like a girl in Victorian old seties like
on Titanic or something.
>> She's got like that set in there, but
she only needs one more and it's like a
single chair. I've got one. I found it. uh
>> about 400 something like that. 4 500
like that. Anyways,
I'm trying to show Natalie
that I [ __ ] I love her and appreciate
her and get
>> Didn't you fall out with her like a few
weeks ago? Is it?
>> Yeah. No, this week.
>> Yeah, there was a time before though,
I'm sure, wasn't there?
>> Yeah, that was Yeah, that was in Blackpool.
>> But this is the thing.
>> When when she when we've had a drink, we
argue. And when we haven't No, in fact,
when we've had a drink, we find we're
good. It's when we come on to YouTube.
Me and Nie, we are a good couple. We
don't fight. We don't argue. It's when
we go on to YouTube and [ __ ] starts
whacking the fan. That's when me and
Natalie starts arguing. It's because YouTube
>> makes sense.
>> You know what I mean? Is YouTube what's done it?
>> So I do understand where Nat is coming from. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? Pissing her off,
coming online, doing what? What? So, I
understand why she's done cuz she don't
want this and I understand that now. >> Yeah.
>> It's my it's my disability. Like, I
don't understand. Well, I do understand,
but I do the opposite
>> what I say. And I need to stop doing
that. I need to do what I say and stick to it.
>> That's what I need to do. And I need to
be a man. I need to stand up and be a
man. I've got two daughters who [ __ ]
need me. I need to stop
putting women first now. >> Yeah,
>> that's what I've been doing. Obviously,
my kids live with my mom anyway. So,
it's not like I've disowned my kids or
anything like that because they haven't.
It's just that I keep putting women when
I was I was back at Warsaw Mansfield. I was like
seeing my kids and that
to sort kind of sort me out and that and
then I end up getting with Natal and
they end up moving to Birmingham. Lola
ended up getting Lola would go that I
moved to Birmingham
because Lola Ollie talks about me. She
brings me up all the time. She she talks
about daddy all the time. Lola does my
daddy this. Daddy that. Daddy le oh lord
[ __ ] adors me never talks about kaya
never it's always my daddy le my daddy
that le that my daddy took me to the tunnels and yeah
you know and I've I need to find who I am
I don't know who I am anymore Wow.
You're listen. I took my daughter to all
places. metal protecting
underground tunnels like army tunnels,
second world war bunkers
took her to all them. She loved it.
Are you PJ?
Yeah, you are nons in this community.
[ __ ] idiots. Shoot. Why do these
people talk about nonsis? You people fancy pedophile
then calling people mongos. A lot of the
[ __ ] in this community is Timmy [ __ ] Eldrid.
Natalie, you saw him. She's in a bedroom.
I'm just leaving her alone. That's what
I'm doing. I'm not going in there.
This is not my room. I'm just leaving her alone.
She's in a room. She's in the room. I
don't know. She's gone bed and sleep or
what? What? I don't know.
Go tell her.
Oh, I've already told her. I'm not
telling Natalie no more. Oh, I'm just
leaving her alone. I'm leaving her
Natalie knows my feelings. She knows how
I feel for her.
I've told her I've told her times
times I've told her
I'm not bothered anymore to be honest.
Be a man. I am a man.
But a woman's not a woman, is it? When
they ignore you and they [ __ ] don't
want to speak to you or
I'm just going to wait for her to ring
me. I hope she does ring me because soon
as I get paid my disability, I'm going
well my normal money, I'm going back up
north. I'm going back to Manny.
I've had enough.
Go back to the tent, [ __ ] I'm all
right. My tent's here. My tent's here.
Go back to my tent. My tent. My tent is right here.
Show you my tent.
There's my 10. Nicker.
My tent's here. There's my tent. Look,
there's there's my 10 port. It will go
into my tank. There's
my 10 pegs.
I've got everything here, man. Look,
I've got all my [ __ ] here.
This room's a [ __ ] all. I need to clean this room.
Look at this. My green sheep. I've got everything here.
Where the [ __ ] my cooker?
That cubbage stinks are sweaty deep.
I've got a cooker in me. Where the [ __ ]
my cooker at? Oh, it's Here's my cooker.
Where's my cooker?
There's my cooker, peeps.
You think it doesn't work and you think
it's not a cooker? Sure. It's a cooker.
We've got a couple in the room, please.
I told you I'm a survivor. I am a
survivor. Listen, you won't last 5
minutes in a 10 in a one. Literally Natalie,
she can she can last [ __ ] weeks in a wood.
Here we go. Gas bottle.
What we do that for
this is leave it down again.
Oh, that's why my cooker switch.
There's going to be gas running through
this now. Let's find out. Maybe not.
Oh, that's right.
There you go. It's done.
There you go, peeps.
Turn that off.
Take my gas bottle out obviously because
take that out. So that's safety comes
first peep. Safety comes first. So now
it won't come on.
This gas won't come out come out of it either.
Where's PJ got off Do
let us go fire. There's no fire.
It's no player.
These are This is just all my survival
[ __ ] I'm all about survival, mate.
If you not If you don't know anything about survival,
there is no point. Natalie knows a lot
about survival to tell you the truth.
She knows how to live wild. that woman
does. I tell you now, he's done it with
me in um Mansfield when I was homeless.
That's when I was homeless. She So,
she's already done it once with me when
I was in Nottingham.
So, I know Natalie can [ __ ] do it cuz
she's done it once already
with me in Mansfield.
Natalie's just come out of her bedroom.
She's going toilet.
I'm not talking to her. I let her come
to me and talk to me when she's ready.
I want Kayie back. That's not me, by the
way, on that account. I do not want Kayie back.
I want Natalie back. Not Kayie. Natalie.
Okay. Now that
you This is all what you thought. You
thought I was going to go back out with
Kaye, didn't you? [ __ ] off. I'm not
being funny. I'm not getting abused.
I need a woman who loves me.
Wow. That pretty hard.
Hello. How the [ __ ] did that move when
it's all going to come down?
Can't even touch that.
I just need Natalie to ring me for five
minutes so I can talk to her for five [ __ ] minutes. I said,
>> I will never go back out with Kaye.
Never ever ever
go back out with Kayie. I'm single now.
I can go back out with Kayie now, but I
don't want to go back out with Kayie.
Close. I got I don't have no chance cuz
I don't want her back anyways.
And she don't have a chance either.
I just need to keep off YouTube to be
honest with you people and stop bringing her up.
But I'm only back on YouTube is because
I want Natalie's attention. I want to
get her attention.
That's what I want to do. I want to get
her attention. So, but this is probably
[ __ ] it up even more for me to be
honest with you
with being back on YouTube. But people,
I'm not asked anymore. A woman can take
me who I am or they can just [ __ ] off.
Yeah, that's what what what what my
saying is now. Yeah. If a woman can't
take me for who I am, they can [ __ ] off.
And that includes Natalie as well. She
cannot take me for who I am and I can
take her for who she is. I can take any
mistake what she does. I will never
never ever ever finish a woman for
making a mistake. Never. Because I know
it's a mistake like I make a mistake
going on YouTube,
you know. Never finish a woman for a
mistake called talking starting it out
and move on and that's it, you know.
If you love someone, you you take as
much as you can off them.
Not just chuckling [ __ ] under the bus
every time it gets hard. Cuz that's
relationships for you. They get hard,
they get easy. They get hard, they get
But when a woman
just breaks up with you just for [ __ ]
for nothing, it's it's hard. It's like I
can't I can't do it to be honest with you.
Where's PJ? PJ, come back, man. I'm
going to go and kick that [ __ ] account.
I'm leaving a woman alone anyways.
Natalie's not pregnant.
I can get her pregnant,
but obviously we I can't now. Obviously
not cuz she she won't she's not talking to me.
I better I [ __ ] hurt her by going on
YouTube. I'm hurting her by staying on
YouTube. I need to stop coming on
I need to be a man. I need to sort myself out. Like literally,
I don't know what I want anymore.
I really do not know what I want anymore.
What you want about Tik Tok?
I can go live on Tik Tok.
Is that what you want me to do? Go live
on Tik Tok? Get rid.
What you want about get red?
No, I won't put you in my pocket. If I
was going to talk to Natalie, it'd be
just me and Natalie, not on YouTube. And
if Natalie does ring me and me and
Natalie sort [ __ ] out, I will never be
coming back on YouTube again. I will
never come back on YouTube again. I'm
only on YouTube now. noise cuz I don't
have no [ __ ] to talk to.
You know, if Natalie rings me or [ __ ]
comes into the bedroom or textes me to
come in, I go in or she me to go into
the bedroom, I go in to her, but I'm not
doing I'm not I'm not a stalker and I'm
not a rasser. I'm not doing that.
And I'm not putting you in my pocket to
listen to my conversation on my business anymore.
I'm only telling you what you want to
hear now. Well, I'm only telling you
what I'm giving you. That's it. I'm not
giving you nothing, absolutely nothing
about Natalie or myself anymore.
Only what you people know is that I was
homeless in a tent in Mansfield. Natalie
come and met me in Mansfield. See me.
Natalie got me into his place,
into his house. I [ __ ] appreciate her for that.
But if I if I haven't got Natalie, I'm
going. I ain't got no one.
EJ, where is PJ?
My mom loves Natalie. My mom likes her. She [ __ ]
She likes Natalie.
Natalie is [ __ ] part of the [ __ ] family.
This is part of my family, man. My mom's
gotted. My mom is literally gutted that
this has happened
between me and Natalie. My mom's Natalie
is only the per but my mom knew it. To
be honest with you, my mom likes her,
but my mom did have an inkling that this
was going to happen. This is why my mom
told me, "Do not move to Birmingham
because if it if it ever ends, you you
are going to come back. You're going to
come back." And now it's ended. My mom
knew that this was going to happen.
My mom even said this the your
relationship's not going to last.
She said it with all my misses, all of
them. But she said that Natalie is the
best one out of every one of them.
She is the best one out of every single
woman I've been out with. The best one.
And I'm a [ __ ] up. I'm the [ __ ] up to be honest.
My mom loves her. She likes her. My mom
wants Natalie to talk to me to sort [ __ ]
out with me and that. My mom wants her
to cuz my mom wants
I can't talk much. I need to talk to
Natalie about this anyways cuz it's not all YouTube.
What my mom was saying that's got
nothing to do with me. It's what my mom
was saying about that and it Natalie
needs to hear it. But it's not for your
hearers people. So I'm not saying [ __ ]
only. What I'm saying is that my mom wants Natalie
my life, my mom's life, and my
children's life and [ __ ] like just put
that out there. Just say it like that.
He wants Natalie
in my children's life.
Not step more, anything like that. just
just there basically cuz
I'm not even [ __ ] lying. Natalie's
met my kids. Natalie has met my kids. She She's
met my children.
My daughters adore Natalie. My
daughters, especially Lola. Lola likes Natalie.
Prim a little bit shy with Natalie, but
she likes her. Natalie adors Prim.
Literally, Natalie does adore Prim.
And that's what I mean, man. He adors my daughters. Your mom.
My mom loves Natalie.
My mom's even been trying to text her to
to talk to her and that literally my
mom's tried to text her to talk to her.
My mom told me she text her saying that
my phone's coming but she got in contact
with me after that. So
my mom couldn't get hold of me. talking.
I give Natal my mom Natalie's number
and then my mom contacted Natalie a
couple of days ago trying to talk to Natalie.
Your mom was
I didn't get Natalie into cocaine at all.
I didn't even put Natalie on a coke.
And me and Natalie don't take coke anymore.
We don't do that [ __ ]
We don't even drink anymore.
We don't drink and we don't [ __ ] take
that [ __ ] anymore.
Cuz when we've had a drink, we we always
end up on YouTube or we always argue or
[ __ ] up and that.
And I don't want to do that anymore. I
don't want to [ __ ] up anymore. I am a
[ __ ] up. I'm a big [ __ ] up
and I can't wait to meet PJ today. Uh,
clear my head a little bit. You know
what? If I pull a woman, I pull a woman.
I'm not [ __ ] around.
If I pull a pull,
I'm not going to bring I'm not going to
[ __ ] I'm not going to do anything.
I'm not [ __ ]
yagging any woman. I'm not even going to
be going nowhere near any woman
tomorrow with PVA. PJ can, he can if he
want to bring a woman back or whatever,
but I'm not as
I'm happy with N me. I want to stick with N.
Maybe Natalie's done with me, but I'm
not done with Natalie. This ain't over.
It's more than me and Natalie.
It can't be over.
Well, it can be over, but I don't want
it to be. Not yet. Cuz there's more to
it. There's more to this relationship.
I'm just going to say this. If she loves
me, she contact me. Yeah, that's all
what I'm going to say. If she does love
me, she will go contact me. Not was
you and not was about drugs and alcohol.
No, every time we had drugs and alcohol,
we just argued argued and fight or and
it's YouTube as well. It's YouTube. I'm
not being funny, but I don't know why
Natalie can't forgive me. Because it's
funny when she went live in this house
and she did what she did on YouTube and
I went [ __ ] mad at her for it. Then I
forgive her for it. And I go live just
tell her tell us a little bit of [ __ ]
and it's like, "Yeah, I'm over." This is
what what I mean about women. Men
forgive women, but women never forgive
men. I don't get that.
I really don't get that with women.
It's not that
I need her. I do need her.
I need Natalie. Bongo has
drugs. N is
I don't say drugs anymore. I've quit.
I've quit. I can't be asked with the
weed. I can't be asked with the coke.
Literally, I ain't had no weed at all
today. At all. I'm not going to either.
I can't be asked with it either to be
honest with you. He said
he said what? Wait for him. Take your bags.
Your bags. She doesn't want to. Don't
need to pack my bags. My name's on his house. you are.
I can afford I got I got 60 quid. I can
go get myself 30 bag. I go get myself a queue
was but I'm not doing I am not doing
I chopped all my I had weed people. I had weed.
Natalie will even tell you I tipped all
my weed down the toilet.
Uh, at least a [ __ ] ounce of weed at
least. But it was all bits. Got it all
down the toilet. All of it went down and
I lost the chain.
No. Well, Natalie can try me. Literally,
I will get Natalie anything she wants.
If Natalie wants a [ __ ] 100 bag, she
got to get her [ __ ] 100 quid of weed.
Not It's not the money with me. I'm not
asked about the money with Nat.
Natalie's not a money grabber.
So, I don't know why you go out there
and call Natalie a money grabber when
Natalie's nowhere near a [ __ ] money grabber.
He's never ever ever asked me for a penny.
She has never asked me for nothing.
Nothing. I've gave her and she's given
me, but she's never asked me for anything.
Why did you
Oh, you're weird. Don't
cuz I can't be with it anymore.
And if you think I'm smoking a joint
now, people, I'm smoking a [ __ ] roll up.
There's my back in there right next to
me. Look, where's the joint doctor in
these assays? It's just like basically
more [ __ ] rollups. I've quit. I've
quit. There's a couple of joint dockers
there from the other week. But baring
from that, it's just mostly dockers now.
I've quit the weed peeps. I don't smoke it anymore.
I've quit. And that's how easy it is for
me to quit weed.
That is how easy it is for me to say
bye-bye to the bastard.
But I can't say bye to that. bet you on
weed zoom. No, actually actually I'm not
I'm I'm I need to work out more. Put
weight on. But I'm not putting weight on
because I'm not eating.
But crying. Yeah, I've been crying. I'll
show you a [ __ ] sexy picture of me
crying. You can get it if you want. If
you want it, take it. I'm not asked.
Here you want to see me crying. Yeah. Oh, sorry.
Is it this one? One sec.
I will be lit by the eyes and lows.
Here we go, peeps. See, I've been crying
over. You don't believe I'll put the
picture up now so you can see the tear
on the corner of my eye there.
A little tear. Take that off now.
That Let's find a better picture.
See what I mean? You laugh. He's
laughing. He's not even funny.
At least I've got feelings.
Here, peeps. Book it. Look here. Here.
Look. I'll show you. You want to see me
crying? Yeah. Proper proper crying.
Yeah, peeps. I'm not here. [ __ ] it.
>> here. Let me turn it down so you can't hear. Yeah. Look.
There you go, peeps. I'm [ __ ] crying.
There you go. I'm crying here.
I want to see the tears. Actual tears.
There we go. There we go.
Get a screenshot of that face quick time.
There you go.
Get the p of the [ __ ] face.
I'm not asked. I'm not asked.
At least I've got feelings.
didn't cry for my kids. No, I didn't cry
for my kids cuz my kids went to my mom.
I lost my kids.
I've lost that. That's the difference.
So all you Moon is cry a uh by uh a television.
Yeah, that's only what I've done is
cried and got her a TV.
Not good for the not even funny peeps.
I'm not asked anyways.
I'm not asked.
I'm going to go live on Tik Tok now
anyway. So I see all those. I'm going to
go live on Tik Tok.
So I see all those