We're going to Birmingham today.
See, Monty, man. Oh, Franklin. I'm surprising.
That's very interesting.
Yeah, I got the football today as well.
kind of nervous about it to be honest. I
don't think it's going to win. I think
it's going to lose.
Hopefully it wins.
But then it might lose. Yeah. I Hey, do
you know what? Yeah. Before um
LJ was um before Monty Man was talking
over me. Yeah. So this LJ says that he
gets three and a half grand a month. But
last week it was two and a half grand a
month after expenses. What the [ __ ] Job
in Belfast pays over £4,000 a month
sitting on your ass. Doesn't m You know
what you know the hardest thing with
with being a liar is is keeping up with
your own lies. It's easy to lie, but you
know to keep up with your own lies,
right? That's the hardest thing. Nothing
he says makes any sense.
It it literally does not make no sense.
You know, even in London, you wouldn't
get four grand a month unless you've got
some sort of trade or you're working
crazy hours. Like, he doesn't get no
four grand a month. Why does he lie? Why
does he lie, bro? And I don't care if
someone did get four grand a month. I'm
not jealous of no one. I have my own
[ __ ] money. But why does he have to
lie? This is what I don't understand.
I don't understand the lies. You know
what I'm saying? You do not get no four
grand a [ __ ] month in Belfast sitting
on your ass. What is your profession?
It's not uh property because even
property in London would not pay that.
And London's the [ __ ] capital.
Why does he lie so much? You see me,
Rocky, even Virgin Legs, you know, we
all tell the truth about what what we
get and he has to lie. When
bro, if you was if you was getting four
grand a month in Belffor, you you should
be living the life like I was living. I
was living the life for [ __ ] 4 years.
New city every week. Do you remember I
used to go to a new city every week,
piss it up, be out 4 days at a trot. You
should be living a life, man.
But you're sat on YouTube every day
begging. That's when your lies come to
an end. Why does he lie so much? Jeez.
Like I said, he's on that £400 universal
credit. No more, bro. Trust me. You know,
yeah, he's an idiot, man.
I have the better wins, man.
I'm going to Birmingham today to go and
see Monty. Man,
the things I do for these [ __ ] kids,
eh? [ __ ] hell.
And a woman would never [ __ ] make me
like that, bro. You [ __ ] bad. I
wouldn't be going out today if it wasn't
for going to Birmingham to see Monty. I
don't give a [ __ ] about it anymore, bro.
I know where I'm going. Oh bless.
Oh bless Monty then.
But what I told him was right. Like go
out meet other people and forget and
they always come running back. And if
they don't, bro, you would already found
someone by then. I know all of these
things, bro. I've done I know all of these things.
And then you're talking about a grand a
month, £1,100 a month. Bro, it's not as
it's nowhere near as bad as you [ __ ]
make out. It's nowhere near as bad as
you make out. Jesus Christ.
You could still go out drinking. You
think I'm I'm not going out drinking
because I'm skinn. I just can't be
bothered with it. I can't be bothered
with it, man.
You know, even when I was getting that
money, there was that there was times I
didn't go out for like four six
four to six weeks. Yep.
But hopefully this bet wins. But this
tram is worrying me a little bit.
It's not because I'm scared. I just
don't want to go out drinking anymore.
I'm I'm I've booked a holiday. I'm
leaving. I'm at the age now. I'm ready
to go. You know, that's sensible. You
I don't want to try here again, bro. The [ __ ]
I'm happy just playing GTA. I need to
get into some hobby, though. For real.
For real. I need to go back to the gym. But yeah,
that's what I'm saying. I was living the
life for 3 years. Why are you not living the life?
Four grand a month in Belfast. Jesus
Christ. And you're sat on YouTube every day.
You saw the [ __ ] that I used to do when
I when I used to I used to go to
different cities. I used to go casino. I
used to go on dates.
Just be honest with what you get.
Why the [ __ ] wouldn't I have £500? I
remember he was like, "Oh, I don't even
have Why would I be skin?
Even if I got £700 a month, I still
would never be skinn. I will never be skinned.
You don't need to worry about that. I
will never ever be skinned. Don't you
worry about that, kid." Yeah. So,
I'm going to go about 5:00 p.m.
going to watch the football and yeah,
I will never be skid matey.
I [ __ ] hope this football bet wins though.
It's not even like a high chance.
There's [ __ ] £80 on the [ __ ]
thing, bro. The [ __ ]
Then I'll go and meet him.
Stay over. I'll probably stay out
Saturday and Sunday, to be honest.
Yeah, of course I'm still going. I don't
need a bet to come in. I just want it to
come in cuz I want the extra money. I
still have my own money.
I just wanted to win in it. [ __ ] man.
Just be nice to win a football bet.
You You understand? A little bit extra
is nice when you realize how hard it is
to actually get money now.
It's actually so hard to get money nowadays. So,
that's why I didn't Yeah.
Now, Colchester will score. They will
I think it's Tra that won't score.
No, I'm not panicking. I've got money.
I'm not panicking. Why would I be
panicking? I've got money.
I've got money, matey. I just wanted to
win cuz it would be fun, isn't it?
I don't. They will score. They always
Hopefully it ain't one n mate cuz I need the money.
So, well, I need it cuz I Who doesn't
need an extra [ __ ] almost £300, bro?
It's extra money for the month in it. Yeah,
I haven't in Birmingham in years, man.
And it'll be do it will do me good to go
to Birmingham. I haven't been in [ __ ] years.
[ __ ] years, bro. I think it was when
I was on that date. That was like
[ __ ] I swear like 2 3 years ago. No,
that must it must be 3 years I've not been.
No, it is 3 years cuz when them attendants left
3 years. I haven't been to Birmingham
for 3 years. It's been about 3 years.
Maybe slightly longer actually. [ __ ]
ages. I ain't been there for ages, bro.
They always cry to Peter Belly to pick
up the pieces, don't they?
It was just It was just USA Izzy all
over again, isn't it?
It was USA all over again.
And you should know at his age what
they're like, man. [ __ ] Cuz
that's what happens. You know, you're
like that when you're younger and then
you realize that they're evil and they
don't care and then like
then you know then you should know, you
know, you can't trust them
cuz I never knew they were all the same
until I started meeting them. So now I don't care. Nope.
No, I don't play online.
I don't even gamble really. Just got
done this football bet.
Yeah, I was going to do Aquin and
chilling um chilling, but
I never saw
It's hard to get money now that is ming it.
I think the bet should win.
What do you think? Do you think the bet will win?
Can't even play roulette anymore cuz
that's rigged. So
yeah, it's [ __ ] it, man.
Well, at least I lived the life for
three years. Eh,
it's not the worst thing being back to reality.
It's not the worst thing being back
being being back to reality. So, I mean, yeah,
I'm almost 28 as well, bro. [ __ ]
hell. Probably do this drinking [ __ ] be
And the thing is, you can't win big
online as well. That's the thing.
I remember all and I used to gamble all
the time. Like I said,
I probably gambled more times than that
rock and roller. You know, you know how
many times I've gambled in my life. It's
why I'm bored of it. [ __ ] it bores me, bro.
[ __ ] bored me, bro. So, I don't
really care about it.
I guess the I guess it doesn't need
batteries than this controller cuz Yeah.
was sat I'm just happy he's sat at home
playing Franklin to be honest. Oh, Franklin.
better not finish [ __ ] one N, bro.
Then we'll be [ __ ] up in it.
Then we will be [ __ ] up.
I said to Antman, "Do you know what what
your funniest saying is? The only the
only place you're not going to get I
haven't got a boyfriend is Asia." I
said, "Was you joking?" He said, "No,
why would I be joking? You knew you know
it's true as well." That sounds funny as
[ __ ] He said that's the only place
you're not going to get it. Whoa. Bless you. Oh, Franklin.
Let me check my emails. I haven't check
my emails today.
doesn't make any sense. How can I have
too many drivers everywhere when I've
already changed the [ __ ] address,
bro? What the [ __ ] man? That's impossible.
How do they have too many [ __ ] drivers?
You could have made money on that,
matey. £150 a [ __ ] day. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah. So, like I said, if you want to go
down the security route, you can get the
badge, which costs about £540,
but then you're not guaranteed um
you're not guaranteed um shifts without
references. So you can go and get that
badge, pay all that money, which is a
lot of money now, and you might not even
be guaranteed work. So yeah.
So yeah, you're [ __ ] be [ __ ] basically.
It's hard nowadays, matey.
[ __ ] hell, matey.
The only thing you could probably do is
like [ __ ] construction and [ __ ] but
the thing with that is it [ __ ] your
whole body up. I'll never do that. that
you have to be guaranteed work with that. But
and there's no money in gambling
anymore. There's no money anywhere
It's really bad, isn't it?
That changed after like December, I think.
This is what I don't understand, bro.
This guy was like, I bet you're going to
do some sober approaches today. I was
like, no. What part of I'm done? Do you not understand?
Oh, do I play online slotes? No, I don't.
Sorry, I didn't even clock you like that. So, yeah. Yeah, man.
Why would I do some sober approaches?
Why would I, bro? What the [ __ ] I don't
give a [ __ ] about that [ __ ] anymore.
If it wasn't for Monty, even if I win
this bet, I wouldn't go out. Oh, bro. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, it wouldn't for body if I even if
I win this bet, I wouldn't have went out
anyways. Even if I win the bet,
you get to a point, Bombay, where you
just realize what you're going to get
when you go out
and then it's just like just pointless
even going out.
You know what I'm saying?
for like six weeks
cuz it's just the same old thing, bro.
I've done I've done it more than anyone.
So, it gets boring, you know?
I have boyfriend. It's boring. It's
annoying. So, nothing to do with money
at all, bro. What the [ __ ]
I got it's probably because I got them
30 numbers it and them two weeks ago 30 numbers. >> So,
but the good thing with having all of
them numbers is you can message them
again one day and see if they want to meet you.
Sometimes it has worked. So,
that's the only good thing is they're
not done forever. But yeah,
I just can't be asked of it anymore, bro.
What do you think about making money
nowadays? It's [ __ ] hard, isn't it?
It's really hard, matey. It's depressing.
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro.
I'm used to being active. I'm not active
no more cuz there's nothing to be doing. Save. Yeah.
No, not really, bro.
I miss you. Say Izzy's kisses.
They were nice. They were nice kisses. Oh [ __ ]
I fell over. Yeah, that's it.
Yeah, they were lovely little kisses.
They were love kisses.
They were love lovely kisses.
They were lovely kisses.
They're lovely kisses.
What do you think of Bonnie and Natalie
G? It's funny, isn't it? Bless him.
Bless him then if he's in love.
What do you Thank bless.
I think I only won a couple of bets last season.
Yeah, I only won a couple last season. up.
They were nice kisses.
Oh, who the [ __ ] is that little guy with car?
This one looks good in the SW.
[ __ ] What's wrong with my back, man?
I might go to Norwich. Yeah. purch.
I love it when they change their picture.
Bit later, mate. Just waiting for the football. Yeah, man.
I want to go on YouTube when I go there,
but the problem is is [ __ ]
I don't want this [ __ ] Timmy, man,
cuz people going to start calling up
pubs and [ __ ]
So, that's I'm not We're going to do
videos, but we're not going to go live.
I don't think we're going to go live.
We'll just do some videos and upload
some videos. I just don't want this
[ __ ] [ __ ] coming in the pub being a
[ __ ] and that, bro.
You know what I'm saying?
So, I'm not sure. Oh, we'll go live. We
will go live actually
when we're in the house cuz I want this
plastic and these people call up pubs and [ __ ]
which I don't even know why they do
that. Call up pubs. It's so silly.
Well, I don't know why they do that. Why
they stay in? Why they call up pubs?
It's so [ __ ] I don't know why they do that.
Oh, yeah. Joe, that large apparently gets £3,500
a month after expenses.
Yeah, he's he's um I think he's he's
lying to himself.
There's no way someone in Belfast gets
over four grand a month sitting on their
ass. You don't even get that. Most
people don't even get that in London.
And you know the wage in London is is is
is higher than most places.
It goes by where you live. He's an
absolute [ __ ] liar, bro. I've never
known such a liar in my life.
It's crazy, bro. He is a [ __ ] proper
liar. He's on benefits. He's on £300 a month.
£300 a month universal credentials. I
call universal credit universal
credentials. I'm not sure why, but
he's [ __ ] skinned.
He doesn't have properties though.
He doesn't have properties because even
if you've got properties in London, it
doesn't pay like that. He doesn't have
properties, bro. He's the liar.
Everything points to him being on that
£300 a month.
Begging on YouTube. It's [ __ ] Cuz
even if you've got even when I was doing
it in London,
I was getting like three grand. And that was London.
Belfast, you can probably buy a house with£1.
He doesn't, bro. Everything points
to him being skimp. They literally everything,
you know, he doesn't have money. I don't
know why he goes on like he has money
because, bro, listen, listen, listen. If
you was getting four grand a month, you
would not be on YouTube
begging. It's it's that simple. You
would not be on YouTube begging. There's
no way. You'd be out living a life like
I was living for 3 4 years. I was living
the life. Everyone saw me living the
life. You're getting over you're get So
you were getting more than me. Okay.
Okay. So you're you was getting more
than me in Belfforce, but you're sat on
YouTube begging. Something does not look
right there, bro. The evidence suggests
it. Like this is why I go by the
evidence. You would not be on YouTube
every day begging if you was on that
kind of money.
It all points to him being skinned.
That that that literally that that's
what I'm I'm actually trying to get at.
It took you about [ __ ] 10 years to
save up to go to Vegas. Why would it
take you that long if you're getting
that kind of money a month?
It doesn't add up. Even with children,
it it doesn't it doesn't add up. It
doesn't add up. Cuz don't forget, it's a
lot cheaper than London as well.
You don't have no properties. You're
[ __ ] skint. Stop lying. I don't like
people that lie, bro. I hate liars.
Rocky Roy tells the truth. I tell the
truth. Monty tells the Monty even showed
you how much he got.
Monty even showed you how much he got.
Why does he need to lie? I don't
understand the lies. What's the lies for?
Jesus Christ. It's madness.
It's actually a madness.
You don't get no [ __ ] You don't have no properties.
Yeah. He went to Vegas. It took him
about Bro, he buys stuff. Okay, bro. I
can go out and buy stuff. I can go out
and buy stuff right now. I can go out
and buy some trainers. I can go out and
buy stuff. That doesn't mean anything,
bro. People on benefits can do that.
Look at Monty man. He was always buying
[ __ ] Hugo boss. You went to Vegas
after about 10 years of saving. My point
precisely. Yeah. What? You buy a new
pair of trainers, bro? Anybody can do that.
So, he's on benefits.
He's on £300 a month. Do not let him
tell you that he gets any more. He does
not get any more. Trust me, bro.
It all points to you being skinned.
Someone that owns properties and gets
all this money would not be on YouTube
begging for an extra £200 a month. The
evidence is there, you know.
So, you don't own properties. Do you
think somebody could just go?
Well, they can. I Bro, bro, listen,
listen. You can go to Vegas on benefits.
You can go anywhere. You can do anything
on benefits. You just need to stay for a
very long time, which is what he done.
Okay. Okay. If he gets all of this
money, why is he on YouTube every day
begging, not out living a life, not out
Well, it doesn't need to even be out
drinking. Why is he not out living a
life? Why is he barely traveled for
somebody that's 42?
It doesn't make sense.
It doesn't make sense. I mean, 42 is not
even old compared to a [ __ ]
65year-old, to be honest. But it doesn't
It all points to benefits.
All All the puzzles point to benefits.
What? Just because somebody buys a new
pair of trainers, that means they're on
four grand a month. Bro, hear yourself
for a second. Hear yourself, please.
Bro, it's clear he's on benefits.
You know, if he was if he was on that
kind of like you I could save up to go I
can go to Vegas in about 5 months if I
really like well I can go before that
but say I was starting for benefits now.
I can go to Vegas in about 5 months, you know.
I could go to B. Yeah, probably about 5
months, maybe. Maybe 6 months. You can
do it even on benefits. It would just
take a very long time.
And I have nothing to be jealous of cuz
I've got more money than him and I have
my own money. But he People don't just
own property. people. So what? Someone
this one day decides to own property.
Bro, the story does not make any sense.
Story does not make any sense.
Yeah, no one cares. You little s. Go
somewhere else and simp.
Yeah, you can't even spell [ __ ]
Yeah, go s somewhere else, you little s. [ __ ] s.
[ __ ] off, s. But yeah,
why am I wasting so much money? What do
you mean why am I wasting so much money?
Cuz I don't want to go to Vegas. I was
using it as an example, but he ain't on
no four grand a month, bro. Trust me,
four grand a month is a lot of money
even in London. Trust me, he ain't on no
four grand a month.
He's a billy [ __ ] bullshitter.
Like he he is not on. And also he
changed his story because he said three
and a half grand yesterday and then last
the week before that he said 2 and a
half grand. He is not on none of them
payments. Trust me if somebody was on
them payments they would be living that
life bro. Like I was living the life in 3 years.
So it's all [ __ ] Anyways, you go by
people's YouTube activity
and he is on YouTube every day begging.
That's all I need to know. On YouTube
every day, can't get off of YouTube
begging. That tells me everything I need
to know. Like there there's no point
going back and forth, back and forth,
back and forth.
He he can't get off of YouTube. He's sat
on YouTube begging every day. He has got
to be on benefits. There's there's
there's nothing else.
But he can keep lying to you and fooling
you. I don't It's what you choose to believe, bro.
It just none of it makes any any sense whatsoever.
And then he's taking a piss at £1,000 a
month and he doesn't even have £1,000 to his name.
They don't even have £1,000 to their name.
Yeah. And I can prove Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And I can prove that these people are
skin cuz they can't get off of YouTube.
That's the proof. I've already got
proof. When they come on YouTube doing
what they do every day, it says that
everything that they try to call other
people is themsel. That's the evidence.
Because if they got all of this money,
it wouldn't be on YouTube. And I stick
by my guns. I'm only on YouTube cuz I'm
[ __ ] I ain't going out for a little
bit. I'm [ __ ] I Monty Man got me on YouTube.
They wouldn't be on YouTube. If they had
all this money, they wouldn't be on
YouTube. Trust me, they wouldn't be on
YouTube. Yes, it does mean your skin. Of
course it means your [ __ ] skin. Of
course it does. You can't take one day
off of YouTube. That must mean your
skin. Huh? Does that apply to me? Um,
well, I mean, you've seen my YouTube videos, right?
going out, winning money. So, no, but
no, no, let me rephrase. You people
literally cannot get off YouTube. Not
even for one day. You're on YouTube all
day, every day hating. Someone with
money would do that. That's why I'm
saying people that have money wouldn't do that.
It's must be themselves they're talking
about because if you're on YouTube every
single day hating, you've got all this
money and everyone else's skin. You
wouldn't waste your life away on the
internet. You know, it doesn't work both
ways. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. It
doesn't work both ways because I don't
sit on YouTube all day every day hating.
It doesn't work both ways. No, it
doesn't work both ways because these
people Okay. Okay. Right. I can say to you,
I will not be on YouTube for a week. Can
you come off of YouTube for a week? It
doesn't work both ways at all.
Because these people have been on here
for years and they can't get off YouTube
for whatever reason. So, it must mean
their skin. Being sat on YouTube every
day must mean your skin.
It must mean your skin.
Well, it doesn't work both ways at all.
How does it work both ways?
You could they can't take one day off of [ __ ] YouTube.
[ __ ] hell. Not even one day sat on
YouTube every day. They have to be skin. So yeah.
Okay. They aren't skin. Well, if you had
all this money, you would be on YouTube.
That's what I say.
Oh, that ind that Indonesian guy was
best to me. But LJ is skinn. Yeah, there
is shop. There might be people that
aren't skin, but he is most definitely
definitely definitely definitely skinn.
And here's another thing, right? Let's
let's just go by this, right? Let's just
say that he gets more money than me,
which he doesn't. I have a better life
than him. Even if I was on £800 a month,
I'd still have a better life than him.
He's sat on YouTube talking to losers,
doesn't leave the house. So, bro, even
if I got £800 a month, I'd still have a
better life than him. Really,
I'm saying if somebody had all of this
money, why would they spend all their
life on YouTube all day, every day on a
community like this hating? It doesn't
make sense. If someone had all of this
money, they'd be out traveling the
world. They'd be out living their life.
They wouldn't waste their time with this
community. That That's what doesn't make
any sense. They wouldn't be on here
every day if they if they weren't skin.
They're on here all day every day. Why
would someone that's got all this money
spend all their life on YouTube?
No, just like I don't I don't even know
why. I think I was just trying to warn
you, but you'll believe what you believe anyways.
Yeah, but like I said, even if I had
7800 pound a month, bro, I'd still have
a better life than all of these people.
I'm not on here every day. No, I'm
[ __ ] not on here every day, mate. I
was off for days and I've been off of
YouTube for weeks. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, not at all at
all. Because Monty Man got me back onto
this YouTube. And don't forget, I was
off of YouTube for like 5 days.
Monty Man got me back into it. These
people were still on YouTube. So yeah,
and I'll be off of YouTube again tomorrow
after I leave Monty. I won't be on here
again for maybe a week, two weeks. So,
but like I said, bro, I could have
[ __ ] Yeah, I was I was doing six
streams yesterday, man. Because I was
with [ __ ] Monty, man. You [ __ ]
[ __ ] Because I was talking to Monty,
man. You [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] man.
because I was talking to Monty man who
got me on YouTube
who got me back on this [ __ ]
[ __ ] I had no plans to go back on
this. But anyways, let's stop all this
[ __ ] anyways now. Yeah, after
let's say Monday, right? I'll come back
after this Monty man thing. I will come
back on Saturday
and I don't want to see any of you
people on YouTube that call anyone skin.
All of you people that say people on
this people that or it's not even about
skin. It's not even about skin either.
It's about you know when you're calling
people the manta or or you're saying
that people got no friends. I don't want
to see any of you people on YouTube.
When I come back, I'm going to go
through every single day and I don't
want to see any of you people on YouTube
because I'm just going to say they were
talking about themselves. They can't get
off of YouTube. You know what I'm going
to say when I come back, you know?
So, yeah. Anyways,
what are you saying about this bet?
Yeah. So, hopefully the sort of wet wins.
Yeah, but why would you like a disabled
community? There's nothing to like about
it. It's full of [ __ ] bongos.
I mean, when I mean skin, I mean, these
people literally have nothing. They're
just like belly.
I mean, LJ says that £650 is skin, which
it [ __ ] isn't.
But like I said, even if I had £700 a
month, I'd still even when I had £700 a
month, I was I still had a better life
than all of them. That's the funniest
thing about it. I still had a better life. So,
but anyways, he's just a bullshitter.
Anyways, enough about that.
Yeah, you don't lie. Uh
yeah, but he thinks he's rich. That's
the thing. him and Virgin Boy, they seem
to think that they've got money, but
they don't have anything. That's the
weirdest thing about it is they actually
think that they've got money when they
really, really don't.
So, and LJ literally is skint because if
he had all of this money, he would not
be on YouTube every day begging,
you know? That's that's it's it's
straight right, bro. Like I would say
most people that go on that channel
can't even afford to go out for some
drinks. That's how bad it is, you know.
Anyways, I just let the evidence show
everyone everything. I don't even I
don't I don't want to call anyone
anything. I just let the evidence show
that when these people can't get off in
this community every day, then it goes
it doesn't look good. It doesn't look
good, does it? So, yeah.
And I've got my own money. I've got two
grand. That's more than enough for a single person.
Still get money a month. Why would I be
jealous of anyone, bro? I've lived I've
lived a life in 3 years than these
people will never live. I I'm 27 and
I've had more of a life in 3 years than
these people ever will. That's That's
the maddest thing about it. 4 years I've
had a better life than they would ever have.
I done more in three years than they've
done in their whole life. That's that's
the maddest thing about it. So stunt.
That's how bad it is.
More than they will ever than they will ever have.
Yeah. And that's good. Yeah. And that's
good. It doesn't matter. I I I've lived the life.
You don't even have 2K to your name.
Again, this is how you also know that
these people are skinned because the way
they talk about money, no normal person
in the real world talks like that. Two
grand is peanuts. No normal person
speaks like that. Like you go to your
sisters or your mom or you got friends
at work, nobody would say that. only
people that don't have money, like
people in this community, like nobody
would ever ever ever say that. You know
what I'm saying? I mean, I mean, to be
fair, I used to have it before when L
tried to say certain amounts of money is
nothing. It's all fantasy land. They
believe their own lies. Like him telling
himself that he's on four grand a month,
Virgin boy thinking that he's got money.
They're living in fantasy world. Like
you got people that saying that [ __ ]
um how much money they're showing is
nothing, but they don't even have a bed.
They don't even have a [ __ ] bed.
That's That's the maddest thing about
it. They have charity shop clothes and
they don't even have a bed and they're
talking like they're rich. It's madness.
It's a It's a [ __ ] madness, lad. You know. So yeah, man.
See, somebody said before they were
getting 40 grand a month on YouTube. Now
I can believe it because they travel the
world. The [ __ ] they used to do. There
was some kind of substance there.
Yeah. Well, more for you. Yeah. Well,
that's more for you. Gambling 2.3K a month.
Uh, sorry. Um, 23K a few days ago. Well,
then you're a loser, aren't you?
But again, you're all fantasist when it
comes to money, bro. And why do you even
talk about money anyways?
Well, he is skinned as well. So, he is
him and he's also skinn. Yeah. Why do we
even talk about this anyways, bro? Like,
yeah, [ __ ] all of this.
The point of the the fact of the matter
is, right, these people call people
skinned because they are skinned. End of
the day. They stop saying it about other
people and they stop coming on YouTube,
then they're not skin. Simple, you know?
Yeah. And if these people really had
money, they wouldn't be on YouTube every
day. Back to my point. Simple.
But yeah, he looks Imagine that he looks
that way. And he is skinned as well.
Why are we even talking about this money
thing as well, bro? If if all of you had
all of this money, you wouldn't be on
YouTube. I stick to my guns. Like that.
That's it. You wouldn't be on YouTube.
I've shown you thousands. [ __ ] other
people have shown you thousands. None of
you people can show anything. It we all
know who the skin people are in this
community. I don't even know why we're
talking about it. If they had all of
this money, they wouldn't be on YouTube.
I stick to my guns. End of. Just like on
Monday, you're not going to see me on
YouTube. Like, we don't need to keep
talking about it.
See big last thing I'm going to say is
you see these big YouTubers when they
used to say, "Oh, I made this from
YouTube. I made that from YouTube."
Well, we can kind of believe it when
somebody's traveling all over the world.
But when someone's not
um well considering they can't come off
of YouTube all day every day hating,
I've got a pretty good idea that
somebody that had all of this that has
all of this money wouldn't be doing that.
It it it kind of pictures their life
when they're on YouTube every single
day. You can kind of build a picture of
what their lives are actually like.
Think about it. Someone that's got all
of this money, all of these friends
would not be on YouTube every day hating.
So, it kind of builds a puzzle what
their life actually is. So, yeah, I just
go by the evidence when they can't get
off of YouTube cuz I know, bro, if I if
I had all of this money in the world,
bear in mind I'm taking a break and I
was calling people skint every day and I
was rich, I wouldn't be on YouTube, bro.
I'd be on an island.
[ __ ] like Richard Branson. If I had
all this money these people claim they have. So
you just said money gives you freedom
and opportunity. So if you have lots of
it, why would you waste your life on
air? Doesn't make sense.
Does not make any [ __ ] sense.
Think of it right. If I was really
getting four grand a month like L J, I
would go to some of the places that I've
not I've not been because he's barely
been anywhere at 42. He hasn't even been
to Asia. [ __ ] hasn't even been to
Asia at 40 [ __ ] two. I'd start going
to some of the places I've not been
just a double both teams to score.
And another thing, main man, can you
give me two grand? If it's peanuts to
you, can you give me two grand?
I want [ __ ] two grand if it's
peanuts. That's another thing. You You
on here all talk like you're
millionaires. You used to do it in the
Fraser days as well.
You always used to do it in the Fraser
days. I mean, that was the whole point
of the money game, but no one could show
me anything. I showed them [ __ ] six grand
and no one could show me anything, you
know? I'm just building I'm building the
I'm building the evidence together. You
know, sat on YouTube every day. Can't
take one day off of YouTube. Will run
away when you show them money. They've
got to be skin.
You know, if you if you took it to a
court, right, the court would say they're skin.
No, I won't gamble it, bro. Give me two
grand if it's peanuts.
>> I think you people are fantasists. Really?
You a You haven't shown more money than
me, mate. No one has shown more money
than me. I'm still waiting to be shown 10 grand.
I don't think I'm ever going to be being
shown 10 grand. You No one has ever
shown more money on here than me except
maybe Mr. B. So yeah.
And even the way LJ talks about money, I
think he said that three and a half
grand. Yeah, he's a fantasist, bro. To
be honest, they're all re [ __ ]
idiots to be honest. Just leave it at
that. But no one no one has shown as
much money as I have.
No, he [ __ ] did not, mate. No, he
[ __ ] did not. I'd love to see that
video. No, he [ __ ] did not.
Like, you're all fantasists.
You're all fantasists.
You you you claim that you've got all of
this money. Why would you waste your
precious life on YouTube? And and it's
big amounts of money you're talking
about as well. You know, 2.3K is nothing.
You know, I remember I lost two grand
before and I was getting more money than
you and I was like I felt a bit sick.
That's how I know these people are just
fantasists. Just the way they talk about life, money,
pe normal people don't talk like that,
you know. No one no normal person talks like that,
bro. I'm [ __ ] richer than you. You
don't even have anything. I'm richer
than you, bro. I'm richer than most of
you on here cuz you're all skinned.
I'm richer than all of you on here.
You're all [ __ ] skinned. You can't
even show anything.
And another thing is right,
let's just say this. Even if you have
all of this money,
yeah, I don't want to see five grand. I
want to see 10 grand.
You know, I don't want to see five
grand. I want to see 10 grand. I've
already shown over five grand. I want to
see 10 grand.
Why do I want to see five grand? I want
to see 10 grand.
No, not five grand. Can you show 10
grand? Which is what I've been waiting
for. Why do I want to see the same
amount that I've shown?
No, I've already shown six grand and I'm
not showing it again. I'm not going to
my bank account to pull out any more
money. You have seen six grand. If
you're not going to show me 10 grand,
I'm just going to block you. Simple.
Stable old atmosphere. This is exactly
why I left.
You know, bro, I shown six grand for
about three months last summer. I want
to see your 10 grand. Simple. So, you're
not going to show me 10 grand?
No, you're not going to show me 10 grand.
There you go. I can show it right here. Actually,
same atmosphere in here every day. That's
Five 5 point. There you go. I still have
the picture of it. And don't ask me
where it is now because whether I have
it now or I don't have it now, you have
been shown that amount of money. I could
have borrowed that money and there it
is. I want to I want to see 10 grand.
You know what? I want to see 10 grand.
I want to see 10 grand, bro.
That's proof that at the time that I
showed it before. So, I want to see. Yeah.
I mean, to be honest with you, bro, like
there's not no reason to not be shown
[ __ ] £10,000. To be honest with you,
I don't know why no one's shown me £10,000.
It's like It's like L J, right? Let's
Okay, I'm I'm wrong about L J. He gets
over four grand a month. Okay. So, can
you show me this 10 grand then? It's
only two 2 and 1/2 months money. Can you
can you show me 10 grand which I've been
asking to be shown for [ __ ] god knows how long? Yeah.
You can't do that though, can you matey?
I remember when [ __ ]
uh that Lee Liberist used to say four
grand is [ __ ] all. That's what I'm
saying. They're all fantasists. Somebody
in Wales, right? Like any even someone
in London would never say that. Never.
You know how many friends that I've got,
but these people where they have no
money and they've never had money, they
don't understand what money buys. You understand? So yeah,
I remember that Lee Libra. Yeah. I said,
"Bro, I could literally buy you with 4
grand." Like you live in Wales. I could
buy you and I could buy an apartment
before grand. That's how bad it is. You
live in a [ __ ] village for [ __ ]
sake. But they're all fantasist because
no normal person, no one in the real
world talks like that. Like they might
say, "Oh, it doesn't really go for
nowadays." So, but no one talks like
that. Not one person of this community
would ever talk like that. That's how
you know they're fantasists. They've
never had money. You know,
they're fantasists, bro. They don't have
no money. That's why they go on about
And to be honest with you, right, let's
just say that you have all of this
money. What are you going to do with it, bro? Cuz
even when I was 21, 22, I was living a
better life than them.
And I was on, like I said, I was on £700
a month. Imagine that. £700 a month. I
was on £700 a [ __ ] month. And I was
living a better life than them. That's mad.
£700 a month I used to get, bro. Yeah.
And I was living a better life than all
of them. And they were still jealous. So,
so it doesn't really matter, does it really?
But I can actually say things I've done
in my life. I've been loads of places.
I've stayed in nice hotels, bang loads
of escort, drunk, gambled. What do you
people do in your life yet you've got
all of this money? I think that's that's
I think that's a fair point, you know. You know,
but then I think it's also autism as
well. I think it's also autism,
you know, obsessed with money and [ __ ] Yeah, man.
And why are you gambling two? Like me,
right? If I gamble 2.3K, which I
actually have lost 2 grand before and I
was sick. The way I would see it is even
£1,100 I like, oh [ __ ] you could go
America with that money. Like, doesn't
matter. And I was on like three grand a
month. So, it just goes to show when
you're calling certain amounts of money
peanuts, it doesn't matter if it gets
you four or it doesn't get you four.
You've just lost £2,000. You could go on
holiday to probably most places with that money.
So, it's it's a lot of money, you know.
It's a lot of money. Really, if you
think about it, it's a lot of money to [ __ ] lose. So, yeah, man. Oh [ __ ]
Cuz here's the thing, right?
anxiety. You should be out living the
life, bro. You should be out living that life.
Do you know how much [ __ ] I've done in 3
4 years? Oh, bro. You wouldn't even
know, bro. 3 4 years. You should be out
living that life, bro. I got a
[ __ ] say that they're in Turkey
and they're still watching Lord Jay.
to think I would be on here watching
someone if I was on holiday.
[ __ ] me. Are you mad, bro? I would
literally delete the YouTube app.
But it just nothing
they say makes any sense. Oh, they could
have money, but then they've got anxiety. So, yeah.
Nothing they say makes any sense. I
remember I used to go out every Friday,
Saturday some well sometimes I used to
do Friday and Saturday when I used to do
this approach and [ __ ] drink and [ __ ]
and I remember I always used to go on
large and it would be the same people
the same spackers right and I'd go on it
for like 2 minutes then I'd come back
about 6 7 hours later and it'd be the
same people on YouTube and then I'd be
like hold on a minute so they these
people are called you skin they're
saying that you've got no friends.
They're saying that you've got anxiety,
yet they have been on YouTube for
[ __ ] hours on a Friday, Saturday.
Like, [ __ ] the money side of it, right?
For a minute. If they had all of these friends
and they didn't have anxiety and they
there were none of the things they call
you, why are they on YouTube every day?
Strange, isn't it? Unless they've got no
arms and legs, you know? I mean, just
doesn't make any sense.
This does not make no sense, bro.
No, I I was saying that like if these
people have got all of these friends,
why are they on YouTube every day?
Yeah. And I've still got money now and I
don't care about money anyways.
Yeah. I don't give a [ __ ] And guess
what? I had that money and I spent that money good.
I'm not on YouTube saying I've got all
of this money but I can't get off of
YouTube. You see, money is meant to be
spent. These people claim they've got
all of this money, but they're on
YouTube every day. That's what I find
mad. I find mad how what I find mad is
how these people say that people ain't
got no friends. They've got no life.
They have none of these things. Not even
money, right? [ __ ] the money thing for a
minute. Yeah. But they can't get off of YouTube.
Every Friday, Saturday, I used to do the
test. every Friday, Saturday, I'd be the
same people on YouTube. Just goes to
show they were talking about themselves
all along. Yeah.
So, yeah, that it just goes to show they
were talking about themselves all along, matey.
Yeah, these people are they're just
prolific self projectors. End the story
in it. So,
and it's not even that. It's like when
they say that people have got no job.
Why are they sat on YouTube every day?
If they like, bro, and you said to me,
right, that oh, you come on YouTube
every day. Okay, I'll come off of
YouTube for a week and I'll come back.
Do you want to do you want to play that
game? Cuz I can do it.
I can do it, bro. I can play that game
again. I'll come back on YouTube next
Saturday and will I see you people on
YouTube? And that's how you your
argument comes to an end. You know,
that's how your argument comes to an end.
Like, what was I doing with that six
grand, bro? Traveling around [ __ ]
escorts, [ __ ] women, drinking
alcohol. You people are sat on YouTube.
That's my whole point, you know.
going to try and use this rail card
today. When I go to Birmingham, to be
honest, I'm going to use this rail card.
But yeah, hopefully this football bet
wins cuz back to that again, it will pay
for everything. What's that? 285. Yeah,
pretty pay for everything to be honest.
It'll probably pay for the Saturday and
the Sunday to be fair. Yeah.
Yeah. Enough about the money [ __ ] Anyways,
I'm going to go and [ __ ] throttle
Monty today when I [ __ ] see him. I'm
going to strangle him, bro, for putting
me back on this [ __ ] shitty
community. [ __ ] you, man.
Put me back on this.
So, I'm kind of lazy, but no, I
definitely want to go today, bro. I
definitely want to definitely want to go.
Definitely want to go, bro. It'll be fun.
I ain't been on a train in I can't
remember the last time I was on a train somewhere
like that. Maybe.
Bro, it's been maybe Manchester actually. Maybe
I think it was Manchester,
Manchester, I think. Yeah.
Yeah, I want to go new city today, but
chill, you know. Uh, let's see.
Don't [ __ ] bail out on me, bro. Now.
Yeah, it might not come in though. Then
then we'll be [ __ ] up in it. No, it
won't be [ __ ] up.
I need to start getting ready then if
I'm [ __ ] going to meet this [ __ ]
It's already 11.
The only thing I used to hate about
traveling is getting my haircut. It
takes so much time out of the day. You
know, when you need to wait and then get
your haircut. I [ __ ] hate it, bro.
I used to hate getting my haircut, bro.
[ __ ] when I used to go to Manchester
and that. I used to always get it done
the day before. It just takes so much
time out the day, you know.
Yeah, it doesn't matter, bro.
Yeah, I do actually want to go B. I need
to go out today, bro, but I ain't done
nothing [ __ ] for a while. So,
I just I just want the bet to come in.
Used to be fun getting at 3K a month, man. But
live life to the fullest, mate. Live
life to the fullest. That's what I did.
I just live a normal life like everyone
else. I don't like to live a normal life
like everyone else though.
Let me see if this guy is still meeting.
Start getting ready soon if we're we
going. Oh [ __ ]
You might go there and get [ __ ] Might
go there and get [ __ ] ambushed.
I might go there and get [ __ ] ambushed. My god.
Does Monty have Wi-Fi in his house,
though? Cuz obviously his phone's blocked. So
that's another thing. I need to sort
this phone out as well. [ __ ] sake.
There's so many things to do. Man,
it's like a million things that [ __ ] once.
It should do what? Come in. Yeah.
[ __ ] me, bro.
You see what he's saying? This is still
going to me.
>> What do I wear today?
I'll just go overnight in it.
Uh, jeans, trainers. Oh, [ __ ] bad
about them trainers, aren't they?
Wait, let me see.
I remember there being like the trainers before trainers.
Why is he gone quiet? Has
he even got a [ __ ] bed? Yeah. Um,
should I wear my little cap?
Should I wear my little cap? Oh,
bless you. Look out. Bless you. Bless Bless. Oh.
Feeling a bit hungry now.
No, no, no, no, no. I just can't be
bothered to get my haircut. It's all
[ __ ] long, is it?
It's all [ __ ] long, bro.
feel your haircut. Don't be annoyed with it.
But you'll probably spend less money
there than you would going out in
London. That's the funny thing. Yeah. Monty
of Black Ops.
You must sign into Xbox Live.
What should I wear today? Oh.
Oh, please. Thank you. Yeah, mom.
Yeah, I'm contacting Mon, but he's not answering.
He's not answering, bro. Hold
on, bro. What the [ __ ]
Yeah, he wants to meet. Yeah.
Give it a whirl in it. [ __ ] it.
Give it a little while.
The only thing I hate about is is is
getting a haircut.
Yeah. Skint, bro. Yeah, man. Can you
lend me £5? I'm really skint.
Yeah, I'm really skint, bro.
Yeah, man. Can you give me some money?
I have one pound to my name. I'm really skinn. Yeah.
Yeah. Can you give me Can you Can you
give me some money, please, bro?
I'm really skinn, bro. I'm like
starving. Yeah. Yeah, I gambled, bro. I
lost all my money.
Yeah, I lost all my money, bro. I'm [ __ ] skin.
Yeah, man. Can you lend me some money?
I'm really scared.
Yeah, man. I want some of you
millionaires to lend me some money.
I'm being sarcastic, you [ __ ] idiot.
I have a football bet for today, though.
80. Um, both teams to score. Double both
Yeah, I'm going to go Birmingham today. Meet Monty.
Oh, I have to get my haircut first. I
hate getting my haircut. It's so long.
It's boring sitting in that chair for
[ __ ] You know what I mean?
Yeah, I didn't really gamble while I was joking.
Look at these tickets then.
Where's a new stream? Been on this
[ __ ] journey for a long time, bro.
So it's like £50.
Got one here.
Some of them are £22. Jesus.
Was that an open return?
They're longer trains, but I mean £22 is sick.
£22. That's really cheap.
Very cheap, isn't it?
£23 for [ __ ] return.
probably do the whole thing with like
[ __ ] almost [ __ ] 80 quid to be
fair except the haircut.
You could probably get a train to
Birmingham and back and get on the piss
for probably less than £100.
It's very cheap, isn't it?
That is cheap, bro. It 22 [ __ ] pound.
[ __ ] hell. You spend more than that
in the [ __ ] corner shop nowadays.
That's actually cheap, bro.
And the only thing that's making me not
want to go is [ __ ] get my haircut.
It's just boring. I hate it. It's just so long.
[ __ ] boring as [ __ ] I hate waiting
for things as well.
Should ask anyone that's met me. I hate
waiting for things, but at the same
time, got nothing else to do. So um
trying to decide what to Yeah.
A lot of people don't play uh play Black
Ops 2 anymore.
Host ended the game. How could a host
end the [ __ ] game, bro? What the Oh, [ __ ]
Maybe I'll just go there and we just
fight Timmy in it. We should just go
there and fight Timmy.
Yeah. Be funny, isn't it? Be a laugh,
mate. It probably won't even cost more
than [ __ ] £100
to be fair.
probably won't even cost more than
[ __ ] 100 quid. Well, obviously the
haircut, but haircuts
just in what you get anyways. That's not
counted with expenses, you know.
Yeah, I might go actually, but I'm not
I'm not going to lie. I might actually
go. [ __ ] it.
Give it a whirl. Give it a whirl. Yeah. I would
give a little try. Give her a little world.
Let's showing life.
Oh, I need to have a shower. I'm feeling
a bit staley, you know.
Smelling a bit Staley neighbor.
But can I be asked? Can he be asked?
That's the question, bro. Can I actually be [ __ ] Um. Getting
a haircut is so boring.
LJ wouldn't know the struggles, would he?
I wonder if people still play that
Smackdown versus War 2009.
Family connections are not good.
[ __ ] camping. Can't slowly.
It's been going very slowly.
There we go, [ __ ] I beat you.
I got the first kill. Yes, sir.
Oh, you [ __ ] dirty camping [ __ ] [ __ ] hell.
[ __ ] dirty camper.
[ __ ] dirty camper, bro.
[ __ ] bro. Why is there so many
campers on this [ __ ] game, bro?
Dirty dirty camping [ __ ]
Just campers. That's all they do is camp
every time, bro. Every [ __ ] time
got orange friends.
You know what? I'll go if the football
wins. If the football bet wins, I'll go 100%.
What time does it finish? like
five barbers 100%.
Then I'll go on 100%. If not, then I
can't be asked. I can't be annoyed with it.
I need to be put in a good mood. If I'm
[ __ ] sitting in the barber sh, you
know, you got to sit in that barber
chair for an hour and it's so boring, you know.
But I think it will win. Hang on.
Oh, one second. But yeah,
get my haircut. It's so boring. Yeah,
I'm going to go meet Monty today. Um, greasy.
I'm just [ __ ] I just hate getting my
haircut. It's just boring, bro. Just sat
in the chair for an hour, you know. Yeah,
we're going to get some batches. There
you go. Montling man.
That's why I called you. Monty Monontto man. Montoing man.
[ __ ] bro. This game is full of
[ __ ] campers, bro. On this [ __ ]
Call of Duty. I'm telling you, it's full
of camping [ __ ]
This gun is [ __ ] as well. One sec. Yeah,
they're just [ __ ] They're proper campers
on this game, bro.
Have you noticed that there so many campers?
Have you noticed that, Grezy? So many campers.
Are you joining or what?
I'm hoping this football bet wins, bro.
Yeah, it has. [ __ ] camping bastards.
What's the best gun? The one shot one, is it?
What the [ __ ] The game is just frozen.
Grezy, what the [ __ ]
Okay, I'm gonna go back on Franklin cuz
the game's frozen.
Should I go and see Monty today?
You can get a train to Birmingham and
back for [ __ ] £22.
So, you could probably go Birmingham,
get on the piss and eat for probably 80 quid.
You could probably do everything with
that [ __ ] 80 that you just got paid.
Ain't it greasy?
Probably in it.
Yeah, pretty well most of it anyways.
But the haircut
I could probably go out today and spend about 150
which is quite cheap to be honest, isn't it?
I want to win this football bet.
But I think it'll be funny. Me and Monty getting drunk.
You got nothing better to do in it.
Me and Monty getting pissed.
What don't you Why don't you tell us
what you think, Grezy?
Like, Zippy, why don't you tell us what you think?
I just don't want to get my haircut.
It's boring, bro. I hate it.
[ __ ] hate getting my haircut. It's so
boring. That's what I used to hate about going out.
So annoying sitting on that chair.
Nothing to do. It's boring.
It's so boring. Grievy.
Oh, bless you.
bless you alive.
Yeah, but that means me getting my [ __ ] haircut.
[ __ ] long, is it?
Do you know what? Yeah, I might actually
go, bro. [ __ ] it.
With a Mickey M. What about the What
with the Mickey Mouse cap, Grezy Boss?
What with the Mickey Mouse cap?
You know, we can call out Timmy and we
can all have a big fight.
We can all have a big fight.
What do you think about that? A big big old fight.
What a big fight. No, I'm not going to
fight, bro. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that [ __ ] bro. I'm not
spending money to go out and fight people, bro.
Well, we wanted to go live, but the
thing is is that we're going to get
mongos like [ __ ] Timmy and people try
calling up the pubs. That's the problem.
I would say we'll keep it private and
then when we go back, we'll go live,
but we'll still be drinking. We can't go
live in in the pubs because they're
going to try and get us kicked out and
[ __ ] You know what these jealous mongos do.
So probably when we go back to the house
then we'll just get we'll just get drunk
and go live in it cuz we can't go live
in the clubs, bro. Cuz the people on YouTube
try to get people kicked out and [ __ ]
and Timmy will start trying to be a
[ __ ] and that. So,
cuz when I go back to Monty's, I'm just
going to tell them to come to the
address. I'm I'm a [ __ ] like I'm a crazy
[ __ ] I'll be like, "Bring whoever you
want now to the address." That's what
I'll say, bro. When we're done now [ __ ]
approaching, when I've done the
approaching and drinking, I'll just tell
them to come.
I will end it. Like all of this [ __ ]
that's been going on for like years, not
years, like for months with these two,
I'm just going to end it because I'm
just telling them to come. Simple, is it?
I say bring who the [ __ ] you want.
Money, Mike. Bring bring the lottery.
That's what I say. Yeah.
No, he's not looking for me, mate.
and we'll do some videos like but we're
not doing uh
we're not doing [ __ ] we're not doing
that madness with uh you know I'm
actually going to go bro [ __ ] it I think
yeah [ __ ] this
I'll be with you
I will be with you shortly
>> yeah [ __ ] women I can't be mate anymore
I'm done me now I woke up happy I'm
happy now I'm [ __ ] over it literally So
>> yeah, cuz we're meeting and [ __ ]
we're going to get go out and get laid,
PJ. If we are going to go out and get laid. >> Yeah,
that's what I like to hear. Boss,
>> we're getting laid, PJ. [ __ ] women. They
can't be asked anymore. Yeah, it's
pretty funny that
woman can't handle handle a
relationship. What's the point of being
in a relationship if you can't handle
the bad parts?
Yeah, true. I'm going to wear my little
cap today, buddy. I'm going to wear my
little Mickey Mouse cap.
>> Yeah, look. Yeah.
>> Look, I just got up me, buddy.
>> I just got out.
>> You did what? >> Look.
>> Look, I just got out of bed.
>> Yeah, we're going to meet up, bro. Are
you going to be doing some cold approaching, too?
>> Yeah. Look, Paige. Yeah, I just got out
of bed, mate.
>> God bless you. Bless me.
I'm in my box.
>> I'm in my boxes.
>> Oh, I don't know what to wear. I'm I'm
just picking out something to wear.
Monty. Monty Moon.
Monty Moon. I'm just picking something
to wear. Monty Moon.
>> I'm going to wear my little Mickey Mouse
cap. What are you going to wear?
What? I'm wearing a [ __ ] man bikini. Me?
>> Nah, you can't
>> wear a man bikini. >> Why? >> No,
I'm just going with women. Me, PJ, I'm done.
>> And we'll call out We're going to call
out that Timmy. We're going to call out
that Timmy [ __ ] as well.
>> Yeah, Timmy. Hurry up, bud. Hurry up,
Timmy. Chop. Chop. Timmy.
It's all going to be a big punch up, isn't it? turned.
>> Yeah, we'll [ __ ] him right up.
>> You'll [ __ ] him up the [ __ ] isn't it?
>> Yeah. The funny thing is here is why
does why does a man villa a woman
through the eyes and lows, but when he
get his eye for a woman, she [ __ ] runs?
>> Do Do you want Do you want my opinion, Monty?
>> No, I don't need it. I don't need it. I
really don't need it.
>> They're all I tell I tell you why.
Because they're all [ __ ]
>> Is that funny?
>> It's not even that. My mom My mom likes
her. My mom thinks she's a [ __ ] Mason woman.
>> So my kids like her as well. Yeah. But
I'm going to tell my mom anyway. I'm
going back to Birmingham. I mean
Nottingham. Me anyway. It's me, lad.
>> Well, bless you.
>> Back to Nottingham.
Can't be women anymore.
>> It's like she took a bite in my mouth.
That's what it's like. It's like she
took a big [ __ ] in my mouth.
>> They're horrible bastards ring isn't it? >> Yeah.
I'm going to go get a shower.
>> I'll be here. >> Huh?
>> I'll be 2 minutes. I'm just going to get
in a shower.
>> Yeah. Same.
>> I'm going to stay on though. Stay on.
Just need your m and come back.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. One sec, bro. One second.
>> I can't be chasing a woman who can't
handle when it gets hard.
>> I don't get women like that.
>> Handle when it gets hard, is it? Yeah.
>> You can't handle it when it gets hard.
It's all right when they kick you out of
place as they shout at you and you're
like, "Okay, okay, okay, I change." But
as soon as you do something, soon as you
do something back to them, he's like,
"Right, it's over. It's done. That's it.
That's it. You can't do that to me. But
I can do it for you."
>> Do you want me to bring you a cap? I've
got a new cap. I've got some caps I've never worn.
>> Have you?
>> Yeah. I bought some the other day. I've
only worn the Mickey Mouse one. I've got
Donald Duck and I've got a panda one. Oh, >> okay.
>> Which one do you want? YouTubes.
>> You choose. I'll show you them.
>> No, you choose. PJ YouTube. You choose.
>> I don't mind, bro. One sec. Oh, [ __ ]
Look, we got this one or
>> Oh, you got Oh, you got Donald.
>> You choose
>> the panda one, I think.
>> Panda. Go for it. I don't mind. And I'm
wearing I'm going to be wearing this
one. Hold on.
Mickey. Uh Mickey.
>> Mickey Mouse. What?
>> Yeah, I'll be wearing Mickey.
We're going to do some videos. Yeah. >> Huh?
>> Go on then. The Donald dog's pretty good.
>> So, do you want the Donald one then?
>> Oh, stick with the one what you give me.
>> They're only They're only one They're
only two pound each. You can have which
one you want.
Okay, I'll go for the Mickey Mouse one
then. Mickey Mouse, that one's my one.
>> Yeah, go on. I go for the Donald Duck.
>> Okay, then I'll bring the Donald Duck one then.
>> Reminds me of N a little bit. Not that
not in a bad way.
>> Okay, bro. Okay. Okay. Okay.
One second. I'm trying to find that
other t-shirt. the the black one with
the one second, bro. Where the [ __ ] is that?
>> No, man. I hear [ __ ] women who can't
handle it when they get stuff. This is
what what I mean about women. You women,
you think that men have got arts off
that men don't feel [ __ ] pain. That
men don't go through stress or anxiety
problems or whatever.
>> Yeah. They don't care, do they? Of
course they do. No. No. Do they [ __ ] I
don't give a [ __ ]
As long as they they've got their [ __ ] you know,
I mean, as long as they got their
[ __ ] [ __ ] you know?
>> No, it's not that. It's [ __ ] women.
They think about other people where men
will just think of one woman where a
woman will have multiple choices in her head
>> where man will only choose one person.
>> It's true. It's true.
>> Of course it's true. Of
>> course it's true. A woman A woman always stays optional.
>> A man doesn't.
>> It's true. Yeah, it's the truth, bro.
>> Of course it is. So if you want some
[ __ ] relationship as if your woman
finish you when you're arguing, it's not
worth going out with him cuz you know if
you're going to argue again, you're just
going to get finished again. Or if you
make little money, these people was
trying to call me skint this morning. >> Well,
you're going to go out and get some
[ __ ] furniture today, PJ.
>> Yeah, you're going to be wearing the
Donald. I'm going to get you the I'm
going to give you the panda one. The
panda one looks better.
>> Give me which one? Well,
>> I think the panda one looks better cuz
the Donald Duck one, you might look a
bit of a [ __ ] in it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Go on then. I
have the panda one.
Yeah, that knowledge. Okay. One sec.
>> Now I don't have to wear Natalie's at
now cuz he's reminding me of her. I'm
not getting rid of anything. What
Natalie got me?
>> I'm not getting rid of my shorts or
t-shirts. She's got me all my
>> You just going to wear I'm just going to
wear a t-shirt and jeans.
>> Hey, you know what? With PG I might join
you actually. T-shirt and jeans. Yeah,
>> I'm wearing t-shirt, jeans, and trainers
and a cap. I join you on that. Yeah.
>> Yeah, why not?
>> Why not? Why not? I got some jeans downstairs.
>> Where's one of the t-shirts?
>> Just let me go and get a quick car show
when I show you my jeans. >> Yeah. [ __ ]
>> I don't want a woman to want off on me,
but [ __ ] it.
>> I got some nice Dior after shave as well.
>> Oh, yeah. myself.
>> I've got some gorgeous after just let me
put that that cuz I don't want you to
see my [ __ ] bones in my pants.
>> Okay, boss.
>> That's gorgeous. PJ,
>> let me see.
>> You go, boss. >> Really?
>> Yeah. That's gorgeous. That's nice. Nice.
>> I'll show you.
>> I've lost a lot of weight. I haven't
been eating properly. I haven't ate for
like six days now. Six days.
>> Be open. Ain't even been opened yet. I
kick I kicked [ __ ] out of my McDonald's
burger, PG. I kicked [ __ ] out of it. I
kept on punching my burger. I didn't
even eat it.
>> Why was you punching it? You was punching it.
>> I kicked [ __ ] out of my cheater. I only
had a couple of bites out of there.
Started kicking [ __ ] out my burger.
>> You're crazy. You are.
>> So I shut my burger outside in his box.
Yeah. Went back out to show someone.
Look what I done to my burger. I kicked
[ __ ] out my burger. Shown someone. The
burger is already gone with the box.
Someone's gone and picked the box up and
at the burger inside the box. What I
kicked [ __ ] out of.
>> Really? What a [ __ ]
>> Yeah, someone at it. I spat on it on everything.
>> [ __ ] hell. What a [ __ ] mate.
>> Then someone picked it all from
Birmingham and at it.
>> Jesus. What a nasty can. Is it Monty?
>> Yeah. So, when I got the McDonald's last
night, I didn't even eat it. Nothing. I
had nothing yesterday. still and they
waste that money on McDonald's for nothing.
>> God bless.
>> It's just what I go through. It's what I
go through with women in it. I go
>> They're horrible [ __ ] aren't they?
>> I go through the pain. Bad. Bad. Bad.
[ __ ] bad. I'm not doing it no more.
Look at me. I sliced all my arms open and everything.
>> Yeah, but you like it, Monty.
>> No, I don't like feeling like this over any woman.
I've never felt like this over any woman
for a long time, mate. >> Huh?
>> I've never felt like this for a woman
for a long time.
>> Did she even reply? Did she even reply
to any of your [ __ ]
>> No, she [ __ ] replied, but I'm not as to
be honest with you anymore. I'm not [ __ ]
She wants it to be over. It's over. I'm
not chasing after women anymore. I'm
done. I'm done with it. >> Yeah.
>> It's It's depressing the [ __ ] out of me.
It's [ __ ] hanging, isn't it?
>> Yeah, of course it is.
She She's the one. She is the one as
well. She's the right woman for me. She
is the one. I'm not just saying that. She >> Yeah,
>> we're perfect together. We make a good
couple, but [ __ ] it. She wants it. If
she wants it over, it's over. >> Yeah.
>> My mom My mom likes her. My mom adors
her. Like, literally.
>> Yeah. You know, but the thing is I want
a woman like my brothers have got a
woman who will stay with him and love
him and jump and give him a cuddle and
kiss or whatever. >> Yeah.
>> Bless you. Bless you in life, M.
>> Bless me in life. My life's good, mate.
Getting laid today.
>> Yeah, we are getting laid. That's right,
son. That's right.
>> I am. I'm not asked anymore. I can't be
asked. Okay. see what we mean. Now they
can't say that I'm cheating on her
because I'm not.
>> Yeah, damn right.
She's a knowable old, isn't she?
>> No, she's not horrible. I love her. I
[ __ ] love her. I do love Natalie.
I'm not going to set you and slag
Natalie off or call Natalie to [ __ ] I'm
just done with it. I'm done with getting
out another woman. That's it.
>> Yeah, I get you, bro. I get you, son. Sunshine.
>> One sec. Sure. I'm missing some t-shirts here.
What is it? I'm sure I was missing some.
>> I was huh?
>> Yeah. I had weed for three days. I'm
quitted. I'm not smoking it either.
>> Let's smoke some weed today.
No, I'm all right. Me, PJ, I don't want
to smoke it. >> Really?
>> Really? I don't want it. I don't want it
anymore. I'm done with weed. I'm done with it.
>> I've quit weed.
>> Weed is making more me more depressed to
be honest with you. Smoking it going through this.
>> Mhm. Really?
>> So, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> For sure.
>> Why does everyone keep saying bless you?
Bless you. What the [ __ ]
>> It's just a little saying that we we say it.
>> Bless you. I have sneezed
>> these Monty. These people are skin is in
it. Do you remember?
>> Do you remember that Monty? These people
are skin isn't it?
>> These are always skin.
>> You like it though, Monty?
>> I don't like it. I like being skin. No,
definitely desking, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> We're going to have a nice little burger
meal. Yeah, it's on the house.
>> We're going to have some nice food as well. Yeah.
>> That's your [ __ ] That's if I'm in the
mood to eat, PJ.
>> Oh, come on. You like a piggy burger, huh?
>> You haven't been in the mood for days to eat.
>> Yeah, I get you.
Yeah, but Monty, if we go live, they're
going to fight. They're going to call up
the pub and [ __ ] aren't they?
>> No, you go live before you go pub
>> or after. Is it?
>> Oh, after the pub. Yeah, you go live.
>> We'll do some videos. We'll do some
videos. We'll do some videos and put it on YouTube.
>> Yeah, we do some videos. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, we go live before we go to the
pubs and then we'll make videos.
No, we'll do videos and upload it and
then go live. Yeah, because you know
what happens when when you go live in the pub.
>> Yeah, of course. I know what happens.
They get you kicked out >> hotels.
>> Yeah, they're [ __ ] idiots. Idiots.
>> That's stupid. That's stupid of you
because they want content. Yeah. And
doing that, it stops the content. It's
weird, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> So, how many beds have you got where you
are? Are you sure I can stay?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Is there a bed? >> Yeah.
>> Well, how how many beds is there?
>> I'm not these [ __ ]
There's two beds. >> Really?
>> Yeah, there's two beds.
>> Have you calculated how far it is from
the city center yet? No.
>> Yeah, I'll tell you now. It won't take
me long getting there anyways.
Birmingham city center.
Oh, put train station in it. Birmingham train station.
I be the passion.
Oh, okay. It's only an hour walk for me.
>> An hour walk?
>> Yeah, that's it.
>> [ __ ] If you can't walk, you're not
going to walk an hour though, is it?
>> Yeah, I walk an hour.
>> No. What the [ __ ] No, seriously.
>> Yeah, seriously. I'll walk an hour. Can't
>> you get a bus?
[ __ ] the bus. I walk. What the [ __ ]
Where am I going to get the bus when I
got two perfect [ __ ] healthy legs, mate?
>> Yeah, it's not too far, is it? To be fair.
>> No, it's not. I've walked four miles
walked four miles to Cosmic Kitty's
house. I've walked further than that.
>> Oh, do you remember going where have my
little legs take me? Grezy, do you
remember that, Grezy? Go where have my
little legs take me?
>> No one likes me. That's [ __ ] hilarious, man.
>> What do you mean?
>> No one likes me. I like it. I like it.
>> What do you mean no one likes you?
>> No one likes me. No one. No one.
>> Of course they do. You see the case?
>> No, they don't.
>> Stop it. Goose.
>> I'm going to get a shower. Yeah, but I'm
staying here. I need my mic.
>> Okay. I'll
>> be right back. Right.
End it. Don't end it. Stay alive. If
you're going to get a show, we're going
to get one to stay alive.
>> Yeah, of course. People like you. You silly goose.
>> People like me. Who likes me? Who? Who? Who? Exactly. Me.
>> Oh, what happens to me is I get [ __ ]
bullied. Bullied off women.
>> Join the club.
>> I need to stop being a [ __ ] wimp with
women, man. And tell them straight. [ __ ]
you all. You [ __ ] bastards. [ __ ] you
>> Yep. That's >> PJ.
>> I'm gonna be shagging PJ when he gets
here. I'm gonna be buming him.
>> Well, you [ __ ] not. You dirty [ __ ]
Do you reckon I need a haircut, Monty or Nah?
>> No. Do you [ __ ] Do you [ __ ] need a
haircut? You just [ __ ] sort it, don't
you? Really? Basically, fashion it out.
Oh, bless you. Bless you. You
>> got me to give you a haircut, PJ. I give
you short back and sides. >> Really?
>> Yeah. I just put a ball on your head and
cut around it.
>> You're going to wear the panda hat.
>> I I need that. I need a
>> Yeah, I love an adventure. It's quite
cute. We're going to get on the baby
Guinnesses. Oh, I can't wait on some
baby Guinnesses, man.
Baby, get King.
>> Yeah, too. Right.
>> Well, I'm going to have a shower anyways, bro.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that's what I'm doing. You
just stay alive, though. >> Yeah.
>> Stay alive. >> Yeah.
>> It's just I'm looking for my towel.
>> Nothing wrong with a little adventure, ain't it?
Do you know what I mean? An adventure. >> Huh?
>> Yeah. Show what I'm wearing.
>> All right. I can't.
>> Hey, PG. I show you what I'll be wearing. Yeah.
>> One sec.
I don't even sleep in this room.
>> I don't even sleep in this room.
>> No. No. Don't. Don't be a Don't be a silly goose.
>> Don't be a silly.
>> Don't be a silly goose.
>> These are what?
>> Who's the first round on? You or me?
>> Yeah, I'm wearing jeans like that as
well. I'm wearing some money jeans.
>> You go boss and you putting his t-shirt on.
>> Someone said, "Look at your forehead, Monty."
>> Yeah, I know. I'm bald. He He stress off women. [Laughter]
Stress off women.
>> Yeah. So that's what I'm wearing then. >> Jeez.
>> Oh, I wear something better then. PJ.
>> No, it's nice. It's nice. Is
>> that good? Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Someone said you've been bold since 19.
No, they got it wrong. I've been bald
since we're 16.
>> Oh, bless you.
>> It's cuz my ears dead fine. Natalie will
tell you I've got [ __ ] fine hair. My
ears it it falls out. It's just too
fine. I got thin hair.
>> Very thin hair. Bless you.
Bless you. I've not sneezed. Okay.
Which t-shirt should I wear then?
I've got a Hugo Boss polo t-shirt. I
might wear that to be honest.
>> Do you want to see it? >> Yeah,
>> I'll show you. Yeah, I think you'll like
it. I've not worn it for a very long time.
>> PJ W to the word. Yeah.
>> One sec. One sec. One sec.
>> Oh, that one. I saw that one. Look. Polo.
>> Oh, nice.
I might wear that with a little cap to I
might wear that with a Mickey Mouse cap.
>> With a Mickey Mouse cap,
>> what do you think?
>> It's up to you in it. Whatever you
Whatever you like.
>> Yeah, but do you reckon it will go with
the Mickey Mouse cap? Should do it. Yeah.
>> Yeah, of course. Of course.
This is the Natalie got me. I like it.
This is the Natalie. Natalie got me this
t-shirt, that t-shirt. She got me the
shorts and t-shirt to him. She got me another t-shirt.
>> If the bet doesn't If the bet doesn't If
the bet doesn't come in, Bombay, then
we've had it, haven't we? If the bet
don't come in,
>> what do you think, Monty? If the bet
don't come in, we've had it. E.
>> Yeah. And that's the app Natalie got me.
>> Do you know what that means? One sec.
Let me see.
>> Do you know what that means? We've had
it. That's the app Natalie got me.
>> Natalie got me this as well. And that >> means
you know what that means. Um, we've had it.
>> We had it.
>> It means you're [ __ ] in it.
>> Well, I [ __ ] had it and I'm [ __ ]
>> It means you're [ __ ] in it. Yeah.
I just hate women when they get sad,
they run off. I [ __ ] hate it.
>> Do you hate these people on YouTube, too? >> Huh?
>> These Yeah, of course. Not all of them,
cuz there's some good people in here.
>> Yeah, but they're weirdos, isn't it?
>> Not all of them.
>> Well, most of them, is it?
>> A lot of them are. Yeah.
>> Most of them are weirdos, isn't it?
>> Yeah. A lot of them. A lot of them are
weirdos, mate. a lot of them. I can't. That's why
that's why I rather just be normal to do
normal channels instead of reacting to
these clowns because these are supposed
to be bit older than us, but they act
more [ __ ] spasticated than us.
>> Yeah. It's weird, isn't it?
>> Yeah. But Monty, does that top and that
hat go? I think it does, don't it?
>> Yeah, it will do. Will do. You know
yourself when you put it all on.
Like it's it's it's black and white and
then there's black and red.
>> Which oneever you want to wear? Black
and white or black and red?
>> Yeah. Together.
>> That's what I'm basically wearing. Well,
black but with a red. You go both side
>> with like a blue,
>> gray or white t-shirt.
>> Right. I'm going to get ready. One
second. I'm just going to have a shower. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. That's what I'm going to do
now. See you in a minute. Yeah, man.
>> Stay alive. Stay alive. And when you
finish the show, you can just come back
on and start talking.
>> Oh, I can't. Oh, I can't.
Is that funny or I can't?
>> Oh, you like it, is it?
Monty likes all of this. Is it
likes all of this [ __ ] >> Yeah.
PJ, let me back up. Just one second. Yeah.
>> All right,
just let me do this. Yeah, I'll be right back.
>> All right, can
was that funny? All right.
Oh, I can't Batman. That grimy Batman. Batman.
I happen to go to another city now to
look for love. A I have to go all the
way to another city now to look for love
cuz I can't find any love here. So
in the shower, bro. Two sex, bro.
You know what? Yeah. I was actually
going to invite [ __ ] Virgin boy, but
no skint flints allowed on this trip.
Isn't that right, Monty?
No skimp flints allowed on this trip.
No skimp flints.
Isn't that right, Monty?
No skin allowed on this trip, sunshine.
What do you think to that?
No skin flints allowed to this trip, sunshine.
Sorry, mate. No.
Sorry, mate. Nah. Oh, [ __ ]
Not at all at all.
>> Yeah, bro.
[ __ ] this bastard thing. Could be. Who knows?
Maybe I am and maybe I'm not. Who knows?
Just got out of the shower.
Just about to play some Xbox.
This [ __ ] bet better [ __ ] come in today, man.
Better come in.
Never you mind, matey. Never you [ __ ] mind.
I need to get a haircut as well.
It's annoying, isn't it? [ __ ]
hate getting a haircut, bro. It's so long.
>> It's long getting a haircut.
>> Why? What you doing? Getting a haircut at you.
>> Yeah. And I'm coming, bro. I just got
out of the shower.
>> I won't even get a haircut. Just come.
[ __ ] the haircut. Don't need one.
>> I need need a haircut, M. I'm very
hairy. I've got a hairy beard.
>> Yeah, I've got a hairy beard. In fact, I
need to get some shaveish, actually.
>> No, I've got a really hairy beard, bro.
I need It's not the hair, it's the
beard. It's the beard as well. I can't
come unless I'm looking fresh. Monty,
you should know this, son.
>> Yeah, I need to get my ass beat as well,
to be honest. If
>> we're getting [ __ ] today, bro, we
need to look our best, you know.
>> Exactly. Exactly.
>> Yeah, you horrible [ __ ]
I don't want to get no [ __ ] but I'm
doing get in. I'm not [ __ ] [ __ ] around, mate.
>> Mate, listen. We're going to get you
some [ __ ] We're going to get you
some [ __ ] today. Then we're going to
send it to Natalie G on WhatsApp. We're
going to show her who's bossing it.
>> No, we're not. No, we're not. No, we're
>> We're going to show her who's boss.
>> No, we're not.
we're going to show her who's bossing it. No,
>> I'm just going to show Natalie what
she's actually losing. >> Yeah.
I say I don't want to lose Natly, but [ __ ] it.
>> I'm walking away. I'm walking. I'm
walking. I'm walking. I can't be as
>> I love her. Don't get me wrong. I love
Natalie. I got feelings for Natalie, but
I'm not letting my feelings get the best
of me for a woman.
>> I can't believe you bought her a TV.
>> Yeah, I got her a TV. She can have the
TV. I'm not bothered about the TV. I'm
not bothered about the set I got either.
And if you don't believe that I got a I
can show you the textes of my mom that is coming. >> Mhm.
>> I'm pay I've got a TV. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean?
>> I was going to virgin.
>> I was going to invite Virgin Boy Bombay,
but no virgins allowed on this trip. No
skin virgins allowed on this trip. Is it Monty? North Skins.
>> No, mate. What?
One sec, bro.
>> No. No. Go on. Go on. Shake your hand.
Bad boy. Bomb. >> Huh?
>> Bad boy. [ __ ] them [ __ ] pop noodles.
>> They're vegan. You know that, right?
>> You're a [ __ ] vegan.
>> They are vegan. Look in the back. They
>> Who's vegan?
>> Look in the back. They're vegan. >> Who?
>> They're pot noodles.
>> Oh, they
>> Yeah, they're vegan. Look. Look it up. It's madness.
They're [ __ ] vegan, bro.
Yeah. Yeah, me and Monty's meeting
today. Seaside Mark for a little session, aren't we? >> Little
>> Yeah, that's that's pretty greasy. I
believe that. I quite believe that, son. >> Yeah. [Laughter]
Oh, this is going to be a lovely site
today, Bezy. I've been looking forward
to this. Obviously, I need to bring my
football bet with me in case it wins,
which, let's face it, this this will
just be perfect today if this football bet wins.
Yeah. Me and Monty, man. We're going for some drinks.
By some, I mean a lot.
We're going to have like a blackout
session. Isn't that right, Monty?
Yeah, I was going to invite Virgin Boy,
but no skimp flints allowed. Sorry, mate.
I mean, yeah, I might I might need to
win this [ __ ] triple bet and stuff.
Well, not YouTube, but I'd like to win
this triple bit, but never be a [ __ ]
skin flint that [ __ ] virgin. You know
what I mean? Got to be put my nice Dior
after shave on.
Yeah, nice after shave on e put some
the colors don't look too rusty as nope
a little bit right
Monty, you won't know what's hit you,
son. Honestly, you won't know what's hit you.
You really won't.
Virgin boy should come, but he ain't got
the money. He's skinned. He's skinn.
That's what he is.
He's skint [ __ ] skin
up. And my I'll be bringing the cap for
you as well, boss. Obviously, you wanted
a little cap, didn't you? Well, bless
you then. If you want a little cap, God bless you.
Yeah, obviously money man wants a little
as well. So, yeah, get you a little cap.
It's all right. Yeah, be right. I look
[ __ ] sexy, bro. I'd be looking the [ __ ] bollocks.
Be [ __ ] looking better than that
[ __ ] virgin, Mark. Better than thating virgin.
I'll be looking better than that [ __ ]
pent virgin, mate.
Better than that pent virgin.
Skinner than a [ __ ] skin. There he is.
than the freaking skin fl
than literally a [ __ ] skin flint
then then what you thinking skin fl
because sometimes your dad let Let's you
suck his dick for a bit of bum change,
mate. Don't mean you ain't got anything, son. Nah.
Oh, Grey just loves them sayings, don't you, Grezy?
Don't you, Greavves?
Bless you. Bless you in life, Grezy.
Yeah, well, I need to leave soon, bro.
Want to be in time for this football as
well. You see? Yeah. I want to be in
time for the good old football.
Have to be good old football maybe. Going
to put the after shave on last. I think Greley
okay with you boss.
Yeah, I'm going to put the after shave
on last time. It's qu socks man.
I have to pop the thingy and get some new socks. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
Fortunately, I do
cuz some of us actually have hair.
Unlike people in this community, some of
us actually have [ __ ] hair, son.
Some of Some of us actually have [ __ ]
hair. You know what I mean, bro? [ __ ]
I don't think I've ever done Birmingham
on a Saturday, you know? money.
Imagine the trains pack up.
Imagine the trains up. We'd be
bringing it back to the good old time day.
Good old times. old times.
Wendy's fresh trainers as well.
You never ever want to end up whatever
you do, son. You know,
never want to end up like that [ __ ] skin virgin.
They're towing on this all the time.
You never never want to end up like that virgin.
You love you take the piss out of it.
I don't think it's anything to really
take the piss out of, mate. Then I got
that little skin flin from Kent.
A little skin.
That old skin.
That old skin boy. Ain't going
nothing at all.
Where's my football bat? Here's my
football bat. Oh, I'm actually ready for
this. It's been a long time coming for this.
They will call him out tomorrow. We talk about
Yeah, I was not expecting that.
>> Yo, Monty. >> Yeah.
>> Can you hear me? >> Yeah. >> Yo.
>> Yo, can you hear me? Yeah.
>> I just had the shower. I'm ready, bro.
>> Yeah, man. Yeah, man. I'm [ __ ] I'm
going to leave you to get laid down. I
I'm not doing it. I'll come home. But
>> Monty, come on.
>> Come on.
>> No, I'm not going to do it to Natalie,
mate. I'm not gonna shag anyone behind.
Well, after this break with Natalie
>> anymore, Monty.
>> Yeah, I know I'm not in a relationship,
but you're still respecting Natalie in it.
>> No, because you're not in a relationship.
>> Yeah, I know I'm not in a relationship,
but you're still showing Natalie
that I'm still looking.
>> You know what I'm saying?
I [ __ ] appreciate it, man.
So, I can't [ __ ] do anything honor
again. I'm just thinking then cuz if I
do do go out and shag, I'm coming out.
But if I go out,
>> you don't believe I'm ready, Monty. I'm
ready. You don't believe me, do you?
>> I am ready. I'm ready as well.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I'm just going to let my
phone charge a little bit more and I'm
going to go get my haircut and I'll be
on my way.
>> No, I can book it in.
>> I'll tell you where I am as well. Yeah.
>> Yeah, I'll tell you where I am.
>> See, I'm ready, too.
>> I'm ready, bro.
>> Yeah, look, I'm ready.
We can do it till uh
>> I'm ready, too, buddy. get my haircut
and then I'm coming.
I've got your little cap as well.
I got your little cap.
>> Got a little cap. Have you? >> Yep.
>> Yo, people, what shall I do? Tell me
what what what shall I do? Shall I go
out and get laid?
>> Yeah, go.
>> Or should I have or should have proper
respect for Natalie and not do [ __ ]
Go out, get laid. If she had respect for
you, she'd be replying.
>> But she's not replying. She's being a man. >> True.
>> So, mate, if she she knows how much
you're hurting and she has no respect,
>> so [ __ ] her, man. That's what I'd say. I
say [ __ ] a lot of it.
>> No, no, you're right there, PJ. You're
right, actually, buddy. You're actually
right. If she doesn't respect me when I'm hurting,
>> one sec. Let me just brush my teeth.
Yeah. Two seconds.
>> No, go on. That's what I need to do actually.
Yeah, I need to go brush my teeth actually.
Good job, Batman.
Just in case I'm chat, just in case you
think that chat [ __ ] like don't brush my
teeth. There you go, peeps. I brush my
teeth. I'll be right back, PJ.
your peace. What do you have?
Yo, be peeps. What do you reckon I
should do? Have respect for Natalie.
Complete respect like I do.
>> Oh, [ __ ] I don't know what to do.
>> Yeah, sorry about that. I was just my teeth, mate.
>> No, no, you're right. I have I do have a
lot of respect for Natalie, mate. I'm
not going to do it. I'll come with you.
Listen, she knows she knows how you're
feeling and she doesn't give a [ __ ] You
understand? And I'm not I'm not even drunk. Of
>> course, but I'm not a man to [ __ ]
around. You know what I mean? They have
respect for like even if they don't have
respect for me.
>> I haven't even started drinking yet and
I'm a mad bastard.
>> I'm a mad [ __ ] Yeah, man.
>> Well, we're gonna get him some Yeah.
Listen, you're saying this now? Yeah.
But when we get on the [ __ ] baby
Guinness shots later. Yeah. You're not
going to be saying that, son.
>> But listen, Monty. Yeah. We're not going
to do this Timmy [ __ ] and that when
we're out drinking. We'll do it before
or after if you really want to. We're
not doing it whilst we're enjoying
ourselves, you know, cuz you know what
they do. [ __ ] them, bro. We'll do it after.
I'll even say Sunday in it. I'll even
stay over Sunday, bro. We can sort them
out on Sunday or late or whatever. You
know, doesn't need to be [ __ ]
>> You get me, bro. Ain't it? >> Yeah.
>> Going to charge my phone up a little
bit. Going to charge my phone up a
little bit and then like I said, um get
my haircut and then be on my way, bro.
But the old football that's PG. That's
fine. I going to set off now in a minute
myself. It's going to take me an hour to
get there, actually.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Just just stay around like
the city center, is it?
>> Yeah, that's what I'm going to do.
>> Did you Did you put your after shave on yet?
>> No, I'm going to be doing that in a minute.
>> Yeah, I'm going to do in a bit as well.
Yeah, brand new after get a jumper on stick on.
You know where all the drinking places
are, is it?
>> I've never been to Birmingham. I never
been to out like place.
If I got to pay in clubs, I'm not paying
in no [ __ ] clubs. You can [ __ ] off.
>> I don't think you have to in Birmingham.
>> No, I'm going to say I'm not paying into
clubs. I'm a [ __ ]
>> No, even if it doesn't win and we're
still going out. Even if the bet don't
win, we're still going out. I've still
got money. All right. But it should win.
Yeah. Hopefully it does win. [ __ ] bet wins. >> What?
>> Oh, I just done an 80 pound football bet
the other day. Hopefully it wins.
You get me in it.
One sec, bro. Ah,
one second. Yeah, my phone's on 63%. I
need to charge. Well, I'm I'm going to
go go off live. Yeah. And I'm going to
charge my phone cuz it's going to charge
slow and I'll let you know when I'm on
my way in it.
>> No, no. Yeah, go to the edge. Yeah, I'm
>> coming. I'm definitely coming, bro. I'm
dressed and everything. So, I'm I'm coming. So,
>> yeah. Yeah, that's fine. in a bit. Yeah,
I messed up.