Should we join? Let him join.
>> Let him join. Let him [ __ ] join. >> Join
join. Come on.
>> Join. Well, [ __ ] him. All right. Yeah.
>> Body man's a legend. That's my boy, bro.
Me and you go way back. Let me go way
>> Way back.
>> You go way back, bro. [Applause]
up to you.
>> Yeah. Baby,
>> we're [ __ ] steaming, aren't we? We're
[ __ ] We're [ __ ]
>> Yeah, son. We almost done, didn't we?
They're [ __ ] I told him
offered me outside. I told him, "Let's
go for it. Let's go for it." I told him, "A [ __ ] off."
So, Timmy, let's go for it. Timmy. Timmy
Aldridge. You know where I am.
>> I'm in town. me. I'm in South [Applause]
Crime, you [ __ ] I'm in your city. >> Prime,
>> you know, move me. [ __ ] move me.
>> I'm in your city.
>> Yeah. Yeah. >> Prime.
>> It's a prime. Yes.
>> Yeah. No, I'm calling the prime. [ __ ]
come and move me, you silly [ __ ] Come
and [ __ ] move me. I'm in your city,
[ __ ] picking your bird.
>> How many numbers did I get? 10. Look,
>> he got loads of numbers, but we've been
ting videos to come. Videos to come,
bro. Naturally, I [ __ ] love you now. [ __ ] it.
>> All right, Timmy, you [ __ ] Oh [ __ ] Timmy.
>> Come on, you [ __ ] And you,
Prime. Come on.
>> Come on, Prime.
>> Come on, Prime. [ __ ] prime.
>> I'm in your shitty and I ain't [ __ ]
moving. I love it.
Too hard. Here we go. Hey, Timmy.
Timmy, I'm going to put it.
>> Come on, son. Come on, bro. Come on, Timmy. [Applause]
>> Yeah, I know. I saw you there. fantasy.
>> This reminds me of Py [Music]
I just want you to
There's a bird there. I can't >> [ __ ]
>> Go on, mate. Go on. Stop that. Go on.
What you got to lose? Nothing. You got
nothing to lose. Baby up. Baby, baby,
>> please try to get me with other women. I love that.
>> I love [ __ ] that girl in America.
>> I love that.
>> We love We both in love. We're both in
love. We're both in love.
>> Both in love.
>> We're both in love. Yeah.
Me and him is both in love.
Both in love. [Music]
I love you.
>> I love you, too.
You too, buddy. Just do it. Give me a
roll. Give me a roll. Give me a roll.
No. No. Give me a buck. I can't.
You know what that in your messages?
>> It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter. It
doesn't text me. I love Yeah.
I love it. I love you.
We're open up.
We're open up. We're open up. Hey, I
showed money the message earlier. Yeah,
I'll send you a message.
Don't drop it, please.
>> Yo, Natalie, I [ __ ] love you. Yeah, I
going got late tonight, but I said [ __ ] off.
>> Listen, daddy, come here. [Music] Yeah, bro.
>> Yeah, boy.
Yeah. Birmingham. Where's Birmingham, buddy? >> Birmingham.
>> Let's do a little cover shot.
>> Cover. Yeah. Yes, Natalie, I love you, Natalie.
>> I love you.
>> You know you are. I love you. Yes.
>> I want a football today. Yep. [Applause]
>> Come on, where are you?
>> Where are you? [ __ ]
>> Come on, I love you.
>> Come on. Come on. Price, come on.
Brian, come on. You [ __ ] Come
on. Your city. Come on. Move me. Move
me. [ __ ] move me. I can't. >> Y [Music]
Let me hold it. Hold it. You hold it.
It's coming back. He ain't going to come
out. He'll get [ __ ] up. [Music] >> Yeah. Please note. All right. Come on. Hello. 2 Go.
Come on, [ __ ] Come on.
I think they're coming in. Go on.
Come on, buddy.
I'm recording, man. I'm reporting, man.
I'm in. I got two numbers. I'm in. I got
>> I got two numbers and I won the football
bet as well.
Come on, [ __ ] Come on.
>> I'm in your city. Move me. Move me, you
dirty. Move me. Come on.
You're going to put me north. You're
going to [ __ ] fall, you [ __ ]
Come on then. Come on, big man.
And this time I'm acting in your seat.
I'm in your seat this time, big man.
Come on. Move me. You come on. I'm in your se
no one. You little [ __ ] [ __ ] You
[ __ ] [ __ ] You ain't moving no one.
You're going to move me. I'm in your city. Anyway,
I got two numbers so far
in I want a simple bet today. 80 return 285 return 285. I'm Steven.
Get up there. Listen
and I love Morgan. How about that?
Come to me that
why don't you ride that right now
I'm not going to go.
What is my voice?
I got two
of my brother number.
>> Did you get her number? I need your number.
I just got beyond this one. What?
That's why he [Music] I want my Tiger tiger tiger. Tiger,
>> I'll give you your [ __ ] blood. No. stop. [Laughter]
They come from you people.
You people don't me good now. [Applause]
It's coming in. [ __ ] [ __ ] weakling
weak [ __ ] bastard
Are you going to Are you going to down
with your eyes today? Come on. Come on.
Come on. Shake it. Come on.
I want to know why you do the last you [ __ ]
Are you going to come in? How much is [Laughter] there? Hold
on. Hold on, [ __ ]
Come on, [ __ ] Come on. Come on
boy. Come on. Come on Timmy. Come on
Timmy. Come on [ __ ] Come on.
Come on you [ __ ] Come on. Come turn from China.
All of you who live in B Darling,
I [ __ ] love you, darling.
Come on, Timmy.
Come on. I tell you where we at. I will
tell you where we are.
>> I will step you where we are.
>> Come on, Jimmy.
You step you today. Let's
go for it. Let's [ __ ] go for it.
Let's go for it. Get arrested. prison me, darling. What happened?
Come. Come on. All right. Right.
Let me tell you something funny.
Do it. Do it. Do it. Do it. Do it. I
thought you were cool. You got to do it now. Stop it.
>> Don't worry about my life. Listen, I was
a fun hearing about this [ __ ] Oh, is
going to meet people. Oh no. Come on.
You said you will meet. are.
Where are they? Where are they?
No, no, no.
They know about [Applause] it.
They know about why they don't. Come on.
You want to go? They're all [ __ ] cry. Come on.
Timmy, come on.
Come on, Timmy.
Come on. Come on. Come on. We're in
their city and they're not coming out
here. Come out.
>> Come on. They're never coming out. [ __ ] here.
>> They're not coming out. coming down. You don't need the end.
This is funny.
They're not coming. They never coming.