[Music]
You're [ __ ] Peter Griffin going on it
and that, bro. Getting on it.
Sheesh. Yeah, that
Yeah, man. Sleep. Well, we got Peter
Griffin still obsessed mentioning me.
Oh, man. These people's Peter Belly's
addiction is is too much. You know, I
was going to reply to that 9m minutee
video, but I thought, what's what's the [ __ ]
point? What's the point? Uh, it was
funny though. The the first bit of it
was funny. Stop before I go and um give
the before I go and thump that big nose.
Yeah. Just like you done it the last
three times when I went to your area and
I had you running to the police in it.
Yeah. You really thumped my eye cro big
nose then virgin boy when you uh went
running to the police uh claiming how
you're not a fighter and using your
disability as an excuse. Yeah. You
really fought me that time too, didn't you,
buddy? Yeah. Didn't you?
Um, but yeah, you're you're so weird,
man. Like, the only one with erectile
dysfunction is yourself. That's why
you're still a virgin. Nobody cares that
you've been in a relationship with a
[ __ ] for 3 years when her her her
needs remain unfulfilled. Like, literally, bro,
nobody actually cares, lad.
Yeah, that's true. Let's see.
[ __ ] just woke up,
man. Oh, you never guess what I sent that Muslim
woman. I sent a bacon and cheese wrap.
Yeah, I don't think she uh she approved
of that very well, but
Yeah. Yeah, the bacon and cheese
wrap. I'm so
cheeky. I'm [ __ ] cheeky,
though. I'm cheeky. I said bacon and cheese
rap. Who's that? What's me
think? Yeah, I said that bacon and
cheese. Yeah. How's that one for the
alcohol? They're [ __ ] lost, bro.
our numbers up to be fair. Almost back at 100,
sir. Ain't bad, is it?
Yeah, I'm [ __ ]
man. See, it's so tempting to go out
today and send it. That's what happens,
bro. This is This is where it becomes [ __ ] dangerous.
like you know when money is no object e
and you have all the time in the world
but now I'm taking a month off. Well
yeah I need my passport anyways but I
mean I still could have went to a few
places. They should get that passport
tomorrow. I should get it hopefully by
Friday but hopefully I don't get for a
while be wasting money in this country.
Yeah, I fell asleep. I was [ __ ] I
just had some bacon and cheese wrapped.
Was it just knocked me out, bro?
defeated. I just get life, lad. Any
luck? No, not really,
bro. A football bet let me down. One
team let me down yesterday for
£153 on the 90th minute. It was the 90th
minute. It is harder to win. There's no
money in the industry. I don't play the
machines anymore, man. I just I just
thought I'd give that machine a go like
for the month, but I'm not serious on
them machines, bro. It is hard to win
because there's no money in the industry
anymore like they used to be. So, that's
why it's a waste of time doing it.
Obviously, Saturday I just do a football
bet. So, yeah.
Yeah, lad. Yeah, it was easy, bro. It
was easy. Like the landbased casinos,
the betting shops. Online is hard to
win, bro. See, bro, you go online is the
hardest to win. See, back in the day,
online used to be easy in the actual
landbased. Now, you can't even win on
any of them. You might as well just stop
gambling, bro. You know, I'm I'm not
wasting my money on it anymore. You
know, I I was a [ __ ] for months, bro.
Like, I'm not doing it no more. I
learned that machine yesterday. Saw me
the other day to prove a point. Dude,
put some content on my channel. [ __ ]
280 down. Done. Cool. Whatever. No one
cares. I'm done
now. You know, so I won't be drinking
for a month either. See, Mark, I tell
you another thing that's very hard now,
Mark, is trying to pull. Trying to pull
[ __ ] women is [ __ ] hard. That
never also used to be hard. But as they
say, you know, all good things must come to an
end. And to be fair, I'm a believer in
that. So all good things come to an
end. You can't really pull
women. Like I went out, Mark, on
Saturday. I must have spent I got my
passport renewed. Got my head. I
probably spent about £500.
Yeah, I spent about 500 quid. That's
London prices for you, bro. Ain't it?
It's like, what am I supposed to do? Go
out every week spending £300 in hopes
I'm going to meet someone? I'm not doing
it, bro. It's [ __ ] up. It is [ __ ] up,
lad. You know what I'm saying? I'll show
you my face,
bro. You want to see
it? I got my hair done as well. It was
actually quite sick.
Yeah, my hair, bro. Sick. Sort of a bit
hung over there though from the drinking
and that, but
yeah, I look I got my hair done, too,
bro. It's a sick fade
day. But yeah, that's how it goes,
lad. So, I'm taking a break for a month,
so it'll be hard, but it be worth
it. Why does the film come out on the 7th? Yeah.
H just it's just just sucks, bro. This country just sucks.
Uh but obviously I went out just before
my passport expired, so I thought
[ __ ] let me go out and give it one
hurdan. To be fair, we did get four
numbers. See, this is how it works in
this country, Mark. Yeah. you need to go
out and then you need to you need to do
these approaches and then you need to
get these numbers and you need to get
these numbers that reply to you and then
actually beat you which even seems to be
getting harder, you know, even though
we've done it before. So, it's very it's
very hard, bro. This this country is
[ __ ] for everything. Weather gambling,
[ __ ] stuck up [ __ ] I don't know
if like the women where you are are, but
they're stuck up as [ __ ]
here. They're all It doesn't matter. I
feel like it doesn't matter where in
England you go, it's like a foby.
They've all got the same attitude. You
see the same men, the same attitude, the
same ridiculously insane standards. And
I feel like it doesn't matter where you go,
bro. You know what I'm saying? If that
makes sense. Hopefully, it does. So, I'm
getting my passport. Um, my passport's
on its way. So, just got to leave this
country again. So, yeah, man. But
yeah, there's no money in the industry. Believe
that. I woke up depressed [ __ ]
uh yesterday, bro. It's [ __ ] cuz
they're drinking it. It's crazy, bro.
Yeah. Come on. It is what it is,
eh? Yeah, social media [ __ ] it up.
Social media and simps [ __ ] it up.
Like I got this woman last week from
Scotland. I was kissing her and that,
but it's like in terms of anything
longterm, it just seems
impossible cuz it's like you get I got
four numbers, Mark. Yeah, they replied.
Uh, how many of them replied? I think
three of them replied, one blocked me,
and the other the others just didn't
they didn't reply after.
So, they replied, but then they stopped.
Or yeah, free reply. I got a bartender's
number, but it doesn't really matter
because it's just the same as online.
They always go quiet in the end, so it
doesn't really matter.
But they just go quiet in the end. But,
I mean, at least I went out and got the
numbers in it. So,
I went I went up to this woman right
last uh it was when I went out on Friday
and we was talking. I think she said she
was from Switzerland and she was living
here. No word of a lie. I was like oh we
should do something one time. She said
I'm sorry I only love black guys. I was like
wow [ __ ] hell, bro. That's
racist. But they call us racist. I was
like what? I initially looked at my
friend. Yeah. I was like, "Bro, I mean, you
know, you're sorry about my dad." Oh,
Mark. Okay. Yeah. My dad died when I was
[ __ ] 11, man. I thought you was
talking to me. Yeah. Apparently, your
dad died, Mark.
Bro, it happens, man. People die in
life. My dad died when I was 11, you
know? Um, not that like I really like At
least you actually got time to spend
with your dad. Not that I really cared.
I didn't. But I mean, I guess it's nice
for you that you did, you
know? So, at least you had a dad um
to see you grow up and [ __ ] You know
what I'm saying? Whereas mine died when
I was like
11. It's so mad though cuz if my dad was
still alive, I don't look nothing like
my [ __ ] dad. So, I did used to think,
"Oh, it be I wonder what would it look
like him seeing you grow up instead of
just your mom, you know? Now I've only
got my mom now and she's
64 and I don't want her to die because I
know people die in their 60s, but that's
basically the Well, obviously cuz my
dad's dead. So, yeah. Yeah. It's all
right, bro. It was when I was a
kid. But I'm just saying like I always
sometimes I do think oh what would have
actually been like him seeing you actually grow
up is what it is bro people dying it.
So yeah knew she was a [ __ ] knew he
was pretty much an old man when he died.
[ __ ] Mark you know. Is your mom still
alive? Mark is your is your mom still alive buddy?
Yeah. Yeah. See you. Well, I don't think
my mom's going to still be alive when I'm your
age. So, your mom must have had you when
she was young, huh? My mom had me when 37. So,
yeah. You have another I don't really
have anything to do with my sister's I
don't know I speak to one sister but the
other one I don't speak to. Not because
like we hate each other I just don't.
The only person I speak to is my mom and
my sister. One of them but not like that.
Yeah cuz I saw it as
like Yeah. I just don't man. But that's
who I really speak to my mom to be fair. But
Oh, where's that mole come from? I had
before. But yeah, you should come to
London sometime, Mark. Bro, we'll do
some uh we'll do some approaches. We'll get some
[ __ ] Hopefully, you find a woman to
settle down with in this day and age. I
don't think so,
buddy. I don't think so in this day and
age, buddy. Not in this country anyways,
or Scotland or Wales. I don't think so,
buddy. I don't think it's possible. Not in your
20s. Because the reason it's not
possible, Mark, is because you go on
these dating apps, they don't work for
obvious reasons. You go out and you try
to start a conversation with someone,
they pretend they got boyfriends or they
give you their number, they play games.
It doesn't matter. Like, what whatever
it is they do. Like, bro, I went out
yesterday. I went out on Friday and I
can't tell you the amount of makebelieve
boyfriends that I heard. [ __ ] I lost
count, bro. But I was drunk as well. So
yeah, it was I definitely heard
that. Definitely definitely heard that.
And that's all you get when you go out
in England, bro. It's actually boring as
[ __ ] But like I said, the passport was
just about to expire, so I thought, [ __ ]
it. Yeah, if you go to Thailand, you're
not going to get anything in this
country, mate. As in me, not you. You're
older. You might, but I'm saying me. The
situation I'm in at my age is very
unlikely, bro. Very. It's impossible.
I'd even go as far as saying it's
impossible because look, take take
yesterday. Take Friday for an example.
I'm decent looking. Yeah. I smelt good.
I dress good. I went out. I sent it.
Didn't get [ __ ] all. I got numbers.
Yeah. But they didn't go anywhere. They
all go quiet when it's to do with
meeting. So, I mean, that's an example
of what what you're dealing
with. And you'll keep dealing with it
unless you get out of this world lucky.
any Yeah. Like that's all that's ever
going to happen,
bro. Like you've got more chance of
winning the lottery than than finding
someone in this country at my age in my
circumstances. That's that's how it is.
Um but that's it. I mean, Ant-Man's in
Thailand now. Ces Mark, you remember
Ant-Man? He tells you um you know you
know you know
Thailand. So he he's been to Thailand
three times this year. Three times this
year he's been to
Thailand. So people Yeah. If you go
Thailand, you're laughing, man. But in
10 years that's going to turn westernized as
well. Oh, we just said that if you want
to get a woman, it's basically
impossible in this country.
But anything else there's there there's
things you can do. So
yeah, but yeah. Funny how you know about
Thailand, is it Mark? Hey
buddy, you know about Thailand, don't
you? Nice, man. Nice.
I thought I looked good as well, but I
still heard about Makebelie Boyfriends. No,
no, I got four numbers, but they just
Yeah, two of them replied. No, three of
them replied and then one of them blocked
me. Um, and then they just went quiet.
The other ones did block me. That's all
that will happen is even if you get a
number, you'll be, "Oh, hi, nice to meet
you, Tet." And they'll reply back
sometime. on a lot of them reply back
and then when it's zoom actually meeting
they go away so it's like it's the same
old in this country bro it is honestly
the same old it will never change it's
not changing all these years but yeah a
lot of them said they had boyfriends
they definitely definitely definitely
did and they've got attitude problems as
well even it wasn't ever no they did
block me only one of them block me there
was this bartender the bartender
replied and she was like um no the
bartender replied and she was like um I
said oh how was it get busy? She said,
"Oh, yeah. It was hella busy." No, no,
no. I said, "Oh, do you prefer it like
that?" I just went to meet a friend and
that and I said, "Oh, let's do something
today, which is tomorrow, which is
today. Let's get a roast dinner and go
for a few drinks." Never heard from her
again. So, why give your number to reply
to then lose interest? It doesn't make
sense. The only one that still replies
to me is this Muslim woman. I sent her
my bacon and cheese wrap this morning.
The Indian guy, he didn't unfollow me.
And that guy that met me, he wasn't even
from Instagram. So that's
impossible. That's impossible. D
lad. That's impossible cuz he's not even
from Instagram. He's from Snapchat. So I
I don't know how you work that one out.
That guy weren't even from
Instagram. So that chance would be a [ __ ] fine
thing. Yeah, I need to make a new
Instagram anyways because of these
stalkers. But that guy was not from
Instagram. Someone might have unfollowed
me, but it wasn't him. I don't have him
on Instagram. Yeah, someone unfollow I
know who unfollowed me. Some Turkish guy.
Yeah, these people stalk my Instagram.
They're so [ __ ] weird. That's why I
don't have no woman on [ __ ] Insta or
nothing. And there was this woman that
said, "Oh, I'll message you later." And
then she just blocked me. So it's like,
"What do I have to do? Go out every week spending
£300. Two300 pound. I'm not [ __ ] I'm
not doing that,
bro." Cuz you look I don't [ __ ] know
why I'm following me. I don't care. But
one day you'll look back, lad, and
you'll be like, "Oh, I wish I wish I left the
country." Because that's what will
happen if you go out every week and you
try in this country, lad.
Yeah. Yeah. But they got the wrong
person because I don't add anyone on
Instagram. I don't add anyone on
Instagram. My Instagram just sits there,
lad. Uh, go self-reflect on another
channel. Don't do on my channel. Thank
you. You ask yourself this question. Why
are you a fat little waster on benefits
that can't get a
life? Is that his name? Ask yourself
that question. Why are you a sad fat
little bastard projecting your life onto me? You
know, [ __ ] me,
bro. Never meet anyone with [ __ ]
autism. But yeah, that's the way it basically
works. And it's not cheap to go out in
London as well.
So, it's not cheap, mate. It's not
cheap. I reckon if you went out every
week in London, you would just about run
out of money, bro. That's how expensive it
is. It's a madness,
man. But yeah, you don't want to spend
money every week. And like I said, I
used to do it. I used to do it every two
weeks. I used to go out every two
weeks. Yeah. I had lush um bacon and
cheese wrap from Greg's this morning. Oh
mate, it sent me to sleep. [ __ ] sexy
it was, man. You can't beat a nice bacon
and cheese wrap. I insist, bro. Oh, if
you ever go to Greg's Yeah, get a bacon
and cheese wrap. They're better than any
steak pie, any sausage roll. I'm telling
you. How you doing, ghosting man? The
reason I was pissed off yesterday, I
tell you why I was pissed off. I tell
you why I was pissed off yesterday about
the football, bro. It's because I had a
[ __ ] [ __ ] Saturday. I mean, yeah, it
was good. Yeah, okay. I went out with
this this associate and that and I got
some numbers, but then you deal with the
numbers that don't go anywhere. And then
[ __ ] I've spent loads of money. I
could have won. I could have done with
£150. Not that I needed £150, but I
could have done with it. You don't understand? Yeah.
And it's a mixture of most things, bro.
You know, I was so close to winning and
it's not nothing to do with 20 pound.
Um, yeah, some replied, the bartender
replied, when I asked her out, she
stopped replying. Some Italian one
replied, then she stopped replying, and
then another one replied, and then she blocked
me. So, I got I got three replies out of
one. Three replies out of four. But then
when I said, "Oh, let's do something
tomorrow. Let's get a roast dinner and
that. They block um they just ignored
me. They didn't block me. One block only
one blocked me, but the others they just
went they just went quiet.
Yeah. So, I got three replies out of
four. Um which is good. The last one
didn't reply, which is the one I liked.
But yeah, that's what happens. Ghosting.
It's like every every week, this is how
England works. Yeah.
Um, you go
out, it's impossible in in the West,
bro. It's you, it's like you're going
out every week with a 5% bit of hope.
That's what you're doing. You're going
out, you're getting numbers, and then
the numbers don't get anywhere
or you know, and then what and and I was
saying, Ghost, it's like, bro, what do
you do? Are you supposed to do this
every week? I don't have a passport now
because I'm waiting for them to send me
a renewed one. What am I What are you
supposed to do every single week? Bro,
most people can't afford that. I mean, I
I can afford it, but it doesn't matter,
bro. Most people can't, and most people
don't have the time. Is that Is that
really what you have to do? Go out every
week? And not to mention how alcohol
gives you depression
after, you know, and this is what I
don't understand. Like, a lot of these
Muslim people, they say pork is bad.
Pork is bad. Not as bad as alcohol,
mate. Yeah. You don't understand that
when you drink, I was depressed
yesterday from the drinking, you know,
and I had a tiny bit of anxiety, but it
was mainly depression. That is from the
drinking, you know, and then you're
[ __ ] for like two, three days. Do they
not understand that that is worse than
eating pork? It kills people, you know.
Have you Have you ever heard people Have
you ever heard somebody die from eating pork? Nah.
Nah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, we've heard it
all before about the big nose. Stop
repeating yourself. It's
boring. Come up with something unique
and original. But yeah, you get what I'm
saying, is it? Ghosting.
Like it's um I went out on Friday. I
didn't go out on Saturday, but I went
out on Friday. But
yeah. Yeah, it's too it's too hard, bro.
It's like wherever you go like
everyone's just got the same attitude
and you know I spent £500 on Friday
bro haircut [ __ ] drinking [ __ ]
£500. Where the [ __ ] did that go
bro? Yeah, but it should be easy
ghosting. Yeah, cuz no homo. Yeah, bro.
I'm I'm decent looking. I look normal,
bro. And it's like you should just be
able to go out and just get someone. You
should be able to just go out and be
like get someone. It should literally be
as easy as that or not as hard as this.
But he like, bro, that's why like you
you think that I take the piss when I
say this stuff. I'm not taking a piss,
though. I might as well have been born
looking like Timmy
Eldridge. I might as well look like
[ __ ] Timmy Eldridge. If you think
about it, I might as well been born like
him cuz you don't get anything anyway.
So, I mean, [ __ ] You might as well been
born a Timmy
Eldridge. And it's not about I've about
at least I tried. I've been trying, bro.
trying. I've been trying, lad. But yeah,
I got this. Um, but yeah, it's just like
you get the numbers and they just go
south. And I was thinking, why don't you
try and not get the numbers and pursuing
them on the spot? That's not going to
work because obviously they travel in
groups. Tim gets women. Tim's still a
virgin just like nods. still a virgin. The Virgin
Marys. Yeah, I was going to reply to
that 9minute video nons leg. I can't
even be bothered, mate. I can't even be
bothered wasting my time on this [ __ ]
virgin. But yeah, it's not at least I
tried, bro. Man's been
trying been trying. He led [Music] Yeah. Yeah,
man. So many of them got boyfriends
ghosting, bro. I don't know if you ever
go clubbing, but I didn't know you find
so many single pe uh so many people in
relationships in bars and
clubs. I was thinking of going to
Glasgow, but bro, what's the actual
point? Like I mean like
like that's cuz I I have a few Scottish
friends in that in it
but they're class and that but it's I
was speaking to this guy in Scotland so
I know I'm coming up soon again but it's
like bro like any other any other city.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Women just reject me
but I've been seen with more women than
you've ever had. Yeah. Congratulations
buddy. Yeah. Instantly reject me.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Yeah, my nose is really big in
it. But you get what I mean, ain't
it? But why should I have to go back to
[ __ ] Scotland, bro? Come
on. Why should I have to go back to [ __ ] Scotland,
lad? It's [ __ ] far away, man.
You should be able to get something in
London. But anyways, I didn't think you
would see so many people in
relationships in bars and clubs
ghosting. It's crazy, man. They all have boyfriends, isn't
it? I think that's just a western [ __ ]
thing that they say in it. That's just a
That's just a [ __ ] thing westernized
women say, huh?
I think that's just a thing they
say. I don't think it I don't think it
matters where you are, bro. I just think
they're just the same everywhere cuz
I've already been to Scotland. I've been
to Glasgow, but I've been to Edin, bro.
And to be honest, it gave London
vibes, mate. It doesn't matter where you
try. I don't know about Glasgow, but I'm
not going to comment on that. Yeah, that
would be the last result. Swindon, ex
bro, it's the same thing. Wales, they're
westernized countries. It doesn't matter
where where it is you
go. The women are suddenly not going to
have different attitudes because you're in another
location. But Edinburgh, I still don't
have a bad thing to say about Edinburgh
because of how cheap it was. It was
cheap and but it gave London vibes in
terms of it was very
touristy and it seemed very well built
on money like London. It gave London
vibes. It did give London
vibes. So you want me to go all the way
to Glasgow just to try and [ __ ] pull? But
yeah, I mean this woman I kissed last
week, she was from Edinburgh. He was
Scottish and there was one from Glasgow
before as well in a club. I you know it just
depends. Don't think you have many
Scottish that say they've got boyfriends
in it. London America [ __ ] England.
America, bro. Straight away I've got a
boyfriend. That's just England for you.
That's what they say. They have
boyfriends. I only went out to have fun
on Friday, lad. I only went out to have
fun, but hearing it was annoying.
Hearing it was was annoying,
bro. It was annoying,
lad. Yep. Not the women. Okay, go away,
white knight. Okay, go away, simp. But
that and and that's and you know these
people that say that ghosting that
you're the problem and you're not women.
These people are simps that don't go out
and speak to women because if you
actually went out and speak to women,
you would know what it's actually like.
No. Ghosting. What it is is these women,
I'm sick of repeating this. They have
got unrealistic standards. Not high
standards because everyone should have
high standards. They have unrealistic
standards due to social media and due to
simps, right? Complimenting them every
single day, right? And that gives them
an ego that they're much better than
they actually are. That's where the
attitude comes from. It's not you. It's
not me. You've seen approaches. Okay.
Okay. For people that always say that, I
say to them, okay, I'm the problem ret.
But tell me what I'm doing wrong and
what I'm saying
wrong. And and they can't. And that's
how you know that you're right. Because
I you I'm sure you've seen my
approaching videos, right? And to me,
they seem fairly normal in terms of
conversation, right? And what happens
when you go out and you try to speak to
people within five 10 seconds they say
they've got boyfriends. So what could
have you possibly done different where
they like the problem with this society
Yeah. is they love blaming men. Doesn't
matter who you are. They will always
blame men. They will never ever hold
women accountable for anything. You
know, even though the proof is in the
pudding that like if you go on a dating
app as a woman, you get 5,000 likes. If
you go as a guy, you're not getting
nowhere near 5,000 likes. This society
loves blaming men, even though there
statistics that are proven that the
dating game is rigged against
men. So, no, they it's because they're
westernized and they think they're much
better than they actually
are. You know, especially in London.
I've not been out of London for a while.
I've not spoke to people in London, out
of London for a while. That's what
London is about. They have got inflated
egos. Everybody knows this, especially in [ __ ]
London. They're looking for the perfect
man ghosting that don't exist. They want a perfect
man. You know what I'm saying? They want
a perfect man that don't exist. And they
will look for this perfect man that
don't exist until they're about in their
mid-30s. Then when they're in their
mid-30s, they realize that this perfect
man don't exist. And then that's when
they start lowering their standards and
stop being somewhat of
[ __ ] Cuz have you noticed that in when
people get to their like mid30s, 40s,
they're not as [ __ ] anymore. Have you
noticed that? It's not necessarily about
the location. It's necessarily about the
age of these people. If you've noticed,
people in their 40s and 50s tend to not be
[ __ ] It's London and it's social
media. You know, you can go on about
other men that met somebody through
work. mate, they're not you. Yeah. More
people struggle than don't
struggle. Yeah. And and these people
that um simp over women that say, "Oh,
it's not the women, it's you." These
people probably live in [ __ ] Glasgow
and they don't even leave their house,
mate. So, what the [ __ ] would they know
about London? Everybody knows about London, bro.
Like it's social media and their
standards because if they it's already literally been
proven. Stop being a s, Mike. Stop being
a white knight. We don't have white
knights on this
channel. Calling a woman a [ __ ] You
will not get one. Um I'm not even going
to answer that. That's pathetic. Stop
singing. It will never get you laid.
Stop white nighting. Ghosting knows the
score, isn't it? Because I assume I
assume you've seen my videos. Isn't that right,
Ghosting? You've seen my videos, haven't you,
Ghosting? You've seen my um videos. It's
even somebody on Reddit said to me, some
women said to me like, "Well, you look
normal and your approaches are normal. I
don't know what the problem is. Maybe
too many stuck up [ __ ] in your
country." I think they were right. I
actually think they were right, bro.
like two two years later like they said
I think they lived in America. Yeah.
They were like a single mom. They said
maybe too many stuck up [ __ ] in your
country. I think they were right,
bro. I think they were right, man. Do
you think they were
right? Yeah, bro. You can't call a woman
a [ __ ] but it's okay for a woman to
abuse you. Double standards,
huh? It's okay for women to abuse you
and take the piss out of you. Yeah,
that's completely fine. But you must not
give you must not call women a
[ __ ] You must not call women a [ __ ]
Ghosting. That's the worst thing you can
call a woman. Even though they can take
the piss out of you, give you attitude,
act like their [ __ ] don't stink. You
mustn't call a woman a
[ __ ] Yeah. Double standards.
Mh. That's another thing with this this
society. The double standards ghosting is [ __ ]
disgusting. The double standards is
[ __ ] disgusting, bro.
It's absolutely [ __ ] disgusting, isn't
it? You're doing all
right. Yeah, you're doing all right. Uh,
where do you live
then? See, the maddest thing about this
ghosting is I've technically had more
women than these people, and I still
don't lick their ass. I still don't act
like their [ __ ] don't stink.
Like I even said in a bar, I think it
was about two weeks ago,
lad. Two weeks
ago, you've never encountered these
problems, Sean. You literally have only
dated about two people and they were
both disabled. What do you mean you've
never encountered these problems? You
literally can't get my sloppy seconds
out of your head. Morgan, Izzy, what,
bro? You've more than encountered these
problems. What do you mean you've never
encountered these problems? The only
people that you attract is disabled from
disabled events. I would say you've
definitely had these problems. And you
will do have these problems. You [ __ ]
virgin. You've never encountered these
problems. You've never encountered these
problems. Have you gone out in a normal environment drinking?
No, mate. If if you never encountered
these problems, then you would shut the
[ __ ] up about Izzy and Morgan. But you
won't. That's how you know you've
encountered more than these problems, bro.
Yeah. But yeah, why why do you do that
anyways? Like Mike, whoever the [ __ ] you
are, why do you simp over women? It's
not cool, bro. It doesn't make you look
good. Oh, you can't call women a [ __ ]
Rare. It's so embarrassing, bro. And
this is somebody that's had more women
than you. Believe it or not, say I've
never had a woman, bro. I've had women
on my YouTube. You can see it with your
own eyes. And I don't know why people
just religiously stick up for them. It's so
embarrassing. Like there's there there's
one thing them being in the right, but
like you just said PJ calling women a
[ __ ] Bro, they literally are [ __ ] in
London. I'm I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm
not scared to say what I think. They
literally are [ __ ] Well, I don't
like call I don't I don't like the word
[ __ ] actually, to be honest. I I think
that's like I just prefer to call them
[ __ ] cuz they are [ __ ] They
literally are [ __ ] Do you know how
many times you have to deal with these
people's attitude? They are literally
the definition of a [ __ ] That's
literally what they are. Especially in
London. Especially in
London, you know. They literally are
[ __ ] and they're racist as well. So
yeah, stop being a white night, lad. It
will never get you laid. Take it from
Peter Belly. It's embarrassing.
If I'm being a [ __ ] I want somebody to
tell me I'm being a [ __ ] If a woman's
being a [ __ ] I'll tell them they're
Simple. And they've got the same
attitude problem. No matter where you
go, even if you don't hit on them,
they've got the same attitude problem.
Have you noticed that ghost in London?
They've got the same They're like NPCs, non playing
characters. If you notice that in London
as well, they're literally like NPCs.
for you today. I think it's going to be
Chinese. Yeah, man. But these people
that that defend women, they
probably probably women weren't like
this back in their day or they live in
somewhere like [ __ ] Glasgow or I mean
even Cardiff. I mean, you know, even if
you live in one of them places, women
are not the way they are like they are.
They are the way they are in London. You
understand? Even though most are
probably [ __ ] but I feel like you
probably wouldn't have found someone by
now that wasn't. You know, these people
wouldn't last a minute in London in their
20s. You know, they they don't
understand anything because they ain't
got a life. You see, they lived their
life back in their 20s. Now they just
sit on YouTube all day. They don't leave
their house. They just sit in and they
think they know how the world
works. And they think they know how the
world works. But they don't know how the
works. And the reason I'm asking you
where you live, there's a reason for it.
And life's hard. I just said to this
[ __ ] woman in Scotland, she's like,
"Oh, life's hard." No, I don't. Yeah,
life's hard. But that's not an excuse
for women being [ __ ] you
know. Yeah. Stop being a white nut. O
rat face. Oi, rat face on a grand a
month. Rat boy on a grand a month. I
spent half of your money on Friday. You
[ __ ] rat face. You and your fat ugly
girlfriend. You and that fat ugly
girlfriend with special needs. And you
said on your video, I watched about 10
seconds of it that you're going to I
know more women than you, Virgin Boy.
I've actually been with people that
weren't disabled. You've only been with
disabled. What would you know, Virgin
Boy? You can't even go to a normal
environment. You have to go to [ __ ]
old [ __ ] events full of old people
because your autism don't let you
function in normal relationships. That's
why you've only been with disabled and
you can't get Morgan and Izzy out your
head cuz you're a jealous [ __ ] virgin.
Also, you said that you've never
experienced um erectile dysfunction when
drinking. I know you never because you
have it normally, which is why you're
still a virgin. Which is why you're
going to die a virgin, mate. Listen, you
can go on about how long you've been
with Sarah all you want. You are a
virgin. Look, you even said it on your
video as well. I've never been in a
relationship. No, but I've had more
women than you. I've had more sex than
you. How the [ __ ] can you say that I've
got erectile dysfunction when there's a
video of me getting a relation in a
relationship, lad? You know what I'm
saying? You [ __ ] little ratfaced
version. You little ugly rodent. Sort
your ugly rodent face
out. Sort that [ __ ] rat face out,
rodent boy. Sort that [ __ ] dirty rat
face out. If you if you could actually
grow a beard, lad. You might lose your
virginity. You might not die a virgin.
No one cares about Sarah, bro. No one
gives a [ __ ] about
Sarah. You're telling me that I don't
know women, but I've had more women than
you. And I've been with women that you
can't get out your head. Molding is he?
You can't get them out your head every
day. Virgin boy wishing it was you that
[ __ ] them and not me. That's why you
have to tell yourself every day that
nothing happened cuz you still a virgin.
And you've literally what? Never [ __ ]
had You've never had problems. Yeah.
I've never mate. Listen, guess what? I
don't want a disabled girl. I don't want
a spacker. I don't pray on the
vulnerable. I'm not denying that. I'm
not denying that. But I've had better
looking women than him. I got more money
than him and that's what worked for me.
Worked for me. He's in a relationship
with a spacker and he's on a grand a
month. I'm not denying that. I'm not
denying that. No, I've not been in a
relationship with a special needer and
I'm not on £1,000 a month. It didn't.
Yes, I admit that. I'm not denying
anything. Am I denying it? But guess
what? The short relationships I have had
live in Sha's head went free.
Sean has had loads of women. Sean has
not had loads of women. I've had more
women than he has had. Mate, do you want
to go back on my YouTube? Dave Ev, do
you want to go back on my YouTube and
show you all the women that I've been
with? Do you want to see me getting a
[ __ ] Sean has only had disabled
women. That's that's the difference. I
have had Americans, Australian, New
Zealand. What? Sean had the same [ __ ]
for three years. Crack on, mate.
Yeah, that little virgin has never had
anything. Why did you run away as well?
Um, on Friday when I sold you money, rat
face. I rat face on a grand a month. Why
did you run away on Friday when I got
that money out? That was over £1,000 for
you, buddy. [ __ ] rat face. [Laughter]
Thank you, Nene. And he also he also and
another thing na na here's another thing
lad. He also is obsessed with my sloppy
seconds like one night stands I've had.
Um yeah lad he uh he's also obsessed
with women that I've been with in the
past. Like every woman that I get with
like that I've had sex with and
whatever. All my hair bro. Okay. Um he
he stalks them. He obsesses over
them. Yeah. He obsesses over them and he
won't um he will not shut up about them
because he wishes that it was him
[ __ ] them and not me. That's another
thing he does. Which Well, it's just an
obsession with me really. Yeah, exactly.
Because he doesn't have no money, bro.
He doesn't have no life. I just took out
over a grand on Friday and he couldn't
show me nothing. Why doesn't he [ __ ]
because he doesn't He doesn't have sex.
He's still a virgin.
This is what I'm trying to say to you,
bro. He does videos on me because he
wants to be me. He's jealous of me. You don't
understand. [ __ ] me. You saw me the
other day. I went live for a little bit. Well, [ __ ]
it. But I'll be right back. I'm just
going to make myself a copper [ __ ] I'm
just going to mute the mighty lad. I
show showed a bit of cash. I watched the
video. Guess what? I show more money
than him as well, to be fair. And to be
fair, I showed way more money than he
showed. Yeah. And everyone saw that as
well. He doesn't [ __ ] mate. Listen,
listen listen, bro. It doesn't matter
that he's in a relationship with a
[ __ ] bro. You people are always
going to pick on things like think it at
the end of the day, you at the end of
the [ __ ] day, you people are fat,
ugly, and you've never even been laid.
You can say that I've not been in a
relationship all you want. You people
are still fat, ugly little virgins that
self-reflect your little sad lives onto
people every day. Yeah. And I No, he
hasn't proved he's got money, mate.
Listen, listen, listen. Okay. Do you
want me to give you two examples again?
Right. I showed six grand, you all went
running away. I showed over a grand, you
all went running away. You don't have
money. Let's play the money game now
then. Okay. Show us two grand. All
right. Okay. I'll be nice. I showed over
1,000 pound bum chains on Friday. Let's
see your two grand. Let's see your
money. Don't run away and show us your
two grand. Come on. Prove that you've
got two grand. Show us your money now.
Do it now. I want to see two grand now.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Prove it.
Prove it. Prove you got two grand. Come
on. Right. Let's play this again.
Everybody saw the money. Baz. Everyone
else. Come on. Let's see your two grand,
Mr. Money Man. Come on. Come on, money
man. Let's see your two grand. He
doesn't have money, bro. Listen. He's
never been abroad. Yeah. He's never been
on a plane. He's not even got a
passport. The skin flint. Show us. Yeah.
And that's another thing, bro. Look.
Okay. Okay. I've been abroad. I've been
all over England. I've been on a [ __ ]
pl. I've been on planes. I've got
designer clothes. Who's the one that's
really got money? I'm not [ __ ] sat in
my bed sitting Kent still a [ __ ]
virgin shopping in the [ __ ] charity
shop showing my monthly [ __ ] money.
Yeah, you have been shown money enough
times and you all go running away. So
shut the [ __ ] up about this money game.
Yeah, I played it with you again on
Friday. I was
drunk. You're a skin Flynn. You do not
have no [ __ ] money, bro. Get your
money out now. Let's see the color of
your money now. Rat boy. Exactly. Show
us your money now, rat boy, on a grand a
month. Come on, you little skin flint.
Come on, you little skin flint, mate.
All he done with that, let me tell you,
bro. All he done, all he done Yeah. All he [ __ ]
done is got his little [ __ ] monthly
benefits, his monthly housing benefits
that he has to give to the house. Yeah.
Let's see your money, rat boy. Get your
money out for the lads. Stop running
away. Show us your two grand. Come on.
Show us your two grand. Show us that you
got money, rat boy. I want to play the
money game. Come on, you rat ugly
[ __ ] with the fat ugly girlfriend.
Your fat ugly girlfriend. Come on, let's
play the money game. Don't run away.
Don't run away from Peter Benny's live
stream. Show us your money. I want to
see the color of your [ __ ] money.
Come on, show us your money. I know
you're watching me. Come on. And I'll go
straight to the bank. Well, I'll go
straight to the ATM and I'll put money
on my other accounts. Come on. Come on.
Come on. But guess what? Guess what,
bro? Dave Everett, everybody owns you.
You fat, ugly little [ __ ] You little
downey on YouTube. Everybody owns you.
Yeah, everybody [ __ ] owns you,
lad. You little downey. Life owns you
and bullies you every day. Get off of
YouTube, you fat ugly spacker. Get off
of YouTube under you little gay account,
mate. I own every single one of you on
YouTube. Look at my YouTube channel.
I've had a better life than you for 3
years. 3 years. I've been owning you
skinny little clowns. I've shown more
money than you skinned little clowns.
I've had more women than you skinned
little clowns. Isn't that
madness? I've been living that life
owning you clowns for [ __ ] 3, four years.
Suck your mother, you little [ __ ]
ugly [ __ ] And if that really is you,
you're not going to feel no, bro. You
got batted the last time you come. You
little downey. Go and suck your mother.
Exactly. [ __ ] spacker.