Yo, [ __ ] hell.
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Shit's on [ __ ] 6%.
Let some people join.
Why the [ __ ] Why the [ __ ] would I lie
about getting a hand job?
What? What? What the [ __ ] would I get
out lying about getting a hand job? If I
was going to lie about something, I'd
lie about [ __ ] getting laid.
I'd lied about [ __ ] bigger things
than a [ __ ] hand job. What the [ __ ]
is a hand job, bro? That takes like less
than five minutes.
Why the [ __ ] would I lie about getting a
hand job? So, no, I didn't get caught
lying because I'm not lying. He's only
saying that so Natalie doesn't think
that [ __ ] he done anything with the
other one. Does he not realize that me
and that girl was alone
for literally 10 minutes?
Did he Does he not realize that? Why the
[ __ ] would I lie about getting a hand
job? Get real, son.
The amount of women I've been seen with
on this community, why would I lie about
getting a hand job? I'd lie about get
I'd lie about getting laid.
I'd lie about getting laid. If I was
going to lie about something, it
wouldn't be a [ __ ] hand job.
And I'd be lying every [ __ ] week. Come on.
Get real, man.
I'd lie about [ __ ] having sex and
getting a [ __ ] if I was going to lie.
I don't know what you done, bro.
Anyway, some of them numbers reply back to me.
Well, if any of them meet, then maybe it
is better. Oh, Monty was trying to say
that I was lying about getting a hand
job when I [ __ ] wasn't. I was alone
with this person as well when he was
talking to the other one. I was alone.
Why would I lie about getting a [ __ ]
hand job? I'd lie about getting laid if
I was going to lie about something. I
say I got a hotel and bang them if I was
if I was going to lie about something.
So, nice try.
Um, yeah. Anyways, put the link up. Forgot.
Get real, kid. So yeah,
I still ain't cast that football betting, bro.
Anytime, boss. I still ain't cast mine in yet.
285, bro. I need to No, he didn't toss
me right under the bus because he didn't
see what happened with me and that girl
because he wasn't even with us at the
end. So, no, he didn't.
So, anyways, I don't care, bro. I'm not
going to sit here and [ __ ] try and
convince you. I know what I've done,
what I haven't done, bro. Believe what
you want. I don't give a [ __ ] Who lies
about getting a hand job? And uh yeah.
Yeah. I need to collect 280 me.
never lied about anything in my life.
No, I didn't tell him to lie about it.
If I was going to lie about something,
right, I'd go out in London every week
and say that I got laid every week.
I've already proven I've had more women
than anybody on this community. So, why
would I need to lie? It doesn't make sense.
I'm the only one that's been seen with
all of these things that you tell people
they don't have.
Who? Why would I lie?
I've already had more women than anyone
on the community. What the [ __ ] would I
need to lie about? So, yeah.
Um, I'm not sure, bro. I'm probably not
going to do one for weeks anyways.
Yeah, man. I'm [ __ ] I had a Vindaloo,
by the way.
So yeah, bro.
Well, he's saying that to try and cover
his own back. That's the reason he's
saying that. So that Natalie doesn't
think that he's done anything with the other one.
He's trying to back chat uh backtrack. Sorry.
Mother [ __ ] bro. Who lies about getting
a [ __ ] hand job? You can give
yourself a [ __ ] hand. You can give
yourself a [ __ ] hand job.
Wasn't Wasn't Wasn't [ __ ] L the one
that was lying about Izzy. Lying about
[ __ ] Izzy. He's one to [ __ ] talk,
right? Because he's the one that was
lying about [ __ ] Izzy giving him a hand job.
Who the [ __ ] can he talk about [ __ ]
lying? What? What? What am I lying about?
He's only saying that to to cover his back.
A hand job is literally nothing, bro.
Why would I lie about a hand job that I
could give myself?
Come on, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. I spent £200 yesterday.
So, I still collect my uh winnings. He
hasn't sold me out cuz I've never I'm
not making up stories that I had a hand
job. I did get a hand job
because I'm not making up stories.
Some of these numbers are replying back
as well. It seems good. I only got I
only got three numbers. Yeah.
285 from 80 is good return, isn't it? I
I'll connect it when I can be bothered,
man. Maybe tomorrow
I need to go to the bookies.
Anyways, moving on from this. Anyways,
that doesn't even trigger me.
That doesn't even make me jealous, bro.
That's how that's how you know you're
[ __ ] bro. When someone's talking
about wins and it doesn't even make you
jealous or want to gamble. It's crazy, isn't it? Yeah, man.
When are these large
When are LJ's followers going to stop
calling themselves skin?
I'm skin. I went to Birmingham
yesterday. I spent [ __ ] £200.
How the [ __ ] can I be [ __ ] skin?
What the [ __ ]
They must be again getting themselves confused. Yeah. >> Yeah.
Nothing about me, kid.
Yeah. and you're going to lose 3K next week. So, yeah, man.
Yeah, but you're not far from a losing spree.
It always happens.
Yeah, man. It's not It's not
You're not far from a losing in on a
football. You can't really do your balls
in. Oh, I can't do mining, bro.
Yeah, I bought two Guinnesses and two shots. £22.
What should you be grateful, man? And I
didn't have to come all the way to Birmingham and
[ __ ] bail him out, you know?
I bought us drinks and breakfast. Drinks. Breakfast.
Gave him a bit of company. He should thank me.
[ __ ] hell, man. Wish somebody would
do that for me. Wish somebody would do
You know what I would say? Yeah. If I
was if I was money Yeah. Listen, I would say that
this is what I'd say. I'd be like,
"Yeah, I was cold approaching women yesterday.
Is it any of your business? I'm no
longer with you. Why don't you [ __ ]
off?" That's what I would say. I'd say,
"Yeah, I was talking to other women.
Yeah, I [ __ ] was. Cuz you're not with
me and you're not replying to my [ __ ]
messages. Damn [ __ ] right.
Damn right. That's what I would have
said to her in a man.
Yeah, I am talking to other women just
like you are probably talking to other men.
That's what I would say. Bro,
are you mad? [ __ ] that.
I'd say yes, I am speaking to other
women and I did I do I did do some
approaches. Yes, that's what I would say.
You're not with them. They're not
replying to your messages.
Why? What the [ __ ] bro?
This is crazy, bro.
I told him about I told him about the
USA Izzy thing yesterday. I went more in
depth about it cuz I don't think he
understood like the real story and I
told him. You think that stops me
[ __ ] going out and trying with other
people? [ __ ] no, bro.
Nah. Hell no, bro.
Money. Women is like money. You see,
they come and go. Well, they don't come
in a sense of like you get them, but I
mean like when if one goes and she's not
loyal enough to stay with you. Oh, you
can just try and find another one. Try
Yeah, but why would he want her back
when he can just try and meet someone
else though? No, but that's what I'm
trying to say. And even if he wants
Yeah, but listen.
If I wanted someone back, yeah, even if
I wanted someone back, I would just do
approaching videos and just ignore them.
I let them come back to me. Do you think
I ever begged that 19, 20 year old, no?
She kept coming back to me. She kept
And then when she went, I said, "Fuck
off. I didn't give a [ __ ] bro." And she
weren't ugly. So, like, you know what I mean?
But it doesn't matter. Even if you want her back,
you need to do all of these things like
ignore, speak to other people, and then
we'll see in it.
You need to be you need to be in
control. Do you know what I mean? You
need you need to take power back.
You understand? You need to be in
control, not them.
And when they're not in control, they're mad.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
You need to to take control back. If you
can't, then you're [ __ ] If they've
got all the power, you're [ __ ]
Is what I'm saying make sense? I hope it
does. Anyways, money wants to drive. >> Yo.
>> Hey, bro.
>> Yeah, man.
>> I was just saying, bro, you need to [ __ ] >> PJ.
>> You need to [ __ ] her off, bro.
They [ __ ] off, Natalie.
>> Yeah, man. >> Why?
>> Because she's not replying to your
messages, bro. Think about it, bro.
She's probably know listen. Do you know last night? >> Yeah.
>> You know, it was I code approaching for
>> Well, I was doing Well, I guess you was
trying for me, but I I I could do it
myself, though. So,
>> exactly. I weren't even caugh watching
anybody last night. I done it for PJ,
>> but I do it myself. So,
>> [ __ ] hell.
>> Here's the thing. Yeah. Like,
>> if I was you, I would just move on, man.
[ __ ] Like, she doesn't reply to
She's probably She's probably speak
She's probably spoke to other people as well.
No, no, she hasn't. But that has pissed
me off with Lord. Yeah, that has really
truly pissed me off with Lord. Yeah,
it's not even that. Natalie doesn't even
know what the [ __ ] happened in town.
>> He doesn't.
>> Money. Monty, listen. Listen. Right. How
many goodl looking people did we see yesterday?
>> Not really. >> No.
>> There was
to me there's only one good-looking
woman in a nice to me. All they were [ __ ] ugly.
>> Come on, man.
>> No, they were good looking. They were
good-looking, but to me, they're ugly. I
didn't want I don't want anyone else.
The same like last night, like like I
keep saying to Natalie, that CL proing last night
>> was not what PJ,
>> you need to stop this [ __ ] man.
Timmy, shut the [ __ ] up. You could have
did me last night. You little clown. You [ __ ] weasel.
I need to stop this [ __ ] I might as
well just move back up north now. >> Yeah.
>> Well, if that's what she really really
wants, if she really really thinks that
I was caught approaching,
>> why is she Why is she even going Lord J? That's weird.
>> It is weird. This is what I want. I
don't know. She she she tells me for
saying [ __ ] but she's the one who goes
around and telling people her business.
I haven't I haven't even told anyone
about her being in a tent and I never
will do and I never will.
>> Money, can I ask you a question?
>> Go for it.
>> I was on a I was reading the chat. Yeah,
they were saying I'm skin. Listen,
money, you've met me in real life. Yeah.
Am I skin?
>> No, he's not skin. But these they still
try and say I'm skin.
>> What am I supposed to do now? I've told
N the truth. I've told her the truth. I
haven't called approached anybody.
>> Money. The breakfast was [ __ ] nice,
was it, bro?
>> Yeah, it were nice.
>> What was it called again? Something in
Canada, was it?
>> Um, Canada or something like that.
>> Yeah, it was nice, man. We got an omelette.
Bro. Oh, we would have been [ __ ] if my
sister didn't um transfer me that money,
bro. It wouldn't have even been funny.
We would have been [ __ ]
Yeah. Do you know what I done? Joe, are
you still there? I'll tell you quickly.
Do you know what happened?
>> Any PJ, let me get a little recording
and send that to Natalie of you just
[ __ ] admitting that I I done call the
proion for you. There's not only things for me.
>> Yeah, but money not. Yeah, but no one
will believe it because
I don't know why they I'm telling the truth.
>> Believe it because they know that I can
do it by myself.
>> Yeah, I know.
>> Yeah, I know. But I done it for you. Because
to be honest with you, I don't know why
I [ __ ] done it PJ for you. >> Yeah.
>> One second. Yeah, so I went to
Birmingham. Yeah. And I've got two bank
account. I got two cards and one's an
old card and I had all my money on one
card and I took the wrong [ __ ] card.
I took the wrong card that had all my
[ __ ] money and I had another card.
Only had £50 in it. I was like, "Oh
[ __ ] what am I going to do? I couldn't
even get the last train back cuz I'd
missed the last train cuz I got there
quite late. It was £29 to get there, by
the way." And [ __ ] I had to call my
[ __ ] sister and say, "I need you to
send me 150. Send you back tomorrow." I
got the wrong card basically.
She sent me 150. Yeah. I would have been
[ __ ] without her. Cuz my mom was asleep.
>> It got declined all night last night.
>> We would have been [ __ ] >> Declined.
>> Yeah. It was an old card. I p I I I got
the wrong one by accident.
>> So I was going to pay for the drink. So,
I pulled the money out of my pocket to
pay for the drinks last night, but he
ended up getting that. So,
>> I tried to get £200 out of her, but um
she only gave 150.
>> Yeah. I just can't believe that Natalie
thinks I was cold approaching last
night. That's one thing I never do.
>> Uh London's better, Kieran.
The bounces are [ __ ] pricks in
Birmingham. We had issues.
>> What happened? Didn't I square up to one?
>> Yeah, they're pricks, bro. Hey, PJ. >> Yeah.
>> Right. Hey, one sec.
>> You haven't you never even been to Birmingham, Kieran.
>> Right. PJ,
>> that's not even up. That's even not
That's not up north, bro. That's like in
the middle. Yeah. Go on.
>> One second. Right. Tell Natalie who I
was called approaching for
me. Tell Natalie who Sorry. Tell Natalie
who I was cold approaching for.
>> For me, bro.
>> Exactly. Exactly. I I weren't even cold
approaching anyone. You only went on to
women for [ __ ] P.
>> Yeah. I had a sleep greasy and I woke up
and wouldn't Indian. I'm still [ __ ]
from that trip, bro. Oh,
think I might have found a new mama.
Greasy. might have found a new mama.
Is that cute?
Oh, bless you.
I feel fat.
[ __ ] me, bro.
I feel like I'm [ __ ] dying, bro. Monty man,
I think you should just give up with
this whole nanny thing, bro.
No, no, no, no, no, no. Long story, but
I had to get free trains back, bro. It
was a nightmare.
He didn't sell me out cuz I didn't lie about anything.
No, long story. But yeah, I had to get
free trains back, bro. Long
like I was saying to these earlier, I'm
not sure how I used to
do Scotland and [ __ ] Newcastle, bro.
I don't know how I used to do it.
I done Manchester. I done two days in
Manchester and then I come back. Don't
know how Don't know how I done it, bro.
I don't know how I done it. Yeah. Long story, bro. No, no,
no. the ticket inspector to come on the
train and I was supposed to only be on
some a certain um train line. So he
kicked me off at Coventry. It was a [ __ ]
as well. We made sure that I got off got
off at Coventry was an overall [ __ ] He
could have easily let me stay on that
train. Then I had to get train from
Coventry to Birmingham but it stopped in
Northampton. So then I had to London but
yeah but I had nothing I had nothing
better to do. It was a trick, but I won
a football bet. I had nothing better to do.
So, it was that odd, dude. I think I did
win £200 on the football. So,
yeah, it wasn't it was a trick. It was long, bro.
I don't know how I done that in
Manchester them two days.
I literally went Manchester on a Friday,
come back on a Sunday drinking. I don't
know how I used to do it, man. Like I
said, I don't know how I used to do it.
Yeah, that's how I used to get free um
how I had to get free trains back.
Yeah, he was trying to be cheeky, that
ticket inspector as well. And then when
I pulled it up on him, he he backtracked.
Yeah, he was a [ __ ] He was. He was a
[ __ ] Proper [ __ ] What's
who the [ __ ] would be a ticket inspector?
Like what? Who
who whose childhood [ __ ] dream is to
be a ticket inspector?
And I wouldn't mind if they were just
No. He was like, "Oh, don't you go
wandering around. you you're get you're
getting off of me and I said excuse me
what did you say I was like you don't
tell me where I can and can't go and he
said then he then he just backtracked as
if I didn't hear what he just said [ __ ] idiot
so I just got off that commentary
because if I didn't get off he would
just hold the whole train and then call
the police because they've done it on buses before
you're not [ __ ] talking to me like
that, mate, about I don't go I said I
don't go where I want.
Yeah, I got off at Coventry because if I
didn't get off, he was he was going to
hold the train and call the police.
Yeah, dummy. Cuz he was going to call
the police, you [ __ ] idiot.
Yeah, cuz he was going to call the
police, you [ __ ] idiot. And and it
would have stopped the whole train. So
yeah, I did get off because the train
weren't going to move if I stayed on it. So yeah,
anyways, moving on.
I remember before Kieran. Yeah,
I I forget what happened. I think I
didn't play the bus. No, no, the car
didn't go through the bus. They stopped
the whole bus. They weren't moving the
bus. They weren't moving the bus.
So yeah, Bombay, stop it. You don't even
leave your house. I've just explained
the situation to you.
Yeah, I just explained the situation to
you a million times. If I didn't get
off, he would have called the police. You [ __ ]
And he would have moved the train. Yes.
So I had to get off because the train
wouldn't move. Dummy dumb [ __ ] This the
same on the [ __ ] bus.
Shut the [ __ ] up. You don't. And they do
it on buses as well. Even on one
pound50s, they won't move the bus, bro.
Trust me. Dummy, dumb [ __ ] If you had
some life experience. Yeah.
Dummy, dumb [ __ ] Yeah, they would just
hold the whole train up and then they
just call the police.
But I was like, you don't tell me where to go.
Yeah, I said you I said I'll go where I
want. That's what I said.
But he backtracked though.
Another one that can start [ __ ] but
can't finish it. But no, he was a proper
[ __ ] that he was an actual proper [ __ ]
You know, there was a Scouse one that
come on before, right? He said, "Listen,
you either pay a ticket or you reby a
[ __ ] rail card." Which I think that
was fair, you know. Yeah. Anyways, moving on. Moving on.
Moving on. Stop it, Bombay. I'm not
money man or Timmy. Moving on. So, yeah,
moving on now. Anyways, moving on.
But yeah, bro. He told me to get off at
Coventry and I got off at Coventry
because I had to. Otherwise, he would
have called the police and the train
wouldn't move. Yeah, I admit it. Yeah.
Yeah. I I admit it. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I literally got off where he said
get off. Yeah. Because he would have
stopped the whole train and then I would
have had to go off anyways. I admit. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
No, I got off. He told me he told me
that I had to get off, but then I
realized if I didn't get off, then they
would have stopped the whole train. So,
I had to get off. I had no choice. Same
as being arrested.
No, he he told me where to get off. And
the reason that I listened is because he
would have called the police. Dumbo.
So, I didn't want him calling the police
and I wanted to actually get back home.
So, I had to get off. Dummy dumb [ __ ] Big difference.
Dummy dumb [ __ ] Because if I didn't do
it, I wouldn't be able to go go back to
London. Dummy dumb [ __ ] So, what was the alternative?
Oh, well actually he did say one second
money. He said if you pay £23
you can stay on. I told him to [ __ ] off.
Yeah. He said if you pay £23
I told him to [ __ ] off. No.
And and I listened because I didn't want
to get arrested. Dummy dumb [ __ ] Dummy
dumb [ __ ] What would have you done,
dummy dumb [ __ ] Stay on the train and
don't move. No, he told me where to get
off and if I didn't get off, the train
wouldn't move. Dummy dumb [ __ ]
Re [ __ ] [ __ ] boy. It's not a case
of he told me and I done it. It's the
case of I wouldn't be able to get back home.
Dummy dumb [ __ ] [ __ ] Dummy dumb
Down syndrome. If I didn't do it, I
wouldn't be able to get back home. You
down syndrome. The same thing as getting
arrested by the police. You down syndrome.
You [ __ ] down syndrome. Are you a
[ __ ] [ __ ] or something?
You [ __ ] [ __ ]
You must be a [ __ ] [ __ ] lad. Yeah,
I know. This is what I'm trying to say
to this [ __ ] that if I didn't get
off, they would have they would have
stopped the whole train. You dummy dumb
[ __ ] [ __ ] No, I got got off because
if I didn't get off, he would have
delayed the whole train.
You [ __ ] That's the reason I got off.
Shut the [ __ ] up, you little [ __ ]
Anyways, if you keep doing this, I'm
just going to call you out, bro, and
show everybody that I tell you what to
do. Listen, you dummy. Dumb [ __ ]
[ __ ] They've done it on buses as
well. If if you don't pay, right, they
delay the whole bus and they call the
police. You [ __ ] idiot. You little
You You dummy dumb [ __ ] [ __ ] No, I
got to Bro, I've explained this to you
about a million times. Listen, do Okay.
Do you want to meet me today then?
You little [ __ ] boy. Do you want to
meet me today? Come in the hangouts and
show me where you are. [ __ ] this. I'll
meet you today. I will show you who's
the good boy. Don't run away now. One second.
Oh, you little [ __ ] boy who sucks his
mother's [ __ ] You sucks his mom's
vagina. You're a good little boy. One
sec, [ __ ] boy. Show me where you are.
Come on, you little [ __ ] boy.
All right. All I'm saying is you suck
your mom's [ __ ] and you can never show
me where you are. Am I joking?
Am I joking? You You suck your mother's
[ __ ] and you're a goodbye and you won't
show me where you are. Goodbye. Goodbye.
I'm literally cussing your mom telling
you that you suck your mother's [ __ ] for
a packet of biscuits and you won't show
me where you are. Cuz you're a good boy
and you know better. Cuz you're a good
boy and you know better.
You're a good boy. Cuz you know what's
good for you. That's why you will never
ever show me where you are. Tell me
where you are. cuz you're a good little
[ __ ] boy and I've got control over
you. Me, I live in London. You can't
show me where you live. I guarantee you
if you come in the hangouts right now,
one second, Monty,
I will come I will come to you today.
Anywhere you are. Yeah. Listen, listen.
Dummy dumb [ __ ] who [ __ ] his mom.
Show me where you are and I will come to
you today. I will literally come to you
today. One second. Let me put my t-shirt
and shorts on. I'm literally telling you
about your mother. I'm degrading your
mother. She's a slag.
And you won't show me where you are cuz
you're a good little boy. Come on, bro.
You suck your [ __ ] mother's [ __ ] And
you won't show me where you are. And I'm
talking about your family. At least I
sent something back. [ __ ] little
[ __ ] Come to Hangouts. One second.
Let me send the link.
Come on, you little [ __ ] Stop shagging
your mom's [ __ ] Stop being a little good boy.
That's how I know I control these people properly. Monty,
>> stop talking to him. Stop sitting there
arguing with a bunch of bastics who are
not going to meet you.
>> Yeah, they won't because he's a good
little boy. He knows. He knows. Yeah,
>> I'm done with Natalie now. Anyways, I'm
[ __ ] completely done with Natalie.
Natalie. One boy won't show me.
One second. You're right. You're right.
I agree with you. I agree with you.
They're never going to meet you cuz they
know what's good for them. Like a good
little boy. I get the last word.
>> I am completely done with no me.
Completely done with her.
>> Yeah. At the end of the day when a woman
slide past me and said, "PJ, that woman
touched me ass. That woman touched me
past me. Woman touched me ass."
>> No. [ __ ] now. going mad because a
woman touched my ass.
>> You'll never be done with that.
>> I'm done with her. I can't be ass with
her. If she thinks that I went alrossing
last night, if she thinks that I like
that woman touching me, even if she did
or didn't touch me ass on purpose, I
don't know. She only went past. You know
what I mean? I'm done with I can't be
honest with the little [ __ ] games
these [ __ ] women play. It's all right
when it gets hard for them and they
expect a man to stand around.
>> No, you like it, Monty.
>> I don't like it. The [ __ ] pricks are
[ __ ] pricks, mate. They don't sit
there and listen. But it'd be so totally
different if it if the shoe was on her
foot. Do you know what I mean? If the
shoe was on her upper foot, I didn't
even go out approaching last night. I
don't peed yet.
Focus my ass.
What do you want me to do about that?
Don't give a [ __ ] Natalie, anymore.
>> Why is she going to Lord J like
>> she's a [ __ ] weirdo? Entertaining the
PE. She's entertaining the weirdos. I
can't believe she's told them. I can't
believe she sat there and told him she
was homeless in a tent. I wasn't even
going to say [ __ ] all to anyone.
>> Why Karen? Have you How's the gambling been, bro?
>> I didn't even tell anybody about her
being in a tent, being homeless. No one.
>> I want to 280. I still ain't collected it yet.
>> And I know that Natal is depressed and down.
>> You know what I mean? I know that
Natalie is proper depressed and down. I
know why is doing this. Okay, now
at the end of the day, I've not done
[ __ ] all wrong. Natalie left me hanging
for too [ __ ] long where I'm not
depressed. I'm crying for her and asking
her for her help and she sat there
ignoring me. But when I go panel, she's
like talking to me then telling me I
can't be asked cuz you're going cold
approach and you're doing that. You're
doing that. You weren't even talking.
You ain't even talking to me before you
even went out.
>> Kieran, so you you just gamble your
money every month and if you lose, you
lose all of it, don't you? You're
[ __ ] a cycle, bro. it.
>> How the [ __ ]
>> you're stuck in a cycle, Kieran? Is it
>> How the [ __ ] do you How the [ __ ] do you
know what a woman wants when they don't
don't tell you what they want? You know
what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> Now they saying it's completely over
because I went cold approaching. How did
I know that now they was going to go
back and talk to me? How do I know that
when she stayed all silent and quiet and not even
>> Yeah, but Karen, what do you gamble on?
Because The online roulette's fixed now.
I just do the both teams to score me. I
I ain't played slots or roulette for
[ __ ] I don't play that [ __ ] anymore. Me, bro.
>> I used to be in that cycle.
>> If Natalie's like this, he's playing
mind games. He's I mean
I don't want Do you want me Do you want
me to come back to Birmingham Saturday
for another session?
>> Yeah, we go for another session and we
actually go out. I will actually go out
and I will actually go out and call the
pro some [ __ ] women this time. I will
make sure I get my dick at the same
time. I'll make sure I go down on that
fanny and make it come to the L. I'm not ass.
>> There you go. I'm not ass now. Yeah.
>> Yeah, Kevin. So what? You just gamble
your money on on the on the fish and
frenzy slots. I'm guessing
>> I'm not ask anymore if Natalie thought I
was [ __ ] cold approaching last night
and for a woman touching my ass.
>> I might play again.
>> I might play it again at some point.
>> Did a woman touch my ass last night? >> Yeah.
>> Did they? >> Yeah.
>> I didn't even [ __ ] know that until
now they actually told me. Okay. Well, I
couldn't help where the woman touched my
ass last night.
>> How are you doing, man? I went to
Birmingham to meet uh Monty, bro. And
it's still It's the same show as it's
always been. It's the same show from two years ago.
All right, them bounces get really
cheeky. Me and Monty took them on yesterday. Wait,
we took them bounces on. I said, "Stop
acting up in front of the police, big man.
>> If you're going to do something,
>> move away from the police.
It makes you look soft."
Acting big in front of police. What
[ __ ] bro? When they know that police
are opp literally there's about 10
police officers opposite the [ __ ] strip.
They're absolute [ __ ] opportunists.
They're actually cowards, man. Yeah, I
don't really like Birmingham to be
honest with you. If
>> I knew N was like I don't like it, bro.
>> If I knew N was actually like least hard
to explain to, I would have [ __ ] got
with her cuz I haven't done nothing
wrong. Not really. Anyways,
>> if we meet if we meet again, Monty.
Yeah. Well, we will meet again. Try not
to be as fishious this time.
>> What? So are you not what do you mean as fishes?
>> Like you hurt my hand.
>> What do you mean?
>> You squeeze my hand and you made me bleed.
>> What do you mean it made you bleed?
>> My finger? You made my finger bleed.
>> What? Did I just make blood to come out
your finger? Like
>> like near the nail. Near the nail. You
made me bleed.
So, you're saying that I push blood from
your hand all the way up to your [ __ ] fingernails?
>> No, but some blood come out. You're quite aggressive.
>> Don't forget I'm very f I'm very
fragile, you know. So,
>> I'm soft pey's
quite strong, you know.
See, he's actually quite strong. I'm not
even joking. He actually is. Yeah. >> M.
>> You hurt me, Monty.
>> You hurt me. You did.
>> Did I about that P if I get you?
>> You're a vicious creature.
>> I'm actually I'm actually a good man. I
got a good It's just that I can, you
know. [ __ ] up, man. [ __ ] bro.
>> I didn't [ __ ] up, Lord. That's the
thing. I didn't do
>> I called up Prime and Timmy yesterday.
Um, LT, they weren't having none of it.
>> Okay, now why Natalie bothered anyways?
Why is Natalie asked anyways?
>> She weren't even with me. You finished
me, member. But why is she taking all
she's all ass now? But why you doing
that now, darling? Why you acting like
you're all ass now? For what? What? what
what I did last night. I don't know like
when I don't know even know what the
[ __ ] you wanted. When you're keeping me
in the dark all the time when you're not
texting me or ringing me and I go out
cold approach and he's like no I'm not
getting back with you cuz you went out cold approaching
can you can you LT can you give some
Monty man some advice? I was basically
saying to Monty man one second bro that
you should just try and meet other
people and just forget about her and let
her come and chase it back to you.
I'm not bothered anymore. I think I
because I've been through this, I kind
of think that's what works, bro. But
>> to be honest with you, PJ, he's done.
He's done. She thinks I went out to go
and get laid. She thinks I went out to
go and [ __ ] do whatever. Yeah. I was
having a good time last night. Yeah. I
was happy last night cuz we're pissed
out my head. >> Yeah.
>> Cuz I were pissed.
>> Money, I come, I come to Birmingham uh
to see you. So we could get some batches
and forget about this [ __ ] you know.
>> Yeah, let's [ __ ] forget about them,
>> All you kept all you kept talking about
was how much like you love her and stuff, Monty.
>> All that all all night last night in
that club and only what I were doing is
helping you out [ __ ] get laid or get
some [ __ ] numbers. That's it.
>> Yeah, but I was doing approaches myself.
>> I know you were, but you obviously told
me to go and [ __ ] do some, but I
didn't do what you told me to do. I went
over and I was asking for you. Did you
not see the woman look right over at you? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Exactly. Cuz they were telling the woman.
>> Yeah. Somebody came on a fake uh fake LT
account yesterday saying that he's going
to beat me and Monty up. He was a fake
you some fake account. Come on,
>> man. I ain't got nothing on my arms.
You're not even scared. Did that those
like cash flow
off? [ __ ] me, man. Now it's not even
worth it to cut myself deep enough.
>> Yeah, man.
>> [ __ ] it. I'm not going downhill over a
woman now anymore. [ __ ] it. You know
what? Can't be ass anymore. She want She
wants my love gone for her. That's [ __ ]
>> Listen, we called out that Timmy. We
called out that Timmy and we called out
that Prime and then we don't know if you
know. Yeah. No, that's it. Yeah. We done
then. Yeah, [ __ ] off.
>> [ __ ] hell, bro.
>> Yeah, I'm sick of trying with her. I'm
sick of [ __ ] crying with her, telling
her how much I love her, how much I
[ __ ] care about her, that I'm always
there for her, and then she thinks that
I went out to go on pool last night.
[ __ ] off, man. Women.
>> [ __ ] hell, man.
>> You know what? I can do so much better
than that then. Yeah. If you think all
that about me, if you think that's the
kind of man I am, literally I can do so
much [ __ ] better. And I will do. I
will do. I actually get with a woman who
[ __ ] wants me
>> for my mistakes and for who I am. And I
told you what I want and I will do. I
[ __ ] will do. Don't you worry about that.
>> Don't forget to pack it. You need to
pack this [ __ ] in, bro.
>> I know.
>> He's gnarly in it. If no one else now
he's just there accusing me yesterday.
They were so many better than [ __ ] Natalie, bro.
>> Yeah, I know. Look at that [ __ ] bird
who was, you know,
look at them two you was walking with
last night. Obviously, they were
talking, but look at them two.
>> Yeah, there was others as well. >> What?
>> Yeah, but
>> they weren't okay. And they weren't even
hitting on any of them. I was only
talking to him, talking to him like
normal. Only why I was actually talking
to him like normal is because he was [ __ ] 18.
Why the [ __ ] am I going to go to two 18y
olds and [ __ ] what? What? What the
[ __ ] Yeah. Yeah, [ __ ] Yeah, I'm
telling you 18. This how serious I'm
being. You know what I mean? Why the
[ __ ] am I going to go over and [ __ ]
cold approach a [ __ ] 18y old girl
when I'm [ __ ] in my 35?
>> Did I look Did I look, you know, people
was Monty? People was saying that people
was more hating you and not me. You
know, the videos we done together, they
were saying that you look like a [ __ ]
but no one said anything about me in it.
>> I look like a Trump. I got I got you box
on. I look like a year.
>> It's my year. What make me look like a [ __ ]
>> Money and PJ called approach. Oh. Oh,
bro. I would [ __ ] an 18-year-old. If If
an 18year-old offened me, I would do it.
>> 100%. I would do it.
>> No, I wouldn't even do that.
>> 100% would do. I would do it. I admit I
would do it. If they if they lied it
down on the table and they were sexy and
they were [ __ ] 18, I would do it.
>> No, I wouldn't.
>> No, I wouldn't do I wouldn't do 16. No,
I wouldn't do 17, but 18 I would I would
I would I admit I would.
>> All this I do is probably in a 20. So I
wouldn't go [ __ ] 18 or up any change
or anything like that. No,
>> they obviously if they obviously if they
had lied it on the table and that like
then I would do it, bro. I can't lie.
>> That is puts up. I wouldn't Well, only
what I done is just talk to him anyways.
>> It's not like I have many options. So
why would I say no? Like think of it.
I'm 27. Yeah. If an 18y old if it was I
mean just sex. I'm not talking about
dating. I wouldn't date. But I'm talking
purely just sex. I would do it. I would
>> I wouldn't even do it. I would I
wouldn't I wouldn't even do it if it was
sex. It's [ __ ] 18.
It's the teen
off the teen.
It's like she's still a teenager. You're
not a fully [ __ ] grow fully adult yet.
>> I was [ __ ] an 18y old when I was 26.
I don't give a [ __ ]
>> [ __ ] that. You never go out going [ __ ] teens.
>> How can it be classed as group? I'm not
almost 28. I'm 27 firstly. And no, you
can't be done for grooming because it's
more than legal. 16 is legal. One
second. One second. 16 is legal. I'd
never get with a 16y old. I never get
with a 17-y old. If an 18y old, which is
more than legal. Yeah. Literally put
themsel on the table for me. I would do
it. If I had nothing else, I would do
>> No, I would [ __ ] do it, bro.
>> No. [ __ ] that [ __ ]
[ __ ] that, man.
>> I'm not I could do that.
>> But not dated though. I I've already
done it. I've already [ __ ] you when I
was 26. What the [ __ ] am I on about? I
did do it. I don't give a [ __ ]
>> Can't believe Natalie thought I was
going out called approaching.
>> How many people How many people have got
a 10year age gap? It's not unheard of.
There was like there was like a Let me
tell you this. There's a 25y old with a
35y old. That's [ __ ] You can say that's weird.
>> Oh, I'm not going.
>> But we're talking about sex. We're
talking about just sex, not dating.
We're talking about just sex. There's a
I think there's a big difference. You
know, I wouldn't date an 18-year-old.
[ __ ] that. What the [ __ ] would you have
in common with an 18-year-old? Nothing.
>> You know, now they thinking I'm called
approaching now in it, man. What the
[ __ ] is going on now?
What? What? Why women like they bring up
I just noticed that then? Yeah. Natalie
has left me hanging. Yeah. For at least
two weeks, a week or so, whatever she's
left me to. Yeah. How the [ __ ] do I know
what Natalie wants when she's not telling me?
>> Here's the thing. Here's the thing.
Here's the thing. Um, LT. Yeah. But even
25 and 35 is weird. There's this guy on
YouTube who was 25 and he was 35 dating.
I found that weird. Not in terms of they
were se like sex, but they were dating.
That is even weird cuz 35 is close to
[ __ ] 40 and you're 25 which is almost
3 years younger than me.
>> So a girl's 25 and a guy's 35 dating
that's even weird.
>> You know what? You know what?
>> That is so weird. Yeah. It doesn't
matter what she is. It's what he is
though. It's what he is.
Let me tell my [ __ ] around
you know put me on big.
>> No. What are you? Bro, are you mad?
>> Yeah, they might just be immature, but
bro, it doesn't matter what she is. It's
what he is.
That's like saying, "Oh, an old man can
date a [ __ ] 25year-old."
>> Are you a PGA? But
>> put me on big.
>> But ideally, I'd want someone my own
age, my exact same age. This woman I'm
speaking to, she's the same age as me,
which is good.
>> Then yeah, it's
>> But you know, you know, Virgin Boy is an
actual nons because he said he would get
with he said he will get with 16y olds
and the way he tries to justify how it's
right is mad. >> Okay.
All this [ __ ]
Why would you be as
bad to the you got me
to the You got me. Yeah.
You got me. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Fair enough. Yeah. Yeah. Let's
Let's go and get the shots and t-shirt
you got me now. Yeah. before that. >> Yeah,
>> you need to stop all of this.
>> [ __ ] her, mate. She wants to play games
with me. There's the short she got me.
There's the short she's got me. I'm
being serious. There's the short me to
play these games. >> [ __ ]
Well, LT, can you can you help us here?
>> I went all the way to
>> I'm going to set these on fire.
Actually, I'm going to burn these
cuz he wants to play these games. Yeah,
he thinks I'm a [ __ ] prick.
They're being washed as well. Bought them [ __ ]
No, I'm not choking that. That's mine.
That's mine. I paid for that. [Music]
want to play games with me? I [ __ ]
hate with me, man. Where's the rest of
[ __ ] you got which you got me?
>> You help us out here.
>> Where's all the [ __ ] you got me?
>> [ __ ] man.
>> I think me, Monty, and LT should go out.
>> Say bye to Stitch now.
>> No, I want Stitch.
Back to Stitch.
>> No, I want him.
Give me Stitch. I wanted I wanted him
yesterday, but you wouldn't give me him.
No, don't chuck him. You're going to hurt him.
>> Bye-bye, Stitch. >> Stitch.
>> I want Stitch.
>> No, I want Stitch.
What are you doing?
>> I'm setting all these clothes now on fire.
What did you just do to Stitch?
Mon, I said to you yesterday, give me Stitch.
>> Oh, no. It was Natalie. I won that
>> I want it.
>> What? You want
>> Is he hurt?
>> Yeah, he's
>> going to be at No, mate.
>> No. No,
>> no, stop hurting him.
>> He's a good little character.
>> Let's see who some get.
>> Hey, no. Hey, Ghosted, to be fair, these
women can drive you insane.
>> I I just expected him to know better at,
you know, cuz he's older than me and stuff.
>> I thought, Monty, you would have known
better at your age, you know. About what
PJ about winning?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. You tell them do the truth. You
tell them you ain't done [ __ ] or wrong
and you [ __ ] you.
I'm speaking to some women I met yesterday
when I was in Birmingham with you. [ __ ]
>> no. But ghosting, the thing is if if a
woman ever does anything to me, I would
expect it. It's what I was saying to
Bonnie yesterday. I would I wouldn't
expect them to do anything less than
what they do. So I I wouldn't react like
that because I know what they do.
>> I'm done explaining to myself to a woman
that I've done all wrong. I didn't go
out called approaching last night. I was
already happy. I was happy. I was
smiling. I was having fun. I was talking
having fun with PJ talking [ __ ]
Talking about cold proion and all that with PJ
and then you say that we're pro. [ __ ] off.
>> Let's go keep everything's funny.
>> Let's go [ __ ] out of stage. Look, look.
Look at that. [ __ ]
>> pick Stitch up. >> What?
>> Um, pick up Stitch.
>> What? What? Pick up a stitch. Yeah. >> Uh, Stitch. >> No.
Bring it. What did you do?
No. Bring him back in the house.
>> Not bringing [ __ ] back in the house.
These are getting burnt, actually.
Why did you hurt Stitch? He's quiet now.
>> Yeah, I'm going to set him on fire as
well. Watch this now. He's going to come out.
>> Jesus Christ, Monty.
>> Don't Don't set my fire.
Hello, Stitch. You [ __ ] You're going bye-bye, mate.
>> No, Stitch. Yeah.
Am I moving in with Monty,
>> baby? Yeah, I am. Yeah. Why?
>> Monty, I think you need to get off YouTube, bro.
>> You want to play these games with me?
Mind games. Games say she would have
contacted me and all that. All the fun.
This shit's getting better, mate. Mind
playing games, mate.
>> What? You need to get off YouTube, mad.
>> Mind games.
>> I'm actually scared you're going to get
sectioned, bro. I can't lie.
>> Section. This ain't sectioning, mate.
This is showing nothing. I don't give a [ __ ] >> [ __ ]
>> You just get off YouTube, bro. just to
make it go up a lot quicker. So, there's
no turning back on this [ __ ] There's
actually no turning back. I've had
enough women [ __ ] me all the time.
I've done nothing to that woman. I've
not even cheated on her. I've done [ __ ]
all. Yeah, me and that [ __ ] fantastic
times. Fantastic times. Black people all
that lot. What? What? just so everything
goes off a little bit quicker. Yeah.
>> Seems like N's not cuz she's not ringing me.
Not like I wanted to. Anyways,
>> yeah, man.
>> I'm doing it. She thinks I'm talking
about, mate. [ __ ] clip this [ __ ]
>> How are you? How are you say you hung
over? M go over. >> Really?
>> There you go.
>> No, don't burn him, please. stop it.
All right, leave Stitch alone.
No, stop it, Monty.
So what pier? Oh,
>> I'm going to have to come to Birmingham
now and save him.
>> You want to save him? Yeah.
>> Yeah. I'm going to I'm going to have to
come to Birmingham now and do a welfare
check on your money. Keep us up.
>> [ __ ] hate women, man.
S. He's a good little He's a good little dog.
>> Leave S has done nothing to you, buddy.
>> Stitch is about to get stabbed, mate.
>> No, don't.
No, Monty. Please don't don't hurt Stitch.
>> Why not to you?
>> Why not? Yeah.
Are you getting treated like a pri of
women? I'm sick of women.
>> I'm sick of them.
>> I [ __ ] likely as
you can't be asked anymore PG with it.
I'm best off just burning it all.
He's best off just going
at the end of the day. This is how women
want to put with my my head and I'm
telling them the truth. I've done [ __ ]
all wrong. I've told no one nothing. N's
[ __ ] mind [ __ ] me. He's [ __ ] my
brain, mate. So you can [ __ ] off now. We
might actually burning it.
You can actually [ __ ] off.
I'm not playing games no more. >> Yeah.
>> Hey. Hey, PJ here. >> Leave. No,
>> I've done it as well. I burnt it. I've
burnt it as well. I've literally burnt
it. It's crisped at the back now. There you go.
>> Why did you do that to Stitch?
Why are you taking out a little stitch?
What the [ __ ]
Jesus Christ, bro.
>> Goodbye, [ __ ]
I can't believe that, bro. Why are you
hurting him? Wow.
Why did you take our own Stitch when he
would We were nothing but nice to you.
No, I'm going to have to kick you now
for that. I can't. You just killed
Stitch. What the [ __ ] No, I'm going to
have to kick you. I can't have that on
my channel. Poor little Stitch. Why
would you take out poor Stitch? He's
done nothing. I've been nice to you, Monty.
I'm going to have to kick you out for a
bit for that.
Why did you burn Stitch?
Why did you hurt little snitch?
Jesus Christ. It is the golf. It is the golf YouTube.
Oh my god. Monty. Jesus Christ.
I told him he needs to get off YouTube, bro.
You You need to get off of YouTube, bro.
I tried to give him advice yesterday. I
went I literally went all the way to
Birmingham to try and help him, but he didn't listen. Jeez.
Come on. Please get off YouTube. You're
starting to worry me.
>> Bye-bye, Stitch.
>> You're starting to worry me now.
>> What do you mean?
>> You're worrying anyone. I'm just sick of
getting played by women.
>> But it's money. We can find another
woman. It's not that big a deal.
>> Yeah, I know. It's not a big deal.
Really, it's not. We can find another
woman. I'll find another woman. Don't
worry about it. Don't worry about it. I
will do myself. Literally, I will do
that with Natalie's titty as well. I run
that for Natalie.
I don't give a [ __ ] anymore.
I'm sick of women hurting me.
Know what I mean? It's over when it gets
tough. But it's all right when they kick
me out of the hotel rooms, peeps, in it.
I've got to stay quiet.
So about when they shouting at me and
only why my mom said something to about
Natalie is cuz Natalie was shouting her
head off down the phone and said, "Oh
no, not enough of Kay shouting."
That's only what my mom was saying cuz
Natalie was shouting. My mom had on her phone
and my mom said, "No, not not enough
shouting. I can't handle shouting. My
head is [ __ ] with it. getting kicked
out of houses,
>> getting kicked out of hotels,
all that [ __ ]
>> Then then Natalie's going to think, "Oh
yeah, I haven't pissed him off."
It's obviously Natalie doesn't know me
then, does it?
>> Don't [ __ ] piss me off.
I ch away. I burnt the [ __ ] clothes
as well. Everything's gone now. Even
Stitch is gone.
>> Oh, not Stitch.
>> He's gone. He's normal Stitch.
>> Oh my god. Why did you do that? He done
nothing to you.
>> Stitch is gone now. Gone.
>> Oh no.
>> [ __ ] gone.
>> Why would you do that to our little Stitch?
>> Watch the TV when the TV comes. That's
getting smashed up as well. Watch when
the city comes. What? I got I'm going to
set that on fire as well. What? What? I
got her. I'm going to set all on fire
the [ __ ] What I've got her now.
>> M I think you need to chill out.
Everybody knows that you're a crazy [ __ ]
>> Oh, please, man.
>> You need to stop, bro.
>> How can I stop PJ? She's the one who run
me all the way down to [ __ ]
Birmingham. Yeah. I thought I was going
to be good with Natalie. Yeah. I thought
he was going to lash with Natalie. I
thought Natalie could handle arguing. At
the end of the day, yeah, you understand
getting on the phone to my [ __ ] mom,
but my mom likes Natalie. She told
Natalie she likes her.
She just doesn't. My mom doesn't want me
ringing up anymore. If the argument
breaks out, I need to deal with that on
my own. But at the end of the day,
Natalie needs to understand.
She can't keep kicking me out of every
single hotel. And it's not even that.
She rubs it in and says, "I pay for it.
All right. Spirits will get out.
So what will happen if we put two? Even
though we do put two for hotels, you're
still going to kick me out.
You know what I mean? So you
>> all right, man?
>> I'm sick of women, man. I'm just I'm
sick of it, mate. And I've told her the
truth. I've told her the actual truth. I
did not go out and approach anyone last
night. I said to Peter, "A girl touched
me ass." How the [ __ ]
she pass me?
>> She walked past me. You could have sleep
past me and touched me my ass by
accident. How the [ __ ]
I said PJs and Burgers took me to touch my ass.
You could have been by accident or
[ __ ] purpose, but then you get out.
Some girl touch your ass getting all
jealous about it. I want to even with
you. So it doesn't matter if I went out
last night and got a [ __ ] last night.
But I didn't because I weren't looking for it. >> Yeah.
>> She loved me. >> Yeah.
If she said if she barely loved me. Yeah.
Then then she'd be able to handle all
the all the arguing and all the
[ __ ] Yeah. I can handle it. I don't
want I don't want to get kicked out of
hotel rooms when I can just sit there
and just talk, sort arguments out. I
don't like shouting.
I hate it. It [ __ ] my head up. This is
what it does.
It brings my disability out. I'm not I
don't people. I need this place, but I'm
not getting one. I don't want one. I'm
quitting weed. So Natalie can try and
piss me up as much as she want. I'm
still quitting weed. So, I'm not doing
it for Natalie, peeps. I'm doing it for
myself. Oh, peeps. I'm going to be a big
[ __ ] mate. A big [ __ ]
He's got a [ __ ] And a lad as well. A
lad will [ __ ] always stand by you or
a lad will always fight a [ __ ] battle.
A strong [ __ ] lad. I can even pick
out of the York.
>> I'm just done fighting with him. I'm
done fighting with women, man. And I
just need N to listen and I haven't done
no [ __ ] wrong. I have no anyway. Stitch is dead. >> No,
I lost Stitch. He's my little friend.
>> Well, he's going. No, no, no. If you
want him back, you can. I just put him
in a cardboard box for you.
You know what, PJ? You can knock me out
of this room. Yeah. >> Really?
>> Yeah. You can have this shitty room. >> Okay.
Yeah. N I might as well tell everybody
what you done then. Is it? You know,
you've told everybody else your [ __ ] so
I might as well tell them what you've
done. Yeah. You can offer her room anyways. PJ. Thank you.
>> I don't really want to be in that room.
>> What? When are you coming to your TV?
I've texted a guy already for you. >> Saturday.
>> Well, you've got the bedroom. >> Saturday. Natalie,
>> I'm not going anywhere. I'm staying in
Birmingham. I'm going to be cold
approaching every single day in now in Birmingham.
So, I don't need to go. You got me here,
Natalie. That's your problem.
I'm going anyway.
>> What has she done then? What? What has she done?
>> Well, just stay where you are, PJ. Just
stay where you are. What has she done?
>> What's done? I bet you might as well
tell tell everyone what she's done. What
has she done?
>> I'm not saying [ __ ] Pet. I'm not saying
>> she said she said [ __ ] on Lord J, so why
not? Oh, no. No, she did. I'm not
listening to her level. I only why she's
done that. Yeah. Told everybody her
business. Yeah. Is because she didn't
want me putting her biscuits up there.
But I want to put that up there. Either
way, she's done that. Not even thinking.
I was even going to tell anybody she was homeless.
But it was all right. When I was in that
tent with her, when I still had a roof
over my head, I would always stand by
that through that either [ __ ] way.
But when she's arguing with me because
she's homeless and I'm with her,
confidentate in her and all that. And
I'm just getting shouted at and I'm
confident in her and all that. Look,
I know that she's going through a lot
cuz of these little clowns in this [ __ ] community.
We've done what they've done to her
and all that lot. And I'm the one
getting a blame for it. I'm not the one
sat there trolling the [ __ ] out of Natalie.
I'm not the one calling it.
They've all done it for years in this
community. They've all picked on Natalie
for years. Now, don't blame that on me.
Don't turn around and say you're
trolling Natalie because he's with me
when you all [ __ ] trolled her either way.
Yeah, PJ, you can have this room. Look,
I'm I'm taking my [ __ ] back out of it.
Hey, Nie. [ __ ] police as well. Yeah,
this was not a list. [ __ ]
Here you go. Not this. What can I not
give me that by the way? That'll be asked
in a bit. No. Yeah. What else?
Nothing else. Nothing else. That's it.
I'm getting out of this shitty room, mate.
I might just go back up there to be
honest. Up north. You might as well stay
where you are, Pia.
That woman [ __ ] ruined my life. She
made me get rid of my [ __ ] god. You
know, if I knew that Natalie would have
finished me like this yet, I would have
moved up here. I would have kept Diesel
instead where I should have [ __ ]
stayed where were
Why the [ __ ] did they get rid of my dog?
I tell you why people. Yeah, because I
thought Nie was the one.
>> Oh, bloody bad.
>> I thought she was the [ __ ] one.
>> Obviously, she's not the one. When she
was the one, she'd stand by me. No
matter [ __ ] we go through,
just like her, I will stand stand by you
through anything. You know, I could have
said, "No, Natalie, I'm not, you know,
[ __ ] that man."
And they have done nothing. S girl,
nothing. Not like her mom has. Her mom
docked her [ __ ] address. This is her
mom's fault. Why? She's been kicked out
of the house. That That's her mom's
fault, P. Yeah. If her mom didn't dox
her address, Yeah. Then then that is it.
They wouldn't have got us. Natalie would
have been still here now. Literally now.
>> You But you know at the start before all
of the madness, you found YouTube funny then it
has been on this long run [ __ ] me. So
I don't know why she's crying at me. Get
off YouTube when she's still on YouTube
watching him. That's pathetic to be
honest. You have money. You're still on
YouTube. You watching him?
>> What the [ __ ]
>> Do you know what I mean? Sat watching
him still. That's basically still being on YouTube.
>> I went on YouTube cuz I was angry. Angry
of the matter of fact kick me out. I'm
done anyways. [ __ ] it. She wants my love
gone for it. That's very easy. Very
Fair enough. Love's gone for it. It's [ __ ] gone.
Oh Monty, man. This has to stop all this [ __ ]
Think of it, buddy. You could be texting
a nice woman right now that you met
yesterday if you don't k.
>> One second. I cly cosmic kitty
slept with me to get back out of [ __ ]
Yeah, she really did. I see it. Yeah,
cuz if she really [ __ ] loved me like
she said she did. Yeah. She won't one
off and [ __ ] gets out.
You know, only what she have to say is
stop [ __ ] ringing your mom up of
every argument we are for [ __ ] sake.
Even though I just told my mom on the
phone that I need to stop doing that and
stop doing that.
You know what I mean? At the end of the
day, my head's [ __ ] off. Kaye
completely [ __ ] And now none of this
makes it 10 times worse by using me.
Getting me rid of my dog.
There you all go, Pete. You're all one.
I'm on my own now.
What have you done it?
Well, it don't really matter cuz you
don't really want because I can just go
back up north and be near my kids. I
don't really make a difference.
Yeah. PJ, just stay where you are. Yeah.
There's nothing here for me now anyways.
I might as well just walk up. Back up.
No. No. Anyway, so literally
I'm not waiting around for Natalie to
make a choices decisions
fought for that [ __ ]
I already come out of one bad relationship
went into a tent and then straight got
with Natalie and then left it for like a
couple about 10 months. month four or
something. Although we run out of four
month what what did Natalie do to upset
you just break up with you? Is it?
>> No, she keeps kicking me out of the
hotels. It's not even that. Every time
we argue or a lot of arguments, she
keeps on saying, "Oh, it's over." Oh,
it's over. Every argument it's over.
It's over. Every single argument it's
over. You can't handle arguments.
Every argument you have with her, oh,
it's over. That's it. is finished over.
It's like, "Oh, please. Please don't
don't don't why why what?" You know what
the [ __ ] If a woman can't handle a
[ __ ] argument. Yeah. And tell a man
it's over. That's pathetic.
Really [ __ ] pathetic. It just shows
now they can't handle content.
>> It's so weird, isn't it?
>> Of course it is. I would never finish
Natalie if we had the argument. Never. I
try and calm her the foot down.
>> Why do Why do you want to be with her?
Someone asked. That's a good question.
>> Why do I want to be with her? Oh, I
don't want to be with her. Not now. Not [ __ ] now.
>> Pushing me out later and whatever.
>> It was all night. It was all night.
>> It was all night, bro.
>> She's only the woman who stood [ __ ]
by me when I was in that [ __ ] tent.
the woman or the woman who's been there
and then Natalie gets kicked out on this
property and I go and spend my time in a
tent with Natalie when Natalie's home
she's not I money I know if you if you
did want uh if you did want Natalie G
back right I I I know how you could do it
>> I don't want her back [ __ ] off I'll let
>> if you well if you do ever want her back
just go out and get some black Get it? >> PJ,
you don't ever [ __ ] call N that again. Yeah,
>> I said black.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But I know what what
you're getting at. Get some black paint
for that. No, I know what what you're
getting at with that. >> Shagger.
>> No, I never said that. I said black.
>> Yeah. Well, black don't really matter,
but that's Natalie doesn't like blacks
anymore. He can't stand them. She hates
them. She She hates them. She She cannot
stand blacks anymore. Not what what they've done.
>> I was I was only trying to help you.
>> Yeah. No, Natalie can't stand blacks
anymore. She hates them. Can't stand him
because she's been through a lot with
him. Like literally been put down, shamed.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that's why I never get with
anyone off YouTube, bro.
>> And that's the thing. I said to myself,
I never get with one of them women, but
I did. I [ __ ] did.
>> Yeah, Monty, you was on about this all
night yesterday, is it? I had to listen
to you, bro.
>> Yeah, I'm I'm sorry. I'm I'm sorry, PJ.
>> No, no, it's not. It's But any advice I
gave you, you just ignored it in it. So,
>> I'm taking your advice, PJ. Believe me,
mate. I'm taking your advice. I'm just
[ __ ] pissed off. that I feel that are
being used by a woman again.
>> Well, well, I'm sure you're not the only one, Monty,
>> who's been used by a woman. I think everyone has.
>> I'm not being funny. Why is it my two
brothers who's got the best
relationships in the [ __ ] world? They
misses love them to [ __ ] pieces. One
of them's [ __ ] married and one of
them's [ __ ] married as well. I live
too. And then he got me [ __ ] in village.
>> Yeah, it's funny, wasn't it?
>> [ __ ] not funny, man. I just want to
settle down with one woman and be happy
and be happy. That's it.
I'm guess not the one for that len.
I might just go out with cosmic kitty
next for [ __ ] sake. Jesus, Monty.
>> No. Oh, yeah. That's another thing.
Monty, you thought I was talking to
Natalie yesterday cuz one of the numbers
that I got looked like Natalie. I was
like, "What the fuck?" No, bro. What?
>> Yeah. Yeah. One of the girls thought
like Natalie on the pitch. Yeah. A
little bit like that.
>> You was You was paranoid, man. I was
like, "What the [ __ ] You thought You
thought I was texting her?"
>> Yeah. We're going mad, mate. Like, what
the [ __ ] She's texting that for what
the [ __ ] Why you doing that?
>> Yeah, it wasn't even there. What the [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I know. I know. Yeah. So, you show
me the picture. Okay.
See, Natalie and [ __ ] This is what I
mean about Natalie. She doesn't
understand how much I love her. But I'm
not doing this anymore. I'm not fighting
for I'm I'm done. I'm I'm done for it.
Literally, if she thinks all that about
me, that I went out just to go and pull,
just to piss Natalie off. I didn't do
that at all. That wasn't intended to. I
went out to clear my head last night. I
was texting that all night. Are you
coming out with me and PJ? Come out with
me and PJ. I can even show you all the
textes. You know what? I'm going to show
you all the textes. Actually,
I was asking I was asking Natalie to
come out with me all that night. Literally,
>> I think you need to get off YouTube,
bro. For real.
>> I just don't need to, mate. I'm not
getting off YouTube. I don't need to.
Now, I ain't got no one. Who the [ __ ]
I'm going to talk to you? Walk around
the house and feel my fingers. What I'm
going to do now is shut the [ __ ] up
about that. How have you been, please? Yeah.
>> Okay. Starting from now. Yeah. Now,
what you up to?
>> Just chilling, bro.
>> Talking to some of the numbers that I got yesterday. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, man. That's good.
>> Have any of them talked to you yet? Yeah.
>> Yeah, I'm speaking to one. One of them's
talking about coming to London at some
point, so we'll see.
>> Oh, nice, nice, nice. What's going on? You lot.
>> You should have done some, bro. Yeah.
>> Oh, no. No. That's what I mean. I I I
wasn't going I wasn't called
approaching. I weren't doing any of that [ __ ]
>> I left it to you, me.
>> I didn't want to go. You know,
>> I was good at
>> I was good at in it.
>> Yeah. You're all right.
You saw me. How many did I do in the
first place? Like three in the first place.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Three numbers we got
in one night.
>> I I done one sober. I done one sober and
then the others we just I'm pissed.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Then then we got two flower seats.
>> I just g the girl the flower and just
[ __ ] up. AJ were like, "Here, can I
have your number?" Me and me and that
other Yeah. No. Yeah. I [ __ ] up, mate.
I [ __ ] up.
>> Yeah, man.
[ __ ] three quid was it for them flowers. Yeah, man.
>> What did I say to her? I said to her, I
can get them for a [ __ ] quid.
>> I gave one I gave one a flower. I gave
one a a rose coasting and then she said
she had a boyfriend. You reckon she did?
Probably not. And it probably not.
>> Probably even. That's what I mean. The
white rose what I had, I just gave it to
the girl and said, "Erate that." I
didn't even ask her a question or
nothing. I just tapped her and just give
her the flower. See you later. Not even
a chat. Not even a not even a boo. Did I
even Didn't I just dance with the flower
and just said here a mate?
>> No. Someone just gave me a flower. I
didn't I didn't buy it. Someone just
gave me it. So I thought [ __ ] it.
>> I just tried it. I just tried it for the
lows, bro. I'm not a s.
>> No, it was a flower. It was like a rose.
It was just a rose they gave me.
>> Yeah, it was a rose.
>> Not a flower. So I just thought, "Fuck
it. I'm I'm not a s, bro.
Monty's a s. I'm not a s.
>> I'm not a s.
If I was a s, I would have [ __ ] took
the prices down.
>> No, but you gave them free at the end of it.
>> So you don't think that you're s Monty? >> No,
I'm special needed, mate. Special needed
>> because Monty Monty won't come to London.
I come to London, but you don't go to
pull in London.
>> Yeah, Birmingham's not the easiest
either. It's still quite difficult, bro.
>> I don't even know cuz I weren't even
trying last night.
>> Well, I [ __ ] I was.
>> Yeah, you were. I weren't. I was just
watching you on some of them and then I
went over and asked for you with some of
them and that's it. I never I had even
called approaching on a woman that night. M
>> yeah we're the we're the same height in it.
>> I am just a little bit titty a little
bit bigger than you.
>> I'm just a little bit little bit taller.
>> 0.1 in.
>> PJ didn't get in a club cuz he had terrain on
>> Yeah. You don't get Oh yeah, that's
another thing you don't get in London.
You can wear club You can wear trainers
in clubs in London, bro. This is how you
know in Birmingham they're just wannabes
because in London Yeah. Even if you wear
trainers like normal trainers, they let
you in. You don't need to wear shoes in
any club in London. Not Not most of
them. No, you don't. I swear to God, not
most of them, bro.
>> Look at Look, we got into remember that in Birmingham
they were saying to me and Monty. Yeah,
they were saying to me and Monty. Yeah.
Uh that one second Monty that we can't
come in because we need a group of
girls. Never heard that in my life in
London. And then they said, "Oh, you
can't wear trainers." Even though they
were normal trainers. Never heard that
in my life in London. Where in London
you don't get none of that.
>> It's not. And then about [ __ ] as
well. Another thing. >> Yeah.
>> I was asking Natalie all last night to
come out with us with me and PJ last
night. I was texting her all night last
night. Come out with me and PJ. Come on.
Come for a drink. Come on. Let's go for >> London.
>> No. Why don't you
>> What What do you prefer, Ghost? London
or Birmingham? I prefer London.
>> If that is watching, go and look at your
Texas now. Sorry. Not bringing her up
>> You just brought her up again.
>> Yeah, because I'm telling N to look at
her Texas from last night when he was
asking her to come to the pub. come for
some drinks with us. And that's what I
were doing, but no. Okay.
I wanted her to come out with us last
night. I literally wanted Natalie to
come out for some drinks with us all
night last night, but she didn't.
>> No, I I prefer London because they Yeah,
but I remember I had that problem in
Birmingham last time. Um you need to um
you can't you need to wear shoes,
which in London you don't get that
anywhere in London.
I prefer London me.
You're saying that London's cheaper, but
bro, Birmingham's cheaper. Not by much.
Birmingham's expensive, it Monty. >> What?
>> I bought two Guinnesses and two shots.
It was £22.
>> Well, well, well, actually. Well, actually
it is a lot cheaper because
I bought um
two shots for6 pound.
So it is a still
it's still getting there though. Expensive.
Yeah. Two shots six pound bargain, bro.
We got two shots for6. That's a bargain
to be honest.
We got [ __ ] didn't we, bro?
>> Yeah, we did, didn't we? Hey, there we
go. Let's go and get them [ __ ] shorts
and t-shirt back in. Yeah, I'm not that
[ __ ] criminal. Well, st cruel. He's gone.
>> I can't believe you killed Stitch.
>> What do you mean?
>> You killed Stitch. You can't.
>> I killed him.
Yeah, I I I prefer London and Birmingham
though for different reasons.
Maybe because I'm from London, but I don't know.
>> No, I didn't get pissed off one pine. It
went one pine. I got pissed off. We were
drinking shots all night.
>> I can't believe you you killed Stitch, though.
PJ, I'm not being funny yet. When a
woman plays with your head like that, yeah,
what the [ __ ] am I supposed to do? You
know, I won that. I did like that today.
I wanted her.
So, I burnt it.
I won it and I burnt it.
I bought USA a nice steak meal. Did you um what?
>> No, we didn't. We didn't shag them.
>> Shag it.
>> I didn't shag them.
>> Oh, do you know what? We should run PJ.
We should have done. We should have
done. We should have done. We should
have. I'm joking. [ __ ] that. I'm being a
prick now. Yeah. I need to stop being a prick, brother.
Monty, you're you're beginning to sound
like you're from Birmingham now.
>> What do you mean?
>> You're picking up the accent.
>> What? The Birmingham accent? >> Yeah.
>> I'm a [ __ ]
>> Yeah, you are.
>> What? I'm turning Birmingham now, am I?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> I haven't got the Birmingham actually. You do.
>> Do I [ __ ]
>> Someone said yesterday that I sounded
like I was from Yorkshire. I was like,
are you mad?
>> I sound like I'm from Yorkshire. Are you
mad, bro? I don't sound nothing like [ __ ] Yorkshire.
>> There was only one woman at the bar.
>> I'm a [ __ ] Londoner.
>> That woman at the bar quapping my head
because of a bald tapping it.
>> Yeah. And she was touching the other
guy's head as well. She didn't want me.
>> Yeah. No. No.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Poor man.
>> Because she had her PJ. She wanted a man
with nowhere. But nah, she was just st
she just started touching me. Started
stroking it for no reason.
>> God bless you.
>> I didn't move. I didn't move. I like it.
I do it.
>> I think next time we go out yet, we
should invite Timmy just for a drink.
>> I'm going over Timmy out now. see me.
You want to meet me now?
>> No, I'm [ __ ] not. I'm from [ __ ] London, mate.
>> Born in red London.
That's me, matey.
Hate the accent. It's [ __ ] horrible.
I hate that G's accent, too.
I'm not going to leave her alone now.
Anyways, I'm just going to leave her alone.
If she thinks all that about me, then it
just shows what she really thinks of me really. So,
>> I think you should meet up with with long legs.
>> You stop bringing him up. That's why you
keep him going for you. That's why he
keeps on coming on your panel all the
time cuz you talk about him.
>> Stop bringing him up. Your psychic fancy.
>> He's the [ __ ] reason.
>> I I I like I said, I met him through you. So,
>> no, you didn't meet him through me. You
met him through the community on PlayStation.
>> YouTube's mates.
>> I've never been No, I've never been
Sean's mate. Never. I got introduced to
Sean through [ __ ] Dean.
Dean introduced me to him.
I' I've never been Sean's mate. I don't like pedile.
He's Elvis Presley [ __ ] in it.
>> He sits there [ __ ] with Elvis Presley
all over his [ __ ] wall.
I'll be right now [ __ ] his friends
song where he sings about a kid.
>> He's not he's not that bad. He just
needs to get laid.
>> No, he sh sp he sh spast sticks. He does.
>> He never sag nothing.
>> Don't be asked any women p the [ __ ] [ __ ] mate.
>> I remember I told you about the one
yesterday from America. You laughed,
didn't it? You thought it was funny. At least
she told Lord Yeah, that was a good
shagger. Lord, she did. She did sound
like that was a good shagger.
Don't lie. She's not going to get
someone like me again. She's not.
Someone so experimented in bed
apartment. She knows how experimented
they have. She knows how good I'm in bed
as well with my tongue included. I'm
[ __ ] the expert with my tongue. Okay, now
>> too much information.
>> Natalie, come with my tongue.
>> All right, so Stephen, how would you put
60 on the on the bet and return how much? 220
220 isn't it?
>> It's never going to get a better [ __ ]
me anyway. Let's put it that way.
>> It's not even that. I always finish it
off even before I finish myself off.
Always finish her off first.
>> What do you mean?
>> Always make to come first.
>> Too much information. It's disgusting.
Too much [ __ ] information
>> and then going down where the cum's
coming out of and licking it.
level. My base is me. I need
a l crack as well. Her [ __ ] lit that too.
No chatting [ __ ]
[ __ ] done everything with N. But
hey, mind you, buddy.
Okay, now I'm leaving that now. They rip
whip me and all that [ __ ] man. [ __ ] awesome.
I'm not talking about my sex life now.
[ __ ] it. I'm done.
I'm done. I'm proud of that. That That
was all right, though.
I've even licked her [ __ ] armpits, mate.
L your armpits and belly button and
everything, mate. And everything.
>> Sorry, I was doing something, bro.
Yeah, I bet you wish you had more in it
now. It um
>> Steven Howard,
>> what what did you bet on? What company
was it? I I don't mind with um what book
what bookies did you do your bet? Oh,
>> okay. P.
Um, probably not for a few weeks to be
honest. Ghost then
maybe two weeks.
>> PJ, I told you that [ __ ] some birds
like bald men. Anyways, didn't I? I told
you that some birds like bald bald men.
Some women like men with bald hair. >> Yeah.
You used to laugh at Little Britain.
>> Oh, him in a wheelchair. Yeah.
>> Yes. That's Timmy in it.
>> No, I was going to say that would cost
me K. No, I'm joking. K. I'm only
That was a joke.
>> Yeah. Hey, I remember when you used to
laugh at them people with Tourette's.
>> No, I've never laughed at people with Tourette's.
You used to.
>> Oh man, I just need a woman who
appreciates me, man.
>> Are you Are you Are you doing a bet on
Tuesday? Um, ghosting.
I still need to collect my winnings,
bro. I'll do it tomorrow when I go into town.
>> Yeah. No, there's no point moving your
PJ. I'm just might just go back up north
my mom's go back in the tent again make
my own [ __ ] house. No people when
when Oh [ __ ] Don't worry.
Let me just shut the [ __ ] up. PJ, just
give me a slap. PJ. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I might do
I might just I might do a 10 pound one.
I'm I'm [ __ ] I don't even take weed
anymore. I don't even take cocaine
anymore. I don't do any of that [ __ ]
I really don't. I'm not
>> I hate cocaine.
>> My name's on this property. I don't have
to leave this property. I can stay here.
>> Monty, what did I stink in real life?
>> No. Did you?
>> I smelt nice in it.
>> I smelt nice, didn't I?
>> Yeah. Did I as well?
>> Did I smell nice though? Did I? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It smelt nice.
>> After shave in it. >> Yeah.
>> I never listen. Yeah. If I go back to
the tent, I won't be in a tent. You know
when you was all like, "Oh, you wanted
Natalie to live in a tent." I didn't
want Natalie to live in a tent at all.
At all. what it was. [ __ ] Natalie
couldn't get a roof over her head.
Everyone was turning her down for a roof
over it. So, she only had one more
option. Well, two options. Ring one more place
or Yeah, especially the teddy as well. I
can't believe you burnt Stitch. It's so
hard to win them toys and them grabbing machines.
It's so hard to win them. I was trying
to I was trying to win Nemo the other
week. Ghost. I put 10 pound for it.
Nowhere near. I was trying to win Nemo
from finding Nemo. Couldn't get
>> I'm good on the machines though. That's
the thing. I can win them all again. I
can just get a new one for her. But I
don't think we're going to get back
together. I don't know. I've not done
nothing to Natalie. Nothing at all. Go live.
>> Who you want about get it? Go live. Who
who you want to about get it?
I don't do YouTube no more, K. I only
join people's panels. That's it.
>> What? Hey, why did you quit YouTube again?
>> What? What's so fascinating about it, PJ? >> Nothing.
>> You know what? I might I just might
chill with Cosmic Kitty, do some [ __ ]
ghost [ __ ] hunting videos and [ __ ]
>> Yeah. What? No, but seriously, what why
was the main reason you quit though?
>> I quit for Natalie. I quit. Me and
Natalie were quitting together, but I
went back on YouTube being a prick
at the hotel and everyone at about the
hotel, but I said we was in Manchester,
so everybody would have been ringing up Manchester, not
>> I don't want to go to your house.
Literally, I really don't want to go to
your house. That I'm okay on that one.
I'm [ __ ] fine on that. Literally, I
definitely 100% do not want to go back to yours.
You know, was calling me skin earlier.
He was trying to call me skin. Funny
>> D. You're the one in You're the one
invited me to your house. You're the one
I asked you if if I could come to your
apartment. You said Yeah. You know, you
knew your your apartment was a [ __ ] hole. >> Why?
>> Why is literally no obsessed with money
and skin people? It's weird. Why?
>> Because a lot of people are after money
in this community. I'm not I've got
money. I don't need money. I [ __ ] I'm
I'm I'm just going to cancel all this
[ __ ] to be honest with you. This be everything.
>> I'm saying why is he calling me skin?
Obviously I'm not skin, bro.
>> Is it a fake kitty? Yeah.
>> No. L calls me it.
>> No. No. Go check if that's a fake kitty. PJ.
>> Yeah, it is.
Okay, it's a fake one. Sorry. They cost
me kit to the real one.
>> Like Monty, how can they call anyone
skin? They don't know what people have.
>> I don't know. [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but they don't know how much
people have. So, how can they say that?
>> They call people skip. It's cuz they
skip the sales. PJs. Just wick it out.
Work it out.
>> Yeah, but it's every day. It's boring, bro. like
>> you think about it. Yeah. Lord Yeah.
doesn't sign on and doesn't do any of
that because that's why he got his
PayPal up every single day to get money
off these clowns. A bit like [ __ ] um
Belly and the rest of them. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? But you can report
them. You can report them for that.
>> You can report them for making money off
YouTube when you're not really supposed
to be. winning really using proper content.
>> I got banned. I got banned for it. I
couldn't even go on any account. Every
single account I made got banned
straight away off YouTube because of money laundering.
>> Hope you'll be all right. I hope you'll
be all right for them two weeks though, man.
>> What? Two weeks.
>> Until you get paid again. Is it?
>> Yeah. I've got burgers downstairs. Got
[ __ ] tons of burgers. So I just met some
burgers so I get paid. Do you know what?
I left myself. Do you know what? I
shouldn't have done that. I shouldn't
have done that. But I did. I did. Okay.
Now else me and Natalie would have had
no food, no nothing, no electric or
nothing. I spent my money all on taxes
and takeaways that day. So I couldn't
even put food in my in the freezers. I
couldn't do any of that [ __ ] Then
they only had 20 quid. I I give PBA the
rest of the money out of my pocket. I
only had 20 quid left and that was to do
that would last me until I get paid.
>> Yeah. You have 20 for You have 20 pound
for two weeks, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Two weeks. 20 quid to last me two [ __ ] weeks.
>> That's mad.
>> I managed though. I manage.
>> Don't forget
I haven't been eating proper law. This
is the [ __ ] thing. I haven't for days
on end, mate. I promise you that now.
Look at this. Look at this. I'm even chatting [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but 20 for two week. That's mad
though, is it?
>> Yeah. Do you want to see? So, I show you
what I actually get with 20 quid.
>> It's less than It's less than It's less
than two pound a day. That's less than
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I show you now what
what I'm eating. I sure you know.
I sure you know what what I got. >> Jesus.
>> Sure you know.
>> I got these to last me.
>> I got leg. >> Yeah,
>> that burgers just to last me a big ass
box of them though.
Just a [ __ ] last minute. I had to be
get the muffins as well. So, I'm just
gonna have like one body a day. This is
[ __ ] [ __ ] up, man. But I hate women, man.
>> What about when I was there? >> What?
>> It's all right when he had Natalie's
[ __ ] back and all that though.
[ __ ] camping out with her, helping
her out. Not like when was homeless.
>> What? It's like It's like she's left you
with [ __ ] all it
>> basically. Yeah.
It's not even that. Look at that PJ.
>> Okay. Look at that. Skinny
fing that one.
>> You think it's funny?
>> I don't think it's funny. I don't think
it's funny one little [ __ ] bit.
I haven't been eating.
or nothing like that. I'm just going
like [ __ ] fell skinniness now. I'm
just gone like [ __ ] fell 420 and if
that leave her to it. >> Yeah,
>> that's what I'm saying. Leave her to it.
If she wants to be a prick and [ __ ]
just dump me. She's the one who got me
in Birmingham and just dumped me right
on my ass.
Bang out on my behalf. That's the worst
thing anyone could ever do. Yeah.
>> You know what I mean?
Every time I went out and got myself
some monsters, they always got us some
Red Bulls. And I don't mean I don't mean
just one Red Bull. I got a crate of
them. Whole crates of them. Every time I got
>> a belly like that. Nah, not really, bro.
My belly is getting fat. Too much takeaways.
>> Too much takeaways.
That That was nice though. last night
that you know when you had nothing to
eat for days and then you just have
something to eat and it's appreciating that.
>> Yeah, I bought you I bought Monty me and
Monty a breakfast omelette and and a
hash brown and some coke.
>> It was nice.
>> That breakfast place is nice in Birmingham, man.
I'm not even slagging that that off to
be honest with you. I'm just saying the
truth. If they can do to me, I don't
know what to do, mate. See,
you used to think this curly was a lot.
>> [ __ ] I got a question for you. You're
sat there, right? Crying on a panel,
Crazy little sad little [ __ ] rat.
Let me ask a question. Who ask yourself
a question? Why do you sh granny's? Why
can't you Why do you [ __ ] jump on my
life? So what's rise?
You [ __ ] [ __ ] is a rat.
Don't concentrate on your own [ __ ]
life instead of mine.
[ __ ] mongos, mate. Am
I your best friend?
>> You're my best friend.
>> I wanted Natalie as a best friend. I
wanted her in my life.
>> But now you've got Peter Belly.
Be with you. I don't have no one, mate.
I don't have anyone.
>> I've only got myself in this world to be
honest with you. And you know what?
You blast that.
Oh, I think delete my video on Tik Tok
now. People are liking me crying over a
woman on Tik Tok now.
You know what? I just might go and meet
me and get [ __ ] late tonight.
>> You might as well.
>> Yeah. Go and meet me and go get myself
[ __ ] late tonight. Yeah. [ __ ] off.
Not a chance.
Even if it's all credit. Let's find out
when I get paid.
Not that long now. Anyways,
your next payment
is the 17th of
what's a uh >> August. >> Yeah.
>> A U G U S T. August. Yeah.
So, when's that then?
>> It's the 17th of August.
>> What is it now?
>> What do you mean is it now? Is it like two weeks?
>> It's in two weeks.
>> Is it now? Funny bastard.
>> Right. She can't even get anyone. You
[ __ ] see look like quack.
>> Two weeks is nothing, is it?
>> Two weeks. No, it's not really. What?
The seven days in a week. >> Yeah.
>> So, I get seven days over with. Get
another seven days over with. I can just
[ __ ] I've got a choice. Stay here or
[ __ ] [ __ ] up back up north.
I'm not crying over her normal day. I'm
not doing it. I'm not doing it. You want
to be a prick with me? Let her be a
prick with me. She thinks I went out
last night to go and cold approach other
women either. Well, we're single. So, so
it doesn't matter either way if I went
out to cold approach or not really when
I was single. He's the one who [ __ ]
finished me. Or does she expect me to
sit there on you [ __ ] wait for her?
Is that what she wants me to do? Wait
for her until she's ready to jump and
talk to me. How the [ __ ] do I know what
a woman wants when they don't even tell
you what they want to it? >> Yep.
>> You know what I mean? So obviously I'm
going to [ __ ] do whatever I'm going
to do because I don't know what Nat wanted.
I knew it was over and I was waiting
weeks and weeks for her.
Man, I pull. I can't pull. That's the
thing. I can
I might just go out with cost me kitty next
>> What do you mean I should move to
London? I live in London, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] I live in London.
>> I might go out with
No, they're ugly anyway. won't go out
with ugly people again, ever again. To
be honest with you, I'm not even going
to go for a [ __ ] bodybird.
>> Sorry, PJ. Sorry, buddy.
You know what, PJ? Let [ __ ]
bit longer, mate. And pulled some vers
to be honest. If I knew this was going
to happen now, I want to go [ __ ]
further if I knew that this was going to happen.
You kept talking about Natalie, in it
>> all night last night. Yeah. All night
last night. All they were talking about
was Natalie. Natalie. Natalie. All night
last night. I didn't go out cold approaching anyone.
And for the woman slapping me ass
whatever happened, she didn't slap my
ass on purpose. I don't think she walked past me.
She must have just slid past me because
I was in in between a ch that kind of
thing. Yeah. Entrance off the door. I
was basically blocking the entrance off.
So she sleep past me. Touched me ass.
The top PJ. She just touched me ass.
She just sleep past me. That's all. Cuz
if you think about it, the woman who
touched me ass, you would have [ __ ]
chatted to me, wouldn't she? But she
didn't. She walked off. So she was
walking out the building straight past
me, cross me ass by accident.
You're crazy, bro.
So, when are these [ __ ] going to stop repeating them?
>> I will. Yeah, next one's going to be
[ __ ] lovely and slim blown nice ass
body. I swear I What? What? What?
Natalie and that think what they want
about me. What's what I pull next. >> Okay.
>> What's depressing me? I swallow.
>> What about depressing?
>> Yeah, I wasn't lying.
Oh, why did you say yesterday I didn't
get a hand job? Yes, I did. Monty,
>> you didn't
>> You wasn't You wasn't with us the whole time.
>> No, I weren't with you the old time. No,
>> you were. We was We was alone for five
five minutes when you was talking to the other one.
>> Yeah, I know you were.
Huh? Where did you go? You used to
anyways. We were just sat there waiting.
>> Just went around the corner. Just got a
hand job and a kiss.
>> A kiss.
>> I didn't get any of that. I didn't get
>> That girl's old enough.
>> Yeah. Five minute hand job. Anyways, why
are you people so obsessed anyways on
YouTube? Five minute job.
Anyways, why are you so obsessed as well?
Didn't Monty didn't LJ lie about um
[ __ ] Izzy and [ __ ]
>> Yeah, he's a he's a prick every time.
>> Why? Hold on a minute. Hold on a minute.
They said they don't like liars. Yeah.
>> So why don't they say anything when L J
lies? Cuz they won't they won't they
won't say [ __ ] to the people who they like.
>> Yeah, they're weirdos.
>> They won't say [ __ ] to the people who
they like. They only say [ __ ] to the
people who they don't like.
>> I'm not a liar. I don't lie about
anything. That has left you with [ __ ] all [ __ ]
>> It is pretty bad. 20 for two weeks. [ __ ]
That's bad, is it?
Hopefully you don't die.
>> Oh yeah, with me.
>> PJ, have I lied about anything from last night? >> Yeah.
>> What have I lied about?
>> You didn't tell anyone that you was
kissing a man.
>> Oh, okay. That were you like when we're kissing?
>> [ __ ] is a snake. Don't trust him, PJ.
>> Oh, am I a snake? In what way? Am I a
snake? PJ's knew me a lot longer than
you. I've never snaked on PJ. You're clowns.
Never ever sn
I've never turned to PJ under anything.
I've never done anything really to PJ. I
even done anything to Natalie.
That's the [ __ ] funny thing about it. >> Yeah,
>> really. I haven't. Literally, I've done [ __ ]
She aimed it because it got hard. [Music]
>> Yeah, you are a snake though. Sometimes
>> in what way?
>> Just sometimes in it.
>> I'm not a snake. I'm a [ __ ] What? In
what way? In what way am I a snake? What
do you mean?
You tried saying I lied about getting a
hand job and I didn't.
>> You just Well, you just said you didn't.
>> And it was actually you that said it as well.
>> Yeah, it was me who made it up.
>> It wasn't made up.
>> They were real.
>> You should ask.
How can I ask Rice for dating tips?
>> He's a [ __ ] virgin. He's heard cobwebs.
>> Money. Would you say most of the people
in this community are virgins?
>> Yeah, a lot of them are. >> Yeah.
Monty, do you remember same atmosphere?
>> Always same atmosphere.
>> It would always be.
>> To be honest with you, I don't know why
I actually went out with Natalie to be
honest with you. I don't really know.
[ __ ] it. It just say I don't even know
why I went out with her.
>> Cuz you wanted a little mini.
>> No, I did like Natalie. I did really
like her. I still
I don't know.
She just runs off when it gets hard,
mate. Can't do that. I deal with women like that.
Save me, Grezy.
>> You need save him. PJ,
>> save me.
Now he has big tits. Yeah. So what?
They're not that big. They're not
They're just normal regular size tits.
They're not big ass tits.
They're just normal regular size.
They're not big at all. They're just
normal size tits.
Imagine even a girl you groomed for a toothless brmy.
Yeah. USA is he has some big tits.
I'm a sucking on them me
my milk supply it greasy
vitamins and nutrients
I'm not trying to prove anything in the
motor woman me PG you can you can but I'm not
mean I can
you're the one that keeps going on about
I can't stop talking about net.
>> Yeah, I know. >> Okay,
>> Greavves, can you give Monty some
advice, please? You seem to talk a lot
of sense. Could you give him some advice?
>> You know what? I might go outside and
make a buddy outside the PJ in it.
[ __ ] chill out and [ __ ] a boy outside.
>> You know what I mean? You know what I
might do? I'll make a little bit of
content on PJ for him.
>> What's your advice to Monty?
>> Sit back and have a wank and chill out.
I can't even read the comments anyways.
Even if it does give me advice, no
advice to give either way. When I've
told Natalie the honest truth, you know
what I mean? It's up to Natalie what she
wants to believe or not. If she thinks
I'm chatting [ __ ] that think I'm
chatting [ __ ] Make sure there's no
advice to give me really when I'm told
Natalie the honest truth. I haven't done
[ __ ] all. I haven't even called approached anybody.
I was talking to people. Yeah, I'm
allowed to talk to people. That's not a
crime. I've never cheated on that.
>> And even if I did get even if I did get
with someone last night, that's none of
that business. I wasn't going out with
Nat last night.
So that's none of N's business when
she's leaving me angry. said Grievy said
Grievy said get her gone. She was
obviously messing you about she can go
days if she can go days say nothing to
you but then pipes up and accuse you of
cold approach and touch touching ass it
proves she's no good.
>> Yeah. No, no, you got that right there,
buddy. You're literally that. I agree on
that 100%. Like she would learn she
would learn for three days. Listen to
this. Yeah. This is what what what you
call man. Yeah. I already had a roof
over me head. This house here, but I
mean now. Yeah. Look, Natalie's whole
[ __ ] bed there. Yeah. Obviously, you
can't see. Yeah. But yeah, I could have
stayed here and left Natalie in the
tent. I could have stayed in the tent
three days like she said with me. Three
days in the tent. She stayed three days.
I didn't. I stayed there with her until
she got a roof over her head. >> Yeah.
>> I stayed, you know what I mean? I stayed
with her until she got a roof over her
head. I did not leave her sight. All the
time I left her sight is to come home to
charge this up. >> Yeah.
>> She had a screen PJ.
>> What's that?
>> I I used to go I went home to charge
this up. So, we got electric all the
time. Yeah. This is where all my money
went. Literally, this is where all my
money went on coming back here, charging
this shitty light up
all the time so we can charge our phones
up. We had solo panels and all that
going. Look at all my survival gear,
peeps. Look, I I stopped buyer.
Look at this [ __ ]
[ __ ] peeps. [ __ ] [ __ ]
solo panel [ __ ] lights.
solar panel lighting [ __ ]
another solar panel [ __ ] big thing here
and that's a phone charger that is a
phone charger that charges up your
phones so you don't so I don't need
electric with this you know
so I was with Natal with her all [ __ ]
that time no [ __ ] around or nothing
going home coming back to N coming or
we're about to nap. I never left this site.
>> Nice handbag. That was Natalie's bag.
No, that's just my bag. What? I just put
all my survival [ __ ] in like my cooker,
my lights, and everything else like that
in that bag.
That's what I mean. That's what I mean.
Women don't I don't get women why they
leave me with the bags as well. I've got
K's old [ __ ]
That's Kis old one suitcase. That's K's
old suitcase. Yeah. And now I've got
[ __ ] N's old [ __ ] bag.
What the [ __ ]
Use in a bag.
I don't know what to do with myself,
buddy. No, he's right. He's actually
right on that because I was texting
Natalie. Yeah. He's actually right on
that question what he g me. Yeah,
because if Natalie did cur Yeah. She
won't have left this long. And then as
soon as she found out that I was out
last night with PJ, I was texting K I
mean Natalie last night. I was telling
her to come out with me and PJ. I can
show you that text now actually.
Okay, I'll show you that text that I was
asking her to come out last night with
me and PJ,
but she's decided to stay there.
And then he chat [ __ ] saying that I went
out cold approaching yesterday.
Grezy USA Izzy was my mama in it.
I'm going to find this way text at the
the [ __ ] pub. Did you come for a
drink? One sec yesterday. Natalie.
Natalie. Here we go.
>> How do you know she's my mommy? Grezy.
>> Here we go people. So if Natalie is
saying that that that I would called
approaching last night. Yeah. So what
does that say? Peep. It's right there.
Oh, you can't see it. Right there. What
does that say right there? Are you
I I am meeting PJ now.
>> She only likes She only likes to black.
>> Come. She don't like blacks anymore. PJ,
you don't like blacks? No, that's the
comment. I never said it.
>> You don't like blacks anymore. cuz he's
done with the blacks.
>> Yeah, I I was reading the comment.
>> I stick for Natalie on that. I will do.
She's not into black.
>> How do you know USA is is my mommy? Greavvesy.
>> Does she look like me?
Same here, same eyes, isn't it?
>> Yeah. No, he's right. She played that
game well. Like got me all the way to
Birmingham. But it's not like she put
herself up as well because now she's had
to leave her own [ __ ] property into
another one. But does she look like me? Grezy. >> Hey.
>> Oh, someone.
Do you remember Grezy? Tam is your dada?
Someone said that to me. Money. If she
dated another bloke, would you get
jealous or mad?
>> I get mad. I go angry. I be [ __ ]
pissed off. I don't give a [ __ ] about no
bed going out with anyone else.
But I've got a [ __ ] strong feelings
for Natalie and very strong feelings.
>> I never will.
>> Was it? Yeah, I hate the Birmingham
accent. Birmingham accent's the worst.
>> Yeah. Go on. What were you going to say? The accent.
>> Yeah, she looks like me. Greavves.
Greasy. The hair and the eyes. Isn't it?
She's definitely my my mama.
She had me at hospital. Feel
like breaking someone's jaw. BPJ.
>> Oh, best.
>> Can I break your jaw? Yeah.
>> K is up at Rice's. What do you mean?
>> Kelly is not even at rises, you [ __ ]
I don't even [ __ ] fancy car anyway.
So, good luck on that one.
>> Who's this?
>> Hello, big nose. You know, shut yourself talking
like a prick. Bye-bye, skin virgin.
Who's that sh
>> still up? Still obsessed with me.
>> Go s out your ugly rat face. You balding ugly bastard.
>> I'm saying stop stalking men on YouTube.
>> You [ __ ] virgin. He is obsessed with me, bro.
>> Yeah, cuz you want to talk about
obsessed, bro. You want You want to talk
about obsessed? This virgin is obsessed with me.
Look. [ __ ] making London Taylor
accounts. He's obsessed, bro. That's the
definition of obsession.
>> This he's a [ __ ] weasel, boy. Won't
meet you. I'd rather ring the police.
>> [ __ ] games.
>> Ring just let him up then record him.
Then ring the police then get him done.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I've I've already I've
already done it. I've already been doing
it, bro. I've been keeping on it as well.
>> Yeah. Keep on it. The man will get [ __ ]
for it. It go it come back on him
because he's coming in harassing you.
But if you sat there bling him up, it's
not going to look good on you either.
>> Yeah, I've already got enough I've got
even more than enough as well anyways
that I've sent them. So >> yeah,
>> anyways, moving on.
Um, so yeah, back to Natalie.
>> Back to Natalie. No, listen to this.
Yeah, I run my mom up. Yeah, so my mom
So not like today. I hung her up today
when I was on the phone to Natalie. Not
for my mom. Just so my mom could talk
and I like so my mom could tell Natalie
she likes her cuz my mom likes Natalie.
That's all my mom my mom wanted to talk to her
but she weren't even picking up the
phone to my mom. My mom weren't even
going to have a go like she only wanted
to talk to her. She wants to talk to
her. That's it. She wanted to get to
know Nat and talk to her like she's been
trying to but she my mom texts me saying
she she's not even not picking up.
My mom wants to talk to her and all that
look to tell her and all that but
that she's you know
she's got people who like her. She's got
people who want to multi KKK.
What does that comment say?
I'm going to tell LT the Virgin's making
fake accounts of you. Beware.
>> That's who it was.
>> No, the bottom one up top above the
bottom text. The one with the red
appetite. Multi KK. Never
did. What did it say? What's he saying?
I'm trying to text someone. Hold on.
>> Yeah. No, that's fine. I'll read it
myself. I got two phones.
I've lost the other phone now as well.
Not can't even
get my mothering phone out.
I guess that's what happens when you've
been starved all your life. Starveled
all your life by your mom. I guess
>> I hurt you.
>> To be honest with you, I ain't even hurt Natalie.
I think she was a player to be honest
with you. Getting over and done with
being with him. Get rid of him.
I think that's the reason. I never see
what your guy was saying. Anyway, PJ,
I [ __ ] love you, PJ.
>> Yeah, man.
>> Steven Howard, Pip King, M number two,
never dated Black Monty.
Why the [ __ ] did you have to introduce
me to this virgin man?
>> I didn't introduce you to him.
>> Smell your
>> You [ __ ] my life up, bro.
>> King number two.
>> I fought your life up. You're the one
who was Sean's mate. You're the one who
went to Sean. I told you about him. I
warned you about him. But you weren't
listening to me. You were like, "No,
he's a good lad. He's all right. He's
all right." I told you he's a [ __ ] weirdo.
I did tell you he's a [ __ ] muppet.
I did say that PJ ago
>> like on PlayStation and we're talking to him's channel.
>> Extraordinary. Extraordinary. Something
like that. Extraordinary.
That's Vice's channel. Extraordinary.
You know, do you know Timmy's channel?
>> Mad World.
>> How do you remember it?
>> It's not hard. It's hard what Timmy can [ __ ] spell. [Music]
I think they were playing it to be
honest with you. It makes sense.
I try once she get me to Birmingham.
Yeah. Then just [ __ ] off and it gets a little argument.
It weren't even the argument. I knew
that. I knew like she was stressed. I
knew cuz she was in the tent.
>> But I I was like telling her like it's
fine. We're good. You want to get somewhere grievy.
[ __ ] go to bed and get it arrest. I
don't need to go to bed.
Just sick getting [ __ ] played by
women when I tell them the truth.
He had you for a multi.
Yes, indeed. She really [ __ ] did have
me for a mug. It's not that you're right
on that question though. What what you
said a minute ago about
as soon as me and PJ went out last night
cuz she had something to say then but
she didn't have nothing to say. All the
times when I were trying to chase her
all the times we were putting in videos
when I was sad when I were putting my
hand or anything like that. She didn't
give a [ __ ] claim but she gives a [ __ ]
when I go out and cold approach. But I
didn't go out and cold approach last night.
You know what I mean? I did not go out
on cold approach. I did not kiss no one.
I didn't even get a wank. PJ got the
wank. Not me. I didn't even want to with
a good woman wanted to go and wank me
off. I told her no.
>> I just sat down and just talked. Started
rocking my leg. I told her no. I've
already got a girlfriend. She want to pitch you
and that off and myself.
How many times did she do coke when she
was with you? A lot of it.
>> No, not a lot. We only had it about
three times to be honest with you. Be
honest. Three times.
>> She was already taking C for to go with
me. That ain't my fault. That's
>> You used to be bad on the sniffing it.
>> No, I know. To be honest with you, PG. I
don't take sniff like that like all
these fer do. I don't go I don't I I've
only had sniff about what probably about
10 10 times 11 times
something like that
maybe less than that I haven't gone
[ __ ] I'm not up on coke I'm not even
on weed cuz it look like I've had a joint
>> this is why I'm probably being like this
cuz you haven't even had a joint either
>> I've only tried coke cocaine twice
>> I've had it on it, boys. Right. It's not
It's not even good. It's a [ __ ] bus.
It's a It's a [ __ ] bus. I'm not even
saying that. You just got
>> Timmy does it in it.
>> Yeah. The downer on it is hanging the downer.
You know what? I'm going to [ __ ] go
outside in the back garden and [ __ ]
stick the open in the back garden, mate.
>> You mean the calm down is bad, is it?
>> Yeah, the come down. Yeah, it's [ __ ]
hanging. It's I'm not exactly up on
Coke. I don't even like Coke. It's all
right when you're having a drink and
it's like a little B and all that [ __ ]
but the downfall of it is [ __ ]
You know that I'm so [ __ ] laughing
off Coke as well. I've never been so
loving in my life off it.
Try yourself what I got from this
[ __ ] shot, mate.
I'm being serious. I'm going in the back
garden. I'm going to be cooking, mate.
I'm going to be cooking some burgers on
the [ __ ] Did
>> Did Craig get Did Craig ever do cocaine?
>> You might, mate.
>> No. No, not really. No,
he he No, he he used to He's a [ __ ]
He's a [ __ ] psycho in his [ __ ]
>> I miss my mama. Grezy,
>> it's not that correct. actual. He's from
Rivenshaw as well. He is He's actual manchester.
He's actual Manchester like Craig.
>> Do you remember your dig?
Not Peter Belly's mama.
>> St. What about States? PJ,
>> he's cute. Well,
>> he's gone now, ain't he? >> Yeah.
You can go mad at me for that as well. I
don't give a [ __ ] anymore.
Women talking to me like [ __ ]
Calling me a liar and all that [ __ ]
when they weren't even [ __ ] there.
Why don't you take Why Why don't you
look at the text when I was asking her
to come out with us all night?
>> I want to get a steering I want to get a
steering wheel for Xbox. Um,
Grezy, you know, you can use a steering
wheel. It's really good.
You know when you're playing GTA and you
play the steering wheel, it's [ __ ] ace.
You know what I'm talking about.
>> Kitchen this
what I do.
>> We're going
to go in. Yeah, we got to [ __ ]
grab this gas ball. Yeah.
You see it?
One sec. One sec.
Can grab this. Yeah.
>> Let's go out here.
Did you see any of the neighbors today?
>> Who? Me? >> Yeah.
>> I see my next door neighbor. Yeah. He
asked me to go around with him for a drink. >> Really?
>> Yeah. Next door. Yeah. He asked me to go
over. I wanted to drink with him next door.
Don't [ __ ] cooking me, mate. [ __ ]
me, man. I don't use a cocker in there, mate. [ __ ]
Best way to do this PJ
is get some [ __ ]
>> Who's my daddy groovy? Who's my dad?
>> You know what? I'm not stopping eating
because I'm a [ __ ] woman now, mate. I'm eating Congratulations.
I I can't be asked with a woman. I'm not
starving myself anymore. I've gone too
[ __ ] long not eating. How long have I
done not eating, PJ?
>> Six days.
>> About six days. >> Yeah. >> [ __ ] by Grezy.
>> Was that cute when I asked USA if I
could see her boobs and then she pulled
her top up?
>> Is that cute? Grezy
multi moving in with PJ. Yeah. Do you
reckon that they shouldn't write that
content if me and PJ live together? That
would have been actual [ __ ] content.
>> [ __ ] hurts.
>> Yeah, that would be no content you
people would be dreaming of if it was
just me and PJ
in it. PJ. >> Yeah.
>> Is that cute that she is that is that
cute greasy that she pulled her top up?
I don't have no coconut oil me. So I've
used butter for cooking oil.
Know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> Oh, there we go.
>> They come out. They come bouncing out. Grezy,
>> there we go. We got
Let's grab these [ __ ] burgers.
Whatever they are. It's
>> cute, isn't it?
Why is it cute? Grezy, can you just imagine it?
>> Painful, man.
>> [ __ ] hell. Look at all them you get, mate.
All [ __ ] burgers.
Oh [ __ ] man.
Not even breaking, mate.
How to get rid of hiccups.
They hurt, man.
They [ __ ] hurt, bro. Had
>> him all day. [ __ ] bro. Jeez, they hurt.
I think it was a drinking on an empty
stomach or something,
bro. It's weird. Oh,
USA. Is these boobs cute? Grezy,
they were so bouncy.
I was playing with them as well.
It was fun.
Yeah, I've used butter for cooking oil, mate.
>> What the [ __ ] are you doing?
>> Cooking, mate.
>> [ __ ] women in it. I can't cook a
mate. I can't work a [ __ ] For real.
Me work a cooker.
>> I can. It's easy, bro. You can't You can't cook.
I I can cook. I just can't use a cooker.
>> It's [ __ ] easy, bro.
>> You like USA is boobs in it, Grezy. Grezy,
>> why is it with you men and boobs, man?
>> I don't know.
She had nice boobies.
I think that leaves a chicken. You know,
>> I think that need a chicken.
>> You're a [ __ ] man.
>> How am I the star?
>> I need some [ __ ] cookie, mate.
I mean, what would you what would you do
if she offered to show you them? >> Hey,
>> no. Asking Greasy.
>> Who you talking about? Natalie. >> No.
>> Oh, AC. You talking about AC?
>> Pretty much.
>> Okay. You're now storing about easy
after all this time. >> Yeah.
>> You go on about Natalie all day, every day.
>> Yeah. Mine's Vincent. Yours is [ __ ] not.
>> No, it's not.
>> Yours and this is
>> Would you actually say that, Grezy?
would you? That's sure.
It's actually quicker on this to cook as well.
>> Yeah, they're nice to nibble on.
>> Yeah, they nearly done these.
>> I was biting her nipples as well, Grezy.
>> They look bad, but they're not burnt.
I bought butter in this for [ __ ]
cocking oil, mate.
>> Yeah, I like to be fed.
>> Yeah, these are cooking nicely.
You see, I can cook I can cook and [ __ ]
like this outside, man. This is a This
is a life. This is a life I love.
You're a wanker.
>> I'm a wanker.
>> Are you not stressing over money?
>> Who me? Yeah.
>> No, not really.
They [ __ ] burn me. What the
h my finger? Morning. [Music]
>> Yeah. Now, now you know how Stitch felt.
I [ __ ] burn every single one of my fingers.
>> Yeah, I know. It's just fell.
>> I can't believe you killed Stitch.
sit there and then complain about me.
>> I have
>> the jumper. >> What?
>> The shorts and t-shirt Natalie got me.
>> I br in the house. I didn't set them on
fire. I bring them back in. No, that
would have been cool if we done that.
Set on fire.
>> I feel a bit sick. One sec.
>> [ __ ] nice.
>> I feel a bit sick. Groovsy. Oh,
you reckon it's the drinking greasy
that's made me feel sick. Probably
agree with it. We drunk so much, me and Monty.
Didn't we, bro?
>> Yeah, we did. We drunk quite a bit,
didn't we? Last night, to be honest with
you, we did drink quite a lot last night. >> Yeah,
>> that's [ __ ] either. We did. We did
drink quite a lot. >> [ __ ]
bottles are out. Never leave a gas
bottle in them.
I can't believe you like Timmy.
>> Timmy Aldridge.
>> Let's try this out, man. Your [ __ ]
got some good burgers here, man. Yeah.
Let's try it out. Yeah, man. Yeah. Burger,
>> buddy. We could have a proper barbecue.
>> Proper barbecue. Yeah.
>> Couldn't we?
>> We could.
The biggest is the biggest troll on YouTube. >> Nice.
>> I can cook a net.
>> He's better all my fingers. Look, I read
you better all them.
>> Tam's your dada.
You know, you know, when I'm on a train sometimes,
Grezy, I think of funny things on
YouTube that these people have said
like, "Tam is your dada.
Peter Betty can't get tax anymore
because he's already found his mama.
I told you, go on."
Nothing. No. Go on. No, nothing.
>> Oh, I was going to say that all last
night when we was out drinking
>> before we was drinking
>> when I was waiting for you, I was
texting no bed. Well, not no bed.
Natalie, cuz she's not a no bed or Natalie.
You know, when I was texting her, come
out with us. Come out for a drink. Come
out for a drink. So, she knew last night
me and you was out last night drinking.
Then then she comes on YouTube stressing about it.
>> What the?
>> It's weird that is it. Don't make sense. >> Yeah.
>> It's rather we over or she's [ __ ]
jealous that I [ __ ] I'm going out.
But I've already asked her if she wanted
to come out.
>> It's funny though, is it? It is funny
though, isn't it? um music and you know
like the things I've said the funny
sayings that I've come out with I wonder
what the people that troll me think
about it must make them laugh sometimes
is it like where I've come up with um
Peter Betty can't get attached cuz he's
already found his mama
imagine they sat on the train yeah
they'll probably just laugh at that
he's already found his mama Yeah.
Get me appetite, bad, pibs. Get my
[ __ ] appetite back.
I'm not losing me appetite. I know about
a woman. I'm not doing this [ __ ] again
over a woman, man. Not myself. I'm
[ __ ] But I'm stupid. Only what I
wanted is a letter N on my arm. I might
get tattooed, you know. [Music]
My [ __ ] fingers are burning me.
>> DJ, I can even send you a voice note
like you've got one of these rooms here
if you will do want it.
Yeah, I'm going to I'm going to move in.
>> Oh, yeah. >> Yeah.
>> You [ __ ] like a Yeah.
>> So, how much do I have to pay a month?
>> 40 quid a month.
pound a month.
>> That's all right then, isn't it? >> Yeah.
I'm going to get that hat back down
tomorrow. I'm not choking the hat away
because I like that ling what Nat
Birmingham is not up north though.
Birmingham don't count as up north. It's
in the middle.
>> It's like the Midlands. It doesn't count.
>> It doesn't count as up north.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> No, Birmingham's not north. North. North
is like Manchester, Liverpool, Newcastle,
but not Manchester. Birmingham doesn't
count as up north, even though it
technically is north to me. It's the Midlands. So,
>> well, no. No, it depends. It depends if
you if you're down south and then
Birmingham comes up north. Think about it. >> Never midn. >> Yeah.
It's okay, Grezy. I'll just um I'll just wait.
You'll wait. Yeah. Until it's been made.
I love that. Do you remember that in
Little Britain, Monty?
>> It's one
>> when the guy When the guy goes to the
bookshop and he asks for specific things.
>> He says, "I don't want that one in the
wheelchair." That one.
>> No, no, no. where he asked for like a specific thing.
>> Oh, and he's behind the couch. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. It's funny as [ __ ] is it?
>> Yeah. It's all right.
>> It's okay. I'll just wait.
How long have you been down there? Not
long. Just about a week or so.
I don't even know what these burgers
are, but they got like like a curry
spice taste to them. I got them from a
Haitian shop. But it's Asian burgers. >> Yeah,
>> but you get you get [ __ ] tons in them
though. That's why I got them cuz you
get loads. I got like 30 odd of them.
But they will probably last me the two
weeks. Yeah. I got eat burgers for the
last two weeks. I'm going to be a fat [ __ ] mate. Yeah.
You're not my mama. Yuck. Yuck. That
made you laugh, isn't it? Greasy.
Ew. Get away from me. You're not my mama.
You don't even look the same fake account.
>> You was in tears yesterday. Bless you.
>> Who? Me? >> Yeah.
>> I've been crying today as well.
I know. I know. I know. That's how bad
it is. My being are [ __ ] strong as
[ __ ] mate. But she thinks they're not.
She thinks I'm one of these little [ __ ]
who go around playing. I went out last
night to clear my head. That's all.
I only went out to clear my head from Natal.
You know what I mean?
>> That's why that's why we went out and
[ __ ] clear. going to have a drink.
People li talking and that, you know,
>> and then that sees the video and it's
like she's going [ __ ] off her red and
it's like what is it? You're not with
me. So, I don't know why she's getting I
I rated when she when she's finished me.
You know what I mean? I don't get that.
But if she was going to come back to me,
she won't have left it this [ __ ] long.
It's been past six days for less.
You know what I mean? I left it so [ __ ] long.
Oh well, [ __ ] it then. I [ __ ] I
wasn't TV, mate. I just smash it up.
It's coming tomorrow as well. Her TV's coming tomorrow.
And if you all don't believe me that
I've actually got a TV, watch, I'll show
you. It's already been ordered.
I got See, and that's a good man. What
is willingly to go out there and get all
the [ __ ] back once she's lost?
>> I don't think you're ever going to get
over this, Nataly, bro.
>> I don't think I am to be honest with you.
I don't pick it. I'm going to get over
I don't even know why she come into my
life if she if she was just going to
chop me out of her life. To be honest
with you, it br me into her life just to
chop me out of it. What was the point in that?
>> Maybe she just wanted to shag you.
Yeah, because K said he had a small dick
until I pulled it out on her. She [ __ ] out.
She put on a small dick because of Kelly
saying that he had a small dick and a
>> you know Natalie shagged a few people on
YouTube in it.
>> Yeah, I already know Natalie's
background. I don't care about Natalie's shitty background.
But you see, I can't be half with her
anyways. At the end of the day, I'm the
one who chose a [ __ ] prick. But she's
not a prick either way. But what she's
done to me,
she's she I give her the chance. I
wasn't even I with her background
going around what she's done with Asians
and people on YouTube. I would have said
no to that. But I had [ __ ] proper bad
feelings with that.
>> You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. Yes.
>> I had feelings for that. I still do have
feelings for her. So, if she thinks I'm
slagging her off or whatever, I'm [ __ ] not.
She's the best bird I've ever had. I'm
not just saying that. She's the best
woman I've ever had. Not in bed. I'm not
about the bed apartment. I'm not about
sex or anything. I'm on about She's the
best woman I've ever had in my life. And
I'm not I'm not going to get no one
liking that again unless I get someone
10 times better in that who will stand
by me for what I do for the mistakes I [ __ ] do.
But I'm not going to make no more
mistakes anyways. I'm done with making mistakes.
I'm only back on YouTube. It's cuz I
don't have [ __ ] all else to do or no one
else to talk about. What does Natalie
want me to do? Walk around in circles in
this house when she's not even when
she's not even talking to me.
You know what I mean?
>> There's loads of things you can do, bro.
>> What exit have a wank? Yeah.
>> Go gym. Go out. Socialize.
>> I don't tell anybody that though lot. I
don't tell anybody about the gym. I can
go to gym now. Literally.
L I can go to him this second.
I do go to the gym.
Natalie even for that. I I do go to the gym.
That's why I basically got nearly a sixack PJ. >> Yeah,
>> that's I've nearly got one. Look. Oh [ __ ]
>> It's so skinny, mate. It's just all skinny.
You You've actually felt it, aren't you, PJ?
>> Yeah. You're fat, aren't I? Oh
>> no. Is my belly solid or is it not solid?
>> You're just a fat [ __ ]
>> I'm not a fat [ __ ]
I got a solid ass belly, man. Solid.
She's moved on.
Pretty soon. I'm not ask if she's moved
on. She hasn't gone into another
relationship. And if she does, that's
just [ __ ] wow. Wow.
And that just shows that she really
didn't care about me.
She can't move on. I'm done anyways. I'm
done chasing her.
Why am I going to chase someone like
Natalie when I explain to her thousands
and thousands and thousands of times
I've not done [ __ ] all wrong.
And then she comes and reacts when I go
out clubbing last night.
That's what's up.
Put us both on Big PJ.
I feel like
>> I'm naked here.
>> She She's probably sucking someone's
knob as we talk.
>> He's not so Why do you talk like that to
me, PJ? You This is what I'm on about.
You're supposed to be my mate, but you
need to s I'm your mate. What the [ __ ]
So why would you say that?
Why would you say, "Oh, she probably
sucking someone off now." Why would you sell that?
>> People have needs and [ __ ]
>> Needs? No.
I You're saying it to [ __ ] me. A man
who's got [ __ ] mad feelings for that
[ __ ] woman. He's saying she's
probably sucking someone's dick.
[ __ ] hell, man.
Someone saying that to you, PJ, mate.
You know what I mean? It's [ __ ]
hanging. It's a hanging feeling, man.
Never [ __ ] been in love with my
entire life. Not like this.
This is [ __ ] hanging.
What the [ __ ] am I doing? Sort myself out.
You know what? I'm going to get the
door. Give me a second. Yeah, you're
going to hear me banging out, but you
know, give me a second. [ __ ] it, man.
[ __ ] it. [ __ ] it.
Yeah, I just pushed it. Just get the
attack. I need to start.
I just tapped it. B obviously not PJ.
At least you got like at least you got
kids though, buddy.
>> Yeah, I know. I know. I know. And that's
a good thing. At least I've got
something in life and that's my kids.
Even though I like to do live with my
mom, but I still got my kids in my life.
>> If I was you, yeah, I would just like
focus on them, bro. Just [ __ ] [ __ ]
everything else, you know? [ __ ] them.
>> Yeah, that's what I am doing now. I have
been focusing on
>> I shouldn't have this is what I mean.
I'm never introducing an up woman to my
kids. Never. Natalie just walks out of
my kids' lives.
Like not like it's piss easy.
Lola Lola brings her up to me and talks
about Natalie and that on the phone. She
was talking about her today asking that
I was not asking how she don't know what
that word means. >> Yeah.
>> But Lola talks about her. Lola doesn't
even talk about Kaye.
But she talks about Natalus. What does she say?
>> She likes Natalie. She likes her. So
does Proom. Prim likes her as well.
>> Prim's a bit shallow with Natalie,
but she likes Natalie.
>> How many times have I seen Natalie?
>> A couple of times >> really.
E is a p or
is multi. Who's what's he on about?
Let me read that com the bottom.
>> They said that you're a [ __ ] magnet.
>> [ __ ] I'm a [ __ ] magnet. I wish I
were. I could get [ __ ] whenever I
[ __ ] want. [ __ ] is not hard to get.
It's just that I'm not a slag. Like I
don't go out. I don't do that [ __ ]
I don't go out cold approaching like PJ
were doing last night. I I only helped
him out last night. I I wasn't even cold approaching.
I was helping PJ out and then PJ asked
me to go and call approach says granny
looking thing. So I told this granny
pretend. Yeah. And then she was looking
at PJ. I said my over there like she and
all that. Look.
And then she she walked off. awards off.
>> Money, when it's Halloween, please do
me a favor. Dress up as Mr. Burn from The Simpsons.
Monty didn't do more than me. I
approached way more than Monty.
>> I didn't I I weren't even approaching
women. I I
DJ more me the mad bastard went up to
people with when he was with the moms
and dads and everything about bastard.
>> Funny is it? Yeah.
>> Yeah. Two two people. Two. Well, yeah.
Have you been talking to the one with
her mom? Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I have.
>> Yeah. What? She text
>> I said, "Oh, you should come London
sometime." She said, "Yeah, on a weekend." So
>> I think >> Huh.
>> I think he might be in there like like
>> Yeah. Hopefully, bro. Yeah,
>> that's good. That's good.
>> She was saying She was saying that you
was telling her that I had a girlfriend.
>> I didn't say you had a girlfriend.
>> That's what she was saying yesterday.
>> [ __ ] no. No, I was saying I was talking
about that mom next to her.
>> That's what I'm talking about. I even
talking about you had a girlfriend.
I forget cuz she were there talking to
her and then she went, didn't she? You
were with me. You stood next to him when
you were talking to her
>> and then they walked off, didn't they?
The mama the mom and daughter just both walked away. >> Yeah.
Monty got PJ the numbers. No, he never
>> I didn't get PJ the numbers. He got them
myself. Like literally
>> there was somewhere I approached that
Monty didn't even speak to the friend.
So that that's impossible.
>> Yeah, I didn't. Yeah, PJ when PJ was
talking to the women, I weren't even
talking to him. I left PJ to it.
I w even cold approach in one little
bit. I was helping PJ out.
>> I didn't I don't need a cold approach. I
only like I was talking about Natalie
all that night. >> Yeah. >> But pulled
I didn't pull nothing. Them two girls
last night. Yeah. was with us for a
little bit and then they got off into
another club after giving PJ a wank.
>> Only one of them did that.
>> Yeah. Then then they both got off into a
different clubs and left us and then me
and PJ are back on our own. And then
then PJ went out called approaching
again. Got some more numbers.
>> I don't know. No, you did do an approach
on the street though. You actually did.
>> I know.
But I got it recorded.
>> Yeah, I know. But I wasn't a code
approaching anyone. I didn't ask anybody
out or get anyone's numbers. I didn't
ask for anyone's numbers
or anything like I was called approaching.
>> I only told you I was only helping you out. >> Yeah.
>> You know that's it. I weren't going cold
approaching at all. I walked up to women
who you [ __ ] weren't walking up to.
I don't go out and cold approach. I
don't do that [ __ ] I rather go online
social media. That's my cold approach.
You social [ __ ] media, not going out
like what PJ does.
If a woman comes over to me and starts
talking to me, like I said to PJ, leave
it. That woman come to us.
Let a woman come to us. A woman sat
right next to me drinking a [ __ ]
drink. I didn't even talk to her.
Didn't even [ __ ] talk to her. Then
she moved and [ __ ] off cuz they
weren't talking or whatever. Did you see
>> Why did some of these accounts have your picture
faces? It's weird, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> You all [ __ ] nons. Your [ __ ]
granddads are nons you [ __ ] Your
granddad raped your [ __ ] dad, you prick.
>> What the [ __ ] Yeah, grandad to [ __ ]
dad. No [ __ ] on that. [ __ ] it on
your [ __ ] family, you prick.
[ __ ] hell. Do you want me to get sh
with you [ __ ] Kelly? Yeah. Didn't your
dad get bummed of his own dad?
Except daddy. Yeah, he did. Yeah, he
[ __ ] did. He got bum raped.
Go on, Kayley. We can spit all your
[ __ ] family business out on YouTube
if you really want to. Kayie, why didn't
your daddy love you, Kayie? Why didn't
daddy love you, Kayie? Why do what? Why
does daddy or they want to stone Kay?
Not a daughter. And why did he disown
you and left you? All yourself.
>> Does anyone know who this is? One second.
Okay, now that Kelly,
>> does anyone know who this is?
>> Anyone know who this is? One left. Yes.
What? You don't know the in between us, George?
You know who that is, Monty?
>> Yeah, he's out in between us.
>> He looks like you a bit.
>> Nothing like me.
>> That was your fate. That's that. He's
got his own YouTube channel, you know.
>> Yeah, I know. I know.
>> He's a gamer. He does gaming and all that lot.
Everyone knows the Ineters, isn't it?
But Monty, the inbetweeners was over overrated.
>> Some episodes were
I said like they could have made uh the
finger one better.
The movie where they go to
>> the movies were [ __ ]
>> The first one were good. The second one
were plenty of [ __ ] The Australian one. >> Yeah.
>> The rest of the other ones were done. It's
>> surprising how they're all still alive,
isn't it? Yeah,
>> money is surprising how they're all still alive.
>> They are age dick. They only young.
>> Yeah, there's people that died in their 30s.
>> Yeah, I know they but they're not dead.
I had to eat that burger. I'd be [ __ ] dead.
>> I had to eat that burger or else I'd be
dead. I swear. Watch how big I get, PJ
now. Yeah, I'm going to get massive,
mate. No, cuz I quit the weed. >> Yeah.
>> No, I get I get bigger now. I start
putting weight on now. We start building out more.
No, I'm going to say to Natalie, [ __ ] off.
>> What train station do you think's
bigger, New Street or Manchester?
Piccadilly. New Street, is it?
>> New Street London, bro. Is it
>> London's bigger? Yeah, London's bigger than Manchester.
>> No, I'm saying Birmingham New Street is
bigger than Manchester Picadill it. Yeah,
>> I'm not too sure.
>> Is not that big.
>> Birmingham's the second biggest city.
>> Yeah, New Street is massive. I think
it's even bigger than Houston, but I
think the biggest station is King's
Cross. King's Cross is massive, bro. driving.
I don't know what I'm going to do, man. We've not
>> I just wanted to believe me, man. Like, literally
[ __ ] her up.
>> I am [ __ ] her up. I'm just going to
let her go.
playing these games with me and like I
am [ __ ] a rock.
I give them my [ __ ] heart and
everything, man. I give them a love,
man. Proper. Obviously, we had our ups
and downs cuz of YouTube and [ __ ]
[ __ ] like that. Yeah. But baring
that and it was a good relationship. It
was really really a good relationship.
It weren't bad one little bit just that
we had our little ups and downs and like
you will do in a relationship. [Music]
But when a woman can't handle it, then
they [ __ ] run off where a man where
they can handle it and tell a woman to [ __ ] chill.
>> [ __ ] knows.
>> I think she was just using you.
M. She had you over.
Okay, I know what you mean. Basically
she got with me and had me over me over basically. Did YouTube ruin?
No, basically the dog said Lisa. Lisa I
blame all this on basically Lisa me like
it's all Lisa's [ __ ] fault cuz if
Natalie's address this address didn't get doxed
then Natalie would have been basically
still here. Obviously, I was sticking up
for Natalie, lying, saying Natalie was
here and she's in the room and [ __ ] like
that. You know what I mean? Because I
weren't telling you [ __ ] all what was
going on with Natalie. I weren't even
going to tell you nothing
until Natalie told you cuz Natalie
thought I was going to come on here and
tell you what was going on. I w to say [ __ ]
to be honest. I say [ __ ] when I'm angry.
>> You know what I mean? When when you're
angry, you say [ __ ]
Why did you really What? Why did you
break up? Why did we break up? Because I
went on to YouTube, told everyone that
we in the hotel and um
but that we in Manchester, but we wasn't
even in Manchester.
We wasn't even in Manchester. So all
them would have been ringing up
Manchester [ __ ] hotels, not [ __ ]
where Nat were. I made some mistake by
telling everybody that we was in the
hotel. Yeah, I knew that. As soon as I
knew that I made that mistake, I changed
it to Manchester.
That's why I said we in the hotel in
Manchester. And I said I've been waking up
like 4 5 in the morning like being in a
tent again. Obviously we was in a tent
You know what I mean? Obviously cuz we
were we was [ __ ] homeless. Well,
Natalie [ __ ] was homeless. Like I was
homeless in a tent.
So Natalie's been where I've been in a
tent ringing up people trying to find
somewhere to to stay. No one no one will
take it because of these threats to
stab. So these these places he she was
ringing. Now it's like to Natalie, we
might have to go up north, you know. We
might have to go to Manchester if you
can't get a place here. I didn't tell
Natalie to move to Manchester. I told
Natalie, we might have to go to
Manchester if you can't get a place here
or go to Mansfield or whatever. >> London. >> No,
you know, or I wouldn't put a roof over
her head. I would have made my own house
out of [ __ ] pellets.
>> You know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> That's what I would have done. I
wouldn't make my own [ __ ] house. So
if I go home this again, I'm making my
own house out of pellets and I'm making
a fireplace, you know, next me. I'm not ass.
And I'm not ass. That's my life. So you
can't sly take the piss out of that when
that is my life dream [ __ ] house. A
wooden house in the middle of the [ __ ] woods.
That is my dream house. And that's no
[ __ ] Even if it's out of pellets or
not, that is my dream house.
And that's [ __ ] So funny, man. What?
>> You just think it's all funny?
>> I don't think it's funny. I really don't
think any of this is funny. I don't
think Natalie going homeless was funny.
But that weren't my fault. That was Lisa
who caused Natalie to be homeless. Lisa
caused that by giving out the address.
If that address gets Natalie be still
[ __ ] here. Literally, that's Lisa's
fault. Why Natalie so [ __ ] here now?
has [ __ ] fought all of it. I'm
telling you, it [ __ ] is
sitting there [ __ ]
saying she's going to doctor her dress.
So I said, "Go on then. Do it then. If
you're going to do it, do it. Don't say
it. Do it." And she did. If she left her
daughter, she would have even mentioned
about doctoring her dress.
>> Yeah, that's true.
>> You know, she doesn't love her daughter.
She loves her son. She doesn't love
[ __ ] Natalie though. She always
[ __ ] chucks Natalie under the [ __ ]
bus all the [ __ ] time cuz shagging
her and [ __ ] like that. What kind of
mother does that to her daughter and
say she hasn't? Of course he [ __ ]
ass. She's going to sit there and say she hasn't.
But you can hear it in the [ __ ]
voice. She ass. >> What?
You think it's all a laugh?
>> I don't think it's all a laugh list,
man. You know what? I adore Natalie. I
[ __ ] adore her.
Like, literally, she
to be honest with you. She's [ __ ]
ruined me, mate.
I' I've stood by her. I will always
stand by Natalie. I told her that.
Well, she don't want me to. She don't
want me to. I can't [ __ ] fart a
woman. Well, I've not done nothing wrong
really, peeps. Not [ __ ] really.
Not really bad anyways. I've not cheated
on her. I've not battered her. I've not
even proper argued with her. We haven't
even had a proper argu.
>> Well, you want me to shut up? Yeah, I shut up. >> Nah,
just find out what you're going to do.
Just find a solution.
What are you going to do, bro? Really?
You make me go side [ __ ] Kelly, you're
going to be arrested.
>> What are you going to do?
>> What do you mean? Kelly. >> Yeah.
>> No. Now I'm going to let the police sort her out.
>> No, not Katie. That like Natalie, what
are you going to do?
>> I'm not going to do now. I'm just going
to leave Natalie alone now. I'm just
going to leave her. If she thinks that
I'm going to
>> I'm going to put that I'm going to put
that 285 on another game on Saturday.
No, I'm joking, bro. [ __ ] that. I'm only joking.
>> You see she thinks I'm chasing after
her. I'm [ __ ] not. Yeah, go and tell
your dad's going to get bummed off his
dad again. Yeah. If I take your wig off,
you dirty [ __ ]
>> Imagine that. Put that on another bit. [ __ ] that.
>> Go and shave your back as well, you
bastard. You got about the same [ __ ] on
your back and your ass as a gorilla, you
bastard. God bless you.
>> No, I'm on about Kayie.
>> Yeah, I just said I bless you.
>> I [ __ ] grate.
>> Oh, you're right as well, Kayie. Yeah,
you shave your beard as well. Yeah. Get
them trees and start plucking them
little black hair out your out of your
chin. Yeah. So, you people didn't know
that Kay had a beard. She [ __ ] does.
>> There you go. You [ __ ] dude.
>> There you go, Rice. KK's got a beard.
Did you not know that?
>> Oh, bless you. Bless you.
>> Literally did not know that. Right.
She's got a [ __ ] bigger beard than I
got, lad. She shaves it all off.
>> Just pack it in, you [ __ ]
>> Yeah, this [ __ ] as well. It's full of
[ __ ] hers. Black hers. A bit of poo
crumb cropping on it. Dropping on it as
well today, [ __ ] Then you can't pack it in.
You know what that means? Money
is Kaye and Rise.
I hope they are. I hope they do go out
together. Do you know what? Two ugly
people make a perfect couple. Especially Lentu.
>> They're both ugly as sin. I'm not being
funny. Kelly was actually lucky to get a
man like me.
>> Literally lucky. He will never get
another man like me. Go on, Kelly. Go
and get another man like me. Go on. Any
money you can't. Any money you can't get
another man like me.
All what you're going to be stuck with
now is all the ugly ass men on YouTube
all [ __ ] all around you. >> Loveless.
>> What man's going to You know what I
mean? You're [ __ ] ugly, Kay. Ugly.
You're so [ __ ] ugly. So ugly.
>> Am I ugly, Monty? Oh, you're not ugly, PJ.
>> You sure?
>> Yeah, you're you're not ugly.
>> Oh, thank you.
>> You're not ugly. You're not ugly, too.
>> Kelly, you know I'm not a non. You know
I've had a DBS. Check. You stupid [ __ ]
>> Oh my days. You like this woman.
[ __ ] man. We had our kids checking [ __ ]
I think you lot a pair of [ __ ] [Music]
>> Yeah, this is [ __ ] ugly. You need
your sign out.
Take your CL glasses off.
Nah, I'm not ugly at all, matey.
>> Monty, apart from special needs, what
else can you bring to a relationship?
>> What do you mean apart from special needs?
>> They're saying that you're special needs.
>> [ __ ] autism. >> Yeah.
>> Oh man, these are [ __ ] weirdos with
the question, mate.
Ky, listen to what you're saying yet.
You know what? I should have put that
brick through your window when I took
that brick out your window that night,
Kayie. I should have actually bounced it
through the window.
When I took that big house break out
your [ __ ] back window should have gone through.
Anyway, the police are involved with
Kelly. Anyways, in fact, I'm just going
to do this.
>> I've got a bet. I've got a good bet for um
Saturday Steven Howard. I've got
>> Leonor Wigan. Anyways,
no one send it to my mom. What are you
saying? Anyway, so yeah, folks, don't believe me.
>> I got I got a good bet for Saturday, bro.
>> Yeah, folks. Yeah, folks. I'm going to
be sending all these to my mom. What are you doing?
>> I got a good one for Saturday, bro. I've got shots.
>> Leon Oran. One second, Monty. I got Leon
Oran versus Wigan. Fleetwood versus
Bristol Rovers and Swindon versus Cambridge.
All both to score no draw.
20 returns 390. So
yeah, that's what I'm doing on Saturday.
>> Yeah, I've got a phone call tomorrow
with the [ __ ] police with about Kelly
and that tomorrow. And it's on [ __ ]
camera as well.
It's on camera with the police and
that's that is >> Yes.
>> Actually, Kelly thinks I'm actually
talking about about that. I'm actually
not. The police are actually involved.
I've already told the police.
What do you mean?
>> One second. What do you mean that's a
drift, Monty? What do you mean that's a drift?
>> What? What? What do you mean a drift?
>> Why is it a drift? Stephen Howard? No,
I'm asking just Stephen Howard.
>> Oh, okay. Okay.
How is it a bad one, bro? Good odds.
Yeah, they going to entertain the little
pedos like Belly and all that. Go on. Go
and entertain the people who put your
picture of our kids up. Yeah. Go on.
>> No, it's not risky. You just put It's
not risky. You just put 20 pound on it.
I'm only putting 20 on it. Um,
so it's a good return for 20.
>> Yeah. You know what? You know what I'm
going to actually do, actually. [ __ ] it.
[ __ ] it. Do you know what Kelly? Yeah. I
might just do what Lee's done to me. I
might just send your neighbors letters
telling them that you're a child abuser
and all that. Look, that's what I might
do. Yeah, send your neighbors letters
saying you're a child abuser like that
like you smart kids. That's why you
ain't got your kids. I'm going to say
and that's what I'm going to do. That's
what I'm [ __ ] going to do. Actually,
I'm going to do that [ __ ]
>> Watch what happens. I'm being honestly
serious. I'm going to send them letters
out. I'm going to get them. I'm going to make some
No, don't do that, Monty.
>> I'm I'm doing it, PJ. I think a
neighbors know what what they living with.
>> It's Yeah, but it's cowardly.
>> It's not cowardly. I think the neighbors
know that that they're living with a child abuser.
I'm not even chatting [ __ ] about Kaye
either. I swear down there in my kids'
lives, she's a child abuser.
And she's sitting here. You can tell the
fact she's an abuser. Where is she going
on at me? I'm not even going out with
her. So I don't know why she's going at
me. Yeah. Sort yourself out, you man. Looking
>> said that your skin is skin. >> Yeah,
>> his [ __ ] skin. The man can't get
laid. He only can get laid up granny's.
That's it. He's a granny [ __ ] He's
only had one sex in his life and that's cobwebs. Literally cobwebs.
Kayie, why don't Kayie, why don't your
dad actually love you? That's what I
actually been thinking about for a
while, actually. Why don't your dad love
you? And why did your mom choose her
partner over you and kick you out?
That's what I want to know as well. And
then you sit [ __ ] up with with your
mom and she kicked you out. She was a
man over you.
That's the thing. I will never choose
anyone over my children. I haven't chos
anyone over my children. I will always
be in my kids' lives. Always.
No matter [ __ ] what?
Do you think we would hear what you say?
Yeah. You're a soft ass. You're not even
You're soft. You're soft ass. Yeah,
you know I can get I get you batted off
Christina. I get my cousin Christina to
b you. You silly [ __ ]
Simples in it. I will I get my cousin to
kick [ __ ] out of you. Literally
I'm not even chatting [ __ ] and she woke
[ __ ] out of you. I can get my cousin if
you want. All my cousins are females
either way. You know that already Kay.
So, will I get my cousin Vicky or
Christina to knock you the [ __ ] out? You ugly [ __ ]
I'm not even joking. I I'm going to give
my cousin anyways. I'll tell my cousin
try to house out. I will do.
I get Kelly B off my cousin.
Come on, Kelly. You start calling my
cousin if you want. If you
both my cousins will walk out here.
Laugh all you want, Kelly.
Don't forget I don't like women, Kelly,
do I? But I teleported your fat ass
across the room, you fat [ __ ] Do you
know what? I should have headbutted K. I
should have just headed and just snapped
your nose. You ugly little man.
You look like a dude in it. So I get
away with it. Sorry PJ. I'm [ __ ] up
your chat here, lad. Go on. Carry on, PJ.
I'm just reacting to lag.
You know what, PJ? I'm just going to
send a link to my mom. Yeah. Um, of your
channel. Just give me a second. I do it
now on camera.
I do on camera. So, Kelly can actually see
can actually see. Hey, Kelly. Ready for this?
Ready for this, Kelly? Yeah. No people.
There's nothing on my phone. Nothing at
all on my phone. Nothing at all. Are you
ready for this, Kelly? Are you ready?
Watching this. Watching this, Kelly.
Wait. Sorry. Sorry, PG.
Watching this, Kelly. Yeah.
All right, that one second.
Go on, Kayie. Carry on.
Carry on, Kayie.
Go on, Kayley. Carry on.
You're more welcome to carry on now. Kayie,
it's off. I sly car ran off. She's
popped off now, ain't she?
There she is. She's there up top there.
K X K H H H H H H H H H H H H H H H H H
H H H H R O Yeah, that's Kay, you fit [ __ ]
Yeah. So anyway, so yeah, Kayie, I've
sent my mom a link so my mom can
actually watch what what what you're
talking about now. So go on, Kayie,
carry on talking about the same [ __ ] and
we could be watching right second. I
don't [ __ ] know. But go on, keep
writing your [ __ ] Kayie. Keep
calling me a nod, Kayie. Come on,
Miy. Why do you keep ringing? No, I just
want to just want my mom to see what K
writes about me and all that. Look, but
K stop now and [ __ ] off talking now, won't she?
That's why my mom needs to see what
Kay's talking about and see what she's
[ __ ] doing. That's why I've done it.
Because Kay can't just keep coming on
YouTube taking a piss and then going to
my mom acting all innocent and all nice.
That's what she does.
That's what she does. She plays with my
mom that's all the innocent and cause me
to [ __ ] this [ __ ] scared of my mom.
She's scared. My mom will go somewhere
else. My mom kick the [ __ ] out of her.
My mom will kick [ __ ] out of her. My
mom's in her 50s and she kick [ __ ] out
of Kay and her mom. That's why Kay's
[ __ ] ran off.
That's why she's not writing now
cuz she knows
she could be watching. I don't know. My
mom's not going to sit there and write.
But if you don't believe me, I sent it
to my mom.
Oh, she's seen it as well. She's
literally seen it. KS
in the thing.
>> Yeah, I know. I know. I can't I can't be
honest with her either to be honest with
you. I've been talking about my [ __ ] all
day. Now, if you want to see what I've
been talking about about all this code
approaching [ __ ] ask PJ. I haven't
a cold approached anyone.
Can't be with women anymore, man. Jamie,
what what's Natalie saying? Is a big
It's not even Natalie Ch is a fake account.
It's Kay or not? It's fake account PJ.
>> Yeah, I kicked it.
>> Yeah, it's Kayie. It's [ __ ] Kayie.
It's N come up in it. If it is Natalie,
but it's not Natalie. It's a fake account.
Not call me a n or anything like that.
Kay, you are a nons. You're a nons lover.
You're a pedophile lover.
I'm not even. In fact, just take care
Kelly, please. Please. Yeah, get rid of
her. Get rid of her to try and remind me
to [ __ ] up. That's why she's here.
I'm not telling you to get rid of the
channel. Get the [ __ ]
Yeah, this body.
I can [ __ ] stop talking about it.
That's only what she does. She [ __ ]
call me to [ __ ] That's it.
But it's all right when she was talking
my dick. All right. When I were [ __ ]
shagging her, she weren't calling me
then. Or was she? when she was shagging me
when all this [ __ ] was all going round.
>> You like it when she sucked her dick. >> What?
>> Did you like it when she used to suck your dick?
>> Not at least better.
>> Not at least 10 times better. >> Really? >> Yeah.
That's why I never [ __ ] chalk Natalie
away. I'm not ask if Natalie choke me
away. I always stand by Natalie.
I will always stand by her. I'm not ask
she's ch me away. I will always stand
by. I stick up for her no matter what.
She's the best [ __ ] woman I've ever
been with. I'm not just saying that. I
say [ __ ] this the best woman woman
I've ever been with. PJ
and she respected me and I just treated
her like a prick.
Oh, you come on a [ __ ] other account.
We kick it, man. Again,
>> both of them. They're coming on a fake
account with this. Um Yeah. And the
Kerry one. Um the one with um the [ __ ] um
Yeah, you got it.
Coming in cows.
It's not Natalie.
Natalie said she were going to sleep to
me. So it's not Natalie. It's Natalie
said she's going to sleep. Natalie
Natalie does go to sleep at this time.
So I know 100% it's not
trolling. Yeah. Yeah, she is. She's a
[ __ ] idiot. He's not even a good
troll anyways cuz my mom's actually
watching this [ __ ] I think Kelly's
[ __ ] herself up evil way.
It's going to my mom's going to end up
stopping her from seeing the kids
cuz it's a son who she's going for.
But it's pretty funny. Why is a woman
like Kelly going for me when I'm when
the the dad to her kids? That's crazy.
You know what I mean? She's attacking a
her a kid's dad.
That's what she's doing. She's attacking
her own kid's dad. That's [ __ ]
pathetic to be honest with you. You know
what I mean? If you don't like [ __ ] off, is it?
My mom. My mom.
>> You like it? You like it though?
>> No. Only why I got my mom on Kay just
now. Yeah. Is because [ __ ] my mom
needs to see what Kelly is doing.
>> I'm not getting my mom involved. My mom
needs to see what that [ __ ] woman's
doing, what she writes, and what she
says about me and [ __ ] like that. So my
mom just need to see that [ __ ]
But my mom's a sleepy. My mom's asleep.
Haven't really sent it. I sent it, but
she had seen it. So she's not even here.
I'm just saying my mom just need to see
the [ __ ] what she says and does. And
then do you think I want that near my kids? Really?
They're not even kids people. They not
even care and PJ should go Blackpool.
>> They not even care this case anymore.
Kelly lost them.
>> How come that that rice never starts on
me, do you think? >> What?
>> Why do you think that rice never starts on me?
>> Because he's not jealous of your life. That's why. >> Yeah,
>> it's not. He's jealous of my life.
That's why he's going on to me because
I've been out with [ __ ] Natalie and
I've been out with Kayie
and he [ __ ] jealous about that.
That's what it is. It's [ __ ] complete
jealousy with it.
Don't forget these people have passed
Natalie out and they've all Natalie's
turned them all down. >> Yeah.
>> Not all of them obviously. Oh,
so yeah, it's turned a lot of people
down in this community.
Well, if Natalie does appreciate me, I'm
going to like I'm just going to pull off
now and just let Natalie come to me when
she's feel when she's ready. If she's
not if she doesn't want to come back to
me, that's fine. But I know 100% I've
done nothing wrong. I've not called
approached any woman. Not like that anyways.
I've not even got off with any woman.
I've not even shagged another woman.
I've not even kissed the other woman. I
don't even have no other woman's [ __ ]
phone number in my phone.
Literally, I do not have another woman's
number in my phone. I didn't even get no
numbers last night. I wasn't even
looking for numbers last night.
I could have got numbers last night, but
I'm too scared. I'm not too scared,
obviously. Not, but I respect Natalie.
I was not going out cold approach and
getting numbers. I talking to people
like Natalie knows I can actually talk
to people. So understand that now.
>> No, it's not. It's a warm approach.
>> It's not even that. I was asking her to
come out with us all last night. P. It's
like Natalie, come out for a drink with
us. Come out for a drink with us. What
the [ __ ] Come out for a drink with us.
Let's sort [ __ ] out. Come out. Ask
friends or let's sort [ __ ] out. Come on.
So the Texas were there. So she knows
I'm was asking her to come out clubbing
with us last night.
>> Rice, you're from Rice. You're from Cardiff. It r
coming making fake fake um accounts.
>> Rice is from Cardiff.
>> Rice is a soft c like half these little
[ __ ] on this community.
>> Who would win in a fight? PG out me and rise >> me
>> me it would not mean you PJ
then next time I meet you yeah I'm going
to grab you by the back of your neck
yeah and squeeze like I've done with
your hands yeah >> okay
>> [ __ ] off man you be like
rice do do 30 presubs rise
30. Do 30 press ups. Not said do 30 on
your knuckles. Rise. On your knuckles.
Me right. She said it's harder on your
knuckles. I go and do 30 press ups on
your knuckles. Rise.
Yeah. Good on your eyes. Literally good
on you if she's sleeping in your bed.
That's a bit weird because she's on her
own account. That means that she's at
her own house.
>> Right. You talking about Kay doesn't get
me jealous, lad. Take her have it.
Literally have her lad. You literally
like if Kay thinks I'm going to get like
[ __ ] jealous about her or whatever
else, you can have [ __ ] Kelly take
her. There's only one woman who I
actually care about. one woman
and that's not I don't care about any
other [ __ ] woman. Sorry EJ all the
connection keeps going. Take care. So if
you think you were going to get me challening whale
I need to get that art back as well out
out the tree. I'm not chucking that out
way. Natalie got me that. I don't like Look, Natalie,
look Natalie, I haven't charged him away
or I haven't burnt them if you think I
burnt the shorts and that. Look,
look, Natalie, the old they the
see I haven't burnt them.
If you if you are watching Natalie,
your t-shirts you got me. I haven't
burnt them. That needs washing again.
All the shorts. See, I haven't burnt them, Natalie.
I would never ever burn these. I will
never ever ever burn them. A titty I
burnt. Yeah, anger. But I can't burn these.
I can't burn him.
So, I do appreciate that. Just [ __ ]
the cheddar I burnt. Still talking
about that. I can't help it. Mr. Bean,
man. I was only about last night. Can
she not say? [ __ ] hell. They weren't
even [ __ ] doing what she was saying. Okay. Now
give the TV
to York. I'm all right. Y is not in my TV.
That that TV is Natalie's TV. Like I
said to Nalie, it's her TV. I told
Natalie I was getting all the [ __ ] back.
I've already ordered a seti as well.
A seti is on its way. I've even rung up
the shop to get it all [ __ ] sorted.
That's coming in the next two weeks.
They're just waiting for the [ __ ] the
payment and that this new city will be
here exactly the same one what she had
exactly the same color.
You know what I mean? And she's saying I
don't care about her and all that. I
went cold approaching. if I didn't care
about her. I would have got her a new
TV. I want to have got her a new [ __ ] seti.
And it's not that I'm even getting her
Xbox [ __ ] one or whatever they are.
Not the Xbox 360, one of the the newest Xbox,
the newest Xbox, cuz she got rid of
everything. And I think that's tight as
[ __ ] is that cuz she had to get rid of everything.
And her mom caused that [ __ ] man.
That's what I mean, man.
I've got a good mom. That's why I I talk
about my mom a lot cuz I've got a really good mom.
>> What? The TV? You know, it's Natalie's.
It's Natalie's TV. It's not my TV. It's Natalie's.
>> Can I have the TV?
No, it's not.
>> Do you want to see the TV? You
>> want to see the TV I got? Yeah.
>> I can show you the TV I got.
It might be on this phone. What's up?
Yeah, this is the the the TV I got.
It's all the catalog. I don't give a
[ __ ] But this is what I got.
I got that TV.
That's the TV. I got her.
It's only a 32 like, but
>> I think you like this whole YouTube thing, m
>> nice. What?
>> I think you like this whole YouTube thing.
>> I don't do a [ __ ] Do a [ __ ] [ __ ]
I'm already on you since I ain't got no
one to talk to now. Nobody. Who the [ __ ]
have I got to talk to now?
No one really.
Unless I just sit here like this on my
own. That is one sec.
Let me turn camera around.
Unless I just sit here like this.
Yeah, I'm still talking to that woman I
met yesterday. You remember what? What?
>> I'm still talking to that woman that I
met yesterday with her mom.
>> Okay, that's good. That's good. See, I'm
talking to nobody. Yeah, I ain't got
nobody to talk to. I don't even have a
[ __ ] woman anymore because she thinks
I would approach him last night.
[ __ ] hell, man. Don't you think if I
called approaching last night, I would
have been texting birds the second myself?
>> Wait, let me see. What? Where's the TV?
Have you got it?
Did you not see it?
>> No, I saw it. I was busy. Sorry again.
>> No, I was busy.
Let me see.
Get back on. Meet me. I'm not going back
on Meet Me. I'm not going on Meet Me. I
rather just wait till Natalie's ready until
Wait for Natalie.
>> Is that Is that how big the TV is? It's 32 in.
>> 32. Yeah, that one.
Nice one. It's a nice TV. It's a lot of
nice TV. It's all right. It's not bad.
>> What brand is it?
>> Where does it say the brand?
The fivestar TV.
>> Yeah. What's the brand? Oh,
>> yeah. It's good TV. is really good TVs.
These are they are really really good
TVs. Look at the [ __ ] picture quality.
You know what I mean? So, it's not
exactly picture quality either way.
And this is also what what I'm getting
now as well. I'll show you. I've already
[ __ ] ordered the [ __ ]
I'm not even chatting [ __ ] I've already ordered it.
I'm not being funny. Look how happy me
and Natalie look.
>> You want to see my TV?
That's my TV.
>> Yeah, I've got a cinema. him. I've got a >> Franklin. >> DJ.
>> I told Natalie I'm getting a [ __ ] back.
I've told her this. I promised her it. I
told her I keep to my promise. I've got
a TV back. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? Why am I going to
parade my promise to her?
>> Franklin goes flying.
>> Look at this. This is also what I got as
well. I'm getting a list.
This is what I'm getting her as well.
I'm getting it all back.
>> I found it all.
You know what I mean? So, I am getting
her a new set.
Literally, I am. I'm getting her a new
set, a new TV. I don't give a [ __ ] She
can hate me all she wants. I've done nothing wrong.
How many people have you got watching?
I'm a fool.
I've already ordered it all. This is
what I'm talking about, peeps. I've
already ordered it all. I promise not
all this [ __ ] And I'm not breaking my
promise to that woman.
>> No, I'm a good man.
>> My TV.
>> Yeah. It's not better than my TV though.
I've got a cinema, me a cinema. longer
begging for nuts. Sit. What?
Say something. I'm giving up on you. I
be the one if you want me to. Anywhere
while I follow you.
I like that song. It's a good song. Yeah. Song
coming out called Weapons on the 7th.
Greasy. It's called Weapons.
I'm going to go to this more and watch
it. It's called Weapons. I'm
>> sure you've heard of it.
I'm still [ __ ] from yesterday.
>> I'll be a lovely ex partner.
>> I've only got one ex and that's it.
You know, you know never going to get a
man like me again. Well, he is, but he
isn't. who a man who can afford all this
[ __ ] for her. I can afford it, people.
This is what I'm talking about. I can
afford this [ __ ] for her and I'm getting
it all back for her. I'll bet you any
money yet. I bet you any money tomorrow.
Not even chatting [ __ ] now. This TV will
be here tomorrow. She can pick it up.
>> Okay, I'm going to have to kick him for
a little bit, bro.
>> This is getting ridiculous now, bro. He
was talking about this all night
yesterday and he's talking about it all day again. Oh,
sorry, bro. I'm going to have to time
you out for a little bit, buddy.
You actually giving me a headache.
Bro, he's actually giving me a [ __ ] headache, bro.
Am I Am I Am I the only one?
Oh, bro, you're actually giving me a headache, bro.
Like Monty, bro. No offense, bro.
You need to change the subject, bro. [ __ ] hell. Jesus.
No. Bad, bro.
I went I went all the way to Birmingham
yesterday to see him. Yeah, bro.
Jesus Christ, Monty, bro. Jesus.
That is a madness. Uh
yeah, I paid for both round night out.
It cost £200.
I don't care about that, bro. I bought
us breakfast. So what?
I need to take some cocoa in a minute. I think actually
he's actually giving me a [ __ ] headache.
He is actually giving me a [ __ ] headache, bro.
It's been all day, isn't it? All [ __ ] day.
All day. It has been. It's been all day, mate.
Oh my god, bro.
No, back in, bro. cuz he's just going to
talk about Natalie.
I gave him the best advice as well. [ __ ] hell. Jeez.
Yeah, I'm on these friends. Jesus Christ.
What do you think, Grezy?
It gets annoying in it, bro. [ __ ] bro.
Oh, bro. No. In a minute.
Yeah. In a while, bro. I need a break from it. [ __ ] hell.
Who didn't want Natalie?
No, I don't go on about women every day. at all.
Some people today
And I tell you things that I've done
like go out approach and that
I'm going to have to cut him off, bro,
if he keeps talking about it, bro.
Do you blame me? Crazy. Jesus.
I'm not showing you no approaching videos, matey.
I've got plenty of approaching videos.
There were some good women out
yesterday. He could have tried it with them.
I know what he means cuz obviously with
me that USA Izzy, but with that USA
Izzy, I was younger
now. He's a lot older than me.
Two faced, not two faced about anyone.
Never have been, never will be.
No, definitely not.
But um it's He's older than me, bro. So
he should know. You know,
this is supposed to happen when you're younger.
This is supposed to happen when you're
younger. You know what I'm saying?
Anyways, we'll let him back in now. Franklin.
There you go. >> [ __ ]
I up. I show up. I should up.
>> You can't help yourself, lads.
>> I can't ignore P. I really can't. I
can't. I really can't. I tell you the
truth. I can't.
It's not me. is my
>> almost like [ __ ] that [ __ ] long
legs in Britney, bro.
>> No, PT. I've never been like this for
anyone in my entire life.
This is my first time ever being like
this for any woman.
I really never ever felt like this.
Natalie took my virginity, mate.
>> Yeah, right.
>> So, you think she's good looking?
Not all right. She's not bad looking. >> Yeah.
I like her, man. I just I don't know why it is.
She's putting me under a lot of [ __ ] I
ain't she I need to just let go and I
can't help myself.
>> No, I know I can't help myself. I know I
can't. But she [ __ ] don't understand
that, does she? She thinks I'm a [ __ ]
going out cold approaching and [ __ ]
[ __ ] like that cuz she [ __ ] recorded
me and [ __ ] like that doing it. Even
though I wasn't even cold approaching
like that. I wasn't even looking for
women last night.
>> You should have been.
>> I should have been. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. To
be honest with you. No. Yeah.
What's actually confusing the [ __ ] out
of me? Yeah.
Is all this time me texting her, I'll
just say her. We'll bring that name.
Lovely. Every time me every time I'm
texting her and stuff like that, it's
like completely blank. Ignore. >> Yeah.
But when I go out with you last night
and then she's there going mad at me for
going out cold for going out cold approaching
when she's finished me but I wasn't cold
approaching last night cuz I were
talking about Natalie all night last night. >> Yeah.
>> Know what I mean? So I was sexually cold
approaching. I did talk to some women
last night. I'm not saying that I
didn't. I talked to men too last night. >> Yeah.
>> You know. So
>> swim by it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Of course. Course. I I
wasn't out last night to go out and go
out on the pool or nothing like I wasn't.
But if she really really wants me to, I
can go and do that. I really can. But I'm not.
>> You swing both ways.
But that's confused the [ __ ] out of me
because it seems to me
she's having me waiting for her for her
choice and for her answer what she wants.
You know what I mean? She could have
just said here we got a time out. Sort
yourself out and then we'll see where
where we go from there. Yeah. But
instead she just blanks. >> Why? >> What?
So heads up people if you do go out with
Natalie. Yeah. Heads up. Yeah. You don't
get you don't get chance to speak. You just get
>> And also what's weird is why
>> why is she going on Lord Jay's? That's weird.
>> Yeah. It is weird. It is weird. And then
talking about what
>> she's going on mine. She's going on Lord Jay's.
>> Yeah. And Lord J were calling the [ __ ]
out of her. Lord J were calling the [ __ ]
out of her to with her mom and that. And
then you get me who's actually there
sticking up in Natalie against Lord J
and against her basically her mom and
her mom doxing the [ __ ] out of her and
going around shagging her partners.
You know what? I never shagged Nat's
mom. Never. She's [ __ ] ugly as sinners.
She's not even attractive. Lisa is not
attractive one bit. after he is
told to be >> what
>> was Natalie told her to be?
>> I'm not saying nothing about Natalie's
eye or nothing like that. I'm not saying
[ __ ] about that
cuz I don't want Natalie think I'm
taking a piss or no I'm not saying
nothing about Natalie Natalie size or
whatever else that
think of it Monty. Yeah,
my name Mike was obsessed with Danny G
and then she never went she she never
got back with him. So maybe she'll never
get back with you.
>> If she doesn't I'm not asked anymore PJ
to be honest. I'm not a money m maybe
I'm going on about it now. Yeah, cuz
it's just recently happened. Money might
go on about it constantly where I will
end up stopping talking about it and
then that's it. I'm done.
You know, I'm one of these I only stay
so long and I'm done. Yeah.
>> You know what I mean?
>> That's what I mean. If a woman's not
with you long term and she knows she's
not going to be with you long term,
what's the point of saying yeah if she
knows she's not going to be with you
long term or she's not going to give you
a chance if you [ __ ] up or whatever or
don't give you a chance to talk or you
were like I don't believe you. I don't
believe you. You went out cold. You know
some woman touch your ass. Oh yeah.
Since you all passed didn't even talk to
any [ __ ] room at women hardly last
night. That were [ __ ] PJ who talked
to the most women last night. More women
than what I did. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? Some woman pass
me, walking past me, talk to me ass. It
went by purpose. I knew that. I just
said PJ should just talk me out. That
woman pass. Not that. Look. Yeah. This
is how I was stood. Yeah. I show you.
Yeah. Right. Just say this over here.
Not bad. It's not explaining showing. I
was basically blocking the door off
basically and a woman slid past me,
scraped her arm across my ass or my back
or whatever it was. It was the accident.
But I didn't feel no woman's asses. I
didn't even kiss no women last night. PJ
did. Lonely lucky bastard.
I don't I got a wank. >> Yeah.
>> You know what? I should have gone with
that girl last night. Don't know. I
should have gone around the next corner. >> Yeah.
>> I would have gone for the wank. I would
have gone for the full multi. >> Yeah.
>> Basically, I would have gone for the full multi
is boring now. Multi brother. Okay.
No, I'm talking about me and PG on a
night out last night. That's what I'm
talking about now with them them two
girls from last night.
You know what I mean? But it
really weren't that bad looking to be
honest with you.
>> I think you're fit.
>> I'm not fit. Yeah. Do
>> you know there's dogs in GTA 5? Um 5. >> Mhm.
>> It's weird, isn't it?
>> Yeah. There's birds and hats and that gets what?
Why don't you just go with G Monty?
[ __ ] off. Are you [ __ ] mental?
You've been dead in the next week.
Can't handle that. I can't handle women
shouting, mate. I can't handle it. I
can't do it. It's just when it's just
shouting. I can't
>> a bad place.
>> I can't I can't do shouting, mate. It's
shouting. I just can't handle it.
>> I can handle it.
>> I can't believe we was in the same city,
right? where where [ __ ] Jack the Ripper lives. Yeah,
>> it's weird though.
>> That is weird.
>> I wonder if he still lives there, bro.
>> Yeah, he will do. He will do.
>> He was in one of them He was in one of
them places where he was in one of them
[ __ ] rehab center. be with
>> always used to do that [ __ ] stupid
American accent. That fake American
>> No. What pissed me off about him? Yeah.
Is that he used to run around his
bedroom naked? All it naked back on the
PlayStation 3 camera and that
>> no then he has his teddy bear. He have a
full party and he weren't asked. He's
shacking a teddy bear and everything.
who who slid through the teddy bear and
[ __ ] shagging the [ __ ] out of the
teddy bear. You sick [ __ ]
You met that guy as well, you mad bastard.
>> His name is Luke Lambeath.
>> Yeah, I know. When I first met him.
>> he was an actual psychopath.
>> Yeah, we were bouncing on the bed naked.
>> Literally, that was the first time I met
him. We were bouncing on the bed
completely [ __ ] bothered naked. I I
got all the I couldn't stop laughing. I
couldn't even press the exit button. I
was in stes where we were bouncing the
bed with his knob shaking up and down
and [ __ ] [ __ ] mental and then
shagging teddy bears. And then you're
just there talking and with lots of
people and next minute chap the rippers
walking past the camera [ __ ] bullet
naked. No, no pants on nothing at all.
His [ __ ] balls are dangling and his
ass cheeks are all out.
Yeah, he lives in Birmingham. That one
he I went to a comic book store with
him. He used to go to a comic book store.
>> What makes you meet him? Not your
[ __ ] men or you?
>> I don't know to be honest.
And he become obsessed with me and that.
>> Yeah, he's do you know he's bisexual or
gay or whatever? Yeah, it must be.
that's [ __ ] [ __ ] up that man. You
[ __ ] met some
people. You tell you that now. Yeah, I
met them all through
>> EG. Who is it?
>> Think about it, Monty. Monty, they are
all weird. They are all [ __ ] up, but I
met them all through you.
So, what does that say about you then, Monty?
>> No, it's [ __ ] PJ. What?
>> I have met some weird [ __ ] up people,
Monty, but I met them all through you.
So, what does that say?
Yeah, that's the [ __ ] community in
it. That's what that is.
>> I met them all through you.
>> Yeah, that's actually download [ __ ]
meet me. Why not? [ __ ] it.
Meet me. Meet.
>> Yeah. Give it a while.
>> Give it a while. It
>> Yeah. Go on. Go on. Here. Download it
now. Yeah. You see in it. This is it.
Let's go and check some birds out in this.
>> Why don't you go make money, Mike or Bill?
Go on, stick us on medium and we'll go
and check these birds out.
>> You're obsessed with women. Yeah,
>> I'm not obsessed with women. I'm just
[ __ ] I'm I'm bored getting [ __ ]
treated like a prick of women. I'm not
even downloading it. I'm not I'm not
even I'm not even doing that. I'm not
even downloading a [ __ ] Look, I had downloaded it.
Look, it's not downloaded. See,
I don't want it. I don't want me to be
I'll be honest with you. I might say
done. I'm done. I'm done.
>> If she wants me now, I'm I'm done
talking about her. But I'm just going to
say one thing. If she wants me, she can
come and get me. I'm done chasing her.
I'm done talking about her. Meet me.
>> Sorry, Luke. I'm not gay. >> Luke,
>> I don't know him. I'm not saying I'm
>> You like my food? Do you drink your Pia?
>> You know that Jack the Ripper used to go
weeks without showering.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You like my new phone, don't you? >> What?
>> You do that in it?
>> No, you have showers every day nearly, mate.
>> I have a shower. If I don't go out, it's
every two days. When I come out from
Birmingham, I go in the shower straight away. >> Yeah,
>> I got fresh clothes straight away, bro.
But sometimes I shower every two days.
I want Diesel back now to be honest with
you. I want my [ __ ] dog back.
>> Get him back then.
>> I can't get him back. He's gone a he to
pay for him now.
>> Well, do you know where he is?
>> No. Do a [ __ ] I left him in the dog kennel.
>> So, you basically have lost everything
really in it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I've lost everything, mate.
Everything. Natalie's lost everything as
well, but I'm I'm getting everything
back for Natalie. That's what I'm
talking about. You know what I mean? So,
she hasn't lost anything really because
I'm getting it all back for her.
But either way, she hasn't lost anything
in some form of way because she's got a
good Well, she had a good man who
started Monty. Yeah. You was on here
with Kaye and the dog.
>> That's how you started. remember? >> Yeah.
>> No, no, no, no. I started with with just
me first. It was just me on my own in my
own house. I didn't even have Diesel
when I first joined into this. Then then
he ended up having Diesel. Then we got
Then then I moved in with Kayie with my dog.
met Natalie. Then then Natalie asked me
if I wanted to move in here with her. I
said yeah. Then they said you the dog's
not allowed in though. I had to get rid
of the dog for a better better roof over my head.
So I got rid of Diesel,
moved in, but I thought that me and
Natalie was going to actually last. I thought Natalie
did actually love me. Like
because if you love someone
then you don't treat them like you do
like you don't ignore them. You sort
your troubles out. You don't [ __ ]
fight. You sort your [ __ ] out.
She can't do that though.
>> And all he is left with is a 32 in telly.
>> Can't go with that. Anyways, I'm sick of
getting [ __ ] I'm sick of getting [ __ ]
and then just what I mean. I've Have you
not noticed I don't stay in one spot.
I always move around.
>> But you're actually [ __ ] in it.
>> Me? Yeah. Yeah, I'm [ __ ]
>> Why did you say to me earlier? Yeah.
Well, yesterday like when I go back to
London, I'll still have money. What's
What's that got to do with anything?
>> What? What do you mean? You said that
when I go back to London, at least I'll
still have money. What do you mean?
>> At least I still have money. Meaning
still got something.
>> No, you said I'll still have money. At
least if I go back when I go back to London.
>> Oh, okay. Yeah. Meaning at least you
still got money to spend. That's what I
meant. Like at least you still got some money.
>> Yeah. You then you just have to build
yourself up. But
>> I've got I've got I've got money. This
went comes in my bank. It's [ __ ]
You know, this is why I've quit weed now
because I'm sick of spending my money on
weed. I'm not
>> I'm worried about you, man. Cuz £20 is
not going to last for [ __ ] two weeks.
That's less than two pound a day.
>> Yeah, that's gone. Not that now. I spent
like 20 quid.
>> So, you're [ __ ]
No, not really because I spend it on
[ __ ] 35 [ __ ] burgers
to last me two weeks. >> Jesus.
>> Yeah, five burgers to last me a week.
So, I'm on burgers, me,
>> you really are [ __ ] in it.
>> I am truly unfort Yeah, I am. Yeah, I Jesus [ __ ] over
you. You could just lose your life over an app, it
to your pin number. I'm not giving you
my pin number.
>> I'm It's all because you wouldn't get off YouTube.
>> I was off YouTube. I just [ __ ] stupid
getting kicked out of places, man. You
know when you're getting kicked out of
places 24/7 off women it [ __ ] your head up.
>> You got 35 burgers. You spent the 20 on
35 burgers. Yeah. So
what drinks are you going to drink? >> Yeah.
>> I can see you ending up dead me. >> Monsters.
How do you monsters?
>> I've drunk all them, mate. They're all
[ __ ] empty. These bastards.
Oh, these are [ __ ] empty.
>> I've got water. >> Jesus.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] it. I'll show you the
[ __ ] burgers now.
>> There's [ __ ] in the freezer, but I'm not
eating that [ __ ] There is food in the
freezer, but that's [ __ ] been there
for [ __ ] years. I don't know how long
that shit's been there. I don't I'm not
eating that [ __ ] in that freezer. Not
even my food in that freezer. I won't
eat anyone else's food.
>> Mr. Beast said you're more skinn than Timmy. >> No, the
36. It's 36 burgers
that cost me £8.99.
You have to go to a food bank.
>> I'm not going to go no food bank.
>> I get paid in two weeks.
>> Know what I mean? So I get paid in two weeks.
>> Yeah, but two weeks is a long time and
you ain't got money.
>> I just got a [ __ ]
[ __ ] Lord, idiot. What I'm going to do? [ __ ] Lord.
I should have moved up here. Well, down
here. I couldn't have [ __ ] moved down
here to be honest with you. I should
have stay dead where
I would have still have a [ __ ] dog.
At least I would have still had someone
on something. Now look at me now. That's
why people say never get rid of your dog
cuz that dog will never get rid of you.
Know what I mean?
where women where people do
>> people's feelings change and that's [ __ ] angry.
>> Can't you get a loan out?
>> No, not yet.
>> I'm sure you can get a loan from Universal Credit. >> No,
you should be able to. You can apply for it online.
>> No, no, because when I was homeless
cuz I had to sign back on, didn't I? cuz
I was claiming with Kick
and when I was homeless she had actually
signed back on but I didn't get my money
there and then you know what I mean so I
had to [ __ ]
get a CL I had to get a claim then to
get some money so I've already had a bit
of that I only got I only got 200 out of
you know what I mean so I had 200 out of
that already and then then you can't go
out and get more out of that. Either
way, you got to wait until you pay that
back before you can get another load.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> I feel bad.
>> I had a nice take today.
>> Is that what women think?
>> I bought I bought you breakfast and that
is it. So,
>> no. Of course, course. Appreciate it.
I'll give you that money back.
>> No, I don't want the money back. I don't
want it back, bro.
>> No, I'll give it you back.
>> I don't want it back. >> Dave,
>> [ __ ] that, bro. But it was nice that
breakfast place. I wish they had one in London.
>> Dave in PJ. PJ, don't say me. I'm good,
buddy. If I die, I die of [ __ ]
starvation. I die.
>> If I die,
I'm not laughing. It's just the way he says it.
Just the way you said it.
>> If I starve, I That's funny.
>> We have money.
>> Mr. B, do you remember when Timmy was so
skinn because of gambling he had to eat
um expired bread?
>> He said he had to like eat expired bread and that
>> when he lost all his money gambling.
PJ, did you take?
>> Um, no. It's just I buy people food anyways.
>> You didn't eat in six days. No, I just I
just wanted to get
>> I haven't in six days. That's why I
haven't been eating poops. I haven't ate
for like six days.
>> Me and Monty had a bacon and cheese
omelette in it. Ham and cheese omelette
with a coke. It was nice. PJ, what see you?
>> No, he said I take Yeah, PJ won't see
you starve. Yeah, I won't see Monty
>> No, same as me. I'm a I never see anyone
starve. I'm [ __ ] can't do it.
Now yesterday I Peter will tell you I
had a bunny on me yesterday. He only had
about what 50 quid. I ended up getting
some homeless man a [ __ ] cup of coffee
and then we can give him a quid.
Some homeless guy.
>> You know what I mean? So I give a
[ __ ] homeless guy a cup of coffee out
of 50 quid. I kind of left myself there.
Put 20 quid in my other pocket for get
some food in a little bit of food. Yeah,
>> last me the two weeks,
>> but I knew 100% would not last me the
two weeks. So, I had to see the burgers. I seen
>> 36 burgers, so they should last me the
two weeks if I go easy with them.
>> It's just weird money.
>> I need a woman, mate. That's what I
need. I can't do all this house [ __ ] living [ __ ]
>> I can do it.
I can do it, but I can't [ __ ] cook
[ __ ] beans and sauce toast or [ __ ] anything, mate.
>> I'm a good cook. Money.
>> No, there's a really good cook. I'm not
bringing her up. I'm just saying that she is.
>> I'm a good one.
>> I can cook on one here.
>> I don't even know if I a cooker, mate.
Yeah, you can't.
I don't even know a cooker. I'm not even
taking a piss on that either.
That's not funny, is it?
>> No, it's not funny. It's really not.
I'm sick of I'm sick of [ __ ] being
there for people and people are not
there for you. You know what I mean? Obviously.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
I stood by that woman as well, man. You
know when you stand by someone and you
just [ __ ] do you over five times and
it's like what have I done? >> Yeah.
But literally I am missing my dog. I've
been missing him for ye for quite a
while. I've been missing him for quite a
>> I'm not getting another dog anyway. So
>> No, I'm not going to get another dog.
>> I never got bag. Never
me good friends.
Yeah, I rather live off them [ __ ]
burgers for a week. I won't even go
about me, peeps.
>> No, there's food in a freezer. Can I
show you that? No, there's [ __ ] food in there.
>> Oh, I won't eat it because I don't know
whose food it was.
>> So, I won't eat it.
>> I won't eat other [ __ ] people's food
while [ __ ] being in the [ __ ]
freezer. I don't know how long it's been
there for either.
Look, there's food in the freezer. That
is food. But I don't know how long that
has been in there for
the burgers. I got
[ __ ] fridge [ __ ] but I'm having my
milk, mate. I need to look at the D. I'm
just going to drink this. Why do you Why
do you go live asking for donations?
No, I'm not asking for no donations. >> Why?
>> I'm not a foc
or or a lo.
I'm not going to do [ __ ] like that. PJ
>> Kieran, are you skinned right now?
>> I am skin right now.
>> Not you said Kieran. Not you, bro. I'm
not talking about you.
Not that this move me up anyways. I'm
[ __ ] down at home, mate.
>> Is it off? >> No.
>> I feel bad, Monty.
>> Why do you feel bad?
>> Cuz you're [ __ ] in it.
>> I'm [ __ ] I'm allowed to be [ __ ]
So, what do you just play the slots in
the arcades then, Kieran?
>> I might try that fishing frenzy again at some point.
>> You reckon it's a good idea if I try it again, Kieran? What? Monty,
>> what was Kieran saying?
>> No, we're just talking about
>> No, about N. Oh, okay.
Birmingham was long here and oh bro
getting back was so long. [ __ ]
>> that was a night last night though. I'll
give it that. That was a [ __ ] top
like that last night.
>> Was course was it was
even check [ __ ] on that either. That was
a last night.
>> Yeah, I get you killed.
>> We went live. No, we didn't go live, did
we? We make videos and uploaded them
every we went to
>> No, we did go live. It wet. >> Yeah, few times.
>> I can't believe [ __ ] she she thought
we're [ __ ] cold approaching, man.
Oh, there's a
>> Yeah. Yeah.
You know what? Next time we go out, PJ.
Yeah. [ __ ] watch the [ __ ] [ __ ]
I get. Yeah.
I'll show you how to pull, lad. Yeah,
I'll [ __ ] pull. [Music]
I can do it now. I can go out now and do
it now so I'm not asked.
>> [ __ ] it. No. Yeah, we go out again. Yeah.
My turn to get the beers in PJ.
>> Yes, C. >> Yes. [Music]
>> [ __ ] go around dancing with the
granny's. Yeah. Right.
See the thing is as well I don't think
no [ __ ] it up
But don't worry,
she's probably thriving off it to be
honest with you cuz I'm talking about it
too much. So, I'm just going to stop.
Yeah, I know. I'm stopping. It's [ __ ]
hanging. I'm saying it myself. It's Come on.
What? Get back on the to
sub t sub t sub t sub t sub t sub t sub
t sub t sub t sub t subs tubes. I'm not
getting back on the tubes. I'm not
coming back on here. They only jump on
the panel there again with PJ and but
I'm never going back live again.
I'm never doing that [ __ ] multi ass sleep.
I've not been sleeping to be honest with
you. I haven't been asleep either. I've
not been eating. I've not been sleeping.
That's why I look like a [ __ ] one
eyes up, one eyes down. Oh, look.
Back in my pants now.
That's all tobacco people. It's not a
stain. Only tobacco. Look.
Only tobacco pants.
What was I showing you then?
Oh yeah, my face. I been asleep. See you
now. I cut myself there bad with the shaver.
Yeah, I ripped my skin off with with the shaver and uh
rips all my skin off
and that was with a planet shaver
or to get a new bird
go live. I'm not going live.
I love PJ too much. Multi most England
mostly needs a real woman. I do need a
real woman. I really do need a real
woman. A woman who's not going to run
off when [ __ ] gets hard. Of course I do,
buddy. Of course. Matt is
using you. It seems it to be honest with
you. It does seem it
run up when it gets hard. Oh, yeah.
PJ is right though. I'm going on a bit
too much about it. Obviously, it's not
me who's going on about it. It's all used really
needs to go away. Yes, she does not.
It's not even that Kay thinks she's
bigger than me. There's nowhere near
bigger than me on YouTube. I'm more
[ __ ] well known than Kelly on
YouTube. More well known than what she
will ever be on YouTube. Kay is only
known on YouTube because of me. That's
only why Kay's known on YouTube. If it
weren't for me, she won't even be known on YouTube.
And that is true. I don't know why Kay
is getting all bigheaded when no one
knew knew Kay only through me. Good night, M. Good night. Multi can away
need to start using my [ __ ]
translator. [ __ ] [ __ ] to read these comments. One sec
some of these comments. See what I mean?
I took over PGR. It's just left it down to me.
>> Steven Howard King number three. Monty can.
>> Oh, Monty can always pull.
>> Monty crying. Monty been crying. Say
something. I'm giving you
>> Say something. I'm giving up on you.
I be the one if you want me to. Anyone follow you
to say something? I'm giving up on you.
Feeling so small.
It was over my head.
Learning to love or starting to crawl. No.
At least I got balls low. Peeps [ __ ]
putting videos up there of me crying. Come on.
Monty crying. Say something. I'm giving
up on you. Kieran. Good night, Pip King.
True brother Rob and OPJ supporter. It's
a struggle. I know. Sutton
F. Luton. Say something if giving up on you.
It's a good song though. I like it. Say
something from giving up on you. It is
>> good song. I've never sung that a song
to any woman to no one or but just one
person I've sung that actual song to
that's actually Natalie. Only sung that
song to actual Natalie. Not sung it to
any other woman at all. I've probably
sung that song to myself cuz I like that
song, but I've never sung that song to
any woman for full. I'm giving up on her
anyways now. I can't be asked. I think
she knows it now cuz I'm not a text or [ __ ] what?
So, I'm not asked anymore. I'm not
[ __ ] I'm not trying anymore. She
wants me to go, I go. Not asked. Do you feel
Monty, do you feel stupid for loving that?
>> Yeah, I do feel stupid loving that.
Yeah. Yeah, I [ __ ] do. If she can do
this to me. Yeah, I really do.
She said she loved me. She She was there
for me. And then I get rid of my dog cuz
I'm thinking that I'm going to be with
that for her for a long time.
And then I thought she was the [ __ ]
one. I thought that Natalie was the
[ __ ] one. I really did. I [ __ ]
really thought she was the one. Well,
guess [ __ ] happens. People guess she's
not the one.
Cuz if if she was the one, she would
have stopped by me. crying turnts
burns true and crying. Hey Su for her
too. Welcome to live chat. Remember to
guard your privacy and abide by our community guidelines.
>> So she did love me. They need to
understand it. You know what I mean? She
wouldn't have let me go like she did.
Don't matter what mistakes I make. No
matter what I do.
You know, you stand by, you love
someone, you stand by them. You don't
let that person go. As soon as you let
Soon as you let that person go, I'm
talking to another phone. You think I'm
on that phone. Soon as you let a person
go and that's it, you're basically
[ __ ] What are you going to do then?
Do you know what I mean? Y
what to [ __ ] me over?
I can just [ __ ] over 10 times worse
by just going out just getting proper
laid and doing it live.
Proper sning going snogging birds and
[ __ ] I can go out and do that. But I'm
not doing that [ __ ]
Like literally, do you know how many
numbers I could have got got last night
with PJ if I actually put my mind to it
and actually went and [ __ ] done cold
pro? I could have got bare numbers last night,
but I didn't literally did get no
numbers last night cuz I weren't looking who
yourself. What you on about?
It was just a time. It wasn't a tie. Me
and Natalie, we were good. We were good together.
We was We was actually good. It's not that she
It just feels like being played to be
honest with you. That's how I feel like being played
cuz when [ __ ] gets tough women
Kay still fances me you know peep she
does Kelly still actually fances me cuz
if you think about it all the times and
that when Kayie is on her [ __ ] panels
I I would never go back out with Kelly
anyways never never ever but I think she
does actually still find me because every time
I mention something to tell her that I
never loved her or anything like that.
You can hear it in her voice that she
she it's her inner
knowing that I've never loved her.
Exactly. Yeah. Kelly follows me
everywhere. Everywhere where I go, she's
there. She's [ __ ] there and then
she's calling me and all that. You know
what I mean? Kelly. Kay's probably the
only one who [ __ ] loves me.
It just makes sense. But I never go back
out with Kayie. Never ever would I go
back out with that.
Not even that. K's [ __ ] ugly. P. She
is. She just [ __ ] ugly. She's [ __ ]
ugly. To be honest with you, I don't
know what I seen in it.
PM number two, Bill the Kraken. When the
going gets tough, women get going. PJ
knows all about it. Still fancies you.
>> Yeah, that's what women do, you know. I
thought Natalie was strong stronger than
that. Like I thought Nat was going to be
the one who was actually going to stay
with me through the arguing
and not me and Natalie weren't even
arguing. It wasn't even arguing what
what we were doing. We just didn't
really bad disagreements. It weren't
even really bad disagreements. It's
because I woke her up by accident.
Obviously, I already told you, so it
don't really [ __ ] matter. You know
what I mean? So, and then she's ending
it straight up. Every time we every time
we argue or whatever, it's over. It's
over. It's over. It's always over with
Natalie. That's why don't go out with
Natalie on YouTube, dude. Just don't
[ __ ] that, man. Just [ __ ] your head up.
I should have listened to people. Don't
go out with Natalie. She's looking. She's No.
Now look at me now. I'm stuck in
Natalie's [ __ ] old house now.
Now I'm stuck in Natalie's old [ __ ] place.
[ __ ] crazy, ain't it? Multi man
living in Natalie's old house.
That's mental. That's [ __ ] crazy
Yeah. You never thought it though, would
you? Never think that [ __ ] be living at Natalie's.
Are you Well, I need to start using
translator to read these comments proper.
I keep my phone on translating.
All right, start from that here.
>> Mr. Monty Burns Nat was never looking for love.
>> I don't think she was looking for love
either to be honest.
Why do women
>> because I'm too soft with women? Hilly
Billy. I'm too soft with them.
Go back to lieutenant life and I'm all
right. Not I don't need if I do if I get
booted up here then I will do you a victim_rock
why do women bully you?
>> Are you a victim?
No. Obviously I'm a [ __ ] weakling
when it comes to women. I [ __ ] I'm
too soft. I don't know what to do with a
woman. You know obviously I know what to
do with them but
just a soft ass when it comes to women.
I don't know what to do with them. It's
not me, it's them. You know what I mean?
Right. This is the difference, right? Kay,
right? If you get in a relationship with
with Kaye. Yeah. This is what what is
going to happen. Yeah.
You are not the boss in that
relationship. Kay's the boss. Yeah. Kay
is the boss in that relationship. And
this is what I'm on about with Natalie.
No one was the boss.
You were both were equal where Kaye,
she's the boss of that relationship. What goes
and that's where Kaye gets very
controlly and very argumentative is cuz
she thinks she's a boss in a
relationship. [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
What YouTuber am I going to shag next anyways?
Who's next for multi?
What YouTuber females next for multi now?
>> Mr. Monty Burns, now you're stuck. Mr.
Monty Burns, go back to the 10 line.
Steven Howard, pimp king, M number
three. Mr. Monty Burns, the weather's
good. Steven Howard, pimp king M number
three have told PJ to shove out
will end up like dart.
>> No, I don't want ugly birds, mate. I
don't want ugly women anymore. Like I've
been out with one ugly woman and that wouldn't [ __ ]
kill it. Only went out with one ugly
woman in my life. Never again.
Mel8 is ugly and G's ugly. Guys, let's