Oh [ __ ]
Jesus Christ, man. Had a lovely snooze.
Lovely little slurs.
A lovely little snooze.
having a little snooze.
Oh man, I definitely need to go collect
them winnings today, bro. [ __ ]
It's been two days.
Yeah, I get. Yeah. Do you know what made
me laugh, Grezy? Now you know how I feel.
He burnt his finger and he said, "Ow."
And then Stitch was like, "Now you know
how I feel." Nice shot.
Yeah, bro. I went to bed last night,
bro. I kept I had hiccups all day, bro.
And it was hurting me.
Horrible hiccups. They [ __ ] hurt,
bro. So, I just went to sleep. Yeah.
Hope we don't hear about Natalie today.
just playing some Franklin.
Yeah, I just hope we don't hear bad
today. But I'm still talking to this
woman, Greavves, that I met in
Birmingham. So, well, I'm talking to two
actually and they they keep replying. So,
Maybe I'll meet one of them.
It's cute, ain't it?
Oh, bless you.
Oh, what are you going to get for
McDonald's today, Grezy?
You're just trying to get me fat. I know
your little plans.
You're just trying to get me fat. You
want to do a£10 football bet for um Saturday. Uh
Really? You're getting worse. You
You fat bastard.
What the [ __ ] Really?
You fat [ __ ]
Jeez. [ __ ] madness.
What? So, you're going to eat 20 nuggets
and a burger, you fat bastard.
You're a fat [ __ ] You are.
Yeah, she's replying. Definitely.
She's already replied. I think this one
should meet, man. She's been texting me all day.
Well, I mean to be honest with you,
there's less people in Birmingham.
So, I mean like
there's less competition.
I think there's 9 million people in
London near enough. And then there's
obviously like 2 million people in
Birmingham, which is obviously a big difference
even though Birmingham is the second
biggest city, right? It's uh it's
obviously a lot smaller than London even
though it's the second biggest. So
maybe it's cuz they don't have there's
not as much competition over there, you know,
you know. Yeah, pretty much.
It depends. You can't really compare it.
But I mean like if if even if one of
these meet you Yeah. Then
obviously London, it's got to be easier
than London. If one of them meets you,
it has to be cuz yeah, you could just
say you got lucky. But I mean, [ __ ] How
many times do you go out in London and um
you know, you you go out week in week
out and it's very hard to even get a date. So
we'll go we'll see in it. If they meet
you then obviously it must be easier.
But you still get the stuck up [ __ ]
But you know,
Do you like what I was wearing?
Yeah, I tried I've tried helping my I
bought him a breakfast. I went out
drinking with him and stuff,
but I had to end it I had to stop
yesterday, bro, cuz he kept going on about Natalie.
Yeah, bro. But it's just a Natalie thing.
Yeah, but it's not just a Natalie thing.
Is it really? He's actually is [ __ ] I
said that to him yesterday. He's [ __ ]
He is actually [ __ ]
Like if you compare to how he started on
YouTube, right, and now, right, you you
you see the difference. He is actually
[ __ ] I said that to him yesterday.
Well, for now anyways,
cuz obviously my situation was quite
different cuz obviously he had like he
was in a relationship, had kids, and
then had a dog and now he has nothing.
Now he has 20 to last him for two weeks.
Whereas me, I went through a lot of
[ __ ] Like I got nicked and people put
up posted about me. But now I'm I'm all
right me. Like I'm [ __ ]
I've got money, like enough money. I you
know, and I'm just chilling in life,
bro. Even though I've been affected by
YouTube, there's no sort of like, how do
I explain this? Like there's no end
result now. There's an end result with
him now. Whereas me, it's just like I'm
back to just like chilling.
Even though I have been affected,
everyone's been affected by YouTube, but
he has long-term effects, if that makes
sense. I can't explain it, bro. Like,
you know what I mean? Yeah, he has 20
quid. He told everyone himself, bro. Like,
I don't have loads and loads and loads
of money anymore, but I have enough
money to have enough money to go and do
what I want. Yeah.
Yeah. 20 to last two weeks. Jeez. I feel bad, bro.
And obviously I've always sort of been
single. Like I've been on dates and I've
been with women and stuff, but I've not it's hard.
And obviously I've got like I don't know
how to explain it
how I was before. So
I told him I need to get off YouTube.
And obviously I still talk to my family.
There's only one sister I don't speak
to, but that's just how it goes. I speak
to all my family and [ __ ] So, I'm I
don't really have any problems, bro. Yeah,
he he is actually he is [ __ ]
He is actually [ __ ]
I can imagine though 20 lasted me two
weeks. But I did help him. I bought him
drinks. I bought him a breakfast and stuff,
you know. I'm not like Sorry.
Peter Belly was here to pick up the pieces. pieces, matey. As usual.
Yeah, man. So, it's [ __ ] in it.
I don't know, bro.
He just needs to be careful with his
money when he gets um his money again.
He just needs to be careful.
That's it. Yeah, I'm going to do a£10
football bet for Saturday. I'm not doing
any more than10 pound. When I collect my winnings,
I'm going to do a 10 pound football bet
with like long shot odds, bro.
I'm going to pick a nice one.
I'm only doing £10. I need to collect
that 280 today in it. So yeah.
Yeah. I spent about £200 all in all the
Birmingham trip, the trains, the drinking.
It was good, man.
Yeah, I know, bro. I know. [ __ ] knows.
I don't play it anymore, bro.
I don't play that roulette. I don't play
the slops. I only do the football.
Nah, it's not a lot to me. I won a
football bet, bro. As well. So,
I don't have loads of loads of money, bro.
I think I got about still about 2K.
That's about it, bro. I don't get loads
of money a month anymore. So, I mean,
but obviously I'm by myself. So, um I
don't have to struggle about I don't
have to struggle with money, you know?
So, it's good, man.
Got Xbox, got a TV, got a phone.
Is it a lot to you? How How much do you
How much do you get a month?
Well, I mean it is a lot. It's a lot to anyone.
Well, it is a lot.
Yeah. Here comes the fantasy.
Like I said, if it's nothing, give it to me.
These people on YouTube that say 200
nothing, 2K is nothing.
They're just fantasists.
At least you're real. 200 a lot to you.
Uh well, it's not peanuts the way you're
making out. No.
Yeah, but the thing is Yeah. You're like
you're normal though, aren't you, Gavin?
That's what that's how normal people
think of it.
That's how normal people think of it.
£200 a lot.£300 a lot. But these people
on YouTube, these fantasists,
they seem to think like thousands is
nothing. It's mad.
And no one in the real world would ever
say that. You know, most most people you
meet are probably broke.
Like if you go out and I would say I
wouldn't say they're like Monty, man,
but I'd say 70% of I'd say 70% of the
population is struggling.
So, I'd say I'm probably even better
than a lot of people.
I would say most people, but a lot of
people, you know. So, it's like
that's how most people would see it though.
Yeah. That Lee that Lee Librance was
trying to say 4K is nothing and he lives
in and he lives in Wales. He live and I
and I said to him before, "Oh, yeah, it
was six grand, wasn't it?" I was like,
"Bro, I can buy you with six grand. What
are you talking about? I could I I used
to say to that Lee, I could buy you and
a house where you live with six grand. I
could literally buy you and the house
with six grand. They're just fantasists.
Like I said, no no no normal person
talks like that. Like I've got sisters,
I've got a mom, I know people. They
People don't talk like that in real life, bro.
life, bro. trust me.
So, nothing, man. I just need to collect
the football bet today. I just haven't
been a time to.
I'm still talking to that uh
that woman keeps texting me, so
hopefully I can get to meet her. Yeah, man.
I think I think one will meet out of
this Birmingham trip. I think I will
have one that will meet
when you got two people texting you
constantly. I think one didn't reply.
I think you should get one.
Yeah, it should be one that be up for meeting. Uh
but yeah, I found there was a lot of
stuck up [ __ ] in Birmingham as well.
What's it say?
Yeah, I told him to come to London, but
he doesn't have any money to come to
London at the moment, bro. So [ __ ]
No, not that one. It's another one.
No, it's another one.
So then I'll be able to actually compare
it. If one of these meet, it could be
any of them,
right? I then it is easier than London.
Then it is easier than London if one of
them actually does. But again, I don't like Birmingham.
Yeah, I was just saying to I was just
saying to Joe, not Joe, this guy here
that come on. Yeah, she did. I was just
saying, bro, that we've all been
affected by YouTube, right? But it's
like he has long-term effects like with
like with him. Yeah. He started off with
like in a relationship with a dog, with
a with a kid, like with kids and that
whatever. Yeah. now he's by himself
with like nothing. Whereas me, I started
off on here by myself and yeah, I've
been affected by it and yeah, I've been
nicked and I've had posters, but now I'm
like back to normal, living a normal life.
So, it doesn't seem like I had long-term
effects. Whereas with him, it's very
clear the effects.
That's what I was trying to say to this guy. It's
and obviously I'm I'm a lot better than
I and I'm if anything I'm better than I
was before I come on here.
I never used to have money.
I never used to even have money.
Could I put him up at mine? Not really,
bro. And I don't Why would I do that?
He's not homeless. He He's got somewhere to live.
But he lives in Yeah, but he's not
homeless, bro. He's [ __ ] lucky they
gave him that house. In London, they
wouldn't help you, bro. In London, you'd
be [ __ ] They wouldn't even put you
where he is. That's actually right where
he is, to be honest. In London, they
wouldn't give you nothing.
They wouldn't give a [ __ ] if you were in
London, bro. So, it seems like in
Birmingham, the council actually helps
people. They don't care.
No, no, it's his place, bro. So, he's
not homeless. He's [ __ ] lucky to to
to have got there.
Especially if you don't have kids.
Jesus, bro. You're lucky to even get
that in London. They wouldn't give you
nothing. They give you [ __ ] all in London.
So, he's actually very lucky.
And then I could stay with him if I
wanted to and pay £40 a month.
I could [ __ ] That's That's [ __ ]
easy. That's cheap. That's not even bad,
bro. But I don't think I could live in
Birmingham, bro. I don't think so, man.
Nah, I don't think I would live in Birmingham, bro.
It would make no sense. Yep.
What do you think of Birmingham, Joe? I
just hate the bounces.
I don't know, man. It's like they're
trying too hard, bro. Do they realize
that London's not like that anymore?
Cuz you go in London, you try to get
into a club in London wearing trainers,
they let you wear trainers. That's like
15year old [ __ ] bro. That doesn't even
happen anymore where you wear trainers
and they turn you down. Nah, I I
remember when I last went to Birmingham,
there's, "Oh, you can't wear anything
cuz your trainers have got bobbles on
it." Bro, that doesn't even happen in London.
They don't even say that in London, bro.
You can get into any club with smart trainers.
Um, do I think he can look after himself?
Not really. No.
See, look. This is what makes me laugh, right?
Yeah, he did. Yeah.
That's funny. Everyone was saying that
he looks like a trap. No one said
anything about my appearance. Is it like
that [ __ ] all night spaz everyone was
like talking about when we met, but no
one said nothing about me. They can't
say nothing about me, bro.
Even though I didn't even have a
haircut, they can't say nothing about me, bro.
So, but yeah, I do feel bad. But look,
look at all the [ __ ] Kaye says, "Oh, he
got your kid strip searched." No, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. But here's
the thing. Who's there? Who's there for
Monty now? Not you and not Natalie. So
that's something that he need if he ever
does speak to Natalie again or if he
ever was. You're not there. Natalie's
No woman's ever there, are they? Nah.
You're not there. He's not there.
Like I was like Monty. But the thing is
Joe, what shocked me is because
obviously I was like that over at USA
Izzy. But the thing is what I didn't
expect is cuz he's a lot older than me.
You know, you act like that before you
know what these women are like. You act
like that. What made me think it was
weird is cuz he's a lot older than me.
So he should have he should know what
they're like. That's what I meant.
Cuz I was like that with that USA. But
then I know what they're like and [ __ ]
And that's what I mean.
So, but you Yeah, that's what I meant.
But he was going on about her all day yesterday, bro.
I had to kick him out for 5 minutes.
Like, [ __ ] bro.
I think you're right. what you want what
what what you wrote on Lord Jays is that
he doesn't think he could get any better,
you know, like that's why he why he's
doing this cuz if he if he tried in
Birmingham, there's a lot good-looking
people there he could have tried with, you know. So,
I don't know, bro. I can't relate to
being in love anymore because I can't
fall for these [ __ ] So, I can't be
in love anymore. So, I can't even I
can't even give an opinion, bro.
Because I I I wouldn't get in love
anymore. I wouldn't get attached
anymore. So, not not in that way.
Like, how do I explain it? I could get
attached maybe, but then if they [ __ ] me
over, then I wouldn't care.
Uh it's hard to explain what I mean. So,
yeah, I would expect them to do nothing but that.
That's the point I'm trying to [ __ ] make. So
yeah, I bought drinks and I bought us a
breakfast as well. Yeah,
I didn't give a [ __ ] bro. I just don't
care about money, bro. I don't care.
Yeah, I just bought him I bought her some drinks. Yeah, man.
Monty needs to grow a beard, though. I
You need to grow a beard, bro. If you
ever come out with me again, bro.
Like, there's nothing wrong with being
bold. I wouldn't If I was bold, if I was
bored, bro, I would just grow a beard
and get my beard shaped up. Just get
your beard back and grow your beard as
much as you can and get it shaped up, bro.
Cuz he looks a bit ill. I said that to
him as well. You look a bit ill, bro. You know,
he looks a bit like I don't even want to
say the word. He looks a bit like a cancer patient.
He needs to grow his beard and then he
will look good, bro.
Gain some weight and Yeah. You look ill,
bro. If you had your if you had your
beard and you had your beard shaped up,
you look a lot better. But no hair and
then no facial wear, you actually look
[ __ ] really ill, bro.
Um, I spent Well, the whole thing cost
like 1701 180. The trains were £29.
My sister lent me 150 because I brought
the wrong card cuz I'm an idiot. I had
to pay the money back when I got back. Um 130.
Yeah. And I I think I paid
15 140 drinking taxis and the food was about 140.
Yeah, bro. I went to Birmingham. I've
got two cards. Well, I had two cards.
One doesn't work and the other one
works. And I and I brought the one that
don't [ __ ] work by accident with all
the money on it. So, I had to call up my
sister to [ __ ] send me 150. Oh, it's
a [ __ ] nightmare, bro.
Yeah, I would have been [ __ ]
I would have been [ __ ] bro, without
without her, bro. I'm not even joking. I
would have been really [ __ ]
And I wouldn't be able to get the last
train back. So, I would have been stuck
with £50 cuz I bought my other car with
me. Had50 on it as well. But all my
money was on the other card. So, I would
have been [ __ ] Um,
no. I don't want the money, bro.
I don't want the money back.
No, I don't want the money back, bro. No. No, man.
I just want him to move on from this
[ __ ] Natalie J. That's what I want. Yeah, man.
Yeah, man. I got
I've got a very fluffy beard.
Yeah, I'm still talking to this woman.
So, in a way, it was good. I went to um
Birmingham in it.
I think she'll meet, but she said she'll
come London. I can't be bothered going
Birmingham again, bro. It's long.
Birmingham is [ __ ] long, mate. Trust
me, it's [ __ ] long, bro. And it's
even worse when you've been drinking as well.
It doesn't Well, it's not even It's only
the Midlands, but it's [ __ ] Feels
like forever, bro.
No, I think he's 35, bro.
No, I think he's 35.
Yeah, Joe. I had really bad hiccups last
night, so I just ended a live stream and
tried to go to sleep. [ __ ] nasty
hiccups, man. I hate them.
[ __ ] hate hiccups.
Hiccups. Hiccups. Yeah, I'm going to nip
into town in a bit. Oh, [ __ ]
Nipping into town. How cute is that? Uh,
nip into the town and [ __ ] collect
the winnings. Maybe go get something to eat
and then come back and chill. I need to
go cinema on Thursday.
I'm going to try and get this woman to
come London this weekend.
Nah, I'm not going out this weekend. I
don't really go out. It's pointless. I I
only went out to Birmingham to see
Monty. There was nothing else to do and
I won the football bet. Otherwise, I
wouldn't have even went out.
I don't go out like that anymore, bro.
It's just a It's a waste of time and
money in this country. I need to start
the [ __ ] gym again and [ __ ]
thing. Um, no I don't go out every
obviously if she comes to London
obviously then I will go out obviously
but just can't be bothered with it. Maybe maybe
bro but it doesn't matter I got two
numbers. They're both texting that. Uh
um so Natalie didn't think that he was doing anything.
And another thing is I'm not lying about
that. And another thing is why is L J
saying I'm lying? He's the one that lied
about [ __ ] Izzy. What the [ __ ] And
I'm thinking how can he make videos on
people when he is already proven to be a confirmed liar?
Who the [ __ ] lies about getting a hand
job, bro? What the [ __ ]
Hand job is literally nothing. I
wouldn't even class that as cheating.
Nah, I can't afford it, bro.
I can't because this woman might want to
meet me this this week and I don't want
to and I need all the money I can have.
I don't get a lot of money anymore, you
know. So, I need to be careful with the
money that I do have.
I still can't believe none of these jobs
have got back to me. What the [ __ ]
Jesus Christ. None of these [ __ ] jobs
have got back to me, bro. Can't I can't
I'm not doing it, bro.
Oh, bless you, Frankie.
Not Not this week anyways,
cuz then there'd be no point of winning
the football bet.
there would have been no point of
winning a football bet.
But I think that's the only way you can
win now is the football bets, isn't it?
I think that's the only way you can win
now. Is it?
I didn't try go. There's casinos in
Birmingham. I didn't try to get in. They
I probably would have been able to get
in to be honest.
Yeah, that's good for you, bro. It
doesn't even trigger me.
That your winds don't even trigger me, bro.
That's the funny thing is they they
don't even trigger me.
Yeah, but I don't think Frankie's playing.
paying. Sorry, I don't think Frankie is Is he?
He wasn't playing Frankie.
How much do you want me to put in it?
How much would you want me to put in?
No, it's a waste of money though. Nah.
What did I do last weekend?
No, well, I'm doing a football bet this
week, but I'm doing 10 I'm doing 10 pound.
>> Yeah, it's not a,000 a month though
because it's not guaranteed.
I'm only doing this until I can get a job again.
Stop trolling me.
Hops are back. Stop trolling.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Nah, I'm not playing that, bro. Ranka. Bless you.
Bless you with life. What about 152 spins?
Frankie's [ __ ] rigged.
I know that much.
Online roulette is rigged. I know that much.
I might buy a nice little stony today.
I've got 2K. I'm almost skinn, matey.
I've got 2K. I move my skin.
>> Yeah, he is
Frankie's [ __ ] red, bro.
Only play with the winnings. What? Put 28.
Put 200 pound in Frankie.
You're having a laugh.
You can buy a Stony with them winnings.
What if you add 15 pound to it? Pointless.
Them them burgers have got to last money until
2 weeks. Jesus.
Jesus Christ, bro.
You're trying to get me skin
like the virgin, Joe. I know what you're
trying to do.
You're trying to get me skin like the [ __ ] virgin.
talking about yourself.
No talking about yourself on my channel.
No self projecting on my channel. Get gone.
These losers self-project every day of their life.
You know what I done on Saturday going
to Birmingham? That's probably more than
[ __ ] what these have ever done in
probably 10 years, isn't it?
None that [ __ ] bro. Why not?
What do you mean there's more content to
go out and about?
I can go out and about. I can afford to
Just cuz I don't want to drink every [ __ ] weekend.
I don't want to go out and drink every
weekend cuz it's boring, bro.
When you win, you do more. No, I don't.
cuz I would have went out this week if
it wasn't for um Monty. wasn't for
Monty, I wouldn't have went out this week.
Regardless whether I even if I did win,
which I did, but no,
if I went out today
and I won5600
on Frankie, I wouldn't go out this week.
I wouldn't go out this week, bro.
probably not even next week. So,
cuz it's boring, you know,
so yeah, bro.
I told you the whole time it's not money
why I don't go out.
It's just boring in this country, you
know. That's what I meant.
It gets boring. Like I said, you've done
something so much for 3 years, you get
bored of it.
But it depends. If one of these meet me,
then maybe I'll go out more in Birmingham.
At least it'll be fun because you can
actually get something, you know.
No, it's boring, bro. You go out, you
what? You try to speak to people, they
say they have boyfriends. It gets old,
bro. It gets old when you've been doing
it for years.
Yes, they have replied. I've just told
you that I'm speaking to both of them.
Well, I got three numbers and two
replied and I'm still talking to them. So,
if it was like that in London every week
and one actually meets you, then I would
go out every week.
Obviously, they've replied. I've just
said that they replied.
What the [ __ ]
I swear some of you people got brain
damage. I swear to God, bro,
you don't process things. I was speaking
to one yesterday and we're still talking now. So,
like I said, if they meet then it would
be worth going out every week.
But if not, there's there's like no point
drinking, getting hangovers, but it's
not there's no point. I'm going out I'm
going to cinema on Thursday anyway. So, Oh,
Ty, you're nasty bully.
Kay's a nasty bully.
Nasty bully. Kaye,
you You're just like that [ __ ] skid
virgin from [ __ ] Kent. That's what
you are, Kayie. Skid Flynn.
Wouldn't you get bored going out
drinking every week though if it was the same [ __ ]
That's how it should be. If if one of
these people meet you.
Yeah. Which I I've got a feeling one of
them at least will meet you. Yeah.
Let's just say one does meet. Let's say
hypothetically one does meet. That's the
way it is supposed to be with somebody
that looks like me. Go out,
meet a couple of stuck up people.
people that aren't interested and then
eventually you'll find somebody that
gives you a chance. That's the way it
should be. Even every week with the way
that I look, that's the way it should
be. But in London, that's not the way it is.
When that is the way it should be, you
know, but it ain't.
Yeah, but there's other things to be doing, Joe.
Hobbies, going to different countries.
And if you go out every week, you don't
enjoy it as much.
You don't enjoy it as much if you go out every week.
Why do you think there's such such thing as detoxes?
No. Then you don't enjoy it as much when
you do it every week as well.
I didn't make it focused on women
either. I went to go out and see I went
to go and see Monty. I didn't go for
women. I went to see Monty
and I hadn't been out for two weeks. So,
I thought, "Fuck it."
But I've done some approaches, you know. Hey man, cops.
Oh, bless you then.
Bless you then. If you go Newcastle,
how much you going to gamble the casino
then? Bless you.
Yeah, every two weeks is fine. Every two
weeks, every 3 weeks. Yeah, but not
every week. It gets bored.
Oh, bless you then if you put 500 pound aside.
God bless you. Oh, bless.
Bless you then. If you if you don't want
to lose 500, bless you.
I wish I could get into casinos.
Yeah, I wish I could get into casinos. I'm jealous.
I can't get into none unless I leave the country.
Unless I leave the country. Unless I
leave the country then
or like we said before, I can go to
Nottingham, but then it's trying to get paid out.
You know, they look for excuses to pay out.
You know, they always look for excuses
to pay out, don't you?
They look for excuses to pay uh to not pay out.
So that would be the greatest excuse. Ah,
you're bad. We're not going to pay you. So
now I've already done it all before.
I've done it a million times before.
I went on a little adventure on Saturday.
Is that right? Um,
no, I prefer like arcades. At least you
know you're going to get your money.
At least in the bookies, you know you're
going to get your money.
But in casinos you don't do.
So you know Cuz
if you go to an arcade or even patty
power, say you deposit, right
on your card and then you withdraw.
And then you withdraw. Yeah. So when you
um it goes in your bank instantly.
So they always pay you. Whereas in
casino casinos they will look for
excuses not to pay you. I just don't trust them.
And look what they done with my ticket
that time before and I lost that £500.
I don't trust them bro. I don't trust them.
I don't trust them at all. At all at
Yeah, casinos are dodgy, bro.
Yeah, they pay you instant. The only one
that doesn't is William Hill, which
William Hill is my favorite bookies, but
they don't pay instant, but casinos will
find reasons not to pay you.
I remember I won £69. Yeah.
And trying to get that money, they have
to ring this person up, that person up,
which is mad because that's they're
quick enough to take your money.
It's like Nottingham when I went with
Adman. I I told I'll tell the story
again for the millionth time. 200 in,
right? It was a walking casino
and I won 350. I had I won 150
which is £350. After like an hour of
playing up down I was like [ __ ] it. I'll
just take the 150 up.
And then they were trying they oh do you
have anything with your name on it. No
no no no.
I wouldn't mind it was only one [ __ ]
50 you 350.
So that's why that's another thing I
don't like about them casinos. And it's
not money laundering. It's not money
laundering at all.
They just don't like paying.
That's why you go to the casinos
and all of them machines are always out of service
cuz then they know that there's certain
people in the casino
that's not supposed to be in the casino
that that that or they're not supposed
to be in the casino.
So, think of how many people they get
get away with not paying
cuz there I think there's about four
machines and they're always out of
service. Well, not always, but a lot of
the time they're out of service. Why are
they out of service? Oh yeah.
Yeah. It's dodgy, is it, Joe?
So if I went to Notting again and the
machines are working,
then I'd have to do 150 to 450.
I'd have to do 150 to 450. Another 150
to450. That's another thing. It's not
even £500, Joe. When you try to take
500, they ask you for ID. Whereas if
it's like 470, if you try to take 470
out, they let you. I think there was a
guideline if it was 470,
they let you. So that So you have to
keep doing like450, 460, 470,
but £500 then they ask you for ID. It's
just all a scam.
Yeah, they do. cuz when I used to go hippo drone. Um
but I I kept going back getting the
money out and um
get the money out and uh
Um, and when I tried doing 500, they
asked me for ID,
so I had to take the ticket back out and
play to 470.
Why do they just pay fair and square?
You win, you get paid, done. I don't
understand it. It should just be that simple.
They take your money. So
they should pay your money
and they can avoid tickets as well. It's dodgy.
Like I said, they can void tickets as
well. They can void tickets.
So just remember, they can void your
ticket as well.
They voided my ticket and I couldn't
even cash out. So yeah. So yeah,
at least bookies pay you in it.
What do you prefer, Joe? Bookies or casinos?
They should have let you in there. They
shouldn't let you in there. I always I
will stick by my guns and say this. They
shouldn't let you in there, right? If
you're banned, they shouldn't let you in there.
Otherwise, the whole process is ridiculous.
They shouldn't let you in there. They've
got responsibility to not let you in
there. If they let you in there and they
have let you gamble and they have not
stopped you, they should pay you. end of story
like that it's end of they should not
let you in there think of it right they have a
um self-exclusion policy right
what's the point of a self-exclusion
policy if they're just going to let you
if they're just going to let you in
that doesn't make any sense Why waste your time?
Why waste your [ __ ] time, bro? Even
filling out that form if they're just
going to let you in. It doesn't make sense.
Check to see if it works. It doesn't work.
And yeah, they you can say, "Oh, well,
the consequence is they don't pay you."
But you won't know that unless you win
and then they don't pay you the first time. So yeah,
doesn't matter. Anyways, do you still
play online, Joe? I I I don't think
I don't think I'll play online again. I
don't really play.
Online is just too rigged.
It's just too rigged online. Would you agree?
Nah, it's too rigged. The roulette is
too rigged. As soon as you start betting
big on the numbers,
you done GameStop. When did you do Gamtop?
Nah, online roulette is too rigged. Trust me,
online roulette is definitely rigged.
And you must have done that recently
then. That damn shop.
What limits were there?
What limit? And the thing is now I can't
even use a UK site. I can't even use a
UK site now.
I can't even use a UK site.
So, you could use one of them sites and
they can refuse to pay you.
So, and then there's nothing you can do
about it because it's not even in the
UK. So, you'd be [ __ ] Yeah.
Wow. What the [ __ ]
Do they pay you to 7K?
Do they pay you though?
That's madness, bro. What the [ __ ]
So, I've played on I I used to play on 32 Red.
You know, 32 Red.
Yeah. With bookies, it's easy.
Yeah. With with the bookies, it's easy.
You win. Scan your ticket. Pay. Bam. Done. Yeah. Yep.
Just stick to bookies.
Is there any way I could ever get into a
casino a casino again?
Yeah, there is. You go to Paris, you
have to go to France. If you don't go to France, then No.
No. If you left the country, Yeah. You
can't in Thailand. Gambling's illegal in
[ __ ] that though, bro. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, it' be it' be a good little video,
wouldn't it, Joe? Yeah.
Yeah, it be a good little video.
Just get a Euro star to Paris, isn't it?
And then gamble. You go go stay overnight,
go on a Saturday, get drunk, do some
approaches, go for a gamble and come back.
It would be expensive though. Maybe £500.
Do you think £500 would be enough?
Train, hotel, drinking,
a little gamble.
How much we talking? 500. Maybe 500.
What do you think? Oh,
what' you say? Oh, [ __ ]
Would you say that would be enough, Joe? 500 lb.
I think so.
I think 600 would be enough.
What do you think?
answer me, you [ __ ] buffoon.
Answer me, you [ __ ] buffoon. Right.
I'll be back later.