Yo yo. Oh.
Oh, [ __ ] Who said go live? Monty go.
Oh [ __ ] man.
Yeah, I put £50 on the Frankie and nothing.
You can't take a day off. You're here now, boss.
I've already took days off, weeks off.
You're the ones that can't take a day off YouTube.
Yeah, I done 50 pound on Frankie. Yeah, nothing.
Well, I tell you the truth, I put 100 pound in
and I played it down to 50 and I was
like, "Fuck that. I'm not putting no
more money through this rig [ __ ]
I'm not YouTube dependent. No, I'm [ __ ] not.
I've come off YouTube for [ __ ] days
and weeks. Something that you people
can't do. I'm not [ __ ] YouTube
dependent. I'll stick to my bet. I bet
you 100 I bet you all my money.
No, he didn't. I I I bet you all the
money I can take a week off YouTube, but you can't.
I'm not a [ __ ] YouTube [ __ ]
dependent. I'm my [ __ ]
Money kind of got me back on this [ __ ]
No, I put £100 in and I took 50. There's
no way I was going to give that another 50.
[ __ ] that, bro. You mad.
No, that them slots. Hey, I was get I
got really mad when I lost that 50 as well.
I got back. They paid 285
and I got 50 note as well. So
yeah, it's [ __ ] so [ __ ] fixed. Oh.
Oh my god, bro. It is so fixed. It's
unbelievable. Yeah, I only put 50 on it
though. Well, I put £100 in and I took
50 out. There's no way I could justify
losing 100 pound on that, bro. No way.
Not a bonus to save your life.
I was doing one pound spins. Can't even
get a [ __ ] bonus, bro.
So, I just took 50. So, I only lost 50.
I just banked the 235.
Yeah, I had 235.
Obviously, I didn't get a feature. I
just told you I didn't get a feature.
You [ __ ] brain dead.
So, I just took the 23 and I just So,
then I got 235.
It is a [ __ ] enough, mate. Cuz I kept
getting base game wins. It is enough cuz
I kept getting base game wins.
But somehow I kept losing. Strange, eh?
I got base game wins though.
I'm not getting into it again, bro. New
day. Move on.
I'm absolutely skinn. You wish I was
skin. You're the one who's skinn. That's
why you call me skin. Yeah, I'm skin,
bro. I went to Birmingham and I spent
£200 and I've still got loads left. How
the [ __ ] am I skin again? You're talking
about yourself. All of the people that
call other people skin or skin
themselves. That's why they bring it up.
These people aren't your [ __ ]
personal bank accounts.
Figure it out, bro. They call people
skint cuz they're skint themselves. I
don't need to prove. I've already proved
to you millions of times I'm not skin.
You prove that you're not skint.
I'll put the link up for you, man.
Right. Hold on.
They call people skin
because they're skinn.
Look at what me and Monty was doing on
Saturday. Well, he he actually is
skinned. But I mean, like, no, I'm going
to Thursday, but I mean, he actually is
skinned. Think of it, bro. Went to
Birmingham, spent money.
Yeah. Let's see all your money. Come on.
They call people skint cuz they're skint themselves.
It's just self projection.
I ain't [ __ ] skinny. You mad. Yeah, man.
Yeah. Anyways, after that £50, I weren't
going to put any more in it.
Well, I'm not putting no more money in
that rig [ __ ] [ __ ] that.
Talking about yourself. Hey, no self
projection on my channel.
I haven't got a pot to piss in, bro. The
link's up there. Come on, let's play the
money game. Come on.
Talking about yourself again.
I think these people's disabilities get them confused.
Um, they get they get themselves
confused with you. I proved them wrong
many many times and they still call me
skin. They're talking about themselves.
That's why it doesn't matter how many
times you prove yourself to these little
mongos. They're talking about themselves.
So, it doesn't matter what you prove
because they they've got you confused with themselves.
Their brains don't work properly. D lad,
>> you can ask Monty man what I done what
we done in Birmingham.
>> One second, bro.
>> Listen, come in and show us your money.
You started something. Now finish it.
Come in and show us your money.
Come on. You You just come in. You just
say that I was skin. Come in and show us
your money. I want to see what money looks like.
There's no point coming on YouTube like
a [ __ ] every day starting [ __ ] you
can't finish. Don't start something you
can't finish. Don't be a London cyclist.
Show me your money. You come on here.
You started on me. Are you coming in or not? Simple.
Simple. Are you coming in or not? Skin.
Are you coming in or not? Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. Hey, come in and show us your money.
Nothing, man. I just lost £50 frenzy. Yeah,
I actually showed six grand actually in
cash, but yeah, there you go.
One second, bro. Hold on.
One second. Yeah, Joe. I put £100 in and
I just took 50.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. We've done this before and every
single time I show you something, you
run away. You call me skin, show me your
money. You started coming on here
calling me skin. Let's see your money.
jump on. I want to see your money.
Otherwise, I'm banning you. Come on. Are
you coming in or not?
I put 100 pound in. I took 50. So, I
only lost 50. There's no way I was
putting the last 50 in. [ __ ] that, bro.
I don't even know why I put 100 pound
in. I just took 50 out. There's no way I
can justify losing more than 50 on that [ __ ]
And you're gone. Bye-bye. You got chance
after chance after chance after chance. After
chance. After chance. So, bye-bye now.
Go self-reflect on another channel. You
started something and I was prepared to
finish it and you won't join.
So, bye-bye now. Go call yourself skint
somewhere else. Bye-bye now.
They bring money up because they're
skint themselves. That's why they call
people skin cuz they are skint. Where do
they get the idea skint from? Went to
Birmingham, met Monty, go out all the time.
They must be Skint themselves.
Well, okay. Your show money. Okay. How
much is that?
Let's count it. Okay. Well, someone's
coming in. Show money. Nice, man. How
much is that? >> 8K. >> Okay.
It's 8K. There you go. 8 8.5 or something.
>> There we go. So, why couldn't that other
guy come in and show money then?
>> There you go, man.
>> Three log.
>> Wow. See, it's not that hard, is it?
It's not that hard, is it, man?
Yeah, I was at a food bank. I've never
been in a food bank ever. But yeah, I
didn't even get a bonus. Anyways, I've
already shown mine. And that weren't a
guy calling me skin. I've already shown mine.
I've already shown you money time and
time and time and time and time and time
and time and time again.
What do I think of that? I don't care
because I'm not obsessed with money.
That's I I generally don't care.
I've got more than enough money to do
what I need to do. I don't give a [ __ ]
Good for whoever has that. Good for
them, bro. I don't give a [ __ ]
So yeah, man.
Money is not everything. Unless you're
like [ __ ] Monty.
So I mean, unless you unless you're like
Monty at the minute, doesn't really matter.
No, I'm not showing you [ __ ] nothing.
I'm not showing you nothing
about me showing my 50. I ain't showing you nothing.
And that guy didn't even beat me either.
I asked to be shown 10 grand. That
that's not even 10 grand. So like I
said, I'm still yet to be beaten. Unless
you're like Monty, then then it matters.
So yeah, it's actually 10 grand that has
to be shown to me. But yeah,
why are these people? So anyways,
Richie, like where do they get the idea
from, bro? Like people of skin. I went
to Birmingham, went on the piss with
Monty. Where the [ __ ] do they get this
idea of skin from? There's no lifestyle
that supports what they're saying. And
then the only thing that can make sense
is that they're talking about themselves.
You understand, Richie?
It's because they're talking about their
own skin selves.
You know what I mean?
I'm on 2x. You don't know how much I have.
You don't know how much I get. Exactly. But yeah.
Yeah. They're [ __ ] disabled, bro.
They proper are disabled.
Yeah. It doesn't matter how much I get.
It's none of your [ __ ] business. Just
like it's none of your business how much I have.
>> Money. What is it with these people and money, bro?
>> Stop mentioning me like like multi skin.
I'm not asking ask if I'm skiing. Money
is just [ __ ]
>> I'm using it as an I'm using as an example.
>> Yeah, but the example is it's what is
money? Money is nothing. What's more in
what's more what cost more money or a
house over you? What or a book? Yeah.
>> Why do why? Hey, why do you not keep
bringing up money anyways, bro?
>> Cuz money is nothing. You spend money,
you lose money. Money comes and goes.
>> That's what money, you know what I mean?
It's these people are [ __ ] idiots.
Paper. It's [ __ ] paper [ __ ]
money's for nothing. It's no [ __ ] I
can't even say that word. There's
nothing to money. Yeah. Just say just
say if you went to a snow. Yeah. And got
a a marble comic book or something like that.
>> Oh, by the way, sorry to cut you off
money. Yeah. It's lucky that it was
only50 because I was getting them severe
mood swings again. Then I went to Gregs
and got some sausage rolls and calm down
after like 10 minutes. It's not a good
idea. I play these things, bro. It was
giving me really bad mood swings again. Sorry, Monty.
>> Yeah. So, so if you go to Aston, buy
yourself a Marvel comic book. Yeah. Or
just a normal regular book. Yeah. That
book inside will go up in price. Money
doesn't. Money drops.
do goes up in price. Money is for call.
You come with money, you lose money.
Items are worth more than what money is
because you can get more for items in
the future times to come. You know what I'm saying?
>> Yeah, but how do you get it? Yeah, but
how do you get items?
>> Basically from Tesco's houses, these
books like comic books, stuff like that
because in time all that will cost
money. You know, you know what I'm saying?
>> Like money's [ __ ] money. You you you
you spend your money. You don't see that
>> Money's nothing. Money's just anymore, Joe.
>> That's why I don't do it. Do you do you
reckon I win another football bet this
season, Joe? Maybe not in it.
>> I'm jumping up anyway. Yeah. >> Why?
>> Because I'm not on YouTube no more. I
just come up and said I'm off this [ __ ]
I'm off it. There's nothing here. Big
weirdos, mate. But um yeah, I've got
Natalie TV now anyway. So Natalie TV's
come now anyway. So, look, I show you.
>> Did you un Did you unbox it?
>> No, it's I'm not going to unbox it. It's
staying in this box. It's not my TV.
>> It's here.
>> Not my TV. It's Nice. >> Yeah.
>> Nice TV. Like I said, I always keep to
my word. Always keep to my word. Never
lie. When I say when I say I get it, I
get it. That's what I'm talking. Do you
know what? You know what I mean? I can
still get so it doesn't matter. I've got
a lamb shank for dinner in it today, Joe.
>> Good. I'm jumping up. Yeah.
>> Can I see that? Can you unbox it?
>> No, I'm not unboxing it. It's not of
this TV. I'm not opening it. It's not
this TV. I'm not going to open that.
This [ __ ] gift. [Music]
>> I'm just going to sell it.
I'm going to jump off. Yeah. In a bit.
>> Yeah, man. Going to be here. But yeah,
remember that money's for call.
>> It comes and goes in a bit. Yeah.
>> Yeah, bro.