N I'm back.
All look like [ __ ] robots.
They all look like [ __ ] robots.
Well, she's unblocked me, which is weird.
That is strange. She definitely did
block me. I know for a fact she did. Wow, man.
Still playing these silly games at
[ __ ] 28 years of age, eh? [ __ ] me.
I was watching this guy's approaching
videos. I was looking in at their faces.
Yeah, they even look like [ __ ]
robots. They literally look like non-playing characters.
Now, she didn't turn her phone off
because her picture disappeared
and her last scene disappeared. Her last
scene disappeared and her picture
disappeared. Bro, I know when someone's blocked me.
Skint mun. You are the skint. You're the
one that dates disabled. I've got more
money than you'd ever be. Go and suck
your dad's dick for £600 again.
Go and suck your dad's dick for £600
again and keep thinking that you got
money, mate. When in reality, we all
know that you ain't got a bed. You have
to date downies. That's the real you.
Stop showing your benefit money off, you
skint bastard. You ain't even got a [ __ ] bed.
You are m you are. Stop talking about
yourself. Yeah. So, yeah, she did block
me. All of a sudden, the pictures come
back and the last scenes come back.
the [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, I know when I've been blocked. I
hate that, bro. It's like you're
underestimating my my intelligence.
I know, [ __ ] when someone's
[ __ ] blocked me. Oh my [ __ ] god,
bro. And then they've just unblocked me. Weird.
I know when someone's when someone's
blocked me, bro. I don't know why people
say, "Oh, are you sure?" Or, "Yes, I
know when someone's blocked me, bro. [ __ ] hell.
That's so weird, bro.
I'm just going to pretend like I didn't
know anything. [ __ ] bro.
Anyway, who emailed the [ __ ] um
Jamie's house? So now I can't move in.
You little grass has been grassing again.
Why are you sending emails to the [ __ ] housing?
You sandle autistic people ain't got a life. Yeah.
Oh, I can't move in with Monty now.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
I'm coming off this I'm coming off this
YouTube soon, but Oh, for real? Yeah,
I'm coming off this YouTube soon, bro.
She blocked me then unblocked me.
Then she replied back, "What the [ __ ]
Is she all right in her head?"
Then she unblocked me. And she
definitely did block me before you say,
"Oh, are you sure? Yes, I know when
someone's blocked me." They either
blocked they blocked me or they No, they
blocked me. They did block me. So they
block you to then unblock you.
Maybe they blocked me to stop um me me
me me me me me me me me me me me me me
messaging because I'm at work maybe. But
I don't know. But they definitely did
block me anyways. Now they've unblocked me.
Why does she block then unblock and then
message like it was normal? Weird.
Who's my dad? Nic Nicolo, bro. I can't
[ __ ] I don't even know who my dad is. H
I was laughing my ass off. Yeah. When I
was on that train in Birmingham. Yeah. I
was thinking any one of these people on
the train could be these people on
YouTube repeating what I say. You know,
like how you found your mama eat belly.
Like any of these people on the train
could be one of them people writing on
YouTube. I was pissing myself laughing, bro.
You know, that is mad.
That is funny, bro. Yeah, man.
I will be off YouTube soon. Anyways,
yeah, I can't believe I lost 50 pound on Frankie, bro.
That was [ __ ]
Yeah, that's true. They are all
agrophobic to be fair.
I like less, you know. At least he
admits his [ __ ]
That's what I like about Lim, you know.
At least he admits it. He owns his [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
I want to try and win another football
bet. Not this week though. Yeah.
Well, then you really are [ __ ] aren't you?
>> I want to win another football bet, man.
Why did she
Who the [ __ ] blocks and then unblocks? Oh,
I'm never going back to Birmingham, bro. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, I need to go cinema on Thursday. I
might invite some people out.
I'm going to say, "Do you want to come
cinema on Thursday?" I don't want to go
by myself this time. Invite them out to
the to the um pictures.
Nah, the numbers will go somewhere, bro.
Stop being negative.
It will happen when you least expect it.
No, it will happen when you least expect
it. We're only young.
That's what Laney used to tell me. Laney. Yeah, man.
Do you think I'll win another football bet? Nickelodeon.
No, I won one on Saturday.
I just do
double both teams to score. Me?
I just do double both teams to score.
Nah, because how are you going to play roulette, bro?
How are you going to play roulette?
Online roulette's fixed.
So, how can you how can you do that,
bro? I'm not going to bet this week.
I'll bet next week, I think. I'll bet on
the football next week. This week, cuz I
don't like the games. See, there's
certain games I like betting on, you
see, and I don't like the ones for this week. So,
If there's perfect lineups, then I would
put about 150 on it. If there's like a perfect lineup
like Swindon and Oxford United, then I
then I will, bro.
But where are you playing a fair game of
roulette nowadays, Nicolo? It's all
[ __ ] rigged online.
Yeah, that's weird cuz she definitely
blocked me, bro.
She definitely blocked me.
Unless she took her Sim out or something.
Strange, strange, strange guy.
But she definitely did, bro. Unless she
[ __ ] took the SIM out of her [ __ ] phone.
That is so weird, bro.
But even if one of these numbers said
they would meet me, I've got to go
[ __ ] Liverpool. I [ __ ] go Liverpool, bro.
I ain't going to Liverpool. You [ __ ] mad.
[ __ ] going Liverpool.
N [ __ ] that, bro. Oh, pleasure.
Oh, bless you. Nah, nah, bro. No. Oh, Franklin. Wow. Nothing bad.
These [ __ ] are crazy. One a I'm set. No, mom.
Well, I'm gone, bro. Reb.