Well, that didn't last long.
Oh man, they really can't get off of YouTube.
I beat them.
I beat them, bro. I beat them.
Yeah, I beat them, lad.
They went back on YouTube. I said from
today, the first one that goes on YouTube loses.
Oh, they're on YouTube.
Again, not starting anything or anything
like that, but these people clearly
can't get off of YouTube, so they must
be the skin ones.
They must be the skin ones with no like.
I said, "Oh, from tomorrow,
yesterday, right? Let's see if these
people can stay off of YouTube." And
they were on YouTube again. It just goes
to show that they're all the things that
they call other people. Nope.
No, I didn't hear. Yeah,
that was before the skin ones. Is it
can't get off a YouTube
talking about then? Well, they go and
get over your job. They go and get off of Y.
How did I know? Because I told somebody
to email me if you see any of these
people on YouTube
and I got emailed.
So it must these people must be the
skilled ones. No friends if they're sat
on YouTube every day. Who's my point?
No. Somebody was emailing me, bro.
So I won, bro. They can't get off YouTube.
They can't call anyone [ __ ] skin.
They can't talk about anyone now. They
clearly can't get off of YouTube. So,
you had a nice curry today, Grezy. I had
a nice curry, lad.
Oh, you skin, are you? It's okay.
It's okay, J skin.
It's okay, man.
It's all right.
Same people every day in a greasy.
Oh [ __ ] bro. Yep. Same repeating people every day.
Is that right?
Same repeating people every day, lad. Mhm. One second.
I'm buying my nail. [ __ ] man.
What's the day tomorrow? Wednesday.
And he's got cinema on Thursday.
Is that okay with you? Grey boss
bit on my back.
Is that okay with you, boss? Yeah.
These people can't live without YouTube.
Makes you wonder, is it? If they had all
these friends and all this life and all
this money, why they'd spend all their
life on YouTube?
Doesn't add up, does it?
See, I I don't, like I said, I don't
call people stuff. I just go by
evidence. I just put the evidence to
them, you know,
when they're sat on YouTube every day
ain't got a life. I just put I just put
that to them to be honest,
you know. So
yeah, I don't I don't call them anything. Were they?
I don't know that.
How do you know that then Greavves?
>> Yeah, I saw it. But he wasn't suicidal. Yeah, man.
Yeah, I was speaking to someone on
Instagram earlier, bro. Oh,
she's [ __ ] boring, man. Well, she was
all right, but you can you can just
sense the entitlement.
That's why I don't [ __ ] with these
[ __ ] here anymore, bro. They're
[ __ ] They've all got the same attitude.
They've all got the same attitude,
Gregy. They're not playing characters,
lad. They're all NPCs.
They're [ __ ] NPCs, lad. Yeah. Anyways,
yeah, I am
going to bite my nail here. Anyways,
when will you people get off of YouTube?
Get a laugh.
Get off of YouTube.
Just wondering why these people are
still on YouTube
when they come on here and call people
skint every day and everything. Why
they're on YouTube.
That's what I was wondering, bro.
That's what's occurring. I just want to
know why why they're on YouTube every day.
Cuz obviously I'm here to do a welfare check.
You know, like Monty, I went to
Birmingham because he was in a bad
place. I went to do a welfare check
and I'm doing a welfare I do welfare
checks on YouTube. You see, Greavvesy,
I'm I'm an expect I'm an inspector. I do welfare checks.
And it seems to be the same people on
YouTube every [ __ ] day
like all other people, lad.
Uh, no I'm not. I've been off of YouTube
for days. I've been off of YouTube for weeks.
You know, skin. Yeah, you're talking
about yourself. I'm skint, but you're
the one sat on YouTube hating. Okay, bro.
Like I said, you can say whatever you
want behind a fake account. But again,
you people on YouTube all day, every
day. So, we know that you're talking
about yourselves. The evidence says
you're talking about yourself
because you're on YouTube every day.
It's [ __ ] obvious.
Yeah, I paid for Monty's night out. Yeah, man.
I'm despised on it by a bunch of skin
[ __ ] low lives. You think I give a
[ __ ] I wouldn't give a [ __ ] if all of
these people on here died of cancer. I
wouldn't give a [ __ ] I'd sit there and
laugh. You think I care about any person
in this community, lad?
Why did I pay for money? I only bought
him a few drinks.
Why not, bro?
Uh, he's all right. Yeah, he's all
One second. Let me You've been on here
19 times since Friday. I'm not
complaining. No, no, no, no, no. But
here's the thing. I've been off of
YouTube for days and weeks.
days, a week, weeks. You people can't
get off of YouTube.
It's concerning. You actually can't get
off of YouTube.
That's the thing.
And if you can't get off of YouTube,
stop [ __ ] talking about other people
then being this, being that, being this,
being that, cuz you wouldn't be on here
if none of them things apply to you.
I'm all Monty has here. Maybe.
Anyways, [ __ ] the YouTube thing.
Yeah, you don't see Natalie there for
him. You don't see Kaye there for him. I
don't give a [ __ ] about the money. I
wonder that that 200 got money. I don't
give a [ __ ] I don't care. Yeah.
Yeah. My live streams all good, man.
My live streams are good.
I don't give a [ __ ] about paying £200
for a night out, bro. D.
And I'm the one who got him off YouTube.
I'm the one who got him on YouTube. So,
I kind of have a responsibility. You
know what I mean? Greavvesy,
you had a nice curry today, Greavves. A
very nice curry. I haven't had
McDonald's for a while. Kind of fancy
some McDonald's, matey. Yeah.
Wonder would he go for you next?
I had one date this year when you were
[ __ ] I had a few dates this year,
you [ __ ] [ __ ] H
I've had actually had about three dates
this year. Try again. [Music]
How you change this, man?
Would I date you? Nah,
did you have a McDonald's today? Grezy.
I love it. Yeah.
[ __ ] McDonald's. Did you have one today? Gre
[ __ ] nice, mate.
Well, you going to get one later? Yeah,
I had a nice curry with jalapenos. I
went to the calf earlier as well.
I got a nice breakfast from the calf bre.
It was nice.
I had four slices of bacon, two
sausages, egg, and toast.
Then I had a curry with jalapenos.
I kind of found some McDonald's.
I ain't going to lie to you, bro. Yeah.
Should I get a McDonald's greasy or
should I not?
I kind of fancy a Big Mac and six
nuggets. I'm going to lie.
I got some popcorn.
I got some super noodles.
No, I don't want 20 nuggets.
I got some popcorn. I got some super noodles. Um, crackers.
No, I'm going to get six and a Mac, you idiot.
That's what I'm saying. I'm going to get
a Big Mac meal with six nuggets. Not
just six nuggets, obviously, cuz that's
not going to fill me.
That's what I mean.
And if I want a Big Mac as well,
I need to be careful, but I don't want
to go [ __ ] broke now. That's the thing.
I don't want to go broke monty
should be okay now ain't it Greasy
with the [ __ ] and TV and [ __ ] It
should be all right, bro. With food and that
should be all right, is it? Yeah.
Yeah, I have. I was talking to her earlier.
I want to order some McDonald's. One second.
What's the spicy nuggets like? I've not had them.
They any good? Yeah.
Are they good?
I want to get these spicy nuggets. I've
not had them.
They're nice greasy before I buy them.
Well, I'll give him a whirl then.
Do you have any dip dip with yours? I
don't have any dips.
Right. I'm going to get that with a Big Mac Mill. What's that?
Maybe I might get a chicken Big Mac actually instead.
Chicken nuggets with a chicken Big Mac.
I think I might do the chicken Big Mac, bro.
Just have all chicken. Yeah, that looks
nice. I've had that before. That chicken.
Yeah, I've had a chicken mac before.
One second, bro.
I remove Big Mac sauce, remove let uh
lettuce, remove the pickle.
The only thing I don't remove is cheese.
One second, lad.
I only like cheese on mine.
Bro, I'll never be as fat as you, bro.
When you when I get as fat as you
people. Yeah, I will start worrying
about myself, bro. You people are
[ __ ] obese. How can you talk about
anyone's [ __ ] weight? You self projectors,
bro. No one will ever be as fat as you
people. Believe that.
Look at yourself first before starting
coming on judging other people.
Yeah, I'll never be as fat as you ugly [ __ ] Believe that.
You people are [ __ ] fat as [ __ ] Look
who's [ __ ] talking.
You're fat, ugly bastards.
You're [ __ ] obese. How can you talk
about anyone's weight? You're [ __ ] obese.
Literally obese. Fat and ugly. How can
you talk about anyone?
Where's this coat gone?
Anyways, I'm getting this McDonald's
anyways. I will never be as fat as you
ugly people, mate. Believe that. 17 pounds.
Uh, rings a bell. Bro, you're [ __ ] a
million times fatter than me. What the [ __ ]
Look at yourself before talking about
other people. Think about it. Yeah,
you're [ __ ] a million. One second.
Where's this getting delivered to?
You're probably a million times fatter
than me and you're telling me what I
should and I shouldn't be able to what I
should and shouldn't be doing.
Worry about yourself first, bro.
Yeah, I ordered it, by the way. £17.
There you go. Jeez.
What? What car did that come out of?
>> My other account, is it? It wouldn't
come out my other account. But we see.
Yeah, bro. I'm going to go back to the
gym soon anyways.
Oh, got to find one of that.
man. It's weird. Like you people are
like so fat and then as soon as someone
gains a bit of weight temporarily, you
you obsess over it. It's so weird. It's
really really weird.
It's so [ __ ] weird, lad.
It's obsession, bro. [ __ ] really obsession.
Like you're never going to make me
insecure. You're never going to stop me
coming on camera ever.
Look, I'll show you, bro. [ __ ]
The tops actually come back today, lad.
No, you don't mean it like nothing, but
you need to worry about yourself, lad.
Don't [ __ ] worry about me.
Worry about yourself.
Obsessing over other men is [ __ ] weird.
Who used to do that, bro? Bomb did. And
guess what? What did Bomb ended up? What
did Bomb end up looking like? You like
this, don't you, Greavvesy?
Yep. The only one that goes with this
color, bro. So,
well, the navy one doesn't. So, yeah, man.
You like it, Grezy?
Yeah. I got these nuggets coming.
cute with it. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ] mom. M
[ __ ] hell, bro.
But no, I just find it weird how you
obsess over other people's weights when
you're like obese.
That's what I find strange. If like
you're sat there obese and then you're
telling other people that they need to
stop eating McDonald's. Bro, if I am Let
Let me Let me get this clear, right?
I'll make this clear as day for the
minute of time. The day that I'm 1% as
bad as you people weight wise, I will
pack it up and go gym. I will literally
just come off YouTube.
Like that's that that's that's literally
like I I used to say this all the time.
When I'm anywhere near you people,
that's when I need to [ __ ] start worrying.
You know what I mean?
then I [ __ ] 100% will. That's why I
went to the gym when I was at the other
thingy cuz I knew that like I'm going to
end up like [ __ ] L.
I [ __ ] I had to go, bro, cuz I was
going to end up like [ __ ] cuz I had
that foot injury and I couldn't be
active. So, I had to go gym and [ __ ]
So, go back. [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah, man. Going
to see if anyone wants to come cinema
with me on Thursday. Greasy, I'm going
to see if anyone wants to come to um the
cinema with me, lad.
How cute is that?
I know, bro. I know what they are. I
If not, I'll just go by myself. I don't
give a [ __ ]
I bet Grez is a fat bastard.
I bet you're a fat bastard, Grezy.
I won't go skimp, but I'm not going to
have loads and loads and loads and loads
of money anymore.
I don't think I'm going to do a both
teams to score this week cuz there's no
games that I like.
The only way to really win big on them
is put a lot of money on them. Mr. B was
like, "Oh yeah, you should put 300
pound." Oh, 6 minutes away. Nice. used
to put £300 on two teams. I can't do
that, bro. 300 on two [ __ ] teams. Are
you [ __ ] mad? Nah. Nah, bro.
I can't do that. Greasy.
[ __ ] two teams.
Nah, bro. You need to put like [ __ ]
five on the power on two teams. and not losing £500.
If you put £500 on two teams, you get
about 1,500 back. But if you lose, then
you're [ __ ] in it, basically. So, yeah.
I say if you put 500 on it, it's enough.
I couldn't do it, Dad.
I couldn't do it. Please, mate. No way.
Three minutes away. Yay.
These nuggets better be good, lad. >> Yeah.
What is that? Nine.
Better be good.
Would you ever put £300 on a football
bet? Gre. Nah.
If you could win £200 a week every week,
you'd be laughing.
If you want 200 pound extra every week,
you'd be [ __ ] laughing.
You'd be laughing, bro. 200 pound, that's [ __ ]
Yeah, you'd be laughing, man.
If you could do 80 both teams to score
and win every week for a month, you'd be laughing, mate.
You'd absolutely be laughing.
You have to work.
Yeah, we was talking about football bets. Nicolola,
I can't put £300 on a football bet, mate. Nah. Nah, bro.
There's no money in nothing anymore,
bro. You just have to stay [ __ ]
bored. I've got a day. I I I could
probably meet one of them ones from
Birmingham eventually, but only problem
is I've got to go all the way back there.
I reckon with one of them numbers I
could definitely meet them again, but
it's just happening going to go back
there, you know.
I think yeah,
but I can't um
No, I can't put £300 on a football bet, matey.
Just a losing on that on a football bet. Nah. Oh, mate.
No, I don't. I can meet my own women.
I didn't go and meet Monty because I
wanted to meet women. I went to see
Monty because I was doing a welfare
check. I can get my own women. Thanks. So yeah,
>> you're actually better off by yourself
to be honest.
Nah, you're better off by yourself to be
honest with you if you're trying to meet women.
I didn't go there to meet women.
I went there to see Monty man cuz I want
a football bet. And if I didn't go, I
would have never heard the last of it.
Ain't it greasy? I would have never
heard the last of it.
I would have never heard the last of it and
I had no excuse not to go. I've said it
about a million times. So
yeah, it is a laugh. But
no, but there was one though. He was he
was talking to this woman that I
approached and I was scared what he was
saying to her. like I was scared cuz
sometimes people do cramp your style.
Maybe not intentionally. I was scared
what he was saying. Um
that's why you're better off by yourself
cuz you never know like cuz you don't
know what the [ __ ] he's saying. Like
you're drunk as well. You know what I'm
saying? So I mean nine times out of 10
people just cramp your style really. But
no but he was all right to be honest. So
yeah, but I prefer by myself.
But no, I like Monty, man. >> Yo.
>> Yeah. I'm [ __ ] talking to some expert now. Someone >> really?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
I don't know what
>> you're You're a player.
>> What do you mean I'm a player?
>> Why? Do you know them women that I met
on Saturday? Did you tell any of them about YouTube? >> What?
>> You know them women that I met last week
in Birmingham. Did you tell any of them about YouTube?
>> No. By
>> No, just one of them. Did you?
>> No, you did. You was live on YouTube.
>> No, I meant like the YouTube channel and that. No.
>> No. No. Why?
>> No. Just wondering, bro. Someone said you did.
>> No. Tell them nothing about YouTube channel. No. >> Okay.
>> Do you think Do you think that I get
[ __ ] random ass people in this
community of the streets?
>> Yeah, true.
>> It's almost there, Grezy. It's almost
It's almost there at McDonald's.
>> Go away. >> Huh?
>> I'm talking to a girl from I'm talking
to a woman from Liverpool now.
>> God bless you then if you're talking to
a woman from Liverpool then.
>> [ __ ] the other one the other bird who
we're talking to the fight not what I
said. Yeah. She's from Birmingham.
>> She's from Birmingham. She wanted to
meet me but I'm not meeting her. I'm not
meeting her. I'm [ __ ] meeting her. She
[ __ ] I can't handle that, man. She's
[ __ ] too [ __ ] frisky, mate.
>> God bless her.
>> She is frisky.
She was getting proper kinky on the
phone to me and that. >> Yeah.
>> You love YouTube, is it?
>> No, I don't love YouTube. I love [ __ ] these birds.
>> PJ, when I Why can I get birds, man? get
bad numbers and
stuff like that.
>> Well, you didn't get any numbers when
you met me.
>> Yeah, I know. Cuz I weren't trying to.
>> Yeah, but yeah, you did speak to some
people though. I don't lie.
>> Yeah, I did. But did you know what I was
saying to them people?
>> No, but you still done it.
>> Exactly. You know what? I tell you what
I was saying to him. I went over to the
women who you told me to go over to.
Yeah. And I told them, "Listen, listen.
Pretend pretend that I'm meeting on
you." Yeah. My mates watching us there.
Yeah, that's what I said to these women. I weren't
>> Thank you. Yeah. Well, I got the I got I
got the goods, mate. This ordering the Mackis me.
>> You hear me?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I can hear you, buddy.
>> PJ's my PJ is my brother from another mother.
>> Yeah, we're best friends. Did you know that, man?
>> No. No.
>> Your No, your first brother is Timmy.
>> Oh, my Natalie.
>> Why do you think I'm doing this? Why do
you think I'm talking to other women?
I'm trying to make Natalie jealous, but
obviously it's not working. So, I'm done.
>> I've deleted this number and everything.
Oh, this is lovely, man. Oh, what you
got here? What you got?
I got chicken nuggets. I got fries. I
got a chicken
um chicken Big Mac. Chicken mac.
I'll show you one.
Yeah. Yeah. Go for it. I'm just talking.
I'm just texting this girl. Give me a second.
>> They are a bit spicy, bro. They are a bit spicy.
You want to see some nuggets? Nuggets.
>> I just texted. Oh, look at that burger.
>> Why they gave me a [ __ ] big They gave
me a Big Mac. A beef Big Mac, bro. What
the [ __ ] I ordered a chicken one. They
gave me a [ __ ] beef one.
Stupid [ __ ] Wait, that I'm sure that
says chicken mac. One sec.
>> PJ got the wrong one.
>> No, it says chicken. It does say chicken
mac. They gave me the wrong one.
I just gone on an order. They did give
me the wrong one. [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
Large chicken Big Mac. That's what it said.
That's all right. I'll eat it, bro. Not a problem.
No, it's fine, bro. I don't mind.
I like both of them.
>> What? Did you get a free meal, PG? >> No.
No. Fine, fam.
>> Yo. Anyway, PJ, listen. M
>> do you know when we went out that night? Yeah. >> Mhm.
And then Natalie ended up in Lord Jer
going mad at me because I was talking to
some other birds.
>> Yeah. Well, I was just thinking, yeah,
how the [ __ ] am I supposed to know what
Natalie wanted when she's not telling me
what she wanted? You know what I mean?
How the [ __ ] am I supposed to know? Only
what I know is I've been ringing her
text me for ages and she me just big.
>> Yeah, I've deleted a number now.
Anyways, I'm done playing games with women.
>> I'm just talking.
>> I am. I'm done. I'm just talking to this
one woman. I'm not going out with her.
I'm not asking I'm not doing [ __ ] thing, mate.
>> Yeah, man.
I'm not going down now. I will pick
myself up. Nuts.
>> Yeah, good for Natalie. I'm not asked.
I'm not asked, Mr. Bean. I'm not asked.
I'm going back to [ __ ] M.
Look, listen. It's not hard for me to
get another bird. It's not hard for me
to go out there to get laid. Come on.
>> Have you seen how many women I've been talking to?
But I don't want to do it to Natalie. I don't.
>> You should love Natalie.
>> I do love Natalie. I'm not just saying
that I do. I'm not going on about that anymore.
But Natalie should have told me before I
even went out and clubbing with PJ,
>> don't on anybody. Don't do that because
give me time. I'll come and talk to you.
She should have just told me.
>> But but still, I never cheated on Natalie. I've never
>> You still love her. Of
>> course, I still love her. I will always
love Natalie. Always will do. I don't I
don't even mean to hurt her. I don't
mean to hurt her, but [ __ ]
But he's not really.
>> We'll take it more.
>> I've got like [ __ ] six women swimming
lining up here, PJ.
I want to say some words.
>> No, no, you go crazy. You enjoy your [ __ ] meal.
>> Are you forgetting how many dates I've
been on? How many how many people I've
stepped with? I think you forgotten it.
Sorry, Monty's gone.
>> No, the book in this one who I'm talking
to should actually send you a picture of her. Yeah.
>> What this one look like?
This one is
>> need to stop. No, they need to stop.
>> I'm not going.
I Oh, she text me back with a [ __ ] cheeky smile.
>> Oh, bless her. She put I like you to your
These people are weirdos. >> Monte.
Yeah. USA is use so many filters. You
were just saying that my accent is cute.
>> Oh, sex. Wait, what? What?
>> You're a nice bird. >> Yes. Monty,
I'm not even going to explain anything
to you anymore, Monty, because you never listen.
>> Go on. Go on. I'm listening. Go on. Sorry.
>> I said yesterday, Monty. Yeah.
Um, from tomorrow, which is today, I'm
going to stay off of YouTube for a week
cuz I can stay off YouTube. And let me
see if these people can. But these
people can't get off YouTube. You see?
>> No, they can't. No, they can't. They
can't get off YouTube.
They're They're the ones with no life, is it?
>> Yeah. I'm done with Natalie now.
Anyways, I'm I'm done playing games now.
You know, if she wants me, she knows
where I [ __ ] am. I will always get
get with I'm staying single.
>> I'm just talking to women to try and get Natalie jealous.
That's it. I want to get Natalie
jealous. Just say,
>> "Oh, Natalie, [ __ ] it. [ __ ] her." Yeah,
but you're not supposed to say what
you're you're not supposed to say that
you're doing that. Even though you are
>> Yeah, [ __ ] it. Taking off my sloppy
seconds. [ __ ] it. If not like desperate
to go out with someone like ugly or go
and meet someone like ugly, leave it to it.
>> No one's going to get with J. He's an ugly bastard.
>> He is ugly bastard.
>> No one's going to get with him.
I'm keeping my options open now.
tried starting on me yesterday and I
told her about herself and she shut up.
>> Yeah, you see I destroyed her, didn't I?
>> Robin destroyed DC yesterday.
>> Mr. L,
>> let me tell you something, Mr. B.
One second, Monty. Yeah. How many years
is that Lord J been singing over women
and no woman? We've never seen him with
a woman. He's never even been seen with
a [ __ ] woman on YouTube. He No woman
wants the [ __ ] fat ugly fourey
bastard. That's why
>> Okay. No. Why am I doing Jamie? Give
myself a punch in the face. Leave
Natalie alone. Yeah.
>> [ __ ] hell. No. I'm talking to myself.
Telling myself to move on.
>> God bless you.
>> I'm going back to Man I'm going back to
Mansfield tomorrow, mate. I'm going back
tomorrow. I'm coming.
>> I'm moving. I'm moving out of Birmingham.
>> Why are you little retards emailing the
housing? You [ __ ] little [ __ ]
>> You didn't You didn't answer me
yesterday. You didn't answer me
yesterday when I when I when I asked all
of you on YouTube, why are you doing that [ __ ]
>> What? Yeah. Well, you could have been
living here with us in it. Why are you
little weasels eing the [ __ ] um the house?
>> They done it with me as well. That's why
I'm going. That's why I'm leaving as
well. I can't be asked with these
[ __ ] getting me kicked out of this place.
>> They didn't do it to you cuz you're still there.
>> Yeah, I'm still here. Yeah, because I
told them I told them they could even
ask my mom what these do on YouTube and
I've already told him you could give I
give to my mom's number and everything.
How cowardly that is. What they do is so cowardly.
>> Your only why you're not allowed is cuz
you threatened women and raping and all that. Look.
>> But it's cowardly though, is it? >> Mhm.
>> Cuz they know where you are, but they'd
rather do anything and everything by me. I mean,
>> no. If it's called I don't have nobody
in Birmingham. mood we have in
Birmingham that [ __ ] [ __ ] me off and
nothing at all thinking that I'm
cheating on her and all that. Look, I
know I should talk to no birds either
way, but [ __ ] it. Why am I going to I'm
sat here all by myself. I got to swiggle
my fingers and shut up and not talk to nobody.
>> Of course, I'm going to talk to people. I'm depressed.
I'm [ __ ] depressed. I [ __ ] feel
suicidal. And stop ringing a [ __ ]
ambulance on me people saying that I'm
suicidal and all that. Look, I'm going
to call myself and that. For [ __ ]
sake, if I if I do myself, leave me a
[ __ ] loan. For [ __ ] sake.
>> I just think it's weird that he made in
the housing. Do you? >> Yeah.
If I want to talk myself, I talk myself.
That ain't got nothing to do with
anybody. If I want to [ __ ] jump off a
[ __ ] clip, I jump off a cliff. That
got nothing to do with no one but me.
For [ __ ] sake, leave me the [ __ ] alone.
If I want to swing off a swing, I swing
off a [ __ ] swing.
Diesel in Diesel's Diesel's [ __ ]
dead, mate. Diesel dead. He's gone. He's
gone. He's gone. He's dead.
>> You keep saying you are suicidal. People
are worried for you.
>> They're not worried for me.
He does want me to get sex. That's what
it is. I tell the police to [ __ ] off and all that.
>> Why the [ __ ] are you people eing
housing? Just answer me
[ __ ] cowboys in this community. It
>> I don't need to join diesel. I'm happy
me. I'm not going to commit suicide
over. I'm not committing suicide over Natalie.
Oh no, woman. I'm just depressed. It's
Natalie's ignoring the [ __ ] out of me.
Absolutely. [ __ ] all.
>> I like I like these um I like these
nuggets. These nuggets are better,
Grezy. These nuggets are better. Who's
emailing housing? People on YouTube
emailed [ __ ] Monty's housing so I
couldn't live with him.
Is it Monty?
>> Yeah, this housing. Yeah,
he made in them videos of me.
Yeah, them were nice, boys.
They taste better with a coke as well.
DJ could be living here by now. He could
have been in this house by now.
>> Cowardly. It's so cowardly as well.
>> I got the text of a guy um saying he can
move in. I will do my
>> Yeah, they emailed the landlord. They
>> Oh, hang on, hang on, hang on. She's
wrote me. She's wrote to me. I will do
my best to cheer you up. >> [ __ ]
email the housing and the [ __ ]
landlord and [ __ ]
>> PJ, I'm going to jump off you. I'm going
to talk to this bird. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I am nuggets.
But yeah, someone emailed the house. He's housing.
I don't know why they they do that. The
cow. I don't like that cowardly [ __ ] man.
What about you, Bri? No, I don't, man. Yeah. So,
that's what I can't stand about this community
is the [ __ ] emailing and [ __ ] They
they were emailing things that I had said. um
like years ago, Greasy, which is what I
was basically saying to like yesterday
or they know they were here is that's
how you know these people have got
autism because they they obsess over
things people have said years ago,
but they're not willing to do anything but grass.
Like that's the [ __ ] that annoys me.
Even though I was not actually going to
move in with him, obviously I'm never
moving to Birmingham, bro. [ __ ] everything.
No, I never. So,
um it's not even that. It's it's the
whole the whole point of it, you know.
They won't do anything to you. They
won't meet you. They won't do anything,
but they'll get you kicked out of places
um and send housing uh videos. Like
you've got all of them videos saved of
things that I've said what years ago.
Come and do something about it then.
It just it annoys me, bro. It does. That
cowardly [ __ ] like that does annoy me,
bro. I can't lie to you, man. It's annoying, man.
It is so [ __ ] annoying.
Does annoy me, bro. It's the whole
principle, you know.
If I ever find out, bro, where one of
these people live, I'll be going on
their [ __ ] door, man. I won't even
joking. I'll be going on their [ __ ] door.
I have to, bro.
I hate, like I said, I hate [ __ ] like that.
If they were actually going to come on
the door and do something about it or
try to go on that door, whatever, then
I'd be like, "Okay, I respect it." But
they do cowardly things like emails and
[ __ ] So cowardly, bro.
What do you think, Grezy?
Yeah, sorry about that. Right, man. I
just can't stand candy [ __ ] like that.
I'm sorry, man.
Uh uh uh uh.
It's cowardly, isn't it? Whoops.
What do you think we cowardly? Yeah.
You know what I mean?
And they don't care about things that
you said about women. And they don't
care about the things that you said
um like kids years ago. No one cares about that.
They just like to [ __ ] with people
behind the keyboard.
You know what I'm saying, bro? like
they'll find any ways to [ __ ] with people.
You understand? That's what I hate about
these people on here, bro.
I'd love to know where one of these
people live, bro. How's that?
They're just obsessed. Things you've
said about women, things you've said
about kids. You know, that's what made
me laugh. You know, when I first come on
this community Yeah. and I said stuff
about women. What the [ __ ] is it to you,
bro? Like, what what the [ __ ] is it to
you? Like, people have had bad
experiences. What the [ __ ] is it to [ __ ] you?
You know when when Craig Goodson was on
here? Yeah. When he used to come on here
and all that [ __ ] was going on. Who the
[ __ ] is it to you what I've said? And if
you've got a problem with what I've
said, come and do something about it.
And if not, then stop [ __ ] this whole
grass and [ __ ] It's annoying, bro. It's
cowardly. They're never going to meet anyone.
Like, what are they going to do? just
keep [ __ ] emailing
[ __ ] housing and [ __ ]
[ __ ] annoying, man. It's so weird. It's like,
why do they care about things you said
about women? You've had more women than
them. You're in your rights to say how
you feel, bro? Like, you can do you can
say what you want. The [ __ ] are they,
bro? What have they got? Have they got
Ms and sisters? That's their problem,
bro. If they've got moms and sisters,
whatever. I'm talking years ago and that
that's their problem, bro. They they
knew where people lived. It's not like
they didn't know where people live, but
the alternative was they would do all of
this coward [ __ ]
I'm saying, yeah, Craig Goodston was No,
he's not on here anymore, but he was
from here. Yeah. >> Yeah.
It's weird, but
I hate these little glasses on there, bro. Yeah, bab.
Why do they care about things you said
about women? You've had more women than
them in their whole life.
I could never imagine
defending women the way these people
have on here. You know, it's just autism.
Well, that that's a big part of their
autism though. At the same time, their
big a big part of it is their a big part
of that is obviously like their autism,
you know what I mean?
Obsessed over things and stalking and
that, you know what I mean?
Let me go on that um
go on that Jamie Thompson's um thing.
See if he's still stalking me. Not been
on that channel for a few weeks.
Yeah, still stalking me. I've not been
on that account for two weeks.
Uh, do I think I'd ever become a serial
killer? Uh, stop asking stupid
questions. That's your answer. Stop
asking [ __ ] questions. What?
Yeah, that's autism, bro. Oh [ __ ] I
didn't even got it, bro.
Yeah. Why are we still obsessed on YouTube?
He's still obsessed. They're still
obsessed with me. Wow.
He's still obsessed on YouTube.
I don't got that account anymore, lad.
They want me to be a serial killer.
It does seem that way, doesn't it?
still on YouTube stalking me. It's
interesting, isn't it, lad? I've not
been on that channel for a few weeks.
Yeah, that virgin's been obsessed with
me for years, man.
That reminds me, I need to contact the
[ __ ] um solicitor tomorrow about that as well.
Oh, mate, that virgin's been obsessed
for [ __ ] donkeys years. That's That's
nothing [ __ ] new.
It is strange how grown men sit on
YouTube all they obsessed with Peter bed is it
they stalk you every day. It is it just
goes to show that they want to be you
but they can't be you. So they hate you
and they hate the fact that they can't
be you. It's mad, isn't it?
But like I said, it's just autism. It's
just their autism, you know,
obsessed on YouTube every day. It's just
part of their condition.
was part of their their autism, their disability.
>> Don't know, bro. Ask him. Oh [ __ ]
Yeah. Apparently he was getting married
in Vegas. Yeah. He's just on YouTube
YouTube stalking me all day every day.
Yeah, it's mad. One sec.
No. Why am I going to do that? One second.
Yeah. No one Why you bringing that
virgin up anyways, bro? No one cares.
Don't bring that virgin up on my channel, mate.
He does need to get laid though.
Me and [ __ ] Steven Howard, we say it
all the [ __ ] time, bro. We say it all
the time. He does need to get laid. He's
going to f He going to [ __ ] die a virgin, mate.
If he keeps this YouTube [ __ ] up, he'll
die a [ __ ] virgin.
He's going to [ __ ] die one.
He didn't want him back.
I could imagine being a 31y old virgin,
but each their own, lad. [Music]
But yeah, who done them emails anyways?
Who done them emails?
That [ __ ] annoys me, bro. Like I was
saying, that really does annoy me. Even
though I was never ever going to move to
Birmingham, I don't think. And it's just
the whole principle
is that they tried to [ __ ] with people's
life behind [ __ ] emails, behind the
screen. They're still obsessed from
years ago. Like, not even recent stuff
years ago, but they're not willing to meet anyone.
That's the [ __ ] that annoys me. That's
the thing that really annoys me, you know?
It's just autism all over. So
>> it's probably that [ __ ] trauma though
to be honest.
No, it annoys me, bro. It does annoy me.
That does actually annoy me, bro. coward
[ __ ] like that actually does annoy me.
That's why I said to somebody make sure
no one knows the exact um bar club we're
at cuz you know what these little
cowards do on here. These little mongos
like if joins then we'll meet him. We'll
let anyone join the hangouts but don't
say exactly where we are
because you know what these little
cowards are going to do. So yeah,
it was someone. It was someone, mate.
Yeah, it was someone.
If they had If they had it their way,
I'd be [ __ ] homeless if they had it their way.
I need to send that solicitor stuff
tomorrow as well. I keep forgetting. Yeah, mom.
What do women say if you approach Callum?
What do they say? See, people think I
went to Birmingham for women. I went to see Monty. Yeah.
What do you think they say, Callum?
Oh, you don't call approach.
I have a boyfriend.
You missed those single days.
Well, you can be single again. No,
that's what these women say. If you
approach them, they say they have a boyfriend.
I don't even really try anymore, lad.
Me. I just went out to see Monty. I
thought, "Fuck it. Be a laugh, isn't it?
Just had some McDonald's. Yummy. Yeah,
man. Don't know when I'll be out again
drinking. Two weeks. Yeah.
There's so many simps on Instagram, is
it? So many simps.
So many bloody simps. Jesus Christ. [ __ ]
Yeah, I'll meet her. You keep telling yourself that.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that, buddy.
If it helps you sleep at night.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that. Yeah, man.
Yeah, of course it will just happen, bro. Obviously.
I know. Yeah, cuz one day you're going
to wake up,
women aren't going to be stuck up. Women
aren't going to pretend they've got
boyfriends. Women aren't going to be
addicted to social media. Just one day
you're going to wake up and the thing
that's been happening for years is all
of a sudden one day going to stop happening.
Yeah. Cuz I mean that's like totally
believable, isn't it? Yeah. Cuz one just
one day, one day
all of that stuff's going to change.
That's totally believable, is it? Yeah.
Like even though you've been up and down
the country, you haven't met anyone, you
go out every week, but yeah, one day
you'll wake up and all of a sudden it
will be different.
Yeah, man. Totally. That's totally believable.
Totally. Totally believable. Yeah, man. Oh [ __ ]
Yeah, bomb is still on there to be fair. Emily,
money, come back.
So, Stephen Howard,
I can't move in with Monty now because
of these people,
which again, they're so [ __ ] that
they don't realize that if I was
actually going to move in, that would
actually give them content. That's how
[ __ ] they are. All of this like
getting people chucked out and all of
this. They're stopping They're stopping
content. They want content, right? And
they This is how [ __ ] they are. They
They want content and they want to get a
reaction and they want to torment people
te, but they don't realize that all of
this grass and [ __ ] will stop it all.
That's how [ __ ] [ __ ] they are.
They're so [ __ ] They don't even realize that
never stay in a tent.
Yeah, I'll probably have some pork chops
tomorrow to be fair.
So, they're actually stopping madness
happening by grass and stuff. It doesn't
make any sense.
Just doesn't make no sense
whatsoever. That's how [ __ ] disabled
they are in this community. you know. No, man.
None at all.
Yeah, Daz. Somebody emailed where
Monty's staying cuz he was trying to get
me to move in with him and that and
someone emailed him from YouTube sending
them like videos that I've said about
women and people's kids like years ago
and now I can't move in. So they're just
little grasses on here, bro. It
even though they're they're the ones
that are stopping content.
They do this grass and stuff, but they
don't realize that by doing that,
they're stopping reaction. They're
stopping content. So, they're the ones
that are losing out, but they're so
disabled that they don't even realize
that. And I was never going to move
I was never going to move in with him.
Obviously, I'm never going to move to
Birmingham. But the whole principle,
guys, is that like they
they're obsessing over things years ago,
right? It's not like they haven't known
where you live or you know you you know
where you was living for years, where
you was living for months. It's not like
they didn't know where you were. But
they will never come and meet you. They
will do anything but meet you. They're cowards.
They're [ __ ] cowards, bro. Even
though I was never ever ever going to
move with Monty. It's not It's not the
point, bro. It's not the [ __ ] point.
The whole point is they are doing
anything in their power but meeting you.
Like I swear to God, Daz, if I ever ever
ever find out where one of these people
live, bro. Trust me. Like just it just
annoys me the cowardness, man.
It just annoys me the [ __ ] cowardness
of it all, you know? Just like if they
could like get you kicked out of one
place and then you can go into like a million others.
You know what I'm saying?
How many times How many times have you
known where I've lived and you ain't
done anything? You knew I was in [ __ ]
Stratford for [ __ ] almost a [ __ ]
year. None of you little [ __ ] came
and done anything to me. You're just all
cowards, bro. You're all cowards. You're
literally all cowards.
That's what you are. You're [ __ ] cowards, bro.
Uh, that's what you are.
You don't get no women. You're still
[ __ ] virgins. Yet, you're obsessed
with what I've said about women.
Somebody that gets more women than you
will ever have. Somebody that's had more
women than you cowards will ever have. It's laughable.
You know, when you're sat there
defending women and trying to [ __ ] up
people's lives, these women are not
going to sleep with you. They're not
going to get with you. They don't care
about you. But yet you're still
obsessed. Come and do something about
it. Come and do something about it then. Simple.
The only people that run away is you [ __ ] losers.
Smokey B was asked to meet me. He
ignored me the whole time. You're all
cowards. You're all little [ __ ]
That's what you are. wasting your life
away defending women that don't even
[ __ ] like you, that don't even care
about you. It's embarrassing. It's
pathetic. It's absolutely pathetic, man.
But it's all good anyways cuz if I ever
find out where one of you live,
Jesus Christ, I'm going to do the most
cowardly thing ever.
You know what I'm going to do, bro? I'm
not even going to knock on the door and
fight them. I'm going to do the most
cowardly [ __ ] ever. If I ever find out
where one of these people live, work. Yeah, 100%.
it's entertaining. It is to be fair.
Just don't cry when it happens to you.
Simple. Bye-bye now.
Just don't cry when it happens to you. That's it. You know,
some madness, lad.
>> Yeah. Sorry about that rant, man. I just
don't like the cowardness.
recording this, lad.
And they're so low IQ and disabled,
right, that they like, say you was
actually going to move in with money.
Yeah. YouTube would be going live all
the time giving people content. But they
don't realize by doing that they're
stopping content. But that's how
disabled they are. that they don't even
realize that doing that just stops stops
like madness is happening. So it just
defeats the whole object.
It contradicts the entire thing, you know.
Say for example, Yeah. Timmy was going mad. Yeah.
And he was in a pub. It's funny, is it?
We like it. We like the content. So
would we get Timmy kicked out of that
pub? No. They're [ __ ] they're so
disabled that they don't even realize
it. It's laughable to be honest.
You know, I've traveled around the
country, bro, multiple times and none of
these people have ever met me, bro. Ever
[ __ ] met me. So, it is cloudy, bro.
That the fact that they scooped
emailing when they've literally had
several chances to meet you. You know,
they've had your address. They've been a
couple of my addresses. They've had me
live in other cities. They've had me
live in other cities and no one's done nothing.
It's [ __ ] Really? It's really, really [ __ ] up. M. Yeah.
It's weird, isn't it? It's because
it's cuz they're disabled. That's what
it is, bro. It's because they're disabled.
Say if I moved in with Monty, we could
be going live doing madnesses and that
and then people will like it. They'll
keep watching because they like the content.
So, they just they're just so [ __ ] It's unbelievable.
And I was never going to move in with
money anyways. But it's the point still
stands, bro. It's just cowardly, isn't
it? It's just so cowardly.
Yeah. It's weird. It is weird. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Cuz the whole point is to make let these
people make a fool out of themselves so
you can laugh at them.
You can laugh at these people making a
fool out of themselves. But if they're
emailing places and getting people
banned from things, how can they do that?
You see what I mean?
It doesn't make no sense.
Like no sense whatsoever. It's like when
they banned me from the casinos. I
didn't give a [ __ ] bro. I was still
getting over 3K a month. Again, it
defeats the whole object.
You know what I mean,
bro? How many times have I told you I don't gamble?
I don't know how many times. This is
what makes me think that there's
something wrong with your brains. I've
literally repeatedly said I don't gamble.
I gamble like once on the football like
every month. That's all I do.
I literally have said about a million
times I don't gamble, bro. Like that.
And then you ask the same question.
Yeah. I put £50 in.
Yeah. Yesterday, which was the first
time in three months, I don't gamble. I
repeat what I just said,
I collected some winnings. I put £50 in
the slot machine.
That's bro, I don't gamble. That's what
makes I think it's autism as well, bro.
I think it's autism because of like how
they still obsessed with things with
things that you said about women. It's
autism, right? And the fact that they um
um and the fact that they tried to get
you banned from places, but yet they
want the content. So yeah,
I think they've got autism as well, bro. It's weird.
Yeah, I'm thick. You're [ __ ] thick.
Yeah. Okay. So, I gambled £50 in a slot
machine the first time in in in in uh 3 months,
right? So, what do you mean? Am I still
gambling? I gambled once. Why would I
still be gambling?
[ __ ] idiot, man.
But yeah, bro.
You know what I mean, bro? Yeah.
But no, I'm not gambling. To answer your question,
[ __ ] gambling, bro. Well, I actually put
100 pound in the machine, but I just
took 50 out cuz I didn't want to lose
the other 50. No thanks, Jeff. No,
>> no, thank you. M.
But yeah, the cow wouldn't the coward
[ __ ] Um, it does piss me off a little bit, bro. You know,
it's like what that Triple H star does.
He [ __ ] stirs
and then you go to his city three times
and he won't come out.
You know what I'm saying? It's [ __ ]
up. Proper proper [ __ ] up.
And you want to talk about that prime?
Yeah, that was one person years ago.
What about all of the other people, the
ones that actually doing the emails? And
guess what? I can actually say something
about that prime now. Where was he
Saturday? He was nowhere to be seen. And
I was in his [ __ ] city.
And he was nowhere to be seen. Just like
Timmy was nowhere to be seen.
And you was actually in Heath City. It
weren't you weren't even [ __ ] You was
halfway somewhere. You was in Heath City.
So I mean [ __ ] if you want to try and
bring that up. Where was he [ __ ] on
Saturday when we was live god knows how
many [ __ ] times.
So I mean [ __ ]
It's a coward [ __ ] I don't like, bro.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
Who the [ __ ] are they to tell you what
you can and you can't say about women?
Who the [ __ ] are they, bro? That you got
sisters, good for you. You got a mother,
good for you. Don't we all?
You know, [ __ ] good for you, bro.
I don't know what they expect you to
[ __ ] say to them. You know,
the [ __ ] absolute weasels, bro.
Weasels on this community. Proper weasels. Weles. I mean [ __ ] Yeah, man.
And they're so [ __ ] like I was
saying that if they got you banned from
one pub, you just go to another pub and
another pub and another pub and then the
staff change. That's how you know. Like
I said, bro, it is autism with these people. Yeah.
That prime was nowhere to be seen
Saturday, was it? I said to him, I'm in
your city now and I'm not [ __ ] moving.
Nowhere to be seen.
Madness, bro. [ __ ] madness.
They're all [ __ ] weasels on this
community, mate. [ __ ] weasels. Yeah.
[ __ ] weasels, lad. Yeah.
Now that they obsess over things people
have said years ago. Jesus Christ. Where is
It's just on.
Is that the real Monty?
Yeah, like I said, a few months at a
time. Just like the football. I'm not
going to bet on the football this week either, bro.
Maybe week after.
It's just a waste of money gambling, bro. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Do you think it's weird, Stephen? How
these people email [ __ ] places? It's
[ __ ] weird, isn't it? Mad Really?
What's your tips, lad? I might do
football bet Saturday, but I'm not doing
80 pound again. Maybe put 20 pound on.
Yeah, I'll put 20 pound on, but that's about it.
Yeah, I'm not putting 80 on maybe 10 20 pound.
What's up, bro?
I might do a treble.
I might do Swindon, Coldchester, and Crawley.
Let me know. Let me know. Yeah. Whoa.
How many teams are you doing?
I'm just watching his friends where
they're kissing on in friends.
That's how USA is. He kissed me.
That's how USA is. He kissed me. Steven Howard. Yeah.
Oh, there the two teams. Yeah.
Or is three teams too much?
Why is it too much? Three teams.
Well, I done six teams before and they all won.
I'd done six teams before
Steven Howard and I won £75 off a pound
when I was 19.
What do you mean?
Yeah, I was just watching um a scene of friends Greavvesy
where they were kissing and I said
that's how USA Izzy kissed me. Grezy
It's cute, isn't it?
Yeah. I wish I had [ __ ] 80 pound on
it. That [ __ ]
six teams that day, bro. I was had
[ __ ] 80 quid on it. Oh, mate. I'd be laughing.
Yeah, it was.
Yeah. 75 times 80.
It's a lot, ain't it?
Yeah, it's a lot, mate. £6,000. Jesus Christ.
It would have been more as well cuz
obviously the pences add up as well.
Obviously the pences add up, don't it?
I wish I had more on that football bet
that day, man.
You know, it's going to come in. One of
these football bets are going to come in
one day, Steven Howard.
And you're going to wish you had more on it.
That's what someone said to me one day.
And it it was true. And you're And
you're going to wish you had more on it.
>> Yeah. It's true, ain't it?
It's true though. Yeah.
I wish you had more on it, lad.
What's the biggest football bet you've
ever won, Steven Howard?
Mine was at sixfold.
I can't believe I I actually got all the teams madness.
Where is he?
Yeah, I was 19, bro.
Even if I had 20 pound on it, even if I
had [ __ ] 20 pound on it, that would
have been good.
[ __ ] [ __ ] 19, you know?
What's the biggest bet you've won?
where's the biggest bet you won, Steven
Howard, on the football.
Yeah, that sixfold was nice, man.
[ __ ] pound on it. Imagine£300 on that.
Wish bet you wish you had more on it. Is it?
I bet you wish you had£10 on it.
Yeah. Bet you wish you had a tenner on
it though, didn't you? Yeah.
I bet you was thinking that it I bet you
was you was wishing you had more on it. It >> Yeah,
you was, wasn't you? Imagine
you had 20 pound on it.
Not not even not even £50, not £80, just
20. Imagine you had 20 on it. Just imagine Could
have been nice.
It wouldn't be stopped though because
they would pay you in cash
and you wouldn't need to declare it. No. Cuz
they'd pay you in cash, wouldn't they?
When I won that 4K in the casino, I got paid cash.
How am I going to win loads of money
again, man? How the [ __ ] am I going to
win loads of money again? Can't play
online roulette. It's rigged.
Trying to think, bro. Yeah.
How [ __ ] up is that? Steven Howard,
you can't even [ __ ]
play a fair game of roulette anymore.
Online is so rigged.
Wish there was a way, man. Yeah.
New play online roulette. Steven Howard,
you should play it, man.
Greavves is a gambler.
Yeah, Camden. I've not been to Camden in
few years. Well, no, tell her that I was
doing I was doing the Uber Eats there
actually not so long ago.
Yeah, I was doing some deliveries there actually. Yeah.
Yeah. You don't trust online roulette?
Well, do you trust the casino roulette,
Steven? How would
you trust the casino roulette?
Let me know. Let me know.
Gravesy, let me know. Let me know.
I keep hearing that on the Tik Tok memes.
Do you trust a casino roulette? Steven Howard.
So what? You're never playing roulette
again, Steven Howard? No.
You never You're never going to gamble
and rule it again. No.
Let me know. Let me know. Yeah.
Yeah. Them nuggets were nice, man.
Back to the nuggets. Yeah.
Hey, you okay? Kak,
how are you, man?
Yeah, these [ __ ] cowards emailed
Monty's [ __ ] landlord showing them
videos of me speaking about women, so I
can't move in with him now. [ __ ] cowards.
They're [ __ ] cowards.
They're [ __ ] [ __ ] Greasy. Yeah,
cuz they want content,
right? But they stop the content by
grassing because it stops what they
want. So I moved in with Monty and then
I went live and you got actual content.
By doing that, that's stopping it.
That's how disabled they are that they
don't even realize that they're
defeating the whole object. That's how
[ __ ] disabled they are. It's a madness, bro.
They really are disabled, aren't they?
And the fact that they're still obsessed
with things you've said about women, it
just goes to show that they're autistic.
It It goes to show, bro.
And you know the maddest thing is, Richie. Yeah.
You know, the mad thing is with these
little weasels, it's not like they've
not known where I've lived. It's not
like I've not been all over the country.
No, no, no, no. You know what I'm
saying? Oh, you want to mention Prime?
Well, where was he Saturday when he was
being called out?
Where was he on Saturday when me and
Monty was calling them all out? Where
were these people? Where the [ __ ] were they?
Nowhere to be seen.
Nowhere to [ __ ] seen that. So they
can't even bring up that prime thing
anymore, bro. Richie, they can't even
they can't even bring up that prime thing anymore
cuz he was called out along with Timmy
and [ __ ] no one no one come forward,
bro. So they can't even use that anymore
cuz I was actually in E city and I said
move me. I'm not moving anywhere,
you know. So they can't even use that anymore really.
What do you call that?
You didn't know that. Mhm.
This is a lost picture. Um, Grezy. Yeah. Mhm.
This is a [ __ ] lost picture. Yeah, Graves. Mhm.
It's all right.
I'm loving life as well. Yeah, bro.
That Jennifer Anderson looks horrible
now, isn't it, Greavves? He's so [ __ ] old.
It's horrible when we get old, isn't it?
Truly is horrible when we get old, eh?
Do you remember anything he used to say
Cole was fit to fit in?
You little copycat.
Yeah, he's a [ __ ] little copycat.
Ain't it greasy?
If you don't like Chev Cole, you're gay.
Hey, you're a copycat.
What a little copycat.
He's He's trying to fit in. He's trying
to fit in with the crowd. Remember, Grezy.
Yeah, that's copying.
See, even when you look at this Jennifer
Aniston, she's not even that good. They
just look like normal people.
There was a trend with her going as well. Her Beyonce,
Cheryl Cole, they all copy each other.
There's been a few of these t uh trends going that
Yeah, they copy each other.
Why do they copy each other? Greavvesy.
Greavves. Did you ever watch East Enders?
East Enders. Coronation Street. Emadel.
Yeah, East Enders is kind of near where I live.
M&L's Yorkshire and obviously Coronation
Streets Manchester, is it?
If you don't like shovel car, you're gay. It's crazy.
There's nothing special about this [ __ ]
I don't know why people say that. Literally nothing.
It's not even somebody I would cold approach.
I used to like Steve.
So why did the virgin say if you don't
find Cole you're gay? If you don't find
Chevil Cole attractive, you're gay.
That doesn't even make any sense because
I've had more women than him. Guess
it's just copying, isn't it?
Why do you think um Steven Howard,
so if you don't think she's attractive,
you're gay? How does that How does that make sense? Huh?
What the [ __ ] That's copying.
Yeah, that is coffee and lad.
Do you think it's coffee and
no G? I used to like that Steve
in combination street. I thought he was funny.
You remember Steve
and then East Enders
and East Enders. I used to like
Um and then East Enders
I like um Phil Mitchell.
Yeah, Phil was funny, man.
What was that? Michelle's Keegan. What
was her name in Coronation Street?
I mean, people used to be obsessed with
her, but at least she was actually good-looking.
That Cole thing was just a trend. Yeah.
But even if you didn't like her, it
doesn't mean you're gay. You got to
realize that people have got different types.
Do you understand Greavesy?
People have got different types that
they go for. Do you understand?
So when somebody says that you're gay
because you don't like Cheryl Cole, it
is literally copying because people have
different types of
uh people that they go for. You understand?
You understand, bro? Like so.
That is definitely definitely copying.
It is copying, bro.
Because it's the name. You understand?
They copy it because it's the name.
Who that Stacy? No, Stacy's overrated.
That Lauren's ugly. Do you remember
Lauren in East Enders? She's [ __ ] ugly, bro. I know.
Yeah, that Lauren in Eastenders.
I think she's [ __ ] ugly. Me.
What do you think, Grezy?
They used to be obsessed with Penny and
Big Bang Theory as well.
That was also um copying.
These are all trends.
Yeah, they used to be obsessed with
Penny and Big Bang Theory. Again,
nothing special about her,
your average Joe that you'll see on the
street. But because it's a trend,
everyone follows it.
What about me?
Let me know. Let me know. Nah.
So, Greavvesy, do you find shovel car attractive?
I don't think there's anything
attractive about her personally.
I'm not insecure about my sexuality. Matey.
Yeah, but Virgin Boy said that if you
don't find her attractive, you're gay. What's attractive?
I don't know. What's what is attractive about her?
If I could see it,
it must be copying.
Yeah, it's copying, bro.
I don't like copycats.
Did you ever watch Emidel Greavvesy? I
tell you, he was good-looking. Yeah,
I used to like that. Um,
Alicia with Emma down me. I think she was sexy.
Yeah, she was actually I think she was good-look.
She had a nice body as well.
Yeah, people have different types. I'm
sure there's people that like people with tattoos,
you know what I mean? Yeah.
You know, her name was um Alicia in Eva.
She was she was nice. She had a good
body as well. Yeah.
Who the [ __ ] is Zoe Slater?
I don't even remember that. Oh, bless. Oh.
Oh, bless dot in life.
Yeah, dot was very old.
Yeah, she's dead.
Oh, she was 95 when she died. That's not bad.
95. She lived quite a long life then, didn't she?
I can't believe them two from Little
Britain are still alive. Griezy,
it's okay. I'll just wait. You'll wait?
Yes. Until it's been made.
I'm looking for a photo with a depressed horse
with a depressed horse.
That is funny as [ __ ]
Yes, that picture looks but it looks
like that horse has got a glimmer of
hope. So, I'm not sure that will doy.
Yeah, that was funny [ __ ] bro. Funny
[ __ ] Funny [ __ ] But yeah. Yeah.
Going to get some popcorn in a minute.
Can't wait to go to the movies on um on Thursday.
Yeah, I can't wait, bro. Thursday to go
to the movies.
It's going to be a lovely site, isn't it?
Can't wait to watch that weapons. Are
you going to watch it in the in the pictures?
Yeah. I can't wait, bro. Munch on some popcorn. Progress. Oh [ __ ]
It's called Weapons.
It's a It's a horror film called Weapons. Yeah.
She don't want to love you.
He rejected your ugly ass. Oh, [ __ ] Yeah.
What did you did you look up? Um did you
look up for it? Mhm. Oh, squeezy. It
Yeah, it's got to be a good film. Remember,
Grezy, you like it down here, son.
You'll never have to grow up.
Hey, it's your dad. It's me, son. You
like it down here, son. You'll never have
That is sick, bro. It
>> Have you noticed with these horror
movies, they always put They always They
always put [ __ ] kids in it. It's
>> Yeah. Cory, how did you remember? How
did you remember it was the clown?
Uh, you remember your films there, don't
you? You like it down here, son? Yeah.
Hey, Ben, it's me, your dad. Yeah.
It wasn't the '9s. It was the 80s.
Maybe it was the night. I'm sure it was the 80s. Yeah.
You all taste so much better when you're afraid.
You want me to pull it up? Okay. One second.
I will put it up.
You will taste so much better when you're afraid. Come. One sec. One second.
Let me see.
One second, bro. You like
You like it down here, son? One's [ __ ] [ __ ]
One second by please. Let me type this.
One second. What's it called?
Yeah. One second. One sec.
One second, bro. [Music] on. Um,
I hate having to type this out, bro. It's annoying.
I hate this, bro. Give me a minute. Let
me type this. You still there, Gy? Please
is the biggest troll on YouTube.
He is literally
Where is it? There it is. You ready? What's up,
Benny? Come. He's like, Bennett, come here. Come here. 55 in. Hello.
And look, it changes it.
I love this.
And look at this, bro. [Laughter]
I love it, bro.
I love Penny Wise.
He's a nasty He's a nasty creature,
though. Ain't it?
Penny Wise is nasty.
He's a nasty clown.
You like it down here, Benny?
They always use kids, don't they?
That clown is like a pedophile in a way
if you think about it.
And it screams. He's basically like a
pedo that cloud. Okay. Oh [ __ ]
Who is it?
Did you Did you watch that horror film I
told you about?
The one I saw last time.
Did you work here?
>> Yeah. Did you watch it?
I was pretty good, man.
Make sure you watch it.
We both had a McDonald's, didn't we,
Grezy, to celebrate um Stitch's life.
>> Yeah, to celebrate Stitcher's life. >> Yeah.
>> Who who do you remember who killed um Stitch Squezy? No.
What are you feel?
You think it's mad like how much this
YouTube [ __ ] has done to Monty
and it's all on the same website. You
can watch Penny Wise.
It's all on the same website. You can
watch Penny Wise.
That's the scary thing, isn't it?
That's what the scary thing is.
Why do you love Stitch so much, Grezy?
He's cute, ain't it? Stitch is cute.
I was thinking of getting a Spongebob bed in.
I was thinking of turning this room into
like a Spongebob room. Painting it
yellow, yellow bedding,
Spongebob toys. I was thinking of like
decorating the room.
What do you think, Bri?
That clown is funny, bro. Yeah. I want
to find my mama. Yeah.
Where do I find my mama?
Yeah, I can't find my anywhere.
>> What the [ __ ]
Where do I find my mama? Uh,
my mommy was so good to me.
She gave me kisses. She fed me. But then
she abandoned me.
My mama abandoned me. Why?
Where do I have to go to find my mama?
Is she in this country?
Peter belly can't get attached anymore
because he's already found his mother.
Taking a baby away from it mama.
You'll never forget the first time I
said that. Is it? Taking a baby away
from it mama.
I'm trying to get Monty on the live.
Yeah, I'm trying to get Monty on the [ __ ]
Yeah. Hurry up, man.
You like my mama?
Do you think my mommy was good-looking?
Grey, my mommy still ignores me.
I still message my mommy time to time,
but she just ignores me. Mhm.
Sometimes I reach out to my mama, but
she doesn't care. One second.
I can make you laugh. I can make you
laugh. One second. Look. Look what I got on.
Yeah. What's that? One second. What?
Are you sure that you wait there a minute?
I love that, bro. I actually do. Yeah. Hold on.
Where is it?
Where is that thing?
Where the [ __ ] is it?
No, there's a funny scene. Where is it?
Where the [ __ ] is it? Goozy, man.
It's not this one.
No, shut that one. Wow.
No, it's not this one.
You can tell this is 9 in a era. Chucky. Jackie.
I like Jackie. He's cute.
He's cute, isn't he? Chucky. Yes,
What's the problem?
You like Chucky, don't you?
No. Where is it? Bucky.
I want a good guy doll.
You know what? [Laughter]
Oh, I want I Hey, we
I want a
I want a good guy doll, but they're
expensive. They they sell them on Amazon.
A good guy doll.
It's shy in there. Yeah, shy. Yeah.
Oh my god,
bro. I want a good I want a good guy though.
You know, I've got a niche. Yeah. She
pulled Chucky's face once when she was
like 2 years old. Yeah. And I don't know
how she done it. I don't know how she [ __ ]
I don't know how she pulled that face,
but she [ __ ] did. That [ __ ] Chucky face. Mhm.
I don't know how she [ __ ] done it.
Ah, you stupid [ __ ] It made you laugh,
is it? Greasy.
Seriously, Greasy. Huh? Ozie, listen.
Um, I am actually starting to miss my mama now.
Oh, there's a Chucky outfit here. £22.
There's a Chucky outfit here. £22. I
might dress up in Chucky and wear it. I
might just dress up as Chucky. [ __ ] it. Is it? No.
>> Yeah. There's a Chucky outfit here. It's £22.
I'm starting to miss my mommy. Gy,
is that normal? any
normal that I miss my mama. Crazy.
I miss my mommy. Um, Cory,
I miss my mama. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, Corby. We're just watching Chucky and Greasy.
My mama still hasn't accepted me.
My mommy tried saying that I was
stalking her. How could I possibly be
stalking her when she
when she brought me into this world? Boozy.
She brought me into this world and then
she abandoned me.
And then when I tried to find her, she
she said I was stalking her. How does that work?
You know what I mean? Sorry. Peter B
can't get attached anymore because he's
already found his mama. H
That's sad, is it?
Found my mama.
I can't believe my mama left me.
I want my mama back.
Now she's sagging some other fella. Ruby,
now she's [ __ ] shugging some other fella.
Do you know what I mean? Wooy. Yeah. M.
How can you just get into another
relationship when you have a child
to look after?
You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Sig was never your mama. Mhm. Remember,
somebody said to me, "Sig was never your
mama. Sig, not Peter Belly's mama." See
what I mean with you people? You just troll me.
You just troll me all the time.
Well, I'm actually being serious, but
you troll me.
Dig is not Peter Belly's mama.
Mhm. And I said, "Why didn't you say a
tell me that she was Why did she try to
hide it?" Someone was like, "She's
you wanted to keep it a secret."
Yeah. To my milk.
My mama looks really nice. I like my mama.
I love my mama and my mama loves me.
Do you remember that with the Tom and
Jerry? I love my mama and my mama loves
me. I can't even watch that Tom and Tom
and Jerry thing, man. It's so cute with
a little duckling. Oh,
I love my mama. The duck. The duck
thought the cat was its mom.
Why did you take all your pictures down, mama?
Why did you put your
Why did my mommy put her Facebook on private? Queezy,
I can't show you her little photos now.
Huh? I really Yeah, that's the one that
gave me a [ __ ]
I really want I really want you, but I
don't think you want me.
I do, but we can't do it right here.
Yeah, she gave me a [ __ ]
She gave me a [ __ ] in the alleyway.
That was so cute, wasn't it?
I'm going to show you something.
I'm going to show you something, bro. One second.
You're going to love this, Squeezy.
You're going to love this, bro.
One second, bro. Look.
Oh, I hate these adverts. One second,
bro. You're going to laugh at this
>> on.com. Let's select children's shoes uniform collection.
I love this. Oh.
It's true. You're a nice
watch all day. You know,
he's trying to cook you, silly goose.
It's so cute. I could I could watch this
all day long.
>> No, don't walk into it. No. H. Oh,
he's not your mama. He's a cat.
No. How can a cat be your mama?
It never It never gets old.
Never ever ever gets old. Grezy, bless him.
See that that that little duck found its mama.
Mhm. Mhm. You know what I mean?
See what I mean?
Wow, that's so
that is [ __ ] that is good. [Music]
I need to get some more. [Music]
So funny, Grezy. We're the same age, but
we're such kids, aren't we?
We're such kids, aren't we, Grezy?
We're such [ __ ] kids.
We're shot kids in the head, aren't we, bro?
I'll show you a funny one.
Where's the [ __ ] version?
Oh, this is funny, bro. One second.
I love this.
He's trying to He's trying He's trying
to learn a little mouse.
Do you don't you don't you
don't you understand? He's trying to
learn the vows.
That's funny though. I swear you know
the first time you know the f you know
the first time I watched that Yeah. And
I heard his laugh. I was [ __ ] dead.
I was [ __ ] dead, bro.
This is the same website. Yeah. Not
Ronny's had [ __ ] on YouTube. Gregy.
Imagine that. This is the same [ __ ] website
these little characters are on. [ __ ] that, bro.
That's [ __ ] mad, isn't it, Grezy?
Oh, that's close.
That was close, bro.
It's not funny.
Oh, imagine that. Grieving. Me you king
USA is he sleeping on a US ste sleeping
on a Spongebob bed. Steeping in a in a
Spongebob bed in
cute is it?
Yeah. It's cute, isn't it?
That would be a lovely sight.
A Spongebob bed in. Oh
yeah. With a little McDonald's. Oh, this
is my mama.
I'm just looking on my mommy's Facebook.
My mommy has lots of tattoos, doesn't she?
She's my mama.
Her dad her dad commented on her photo
saying what a beautiful woman you turn
out to be.
What a [ __ ] you turn out to be actually. A
yeah, but you think it's all funny,
isn't it? What? So, Grezy, you'd
actually you you actually see yourself
as mature? I don't think I'm mature. I
think I'm very immature,
Grezy. I think I'm immature. Me proper.
No, I'm not. I laugh at anything and everything, bro.
Me, I can't help it.
Ant-Man says to me that I'm immature as
well. I just laugh at any, you know,
when like people go around um
approaching women and they say they've
got boyfriends, I laugh at it. Antman
says, "How can you laugh at it? It's depressive."
He says to me, "How can you laugh at it?"
But he thinks he says it's depressing.
Yeah, it is depressing. Yeah.
I remember I was inspect Sabers with one
of the tenants um
and he had to show something but he
didn't have no internet and I kept
thinking of Bungle Bungled the bear and
I kept laughing and he said stop
laughing like a [ __ ] He says can you go
outside? You're embarrassing me. I
couldn't stop laughing.
I couldn't stop laughing bro. He says
can you go outside? Stop laughing like a
[ __ ] He said, "Yeah, [Laughter]
I laugh at everything."
You hear laughing like a [ __ ]
Thank you, C.
I was speaking to some women earlier
from Nottingham, Grezy. It was a good
conversation but the entitledment
we was talking right she's from Pakistan and that
and we was having banter and then I said
oh can you cook me a biryani like a
biryani and [ __ ] yeah
and she said oh who are you who are you
to me for me to cook for you and I'm
thinking there's no way you're talking
to me like that see they're just all entitled
they're all entitled they've all got the
same attitude Dude, they're not even
worth like [ __ ] talking to, bro.
Like the entitlement, you know what I
mean? I can't be asked, bro.
She's being like, you got these [ __ ]
average Grezy. You got these average
looking overweight women nowadays with attitude.
It's [ __ ] bro. It is really bad. there.
Robert Grezy, what made me laugh here
with Ant-Man there
is he said the only place you're not
going to get I've got a boyfriend is Asia.
But he's right though, isn't he?
He said the only place you're not going
to get that is Asia.
That's what he said.
He said he hasn't got it once and he's
been back for over a month now.
That's the only place we're not going to go.
Do you reckon I'm ever going to see my
mommy again, Greasy?
I kind of miss my mama. You know,
I kind of miss my mommy
and her gigantic boobs. We
will be able to see my mommy again.
Why is she gone? Why, Grezy?
But she said she was going to get a
tattoo with me. I I had the conversations. Greasy,
why is she gone? She said we was going
to have tattoos and stuff. Yeah.
Why did my mommy abandon me? That's horrible.
So, how did Tam and USA Izzy meet? Cuz
Tam's my daddy
and she's my mama,
which explains where where my roots come
from cuz obviously I have Scottish in me. Cuz
I say to Elaine sometimes, "You can't be
my mama. We've got completely different
taste buds." And
she doesn't m like Elaine doesn't like
horror films. Like we've got completely
different taste buds. And then when I
And then me and USA Izzy, we like horror
films. She likes all types of food and
travel. So it makes more sense that I
came from her
cuz me and Ela are completely different
in like taste buds like everything.
Sometimes I try to get Elaine to come
and see a horror film with me. Elaine
wouldn't be seen dead watching a horror film.
So I think them two really are my parents,
you know. I don't know.
I think that is my it's got to be it is my mama.
And Tom can't feed me. Um Greavvesy, I
need to be fed.
I need to be fed, Greavvesy.
My daddy can't feed me.
Yeah, but me and Elaine's got different taste buds.
We're different in every way. Me and Elaine,
we even have our TE's different, steak,
different. We're just different in every way. So,
just can't believe I'll never see my mama again, you know.
Do you think my mommy was pretty, Grezy?
Do you think my mama was pretty?
I know she usually used to use a lot of filters. Oh,
what's that little face?
What's that little face about then? Kingy boy. Kingston.
Yeah, like I said, I called her like a
month ago. She picked up and said hello.
And I said, "Go suck your mom.
Go and suck your mother."
Which which was right in me doing that,
you know. Greasy. Yeah.
Yeah, man. I feel lost without my parents. Griezy,
I can't believe both your parents died.
That's [ __ ] crazy. Grievy,
just absolutely bless you in life.
Absolutely. Bless you. That's all I can
say. Bless you. Well,
if my foster mom dies, I'll be [ __ ]
cuz then I really will have no one.
I have absolutely nobody then when my
foster mom dies.
So, um, anyways,
why can't you stand aside meny?
Do they just annoy you or what?
Yeah, they're rich them. They're rich.
They are the side men.
They're [ __ ] rich them.
They're rich though it gives you them side men.
They're rich in it. Greavves
decide when I'm rich.
But yeah, they are annoying.
Their channel will die one day, bro.
Their channel is going to die one day.
You know that.
Well, be too late then.
They do like hide and seek, don't they?
Have you seen the hide and seek ones?
Have you seen their hide and seek
videos? I bet you haven't it.
Yeah, but you've seen it though. Is it
as like advertised? really.
Name me some other channels and I'll
tell you if I've heard of them.
Let me try and think of some. We was
doing this yesterday.
Your name is son.
Never heard of it. Nope. No.
I was watching this thing. Yeah. This um
guy doing deliver grievously. Yeah. He
done deliver for 24 hours straight and
he made £280.
Do you think that's worth it? No.
I haven't heard of him either.
So, we done 24 hours work and he got 280.
That's quite good, isn't it? Um,
no, I've never heard of him. I just
looked him up.
I don't know how we done that for 24 hours.
Name some more.
I'm trying to think of some as well.
I'm trying to think who else.
No, I hate that Jack Jones though. I
hate that Jack Jones, bro. like you.
Let me know. Let me know.
You like Jack Jones.
I hate ducks, bro.
Name me some more. Nope.
No, I don't know, bro.
Do you know Cal Freezy Grezy? Nope.
You don't look how freezy. Um.
Name me some more.
Do you know owners pranks? Owners pranks.
You know, owners pranks
You don't know who that is.
God bless you then.
Oh, bless you then.
Bless you then, Grezy. Bless you then. Oh, [ __ ]
Have you applied for Uber yet?
Grezy, have you applied for Uber? You
said you was going to do Uber in your little bicycle.
Bless you to get you out of the house. Yes. Little bicycle. Oh.
Yeah, I said to box.
Come in the box.
I would. Why not, Gregy? Give it a
whirl. Earn some extra money.
I would give it a whirl.
said he's going to come in the box. He's
just having a poo poo.
Oh, bless him.
Did you think that if um that Monty was
going to hit me the other day? I did
agree. Do you?
Obviously. I thought when I went up
there he's going to hit me. Didn't you think that
you need to be careful when you meet
people, bro, that you have a history with?
If you have a history with someone, you
never know, bro. They could just hit you. You understand?
That's why you have to be careful.
But that's what I was afraid of. One second.
Let me know. Let me know. One second.
Yeah. Yeah, me and Greavvesy was
watching some Chucky.
Yeah, me and Grezy was watching some
Chucky, weren't we, Grezy? Oh,
yeah. Me and Greasy was watching some stuff. H.
We was watching Chucky, weren't we, Bob?
>> What do you want, PJ?
>> We was watching Chucky.
>> Is that it? You just [ __ ] stop me
from having a W for that.
>> No. What are you doing?
>> Nothing much. Just ke I'm only messing.
I won't be around. I'm just talking to
people. people meet me. I'm not on there
to date people, by the way. And stop
coming over saying [ __ ] >> Yeah,
>> you're talking about Natalie and all
that. Saying [ __ ] we [ __ ] about Natalie. >> Who?
>> All these everyone knows something that
that [ __ ] put this up play. Yeah,
everybody knows or meet me about Natalie. Jesus Christ.
So I don't know why people coming on
saying all that when everybody I'm not
even looking for a relationship on me.
>> If people want a little bit of fun on me
that's fine. That's fine. But I'm not
going out with anyone over there. I'm
not talking. I'm on there just a conversation is it?
>> No I'm not there for the [ __ ] I'm not
PJ. I'm really not because I could have
met that girl tonight. I told her to
[ __ ] off like over.
It's you who's getting me into trouble, PJ.
>> How? You're single.
>> Yeah, I know I'm single.
>> So then you can do what you want in it.
What the [ __ ]
>> I know I can do what I want, but I don't
want to do what I want. I want to show
[ __ ] Natalie. I'm a trust for every
[ __ ] lad. Obviously, I [ __ ] up by
[ __ ] flirting with these women, but
I'm doing it for her
to get to show what she's going to lose.
I don't want to lose her. But if that's
what she wants, then that's fine with
me. I'm not bothered. I'm going to go
back to where and start fresh.
>> Well, yes. So then you're still not over
her then. Of course, I'm not over her.
Natalie, the thing about Natalie, she's
been there for me. Do you know what I mean?
I never be off. That's [ __ ] [ __ ]
up. I will never be off in Natalie.
>> You know what I mean? It's like
>> I'm only on meet for conversation, not
to [ __ ] go around shagging people or
anything like that.
>> Jesus Christ. >> Yeah.
>> But she's probably going to get with
other people when you're not, you know
what I mean? So, like
>> I'm not bothe I won't get back with her.
I'm not going to get back with her.
She's going to end up shagging off a
YouTube. But [ __ ] her, man.
>> Come on. He left.
>> [ __ ] hell, bro.
I would go on that meet me. How am I
getting him into trouble when he's
single? That doesn't make no sense. I'm
getting him into trouble. How can I be
getting him into trouble when he's single?
What the [ __ ] bro? So, so
it's okay for her to go around probably
shagging, but not you. What the [ __ ] man?
That doesn't even make sense. >> What?
I said you can get with who you want. You're single.
>> Yeah, I know I can get with whoever I want. PJ,
>> but only how I know that Natalie still
likes me. Let Let me tell you how I know
that Natalie still likes me. Yeah, she
would have gone up on Lord Jes.
But the thing is, yeah, a woman can't
keep a man hanging for 4 days straight
without no answer.
Do you know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> She left me four days straight with no
answer, no reply, no comment, no nothing.
>> Yeah. So I thought, "Fuck you." And I'm
going to go and meet me and talk to
whoever the [ __ ] I want to. And that's
what I've done. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? And obviously I've
got loads of people talking to me
or even now I've got a text now. >> Yeah.
Yes. Yeah. No, you just had my phone go
off. No, I got a text. No. What the hell
I'm talking to? She's a decent woman.
>> Yes. I
don't even know what that says. Okay.
See, I can't read comments, so I'm all right.
>> It's just all [ __ ] weird, bro.
>> Need to chat. Okay. So,
>> it's just weird, isn't it? If you
look to a girl
literally this girl texting me I'm not
texting her and don't ask me I do it every
see I'm talking one sec one sec
You always need a chat.
Yeah. Go [ __ ] meet her.
>> Go meet her. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Go meet her. What? Don't What do you
mean go meet her?
>> See, is PJ getting me into trouble? Go
meet these girls.
>> Stop being silly. Is it? Huh?
I don't know. How the [ __ ] is this happening?
I'm not even good looking, man.
>> Just go and do it in it.
>> PJ, you don't understand yet. If I go
and meet anybody off meet me, that's not
completely done. You might be completely
done with me anyways, but I I'm gone
anyways tomorrow. Natalie's only got
tonight till tomorrow till 6:00 or
whatever to try and [ __ ] fight for me
back or whatever. I'm gone tomorrow. I'm
not going to be here. I'm I'm going.
I'm literally going. I'm
>> going to be now two weeks.
>> What? Me and Natly broke up. >> Yeah.
>> A week. Mm.
>> [ __ ] knows, man. I don't know. But
you're going um
>> you're leaving anyways, bro. When you in it.
>> Yeah. But yeah. Yeah. There's nothing
here for me. There's nothing here for me
no more. I'm not
>> when you leave then you're going to have
to find someone new anyways then because
you're going to be in a different city.
>> Yeah, exactly.
>> You know exactly like
>> so like
>> that's why I'm keeping my options open.
That's why I'm not rushing into no
relationships. That's why I'm not called
approaching. I'm not doing any of I'm
just having a net a chat a little bit of
banter flirt a little bit of flirtation
but not [ __ ]
um just a joke flirtation not serious or
nothing like that. You know it's not
serious and that obviously with the girl
who I were talking to the other night
who was sent them boys clips off. This
is totally different girl now I'm
talking to now. This is totally different woman.
>> Yeah. been I've had about what
if you going on my I I get be birds
talking to me. Lord, it's not me coming
on to them or me. It's them coming on to
>> It's It's not me approaching them. It's
them called approaching me. It's them
coming up on my panel giving me their
numbers asking me if I want to go a
private chat with them. I'm like
scratching my head. What the [ __ ] So
when I go private chat with them, they
like sending me pictures of the chicks
and the fanny and it's like what the
[ __ ] you are.
>> I ain't even ask for that then. That's
it, man. I start talking flirtations,
>> You're naughty, is it?
>> What? I want my naughty
>> cuz you are. You're naughty.
>> I get numbers. I get
that. I'm never single. I'm never ever
single. Never single. I can get a
girlfriend in a click of my finger. So,
it don't really matter with me. Like,
literally, if people think it's hard for
me to go out and pull or whatever else
out of that, two seconds, I got a bed.
>> What's your location at? What's your
location? Is it Birmingham?
>> No. Meet me works by location.
>> Yeah. So, what is your location now?
Birmingham, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Location. But it's it's
located everywhere around the UK that
you probably you probably got more
chance of pulling on meet and you are
out on the street.
>> I think if you was in London you
wouldn't find anyone in it.
>> PJ I find them all over. I find
>> I don't think you I don't think you
could in London.
>> The [ __ ] knows PGA. I don't know to be
honest with you. I'll say that you know
>> saying that I've been out with one bird from London.
I know we're back on PlayStation. Um
who was she call now?
Sophie. Some girl called Sophie of a PlayStation.
>> I think it were Hannah. Some girl called
Hannah. Not rude girl likes another girl called Hannah.
>> What? Hannah knows
>> emo. So kind of a hot musher kind of looking one.
>> Is that the one that the the [ __ ]
virgin legs lied about [ __ ] sleeping with?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. They met and he tried saying that
he [ __ ] her and she No, she she never
[ __ ] him. No,
>> she didn't. She didn't. Not at all. And
>> she's from um London. Yeah.
>> So, yeah, I have pulled up women in London.
This is what I'm on about. I'm I'm not a
cheater. I'm loyal to a woman at the
moment. My options are open. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? And and that's
what I'm doing. My options are open. If
Natalie doesn't want me or anything like
that, then then my options are are
hoping staying open still. I'm not I'm
not rushing into a relationship. I'm a [ __ ]
>> I want to get to know a woman this time.
I want to find out if that woman's right for me. >> Yeah.
>> If she's going to run off when [ __ ] gets hard
because I can't cope with a woman who's
going to kick off and argue with me and
then tell me it's over because she can't
have no conflict. >> Yeah.
>> There we go. Check me again. You still
say you still staying awake? Yeah, cuz
I'm still saying work. Yeah.
>> Yeah, man.
I'm not doing anything wrong.
>> But anyways, money, you need to try and
meet one of these people, ma'am.
Oh, yeah. You're not getting what I'm saying?
>> If I meet these people, that's going to
[ __ ] it completely up with me and
Natalie. I've not met anyone. Maybe I
had a bit of fun on them. I didn't even
have phone sex with that girl. And it
was only that girl having phone sex. I
was just talking dirty to me. It was
only you having phone sex, not me. We
weren't on camera. It weren't. So I
don't know. Soon as soon as I finish,
>> I can make I can make you laugh. Yeah.
>> Go on then.
>> Okay. I will.
>> Go on then. What? Going to make
>> Yeah. Someone cherry. Yeah. Do you know
what it is? >> Someone
>> I don't know. Steven Howard, go and ask him. >> What?
>> And Monty's not getting all of these
birds. And why are you comparing me and Monty anyways?
>> Who's comparing us to
>> this stupid account on YouTube?
>> Why are you comparing
the bro? Remember,
>> you shouldn't compare yourself to others.
Hey Monty, I've got that video of you
approaching. Should I put it up?
>> Go for it.
>> Nah, bro. [ __ ] it. I don't I don't want
to give these little mongos content, you know.
>> I w even cold approaching her. I just
told her, "Pretend I'm cold approaching
you." That's what I said to her. I
didn't even cold approach her. I just
talked to her and walked off. Well, I
told her just walk off and she did.
That's what I said. I said my mate my
mate talking to her.
>> Yeah. So I didn't cold approach no one
that night PJ. No one. Absolutely no
>> I were talking to her. I told her just
pretend I'm cold approach. She like
coming to you to ask you for your number
and all that. My mates like what [ __ ]
>> So when I just said walk away and she
did and she did.
>> You know I went I didn't want to go out
to code approach or [ __ ] whatever. I
went out to have a good night with you
and that was it. Same, man. Same. Same.
>> You know, that's only what I wanted
obviously. Yeah, we were good pulling
them two [ __ ] birds at the beginning,
but they were just
>> No. No. What did that one say that you
approached the last one, you know, in
the in the in the club?
>> Yeah, that's the one who went over
>> nothing because
I I whispered in the rear, didn't I
saying, "Pretend I'm pretending to could
approach you." She went, "Okay, okay." I
said, "Just go along with it." So, she
went along with it for a couple of
seconds. There must have been one that
you were seriously doing. There must
have been one.
>> No, no, no. I can swear I'm dead now on
my [ __ ] dead brother's grave. I did
not go approaching.
>> What the [ __ ] >> No.
>> Yes, Steven Howard. And so have I pulled
a million times and I'm not lying
because you've seen it. So stop talking
about [ __ ] Monty man because you've
seen me do it a million times as well.
So shut the [ __ ] up. Anyways, Monty.
Yeah. Like I just went to see you to be honest.
>> Yeah, of course. Of course. That were midnight
top. It were
>> It was good, isn't it?
>> Yeah. It were.
>> Yeah, man. [ __ ]
>> I'll just pull all these birds.
>> I'm lying though, Grezy. He seen he
people have seen me as well do it a million times.
So, what what what bro? [ __ ] hell.
>> I ask Wait on I ask her again. See what
what she says. Yeah.
>> Would you like to meet up in the future time?
>> In the future time.
>> Yeah. Meaning further down the line.
>> I agree with you. Do you think Monty
should um meet one of these birds or not
meet them and hold out hope for Natalie?
What do you think he should do? Greavves
a good gives good advice, man. Greavves
is a good guy.
>> Greensby, go on, Ginsby. Give us some advice.
>> I think he should just meet one that's
interested in him that like he's talking
to. I think he should just meet meet one
me. What do you think?
>> Yeah, but if Natalie's interested in me,
then she could be here, shouldn't she?
So, I mean, I'm interested in that. I'm
interested in Natalie,
you know, but at the end of the day, I
need to stop thinking about that woman.
I'm not playing games. I'm not a game
man. I'm I'm a serious [ __ ] man.
I'm I'm a serious You say like,
you know what I mean? I'm If I'm If I'm
in a relationship, I'm loyal to that
woman till the [ __ ] till I die.
>> What do you think, Greavvesy? Greavves
is probably typing.
>> You know what I mean? I'm not late.
>> Listen, listen, listen. This is good.
This is good. Give it until Monday and
then arrange to meet with this new one.
Can't keep holding on forever if she's
100% done with you.
>> Oh, 100% on that question. 100% on that
question. That's why I just text now um
if she want if she would like to meet up
in a future time. I've asked her like now
meaning future meaning could meet her
could not meet her. That's what I just
said to her. Look.
>> Yeah. Look, I've been holding on to my
mommy for [ __ ] over two years. Grezy
and I still see my mama, you know.
>> There you go, PJ. Look, I've asked her
in a future time.
>> No, I've already asked her.
>> What does she say?
>> She haven't replied back yet. Yeah.
>> So, we play back here.
>> Yeah. I'll show you a picture of it. You
want to see a picture?
>> Yeah, why not? Give it a whirl.
>> Give it a little whirl. Give it a
tickle. Give it a tickle. >> Yeah,
>> I am. If I do meet uh if I do meet her,
give her a tickle.
>> Yeah, give it until Monday. I think
that's good advice as well.
Just let me put this skin over [ __ ]
name. Yeah, cuz he's not getting a name, mate. Oh [ __ ]
Bless your money.
There we go.
There she is.
Oh, she's all right. How old is she? >> Huh?
>> Nice. How old?
>> Nice, man. Is Birmingham? Yeah. >> No, she's Liverpool.
>> Oh, [ __ ] me.
It's It's bit though, isn't it? There you
>> go. She text. Oh, no. That's my guy.
That's my mate. He's text me. You like
>> Good, bro.
>> So, you're going to have to go to
Liverpool, isn't it?
>> I will be live soon.
>> So, you have to go to Liverpool. >> Yeah.
>> That's not too That's not That's f
That's That's near Birmingham, isn't it?
>> Yeah. She a go [ __ ] got money.
>> So money if you if you stayed in
Birmingham right and you go Liverpool
from Birmingham it's not too far is it?
>> No. No.
>> Like what 30 minutes?
>> Something like that.
>> Yeah. Birmingham to Liverpool's like 30
minutes I think. Is it?
>> She will. Nice. She's
>> I think it's like 30 minutes in it, Grezy.
>> Don't ask me [ __ ] pull these [ __ ] birds.
>> Yeah, but will you travel to her? Will
Yeah, but Monty, will you travel to her?
>> You know, world.
You're not traveling to where it's not that
I'm going tomorrow. I'm not going to be
in Birmingham no more. And that's going
to probably destroy Natalie even more
knowing that I'm not in Birmingham
anymore and she br me here. Do you know
what I mean?
I'm not holding on
much longer. This is why I'm going. I've
been holding on for a while now for Natalie.
You know what I mean? I made a mistake.
>> I didn't make a mistake going out
clubbing because I didn't do [ __ ] cold.
I didn't even go cold approaching. I pretended to
kept on maring me to do it so I did it.
But I pretended to, but I didn't exactly
pull. I didn't exactly,
you know, because I didn't want to pull.
I don't want to pull now, but my options are open
>> and I'm keeping my options open for now. And
>> I've got a [ __ ] list for the women in
here [ __ ] who's texting me. There's
another woman who tells me why me
ignoring her all the time. Why? Why
don't I text her and all that? But
>> it's like because I don't like you like
you're not my cup of tea. I like you as
a friend. That's why I don't text you
like I text half of these women on you.
>> Liverpool isn't that far from
Birmingham, is it?
>> Yeah, it's far. I'm in the middle. I'm
not coming Birmingham. I'm moving.
>> Yeah, but Birmingham to Liverpool from B
Liverpool from Birmingham is like 45
minutes, isn't it?
Yeah, I [ __ ] moved halfway around. I
lived, think about it, I've lived bare
places in the UK.
I lived in Manchester.
I was down back and forth in Mansfield.
>> You lived in London?
>> No, I lived in London. Um, lived
Plymouth, lived in Birmingham, >> Liverpool.
>> No, I never live. No. You know,
>> you would live in Liverpool, don't it? >> Leester
PJ, you like my phone, you don't you?
>> Yeah. I was going to nick it.
>> Were you going to nick my phone, were will you? >> Yeah.
>> Ain't it gorgeous?
>> Yeah. You've moved to a lot of places, didn't you?
>> Me? Yeah.
>> I remember when you lived in Bristol.
>> I've never lived in Bristol.
>> Yeah, you did once.
>> I've never lived in Bristol. Not even once. >> Oh, really?
>> No, it's not a good look. I've moved all
Listen, I'm on my own in Birmingham. Who
do the [ __ ] do I have in Birmingham,
people? It's not a good look. I'm moving
around because I don't have no one else.
>> You got me.
>> Oh, you're in London. You're in London,
mate. I need,
>> you know,
>> I would have moved in with you if these
little grasses didn't [ __ ] email the [ __ ] housing.
>> Why the [ __ ] do they do You know what?
It's It's really stupid, Monty, though,
because I could be there now with you.
Yeah. We could have been [ __ ] around
and giving them content. They don't even
realize that them doing what they do,
bro. It just stops them getting content.
That's how stupid they are.
>> Yeah. Yeah, it ass. It's proper stop
them from actual getting complete good
content that ass. And it
>> [ __ ] they are.
>> It ass. And that's how fit they are.
Yeah. Because leave them to where they
[ __ ] it up. They [ __ ] it up for
theelves. Not for us. They [ __ ] up for
their ownelves. Like literally that's
how [ __ ] they are because if they if
they actually wanted content, they would
have left you to move here. And
>> we'd be we'd be live every day and we'd
be in Birmingham drinking all the time.
So it's, you know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> Giving them content.
>> And it's same as Natalie N. They say,
"So why didn't you just drink at home?"
I said I said to PJ to get a bottle of
[ __ ] vodka or something like that. We
drink at home. But no, we want PJ went
out. And you know what? That was the
best idea to go out.
>> Yeah. Drinking at home would have been
worse. And I and I and I wanted to try
and speak to some women at the same time. So
Natalie will not be bothered about you
moving away. Yeah, good thing that she's
not bothered about me moving away. I
wonder what you are. Just a little freak who seriously
try and [ __ ]
fish for a bit of attention on YouTube. You [ __ ]
>> This guy got rejected by that energy. I'm sure.
>> Yeah. Yeah, he did. He did.
heard about him or the Muslim guy. Yeah,
you've been idiot doesn't like them
anymore them black people anymore. She
[ __ ] can't stand them. You know what?
I can't wait till they get out of our country.
>> I've heard about I can't wait. Hey, I
can't stand them. I can't stand the
colors. I just can't stand them. I'm not
being racist. I just can't stand them. I
think they're just dirty, man. Dirty people.
proper dirty dirty people. Yeah, I'm
calling you the bottom guy at the
bottom. Calling you you're dirty.
>> You're a [ __ ] rapist. Pedo [ __ ] I
[ __ ] pedo. You're the prick.
>> Did she tell you about the seaside dock?
>> Seaside dark rap. You know what?
I'm going to stop talking about that
now. Yeah. M
>> I'm not ask about Natalie no more.
Like literally I'm not she rather can
come back to me or just [ __ ] off cuz I'm
not believe playing these games.
Like literally I'm not playing these
games. I rather find a woman who does
want me. He wants me for who I am. Who
can actually handle conflict. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? If if a woman
can't handle conflict, I'm not
interested anymore. It's not that I love
Natalie. I will never start with
Natalie. I will never call Natalie ever
again. Never. I love her. Even if
Natalie doesn't want me back or
whatever, I never called her again cuz
she will live for me.
>> You know what I mean? She stood by me
and I will always stand by Natalie or
will always stand by Natalie no matter [ __ ] what.
You know what I mean? And even if it's
against her own mama, I have her I have
her back. Like what what you said Dark
Queen pie Natalie Legend YouTube ruined
Mongo's life. Not necessarily.
>> You You have ruined my life. You You You
didn't even ruin my relationship.
So that's a [ __ ] I done that
myself. I ruined that myself
by coming on to YouTube telling you
little clowns I was in the hotel and that's it.
And if that's and if that is stupid
enough to split up a relationship then
that's just stupid.
So how long was you going to be in
Blackpool for then? Forever.
>> What? So how long was you going to be in Blackpool for?
Hey, me and Natalie.
>> Yeah, we
>> was only there for a little holiday.
>> Oh, okay. And he was he was going to go
back to Birmingham anyways.
>> Yeah. Yeah, we was only there for like
two three days. Two days.
>> I bet you spent a lot of money in it.
>> Yeah, we went out. We went to uh the
aquarium. We went to the [ __ ] Easter
place, the the dungeons.
How much do you reckon you spent? Like £500?
>> I know. I don't know to be honest. I don't know.
>> You know
this person who I'm talking to now, I'm
finding out her hobbies before I do
anything. And at the moment, she's into
the same hobbies as me.
>> Yeah, that's good.
>> Yeah, it is good. It is good. And that's
the thing. You I need to keep options open.
>> Yeah. If I don't keep my options open
and if Natalie doesn't want me back,
then then I can just move on,
you know, I'm not flirting with these
girls. I'm just talking to him. I've
told her I don't >> Yeah,
>> because he's text me again. See what I mean?
>> Come back in like two months, three months.
>> Too long. Too long.
>> You come back in a few months, you know?
>> Amazing. It's amaz
Oh, no. That's my guy.
Oh, okay. PG. I asked her, "Would you
like to meet up in a future time?" She
put, "Yes, I'd like that."
>> That's good. Get yourself
sorted first and then we
>> You think Monty every girl you are talking
you are you're talking you think every
You think Monty every girl you're
talking to Natalie will have 10 times more options.
>> That's the thing. It's not options. I'm
not going for the options. That's what
you are not understanding. I'm just
talking to people because I'm depressed
as [ __ ] Who the [ __ ] do I have to talk
to? I don't want to come onto this
YouTube community anymore. PJ is the one
who told me to come back onto the box.
Yeah. So, I weren't even going to come
back on the box until PJ told me to.
Soon as I leave Birmingham, I'm done. I
was I'm done with YouTube peeps. Why?
Why do you think I'm going live? I don't
even have a YouTube channel anymore,
like Streamyard channel anymore. So, I
can't even go live anyways. I've deleted
all that. So, I can't go live. I'm not
back on YouTube. I'm already here now
because of Natalie and I'm trying to get
Natalie Chel, but it's not working. So,
I'm [ __ ] dumb, man. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? I've got options.
My I got my options are not [ __ ]
I'm not going to go jump in bed with an
expert straight away like it looked like
I were going to do with that other girl
on the phone who I sent PJ had a voice
notes to. It's not that she were [ __ ]
playing with herself when we're talking
kind of [ __ ] dirty to her
soon as I mentioned licking the [ __ ]
come and all that lot
>> yeah I do Howard. Yeah. PJ,
>> have you have you ever been with a skull bird?
>> Have you? >> What?
>> Yeah, but the thing is seaside doc, the
reason she has so many options on here
is cuz the people on here were simps and
they don't need the house. So they so
they obsess over any woman. Even if she
was ugly, even if a woman was ugly,
they'd still simp cuz they don't leave
the house, bro.
>> And it's not like if Natalie does go out
with any of these on here, and that just
shows that she's [ __ ] completely
dead. I would never date anyone of this
community. No one. I only dated Natalie
because I thought Natalie would [ __ ]
you know, normal. The best one on here.
She is normal. She's just going through
a lot a [ __ ] very lot at the moment.
>> Suicide Doc Nat G didn't sleep with you though.
>> Did she [ __ ] sleep with him? He's just
trying to [ __ ] line me up. He just
get rid of him. PG.
>> Yeah, but how do you One second. One
second. How do you even know him though?
>> I don't know him.
>> I don't know him. He's already trying to
[ __ ] w me up. It's not working.
doesn't m I can get more birds than he
can. What the [ __ ] he on about? He can
sit now. When I've had more birds than
he has dinners, man, I've had more [ __ ]
and he's like and he's come out of his
own mom's [ __ ]
>> Only [ __ ] he's had is his mom's and
that's when he come out of it. >> Yeah,
>> that's it. That's only [ __ ] he's had is
his mom's and that was our birth. >> Yeah.
No, I've not not really been out with
anybody from Liverpool. This is the
[ __ ] first girl I'm talking to from Liverpool.
Listen, you're Indian. I don't give a
[ __ ] about you or your little comments
or your little words, something what you
can't get. So,
just dang your [ __ ] coconut tree. Yeah,
>> she got me that [ __ ] money m it
obviously. Yeah, he's [ __ ] bare ugly though. >> Yeah,
>> Natalie doesn't like your color anyways
anymore. She's done with them.
She hates them. She hates them now. She
completely hates them. She recording
them to [ __ ] the hotel and
everything. She doesn't like him.
>> You like You like Tom and Jerry, Monty?
Yes, I will
sort myself out
and I will meet you.
>> No, I don't see.
>> Yeah, I show you this comment now. I
don't want to show your name, right? But
look, she text me back.
>> These people are proper disabled.
>> Yeah, of course. Course they don't
bother me anyways.
>> Read that PJ. Look. One sec.
This first and we can sort something
out. Yeah, she seems keen, man.
>> Seems keen.
>> I'll just meet her, bro.
>> Yeah, I will just I'll just meet her.
>> Just meet her. Yeah,
>> cuz think of it. Yeah. Listen, Natalie
knows the situation you're in. She knows
you're in Birmingham. She knows that you
don't have anyone right now. And look,
she's still leaving you. But it's, you
know, it's not fair, bro. No, it's not
fair. It's not fair. I'm waiting. I'm
waiting for Natalie. Natalie needs to
understand that. I am waiting for her.
I'm not going to jump in bed with the
next bird straight away. I'm a [ __ ]
Natalie wants me.
She can get me. I'm going back up there
today. I'm going back. That's it. I'm
going back. I'm not waiting around
Birmingham for someone who don't want me.
What's the point?
You know, I can do better. I can do 10 times better.
You see what I want or left? Um, seven suicide dog.
Yeah, that's a seven, bro. Yeah, she's
good. Why don't you just meet her? Yeah.
Yo, what happened?
>> This phone [ __ ] my old phone is keeps
kicking me off. [ __ ]
>> Yeah, it's [ __ ] Yeah, I would say this meter.
>> It's not that, man. Here, look at this
PJ. My old are always open. Look at this
one. This one's even been talking to me.
I won't go out with her though cuz she's
[ __ ] Chinese, mate. Even this one's
been talking to me.
>> She's nice.
>> Yeah, she's been talking to me as well.
Look. Sure. You know,
I asked about her name. Look.
She's been talking to me as well. Not amaz. >> Nice.
>> Yeah. Just meet them. I would, bro.
makes [ __ ] lemon. Come on. No,
I'm not making that one though. [ __ ]
um lemon or something. Lemon lemon.
Lemon lemon or whatever.
>> So, my options are always open. Always open. PG.
>> Yeah, it's good.
Wanties and ladies, man.
the ladies man I met.
>> Yeah, you just need to meet one of them.
Just go for it.
>> How many multi got I've had a couple
actually, but some of them are [ __ ]
just want a bit of [ __ ] fun and [ __ ]
off. Some of them do to be honest with
you. Some of them are committed. So it
depends who you're looking for and who
you're talking to or wearing
really. You know what I mean? Like I
said to PJ, he needs to stop going
hitting on women. He needs to wait for a
woman to cold approach him. And that's
what I do. I don't go out and cold
approach a woman. I wait for a woman to
come and cold approach me. And that's
what happens. I don't cold approach
women. That's why I said to PJ, "Don't
do it. Don't go cold approaching."
Because you got cold approaching and
then the woman's just going to say no to
you. You wait for a good woman to code
approach you and that shows that the
woman's more keen than what you think. She
Liverpool AC Liverpool AC
Liverpool AC is here again.
I've not been out with past PJ.
Yeah, my options are good, man.
I don't want to get into a relationship.
I'm scared now to be honest with you
because I'm a [ __ ] up. I am a [ __ ] up.
I can get into relationships easier and
I can get out of relationships quick.
Read it for him.
He said, "Read it for me, PJ." [ __ ]
the Liverpool word.
Oh, I don't need to. I can read it
myself, but I'm on this phone.
I don't get that.
But you fitter. What do you mean a
fitter by that word? Like suited with a war.
You miss. Yeah, I'm not reading your
comments, man. Your comments are just
stupid. You [ __ ] idiot. Not you, the
red guy. Red comment guy. I'm one about
him with the [ __ ] the Muslim guy.
One about seaside dark. It's a [ __ ] idiot.
Oh, PJ's connection's gone. [ __ ]
Oh my god. You're dark.
I feel like snapping someone's jaw,
mate. To be honest with you, peeps.
I really do feel like snapping someone's jaw.
Yeah, that's what I'm going to give her
a try, man. See if she's actually all
right. I'm not waiting around for that
no more. That's why I'm going back up
north because I can't be asked waiting
for someone. I've been waiting too long.
I'm not one of these who's [ __ ] a long waiter.
Relax. It's just YouTube. No, relax.
It's just little [ __ ] idiots on YouTube.
It's [ __ ] mongos. More [ __ ] than
what I am. Anyways, you don't Why do you
people like you say call me the [ __ ]
when I can [ __ ] pull? This [ __ ] can
pull. This [ __ ] can actually [ __ ]
Yeah, of course it would. If Natalie
could fingers cause running back to her.
Of course I would. This is who I'm
waiting for. Natalie, I [ __ ] delete
[ __ ] every single girl who I [ __ ]
been talking to straight up and said
bye-bye now. Of course I would.
I'm the [ __ ] best shag that he's ever
[ __ ] been with and the longest
shagger she's been [ __ ] with, man.
I'm not no two second [ __ ] man.
I can make a woman come. I've made
[ __ ] Natalie come with my tongue.
Trust my tongue. She's come with just my tongue, mate.
I'm not no [ __ ] [ __ ] in bed. And I don't
have no little spooking tiny dick.
One of them with me said, "I've got a
python. I've got no I got a [ __ ] python, mate.
I've got a bat bone. I've got more of a
bat bone than you, lad. Literally
more of a bat bone than you will ever have.
If I can sit there and actually talk to
a woman and get a woman's number with
with just a finger click,
that's something good for me. It's like
I told you I said to you, it doesn't
matter if I'm not in a relationship or
not. I still can get in relationships.
Like I said to you, like
relationships, you got to look at women.
You got to see who the woman is. who
you're talking to. And this is why I
said to PJ, there's no point running to
a woman because you don't know who
you're running to. You could be running to life,
okay? Whatever else that like this
woman's come on to me. I've not come on to her. Yeah. Yeah.
Come on, man. I got a TV and everything.
I got her a [ __ ] brand new TV. I sold that.
I sold it on her cuz I'm not waiting
around for I need money to get me back
up to nothing.
I've got no food in whatsoever. I'm
[ __ ] She's leaving me eat it like
this. It just shows how much that woman
does to really care about me.
If she cared about me now. Yes. She'd
been [ __ ] coming to this house
knocking on her door. Do you know what I
mean? to be here right now
knocking on the door door ringing me or
texting me or [ __ ] talking to me or
do you know what? Yeah. I didn't even
really do anything wrong. Yeah. Y went
on YouTube cuz Nat get me out the hotel.
Yeah. And I told everybody that me and
Natalie out of the hotel but he said we
was in Manchester. So I told nothing. I said nothing.
I mean I'm not really done now. Nothing
[ __ ] serious is bad. Nothing bad.
I've not cheated on her either. So, if
Natalie says that I've cheated on her,
I've not even cheated on her.
Here we go.
She's text back as well.
She's just text me back. See what she says.
I like it. Yeah, she said I like it.
She's writing to me now. Writing to me again. Okay.
Yes, it will be good.
So, I give it a couple of weeks. No, no.
And we will meet.
There you go. And that's how it's done.
Give it a couple of weeks and we'll meet.
And that's how it's done.
What's it was? What was funny? What was
No. Here we go.
No, no, no. I did leave. I did leave.
What it were is Natalie pissed me off
that bad by kicking me out of another
hotel. Yeah, that bad. I did leave
YouTube. Natalie pissed me off that bad.
I jumped onto YouTube and said, "All
right, we in the hotel, but we in Manchester."
But I didn't tell anyone anything. Nothing.
I was just pissed off. I made the wrong
mistake by coming back on YouTube.
Oh, no. No.
Is it Bible? Leave.
I didn't leave. Yeah, I did leave. I
left YouTube. I left YouTube. I only
come back on YouTube because Natalie
decided to kick me out the hotel because
I walk her up by accident.
You know what I mean? And plus, they're
shouting at me and all that. I don't
need to get shouted at.
You don't if you're in a relationship.
Yeah. I tell you I tell you what what
not to do and what to do. Yeah. In a
relationship. Yeah. It's up to you what
what you want to do. Right. One,
if you out in public,
if one of you says something what you do
not agree with and you're in public,
agree with her. Don't not agree with
Even though you even though it is unre agreeable,
unagree with her until you get home.
That's one. Because if you ungre with
her in front of people, you're putting
your own message down and people got
worse to say.
Um it's the same as arguing.
It's the same as arguing. There's no point arguing
because arguing can just [ __ ] break
us up. Like it does. It does.
You're best off sorting your problems
out by talking.
You talk to each other
and that's how you [ __ ]
sort yourself out. Yeah.
If you if you
decide to jump out of a bed next to me
and decide to go and sleep on his Ty,
what's the point? You've only got one life.
Just think about it this way. You could
be on a set and not wake up next morning
and not apologize to your M. No, wake up
in the side of the bed as well. You want
to live one [ __ ] life. One life. And
if you just want to live your life like that, then
I don't. I just want a woman who does
wants me for who I am, for my des for
who I am. Not for
because I'm not I'm not [ __ ] a simple
Simon, now am I? Really? Not a simple
[ __ ] Simon. Do you know what I mean?
I've got my disabilities. I've got my
[ __ ] I've got my mistakes with that.
Do you know what I mean?
But at the end of the day, she text me
back. She text me back. Oh, she's writing back.
Yes, it's fine
when whenever you're ready. That's what
she said there, peeps. So, I've asked
her if she wanted to meet.
She said this.
That's what she said. So, and that's how
easy it is for me. So, it's like [ __ ]
fishing. It's not even fishing for me.
Every time I I catch, I always catch.
You know what I mean? So, there's no
point [ __ ] me sitting here crying
over in Natalie anymore. It really
isn't. And people, if you want to see my
phone, I'll show you my phone prop.
This is my new phone.
This is my new phone. [ __ ] sexy
phone, ain't it?
Look at the back of the bastard. Let's
give it a wrap at the back.
Look at the back of it. Sexy phone.
Watch this, peeps. Watch this. This is
This is how sexy this is.
Let's find a little song. Watch.
Where's PJ again?
Good phone now, mate. Show.
Oh, I'm not showing the photo. I'm not showing nothing.
I'm not showing [ __ ] all the edit so you
see it. I'm not doing nothing else no
more. I'm not showing the text either.
I'm not even putting any of that [ __ ] up
on YouTube no more.
I'm not putting that [ __ ] up on YouTube
no more. I'm not showing anyone or
saying anything else anymore
cuz I'm not letting this [ __ ] my this Well, Steven's
Steven don't want to see it. You want to
see it to have a rank over it, you dirty bastard.
sustained all the lives. I not of boats
that cross the sea. They stick them all
in a B&B.
>> Yeah. I found Tim his brother. I found
him his brother.
>> Found him his brother.
Just a regular bloke from North London.
>> Jimmy's brother. But he had a
spreadsheet crippling indecision.
That with Timmy's brother that
it looking like Timmy's brother.
Anyway, peeps. PJ, you can have your
chat back, clad. I don't know why you
keep getting me on and asking me to join
your hang out, lad.
Anyway, I see you later, PJ.
PJ, come in. Come in. So sorry.