I swear now, man. These people can't get
off of YouTube.
These people can't get off YouTube.
It's all they have. It's all they
[ __ ] have, mate. I swear down. Madness. [Laughter] [ __ ] hell.
These people can't get off of YouTube.
They literally can't get off YouTube to
save their life. It's [ __ ] mad. [ __ ] madness.
Good for him. No one cares, bro.
Who gives a [ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ]
Don't know why you're telling me, matey.
I don't give a [ __ ] I just want to know
why these people on YouTube can't get off it.
Can't [ __ ] get off it, mate.
No, I'm not. I'm just I'm just wanting
to know why you people can't get off of YouTube.
You call everyone else skin, everyone's
this, everyone else is that, but you
can't get off YouTube. So, you must be
the skin ones.
That's what I'm saying, matey. You know, it's weird. Very weird.
Yeah, man. I can get off of YouTube.
I've been off of YouTube for days and
weeks. I can get off of YouTube. You are
the ones that can't get off of YouTube.
I've been off of YouTube for days, weeks.
Yeah, man. You are the ones that can't
get off of YouTube.
Bless you. Not even to save your life.
Not even if your life depended on it.
You can't live without YouTube.
That tells me that these are the skint
ones. Skint ones with no friends. All
alone. If they can't get off of YouTube.
Yeah. I don't say I'm leaving every day.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Do you want to do it
again then? Do we do this challenge again? Right.
Starting from tomorrow, Thursday, right?
So from tomorrow, no one I don't want to
see anyone on YouTube and I'll come back
next Thursday and if I see you people on
here every day, then you are the ones
that are skinn and then go live then and
it proves it by you coming on YouTube
that then I can say it then. Okay.
Starting from tomorrow. Okay. Okay. Okay
then. Starting from tomorrow. Yeah. 100%. Okay.
And then I'm going to come back next
week and I'm going to go on the history
gezy to see who's been on YouTube, you know. Yeah.
No, I'm not gay like you,
not gay like you, lad.
We'll see anyways. Well, we'll see.
I'll be back next Thursday anyways.
The nuggets were nice, greasy, but they
gave me the shits.
They were yummy though.
Now, I fancy McDonald's again.
One who's not on YouTube anymore.
You've never seen me with a woman. Well,
you're blind cuz I've had more women
than anyone on this community. So, you
must be blind, belly, you must be blind.
Uh, just talking about how these people
on YouTube every day ain't got a life.
These little self projectors
can't get off of YouTube.
These people must really be housebound
in it. I think they're Yeah, bro. Generally like
housebound and disabled generally. I I
think these people are housebound and disabled.
They can't have loads of money. They
can't have loads of friends. If they're
on YouTube every day, they wouldn't be
on here. Their YouTube activity gives them away.
Yeah. It's mad, isn't it?
The madness. It is a madness.
I've had more women than you will ever have.
Really? I've had more women than anyone
on this on this community.
Now, do you know what? Do you know what
pissed me off, Joe? I tell you what
pissed me off. Yeah. With these people,
you know, they contacted Monty's housing
about me. I went to Monty's, by the way.
I did go to Monty's um that night. I
went there for maybe a couple of hours,
two, three hours. But what annoyed me?
What annoyed me is that um what annoys
is that they cuz obviously like money
was trying to get me to live there which
I never was going to live there. It's
not the point. It's not the point. The
thing that annoyed me, right, is that
these people have had where I've lived
for years. They've known where I've been
for years and they will do anything but
meet you, but they'll do all of this
emailing [ __ ] and all of this grassing
[ __ ] which doesn't even make any sense.
That's the [ __ ] that annoys me, bro.
That's the thing that annoys me. And
again, like you said, it doesn't make
any sense because if I was to actually
move in there, which I'm not going to
move in there, you know, think of how
much content these people would get.
They're actually missing out on content.
Not that I'd ever move to Birmingham.
[ __ ] that. But it's still the point, you
know. It's not the point. And you can't
always You are the M and you can't al
you can't even use prime anymore cuz I
was in Prime City Saturday. They didn't
come out leaving Timmy come out. So you
can't even use the prime thing anymore.
You can't even use the prime thing
because I called them all out in
Birmingham with Monty last week and
nobody came forward.
So you can't even use prime anymore. And
that was East City. So you can't even
say, "Oh, well Prime done this dude."
Where was Prime on Saturday? Where was
Timmy on Saturday when we was actually
in their city? Nowhere.
So at the end of the day, right,
what I don't understand is they will do
anything but meet you
and they just ruin content for
themselves. No, it annoys me. That
annoys me. That emailing [ __ ] and that
grass and [ __ ] If I ever, like I said,
if I ever find out where any of these
people live, I'm going on their [ __ ]
door, bro. Yeah. and I'm going to do the
most cowardly thing. And I was never
going to move to Birmingham, bro. What
the [ __ ] What would the [ __ ] would I
What the [ __ ] have I got to do with
anything in Birmingham, but it's the
point still stands. It's like, what the
[ __ ] bro? It's not like you wasn't
there on Saturday trying to meet these
people. It's not like they haven't known
where you've lived for god knows how
long. And they do this stupid grass and
[ __ ] every time, bro. And they just ruin
content for themselves as well. That's
how [ __ ] they are. Is that they
actually ruin it for themselves.
that by by getting people bound for me,
they actually ruin it for themselves. I
know he can't live with me. But still [ __ ] madness.
They ruin it for themselves. It's mad. madness.
>> Yeah, of course he would.
>> Yeah, of course. I I'm actually coming
off this YouTube [ __ ] soon anyways. Definitely. Yeah,
I absolutely would.
It's the same people every day.
Well, that wasn't said that I'm not
allowed to go there. I wasn't going to
go live there anyways, but still.
Why? Because it's cowardly and it's very
disabled of you as well. It's very, very cowardly
and it's also very disabled because you
don't even realize what you're doing by doing that.
because it's cowardly and I don't like
cowards. Simple. That's it. It's the
most cowardly thing you can do.
Cowardly little bastards, you know.
So, and it's also very disabled of you
as well at the same time.
They they get people banned from places
that's going to give them content.
They're [ __ ] so disabled. That's how
you know they've got autism. We was
talking about this yesterday with these
these little mongos on this community,
man. We were actually talking about this, you know. Yeah.
[ __ ] emailing places. [ __ ] weird. cowardly.
It's so cowardly as well. That's the thing. Come on.
Anyways, I'm going to leave you mongos
to it soon. Anyways, yeah,
I'm done with this YouTube. Yeah, man.
I'm coming off this [ __ ] soon anyways,
bro. For real.
I'm not [ __ ] addicted. Again, I'll
repeat myself. I've been off YouTube for
days and weeks. I'm not addicted.
Not at all am I addicted.
Jesus Christ. You people can't even take
a day off for YouTube.
>> Have to.
>> Yo, it's me. >> Hello.
>> Hey, why are you so pressed about the email? >> What?
>> Why are you so mad about the email?
>> Because it's cowardly mad.
How is it cowardly?
>> It is cowardly because you're never
going to meet anyone. You're never going
to do anything to anyone, but you want
to hide behind emails. It's cowardly, man.
>> It's not that I choose to hide behind anything.
>> I don't want to meet either of you. Why
would I want to do that?
>> And you're also ruining content for
yourself and other people. So, that's
very disabled of you as well.
>> What content? What?
>> I mean, if I because if I was to move in
with Monty, right? Then we would go live
and give people content. Like when you
when you call up pubs and you get people
banned from pubs, you're just ruining
content for yourself. You do realize that?
>> No. If you and Monty moved in together,
the chances of a woman being raped would be increased.
>> Oh, okay. Really?
>> Oh, really? I I didn't know that. Oh,
>> so you're a s then?
>> A s?
>> Yeah. Why Why so why would I rape a
woman with Monty?
I have you not watched both of your behavior?
>> Yeah, but can I just do could can I can
I just do that in London?
>> Yeah, but hey monthly.
>> But what? So hold on. So if I was to
rape someone, could I do it in London?
>> Yeah, you probably have done it already
to be fair.
>> Oh, really? Have I? Oh, okay.
>> No, I didn't say you did. I said probably.
>> Oh, yeah. Really?
>> Probably. Ah,
>> yeah, of course.
>> You're a coward, man.
>> All right. All right. Yeah, sure.
>> You actually are a coward, isn't it?
>> How am I a coward?
>> You're a coward, bro.
>> Email him. Did you email him about Monty as well?
>> Uh, I did. Yeah.
>> See, cowardly behavior. Yeah. You're a coward,
>> Natalie. Coward. Yeah.
>> What do you mean? It was simple. It was
like a three minute email.
No, you sent videos and [ __ ]
>> Oh, I sent a link. Yeah.
>> Yeah. There you go.
>> Two links, actually.
>> Yeah. You people are low lives on YouTube. >> Okay.
>> You are.
>> What are you doing on YouTube right now?
I'm complaining about everything.
>> Just see if you people are still on YouTube. >> What?
>> I was checking to see if you people are
still on YouTube.
>> What do you mean? >> Huh?
>> Oh, I just wanted to see if you people
were still on YouTube. >> Okay.
>> Cuz you ain't Cuz you ain't got a life, is it?
>> Ain't got a life. Come on.
>> You ain't got a life, man. Bye-bye.
One second. One second.
Now there's some weirdos on this, bro. I
swear to God, Cory, seriously, bro,
I just said to Bonnie, Tom in the box. [Laughter] Yeah,
I'm just somebody to open the box. Yeah. Jesus Christ.
This is a M, isn't it? [ __ ] hell.
That's a Manchester accent, by the way.
And I've been to Manchester before.
Didn't meet me. Funny that, ain't it?
He said he called him because he thought
a woman was going to get raped. What the
[ __ ] Guy's a [ __ ] idiot, bro.
Guy is an idiot.
You're sat here as well, Benny. Yeah. Yeah, man.
One second. I'm just making myself a cup of [ __ ]
See what I mean? Just give me [ __ ]
win, bro. I'm coming off this [ __ ]
I don't want I don't want my life to be
ruined. You know what I mean, Cory? I
don't want my life to be ruined over
YouTube, bro. [ __ ] that. Is it?
>> No, he did it with £1,000.
>> He put 260 in to get £1,000. And bro, I
don't know why you're telling me. I
don't give a [ __ ] I'm not ski
like these people on here, bro. I don't
give a [ __ ] what people win.
Here we go now.
And it wasn't £1,000 cuz you put 260 in.
So it didn't win a,000 and I wouldn't
give a [ __ ] Give me back. I did. I got
my own [ __ ] bag.
>> Yeah, man.
Don't worry telling me, bro. Go tell Timmy.
He's the one that's [ __ ] skin. Not
me. I don't give a [ __ ] I know what you
telling me, but it's done. >> Reclaimed.
Yeah, I know. He put 260 in because I
watched the video. Yeah, cuz I went on
his channel to see if you people still
on YouTube. Ain't got a life.
Yeah, that's how I know. Because I went
on it to see if it was the same people
on YouTube as always.
same [ __ ] people every [ __ ] day, you know. So yeah.
Oh, did they? That's nice for them. Oh [ __ ] Yeah.
[ __ ] I'm in a bad place now. I'm not in
a bad place, man. I'm in a good place.
I'm not the one in my 40s coming on
YouTube every day self projecting like
you people. Nah, you come on YouTube
every day projecting. You can't live without YouTube.
You lost the challenge already. Delayed
you. Imagine that. Can't even live
without YouTube. Imagine that.
These people can't live without YouTube.
That's all they have.
That's why they come on here every day
on Lord JS and [ __ ] I'm not addicted.
I'm not addicted. I've been off YouTube
for weeks. I've been off YouTube for days.
Nap. I've never took fake trips and
you're banned. Bye-bye, [ __ ] Back to
Lord Asia. [ __ ]
Um, I'm not addicted.
I'm not addicted at all.
No, I'm not addicted. Yeah. Yeah, man.
No. Last YouTube. Yeah, man.
It was that guy doing it then, wasn't it? Yeah.
But yeah, these people can't get off
YouTube. It's all they have, Cory.
It's all they have. The little mongos. Yeah.
It's the same spastics every day.
Same spastics every day. Can't get off
of YouTube. Oh,
I get off of YouTube.
Why can't these people get off of YouTube? Oh,
yeah. He needs to go off of YouTube, man.
These people need to go off YouTube.
I can Well, let me let me put this way.
I can take a day off of YouTube.
I can take a day off YouTube.
I've already took days and weeks off YouTube. Yeah. Well,
no, I don't.
I don't need to ask people how he does
it because I've already had loads and
loads and loads and loads of women.
So, I've already had loads of women, but
again, I think you've got uh memory loss
just like I was saying to who was it
yesterday? Steven Howard.
No, I'm good, thanks.
And I was saying just yesterday, which I
shouldn't even be entertaining it to be
honest. Um, the only reason Monty has
got women is because of where he's he
was living in Birmingham. I got three
numbers. They will reply back to me. I
live in London. He lives in Birmingham.
Big difference. Longterm there's a
difference. It doesn't matter. Had I
still had him had and he doesn't have
because Natalie's past tense. So what
all of these women Okay. Okay. Let's go
by your logic then. Huh?
What all of these women that he's had?
What? Two women on Meet Me. Cuz you
can't say Natalie. That's past tense. If
you want to use that logic, okay, it's
past tense. Yeah. Okay. Okay. So, how
many does he have now? But two women are
on Meet Me. Okay.
Okay. And then your point is you can't
say Natalie cuz that's past tense
if you want if you want to go by that logic.
So, I can say um Banger doesn't get no
women. He's never been seen with a
woman. The only one that's been seen
with women on this community is me.
The only one that's been seen with women
on this community is me. L has to s and
women still don't like him.
L sibs and women still don't like him.
Okay. So, he's got a few women on meet.
And and your point is Uh-huh. Okay.
Good for him.
I'm on this thing, bro.
L's never been seen with a woman ever.
He has to resort to sing. [ __ ]
Yeah, one of them numbers in Birmingham
I think will definitely meet me again.
At least one of them, I reckon.
But the problem is I'm not going to go
back up there.
That's the difference, lad. [ __ ] going
Nah, [ __ ] that, mate. Nah,
[ __ ] that, bro.
No, [ __ ] that [ __ ]
That is long.
That trip almost killed me, Richie. It
took me out for a couple of days. It was
[ __ ] long, son.
Yeah. Uh, actually would be me being a
boyfriend material. Really? You [ __ ]
[ __ ] It would actually be boyfriend material.
Scared of what? What would I be scared of?
Not scared of no one, mate.
What would I be scared of? Hey,
it would be Why do you think I'm
boyfriend material, not girlfriend
material? You [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah. Why do you think your girlfriend
material? Well, you spelled material
wrong. It's actually boyfriend material. [ __ ]
Oh, this bell is a [ __ ] [ __ ] ain't he?
Yeah. You meant to say material and it's
boyfriend material, not girlfriend material. [ __ ] idiot.
No, you said what? What? Why do you
think your girlfriend material is
boyfriend material? Cuz I would be the
boyfriend, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Oh, this guy's a [ __ ] bro. There's no
point trying to explain anything to him.
I don't even know why you're still on
YouTube, Ellie. You [ __ ] lost your
kids over YouTube and you're still on
YouTube. You're mad. You are.
>> Your [ __ ] kids was taken into [ __ ]
care over [ __ ] YouTube. That's mad.
Imagine that, bro. Imagine coming on YouTube. Yeah.
Kids being took into care like bellies.
That's mad, isn't it? At that point,
bro, just pack it up.
That's mad. Just Just pack it up and go, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. You need to pack up. You need to
pack it up. Yeah. Yeah, man.
You know what I mean?
Bro, your kid was took him to care at a
very young age. You know what I'm saying?
Just get off a YouTube belly. You're
[ __ ] Do you know this valley is so
crazy? Yeah, he got nicked. He got all
of these devices seized and then the
next day he come back on YouTube.
He come back on YouTube. He got his [ __ ] [ __ ] seized.
[ __ ] madness. You got your devices
seized and then the next day you bought
another device and then came back on
YouTube. That is mad.
You are mad, bro. Yeah.
Can you help Monty out, Joe? Have you
got a place for him to stay?
Cuz I don't have a spare
spare um place.
Nope, you're not coming in, LJ. You're banned, buddy.
Yeah, B, buddy. See you.
What's mad? Thinking I've had loads of
women. I have had loads of women. I've
put them up on YouTube.
I have had loads of women. I've got
videos of me kissing, me getting a
[ __ ] me in bed with women, me on
dates with women. I mean
I mean the video evidence is there. Yeah.
Why are you talking about women anyways?
Why are you even talking about that?
Yeah, I'm scared of LJ. Yeah. No, you're
just just a repeating bastard.
So, no repeating bastards on my chat.
Yeah, Monty's a cool guy.
I like Monty. He's a cool [ __ ]
Why are you talking about women anyways?
Why are you talking about that? They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] Joe. Joe, do you know
Joe? Do you know what Monty said? He
said, "You can see the westerinity in
their eyes." He said he's he's glad he
left. He said, "Yeah, they do seem like NPCs.
They have the same mannerisms. They say
the same stuff." He said, "You can see
the westernity in their eyes."
I was dead. It's true though. You can
They do say the same stuff. They are
literally NPCs. They literally are.
Yeah, it it sounds funny, but it
actually is true.
They literally do the same stuff. If
they were truly different, they wouldn't
do all the same stuff. Yeah,
it's actually true. It is actually true.
You laugh at it, but it's the truth.
Get him around here.
I'll get him in here. So,
I text him. I don't think he wants to
join. He shouldn't, to be honest. I
shouldn't even be on here.
I'm bored now until
I do something.
Them chicken nuggets were nice for
McDonald's, man. I might get them again today.
I said to this woman, "Let's go to the
cinema tomorrow, Joe." She said, "I'm on
holiday." I said, "That's nice. Where
are you on? Where did you go on
holiday?" No reply.
It will never change, Joe. You can see
the westernity in their eyes.
He said, "I'm glad I left."
But like I said, I do think one of them
from Birmingham will meet. Maybe.
Uh, in the end, I'll never be as fat as
you, mate. Never be as fat as you.
[ __ ] no way.
It's just the same old it, Joe. Nothing
to complain about.
How does he get all the fanny? What?
Because he met a couple of people on a
dating app. That means he gets all the
fanny. What? Because he met Natalie
Gene. Natalie G offered to meet me years ago
when I was younger. She said she was
going to meet me. So what? How does he
get all the funny in what way? Well, cuz
he met a couple of people on because he
talking to a couple of people on dating apps.
Because he met Natal G. She's met a lot of people.
She's met a lot of people there. So what
what's what's the point, man? Yeah.
I'm on holiday. Where are you on? Oh,
you know them people on Reddit,
they make up stuff, Joe.
They literally make up stuff in who?
Yeah, he got a woman. Yes, he got a
woman that would meet anybody on
YouTube. That's what I just said. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That Natalie G has met lots of people on
YouTube and she wanted to meet me. So, no,
not at all. Not at all.
And you're also remember forgetting that
we live in different locations.
Um, we actually live in different
locations as well.
Well, actually, it's not better than
nothing because I'd rather have nothing.
I'd rather have nothing to be honest.
Otherwise, I would have [ __ ] met her
when I was still a [ __ ] virgin
cuz I was a virgin at 21, 22 and I
wouldn't even meet her and I was a
virgin. Well, [ __ ] sports, but they
don't count as losing your virginity.
So, actually, I can safely say it's not
better than nothing.
Yeah, I called Prime out. I called Timmy
out and they wouldn't come out and we
was live a few times.
So, they all went quiet and they're still quiet.
Why? Because I had paid for it before
that. But yeah, I was a virgin.
It is sad that Jam has tried to blame me
for his breakup. You spent all that
money taking out taking his mind off
things and all he does is stab you in the back.
It's typical, isn't it?
Yeah, it's typical, eh?
Yeah, I spent about 200 pound day.
Yeah, you're calling me out. Come to
London then. Really?
That's typical though, is it?
It wouldn't be the first time he done
it, so won't be the last. Yeah, man. But yeah,
but like I said, I don't know if any of
the numbers are going to meet me, but
like I said, Joe, I got three of them all reply.
None of them's blocked me yet. So, it does seem
No, I didn't watch it. So it just seems
slightly different to London, but
yeah, I know you wouldn't get that in
London, but I just hate I just don't
like Birmingham. Simple.
They try too hard.
Yeah, it takes two to tango. They also
need to keep up the combo.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. They need to keep it
up as well. It takes two to tango. It
takes two people to be interested. Oh,
and another thing is when you were
saying the other day, oh yeah, you need
to speak to them. What? What? Speak to
them for like a hundred years. What?
Okay, I'll give you an example. Right.
One second. Here's one of them, right?
This this this should [ __ ] this should
[ __ ] all over your logic right here.
Where has she gone?
Not that I care cuz I only went to
Birmingham to see Monty. But let me give
you what was her name again?
So you want to talk about up convos,
right? Okay. One second.
So, this person replied to me, "Hey,
nice to meet you, too. I wasn't too bad,
actually. Just had a family day. Go
don't come back to Braum that often. Did
you make it back to London?" I said,
"Same. It was my first time in two
years." And yeah, I'm back in London
now. Did you make it back to Liverpool?
Never heard back from them.
Never heard back from them. They they
they're I think they're from Birmingham,
but they live in Liverpool. She never
got back to me. See, it takes two to
tango for a conversation
and then yeah, she never replied to that
even though she'd been on on and off and watched that. I mean,
they just lo they'll just lose interest eventually
if you keep trying to talk to them. How
are you anyways, Charlie? You good? But
I got two more anyways.
Yeah. How are you, Charlie? Um, I'm
planning to come knocks again soon.
Me and you could have a blast.
What was the difference between
um what was the difference? Um, I was
asking her a question and I replied back.
That's what the difference was.
Bro, there's no point me even asking
answering your questions because
anything I'm going to answer, you're
just going to make excuses. So, there's
no point me even answering you.
There's literally no point because
you're just going to make excuses.
This is pointless conversation. No
matter what I answer with, you're just
going to make excuses.
Any donk? What does that mean?
So there's literally no point
because you're just going to you're just
going to make excuses no matter what I
do. So it's just [ __ ] pointless. Pointless.
The problem is is
they have got unrealistic standards due
to social media. They're all stuck up
due to Tik Tok and Instagram. That's
where the problem lies. It's not you.
It's not me. It is these westernized
women which is why people go to Asia
that's the problem that the problem is
them but no one will ever admit it
because they would always defend women
so that's why no one but that is the
truth but we can hide behind the truth
all day long. I I don't mind doing it
but that is the truth. Um yeah I gambled
last Saturday. I put £80 on a double and
I won £200
to be honest. I might not even ever I
might never come to Nottingham, bro. To
be honest, I the thing is I only went to
Birmingham because Monty was in a bad
place and I thought, "Oh, let me just
help him and that." And um obviously I
won the football bet and yeah, bro, like
like he uh
yeah, he was in a bad place and [ __ ]
So, and I won some money and I said I
was going to go so I didn't want to I
would I would never heard the last of it
if I didn't go. So, yeah.
But I like you, Charlie, bro. You're a
good guy, man. Actually, Charlie, I big
you up all the time. Char, this unworthy
clock is a is a is a good guy, man.
I'm not being I'm not even joking. He's
actually he's actually a nice guy. I've
met Charlie, man.
He doesn't [ __ ] stir. He doesn't get
involved with drama and that. He's a
good guy, Charlie, man.
It's just a shame when we met last time,
bro, that um you know, you was on a
detox and it
in London, bro, let me know, you know.
Yeah, man. God's a good good guy.
If you're ever in London or whatever,
bro, just you know, I'm here on it.
So, yeah, that's what the problem is,
Joe. Anyways, is um damn.
Yeah, I had to go rock city by my
[ __ ] self, bro.
Yeah, I was speaking to some woman in
Nottingham [ __ ] yesterday. She's such
a [ __ ] man. So, you know, they've got
this [ __ ] They've all got the same
attitude, Joe. They're boring, bro.
They've all got the same attitude.
Honestly, if I didn't go Birmingham last
week, I don't know when I'd be going out
again. Honestly, I don't know when I'd
be going out again.
Yeah, I'm too old for it now, bro. I'm
[ __ ] too old for it. I'm 27. I can't
be going [ __ ] Rock City either, man.
They'll think I'm a [ __ ] pedo or some Um,
would I meet um
Nah, maybe. Yeah,
but I was I wasn't going to live there.
There's no way I could move to
Birmingham, bro. Nah,
I prefer London.
I don't really like Birmingham.
I like Birmingham as a place like they
like there's good food places and stuff,
but I just don't like Birmingham, bro.
They're very very very behind.
It's good for like food and [ __ ] Like
there's a lot of restaurants and that,
but I don't like I don't like Birmingham, bro.
They're boring as [ __ ] They've got the same attitude.
I just gave you like And here's Joe.
Yeah. He's like, "Oh, yeah. You should
keep talking to them, but eventually
they're just going to lose interest." If
you keep texting someone, how are you
going to keep someone interested for all
that time? The problem is is them. It's
not about what you do, what you don't
do. The problem is is literally them.
Like, we know that. I know that. That's
why Mon that's why [ __ ] Ant-Man's
gone [ __ ] Thailand.
It is them. Of course, it's [ __ ]
them. You see approaching videos all the
[ __ ] time. people get the same [ __ ]
you know, but it doesn't matter anyways.
You're always going to make excuses.
There was a woman that I was talking to
on Reddit and I showed her all the screenshots,
all the approaches and she just
completely ignored it because it didn't suit her.
So, I was like, "Oh [ __ ] sorry for
wasting my time."
And like I said, I only went to Bing
because of uh because of Monty. And
obviously I tried because I was there. I
won't be out this week and I probably
won't be out next week. So
I'm over it, bro. I'm [ __ ] over it. Yeah.
It's boring as [ __ ]
Once you've met one, Joe, you've met
them all. I reckon.
I'm a big believer. Once you've met one
woman, you've met them all.
They're all the [ __ ] same.
They all watch the same [ __ ] Tik Tok
[ __ ] They've all got Tik Tok brains.
They're all the same.
They do all the same [ __ ] They say the
Do you know what they are? I'll show you
what they are, Joe. Look, one second.
I'll show you what they are.
I'll show you what they are. One second.
This is what they remind me of. Hold on.
Let me put a picture up.
Here we go. This is them.
That's literally what they're like.
They're literally non-playing characters. Look.
Look, that's them, bro. Them droids of
uh Star Wars.
Yeah, it is the same.
But yeah, no replies yet. So
yeah, I messaged some of the numbers,
right? I tell you, uh, why would I turn
gay when I'm not gay?
Oh, sorry, bro. Oh, I know why you think
I'm gay. Because I don't think Shel Cole
is attractive. Well, guess what? She's
[ __ ] not attractive.
Yeah, she's not [ __ ] attractive.
And the only people that say she is are copycats
that follow the crowd like a certain
person we know.
Yeah. Sorry. I don't I I don't think
she's attractive. I don't think she's uh
I don't think she's nowhere near as good
as people make out. Nowhere [ __ ] near
as good as people make out.
Nowhere [ __ ] near as good.
[ __ ] She's like a six, bro. What the
But again, has to fit in.
They have to fit in, don't they, Joe? Um,
nah, bro. I don't like Kaye. We hate each other.
But yeah, sorry. I messaged all the
numbers that I got the past three weeks
ago earlier saying if they want to come
to the cinema with me tomorrow. Well,
some I said cinema, some I said drink
just to see what they'd say cuz I
figured, oh, you got enough numbers.
Messaged them again 3 weeks later.
Sometimes it's worked. But that's it,
bro. Like, I'm not going to go out and
try and meet new people. The numbers are
there, so you might as well try.
And then and then after that, the only
ones I've got left is the Birmingham ones.
But like I said, it is a bit strange how
three of them numbers in Birmingham all did reply.
That is strange, bro. And it's the And
it's how they replied as well.
One was asking me questions as well. She was like,
she said to me,
"Have you always lived in London?" and
she was asking me questions and [ __ ]
but I hate Birmingham, so I don't know.
But I message these numbers, see what
they say. But I won't be going out
trying again. [ __ ] that.
I wish I was rich again, Joe. I wish I
was rich. Rich again.
It used to be so nice being rich. Yeah,
it used to be fun being rich, matey,
but I'll never be skint like [ __ ] belly.
No, I feel bad for Monty though, bro. I
actually did feel bad for Monty. [ __ ]
Oh, that's what women are.
They're they're NPCs. Like, you know the
the droids in Star Wars? You know how
they're all like robots and that's what
women are like?
Well, I'm not poor. Well, I'm actually
I'm not poor. Poor is [ __ ] 20 to last
you two weeks. I'll never be poor, but
I'm just No, I'm just normal.
Funny enough, I'm actually better off
than a lot of other people, but I'm just
normal. Not poor at all, but just
Trust me, I'm not poor, bro. But I'm not
rich. I used to be rich.
I used to be rich. Not anymore. But now
I'm just normal. Not even poor.
I couldn't imagine that, bro. 20 to last
two weeks. That's [ __ ] That is [ __ ] up, bro.
Oh [ __ ] That is mad, bro.
But I'm not I'm not poor.
Yeah. I'm a danger to women. You keep
Listen, bro. You know all of this stuff. Yeah.
It's not going to make women like you.
Like, think of it, bro. You've got one
life, Diamond Fish. Yeah. You've got one
life. You've got one life. Yeah. God
gave you one life. And defending women
is never going to make women like you.
Like, think about it. All these years,
let let me put this into perspective.
Yeah. All of these years that you have
been defending women and you know,
[ __ ] I got more assets than you and I
got more money than you. Try again. um
all of this um defending women that
you've done for years.
How many women do you think I have been
with since you was on this YouTube
defending women licking their asses? The
only one that's been getting women is
me, not you. It's Listen, bro. Listen to
what I'm saying. Simp is never going to
get you laid. It's never going to make
women like you. You're wasting your
life. Like when you're if you're ever an
old man. Yeah. are just about to die in
hospital. Think of all of them years you
wasted defending women and licking their
asses and they're still not giving you
their [ __ ] It's a waste of time. Why
do you people do it? I don't understand.
I don't need to name the assets. I've
got more than you will ever have.
Listen, I'm the one that won on the
money game. And you don't even have
£500. You're talking about £1,500. You
ain't even got £500.
You skin Flynn. You [ __ ] idiot.
Poverty is defined as a single person
getting less than £250 a week. Bro, I've
got more. Okay, why don't you come in
and show us your assets? One second. Let
me fold the phone. One sec, bro. Let me
Yeah, but here's the thing, Joe. You
don't know how much money I have.
That's the thing. But anyways, let this
doggy come in and show us his assets.
if he's man enough to.
So yeah, anyways, Gam, bro, like don't
run away. Let's have this conversation,
man. I think it's a good conversation.
Defending women. You know when I come on
here when I was 22, right? Back when
Craig Goodson was on here and you always
used to sit there defending women. Where
has it got you in all them years?
Where has it got you in all of them years?
Like, think about it, bro. Like where
has it got you in all of them years? I'm
the only one that's been with women, not
these people that are defending women.
So why are you defending them? And yeah,
you know it it and like I was saying
earlier, that's what annoyed me with
them um contacting Monty Man's house
because Yeah. Okay. You come on YouTube
when you was 22 and you said [ __ ] about
women and it was pissing people off.
Yeah. No, no, no. Come in and show us
your assets. Come on.
Anyways. Yeah. Listen,
so you was coming on uh one second. So,
[ __ ] sake, man. I was um defending
women. So, you come on here and I come
on here and I said mad stuff about women
when I was 22. Yeah. What's What's that
to you, man? What? You got a mom? You
got a sister? Good for you. Good for
you, bro. Good for you if you got a M
and sister. Good for you. Like, what the
[ __ ] And all of these years they've
been defending them, but they've not
been with any. Only Peter Belly has
sing to the max, bro.
So many simps. I I just wish one day,
well, I shouldn't wish really cuz it's
their life they're wasted. Not It's not
my life. That just defending women is
never going to get you laid. It's never
going to make women like you. It's not
the way, bro. It's not the way, you
know. But they still defend women. It's madness.
It's mad how they defend women but women
don't like them. It's [ __ ] Don't know
why they do it. Must be some sort of
condition or something.
They defend them. They've been doing it
for years, Joe. They've been doing it
for years, saying, "You're an incel.
You're a danger to women." And the only
one that's really had a normal life with
women is me. It's weird.
Why they defend women is mad.
Come back on G fish. Come on. So yeah,
I know I'm not just above poverty cuz
you don't know what outgoings people
have. If you have got 300 pound in your account,
you know that's enough to buy food, to buy [ __ ]
Obviously, not to these people on here
cuz they're all millionaires apparently. But yeah,
300 is enough, you know.
Nope. I don't have only 300 pound, but
I'm using as an example.
Nope. You don't know what I have. You
don't need to worry about what I have.
All I said is I'm not rich anymore.
But I don't mind that. I don't mind
that, bro. Like, do you know the thing
that annoys me that that that annoys me,
right? It's not that I I don't I'm not
rich anymore cuz I've been there, done
it. I've got the clothes, done the
women, done the escorts, done the
traveling. That's not what annoys me.
The only thing that annoys me now is
there's not any opportunity to even make
money now. That's the thing. Unless you
want to gamble and risk losing all your
money and then be [ __ ] Huh? That's
the thing really. That's that's the
annoying thing about it.
I don't I don't give a [ __ ] about the
house. I had my life over. I've got [ __ ]
to show for it. But [ __ ] you know,
[ __ ] can't even get a [ __ ]
delivery [ __ ] job. What the [ __ ] bro?
Madness. And I actually done good to be
honest. I mean, I've had a good month
this month. Went to Birmingham, went out
a couple of times, didn't really spend anything. So,
I've been more richer than you.
I've been mocked. Hey, are you going to
come in and show your assets? Another
thing, you're asking me about my assets.
Are you going to come in and show your assets?
If you ain't got time to come and show
me your assets, you ain't got time to
type, you little self projector.
Do you know what I've noticed about you
people? It's been the same people for
[ __ ] donkey's years on this [ __ ]
community. I've noticed that it's been
the same people for [ __ ] the same
spastics for years. I've noticed that as
well. I I actually remember this doggy account.
It's been the same spastics for years.
Uh I slowly lost it all. Uh no, I never
lost it all. And you're not going to get
a reaction, so don't even try it.
Uh try again. Didn't lose any four
grand. I lost four grand, bro. Yeah.
when I was out every day pissing it up
when you was sat on YouTube. No life.
Yeah, I lost four grand, bro. It was
actually more than four grand. But yeah,
I lost it when I was out [ __ ] every
night. Out drinking, pissing it up when
you were sat on YouTube. Yeah. Yeah.
That's me losing four grand, isn't it?
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Get a life, man. Get off YouTube.
Am I right? That £1,000 that [ __ ] L J
has, he should be given to me.
Bro, you don't even have 4 grand, doggy.
You don't even have £100 to your name.
I've asked you a million times to come
in and show your assets, and you can't
show nothing. So, shut up. You're only
as good as what you can show.
Yeah, bro. You ain't even got four
grand. You've never had four grand in
your life. Why are you even talking
about four grand? You ain't got nothing.
That's why you can't come in and show
anything. Shut up. Get a life. Get off YouTube.
And you're banned anyways.
These spastics need to get banned, bro.
[ __ ] hell. Bye-bye.
Same people for years. I'm coming off
this [ __ ] bro.
You know, you don't even need to lose
everything on YouTube to come off this [ __ ]
Yeah. 125. Of course you do. Of course
you got 125k in the bank. Of course you do.
Of course you do. Yeah. You all talk
like you're millionaires on here.
You all talk like you're millionaires,
but in reality you ain't got a pot to
piss him. You ain't got a pot to piss him, bro.
You ain't got a pot to piss him, but you
all talk like you're millionaires. It is
actually quite funny to be fair.
You're all millionaires, but you're sat
on YouTube all day, ain't it? Yeah, bro.
It's believable, isn't it? All millionaires.
Cuz like I said, you go to You're just
all idiots, aren't you? Really? Yeah.
Yeah. I think you're living in La La Land.
I think you're living in [ __ ] La La Land.
Even if I only had 1,500 pound, I've got
more than that. I still way more than
enough than I need as a single person.
Sorry, we can't all be millionaires like
you. Like, I know we You're all millionaires.
Yeah, you're all millionaires, but
you're sat on YouTube every day. Yeah,
it makes sense, isn't it?
Sat on YouTube all day, but you're all millionaires.
I know, man. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
All millionaires. Anyways,
what is this guy up to?
I actually used to be rich. I'd say yeah, man.
I'd say that pretty much is rich to be honest.
You're a single person with seven grand
and you get three grand a month. It
pretty much is rich, isn't it?
It pretty much is if you think about it.
I'd say it's pretty much rich
for [ __ ] well well it depends on your
your outgoings and [ __ ] Yeah, I didn't
really have any outgoings. So, I'd say
you're better than [ __ ] 90% of people
cuz you see nowadays pe most people
don't have anything.
They're not all like Monty, but I mean
like they're struggling monthto month or
they have to be like really really
careful. So, you're you probably better
you probably better than 90% of people
to be honest. 85 90% of people have Um
yeah, bloody doesn't want to come on
YouTube anymore. It's leaving, bro.
I think you people need to get live now.
Let's get on YouTube and get
back where I am, man.
You didn't answer my question about the
sing either, did you?
I mean, if I had all of the money that
you people claim that you've got, I'd be
[ __ ] out there traveling the world
constantly. I'd be out every day. It
just doesn't make any sense. If you had
all that money, why you'd be sat on a
community like this every day?
Your YouTube activity gives you away.
It literally gives you away. Your
YouTube activity literally gives you away.
That's what gives you away. Nothing else, you know. Hey, bro. Oh yeah.
Why? He just me. Listen, this off YouTube. Yeah.
poverty is defined as a single person
getting less than 250 a week. So you're
just above above poverty.
Where did you get that from? Yeah,
I'm coming off YouTube tomorrow, bro. I've decided.
>> Yeah, I'm coming off YouTube, man.
Just get off YouTuber.
See, I'm not even leaving because like
it's ruined my life. But it's just the
same [ __ ] isn't it? It's just the same
And I didn't know having 15 on the And
again, this is what I mean with these
people. They're all [ __ ] idiots on here.
Less than 250 a week. Where the [ __ ] did
you read that up?
You can live off a grand a month and
save some money.
You know, like I said, it's actually
like normal for a normal person, but I'm
just used to a high lifestyle.
That's the difference,
you know? That's that's the difference, bro.
Well, no, I'm not used to anymore
because I've already done it all. But yeah, no
done good for this month, I reckon. Yeah, man.
100 pound is skint
really man. Wow.
Yo millionaires are here. Damn. mad.
See, I like how no one mentioned me on
that LJ channel.
Yeah, man. I like it because they know
that I don't care, bro, what people win.
I've got my own [ __ ] money. You
wouldn't even trigger me in the slightest.
Once you add once you have £1,200 once
you have [ __ ] two grand it's [ __ ]
pretty much more than a [ __ ]
for a [ __ ] you know what I mean
single person. It's good that no one
mentions me man. It's good. Yeah.
at least that triple 8 tells Lord J about began. Yeah, man. Yeah.
Don't want to come see the mall tomorrow.
them cucodamors are like [ __ ] anti-depressants, bro.
They're like anti-depressants.
Past tense like
But yeah, you're not poor, mate. I'm not poor.
You wouldn't have even if you only have
1,500 pound, you're not poor.
You know, even a grand a month is not
poor. A poor is what Paul is what belly is. [ __ ] Yeah.
I actually spent £200 this month to be honest.
No, I actually spent. I didn't save. I one. Yeah. Imagine
if I didn't win that football bet. Then
I would have been
Yeah. Even more down.
They should be here at [ __ ] [ __ ] hell.
I hate this [ __ ] game, man. I need
I need to try and win a [ __ ]
um big football or something, man. Well, Yeah.