[Music]
There we go.
This is my last day on YouTube, by the way.
Yeah, last day on YouTube, man.
No point being on here anymore. Monty's
not on YouTube. He's not coming back.
So, no point me being on here. Oh, [ __ ]
Know what I mean? >> Yeah.
And I brought my point. [Laughter]
I'm only going to go on YouTube now to
watch Chucky. That's it. Yeah. [Laughter]
Try again. No, I'm good, bro.
I don't like Natalie like that. No.
Yeah. And you're on YouTube again. You
can't get off of YouTube.
You can't even get off. You can't even
take one day off of YouTube. Vlad,
do you reckon Monty's watching?
There's no point. Monty Monty's left now, so
no point me being on here.
You know what I mean? Yeah. Spoilers. Absolutely pointless.
But here's the thing. I can take a day
off of YouTube. You can't.
You people, if this app, right, [ __ ]
close down tomorrow, you'd be [ __ ]
What would you people actually do? Like,
let me let me ask you. If YouTube closed
down tomorrow, what would you do? You'd be [ __ ]
No more coming on YouTube projecting.
You'd actually be [ __ ]
Money man told me just get off YouTube.
Yeah, but [ __ ] It's the truth what
I'm saying though.
Yeah, it's true. It's the truth.
Well, you people would be [ __ ]
You'd actually be [ __ ]
Yeah, you'd actually be [ __ ] man. Um,
well, I've took weeks off of YouTube,
but I've took weeks off of YouTube. How
many times have you took weeks off of
YouTube? Never. When was the last time
Okay, let me ask you this question. When
was the last time you took a day off YouTube?
When was the last time you took a day
off of YouTube, beige man?
When was the last time you took a day off YouTube?
Because Monty's not coming back on
anymore. Monty said that I should come off YouTube.
So Monty's told me to come off YouTube.
Monty doesn't want me on here anymore.
and he's not coming on, so there's no point, you know. Yeah, man. So, yeah.
No. Answer me. Answer me, bro. When was
the last time you took a day off YouTube?
Nah, I'm good, bro.
I need to find a way to get money,
matey. I don't give a [ __ ] about [ __ ]
funny. I need to find a way to get rich, Richie.
You know what I mean, bro? [ __ ] funny.
There you go. So you ain't got a life.
But so you come on YouTube every day.
Says a lot about your life, isn't it? If
you're on YouTube every day.
Says a lot about your life, bro. If
you're on YouTube every [ __ ] day. Franklin died.
Why can't you take a day off of YouTube?
That's what makes me think um Cory,
these people are are skin cuz if they
had all these friends and all this
money, they wouldn't be on YouTube every
day. I stick by what I say, you know,
and honestly, the only reason I came
back, I tell you the reason I came back
here is cuz Monty got me back on YouTube
last week. That's the only reason I come
back. He wanted me to go live.
I was never going to come back, but he
got me back onto it,
you know. He actually got me back on it.
I love GTA 6. I'm sorry, GTA 5. It's lush, man.
I love GTA 5 is good.
Yeah, Monty got me back on it to be honest.
I blame Monty.
I love GTA um five, bro. Not 65. Why did
I say 65?
I might get McDonald's again today, man.
Them [ __ ] nuggets were so nice. Them spicy nuggets. Yeah. H. Oh [ __ ]
Virgin boy ain't have been on YouTube.
Has he Cory?
The [ __ ] virgin.
The [ __ ] virgin ain't been on
YouTube. Maybe you finally got laid.
It's good, isn't it? Oh [ __ ]
Maybe finally got [ __ ] laid. Lost
that V plate, lad. Lost that V card.
Maybe he lost that [ __ ] V card, mate. [ __ ] virgin. Yeah.
Drop a virgin. E
[ __ ] need to get laid. That's what he
needs to do. Oh [ __ ] Always, bro. Always.
Everyone owns that virgin. [ __ ] know. Oh, yeah.
All right. PC. I have to leave um
YouTube cuz Monty's told me to come off
of it. And if Monty's coming off of it,
there's no point me being on it.
Yeah. Sorry being on it then. that
you know what I mean?
[ __ ] hell. I'm thinking of getting
that Chucky costume. You know, bro, you
know that Chucky costume? You can get a
Chucky costume where you dress up as
Chucky. It's only 22 pound. I'm thinking
of buying it
and going cold approaching in it cuz you
know like if you go leads and that they
do like stag where people dress up. They
have like a dress up thing. Maybe I'll
do it on Halloween. Maybe. Maybe
Halloween and I'll just dress up as
Chucky. [ __ ] it. in it
cuz there is dressups in it. It's only
£22. So [ __ ]
Well, they'll be [ __ ] won't they?
Like cuz you know Halloween they do
dress up events and even like place like
leads and do like dress ups. So maybe
dress up as Chucky.
Do some cold approaches in Chucky. Yeah,
that'd be funny as [ __ ] is it?
See, the thing is I actually would do
it. That's the thing.
Hi, I'm Chucky and I'm your friend to
the end. Idy ho.
But it will take two weeks to come
though. But £22, it's [ __ ] cheap, isn't it? Sh.
Where's Timmy? Cory, where's Timmy?
Where's Timmy gone?
I'm skint me PC. I'm [ __ ] skint.
I got two grand, bro. I'm [ __ ] skint, lad.
I'm skint me, bro.
I'm skint matey.
I'm actually skinned, bro. I'm fat.
I know. I'm still waiting for you to
give me 2K, but you still ain't gave me it.
Yeah, man. I'm still waiting for that two grand.
You ain't gave me.
I'm still waiting for it, man. It's not
a lot. Give me two grand. And if it's
not a lot, then I have four grand and I
live even more.
Bro, two grand is a lot. And two grand
is a lot to you. It's a lot to anyone.
Don't be so foolish.
It's a lot to me and it's a lot to you
and it's a lot to lose.
Of course it is. You're not a
millionaire. Of course, two grand's a
lot. People in London, they earn what? Four grand?
4.5 grand a month? Bro, of course it's a
lot. Don't be so stupid.
And [ __ ] get you a [ __ ] luxurious holiday.
Oh yeah, Lee. The one that says six
grand is [ __ ] all. Yeah.
Yeah. He lives in Wales.
Yeah. Yeah, man.
>> They're just fantasists. They don't have
money. So, they say amounts or nothing
because they don't have money. You see
where these people never have money,
right? That's what it is.
Cuz how can somebody that lives in a
village in Wales say that six grand's
[ __ ] all when literally six grand could
buy you and and a house where you live?
That doesn't even make sense.
like what you know how long that would
last you in in in [ __ ] Wales. That's
what I'm saying. They're all fantasists.
Real people don't talk like that.
Real people do not talk like that. Oh,
this amounts nothing. That amounts no
people talk like that. Even people with
money unless you're a [ __ ] millionaire.
You know what I'm saying? It's like you
all talk like millionaires.
So where I've never come across such
people only on YouTube,
you know what I mean? Cory,
two grand is a [ __ ] lot. And so is [ __ ] six.
It's nowhere near as like
It's not It is It is a lot of money,
bro. For a single person. Yes, it is.
Yeah, they are.
So is [ __ ] Nons legs. Nons legs is
skint as well. You forgot to add him in
there. He is [ __ ] skinting skin flint.
You forgot to add the third one. Oh [ __ ]
Yeah, you forgot to add the first one. Yeah, man.
How come someone in Wales say six grand
ain't a lot?
That is a madness, bro.
That is a [ __ ] madness. Talk about
fantasy to the next level.
Jesus. This fantasy. They probably never
had six grand in their life.
And I kept saying to him, "Give me six
grand. Give me six grand. Then I'll have
12 grand." And he and he wouldn't give
it. Stop saying it's [ __ ] all if you're
not going to give me it. L.
He doesn't have money. Trying to ruin my
life. He'll never ruin my life. He's
been trying for [ __ ] ages, mate. That
guy's life's already ruined. Have you
seen the state of him? He's a fat ugly
bastard that sits on YouTube and reacts
to me every day. I've already ruined
him. I live in his head rentree. Look at
the state of him. He's already been ruined.
I've already ruined him. He's obsessed
with me every day. You can't I'm in his
head and he's posting about me all the
time. I've already ruined him.
and he doesn't have money.
Most people on here don't have money.
You can tell by the way they talk about
money. This is nothing. That is bum
chains. No real person says that. Even with money,
he doesn't have money. He sits on
YouTube all day stalking me. He doesn't have money.
So, he has this money. He has his wife.
He's got a better life than me. Yeah,
he's sat on YouTube stalking me every
day. Doesn't look right.
Your YouTube activity has given you away again.
again. See, with these people, their
YouTube activity and what they do on
YouTube gives away their real life. Cuz
if they had all of this money and this
wife, they wouldn't be on here.
It's a tough thing to argue with. you
know, their YouTube activity just gives them away.
It it it it's literally tells you what
their life is,
you know? That's it really. Yeah.
But he doesn't have money. Most people
in here don't have money, man. Almost. Yeah, man.
But yeah, that Lee Liberus, he's a fantasist.
Yeah, I remember used to say 6K as [ __ ]
all. Yeah, he lives in a village in
Wales which six grand could literally
buy you a house there. Absolute
fantasists. I I actually think they
think that I actually think they think
that they're millionaires.
I mean, what what do you class as [ __ ]
all and what do you class as a lot?
Like what what in terms of like what
and it also depends on how much you're
getting as well, you know,
but he is he is definitely a fantasist. Cuz
even even even in London that goes fast.
Um sorry that goes far. Sorry. You know
the fantasist, bro. Absolute fantasist.
Even if you had like £1,200 in your
account, that's pretty good. Even if you
even if you have £1,200, you know,
something like that.
Bro, of course it's not to you cuz
you're all millionaires.
Obviously, all of you people on YouTube,
Because if you go out in the real world,
people say is a lot of obviously not to
you people, but that's cuz you're
millionaires. But I mean, millionaires
that spend all your life on YouTube, but
um but in in in terms of real people,
they would never say that.
They would say two300 pound is a lot of
money. I've got sisters. I've got a mom.
I've got friends. I've got friends of
friends. And no one ever talks the way
you people do on YouTube about money.
That's how I know that you're fantasists.
That you're complete and not a
fantasist. The way you talk about money.
You It's It's obvious you you've never
had money if you're talking this way. You know,
you know what I'm saying?
But you don't know how the world works.
>> You don't know how the [ __ ] world
works at all.
Cuz you talk like you're millionaires.
Anyone would if a millionaire said it,
right? Then I'd be like,
"Oh, well, they're millionaires, so I
guess they're used to a certain lifestyle.
No, they [ __ ] don't. No, they [ __ ]
don't. Most people my age, they [ __ ]
they either live with their [ __ ] mom,
they rent a [ __ ] room, or Yeah, some
of them have a mortgage, but I don't
know who you know, mate, but that's not
the way it works in [ __ ] London.
Or they or they they get housing
benefit. There ain't no one in their
20s, bro, in London. There were not many
people that owns their own house.
So, I don't know who the [ __ ] you know,
bro. But yeah.
Why are you skimp? Why Why are you
skimp, bro? Don't you work?
Why are you skimp, man? Don't you work? Oh, [ __ ]
I think the most money I I ever had was
seven, I think. Maybe. Yeah.
So, how much do you get? How much do you
get a month?
I think the most I ever had was about 7K,
but that was all my money. It wasn't like [ __ ]
He wasn't alone or anything, [Music] man.
Well, I don't I don't have kids, so [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah, man. drinking women, traveling about
designer clothes, which I've still got
designer clothes, which I need to get
dry cleaned. That's where my money's gone.
Yeah, I used to spend 7800 pound days. I
used to go out, man.
I've got about two grand in gums that
need dry cleaning. [ __ ] me. I just ain't
got around to doing it.
I just ain't got [ __ ] around to doing it.
Yeah, I used to gamble. Gamble escorts.
No, I'm not still living a life. No, I
wish I was. Well, to be honest, I don't
do too bad considering I don't get freek
a month anymore. I went to Birmingham. I
went on a piss, won a football bet. I
mean, I'm still doing okay. Yes. But
no, I'm not living the life.
I'm still doing okay, you know. No, I'm
not living the life, bro. No,
cuz I don't have a lot of money coming
in anymore. So, I I'm not living the life,
but I've lived it, so I don't give a [ __ ]
Cine more tomorrow. Yay.
Yeah, I banged I used to just go around
banging escorts, going on dates,
gambling, designing clothes.
So yeah, man, it was good.
Let me guess. You gamble your money
away, don't you? >> Yeah. Oh, [ __ ] [Music]
The [ __ ] is this [ __ ] doing?
Yeah, I've had loads of good wins, bro.
I've had loads of loads of good wins.
Yeah, I won that 200 pound football bet last week.
So that's why I just went to Birmingham.
[ __ ] it. It
I've won loads of money. I have
I used to win money every week. I used
to win like a thousand every week easy
when I could get into them casinos. Yeah, man.
Good times, eh? Oh, well.
Yeah, I want like thousands, but I want thousands. Gambling.
But like I said, even if I got that
money now, I wouldn't be doing it all
over again because I've already done it.
I would just go abroad a lot faster.
That's all I'd be doing now. My age, I
wouldn't even be doing it all over
again. I don't enjoy the drinking, going
out, approaching anymore. Like, I don't
really enjoy it anymore anyways. So,
I wouldn't say it happened at the right
time because no one likes [ __ ] losing
two grand above. know what I mean?
How long you going to live the life
forever, bro? You know, but yeah, [ __ ] that.
Yeah, I went into I went to the casino
before with 150. I won four grand,
£4,000 in cash.
It was sick, man.
I had like the most I ever had in cash
was 5.7 I think.
But I went I drunk a lot, gambled a lot,
escort a lot. I was seeing this woman a
lot which was expensive and
I used to go a week and then win more
and then win more and yeah.
So yeah, man.
I got some Stone Island jumpers I need
to get dry cleaned.
They were from Winn's as well. No, man.
And I was getting 3K a month as well.
And I was getting Yeah, 3K a month. I
Jeez. And I wasn't even working as well. Madness.
That's mad. If you think about it, if
you actually look back on it now, it's
mad. But obviously back then, like
you're used to lifestyle, so you don't
see as anything but normal.
That's actually madness, bro. If you think
That is actually [ __ ] crazy.
But no, no, nothing like what I used to have. Matey,
it's hard to get a job now as well. I've
applied for some delivery jobs, but they
still ain't got contact with me. So
they got back in contact with me. So
yeah, I don't think you could ever live
that life again, matey.
You've never had that money. I can show
you the money, matey.
It was here, matey.
I don't even like looking at it, bro.
That's how I beat everyone at the money
game. I showed this money and no one
could show me anything. So, they all ran
away. Every time I got my money out,
they all run away. The little skin flints.
That's why I can't participate now until
they show me 10 grand.
I won the money game.
Still yet to be beaten.
>> Yeah, man.
>> Yeah, I was able to beat me, lad. Yeah. Um,
still waiting to be beaten.
>> Yeah, it was sick, though. It was a good
life. It was a good summer. I think it
was last summer.
Well, I asked them to show me 10 grand,
but they couldn't.
Do you think it's hard? Do you think
it's hard to make money nowadays?
Don't know. I'm trying to get him on
here, but he won't. Come on.
Oh, [ __ ] I used to I used to tease
Virgin Boy about it.
I used to say, "Show me your money." And
he could never do it. Your boy could
It's hard to make money now, bro. I was
only able to
make money cuz I was left the house for
a few years. So, I was able to sublet
the house, which is why I had so money,
so much money. But when stats gone,
you're [ __ ] Which I knew I was going
to be [ __ ] [ __ ] in terms of like um
trying to get extra money and stuff.
I knew then I would be [ __ ] because
there'd be no way
unless you just save on benefits for
like 4 months or something, but there's
there is no way.
They let you apply for these delivery
jobs and they don't even Bro, I've been
on a waiting list for like 3 years.
Yeah, I've been on a waiting list for
literally 3 years, bro.
Three [ __ ] years, lad. I've been on
that waiting list. So
they don't contact you. Yeah, man.
Three [ __ ] years, man.
It's the madness, isn't it?
But I didn't start with that amount. I
saved like 3K.
I'd save money like 3K
and then um
then I just saved and then gambled some
and then one more and yeah
it is what it is.
Yeah, but do they give you accounts?
No, the account that
the account that you want the account
that you want is deliverer.
Doesn't matter how much I've got in the
bank. What about what you've got?
[ __ ] all, bro. Like 2K.
It's good, but I don't have as much
money coming in now, so it ain't that good.
[ __ ] I could get all that money back
if I could get that delivery account. I
could get it back in like a month and a half.
Yeah, I could get it back in a [ __ ]
month and a half
if they gave me an account. Easy, bro. 327. [Music]
[ __ ] that. 327, eh?
You're [ __ ] going to be skint like
virgin boy. You are
you're going to be [ __ ] skint like virgin boy.
You're going to be skinn like [ __ ]
virgin boy if you don't stop. Lo,
do you want to be skinn [ __ ] virgin, d?
Well, you wouldn't do it for a grand a
week. Well, then you're [ __ ] stupid
then, aren't you? Yeah, man.
How come you only got £327?
Watch this. [ __ ] watch him, bro.