Yeah, this is my um as I say, bro, this
is my last day on YouTube. I need to
come off of this [ __ ]
Yeah, man. I was having um a long think about this.
I can't be on this [ __ ] [ __ ] every
day for the rest of my life with these
[ __ ] low lives, bro. Jesus Christ.
That's all right, bro. It is my last
day. Well, listen to this. Has Timmy
took weeks off of YouTube?
No. Days off of YouTube? No. I was just
thinking before I went uh out earlier,
bro. It's just the same [ __ ] you know?
It's the same [ __ ] every [ __ ] day.
Like you don't even need to lose
everything to want to off come off
YouTube. It's just the same [ __ ] every
day. It's just the same atmosphere, the same arguing,
the same self projecting, the same
repeating people all for nothing. It's a
[ __ ] complete waste of [ __ ] time.
It is actually. Yeah, man. It actually
is. I'm actually coming off this [ __ ]
after today, bro.
You know, man, 100% I actually am, bro.
It's the same [ __ ] Greavves. I was like
[ __ ] I couldn't believe it. I went
out yet after I end the lif thinking me
and this Joe guy, we've had the same
conversation and the same argument about
a million times. Oh, show money. No, you
show money. It's just the same old. And
it's like what I said earlier, bro. Like
even if Right. Let me let me use as an
example again. He still didn't show the
[ __ ] 10 grand in his account. The
thing is, bro, yeah, I could have about
£700 in my account and I would still
have a better life than all of these
people. Let's just say I had, for
example, £500 in my account. Yeah. Let's
say I had £500 and they had, for
example, 4 grand,£5 grand and they work.
Bro, I would still have a better life.
Like, not that I have 500 obviously, but
I'm using as example. I would still have
a better life than them cuz bro, like
put two and two together.
But I'm I will come off it. I've been
off of it for weeks. It's boring, bro. I
need to do stuff. I need to get back to
real life as well. But I'm just using
that as an example, you know?
Money don't trigger me, bro. I don't
have autism like these people, you know.
And then you got some other channel
showing money. Like, bro, no one cares
about the same,000 that you've been
showing over and over and over and over
again. Literally, nobody's bothered by
it. It's boring now. Just like the same
self projectors. It's all boring.
Same repeating people, same atmosphere, you know?
You think about it, bro? You know,
I think I had some points with what I
said earlier as well. Gezy,
I think so. Yeah,
that's not the real Monty.
But I'll put a box up anyways. Yeah, but Monty.
Oh, I don't by the way.
Yeah. and then Swindon versus Cambridge
and Fleetwood versus Bristol Rovers.
Just a tip if you wanted one. So, both
teams to score. Yeah, man. Yeah.
So, I have to tell I'll be off here anyways. Yeah, man.
It's not Monty.
No, it's not.
>> Somebody invited me to KFC, but I can't
be bothered to go to be fair. I got
>> that. If it's a pink avatar, it's me.
>> Can you hear me?
>> Yeah, I can hear you. Lisa, why are you
[ __ ] on YouTube [ __ ] talking to a
bunch of [ __ ] uglish bastards who
ain't got a [ __ ] life like self-reflective completely.
>> Hello completely.
>> Can you hear me? >> Hello.
I think my thing's [ __ ] Hold on. Let
me rejoin. Hold up. Hello.
Oh, [ __ ] knows.
No, I won't come back after a few days.
It's boring. It's just the same repeating people.
No, not even, bro. Hello.
>> Yo, can you hear me? Yeah.
>> No, I can't hear, bro. My phone's [ __ ] >> Okay.
>> Right. Let me reset my phone, Monty. One
second. Yeah. Two seconds. Let me
>> Yeah. Go on. Go on. I stay here for you.
>> It's my phone. It's not yours. One
second. Let me reset it. Stay on. Yeah. One sec.
>> Yeah. Go on.
>> I can't hear you, bro.
>> There's a proper [ __ ] self reflection
in this community completely. Not want
to use all my life
yet. Not want to use [ __ ] meet you
yet. Use a little bag if I even leave
you for [ __ ] dollars. Yeah. Hey, I
tell you what. Why don't you go
location? I'm more than welcome to come
to your [ __ ] town.
I don't allow some of you to live where
I am now. I'm literally in someone's
town now. A
but who would meet me? Who would have
meet me in this community? No one. Just
a couple of [ __ ] fat old pensioners
sat at home having no with a pair of
[ __ ] tweezers. That's what used to
do. They self-reflect and pull [ __ ] on
other people's lives and that my life is
perfect. I'm not that place no more.
Like I told you last night, I've got
[ __ ] accommodation now. Literally
all what usually we [ __ ] reflect and
that's it. Do you think I'm asked about
Natalie? Me and Natalie people. I don't
care about Natalie. I've had a test done
today. Yeah. Do you know what? I might
not even tell you if I got anything off
Natalie or not. So when you go out with
Natalie and Natalie and then you won't
know if she's got anything or not.
I've already been tested. I've been
clinic and everything. Don't forget
Natal's green patient and everything. I
don't trust her.
I just sleep with her. At the end of the
day, I don't give a [ __ ] about Natalie
no more. N don't give a [ __ ] about me. I
don't give a [ __ ] about her. At the end
of the day, people
your phone's [ __ ]
>> Can't hear you, man.
>> PJ's phone's [ __ ]
>> Can you rejoin? I can't hear you, man.
What the [ __ ] Why can't I hear him?
One second. Rejoin
cuz I can't even hear him.
>> No, I'm not trolling. I literally can't
hear him, you [ __ ] idiot.
No, one second. Let me let me create a
new live stream. One sec.