There we go. Monty. One day I'm Yeah.
>> Nothing, bro. I'm just saying this is my
last day today, man.
And uh you still didn't show me um
you still didn't show me 10 grand.
Yeah, I just went on Virgin Boys um
thing. I didn't even see that short,
bro. No one cares about the same,000
that you keep showing. Stop embarrassing
yourself. It's boring now, man.
You know, it's boring. They're going to
[ __ ] charge you one day, bro. You
keep taking your [ __ ] housing benefit
out the [ __ ] bank. One day they're
going to take your housing benefit and
it's not there.
But yeah, I saw your thing, but it's not
10 grand. So, I mean, you shouldn't even
be asking me or talking to me about
money until you show this 10 grand.
Yeah. Same boring conversation we're
having. Like, bro, is he ready? Do you
know what? Again, we shouldn't even be
able to we shouldn't even be able we
shouldn't even be a be talking about
this, bro. We honestly shouldn't even be
talking about this, bro. Cuz it's just
like what I just said. I could only have
£500 to my name and I'd still have a
better life than everyone.
Like, bro, I can I I would have a better
life than anyone on here, even if I had
only £500 to my name. So, it's all
relevant really if you think about it.
And also that thing is not accurate. Um
that thing that you put up about um the
poverty that's not accurate because if
that's the case then everyone in London
is living in poverty because by the time
they paid rent they're [ __ ] on like £1,200.
So that's not even accurate.
That I read that as well. That's not
accurate at all. At all at all.
And why does it matter anyways, bro?
Jesus Christ. Like I said, I could have
£500 to my name right now and I'd still
have a better life than all of you.
That's just that's the maddest thing.
That's the saddest thing about it, bro.
You know what I mean? That's how sad it is.
It's not Well, it's not. Well, it's not
because then most of the people in
London are living in poverty then
because they're not left with more than
that every month. So,
well, it [ __ ] isn't cuz it's not
accurate. I read that it's not accurate.
No, the [ __ ] it ain't.
What do you mean they are? So, that
means that most people in London are
living in poverty, right?
That must mean most people in London are
living in poverty. Okay.
Yeah, you're married. Another one's
married. Yeah, I'm still talking to them
Birmingham numbers, by the way.
Yeah, I'm still talking to them.
Let's try and meet one of them soon. I
got things to do. I I I'm coming off
here after today. I've got things to be doing, matey. Yeah. Hey.
Oh, I done a football bet, by the way.
Double both teams to score. 80 pound.
Take a bird to Thailand.
Why would you be taking a bird to
Thailand? You're going to Thailand to be
able to get with a woman, not to take a
woman there. Are you a [ __ ] [ __ ] or something? But
yeah, I am actually giving up for real.
For real. If none of these numbers meet, then
I'm going to give it one last shot.
Maybe in three weeks, four weeks, and
then I am done.
So, I need to start doing [ __ ] now, you
know? I really do, bro. I can't be sat
on YouTube like these losers [ __ ]
repeating every day. I'm getting old,
bro. You know?
Well, people go to Thailand to get a bird.
Anyways, I'm not I'm not I'm not getting
into an argument, bro. I'm not here to
sit here and start arguing.
Yeah, you get a job. Your bum. Yeah.
When you get yourself a job, I'll get a
job. When you get yourself a job.
Yeah. I'm not going to say something
that's going to turn into an argument
cuz I'm not arguing. It's pointless, bro.
It's absolutely pointless, you know. Yeah, man.
No, I'm not wasting my life on this [ __ ]
anymore, bro. [ __ ] that. So, yeah, I got
these three numbers. If none of these
three numbers meet me,
then I'll give it a whirl one more time,
maybe like three weeks, and then that's
it. I'm done. I'm done. Maybe if I win
that football bet, I'll do Thursday,
Saturday, get an escort both of the days
and then that's me done here.
And then I'm out of here, bro.
Simple. I'm out of [ __ ] here.
Yeah, man. I think that's the best
that's the best thing to do. So, you
need a plan, you know? If you ain't got
a plan, what is life, man? And if you
ain't got a plan,
I'll be back before Monday. Nope.
No, not at all.
This 80 football bet returns 230.
What's 230? Yeah.
It's good little football bet I've got on.
No. Hey, YouTube is all you got, mate.
[ __ ] hell. If YouTube closed down
tomorrow, bro, your life would be
[ __ ] You people can't even take a day
off of YouTube.
You people literally can't take one day
off of YouTube. It's literally all you
have. YouTube and projection is all you
have. [ __ ] off. It's literally all you have, mate.
It is literally all you have.
You ain't got nothing. If this app
closed down, your lives would be [ __ ]
Your lives would actually be [ __ ]
What would you do if YouTube shut down?
You'd be [ __ ]
Jesus Christ. Yeah, you're too busy to
stream. You've got a wife and a family.
You're sat on YouTube behind a fake
account. Yeah, man. You keep telling
yourself that, bro. These people would
be [ __ ] without YouTube. Cory, YouTube
is literally all they have. Like, it's
literally all they have. They have
nothing but YouTube.
My friend invited me out today, but I
can't be bothered.
Maybe I might go KFC. Actually, I don't know.
No, I can't be bothered. That means
traveling there and can't be bothered,
bro. I told him another day. Yeah.
>> Well, hopefully it's football. Oh, [ __ ]
I don't have a stitch cap. You [ __ ]
So, I don't know what Monty's going to
do, but I'm going to be off this [ __ ] No. Timmy, I can't Timmy.
See, I can't hear anything. I don't know
why I can't hear anything.
Oh, you trying to porn bomb. Nice try.
No, I can't hear anything. Can you hear
anything? I can't hear them.
Yeah, that [ __ ] was wearing my [ __ ]
Mickey Mouse cap. Yeah, man.
So, anyways, what you spast going to do?
You going to be on YouTube every day
when I'm gone or what? Are you actually
going to get a life? Joe Reevesy,
what you going to do? You going to stay
on YouTube or you going to get a life?
I was speaking to one of the ex-tenants
um Joe from years ago.
From years ago, man.
Yeah. We was talking [ __ ] Oh, you
should come to Spain. Like, nah,
I just live here anymore. I was like,
nah, [ __ ] that.
Nah, I don't think it's entertainment. I
think it's [ __ ] [ __ ]
Loads of people have left, you know.
Loads of people have left.
Uh, what have I got to lose? Um, money, time.
You've never had a woman. You're still a virgin.
You've never I've had more women on than
anybody on this community.
Bad luck. I've had more women than you.
You're still a virgin. But I've got to
lose time. I've got to lose money.
Getting my time wasted. I mean, yeah,
I've got stuff to lose. Could go there
and get nothing.
I've had more women than anyone in this
community. You [ __ ] virgin. Again,
you're getting yourself confused with me.
Evidence don't lie.
Um, I've got Yes, I've got plenty of
time and I've got and I've got enough
money, but I don't want to go there.
Why am I [ __ ] going to Spain?
Nah, bro. It must affect you. I think it
affects you more being a virgin.
I think that it um
that it affects you more being a skinned
virgin on YouTube every day. I mean,
that's got to be been affecting you,
bro. You've never had a girlfriend or
you've never had sex. That's even worse.
Pretend coming on YouTube pretending
that you've got a wife.
Imagine that. coming on YouTube
pretending that you got a wife when
you've literally never been with a
woman. Bless you, you silly [ __ ]
I'm sure if you had a wife and kids, you
wouldn't be sat on YouTube hiding behind
a [ __ ] fake account of Monty, you know?
And this is exactly why I'm coming off
this community. Coming off YouTube,
you know what I mean? It's [ __ ] embarrassing really.
Yeah, man. But you've never had a woman.
You're still a virgin. So, you're even worse.
You've never been seen with a bird. You
have to come on YouTube and pretend that
you got a wife. Unless you're none of
you people in relationships, you're all [ __ ] single.
You know, you're all single, fat, and
ugly. Ain't got a life. Can't get off of YouTube.
sat on YouTube with your skin ugly
selves year in year out. I mean, the
evidence is there. I mean, the [ __ ]
The evidence is there. You people can't
get off of YouTube. It says a lot about
your lives. [ __ ] sat on low days
repeating yourselves every [ __ ] day
cuz you've got nothing. I mean,
yeah. You've seen Yeah, that's Yeah,
that's nice, bro. Let's see your face.
I know, man. Let's see your face.
Let's see your face. And it's not the
fact that No, no. Do you know what it is
yet? It's not the fact that they come on
YouTube and they watch stuff for entertainment.
Uh it's what they do on YouTube. It It's
what they do on YouTube. Sat on there
all day, every day, repeating
themselves. Sat on YouTube all day. It
must mean their skin. It It literally It actually Yeah.
It tells you, it paints a picture of
their life. Skin ugly, no friends, all
lonely on YouTube, repeating themselves.
It literally is, bro. Like, it's not
like they just come on YouTube to watch
and take the piss for an hour or two
hours a day. No, no, no, no, no. These
people sit on YouTube all day every day
because they've got nothing.
[ __ ] all. They can't take one day off of
it. Cuz what would they have without
this YouTuber? They'd be [ __ ]
You'd be [ __ ] without YouTube.
YouTube. YouTube. YouTube. You'd be [ __ ]
It's what they do on it, you know. [ __ ] man.
You know what? Yeah. As much like Yeah.
Anyways, bye-bye [ __ ]
This is exactly why I'm coming off this [ __ ] Byebye.
So yeah, there's a difference like
between coming on here like for an hour,
two hours because it's entertainment and
then obviously doing what these people do, you know?
all day, every day on YouTube. It's mad.
It paints a picture of their life, doesn't it?
about Birmingham is at least I got
numbers that replied and they are still replying.
So I can't like knock it that I can't
knock it that much.
That's the only good thing about like
when I went there to be honest like I
was saying. So it's not that bad. At
least you actually got some messages back. Yeah, man.
And no, I'm never going to Spain. Why
the [ __ ] would I go to [ __ ] Spain? [ __ ] that.
She's saying how she wants to get
married soon and that because she's
getting a bit old. She's like 32.
But yeah, I said you got about five year
and she wants kids and that. So I said
you basically got you've got like 6
years maximum left
cuz the women are not supposed to have
kids past like
38 really then it becomes risky you know
even though my m my mum had me at 37
and look how I come out crazy monster
so you know if it's two years more
yeah 38 you shouldn't really. So I said,
"Well, you got 5 years to find someone." Basically,
yeah, I saw it, bro. And I don't care.
Money doesn't trigger me. Do you know
why? Because the thing is, bro, I've
shown more money than anybody on this
community. And like I said before you
joined. Yeah. I could have £500 to my
name. Yeah. Let's just say I had 500
pound to my name
and I'd still have a better life than
all of these people.
So, what's money to them?
Think about it, bro. I could literally
have £500, just £500 in my name, and I'd
still have a better life than all of these people.
So therefore, money doesn't um
mean anything to them. Um I done a
football bet. I done an 80 football bet.
Slim. Two teams with returns 230. So
yeah, I got a football bet, man. People
can show [ __ ] 10% of what I've shown.
Yeah, that's all they talk about is money.
It's madness. All they do is bring up
money and talk about money. But the
thing is is that all of the money
they've shown is less than what I've
shown. AJ talking to I
>> still can't hear Monty. Why can't I hear Monty?
Must be your speaker.
>> Something's wrong with my [ __ ] phone,
bro. Let me try and put my earphones in
or something. I've got all these
collectors in here. Complete self.
>> Can you hear PJ?
>> These people. Can you hear me? Yeah.
>> I can't even hear him.
>> You people need to get alive. Nobody PJ
can hear me or not. You people need to
get alive. You sad pathetic weasels.
>> Can you hear Can you hear me? Yeah.
>> Yeah, I can hear I can hear him.
>> I can hear you now. I can hear you now.
I can hear I can hear you now. I'm
sorry, man. I couldn't hear you.
>> No, you're good. [ __ ] you. Why you Why
you entertaining people who sat on
YouTube every [ __ ] day? You ain't got
no mates. You ain't got a life. Who's
got self-reflect on other people's lives?
>> Yeah. And all they do is bring up money,
bro. Like, it's
>> Yeah. Just don't answer them. Just don't
answer them. Like literally those
[ __ ] weirdos just on YouTube who
aren't actually go [ __ ] live PJ they
self other people's they self-reflection
other people's lives PG mate they talk
about money because they haven't got
>> yeah it's the truth it's the truth it is true
>> that's it they're just idiots [ __ ]
Mongols the bigger Mongols and what I am
I am I'm just I'm not just saying that
I've got disabilities but these have got
complete wussing disabilities these
people can't even Leave the front door
without a walking stick or a [ __ ]
simmer frame for [ __ ] sake.
>> It's the truth.
>> Never money. Why never money? Why is Why
is Timu coming back on YouTube? It
always happens, isn't it?
>> Just they all are relevant PJ to me.
These they all are [ __ ] relevant to
me. If these can meet me.
>> Yeah, they can meet me now. I'm ass. I
mean, I live where some of these live
now. Do you know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> They [ __ ] idiots. She sat on YouTube
thinking that they got mates on YouTube.
Wow. People who they don't know in life.
That's [ __ ] pathetic.
>> Talking [ __ ] to people.
>> Why you trying Why you trying to boom bomb? >> Huh?
>> It's a [ __ ] They just [ __ ] without
no [ __ ] P.
>> 100% bro. 100% they are.
>> That's it.
>> Go on. Timmy's trying to bone bomb.
>> Get alive. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
little rat lad.
>> Is he showing money? Is he
okay? Not Timmy.
>> He's trying to He's trying to puck.
>> PJ the way you get rid of these little
clowns. Yeah. Don't talk about Don't
talk about money to win. >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] idiots, man.
>> You know what I mean?
>> You being off YouTube.
I'm done with him. >> Sorry. >> Yeah.
>> Why is that so obsessed, lad?
>> They all are. He's not just sluggish.
>> It's not just him. It's
>> Monty. We was in Birmingham. We called
Timmy out and he didn't come out.
>> What did you see earlier when I showed
you? He's back on YouTube.
>> Yeah. Anyways, me and Natalie all this
split up here is because I went on
[ __ ] back on YouTube. Told everybody
was in a hotel. That's it. Natalie
thinks I went out and got off with some
next bird. PJ, did I get off with any
girls in town at all?
>> Not at all.
>> Okay. Now, maybe you've been talking to
women on Meet Me. [ __ ] Hey. Hey, I
tell you what, lot people. I'm getting
to know someone on Meet Me before I jump
into the next relationship.
Yeah, why did Timmy all of a sudden come
back on YouTube? It's weird, isn't it?
>> Because I'm not in Birmingham no more
cuz I've gone out of Birmingham. So I
think so he's gone out of Birmingham. I
can go back to Birmingham if I want to.
Nat, you knew it was Timmy straight away. It
>> PJ I can get me and you a place in in
Birmingham easy without these even not
even knowing. Easy. Yeah, this pisses.
These are just little clowns. Yeah, you
probably still live with [ __ ] mummy
virgin jeans and the rest of it, man.
The [ __ ] virgin jeans.
>> What slug is it? >> What?
>> What is the slug lad?
>> He's ran off. He's ran off. >> Yeah.
>> I can't believe he met Slug Lad.
>> Yeah, I met I met Yeah, I met Timmy.
>> he's slapping his head in that.
>> Yeah, man. He's a [ __ ]
>> Was he clapping?
>> Why did you do Daz? Do you do a football
bit every week?
>> I don't I don't gamble, lad.
>> Why, man? I come out with more money and
he's doing his money. I come out with
like [ __ ] almost two.
>> Waste of money.
>> I don't I always thought you did. I
don't know why, bro. Cuz you're in the
gambling community, ain't it?
>> Yeah, man. M it.
>> Yeah. When did you when did you last do it then?
>> Um about a year ago.
>> Yeah. [ __ ] Is it
>> losing so much money lad?
>> Mad. Yeah.
>> Wild women. So [ __ ] pricks, man. I've
been tested. Me peace. I've been tested for anything.
>> She messaged you back, Natalie.
>> No. No. I'm not asked anymore. I'm not
waiting for it anymore. I'm 5 days is
long enough. 4 days is actually long
enough for someone to text you back or
to tell you what they want or whatever
else. You know what I mean? That's why I
thought to town with you cuz
>> that was a good slug, isn't it?
>> Shout him out. Shout him out again.
>> He's a bacon lad.
>> He is. What do you think of the whole
Daz? What do you think of the whole
Nataly and Monty thing? It's [ __ ] up, isn't it?
I didn't really see it.
>> I didn't really do know me or what I
done. Yeah, this is what happened. I
tell you now. Yeah, it's not my [ __ ]
fault. The the girl the women this
fault, but it's not my fault. The
YouTube bit is my fault. Yeah, but
Natalie keeps kicking me out of [ __ ]
hotel sites. She can't handle conflict.
When I wake her up, she's shouting at
me, going off her [ __ ] head. When I
wake up by accident, not meaning to
kick me out the [ __ ] hotel and now I'm angry.
>> Stay away from that Monty. She's bad news.
>> No, no, no. I am staying away from her.
I [ __ ] am. She is bad news. She [ __ ] is.
>> You know, I've been there for her. I
have been there for her just like she's
been there for me in ways. Yeah. Like
literally, I thought me and Natalie had
really something going on.
>> I thought we did. I thought me and
Natalie was made for each other. later.
If we work, then we won't be doing this
with each other now, will we? >> No.
>> Timmy, stop trying to porn bomb. >> Yeah.
>> Shut the [ __ ] up. You're not
Jimmy. You're a special I called you and
Prime out. I called you both out in
Birmingham and you didn't come out. You
[ __ ] idiot about [ __ ] Prime. I
called you. See what I mean, Monty?
>> Yeah, they're [ __ ] idiots.
>> Money. I called them both out.
>> Yeah. Do you know why? Do you know why
Prime didn't come out or Timmy didn't
come out? Cuz she was with Because she
was with me. That's why they didn't come out. >> Yeah,
>> cuz she was with me.
>> Timmy. Yeah, but Timmy always likes to
turn up with people, don't he? So,
>> yeah, they can't. Anyone can turn up
with anyone with me. Anyone at the end
of the day, these are just people who
would say you get a job and they haven't
even got a job their fuckingelves. You
know what I mean? You [ __ ] really
[ __ ] It's just the same [ __ ] It's the
>> It is. It is. I'm sure our police have
got brain damage or something.
>> Yeah, they do. They do. They do 100%.
They're like robots, Monty. Monty,
they're like robots.
>> And only why I'm doing this to Natalie.
Yeah. Only why I'm only why I'm doing
this to Natalie. Yeah. Cuz I've had
enough of women. I've had enough of
getting abused and [ __ ] Natalie has
abused me. But she keeps kicking me out
of hotels and that. And my mom likes
Natalie. My mom adors Natalie.
You know what I mean? That's the first
ever woman my mom's ever liked. >> Yeah.
>> I would have given Natalie another
chance. I would. I would
>> but I'm not if I do go back out I'm not
playing these [ __ ] kick about games
if we if we get we talk not shout at
each other not not blame each other it's
not me who's put her life up it's all
these little [ __ ] on YouTube who's done
that to Natalie not me I will always
stand by Natalie
>> I have been clinic obviously of course
they have every woman I sleep with they
always get tested out either way
>> you know either He even got chased out
after when I said with Kaye. Obviously Kay's clean,
you know. See, I'm I'm truthful. I could
have called Kay are you are you
expecting to um get something off Natalie?
>> No, I'm not expecting to get anything off Natalie.
>> I'm not expecting nothing. But only why
I'm being nasty now to Natalie is
because I'm keeping the key, mate. I'm
keeping the key.
You got to keep them nasty to keep on
key. Do you know what I mean? No, I'm
messing. I'm just done with getting
treated like a prick and getting kicked
out of hotels and getting kicked out of
houses. Natalie should understand. I'm
not bringing talking about it like did
years ago. Natalie should understand
what Kay done to me.
>> Put me out on the streets, make me
homeless. Kept on kicking my dog out the
house. Kept on kicking me out the house.
What am I supposed to do when I'm a one
who's always getting kicked out of
properties? Do you know what I mean? Am
I supposed to go out skipping with a
smile on my face?
I was angry. I went live and I said I
was in the hotel. I said, "What was that Manchester?"
>> I'm ask if she meets Lord. She just
ain't got no taste or standards there
then, is it?
>> Yeah. Who cares anyways? That's not
going to bother you, is it?
>> You know, it's not bothering me anyways.
I can just PJ I can go out now and just
go and meet somebody now. But I'm not.
I've been talking to her. I'm waiting
for Natalie to text me or ring me
[ __ ] or whatever
>> to actually talking sort this out. If
not, I'm I'm moving on. I am moving on. >> Yeah.
>> Cuz I'm not waiting for that decision or
even if she likes me or not, I don't
give a [ __ ] peeps. Either way, you can
leave his little [ __ ] comments like that. >> Yeah.
>> You know, but at the end of the day,
I've done nothing to that girl. Nothing
bad anyways. I've not cheated on her.
I've not battered her. I've not done any
of that [ __ ] All I done is went live on
[ __ ] YouTube. That's about it. >> Yeah.
To [ __ ] finish it. >> Yeah.
>> It is. It is. If you can't sort out a
[ __ ] If you can't sort out
situations, what's the point being in a
relationship if you can't sort out the situation? >> Yeah.
You know when I went out there people,
do you want the the truth about me and
PJ when we went clubbing? Yeah, I tell
you the truth. Yeah. When me and PJ went
clubbing him, me and PJ pulled them two
girls. Pulled them. We didn't even pull
them. We just were walking with them and
out going out for drinks with them both.
PJ is the one who had the wank off one
of them. I [ __ ] didn't,
you know. I [ __ ] I left.
You know what I mean? >> Timmy,
>> why didn't you come out, you little [ __ ]
>> My heart is whispering.
>> You put up your sad lives on YouTube,
but didn't you lose your
>> Timmy simmyimmy?
Listen to me now. You [ __ ]
run off, Timmy. Run off. Just run off,
Timmy. Just run off.
>> You got about 12immy
loser on the planet, mate. And you're
not allowed. Come on.
irresist now, Timmy. I'll come back to
Birmingham now if you want me to. I've
been off in a [ __ ] room, a different
room in that place, you [ __ ] I've
been ringing all [ __ ] SH
accommodation buildings, you dick.
>> Why do they do this? Yeah. You go to
their city, they don't meet you and then
they [ __ ] they and as soon as you
leave, they start again, you know.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Because they're idiots, man.
I mean, anyone in this community, any
any of these [ __ ] in this community,
I'm not asked about these little clowns
in this community.
getting because I left Birmingham. I'm
not being funny, PJ, but I've been
ringing up. I've got one in Mansfield.
I'm here now
in Mansfield. Like I said to Le I'm
leaving that place. Do you think I want
to be in that [ __ ] scy [ __ ] all
this place? No.
>> I'm I'm in accommodation room now. >> Yeah.
>> In Mfield, I'm doing this for my I'm
doing this for my children. My children
come first now before any [ __ ] else
>> anyone else. I'm if I get in another
relationship and they don't live around
in my local area and they ask me to move
there. I'm not moving. I'm staying here.
>> I'm staying in Mansfield and that's it.
I'm done with women treating me like a
per and I put them first. >> Yeah.
>> Sure you should be. You know they're all [ __ ]
>> I'm changing myself around. I'm being
me. I'm I'm looking for myself. I'm
changing. I don't want
>> Mama Grezy. Where is my mama Grezy?
>> No, I don't want to stay on YouTube.
>> I am staying off. I am There's nothing
here for me. PJ, why do I want to
entertain people who's stalking and
harassing my life?
>> Like, make sure that I don't I don't
These people don't even know me.
>> Don't even know me. And they think And
they think that they're controlling my
life. They're not controlling my life.
They on YouTube like all [ __ ] sad
acts. That's it. They're sad people.
Very sad people.
>> I'm not just saying that. They really
[ __ ] are. They haven't got no [ __ ]
life. So they sat on YouTube going after
people's [ __ ] when they could actually
be making actual content videos. They
haven't got no content in them. TJ lally
what they got is calling people [ __ ]
skin virgin. Three [ __ ] words.
>> Yeah. And it means that's sick.
>> What's so special about these people?
>> When does he get the age test result
back? Ask him when you get the age
result the test back.
>> Oh, probably next week or something now.
I'm not too sure.
>> The needle was a [ __ ] in it.
>> The needle? >> Yeah,
>> I got it all on it. I've had it all on
>> Not nice, is it? I don't like it. Me?
I've had the clap test done on claps h well claps
and yeah I've had the HIV test on
>> what would these people do? What would
these people do if YouTube closed down?
They'd be [ __ ]
>> Yeah, of course he would. Of course he'd
be [ __ ] If social media's closed
down, they'd be f social media. That's
their life. They've only got social
media to entertain theirelves. Yeah.
>> And that's it.
>> They can't sit. They can't sit there and
entertain a woman like I can or you can
or whatever. They got to sit there and entertain
people who they don't know. >> Yeah.
>> And that's it. There's not it's not
bothering me one bit what these people
say about me or what they do about Well,
they're not controlling my life. My life
is my life.
>> You know what I mean? And only one
person can control that and that's
myself. I was a [ __ ] for going on social media,
>> putting my [ __ ] up on social media. I
shouldn't have done that.
>> YouTube hasn't ruined my life.
>> It hasn't ruined my life. It really hasn't.
It really hasn't ruined nothing of my
life. I'm still me. Hey, I tell you who
ruins my life. Women. >> Women.
>> Not you. You can do what the [ __ ] you
want to do to me. You don't bother me
one little bit. You [ __ ] You're all idiots. >> Yeah.
>> If you actually had a [ __ ] live and
common sense, you won't be sat on
YouTube talking about other people you
don't [ __ ] know and putting remarks
on other people. [ __ ] hell. That's it.
>> He's still singing over that bird.
>> No, I'm not singing over that no bird.
I'm done with Ali. I'm done chasing
that. I'm done.
I'm talking to another bird now. She
wants to get to know me. A woman who
does want to get to know me.
>> Do you know what I mean? So, I'm not
pushing this woman away.
She really likes me as well. She really
does like me.
>> It's good enough. She talks she texts me
every day and talks to me every night on her phone.
>> Well, bless her.
>> That's cute if she likes you. >> What?
>> That's cute then if she like I said that
that's cute if she likes you, isn't it? >> Yeah.
Just don't put Just don't put that Just
don't put that new woman on um YouTube in it.
I'm not putting no one on YouTube
cuz then you'll be [ __ ] up in it.
And you'll be [ __ ] up, won't you?
Who the [ __ ] texting me?
Do I know you?
>> Who's that?
I don't know.
It's not old Bill, is it?
>> No. Is it? [ __ ] It's not all about
that. About that, about that. The police
because um all that [ __ ] happened in
Plymouth with me and Kelly.
>> The police in Birmingham are passing it
on to Plymouth Police Station. >> Mhm.
>> Oh, everything what Kelly's done to him. >> Yeah.
So the place I get in that now. >> Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
These people are idiots, man.
>> Yeah. Yeah, they are. I see. I've been
offered another 100, please. >> Cool.
The end of the day, these ain't got no
life yet. I've been to another place in
Birmingham, a shared propation shelter place.
>> No, I'm in one now in Mfield.
>> I'm not going back to Birmingham, is it?
>> There's nothing there for me. But I will
score that. Do you know what I mean? [Music]
>> Actually, no, I'm not actually. I'm
getting with a 30y old. Are you one
about the woman with that woman? You
thick [ __ ] I know way about definitely
not a definitely not a I'm a friend and
that's it. But >> yeah,
>> he's saying I'm getting with a 60y old.
I'm talking to a 60y old
>> these people say they come on YouTube
because it's entertaining. How is it entertaining?
It's it's entertaining for them because
they ain't got a life. >> Yeah.
>> That's why that's why it's entertaining
for them because this is only what they
can do. Sit on YouTube talk about [ __ ]
they don't know
>> and that's it.
>> It's their life. It is their life.
>> They ain't got a live.
>> If they gives me a chance, a second
chance, I won't be back on it ever
again. And I [ __ ] smashed both my
phones up completely. >> Yeah. >> Anyways.
Anyways, PG, I'm off. Yeah.
>> Yeah, I'm going as well.
>> Get off it. Stay off it. Let these
[ __ ] self-reflect. Let them have no
one to speak to. >> Yeah.
>> No one to talk to and that's all what
you have to do.
>> And then they get
though. Yeah. I'll talk to you later.
>> Yeah. See you in a bit. All right. See you, Mom.