Yeah. Whatever.
Yeah, man. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, bro. [ __ ] it up.
That's madness, bro.
To think it couldn't get [ __ ] any
worse on here. Jesus Christ.
Got [ __ ] virgin boy showing his
[ __ ] housing benefit off.
[ __ ] people almost [ __ ] ended up [ __ ] sectioned. Jesus madness. Oh man. No.
Can't believe that Kay man. Jesus. [ __ ] hell. Crazy. Yep.
Yeah, I was just telling Monty he needs
to go on his [ __ ] door. I was I was
just telling Monty on Facebook like,
"Fucking hell, you need to [ __ ]
go on his [ __ ] door."
He's [ __ ] That's bad. That is, bro.
That is actually bad. I was actually
watching it. It's [ __ ] bad, bro.
Really bad that is. I can understand
like people getting with other people.
People can do that. But imagine someone
getting with like someone that you don't
and it's your baby mom as well. That's
[ __ ] crazy, bro. And I'm not saying
I'm not I'm not I never normally get
involved with this [ __ ] And I'm not
saying anything that I wouldn't do. Like
you saw the whole Mark [ __ ] Samson
thing with Izzy, didn't you? Didn't you?
The whole Mark Samson thing with Izzy. I
[ __ ] went there [ __ ] two times,
bro. Jesus Christ. It's y
>> I don't care. Yeah, I don't give two shits. Literally.
>> It's bad, is it? It's bad, is it? [ __ ]
>> just get over it. No one's going to go
kay after this anyways.
>> Come on, think about it. Who's going to
go Kay after shagging [ __ ] Sid or
going Sid? You know what I mean?
No one. Why? What? To be honest, no. I
don't care what they're doing. You know,
they don't give a [ __ ]
>> How many just done that to annoy you? Is
it tried to annoy you?
>> It's not It's not going to work. It's
really not going to work.
>> You know, but I'm saying she's tried to
You do realize that, is it?
>> Yeah, but it's still not going to work. >> Yeah.
>> That's just pushing me completely away from it.
>> Completely. That's not going to get me back.
>> Shagging a [ __ ] monster ring guy.
>> [ __ ] Py, whoever it's called, the one
with one eye.
[ __ ] hell. It's [ __ ] up, bro. Just YouTube, man.
>> Why was in there as well? >> What?
>> And why was Vi in the Hangouts as well? [ __ ] knows.
Yeah, I'm in Mansfield. Me, I assure
you. I'm near my I'm outside my old
front door where I used to live.
>> Look, people don't believe me. You think
I'm in workshop, do you? Think I'm in workshop?
Think I'm in workshop, peeps?
>> I've seen it. I've seen it.
>> This is my old street, peeps. Old [ __ ] street.
>> [ __ ] hell. Show me.
>> I'm back on my old street.
>> No, he's not lying, Stella. He's not lying. >> What?
Someone said that um
Ky's with Rice and someone said they're
lying. He's not lying.
>> No, Kay's with Rice. I'm seen recently.
Believe me, I can do 10 times better than Kay. >> Believe
>> 10 times better. Kayle
[ __ ] Lord, shut the [ __ ] up.
>> That's just desperate as she does PJ.
That's just OTT desperate. >> Yeah,
>> wouldn't that come rice and clearly
perfect couple suited suited to a team?
>> I'm not asked. I'm not bothered.
>> All the way to Scotland for him. That's mad, bro.
>> Yeah, she's a freak. She's a [ __ ]
She is a freak, mate. A [ __ ] freak. I
never see I won't I won't go out with
Kelly anymore. I won't go near K
anymore. I've been there, done that,
been there, done that. There's only one
person who I do love and that's Natalie. >> Yeah.
>> But now now they just fought me off. You
know what I mean? She fought me off for
being a prick.
There's me old bedroom at my mom's old
house. Yeah. You know what I mean? So
Natalie bought me off for being a prick.
I admit it. I was a prick. But I wasn't
a prick to Natalie. Me and Natalie was
prick to each other. Natalie kic me out
of the hotel. I told everyone when I was
in the hotel. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? But Natalie,
she's such a good man away. A very
[ __ ] good man. I would have done
anything or watch anywhere for her and
done anything for her. Anything. I found
out. Yeah, a lot of people in this
community are nerds.
>> They are nerds. They are They are the [ __ ] idiots.
And I don't give a [ __ ] about these
mongos. Let's see if these people
recognize this street PJ now in a
second. And the house
>> same to me Eldidge. Yeah.
>> And the PJ.
>> No, Monty's Monty's not at rock bottom. Not really.
>> Have I thought about rock bottom people?
I thought Have you not seen my video?
What? What? I just p I'm happy I'm happy
I've been I've got sunshine in my hair I
am I'm [ __ ] happy
I am peeps
tell me if you know where I am people
tell me if you recognize this house in a
minute Pia in this corner we go Yeah,
le in a minute. Le will recognize it in a second. Cross over
that house there. PJ No, it house. shops here.
>> Don't remember it. Old house. Do you not remember it?
>> [ __ ] street, mate. I'm [ __ ] home,
baby. I'm [ __ ] home.
>> Bless you.
>> Please bless my little talking.
>> These people must [ __ ] on here, bro.
>> Yeah, they are. There's only one woman
who I [ __ ] love, and that's Natalie.
I will always love Natalie. Obviously
now they don't want me back. That's
fine. I can't force anyone to go out
with me. But I shouldn't have said that
[ __ ] up on YouTube about her either.
But it's me being a prick in it.
>> Yeah. Monty knows. Everyone knows that
Kay's with Rice.
>> Yes, I know. I don't give a [ __ ] I She gets raped.
It just shows how bad the her standards are.
>> And she's just done it to annoy you as well.
>> It's not going to annoy me.
>> Well, she's trying to annoy you. That's
what I mean.
>> Oh, this is [ __ ] up. Look.
A [ __ ] One sec.
It's getting too much all this on YouTube, man.
I don't care. I love it.
>> Single life [ __ ] banging.
>> But Monty is bad though, is it? All of
this YouTube [ __ ]
>> Told you I'm not ask people.
I can get whatever bird I want. I can go
out with anyone if I want. But I'm not
doing it. Well, I can't go out with
anyone if I want because I still get turned down.
Natalie's texting Lord J. Yeah. So what?
>> Yeah. Good. Lately, listen, I don't
care. I'm texting another bird. I'm
talking to a woman. I'm talking to
someone. So what? I am as well. So what
does that stand as a better
madness? But it is actually a madness.
>> It is. I I don't know why you people
think I give a [ __ ] about waiting right
now is not going to have you back now
don't want you back to if she wants me
back or not.
Do you know if she does she does you
have been taking some heavy losses lately.
>> Definitely not.
No, definitely not because I'm talking
to a woman.
>> I don't know why keep coming back. Why? Why, PG?
>> Why? Why? What?
>> Why is Why does Why Why does he keep coming back?
>> I don't know, man. Cuz it's [ __ ] isn't it?
>> Yes. Well, PJ, if they don't believe
that I'm talking to a [ __ ] female. Yeah.
If they think I'm not talking to a girl,
PJ. Yeah. M I believe you.
>> No, these don't. These think I'm asked.
These think I'm not getting nowhere.
>> Yeah. I'm still talking to them ones in Birmingham.
>> Are you?
>> Yeah, man. I'm going to meet one soon.
>> What? One of them who we were talking
No, you didn't even get their number, did you?
>> No, the others though. Okay.
>> I got three numbers. I got three other
people numbers. I'm talking to them in it.
>> So, I'm going to meet one of them.
>> Yeah, I'm not. In fact, I'm not showing
it actually just in case. In fact, I
will actually. Yeah. Look, P. He's not
talking to a woman. He ain't talking to
He isn't talking to a woman.
He's not talking to a bird.
Who's not? Can you see that PJ?
>> Yeah, I can see it. Yeah.
>> Yeah. See, peeps, I'm talking to a woman ask.
>> It's only you people whose assel
people [ __ ] peeps.
>> Yeah, for real.
>> It's bad.
>> What is it? Oh, look at Kay. Look at
Kay's going to get a proper chag.
Congratulations, Kay. She get a minga.
I'm definitely 100% not going back to
you. That's just a put off.
Complete put off. And it's the same with
Nav. Yeah, that's a complete of a put off. [ __ ] man.
That's a complete put off for that.
PJ should get with Natalie G. Nah. No thanks.
>> I don't want no other woman. Me but Natalie G.
But Natalie G. I'm being a prick. Claw.
Being a prick. I'm not hurting no more
people. I'm fine now. I'm I'm not
hurting. I'm not I'm not going out with anybody.
>> The thing is is I'm keeping my options open.
That's the thing. I'm keeping my options open.
>> Why is stepdad ins?
>> Hang on a minute. Rice will never be
step dad to my kids. You little freaks.
Get my kids little pedos.
>> This is what I'm saying. Monty, bro, on Facebook.
>> [ __ ] weirdos. R will never be a
stepdad to my kids. R will never ever
ever ever ever see my kids. Never.
I don't even care that you should go.
You should go in his door and batter
him, bro. Just just like
>> I know you don't care. Listen, I know
you don't care. It's not about caring,
but like who the [ __ ] does he think he
is and that
>> I don't care. I don't give a [ __ ] man.
[ __ ] hell. What the [ __ ] I'm not
going out with that ugly [ __ ] anymore.
He's ugly as [ __ ]
>> Who's this? That's Natalie G, is it? Is
this Natalie G?
>> That's Natalie G, is it?
I'm not too sure.
At the end of the day, man, I'm not the
end of the day, man. This [ __ ] is getting [ __ ]
>> All right, Natalie. What are you doing,
man? Get um
>> What are you doing? Hold on.
>> I don't care anymore about women at all.
I don't care.
>> Talk to talk to me and Monty.
No, I don't want to talk to her. I don't
want to talk to her. I [ __ ] hell,
man. I've had She had plenty of chances
to talk to me. She's [ __ ] left me
hanging. Left me hanging. Made me
depressed. Feel suicidal and everything like that.
Just left me. I would never do that for anyone.
>> Let's sort this out with Let's sort all
of this [ __ ] out once and for all. Yeah.
>> The end of the day, go back out with
Natalie. I give I have a second. gives
me a second. But what's the point?
You know, I I I apologize to her for
everything I did. Obviously, I've been
treating her like a [ __ ] on YouTube.
Shouldn't have been doing that,
you know. Shouldn't be doing that at all
to her. At the end of the day, when a
woman [ __ ] what the [ __ ] are you
supposed to do? Sit there in pain or
take it back out at him?
>> Take it back out.
>> Don't mean to do it to her, but at the
end of the day, I'm hurt. I'm [ __ ] >> Yeah,
>> I've just done a [ __ ] 5 mile walk
just to clean my [ __ ] head.
>> Oh, bless you.
>> You know what I mean? At the end of the
day, I'm not no dick or woman peeves.
Yeah, I'm not.
>> You know what I mean? All the times that
I've been kicked out of Kay's house. Yeah.
>> All the times Kay's kicked me out then
kicked me out of hotels. Two hotels. >> Yeah.
>> Two hotels have been kicked out of
Natalie. I Natalie, come can you come in
a hangout? You can come and meet me. We
was all watching. No, Molly didn't do
anything with them people on Meet Me. He
was only talking to them.
>> I'm talking to him. I haven't done
nothing with anybody. That girl on be
fair. Listen. Listen. When I was in
Birmingham the other day.
>> Yeah. When I was in Birmingham the other
day, Monty didn't even get anyone's
numbers. He went out with me.
>> I literally didn't get no one's [ __ ] numbers.
And them women don't meet me.
>> I haven't been with any of them. I've
not even met anybody off meet me. No
one. I won't do that. Natalie, I
wouldn't. I'm only keeping my options
open just in case I don't get you back now. >> Yeah.
>> I've got I can do that.
Me, I can just delete me in a second and
block everybody. That simple. I'm not
[ __ ] cheating on nobody. I'm not a
cheat. You know, you [ __ ] finished
me, Natalie. You finished me. >> Yeah.
>> You know,
>> money didn't get money. Didn't get any
numbers. I got some numbers though.
>> It is the real Natalie. Just ring me and
we talk. Yeah,
>> it is Natalie.
>> You know what I mean? I've done nothing.
Absolutely [ __ ] Yeah, maybe I went on
YouTube, told everybody that we was in
the hotel, but he only said we was in
Manchester. They would have been ringing
up Manchester Hotels, not Birmingham hotels.
>> You was ready to meet the next girl,
then next thing you're getting tested at the clinic.
>> I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not
meeting anybody. I'm not meeting no next woman.
>> Here's the thing. Here's the thing,
Natalie. Yeah. I got tested when I was
when I was like, I'm on my own.
>> I got tested. I got tested.
>> I'm on my own.
>> I'm literally on my own. [ __ ] to
prove it. I'm single, Natalie.
I'm on my own. Who's here next to me?
Who's with me? I'm here [ __ ] sat on
this wall making a spliff.
That's it. I'm making a spliff.
>> N go and give him a cuddle. Stop being silly.
That that woman really doesn't know how
much I [ __ ] adore her and I love her.
You know what I mean? This whole YouTube
thing is [ __ ] madness.
>> It's getting
she really does not know she's got a
thought. She had a good mander. Maybe I
told her I'm not perfect. I already told
You know what I mean? I've already told
her that when I got with her. I am not perfect.
But I am still a good lad. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean?
I can't stay in that house no longer. I couldn't.
Now if you think I'm still living and
I've still got that place. I haven't. It's gone.
>> It needs Jamie. Do what you're doing.
Meet me getting female senses like you.
If you love me, you wouldn't want other
female. One second. No, no, no, no. One
>> No, I don't want him. Listen, Monty text
you. Monty text you and you didn't even
reply to him. So what else did you want
him to do? You know,
>> I was there for for three I mean four
days, 5 days waiting for you to reply to
me back, Natalie. Yeah, I was hurting proper bad like
you ripped me in part. My feelings for
you are [ __ ] strong. I've never felt
anything like this for a woman in my
entire [ __ ] life.
>> Never. Ever. I'm being serious. I've
never felt literally [ __ ] Kelly. Never.
>> You know,
he's not [ __ ] Natalie. He's my
[ __ ] world. And that's not a
>> Well, anyone anyone's got to be
desperate to meet that Lord J, man.
They've got to be desperate. Anyone
>> got We are desperate. That That is
desperate to meet Lord J. Nat. Listen to me.
I'm not meeting anybody of you that meet me.
>> I'm not meeting anybody off meet me
whatsoever. I haven't got no intend
intention. Well, whatever the world's
[ __ ] called, you know.
>> I'm only in love. Yeah. I'm already in
love with Natalie. Like I keep saying
every [ __ ] day, even in the pubs when
I was in the pub showing, I love
Natalie. I love Natalie. I [ __ ] love you.
>> I don't want anyone else. I don't want
any other woman.
>> But that's it. Do you know what I mean?
She always he can ring my phone. It's all
>> he didn't go out cold approach. I was
the one cold approaching. Not him. I
>> I didn't cold approach anyone. Natalie
and now I'm dead on my kids lives on.
>> Another thing is what you done? What you
done? What was wrong, Natalie? Yeah, you
should have went on large and started
talking this, started talking that when
you haven't even replied to his
messages. That's wrong, man. Why are you
going on that channel full of them [ __ ] Mongs?
>> No, listen.
Listen. Yeah, I don't want anyone else.
Yeah, I swear down on my kids like now.
Yeah, I in town. I wasn't even called
the promotion in town. Yeah, maybe I
went up to one couple of women. I said
pretend to him. I may as well just pretend.
Yeah, I don't want anyone else.
No one else. I'm not a cheat. I've never
been a chick.
>> You know,
>> if you do love me and then you talk to
me on the phone, you won't leave me
[ __ ] hanging like this. You won't.
And you want to do it up on YouTube. Do
you know what I mean?
I want to get off YouTube. I want to
sort myself out. I want to live with you and that.
But I can have a live with you when
you're just completely blanking me out
thinking that I'm talking to other Yeah,
I am talking to other women. But that
can get sorted out. I can get deleted and gone.
>> I'm not going out with anybody.
>> LT, you want to get in Moog's
knickknacks, don't you?
I know what you're about, LT. Don't lie
to me. Monty, do you see the state of
Monty's hair on the night out?
I'm not asking. not ask.
You know what? Women like me with Bheads.
At the end of the day, Natalie. Yeah.
You got a choice. Yeah. Talk to me or
just don't talk to me at all. Yeah.
Because I've not done nothing at all.
Yeah. I'm not waiting around for your
option. What you want?
I'm not waiting around for you for what
you want. And that's what I'm being
doing for now. And I'm still waiting
around for you. You know, why do you
think it text you?
Why do you think it text you a [ __ ]
Eddie every [ __ ] day?
You know what I mean? It's like
It's like you don't care about my feelings.
It's like I've got to care about your
feelings. And I do.
I [ __ ] really do, you know?
And me doing this, talking to other
people and meet me, I didn't expect
loads of women to jump on me like this.
Not meaning it like that because I don't
want other no other woman. I really [ __ ] don't.
>> My mom [ __ ] loves you now. You know,
my [ __ ] kids even like you. >> Yeah.
>> And that's very [ __ ] rare for my mom
to like anybody. Very [ __ ] rare. You know,
>> get back with Monty, man. Come on.
>> It's her choice, PJ. It's her choice.
Like, literally, if she thinks
>> Put it this way, put it this way. You
either want to come on a hang and sort
it out or talk or talk in private or whatever.
>> I'd rather talk private.
>> I'd rather just talk private, not on
YouTube. I'm sick of putting my business
up on YouTube. I am. I'm sick of [ __ ]
arguing and getting kicked out of places off women.
>> You could have met us in Birmingham.
>> I was asking her I was texting her. I
was saying that come Birmingham with me
and PJ now. Come for a drink with me and
PJ. Come on now. Come on. I was asking
her. I was texting her and texting her
and texting her.
I was literally asking her to come out
with me and PJ.
She looks like ties and then she
realized I was asking her to come out
with us. M. I weren't going to leave her
at home on the road. >> Yeah.
>> Or whatever else like that cuz I wanted
her to come out for a drink. Me and her.
So I probably just out
>> and get on with it.
>> And that's it. And that's all I do what
I wanted to do with Max,
you know? We haven't even we haven't
even [ __ ] there's nothing to fall out for.
>> I haven't shed any other woman.
I haven't kissed another woman.
>> I haven't [ __ ] hugged another woman.
>> I've not even got another Well, yeah, I
got numbers, but of meet me. But they
can get deleted easy, easy peasy one.
I'm not going out with anyone
that little moo moogs, don't you, LT?
When they're getting their little knicknacks.
Isn't that right, LT?
So now that if you do want if you do
want to talk ring my phone now if you
don't then fine if you don't
I'm not I'm not fighting for women anymore.
>> I think I think m listen money I think m
um I think Natalie still likes you to be fair bro
>> but she likes me. I don't know. I I love
her. I [ __ ] adore her man. Do you
know what man? She's the best woman. No,
he didn't get any girls numbers. Um, ghosting.
>> I swear I swear my kids lives, bro.
>> Why don't Okay, I'm going to show my
kids lives now. Straight up. Yeah.
[ __ ] hell, man. I love my kids. I
haven't got all 50 female numbers. Well,
>> no, he didn't, bro. He didn't. Cuz I was wearing numbers.
>> I got three numbers. I'm still talking
to all of them. But he didn't.
>> He's talking to women. He's talking to
him. I didn't get any numbers cuz I
didn't ask for numbers. I didn't get any numbers whatsoever.
And I promise you that now
literally I swear my children's lives
I didn't get no women's numbers,
>> you know. I really [ __ ] didn't that.
I got more pride for you now. Like literally. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I was saying?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> No, I'm just laughing now. The whole thing's [ __ ]
>> It is [ __ ] We finished for [ __ ]
nothing just because I went on YouTube
and told YouTube a lie. I told them we
was in Manchester.
>> But if she gives me a second if she does
give me a second chance, I will never do
this [ __ ] again. LT, I bet I bet LT, I
bet you're planning a trip to Miami to
get in that Morgan's nick.
>> I would never do this [ __ ] again if you
g me another chance. I wouldn't I
wouldn't even attempt to do it.
>> You want that little civian [ __ ] don't you?
Don't you, L?
You want that? I don't think, >> huh?
>> I don't think it is that to be honest.
>> No, it is, bro. It is. It is, Natalie.
Yeah, cuz she's gone on large and then she's joined
>> the end of the day. What? She back on
large now? Yeah. >> No.
>> [ __ ] Minger, man.
>> Nah, you want a little You want a little
Syrian [ __ ] don't you?
>> No. At the end of the day, yeah, I've
done nothing to you. Yeah, maybe I
[ __ ] chat chatted [ __ ] a lot. Yeah.
On YouTube. Yeah. I have to apologize to
you for all the blood [ __ ] I said on
YouTube about you. I'm just angry.
>> You should give it a whirl, LT. Give it a whirl.
>> Can you just ring me and talk to me on
the phone instead of on YouTube?
>> Do you know what? Yeah,
>> Natalie, you need to [ __ ] say to LJ,
"Fuck off." And then you need to start
talking to [ __ ] Monty again. Cuz this
is what this is what Izzy used to do.
This is what this is what Izzy used to
do with Craig Goodson. [ __ ] LT. She
used to [ __ ] go on he and [ __ ] do
this [ __ ] You know what I'm saying?
Then they would never defend you. You
know what I mean? With these [ __ ]
these women, bro.
>> I don't want to play these games with
her. I don't I did it with Kaye. I don't
want to do it with Nat.
>> I just want to bet life with Nat.
I don't want to sit on YouTube for the
rest of my life. If Nat gives me gives
me a second chance, I'm off YouTube.
YouTube's getting deleted, mate. It's gone.
>> And I'm not just saying that.
I I delete YouTube straight up. I
[ __ ] get rid of all my channels.
I'm not depressed. I'm I'm I'm [ __ ]
h I just miss her, man. I do. I really
do miss her. You don't understand. She
doesn't understand. She thinks I don't
love her. She thinks I'm cold or
whatever. I'ming not. I'm a human.
join this um hangouts, Natalie.
>> I'm a [ __ ] human. I make mistakes and
I'm willing to I want to fix my mistakes. >> Yeah.
>> And if you want to [ __ ] with a ginger
lad who bullied you with your mom and
then keep me out of it.
I know 100% if you did get with Lo, I
definitely want to get back with you. Is
it the BSM Kelly and a rice?
That's a K and a rice. That is I'm not
being funny, but you have two body for
[ __ ] anyone on this community. I'm
not just saying that. You really are.
>> Did you join the panel?
>> You tell you joined Lord J the other day.
>> She joins people who picks on a P.
That's what she does. If you're those
people who actually pick on her, it's just disable.
>> I'm not fighting for her. I'm not
because every time I do try and fight
for her and all that little PJs, they're
kicking her nuts.
>> So I'm I'm done. I'm done fighting for
someone who don't want me. I've not done
nothing wrong to that woman. Nothing.
just give out YouTube just give them out
information on YouTube about the hotel
and what hotel we're at. I didn't tell
him Manchester. So I didn't even tell
him what hotel we were in or where we
were or what what obviously I get why
she was mad at me. Obviously of course
he get mad at me because I promise I
won't go on YouTube and do that [ __ ] and
I did it. But only why I did it is
because I'm sick of getting kicked out
of places. I'm sick of getting kicked
out of hotels. I'm seeking [ __ ]
I just want a woman who loves me.
>> God bless you.
>> No, I do PJ. That's all what I'm asking.
What I want.
>> I'm not a cheat.
>> I never played it. I never play Natalie.
>> I would never ever play her.
>> You're taking the piss you are.
>> Oh, here we go.
>> I know. I'm not I'm not Natalie. I'm
very [ __ ] not. Yeah.
We all weren't watching you on Meet Me
going live. All them nights she was
going live. I was all watching you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Can I tell you something that?
>> Okay. So, you expect me to sit in a
house on my own depressed out my head? Yeah.
>> What happened? They got me kicked out.
Yeah. I was
Yeah, I know. Ran off yourself just cuz
you're wanted attention.
>> Yeah. I ran off because Okay, I ran off
because you didn't text me. I don't know
where to stand with you now when you're
not ringing it or texting it or telling
me what what you want.
>> Doesn't matter anyway. You don't
>> It doesn't matter. Okay, that's fine.
That's fine. You're done. Okay then.
Then you can go then. And then you can
go then. At the end of the day, I
haven't done [ __ ] all to you. At the end
of the day, I haven't cheated on you.
What? Now, you finish me. What do you
want me to do? She let go down me
depressed and cry my wrist open. She left suicide.
>> She left.
>> Yeah, go. She can leave. She really can
because if that's how she really feels
about me and my feelings
is saying that I'm not allowed to talk
to people or nothing like that. And I
got and I got to stay in the house all
depressed and I can go back to [ __ ]
Birmingham. Literally I can go back to
Birmingham. I've been I got I I [ __ ]
been ringing up in them today. And he
ended up in Birmingham once a day and he
said they in Birmingham and they could
pick me up and take me to it and all
that lot one of them houses what that is
in. So he always can get another one in
Birmingham. So that's not a [ __ ]
issue. I'm out all night. I'm a man.
Only why I left her is cuz she had no on
my own. Now they didn't ring me for five
[ __ ] days. How the [ __ ] am I supposed
to know what a woman wants when she's
not telling me what she wants?
>> That's the first time. Yeah. What? She's
going mad. I don't blame her for going
mad. She can go mad. That's nice. That's
good. I'm glad she's going mad,
>> you know. But at the start of it all,
I'm alone. I was alone in the house. PJ,
>> so what does she want me to do? sitting
here smashing me head me taking her
trying to get hold of her trying to
torture her trying to do what I just
[ __ ] ignoring the [ __ ] out of me I'm
feeling sick I'm feeling that to grab
the rods to my head to jump
Natalie don't give a [ __ ] still not
contacting me still not pick up the
phone to me you know what I mean I'm telling
>> I'm back in the hangouts >> yeah
this is why she needs to ring me to do offline ear
off ear like I'm not done with Natalie.
I never be done with her.
>> That weren't even a talk. I'm just done.
What? What? For for nothing. What?
Because I went meet me to talk to a
couple of people and they go back and
meet me now. Know what I mean? I'm not
with anybody. I'm I ain't got nobody to
talk to. Who have I gone to talk to? Right. Hello.
What is that?
What the [ __ ]
See, LT finds all of this uh YouTube
thing funny, don't you? You want to get
in their little knicknacks,
don't you, LT? You want to get in that little knicknacks?
Yeah, LT wants to try and get another little knicknacks.
My little civian knickers learn how to Oh, Chucky,
I miss you, Chucky.
I was watching you earlier, Chucky. Chucky,
want to play Chucky?
I was watching Chucky earlier.
You want to get in our little Syrian
knicknacks, don't you? You want to get
in our little Syrian knickknacks?
Don't lie to me.
Don't lie to me, son.
This YouTube thing is [ __ ] mad.
Yeah. Friends to the end.
So, where do you live, Chucky?
Where where are you from, Chucky?
Where can I find you?
Nah. See, I don't trust you, Ali, cuz I
know what you do, bro. You just sit
there and pick your moment. I'm not
dumb. I know what you do, Altie. Oh, really?
So, if I come to Hollywood, will you meet me? No.
No, that's that's Monty's lady. I'm not
going to see Natalie G. That's Monty's lady. Nah,
I can't believe like I said to you last
night, bro. If you I'll give you a
winning football bet if you got me and
Morgs talking again.
Nah, I'm only playing, bro. I don't want
to talk to that [ __ ] ugly [ __ ]
She looking [ __ ] old now as well.
I'd probably end up glassing the [ __ ]
prick if I saw her again. So yeah. No, I
was only joking, bro. But no, like
anyways, Natalie G's Monty's lady.
That's Monty's lady. No,
she looking really old, man.
I went I went on a recent picture.
She looking old at [ __ ] USA is he and
she's fatter now as well. Oh,
why is that LT?
I'll [ __ ] glass the prick.
Yeah, I was going to go um to the cinema
today and I walked to the bus stop and I
done a U-turn. I couldn't be bothered. I
just came home and ordered a McDonald's
and had some ice cream. Lovely.
Yeah, I know how agent works. She's
looking really old. Yeah,
I had uh 20 chicken nuggets, the spicy
ones, and then I had a chicken mac. The
spicy chicken nuggets are right, you
know. They don't even taste processed.
You know, like the normal ones, they
taste processed. These ones actually taste nice.
I'll probably have the shits tomorrow.
Yeah, I was watching some WWE earlier. I
was watching Randy Orton.
Yeah, I was watching Randy and John Cena.
Yeah, I was speaking to this tenant
earlier, like an ex-tenant ghosting and
she was saying how she wants to get
married and she wants to get married to
because she wants to have kids and I
think she was trying to hint me
cuz obviously he's only got about 6
years left before he can have kids cuz
obviously the women can't have kids but
it's not um advised that they have kids
after a certain age.
You know what I mean? So
although she was trying to hint
something, but uh not me. I'm not having no bubbies.
I'm not having no bubins.
Nah, [ __ ] that. I'm not having no bubins.
I'll barely be able to look after my
[ __ ] self now, lad.
No, I'm not bringing no bubins in the world.
Yeah. Do you remember yesterday LT?
Leave the old Syrian man alone. He wants
peace at this stage in life. The old Syrian.
You're You know what? I'll give you this
LT. Yeah, you're a good troll. You're a
good troll. I'll give you that. Yeah,
you're a good troll.
See, LT is a top tier troll.
Like he's actually like a good troll. He is.
Yeah, you're a troll, bro. [ __ ] off.
Yeah. The poor Syrian man.
[ __ ] troll, bro. [ __ ] troll.
That might be Natalie on the phone.
Maybe they're getting back together. I
hope they do get back together.
I'm a lover, not a fighter.
Yeah, I'm a lover, not a fighter, Dad. I
hope they do get back together.
No. Why would I try my luck with Natalie
G? That's Monty's lady.
No, that's not mine. That's Monty's lady. Oh, [ __ ]
I I feel sorry for Mony, man. You're not a cruel.
You're not a [ __ ] cruel bastards. really are.
Where are you, Monty?
Yeah, but [ __ ]
the guy's got [ __ ] disabilities, bro. Jesus Christ.
I can't stop laughing at Timmy when he
comes on YouTube, bro. It's funny as [ __ ]
Timmy's funny when all you do is see his
face on YouTube. It's funny, isn't it?
Yeah, that's what that [ __ ] Yeah, lot
I wake up, go on YouTube, and all you
see is like, Timmy, I'm dead, bro.
Yeah, that's what that USA said to me
that I need to um accept it. I said,
"No, I'm not accepting it.
No, I'm not accepting nothing,
[ __ ] bitch." So, I can't [ __ ] talk, mate.
Trust me, I used to be a mad [ __ ] in
the day. I used to be a mad [ __ ]
A really, really mad [ __ ] bro.
Put it this way. Any woman that messed
with me, yeah, they will never forget me
for the rest of their life.
Put it that way, bro.
So, I can't even say [ __ ] like what and [ __ ]
But I know now. I've learned now, so I
know what to do now.
But that's just life, is it, bro?
But hopefully NG gets back with um
it wouldn't be the clinic. It's too
early to be the clinic.
It wouldn't be the clinic. It's too early.
That takes about a week to come through.
That does. It's too quick to be the clinic.
Hopefully it's not G.
Maybe they can patch things up, you know.
Then he's [ __ ] up in it.
At least you have Natalie on here
[ __ ] talking to you, Monty. I wish I
had someone speak to me. They never ever
spoke to me, bro.
They were really They were a [ __ ] to me.
Remember Ali? They were a [ __ ] to me, lad.
I'm not sure, bro.
But hopefully he knows now. Like, women
can't be trusted after this experience.
They're no different. And they're [ __ ]
they're [ __ ] in their head.
Hopefully he's learned his lesson.
Uh yeah, maybe. But she's doing things
the wrong way. like going on Lord Jay's
and talking about it.
Like imagine that. Like that's what Izzy
used to do. She knew me and Craig had
beef, right? And she'd purposely go on
Craig's to [ __ ] her.
And then you got Paley. I know he
doesn't care about Kaye. Yeah, but it's
not the point. Going all the way to
Scotland to meet [ __ ] Rice. Like
that's how sick in the head they are, bro.
They actually are sick in the head,
these women, bro. It's not even a joke.
They're actually sick in the head.
Yeah. Look at what that Kayie did, bro. That's sick.
Even though he doesn't matter if he
cares or not, it's [ __ ] up.
And why is she going on L J's [ __ ]
talking about it, bro? Madness.
They all [ __ ] play these games.
So, are you saying that she's not normal then?
But that Kay is [ __ ] Going all the
way to Scotland. Oh my god, man.
Madness. That is mad. I couldn't believe
that, bro. What the [ __ ]
It's mad, is it? Ghosting. It is mad.
Don't want turn.
Here we go.
Yeah, it's mad. Yeah.
Yeah. Natalie should have met us in Birmingham.
Yeah. I got Rice on WhatsApp. I said to
him, "What's your Yeah. I don't really
I've never argued with Rice. Um,
but see it sounds like I'm [ __ ] but
I've never actually argued with Rice.
I've got him on WhatsApp, even though I
don't speak to him, but I'm saying to
Monty that if that was me, I would be on
that door, mate.
But I have done I have done madness like
that before, bro. So, it's I'm not
saying something that I wouldn't do
myself, but I've never actually argued
with this Rice.
I've never argued with him, bro. So, yeah. Uh,
who's this channel?
I'll link it.
He's never done anything to me.
He always used to invite me to Scotland and that.
Yeah, that's right.
I didn't even know his channel. That's
why I WhatsAppapped him. I'm going Yeah.
Come and spend your money here,
LT. Oh, yeah. I went to the bagel shop
the other day. Liverpool Street. You
know that bagel shop you told me about,
bro. I had to do a [ __ ] U-turn. It
was [ __ ] Choa Block.
It was [ __ ] Chocka.
So, I had to do a Uturn and I had to go
to another shop. Yeah, man. It was [ __ ] Chocka.
Yeah, [ __ ] shocker, bro.
Yeah, I forget it was uh the bagel
factory, but it was cocoa block. LGO
Come back. Monty,
where's Monty gone, man? Oh,
that's what you want to do though, is it
LT? You want to take USA for a little bagel?
Oh, bless you.
Bless you then.
There we go.
Come on. A
Who the [ __ ] is that?
Oh, what's there, man? [ __ ] hell.
I can't stop laughing at Timmy's face,
bro. It's jokes.
He's a [ __ ] He's a pratt. That
Timmy's a [ __ ] prat.
Yeah, it's hard to get a girlfriend
here, man. Unless you've got a million
[ __ ] YouTube subscribers.
See, it's all about [ __ ] social media
nowadays. You see?
Unless you got a [ __ ] That's what Ant-Man said.
Unless you got a million subscribers on
YouTube or Instagram followers, it's hard.
Unless you're a big YouTuber or
something, he said
it's true though, is it?
That's mad though to even say that.
Mad that isn't bad to even say that.
[ __ ] Jimmy, bro.
Oh my god. Yeah, I'm dead.
I can't that Timmy.
I swear down it's just so funny.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
He's a [ __ ] idiot.
That Timmy is a [ __ ] idiot, bro. No.
Well, I'm gone.