What's wrong?
W five [ __ ] hours sleep.
[ __ ] another day. Same old [ __ ]
Yep. I literally told you I'd done my
bets the other day.
I'm just chilling in bed today, man.
Depressed, I think. Oh, yeah. I went to
bed at 5:00 in the morning.
I was just speaking about my negative
experiences. I was on Reddit having an
argument with someone on Reddit.
Well, I done a bet today. Yeah. Over there.
I'm [ __ ] knackered, bro. I I fall asleep.
>> Yeah, I done it the other day. So,
nah, do your own bets.
Nah, you can do your own bets. You can
do your own both teams to score. No.
Yeah. Go do your own bits, man.
Mine doesn't win either half the time.
Yeah, I'm just chilling today. Straight up, bro.
Nothing to do. Boring, isn't it?
Can't go out cuz it's the same old here.
Same old England.
Boring, is it? [ __ ] boring life. I'm
going go back to sleep in a minute.
No point doing anything. today.
That's what happens though in this
country. You're just depressed. That's
what you will be in this country depressed.
Nothing will ever change. You'll always
have the same experiences with women.
The whole thing will always be the same.
It will never change.
Never change. Never. No, bro.
It wasn't the worst summer of my life. It's just
I was just thinking yesterday, man.
Well, yeah, it does get worse cuz
obviously you can't even date in this
country now. It's impossible.
Well, well, yeah, I guess so. It has
gotten worse to be fair. Last time was better.
You can't even date now. Can't even get
a conversation at anyone. How depressing is that?
You can't even get [ __ ] laid. How
depressing is that?
No wonder so many people kill themselves. Oh [ __ ]
I don't know. I'd love to know how they
do. You can't even do You can't even get
a conversation out of someone.
I'd love to know how they hook up.
They probably don't.
Unless the person's got a [ __ ] million subscribers
or a million [ __ ] followers. I don't
think they do. It's depressing.
I'm going back to bed in a minute, man.
Oh man, I'm [ __ ]
Do you snug anyone? I don't
I don't, bro.
It's funny how people on Reddit think
it's going to change
when think about like this. Yeah.
I was thinking about this last night.
What's the odds it's going to change? If
it's been the same, it's like if it's
been the same for three and a half years
and now it's just gotten worse. What's
the odds that all of a sudden it's going
to change? How could it? How could it?
One day you wake up and you go out,
whether it be a Thursday, Friday,
Saturday, you're not going to hear I
have a boyfriend. You're not going to
deal with attitude. How is that ever
going to happen one day?
I'm trying to I'm trying to be logical
about it. How?
And why is it already happened? If it
was going to happen, you know, I think
got some valid points because it's
[ __ ] It will never change in this country. Never.
That's why I don't even go out anymore
in this like in terms of drinking
because it's pointless. I went out last
week to see Monty and look what
happened. Same thing happened again.
Oh yeah, it does get worse. Yeah.
>> Yeah, it gets worse.
But just just know that it's not what
they really believe. These white
knights, they're lying to themselves.
They're in denial, thinking that there's
not a problem and thinking that they're
going to get laid. Just let them keep
being in denial, bro. It will never get them laid.
I could go out today if I wanted to, but
it's the same result. There's no point
going out when you already know the result.
Why would you do something if you
already know the result?
It's like watching a movie but and
you've already watched it. It's no point. So
yeah, I don't know why they do it. It's
never going to get them laid, but they
still simp. It's mad. Oh well.
Yeah. I don't know why they do that.
It was depressing yesterday thinking about it.
The bad experiences. It was depressing.
[ __ ] depressing. It was thinking
about it in bed. Never changes.
Still dealing with it at almost 28 years of age.
It's got a funny way of showing it's
going to change in it. It's got a funny
way of showing it.
It's got a funny way of showing it.
I think that's a good way to put it in it.
It's got a funny way of showing it's
going to change. [ __ ] man.
They're all entitled. They're all the
same. Once you've met one, you've met
them all. That's what I was saying to
myself yesterday. Once you've met one,
you've met them all.
Once you've met one woman, you've met
all of them. Basically,
they all got the same.
They've got the same excuses. They've
got the same mannerisms. They do the same thing.
You can see the westernity in their
eyes. Like what Ant-Man says.
Once you've met one, you've met them all.
None of them are polite. They're all
[ __ ] They're all time wasters.
They're all the same. Once you've met
one, you've met them all. That's what I
think. It's why I don't go out anymore.
It's pointless going out.
There's literally no point going out.
I've proved my point more than enough.
I've been up and down the country a million times.
I pro I've proved my point way more than
enough. I have nothing left to prove here.
That's that's it, bro.
It's like what I was saying to Adman. I
think I was living in the moment for a
very long time and then when I took a
step back and realized how much I
actually have tried
then it makes perfect sense to give up
in this country.
If you actually go through like actually
how much you've actually tried and how
it's not changed then it's yeah I was
living in the moment so I wasn't really
looking like thinking about how much
It's really bad, bro.
It's really bad. Yeah, man.
Yeah, it's got a funny way of showing
it's going to change. It's got a funny
way of showing it.
Funny way of showing it, mate.
So that's where we're at, lad basically.
Just playing some Frank. Then about to
go back to sleep, I think.
cuz where I was living in the moment so
much and I never actually took a step
back to see how much I actually tried.
And yeah, it's actually no joke. You've
actually tried more than anyone in the
world. It's actually facts. You've got
nothing left to prove now.
Go out and get numbers that don't that
don't go anywhere. And you've got and
I've got enough numbers on my phone. So
I feel like, you know, one of these
numbers should be interested.
And if they're not, then there's no
point getting 100 another 190.
So it's pointless. It's a waste of my time. So
once you've met one, you met them all.
So that's it. Start in it.
It will never change. Never.
I know how people think it's going to
change. I don't know what what makes
them think it will change.
I'd love to know what makes them think
all of a sudden
it's going to change.
Like I said, it will change if you leave
leave England. [ __ ] depressing
cuz then cuz like a part of me was
laughing at some of it yesterday and I
was like, "Oh, hold on a minute. This is
actually some serious serious [ __ ]
This is actually some serious [ __ ]
bro." I was laughing at like Antman. I
was like, "Bro, I should I wouldn't be
laughing if I was you." I said that to myself
cuz this guy has not even tried 1% that you have.
So, it's bad, isn't it? It is bad.
Yeah, I got enough numbers on my phone anyways. So, yeah.
If none of them meet, then you got your
answer in this country. Simple.
I'll still talk to you these numbers
I've already got, but I ain't going out
and getting new numbers. There's no point.
It's clear they've made up their mind
about you when it comes to this country.
So, you don't need to waste any more
time or anymore or money here. Yeah.
sucks, isn't it? Bad, bad, bad. See,
like I was saying, like I keep saying
that the the the [ __ ] up thing is
you've actually tried more than anyone
in the world. That's the [ __ ] up thing
about it. It's not like you ain't tried.
It's not like you got yourself to blame.
You can blame yourself cuz you didn't try.
tried more than anyone in the world.
Legitimately, bro. [ __ ] madness.
That's [ __ ] horrible, bro.
It's [ __ ] horrible.
Horrible life, you know.
It's bad. Really bad.
Like like I said, you're still dealing
with it at 28 years of age as well. It
never changes. Not even with that age gap.
So like the age, you know,
it's really bad. Really bad.
It's depressing, bro.
Like I keep saying, even if this
football bet Wednesday wins today, I
won't be going out, bro. Like I said, I
weren't going to go out last week. It's
just that Monty was in a bad place and I
kind of said I was going to go out. So,
I won't be going out regardless.
I don't even need a football bet, but
I'm still not going out even if it does win
230 from 80
cuz you need to, you know, in life,
right, it's all about breaking a cycle.
Do you understand? Like you can be in
cycles and you don't even realize you're
in a cycle.
Like it could be gambling. It could be literally anything.
Yep. Two teams. It could be anything.
You don't know that you're actually in a cycle
until you until you realize it. And then
you break the cycle, which is what I
basically done by this Thailand thing.
Cuz if I don't do it, I'm not going to
break the cycle.
you know, even if it was only for two
weeks, one month, two months, unless you
do this, you're not going to break no
cycle. It's going to be the same thing.
You see, that's, you know, it's the same
thing with gambling. Remember about
breaking a cycle. You know, you come on,
you winge about it. What do we do? We
broke the cycle. Unless you break the
cycle, you're [ __ ]
I realized it, you know,
when I sat back and thought about the
house and all of the traveling that I
done with the house and that, it also
come up that how much you've tried. You
know what I'm saying? It's [ __ ] It's
serious [ __ ] It's serious serious [ __ ]
All the times you went Wales, Newcastle, Manchester,
I think it's it's so bad. You probably
need therapy now
cuz you've been wronged. You've been
wronged by women, you know. You know,
you should go.
You've actually been wronged by them.
You've been [ __ ] over by them all your life.
Wouldn't surprise me if you need some
[ __ ] sort of therapy now, bro. It's
serious serious serious [ __ ]
Like I keep saying, it wouldn't have
been a problem if you're fat and ugly.
It wouldn't have been a problem if you
were too scared to try. Then we could
blame oursel and kick ourselves in the
foot. But there's none of that. There's
there's there's none of that. You can't
even say you ain't tried. That's [ __ ] up, bro.
You know it's [ __ ] up.
We just got takeaway today. Yeah.
Yeah. Will never change. Cuz
like I said, calculate the odds of of
that actually happening.
Think about it, George. Yeah. It only takes one.
It only takes one person. Well, why has
this one person not already been found?
Think of it. Why? Why? If you want to go
if they want to go by that logic, bro,
why is this person not already been found?
It's not like you ain't met enough
women. Why has this one person not
already been found?
You know, it's not. You know what I'm saying? So,
all that [ __ ] just comes to an end.
Yeah. There's no point getting Looks
Max, bro. You're there's no point. It's
just going to be the same old no matter
what you look like when you go out.
I'm just going to be sleeping today.
It will never change. Never.
I doubt I'll be ever going out in this
country again, bro. I can't lie to you.
I doubt I'll ever be going out here again, bro.
Unless one of these numbers want to meet
me or something, I won't be going out again.
I don't think so, bro. No, thank
I'm going to I'm going to complete this GTA.
Bro, there's like there's it actually
like you know I say I was a bit younger
but a while back it's like you'd have
this annoying thing in your head saying
oh yeah but you don't know you could you
could meet someone it might happen you
you know you'd have that in your head
you don't even have that now it's just
It's utterly pointless.
It honestly is the most pointless thing
you could actually do cuz it's not
actually going to change ever
cuz it would have already.
There's like no there's literally no [ __ ] point.
And if he was going to go out, there's
[ __ ] no point even getting [ __ ]
phone numbers if you even talk to anyone. So
there's no there is no point.
There's literally no point, bro.
They've all got the same attitude,
the same unrealistic standards, the same
ciness. You know, I should have gave up
two years ago. Me, when all that [ __ ]
come about and all that [ __ ] happened, I
should I should have really gave up like
two years ago.
I have people in my ear saying, "Oh, no.
You know, it's just the bad ones. You'll meet someone.
Other people will want you as well." No,
no, no, no, no, no. I had to listen to
all that [ __ ] for [ __ ] years, bro.
[ __ ] It's [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, that's why I went to Birmingham to see Monty
and I kept saying I was going to go
there. I didn't go out for two weeks.
So, I mean, I'm still speaking to
someone from there, but
chance of them meeting, bro. Nah.
Excuse after excuse after excuse with them. Never change.
I like this car, but it's good. Yeah.
Yeah, I was thinking about it last
night, bro. It was [ __ ] depressing me.
Really, really depressing me, bro. Bad.
Enough to get anyone depressed.
And I was thinking, you know, out of all
of them years, right? Um, I never had
any positive experiences as well, to be
honest with you, I never had any,
um, no positive experiences with them.
despite people saying that they're not
all the same. They're not all like that.
And all people do is make [ __ ] gay
jokes when they don't like the truth.
That's the thing.
I I had none. I never met any that were different.
Cuz I don't I won't I won't listen to
people and I don't expect people to
listen to me. Talk is cheap. We can we
can talk back and forth all day, but we
need to be shown different. If we're not
shown a change, then it's pointless. And
they you've gave them more upful of
opportunities to prove to prove that
they're not the same. And they are all
the same. Every single each and last one of them.
Maybe in the 1980s they weren't the same. But
like I said, I got them 30 numbers two
weeks ago with the Birmingham ones.
That's 16 right there, right off the
bat. Still not even a single date from
what it looks like.
So it tells you all you need to know.
I think it's [ __ ] disgusting me. Amen.
That person excuses what they have.
about two weeks on.
Is there anyone in this country that
don't play games?
It seems like everyone plays games even
at 28 years of age.
What I find so mad is how
like Ant-Man ain't even tried nowhere
near as much as you
and he left before you. That's so mad.
Not even 1%. like that
cuz you obviously knew it were never
going to change. Yeah. No.
I'm [ __ ] tired, bro.
And then people make gay jokes. It's [ __ ] up. Yeah,
they make gay jokes. It's just
Sad life ever
easy clean the [ __ ] out of [ __ ] All
right. one. You met them all. Never changes. Never go.
I find funny that they don't learn they
don't learn from each other. [Music]
I'm buffing it anyways.
Go some music and sleep. [Music]