Yeah. Yeah, man.
It It takes about a week to complete
this [ __ ] GTA.
It takes about a [ __ ] week. Yeah. Do
you know what you would have been better
off doing? You would you would have been
better off just shoplifting every day,
right? For like two weeks, three weeks. Um
um and then they're just leaving not
doing like 3 months and then going out
drinking every week because you don't
need to go out drinking every week. But
what it's the same old. What would you
go out drinking every week for? You you
best off putting more graft in and then just leaving
because saying I've tried way more than
him. So maybe he sees it differently. If
if I was shoplifting, bro, I would just
shoplift for like two, three weeks
straight and not even go out like and
waste money drinking in this country cuz
it's just the same old every time you go out.
But obviously I've tried a lot more than
him, which is why I don't even try
anymore. But it's always the same. It
will never change. And I don't know what
gives people the inkling that it will
change cuz it's not changed in years.
So I don't know what gives people the
inkling that it will change somehow. How
could it change and what's the odds of
it changing as well? So that's another
thing you need to consider. But I would
just ramp just do it ham for like two
three weeks, bro. Not book in advance
for two months and then go out every
week. What's the point in that bro?
Doesn't make sense. Yeah,
it's always the same. It will never change.
They're full of a load of excuses.
How did I know that they were going to
try and use distance as an excuse?
It's it's laughable.
That's the greatest excuse. that and the
age they they they're full of excuses.
They're just full of [ __ ] That's what
they are, bro. Full of absolute [ __ ]
So that's it. Yeah.
Yeah, man. I'm
I've already considered this football bet lost.
Don't care if it wins or loses to be
honest. I don't give a [ __ ] Yeah,
they use an excuse, then they use
another excuse, and you think to
yourself, why the [ __ ] are they even
texting you, bro? You know, why the [ __ ]
are they even texting you, wasting your
time and their time? It's pointless. Um,
so it will never end. It never ends.
Never change. Never. Never in this
country. It would only get worse.
[ __ ] depressing, bro. Can't believe I
didn't go to sleep until like 6:00 in the morning.
Bad, bad, bad, bad, bad. Really is.
Bro, I was speaking, you're going to
laugh at this one. Yeah. So, I was
speaking to one of these from
Birmingham, right? and I was lying it
down on the table and I was like, "Oh, I
don't know how how this is going to work
because of the distance," which is a
fair point. So then I turn around cuz
they love using distance as an excuse.
They love using age as an excuse and
it's like, "Well, what about all of the
ones in London,
you know?" So anyways, I said, "Oh,
yeah, that is true, but um
uh I turned around and said, "Oh, that
is true, but um what about um
you know, let's meet and see how it goes
and you know, we can see each other
every month, you know, um cuz it's not
too It is far, but it's not impossible."
Then she turns around and said, "Oh, I'm
going to be honest. Um I don't feel the
spark." I was like, "Huh? You gave your
number and you've been texting every
single day. So, it's just never ending.
This is this is exactly what I was
saying yesterday, bro. I was speaking to
a few people on this about this on
Reddit is it will never change in this
country. And I don't know why people
think it would. I don't know how could
they think it would. What evidence would
they have to go by that all of a sudden
it's going to change? How can it? It's
It was the same last week as well. Was
that actually a week? It seems more than
a week ago, doesn't it?
Just excuses after excuses after excuses
after excuses. I've been dealing with it
for years. I said to Ant-Man as well,
like, I know I just said this, but you
weren't here. I basically said to him
that you should have just shoplifted for
like 2, three weeks and just left as
soon as you could. There was no need to
go out every week drinking because it's
not anything to look forward to because
it's just the same old.
So, I don't He said, "Oh, trust me. I
know what I'm doing." I was like, "But
you should have just shoplift this for a
month and then there."
Um, you know, that doesn't make any
sense to book it like a few months and
then go out drinking every week.
It's like me. If I was say I was going
to leave somewhere, right, and I was
doing Uber, I would just do Uber every
day for a month and leave like or you
know 3 weeks or whatever. So
yeah, the whole point is trying to get
out, not try, keep trying in this country. So
it's excuse after excuse after excuse.
Um to be honest, there was a slight
difference is that they reply back,
but obviously in my opinion, I feel like
they only reply back because they feel
like they can use distance distance as
an excuse. It's just another excuse when
Birmingham ain't really an excuse,
you know. There is no excuse for it. You
know, you can go to Birmingham every
month. I know somebody that goes back
and forth and [ __ ] leads all the
time. So, I mean, it's it's not an
excuse. You know, you can get to
Birmingham in near enough an hour on the
train, an hour and 17 minutes. So, it's
not really an excuse. And when they
can't use that excuse anymore, then
it's, oh, they basically admit to just
wasting your time.
It will never change in this country and
I don't know what gives people the
impression that it will. So yeah,
it will never change here, bro. That's
why I can't be bothered with it anymore.
Like I said, went to Birmingham because
I felt sorry for Monty. So
yeah, and look, I got a backlash of it.
It will never change, bro. The only
difference is if you go to other cities,
you'll probably get more replies and
but maybe something like that, but
that's about it
because they're trying to use this as an
excuse when me and you both know that if
I lived in Birmingham, it'd be another
excuse just like it was another excuse.
It will never ever change. Doesn't
matter how old you are.
Like it took me [ __ ] to 7 to You know
what it was? I tell you what it was,
Nico. Yeah. When the whole um house
thing was going on, I was kind of like
living in the moment.
Um basically I was like I was living in
the moment. Now I didn't go to Rosie. I
went to some other ones. Um I only we
only got one by the way. But listen, I
was living more in the moment. And then
when I was reminiscing like yesterday or
the last day at the house, you know,
you're thinking of the good times
because it was good. We had some good
times in the house, but then the
traveling comes into it. And then it's
like, oh [ __ ] Like you actually tried
more than anyone in the world. Like this
is actually serious [ __ ] Like it's
nothing to even laugh at. It's serious.
Like you you've actually the [ __ ] I used
to do, bro. like go to [ __ ] Cardiff
on a Friday, then the next Friday I'd go
Cardiff again and it would just be the
same [ __ ] old like but because I was
living in the in the moment then I
didn't really stop to think about oh
[ __ ] But now like looking back on it
now it's like it was similar to how you
was was saying about how you didn't meet
anyone in three and a half years
which gets me to my whole point is that if if you
the thing is right Nicolo
I know you're trolling that but if
something was going to change and it
only takes one person why has it not
happened in 3 and 1/2 years considering
how much you've tried
Um, and also
what are the odds? Just just think about
this in terms of William Hill. Yeah.
Think of the odds of this. Tell me what
the odds are cuz I don't know what the
odds are. You've been dealing with this
[ __ ] now for three and a half years.
Probably even a bit longer than three
and a half years. Week in week out, week
in [ __ ] year out, week in year out,
right? What are the odds that the next
time you go out, none of this is going
to happen? What's the actual chances?
What's what's what's the chances? It's
like West Ham playing [ __ ] Manchester
City, right? And they've lost 30 games
in a row and it's their 31 30 first
match now. They're going to lose, bro.
They've got a history of losing. It's facts.
It is actually facts, bro.
That's scary, bro. Really scary. But
they still tell you that you're going to
meet someone and I don't know where they
pulled this out from because how has it
not happened now then? You know,
and like the video that I done, which I
didn't upload, is it's sort of like it's
not like you didn't try.
You know what I'm saying? It's not like
you've not tried. It's not like you're
not fat and it's not like you're fat and
ugly. You know, even your body count is
quite bad. You know, for the amount of
trying you've done, you should have had
more than that with my confidence and
the way that I look. It's crazy. It's insane.
Um, but somehow one day you're going to
go out and it's all going to be
different. How could it? How could it be
different? That's, you know what I'm
saying? You can't even get anyone.
It's [ __ ] disgusting. Um, and it will
never change either. And like I said,
I'm in the minority because you know
these people on that channel I gave you
that Oreo man. The difference with these
people is they've never tried. You've
tried more than anyone in the world. So,
it's like what can anyone say to you?
Because also, you've also lost hope as
well because you've tried everything.
You've also lost hope.
Because I mean what can anyone say? They
can't tell you to try because you ain't tried. So
you have to leave the country. That's
the only that's the only conclusion that
that we can come we can come up with.
Now you should be on a date this week.
Even if you had to go back to [ __ ]
Birmingham, you know, you should be on a
date this week or by next week. You got
16 numbers them four times that you went
out and it's just the same old boring.
It's just the same old boring. And and
and you know the thing is right is that
even if I got if I went out again, I'm
not getting numbers no more. There's no
point in me even getting numbers.
Nah, I don't n I don't have it in me,
bro. I don't have the energy anymore.
I'm not doing it for another 3 years. I
shouldn't have to. I've tried more than
enough. I've wasted more than enough of
my life. Cuz you know the the thing is right
they're not short-term. How can they be
short-term? You can't even get laid. So
how how I mean how can they be
shortterm? You can't even get sex.
So short-term for what? You can't even get sex.
So how are they short-term?
Shortterm for what? Of course you can
expect a relationship from them. Why
not? It's a woman. It doesn't matter
where they are. Street club, Weather
Spoons. Why can't you Why can't you find a relationship?
And even if you're right, they're not
interested on the street either. It's
not It's not a right or wrong thing.
It's not a right or wrong environment.
You could do a million approaches on the
street. They're just going to tell you
they got boyfriends. I mean, I put
enough videos out there
You know what I'm saying? And you've
done approaches on the street anyways.
So what what's what's that got to do
with anything that women that go club
are not looking for relationships? Okay.
So what about all the ones on the street
that keep pretending they got
boyfriends? I mean we done a lot of
them. So it doesn't matter where where
they are, bro. Library, mall, street,
bar, club, pub, festival, gig, they're
the same. They're westernized.
It's not one place over the other.
They're all westernized.
I could do 50 approaches on the street
today and it would still be the same old boring
without even having to go to a [ __ ]
club. Does it matter where it is? Oh [ __ ]
So yeah, it doesn't matter where it is
because it's going to be the same. They're westernized.
It's they're they're literally the same.
They're westernized. They watch the same
stuff. Why does it matter where where
where you approach them?
No, they haven't. No, they [ __ ]
haven't. I've done a lot of approaches
on the street. No, they haven't. I've
done a lot of approaches on the street,
you know. No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no. I've done a lot of
approaches on the street.
I would say most of my approaches are on
the street. No, they're not. 95% of them
are not in the bars and clubs. It
doesn't matter where it is.
They are the same women. It doesn't
matter where it is a bar or a club. It's the same,
you know. So, I just have to leave now.
That's it. I'm done. I've got nothing
left to prove now.
So, that's me done, bro.
It took me a long time to realize to
fully lose hope because back then I
never I still had some sort of hope
and that was driving me mad is like the
tiny bit of hope now I've got none like
none at all
which I didn't even last week I just
went because Monty and that you know so
so but yeah you need to really lose hope
and when you have lost hope you will
know you will know it
because if something was going to happen
it would have happened by Now, let's not
underestimate the amount of trying
you've done. So, yeah, you need to leave
the country. You have every right to
feel the way you do as well.
Um, because I do approaches on the
street before the club. I do approaches
on the street after the club.
So, so what?
You're going to go on the street and all
of the So, if I go out today and I
approach on the street, I'm not going to
hear that I've got a boyfriend.
I'm going to get a relationship.
I don't think so, bro. I don't think so.
There's many numbers that I got from the
street that played exactly the same
games as these women in the club. Yeah,
I done a bet the other day, bro. Yeah,
it's either suicide or you leave the country.
That's what I was that was that that's
actually what I was thinking about
yesterday, bro. Cuz again, I've got a
history. I'm not like most people. You
see, most people have to work like they
had to work for 3 years and they didn't
try through various different reasons.
They didn't try, they didn't want to try
or they were scared or they didn't have
the time to try. Whatever it is, the
damage is done. You've tried. You've
tried more than anyone in the world.
You're in this position. You need to
leave. Simple. You need to get out of
this country. That's That's it. Um
all them years. Oh, okay. Fair enough.
So, what about all of the approaches
that I done on the street um
last uh uh two weeks ago? And I done
some on the street when I was in
Birmingham as well. So, what about all
of those ones then? So, what about all
of the approaches I've done on the
street in the years? What about those
ones then where they pretended they got
boyfriends or they'd give their number
and troll or not message back? What
about all those ones? Forget about the
[ __ ] bars. Forget about the clubs.
What about all of those ones?
What about all of those ones? I done an
approach I done a few approaches sober a
couple of weeks ago. Got two numbers
sober. What about those numbers
that didn't reply back?
>> What about those numbers?
If you if you want to if you want to um
would you say it's 50/50? No. You got no
chance in this country.
You've literally got no chance of
finding anyone in this country.
>> Oh, it would have happened by now. It
Like I'm not living in the moment
anymore, you know? I'm looking back on
it now. It would have generally
generally generally happened.
So you either carry on the way you live and depressed
um or you leave England. That's all you
really have cuz this is going to
continuously happen and happen and
happen and happen and happen cuz you're
not breaking the cycle. You see? So but yeah
it will never change.
See, at least if you was like the
Indones at least if you was the
Indonesian guy, you could be like, "Oh,
I never tried. I never tried. I was too
scared to try." And you could blame
yourself. You could kick yourself
because you didn't try. But there's none
of that because you did try. You done inhumane things.
You know, I don't think it's exactly
normal going to Wales two times in a
week. I done the most madnesses. Never
changed. So, I've got to live with that
for the rest of my life. You know what I'm saying?
That is That is [ __ ] depressing, bro.
That is actually depressing as [ __ ]
I generally think if anybody else was
me, they would have ended up killing
someone by now. I I actually think they
would have ended up killing someone or
themselves or they would have just gave
up [ __ ] long time ago. I generally think, yeah,
you must have some patience to to put up
with all of this [ __ ] for years and
years and years. But I always I
[ __ ] it up, bro.
Sorry. I always thought it was going to change. Like,
it will never change. Never. Never, bro. depressing, bro.
I did, bro. Did you not just listen to
what I said? I just told you I done it
in public two weeks ago
and it was the same. I've got a
boyfriend. I've got a boyfriend.
Did you not just listen to what I just
said? I literally told you that two
weeks ago I went out and I'd done it in
public just like I've been doing it in
public for years.
And it's just the same old I have a
boyfriend. It's just the same old people
that aren't interested. Did you
literally just ignore that? I've just I
literally just told you that.
Like, brother, I literally done it in
Birmingham on the street. I literally
done it two weeks ago. They're not
interested. It doesn't matter where it is. Bro,
time for plan B.
And another thing is I've got enough
numbers on my phone, Nicolo. I don't
need any new numbers, bro. I've got
enough numbers on my phone. And one of
them should have met me.
One of some of one of these numbers
should have met me. You got enough
numbers on your phone. You've tried more
than a [ __ ] enough. You shouldn't
have to try anymore. You shouldn't have
to waste any more of your you've trying.
You You've done what you've had to do.
Now leave. Simple. That's it.
And if you approach in public, do you do
you not understand how this goes? Do do
you do you understand, bro? Do you know
how you end up in bars and clubs? You
end up, do you know how you end up in
these clubs, bro? Because you start off
approaching in the public and you're
here and I've got a boyfriend. I've got
a boyfriend and you think, "Fuck this."
Then you get on the drink. That's how
you end up in these clubs. You know,
when you go central London that that
well, I'd say nine times out of 10,
that's how it starts. Oh, let me do a
couple of approaches sober and then you
get so wound up and so depressed by it,
you just get on the drink.
That's that's that's how that's how you
end up in these clubs
like because of the depression from
doing it sober and it never changing.
It will never ever change in this country,
you know? Never ever ever, bro. I
[ __ ] realized it, bro. I realized it
a couple of weeks ago as well. Yeah.
Good for them. And there's also millions
of people that are single. And there's
also millions of people that are single.
And also, it's all to do with luck. If
you meet someone, even if there are
millions of people in relationships,
they're not you. They're not in your
shoes. They're not in your
circumstances. They're not in your body.
And there's also millions of people that
are single. I mean, [ __ ] I don't even
know who makes these statistics up
because most of the people I meet are
single. Most of the people that I know
are single, tenants, people that I've
met drinking, people from the army.
Like, most of the people I've met are
[ __ ] single. I mean, like, one in
four men that I know are probably in a relationship.
Like, that's that's how damn bad it is.
So, I mean, yeah, there probably is, but
there's probably millions of people that
are also single.
Nah, bro. I'm not doing it anymore. I'm
leaving, bro. I rip my tickets. I'm
done. That's it. So, it doesn't matter
if millions of people in relationships
are not. There's millions of people that are single.
It's not a it's not a valid argument
because it doesn't mean you're going to
be in a relationship, you know. You
know, and most of women that I meet are single.
That's another thing. Most of that's
another thing. Most of the women you
actually meet are single as well.
Nah, it's not a me problem. It's a
westernized women problem. And my
approaches and my messages prove that.
It's a w it's a woman in the west
problem, which is my approaching videos
prove that. And all of my messages prove
that. So, at the end of the day, it's
definitely a them problem. Even when I'm
watching other people do it in America,
they getting the same [ __ ] They are
literally getting exactly the same [ __ ]
You're too old for me. You're too young
for me. I've got a boyfriend. So [ __ ]
how could it be when when I'm watching
stuff other people that have no relation
to me getting the same attitude from
women. Got to be a you problem, bro.
Can't be a you problem. And I'm watching
it and it's annoying me watching it. It
It's a them problem. It definitely
definitely definitely a them problem. I
mean, they're not interested in 90% of
people. They're not interested in you.
They're not interested in me. They're
not interested in this, Richard. And it
doesn't matter how much you simp. It's
not going to get you laid. So, I don't
even know why you're coming on here
defending women because it's not going
to get you laid. It will never sing will
never get you laid. So, I don't know why
you sit here and you defend them. It is
women in this country. Trust me. If you
go to another country, you have none of
these problems. None of these problems
with women. It's a westernized women problem.
It's literally right a westernized women
problem. You go to anywhere in Asia.
Isn't it funny? Right. As soon as
Ant-Man left the country, none of these
problems followed him. Isn't that funny,
bro? Isn't that funny?
It's It's literally women in this
country. 100 million% it is. I've got
messages. I've got [ __ ] approaching
videos. It they are definitely the
problem. If you as soon as you leave
this country, none of these problems
follow you. That's that's your evidence.
None of these problems follow you with
these westernized stuckup women. You
have none of it. It's the women in this
country. Like I was in denial for so
many years and then I started watching
like other videos and other people were
getting exactly the same thing as what I
was getting. Think about it, bro. Think
about the odd ball if you was the only
one. And you know, you can talk about
people that are in relationships that
met years ago or the few people in
relationships. It has no valid argument.
It it's no valid argument because most
of the people that I come across are
[ __ ] single. All the tenants were
single. All the army guys are single.
All of the women I come across are
single. What millions of people in relationships, bro?
What millions of [ __ ] people, you know?
It definitely is women in this country
100%. And you know, at the end of the
day, bro, like people can defend women
all they want, but it's never going to
get them anywhere. Let them let them
waste their life defending them. It's
never going to get them laid. So let
them let them crack on, bro.
Nah, you keep telling yourself that, S.
You keep telling yourself that. Get a
job. You keep telling yourself that.
Uh, you know, the funny thing is,
Nicolo, yeah, I know this guy. He goes,
he's got a good job. He goes to the gym
and he's got money. Like, he's with the
most fattest women you'll ever see.
You have no clue. It's the women in this
country that's the problem. Trust me. As
soon as you leave any westernized
country, right, you not you won't have
any of these problems. See, look, you
are unemployed. See projection. Anyways,
I'm blocking this weirdo. Uh, no, bro. I
stuck it on them. Well, three of them.
No, I had problems with three of them, bro.
I mean, what do you think the problem
is, Nicolo? I think it's the definitely
definitely the women in this country. One million%.
And that's what that's what my
approaching videos proved and my
messages. It is definitely definitely
women in this country because of social
media. But even though like the evidence
is out there, people still defend women,
they will still act like they're not the
problem. And it's it's [ __ ] crazy,
bro. I mean, that was the whole point of
the approaching videos is to show that
it's nothing like what people say, you know?
Oh, because one of them stole my after shave.
And yeah, it was a long story, bro. It
weren't all of them. It was only three So yeah,
some really nasty suicidal thoughts yesterday, bro.
Like 5 in the morning. I was just
thinking about these negative experiences.
It's bad, bro. It's actually really bad.
I was getting these like suicidal
thoughts and [ __ ]
I took more a few times.
It's bad, bro. It's bad.
But then you get people that just defend
women all day. Why do they do it? Like,
do they think it's going to make women
like them? Because I couldn't sleep,
bro. I was just thinking of the negative experiences,
thinking of the bad experiences I've had
with women, how it's never going to
change. It's like torment. It's like
it's like you're being tormented. Every
day you wake up, it's like you're being
tormented because of it. It's bad, bro. It's bad.
And I know like the thing is, bro, like
I know I've said it a million times, but
I will never try in this country again.
I will never ever try because the way I
see it is I've got enough numbers on
that phone for one of them to be
interested. And if they're not, add in
all of the years I've tried on it.
That's it. I'm done. I will never try in
this country ever again. Like you you've
got my word now, bro.
So I swear to God on my dead dad on my
dead dad in the [ __ ] Well, he's not
on the ground. My dead dad. I will never try again.
never. Um, and I made it up on my mind, bro.
Reality like all hit me at once, like
with the house and the amount of trying
and the [ __ ] that you've been with for
years with these people. You know, you
don't deserve it. All of this piss taken
with women, the USA Izzy, the bad
experiences, the excuses today, the
ongoing [ __ ] you know, like no one
deserves it. I will never try again.
Never. I swear in my mom's life, I'll
never try again in this country. Never.
Never in a [ __ ] million years. So, never.
My mind's made up. So, it should have
been it should have been made up [ __ ]
two [ __ ] years ago, bro. That April
May, bro. You know, two years ago, I
should have gave up by [ __ ] summer
two years ago.
But I should have gave up like [ __ ]
18 months ago. What the [ __ ] Then
you generally realize, [ __ ] it's never
going to change. Never.
And there's nothing in my head anymore
saying, I'll try. You never know.
There's nothing now. There's that's it.
We're done. There's nothing.
I mean, some people got different
tolerant levels to be honest.
But mine, it took me a bit longer to
realize that it will never change ever.
Never in a [ __ ] million [ __ ] years.
So she's a widow by now.
Once you met one, you met them all.
Like I say, well, once you met one
woman, you've met all of them.
And the past will dictate your future,
which it has been doing three and a half years. Well,
it's like it is like the lottery.
You got think of all of these numbers
you've got over the years. all of the
people that you've met that you didn't
get numbers and you you never you can't
even be intimate with someone. It's not
like like oh you don't have um some
relationships I I could understand would
take years but you can't even be
intimate with someone. You can't even
have a sex life. You can't have anything
and all of them numbers. So what makes
you so sure that you go out today and
another four or five numbers or however
many numbers you get is going to be the same? Never.
Never. I would I would like to know how
many numbers I actually got over the
past 3 and a half years.
So, what makes you think the next time
the next woman you meet is not going to
do the same thing?
Well, you've only just [ __ ] realized
this after three and a half [ __ ]
years. I mean, that's pretty bad to be honest. So,
bad. It is bad. Tell me he's bad.
You should have been sitting in that
cinema by yourself yesterday.
You tried more than anyone in the world.
It would never change.
Never [ __ ] never change, lad.
So yeah, I mean, I guess they reply
because they can use they feel they can
use distance as an excuse.
And then you say, "Okay, well, we can
see each other once a month." There's
another excuse. and another excuse and
another excuse. So, why even give
numbers to reply if you're never going
to meet him? Stupid.
And then this Indonesian guy winds me up
as well because it's like he doesn't try anything.
I want to really make people
um understand that actually the amount
you've actually tried cuz I don't think
people understand it. But I actually
want to get someone and force them on a
train out of London like every week so
they get the gist of like how ridiculous
as it sounds how much you've actually
tried over the years
and see what they're saying after that,
you know, and then see see what they're
saying after that, bro.
It will never change. Never. Just like
what Adine says.
Millions of people in relationships.
There's millions of people that are
single. I swear most of the people I
know are single.
Most of the people I know are single.
You probably to be honest with you, it's
probably 50/50. I'd say now half in
relationships and half not in
relationships. I'd say more people are
single than in relationships now.
I don't know. It seems that way. So,
and it always used to make me laugh when
people used to try and use that argument
because it's like, okay, so say there
was other people that are in
relationships. Okay, well, there's a
reason why they're in relationship. They
could have got lucky. They might have
got lucky on a dating app. They might
have met through work or they might have
met before Instagram, before Tik Tok, or
maybe just one day these people got lucky.
That doesn't mean it's going to happen for you.
You know what I'm saying? It's not
That's like saying that, oh, this person
won 10 grand on roulette. You're going
to you're going to win 10 grand on
roulette. It's not that's not the way that works.
Surely to God, like if you had any
common sense, you would realize that the
the world does not work like that.
Some people are just meant to be single.
But again, it's not that I think that
some people are meant to be single.
Obviously, I I if there was no social
media, we wouldn't be here. We wouldn't
be having this conversation. So,
I mean, you there's even times you will
message people, not message people,
sorry, you will approach people, um,
Nicolo, and they'll just say straight
off the bat that they're not interested.
Yeah. Yeah. Pe it happens. Uh, I think
it happened twice in a month. So, hold
on a minute. So, you've got all of these
people telling you that you're going to
meet someone and it will happen for you
and Yeah. Like you you can simply just
go up to someone and they just tell you
that they're not interested. [ __ ] how
is it going to change? In what universe?
Like I'm all for like starting a debate.
When is it going to change? How is it
You know, it will never
simple. Never. You get people that say
that as well.
But yeah, I'll be sleeping today anyways.
Yeah, I've got no hope. I got no hope
whatsoever, bro. At least before like
the last month, I I was still holding on
to a little bit of hope, but I've got
none whatsoever now.
Um, so that's where we're at, lad. Yeah.
Yeah. You you can even you can approach
people and sometimes they'll just write
back off saying not interested, which is
like, hold on a minute. So these people
are telling you that you're going to
meet someone. These people are telling
you to keep trying. Let hold on. in the
past two days with two different people.
You've just tried to start a
conversation. They've just said straight
away not interested. How is it possibly
going to change? Like how?
It can't. It can't change. Yeah.
And I think if you keep trying, you'll
drive yourself to suicide. I'm telling
you, you will.
You know, it will never [ __ ] change,
bro. You don't need to waste any more
years here doing it. Yeah.
No hope whatsoever.
There's none whatsoever.
None whatsoever. Ever ever ever ever
You've just been ruled out by women just
like other people. Like there's loads of
other people that have as well.
You just have a vendetta against you
just like most other people. There's
nothing you can do to change it. It's mad.
Yeah, I was strongly thinking of suicide
yesterday, but I'm not even joking. had
some mad thoughts. Yeah.
Wouldn't you feel that way? Wouldn't
anyone else feel that way?
Look how mad Antman got. And he had even
tried nowhere near as much as I did.
Oh [ __ ] Franklin got hurt there, boy. You know,
and you can't even get laid either.
That's the thing is you can't even get laid.
Oh, [ __ ] Even if you wanted to get like
sex or whatever. I don't Or maybe you
don't even want sex. Maybe just some
people like spooning,
you know? You can't even get that.
So, there's nothing you could do.
I'll probably have to go to some sort of
therapy or something, bro, to because I
just can't understand how you've tried
all of them years
being decent looking and confident and
you've not found anyone, bro.
I generally need some sort of answers
from like a therapist or something or
someone cuz that is not normal.
That is not normal, you know.
But it will happen. It will happen. They say
so they say.
I'm not an I'm not I I'm not somebody to
say that I told you so, bro. Cuz if I
went out today, it would just be I told
you so. I already know the result before
I'd even tried
cuz I need some serious serious serious
serious answers, you know.
But I'm not somebody that says, "Oh, I
told you so. I told you so." Because
that's why I'm not going out today
because it would just be like, "I told
you the same old."
You know, it will just be the same old.
Same old. So, I'm not telling you to say
that I told you so, bro. Because it will
never it will never change. I don't need
to go out again to show you that it will
never change. Yeah.
But I'm not living in the moment
anymore. I'm back to a realistic amount of money.
All I've got is memories.
It's not really about the money, you
know. It's, you know, it's I I was happy
to have the money. I was happy to go out.
There's no point going in a shopping
mall. They've all got boyfriends.
It doesn't matter where you go. They're
all going to say they've got a boyfriend.
No, there's no point going around
shopping malls. They've all got
boyfriends. I used to approach in
shopping malls all the time before I
used to go cinema.
Same old same old women. Once you've met
one, you've met them all.
I was thinking of suicide yesterday,
bro. I can't lie.
6:00 in the morning, I went bed. [ __ ]
hell. And I woke up at 9 as well.
That's what happens when you got no hope.
That's what happens. You literally have no hope.
It's bad, is it? It's proper bad.
Nah, there's no point. They've all got
boyfriends. They've made They've made
their point. They've I've proved my
point and they've made their point. It's
time to leave now. It's time to move on.
It's time to move on. We're past that
now, bro. We're beyond that.
And we even tried when we gave up as
well when we went to Birmingham.
We're beyond that now.
We're beyond all that.
We're beyond it, bro. Respectfully,
we're passing it now.
That ship has sailed.
That ship has sailed, bro.
Yeah, that ship has sailed.
Yeah, that ship has sailed, lad.
Unless you've got a million subscribers
or a million followers.
You know, it's funny when you get people
on here that that want to try and start
an invalid argument about, oh, other
people in relationships, but the
funniest thing is most of the people
that you come across are actually single.
Like, I've got 189 people on my WhatsApp
and they're all single. Crap.
>> And they're all single, mate. So, like,
where the [ __ ] do they get these this
this millions of people? Because isn't
it funny how if it was truly was as the
millions as they say, then millions of
people have got to be single as well
then because like I said, most of the
people you meet will be single
and you come across single people all the time.
Isn't that funny?
So, all of them contacts are [ __ ]
single to be honest.
So, but it is funny when they try to
compare Nicolo, they generally think
that they've got
um Yeah, I know. Like, but they keep
comparing me to other people. They I
mean, I know, but they keep comparing me
to strangers. So, that's why I have to
bring it up. They seem to think that
just because there's people out there in
relationships that has What the [ __ ] has
that got to do with you?
What? because they might have got lucky
on a dating app or they might have got
lucky at work or they might have got
lucky years ago. And what's what's any
of that got to do with the situation
that you're in?
You know, even if you was to follow
their advice, I mean, I don't know why
they bring that up, you know?
It's impossible now. You can't find anyone now.
Like it's people got lucky, bro. That's it.
People [ __ ] got lucky for one of the
ways I said it. You didn't. You're [ __ ]
Your best bet was before all of this Tik
Tok and this Instagram [ __ ] come out. Uh, Asia,
what do I think of them? Um, good luck
to them, bro.
I would have thought, oh, I would have
got rewarded for my good deeds. I went
to Birmingham. I helped Monty. I helped
him get back with, well, I didn't help
him get back with Natalie, but I showed
him support. And I still get [ __ ] in
the ass by these women.
You know, it was quite long traveling in
all that way. So, some people truly are
meant to have no one.
I don't know why people can't accept that.
I don't know why people can't accept the
fact that some people are made for no one,
but I still think social media is a big
part of it as well.
If there was none of this Instagram,
there was none of this Tik Tok, you'd
have [ __ ] all over you.
That's that's the reality.
Can't get nothing now.
He's back. Yeah. Nice.
Yeah. I I I mean I I've I've
accepted that about a month ago
when when the house got took cuz I was
no live I was no longer living in the
moment cuz I always thought that like it
would have changed.
Like I never thought I would have ended
up like Ant-Man
because I always thought people would
have seen me different than him. You
know what I'm saying? Or I don't know. I
just thought that there was a chance I
might have been better in that way. But
I realized it about 3 weeks ago.
You know, after I got them 30 numbers, I
was like, "No, we need plan B now, bro.
No, no, no. We need to break the cycle
now because we can't keep trying this
year in year out, year in year out,
[ __ ] year in [ __ ] year out, trying trying.
Um, you need a plan B otherwise this is
going to continue to happen. Um,
so you know, I realized about three
weeks ago to be honest with you, but I
went to, like I said, I went to
Birmingham because of Monty and I won
the Football Bear. I had been out for
two weeks. That's the only reason I
went, bro. Like, and I would never heard
the last story of it if I never went.
Yeah, they I know. I knew it. Yeah. Oh,
yeah. I was speaking to one in
Birmingham, bipolar. Do you know what?
You know what she was saying?
Once you've met one, you've met them all.
No, but I I was actually getting some
serious suicidal thoughts last night, bro.
I I you know what? I was saying this to
my mom on the phone. Yeah. When they
took the house, they should have took me
with them. Like genuinely, bro, it's not
even about the money. I'm not too asked
about the money, but there was a lot of
things I lost because of that house. And
the money is not even like a big deal.
But I basically said like when they took
the house, they basically should have
took me with them to be honest with you
cuz um yeah,
no nothing to do with people on YouTube.
No. How can No, nothing to do with
people on YouTube. So yeah.
So yeah, I was speak Oh, by by the way,
bipolar. So you know that one I was
speaking to in Birmingham.
Nah, it's not even about the owner. I've
got savings. I've got savings. It's it
it Well, obviously it was that as well.
I lost tenants. I lost cooking. I lost a
house. I lost money. And then I had to
think about all of the bad experiences I
had with women
but which was enabled by that house
which was only 20% of it. Like when I
was lying in the house by myself, bear
in mind it's a big house. I was like
[ __ ] how didn't you meet anyone in all
of them years?
You did not meet no woman in all them
years. And I think that's what made me
depressed the most because you tried
more than anyone. And it's not even just
about the money, bro. It's not like
it's not even just that
cuz we're leaving now anyway, so it
wouldn't even matter. So, you know, it's um
um yeah, but I basically had to face
reality now, you know, that it will
never change. I'm not living in the
moment no more. So, that's it.
So, yeah. Anyways, I was speaking to
this one in Birmingham bipolar and she's
like, "Oh, I don't know how this is
going to work." Bear in mind we speaking
every day. There's a dis distance
between us. I was like, "Oh, we can meet
and see where it goes. We can see each
other every month. Birmingham's only the
Midlands." Then she turns around and
says, "Oh, I don't feel like I I I don't
feel the spark between us." And I'm
thinking, "Huh?" So you give your
number, you reply every day, you come up
with an excuse, which is the only reason
why you replied. And then when someone
has come up with something positive to
get around it, you've then just said you
don't feel a spark. You see what I mean,
bro? It it it's just the same thing with them.
Even at almost 28 years of age, you know? So
yeah, obviously that obviously they took it.
So So yeah, I've got like two grand left.
Um I'm not asked about money and
obviously I'm asked about losing the
money of course, but it's I had a good
time out of it and it's it's the whole
women thing. That's the worst thing
about it, you know, and obviously the
tenants and other things as well. You
should have met someone in them three
and a half years.
You should have met someone last week.
You should have met somebody the week
before that. Why can't you meet anyone? So
yeah, like I said, when they took the
house, they should have took me with them
cuz obviously you lose the income from
the house, you lose the tenants, you
lose the cooking, you lose the routine, and yeah,
the money wasn't even a big part of it,
to be honest with you.
But yeah, man. I ain't had a haircut in
a couple of weeks to be fair. What's the
point? They're not interested in this
country. They've made it clear enough, you know?
They've made it clear every [ __ ] week
for god knows three and a half [ __ ]
years. Sometimes even three days a week.
I never said I lost a I said I lost a
routine. So the money side of it was not
even because the way I told it is I
lived the life for 3 years. I don't mind
being on a little less income now. You
know, it doesn't matter. I've lived the
life. I've done what I've had to do. If
anything, it's more funner. And
eventually it was going to happen
anyways. So obviously, yeah, you lost a
lot of money, but you know, I've
adjusted to it now. Like at the start,
it was bad, bro. Cuz like you basically
lost most your income, but I've just
adjusted to it now. Just adjusted to it
now. Anyways, yeah, I won the football
bet last week. It's you're still better
off than most people cuz obviously you
adjust, but at the start it was bad. Yeah.
Um and the fact that I was thinking that
you shouldn't be dealing with this
alone. You should be with someone.
Yeah, they are, man. But that's what it
is. at at the at the start it was
but then yeah
there's nothing you can do you need to
leave the country or kill yourself
that's that's that's the only thing you
can do is you either kill yourself or
you leave the country like I said I
wanted to be took with that house bro I
like literally bro they should have just
like took me with that house bro I swear
cuz you lost a lot of things with that house. So
there's only there's only a way down now.
So the only way is down now.
Now I'm back isolated.
Maybe I can find a woman in Thailand.
You will find a woman in Thailand.
There's no maybe about it.
because no one cares. Everyone's out for themselves.
Now he's back in his relationship. He
doesn't give a [ __ ] No one cares.
No one No one gives a [ __ ] bro. As long
as they're okay, they don't give a [ __ ]
about anyone else.
That was long going to burn them as
well, bro. [ __ ] They don't care.
Yeah, they're back together. Yeah. So,
that's just people for you, is it?
But I really feel like I should have
died with that house generally
cuz like you've lost most your income on
it. You mean you're used to it now
anyways? But you lost most your income
on it. You lost the tenants. You lost the cooking.
You weren't isolated away from anyone.
You lost literally everything because of
that house. And you're still single as
well, which you shouldn't still be single.
So it's not looking good, bro. Is it? It
ain't good. Let's put it that way. Oh,
Timu. Yay. It's not good, is it, bro? So, yeah.
No, I don't. Yeah,
lucky have some money left. E, [ __ ] Um,
see I was living like a good See,
when I was doing the Uber and [ __ ] and I
had the tenants, I didn't have time to
think about this [ __ ]
cuz obviously I had them and then
obviously I had the Uber, but now I
don't even have that.
Now I don't even have that, bro. So
So I'm [ __ ] in
so many ways.
It's unbelievable. But as long as
everyone else is okay. Hey, Nicolo, no
one gives a [ __ ]
Yeah, nothing. Just depressed.
Oh, yeah. I've got the football bet here actually.
Um, Swindon, Cambridge, and Fleetwood
and Bristol Rovers.
Yeah, but what's he going to do, bro? He
ain't going to, is he? So, I got them
both teams to score,
which I'm not asked if it wins or loses
to be honest. I don't really care.
I put 80 pound on it. So So yeah,
I don't really know where you actually
go from here to be honest.
I don't know where you would actually even go.
What you'd even do from here
me girls that way. Nah, I'm good. Thanks, bro.
I'm thrown in the towel and I'm leaving
this country. I'm good, bro. I think
I've heard enough I've got boyfriends to
last me the rest of my life.
They're westernized. Again, I'll repeat
myself. It doesn't matter where you meet
them. The street, the club, the bar,
they're all westernized. They're all
stuck up. It doesn't matter where you
meet them. They're not interested in
this country. They've made it clear
enough year in year out, year in, year
out, year in, year out, you know. So
yeah, but the thing is, bro, like she's
not ever going to come out, so there's
no point. She's never going to come out
and say anything to anyone's face, so
it's pointless, bro. He's a coward.
You should have gave up from there,
really, to be honest with you.
You should have gave up from there. or
maybe like two months after he should
have like gave up from there. But I just carried on
to be honest. But yeah.
Yeah, I didn't go to bed till 6:00
yesterday. Greasy, man.
I was getting these [ __ ] depressing thoughts.
These suicidal thoughts, bro. I didn't
go to bed until like 6,
bro. And then I woke up at [ __ ] 9. Yeah.
That's filled with a lie when he says
the only way is up, the only way is
down. It will never change. So yeah,
just going to stay in bed today.
Depressed think. Yeah.
Yeah. Monty's nowhere to be seen out.
Nowhere to be seen.
No, I'm probably going to go back to
sleep to be honest after the football.
It's depressing, bro. I want to die,
They should have tipped me with that
[ __ ] house. I'm not even joking. But
I wish they tricked me with that [ __ ]
house. I'm not even joking.
Kind of wish they did, bro. I'm not even joking.
Yeah. Then the next day all of a sudden
they're not interested. Isn't that
funny, Nicolo? The good old I'm not interested.
The the old the old famous saying, bro.
Eh, the old famous saying I'm not interested.
The good old famous saying.
Yeah. The good old keep trying.
The good old I'm not interested.
That's all you're ever going to get here. Yeah, yeah, mouse.
That's where we're at.
It will never change
ever. I want to sleep. I want to watch
this bit more. Yeah.
Hopefully I die in my sleep today, bro.
It'll be [ __ ] lush. At
least I can say I lived a better life than Greasy.
This life ain't changing, matey.
This life ain't changing for toffee.
For toffee, matey.
Not for toffee, mate. No, I'm just going
to get a pizza. I'm just going to have a
pizza I got in the um in the freezer.
There's no way up from here, Grezy. It's only down.
There's no up. It's only down.
It's only down. Dad, do you believe in
that saying, Greg? It's only down for now. Definitely.
The only way is down, bro.
I was watching Oreo Man Nicolo last
night. I was watching Oreo Man.
Yeah, I was watching Oreo Man, lad. Yeah.
It's only down from now.
It's only down from now, man.
Well, at least we can just hope this
football bet loses.
You remember when Sean Mark done that
video before? I said, "I feel like doing something dafted.
I hope I go to the bookies and I [ __ ] lose.
I feel like doing something dafted."
That's like old school suicide mark. I
don't know if you remember.
And I hope I [ __ ] lose.
Do you remember that? Maybe remembers it in it.
Monty's nowhere to be seen now, is he? No.
Yep. Pretty much.
It's why I don't like people. It's why I
hate going out. I don't like people, you know.
Yeah. I thought he was going to do that
to be honest
cuz you can't trust people you got
history with, you know. I I thought I
thought Yeah. when I was going back to
the train station, he was going to hit
me from behind or something.
I generally thought, yeah, that like
yeah, he is going to try something
before I go on that train.
100%. I did think that that as well.
Look what Fras have done,
you know. Look what Fras have done.
Yeah, I would have. Yeah. Yeah, that's
what I was thinking as well. Yeah.
I thought I thought he was going to
attack me as well.
He was strong in terms of like squeezing
your hand, but I don't think he would
have beat me in a fight.
In terms of like an actual fight, I
don't think he would have beat me in an actual fight.
But who knows, you know. So yeah.
Why didn't you fight back? Um, I was in
Birmingham last Saturday and I called
out Timmy and Prime. They had their
chance when I was in both of their cities.
So that that's that's that's that's
my answer to your question is that I
called him out when I was in Birmingham
along with Timmy on Saturday and none of
them were anywhere to be seen. So yeah,
no none of them were anywhere to be seen.
same high as me.
Yeah, maybe, bro. Maybe.
This is boring, bro. This is boring now. Damn. Anyways,
I'm going. I'll be back later.