Oh,
these people are [ __ ] weirdos, bro.
Talking my [ __ ] bets and [ __ ]
It's so creepy. It's [ __ ] creepy, man.
These people are [ __ ] creepy as [ __ ]
There you go.
Yeah, man. [ __ ] proper creepy in it.
Proper creeps on this community.
That's another bet. That one
told you to get on it.
There you go. 350 in two weeks. Two Saturdays. Easy. Oh, [ __ ] you today. until
I told you I would go out here.
Maybe next week.
>> Yeah, man.
80 to 230.
It was 80 to 280 last week. Yeah, man.
What is it with these people keep
stalking my bets on this um large a channel?
That's 350 and two two space of two
Saturdays. Why the [ __ ] are these people
stalking my [ __ ] bets?
These [ __ ] weirdos on here, man. They
actually like they're such losers. It's
like they follow people's bet share to
see if they've um won or lost.
Yeah. I'm going to stop telling them my um
I'm going to stop telling him my uh football bets.
I've got a headache now, man.
Yeah, I'll collect it tomorrow. Couple days. Should
I eat today? Um,
no. I was going to have pizza. I've got
in the microwave, but I was kind of
fancying an Indian today.
Yeah, I won the football bet. Greasy.
That's That's 350 I've won in two weeks
just by going on picking teams.
Quite good, is it, bro?
Just going in the betting shop for like 2 minutes.
Imagine you done it every week here for
a month. It' be sick in it.
Yeah. I might get an Indian, bro. Um,
when am I out again?
[ __ ] knows, bro. Probably watch Superman
next week to be honest. Can't be asked
with the [ __ ] going out anymore. It's pointless. Um,
got to think.
Yes, I got that's 150. I won £151. Yay.
Twice in a row. That's good.
Yeah, they've been stalking my bets,
bro. They all do it. Trying to see that
if I lost or if I won. They're [ __ ]
stalkers, bro. Proper [ __ ] stalkers.
I've done a lot this month, bro. I went
to Birmingham last week as well.
You just go to Birmingham again doing
madness. Spend another £200.
Spend another 200. [ __ ] hell. Could
you imagine? But I do you know what? I
would actually do it. You know, if I
could actually get into the places, I
actually would just go back there. But
nah, man. [ __ ] that.
spend a lot last week, bro.
Yeah, he is.
Superman next week. Yeah, probably ready
to go out next week to be honest.
Yeah, it's a good bet, isn't it? 80 to
230. It was 80 to 280 last week.
It's not bad, is it? Really, bro? You
don't get the [ __ ] stress from
it will never change, bro. Never change.
But like I said, if I go out, it's
because I want to go out anyways. It's
not because of that. It's cuz I want to
go out. And it's not this week. I'm not
going out, bro. Even though I won that
football, I'm still not going out. It
will never change, bro. It will never change.
Just have a nice Indian.
No, it will never change. It will never Birmingham respond.
It's mad cuz I'm still semi- livingiving
the [ __ ] life, bro. It's madness,
isn't it? I [ __ ] Bro, look, I went
[ __ ] Birmingham last week, man. What
the [ __ ] That seems longer than a week ago. It
was [ __ ] crazy in it, man.
What makes you say things won't change, Grezy?
Nah, bro. Good.
Like I said, I don't know when I'll be
out again. I don't know. Like maybe next next,
next week, week after maybe. And then
put some extra body down for the football side.
So, I'd order KFC, but the thing is it's
too expensive. Reeves,
right? Let me order a bind, I think. [Music]
That's good football
just on fire.
>> It should be Um,
I got something. One second.
No, it was it was it was fun though. It was fun.
Last week was actually fun. But I'm not
Monty's friend anymore, man. Rice has
messaged me. I said to I said this to
Monty, man, as well. Like, I might have
Rice as a new friend cuz Rice actually
messaged me to see how I was doing.
He actually messaged me to see how I was
actually doing. So,
um maybe I'll just be friends with Rice now.
Somebody that actually cares for Peter Belly, you know,
cuz he's I've not heard from him since
he's got back with that
with that tart. You see?
>> No, but in all seriousness, I've not
heard from him since
>> Yeah. Hell with the [ __ ] menu, bro.
What the [ __ ]
Since he's got back with her, I've not
heard from him, bro.
You know, and I done a lot for him, you
know. I bought him some food. I bought
him some drinks. But this week, my money
is my money from the football back. You know, one sec.
I'm going to get a vindaloo, I reckon.
Going to get a lime vindaloo. Only
because a certain person can't have it.
Only because a certain person can't have it, mate.
You know what I mean? Certain birds
can't take that.
Um, right. And then obviously the ticker. No.
God must have really felt sorry for me
having having me win them football bets, you know.
Where the [ __ ] Hold on. Is that one sec, bro?
Oh, what a chicken tick off. What's that? Check.
Here we go.
Chicken ticket star.
That's okay with me, boss. £18.
Oh my god. So my [ __ ] god.
I'll be back later.