Yo, [Music]
yeah, man. I always win these football bets.
Yeah, you should have copied it. But I'm
not tell I'm not saying my football bets anymore, bro.
cuz um LJ's [ __ ] followers follow them.
They stalk my bets, bro. Oh, what the
[ __ ] going on?
Yeah, bro. They stalk my [ __ ] bets.
Proper stalkers, isn't it?
That creeps me out when they do that,
bro. They [ __ ] stalk my [ __ ] bets, man.
Have you seen it, bro?
They check to see like if your bet loses
and stuff. Yeah. I'm not saying my bets
on here anymore, bro.
That's how you know they're obsessed
on here and they're disabled because
why they why are they so focused on your bet?
Why do they stalk your bet? Why don't
they worry about their own bet?
Yeah, they don't. They don't copy it.
They stalk it.
So they want to make sure you lose so
they can laugh at you losing.
No, they don't. They didn't copy it. So
that's why I'm never saying my bets on here again.
I should have done a B I should have
done both score no draw.
Yeah, I should have done a both score no
[ __ ] draw, man.
No, they didn't.
But I'm not saying my bet on here ever again.
I still need to collect the winnings. I
don't know when I will. Can't be ass.
I'm nowhere near that bookies. So,
what about Monty? Monty's single now.
Yeah, Monty's single now.
I' I still got that video, bro.
Um, of, you know, that one in Nottingham,
the one that gave me a [ __ ] me
speaking to her in the hotel room.
I used to actually get [ __ ] but
something changed, bro. Something actually changed.
I used to get [ __ ] but something's
changed over the the past
year and a half.
I think it's Tik Tok, bro.
I think more people's been using Tik
Tok. Something's changed in 18 months.
I'm telling you, something's changed in 18 months.
Something's definitely changed. [Music] Well,
this is what I say to people. Yeah.
If it's going to change, what's the odds
of it changing? If it's not changed in
three and a half years,
um what's the what's the chances of it
changing now? What, like a million to one?
It's like it's got to be like a million
to one or something. So reading what you will,
but I might go Cardiff next week. I'm
not sure, but I'm not going to book a hotel.
Maybe I'll go Cardiff next week.
Maybe the week after. Depends how bored I am.
I don't go out every week. I go out
every two weeks or every 3 weeks or
there's no point going out every week.
Maybe just do an all nighter and come
back and do it all over again. Eh,
I don't know about maybe.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] in it.
I should have just stayed with that Nottingham one,
but I chucked her I chucked her out when
I when I um
I chucked her out when I came.
Yeah, I chucked her out when I came. I
should have stayed with her, man. I
should have at least got like another
[ __ ] in the morning. I was telling
her about you. I was telling her about
USA is he
I actually had chances back that year,
bro. But not this. Not since. I've not had nothing.
Yeah, she selfharmed. But a lot of them
self harm. Even that 19year-old
selfarmed. I don't know if she's still
done it, but she also self harmed. A lot
of them. A lot of them have.
You also know about USA is he think
I'm trying to get O Franklin get an airplane kills.
How does Monty do it? Monty doesn't do it.
Natalie G's met everyone on YouTube. She
even wanted to meet me.
So Monty hasn't done it.
He doesn't do it. And then he went and meet me. So
do you remember that one, Nicola? Yeah.
People thought I was mad. Yeah.
They thought I was mad, bro. They used
to think I was mad. Yeah.
Yeah. All alone.
They're all the [ __ ] same. It's sad,
isn't it? All the same.
You can see the Westinity in their eyes.
Like Ant-Man says, you can see the
Westinity in their eyes.
That's [ __ ] mad. It's like they
literally like watch Tik Tok and they
become like droids. Star Wars NPC
droids. It's true though. They're NPCs. Yeah.
You can see the Westinity in their eyes.
It's true though.
It is true. It is actually true. They've
got that evil look in their eyes.
Yeah, they've got that evil look in
their eyes, bro. Yeah.
Signal Peter Belly's mama.
Sign up Peter Belly's mama.
Yeah, it's funny, man.
I don't know. Maybe I won't grind next
week. It's pointless.
It's [ __ ] pointless.
Utterly, bro. Utterly pointless.
Yeah, but the thing is, if I go there,
she's going to call she's going to call the police
and then Peter Bell is going to get shot.
Isn't that right, Nikolai?
Yeah, they're horrible, man. I was
watching something in America where this
woman was cheating on this guy. Um,
you know, um, and then he ended up
getting shot by the police because he
lost it and I think he shot at the
police. And I was reading some of the
comments like women actually do ruin
people's lives. They actually do.
They're actually they actually ruin people's lives. Yeah,
I've still got two numbers that might
meet like in in a month or so. But
yeah, one was like they don't feel the
spark cuz they're not ready to date. So
in a nightclub, you give your number,
you text every day, but you don't want
to date. That makes sense, doesn't it?
And yeah, I've been dealing with this
[ __ ] for [ __ ] years to be honest. I
don't I don't think I will try again,
bro. I I actually have proved my point.
I was speaking to Ant-Man about this like yesterday.
I fell asleep all through, by the way. I
woke up my father in the morning and
it's like I I feel like I've actually
proven my point.
I've proved my point here, bro. I've
proved my point in these westernized countries.
Like serious, man.
Like on on a real though. On a real
>> Yeah. If I'm horny, then I'll just use [ __ ] escorts.
I'll just I'm just going Thailand. It's
simple. That's the whole point of going
to Thailand because you can actually get
laid. That's the whole point of going
Cambodia because you can actually get
laid. And some of them don't ask you for money,
which is the whole point of moving.
Yeah. So that's why you go to a country
where they're interested, then you don't
have that problem.
Think of it. Yeah. You go Thailand for a
month, 2 months. Yeah. You get all that
sex for 2 months and then Yeah. you come
back to England, but then you're off
again in another 4 months. So you've
only got to put up with it for 4 months
before you you go again. Like I said,
unless you're unless you've got a plan
B, you're [ __ ]
Unless you have a plan B, you are screwed. Literally, bro,
I was saying this to ad man, it's very
easy to think, oh, you got money or oh,
you won money. Oh, let's go out again.
But realistically, how how many years
have you been doing that for?
Yeah, it's weird, man. I didn't I didn't
even see any of it. I was sleeping, bro.
I fell asleep at 5:00 p.m. I woke up at
5:00 a.m. I was tired, man.
All that curry in it, Nicola. I had a
lovely curry. I might have I might get a
Chinese today. I'm not sure. Yeah. Yeah,
that [ __ ] cost me12. I did. I had
some piggies this morning. It cost me
[ __ ] 12 [ __ ] quid.
12 [ __ ] pound, bro.
Lucky I want to cut the football bets in
it this [ __ ]
past two weeks.
So yeah, Nicolo, you can you have to
just go to Thailand
or use escorts or something. Yeah, man.
>> Yeah, cuz Monty man wanted me to go
live. I just woke up and he said, "Oh,
go live. Go live." So, I went live. >> Yeah.
Probably just have a pizza, sir. I don't
know what I'm going to have. [Music] that.
Yeah. Well, good for them.
Good for them, man.
Should I eat today?
Yeah, I ain't had that in ages, man.
No, I've got a microwave pizza. I might
just have that. But there's a shop up
the road that says they've started
selling pizza. So,
[ __ ] expensive, man. Living's
expensive, bro. [ __ ]
Yeah, I might get a pizza, to be honest.
I've got a pizza in the in the in the in the freezer.
might have a nice pizza with some jalapenos.
Yeah, the Papa John's one is nice, isn't it?
Yeah, depends. Let me see if Papa John
doesn't get any offers on. I need to be
careful now, bro.
Never thought I'd be a normal person
again. Hey, Nicolai.
Not careful, but I do want to try and
save some money at the same time.
Let me see. Yeah, I ain't had Papa
John's in ages. I like Dominoes, but
I I had some piggies this morning,
Grezy. I had a whole pack of piggies.
Yeah, piggies. Had a piggy sandwich. Bye-bye.
See you later.
So, what is is Ant-Man right then? They
just aren't interested in this country?
You know what I find so strange is that
they make like dating seem so easy?
They make it sound like so simple.
Like Nicolo, they think, "Oh yeah, you
just go out and um
you know, you meet someone." But it's
literally like a job to to even try to
get a date.
>> It's like they make it sound like so
easy. like, oh yeah, you go out and you
just It's not as easy as that. They make
it sound so [ __ ] easy. There's
nothing [ __ ] easy about it.
Yeah, he does remind me of Mastag. The
eyes and that. Yeah, he does. Like the
eyes, you know, the eyes and the nose.
He has like the same facial features.
Yeah, he does. One second. Let me look
at this pizza. Let me see if there's any
deals on Oh, there's a large pizza for £12. Yummy.
50% off peaches when you spend £15 or
more. Okay, I'm going to go for that then.
But I fancy one with like jalapenos on
it though. I like barbecue, but I like
jalapenos and the two don't go. So, it's
either like you get the barbecue sauce
one or you get the [ __ ]
I want one with like jalapenos and beef and stuff.
Maybe get half and half.
Yeah, maybe get half and half.
What's that one in that barbecue
chicken? So, it's
So, it's barbecue sauce, chicken, and onions. Barbecue
It's not easy. It's not easy at all, bro.
I wouldn't mind if I was getting stuff
like the one in Nottingham with that.
I still remember the [ __ ] he gave me
as well. You can't get anything.
that year. I had [ __ ]
I had um
so many [ __ ] that year, bro. I think
everyone's got I think everyone's moved
to Tik Tok. That's why it's harder now.
Even though like we know Tik Tok was
made years ago, but I think more people
are using it.
That's why it's so hard.
I've been having that barbecue chicken pizza
since I was like [ __ ] 14. We've
been having that since I was [ __ ] 14, man. Yeah, literally.
Let me see.
Right. I want stuffed crust.
I don't know what pizza should I get.
Should I get half and half? One sec.
No. One second.
It's barbecue drizzle chicken, onions, and bacon.
Yeah, I want stuffed crust.
Stuffed crust. It's [ __ ] [ __ ]
I might just get the barbecue one to be
fair, but I'm trying to get stuffed
crust. It's not letting me add the stuff
crust. One second.
Without stuffed crust.
I can't have it without Stuff Crush.
Stuff cross is lovely, bro.
Yeah, I've got a video of me saying,
"How did you suck my dick so good to the
Nottingham one?" And she was like, "Um,"
she was like, "Uh, no comment."
Yeah, she was like, "No comment.
Oh, what a lovely site.
Why is it not letting me do?
Why is it not letting me do stuff?
I want to do half and half. One sec.
What the [ __ ]
Here we go.
I'm going to do half and half. One sec.
It's called It's called a drizzle.
Ah, no, you can do it. One second. One
second. Hold on, please.
Here we go. Uh,
I'm going to get a milk and a hot and
and barbecue. Yeah, pepperoni and
jalapeno is lovely.
Oh, mate, that's going to be a lovely
pizza. Half jalapino. One sec.
I'm going to get extra. I'm going to get
12 slices cuz I'm going to heat it up.
So, how much is that? Yeah. So, half hot
and half American. Yeah.
Is that all it is? £13 for that.
15. That is cheap, bro. And it's stuff
crushed as well. Okay, I'm going to get that. One second.
thing. One sec. Hold on. That's cheat.
Right. Order done. There we go. Lovely jobly. £24.
I got some wings as well. That was
actually not bad to be honest for the
amount I got.
Yeah, same man. Fresh start on [ __ ]
Monday. I need to be careful, bro. I
don't want to go [ __ ] broke. I'll be
like the [ __ ] virgin,
right? If I got takeaways every day,
give it a month, I'll be like that skin
virgin from Kent
who shows you benefit. I'll be [ __ ]
skinty. You need to stop this [ __ ]
mate. Frankie's coming out in a couple of days. Yeah, man.
Save enough money, huh? I got more money
than you. Bye-bye. Plastic.
He needs to stop showing his housing
benefit, Nicolo. Bro, he needs to stop
showing his housing benefit
cuz one day you're going to [ __ ]
charge him and you don't put it in quick enough.
You just stop showing your housing benefit off.
Trust me, mate. I haven't even cast this betting yet.
Oh [ __ ] man. [ __ ]
Yeah, they're going to they're going to
charge him one day, mate. He's not going
to pull it in quick enough and he's
going to get in trouble to cancel.
Do you know what I said? Hey. Hey,
Nicolo, you still there? Yeah. I'm going
to say something and I'll say it again. Yeah.
is that I don't know why all of these
people they go on about money all the
time. Money, money, money, money, money.
But the thing is, bro, like they've
never ever beat me at the money game,
which is why I'll never play the money
game with them again. And this is what
I'm trying to explain, bro. Money. What
is money to these people? Like Monty is
right, but he doesn't say in the best
way. I I could have £500 in my account,
only500, and I'd still have a better
life than them. I had a better life than
them when I was on [ __ ] £700 a month.
I was still having a better life than
them. Going out with Izzy, going out
here, going out there. It's like you
need for in order to make people
jealous, right? You need three things,
which is what I still have and had. You
need to be good-looking. You need money.
And you need a life. Do you understand?
These people have none of these things.
And even if they had money, well, bro,
they're sat on YouTube every day. It's
hardly anything to be jealous of. You
need you you can't just have money. It's
a It's a variety of things,
you know. I could have £4500 to my name
and I'd have I'd have a better life than them, you know.
That's the truth, lad.
Cuz you need you need it. You need a
better life, you know. Yeah, you asking.
That's why you beg for donations. Bye-bye. Now,
yeah, you asking.
That's why you bring it up all the time,
cuz you asking.
This pizza is going to be delicious.
Yeah, USA was USA Izzy was stinking as
well. It's not my fault I get attached.
See who my new mom is. Nikolai. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] my back, bro. Can't wait till
this pizza comes. [ __ ]
Yeah. USA speaks to me anymore. Nicolo. No.
She doesn't speak to me anymore.
I got a half and half.
Do you think she'll ever speak to me again? Nicolai.
So weird she turned like that, isn't it?
No one else has ever done that, you know.
No one else has ever turned like that.
Like even these numbers in Birmingham
and like other people they they don't
they did just block you. People don't
just block unless you had like a 5m
minute conversation. What a coward. E yeah
I say this to Laney sometimes like I
don't think you're I think you brought
the wrong you brought the wrong son
back. I don't think I actually am your
son. We've got completely different
taste buds. We don't look like anything.
Whereas whereas USA Izzy likes horror
films like me. We have the same taste
buds. We both like to travel.
So what's the chance is right that your
mama has nothing in common with you.
That's why I say sometimes Laney, you know,
I don't think Laney is my real mama.
No, Laney's all right, man.
Laney's all right. Laney's all right.
It's just what happens when you get old.
I'm [ __ ] getting old, man. I was I
had to run for the cinema. um the other
day and I had to stop like every [ __ ] 20 seconds.
I used to be able to run for buses and
[ __ ] [ __ ] non-stop. I'm [ __ ] getting old.
No, I'm not sure.
Oh, it's in the oven. I've just chucked
the pizza grooves and it's in the oven. Okay. Oh, lovely.
Be with me soon then. Yeah, mom. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, I used to like Domino's. Um,
I hope this [ __ ] Papa John's ain't [ __ ] allow.
Yeah, Franklin's coming out as well, huh?
Oh, it's expensive. E
Oh, don't remind me, mate.
Don't [ __ ] remind me.
I [ __ ] did go with that [ __ ] virgin.
Yeah, don't [ __ ] remind me,
lad. It's depressing.
I might do a video about that [ __ ]
wearing a pink top, saying that it's
it's you shouldn't be insecure about your sexuality,
you know. Um,
you know, cuz he said that the only
color he wouldn't wear was pink. I've
actually got a pink top and I'd actually wear it.
You know, there's nothing wrong
with with admitting what you are,
you know. And then all and all along I
knew it was this whole that was the
whole Cheryl Cole thing because he
doesn't want people thinking that he's
gay. Nothing wrong with being gay.
There's nothing wrong with if people
thinking that you're gay.
But trust me, I've I've looked into a
lot about this uh a lot in to this um
Sher Cole thing, and trust me, man,
there's nothing to write home about,
lad. It doesn't make you look cool. It
doesn't make you look clever.
You know, it's just copying. Copycat. A copycat.
No one likes a copycat, Nicolo.
Yeah, I did.
Yeah, pineapp I've had pineapple on
pizza. It's [ __ ] stinking, bro.
I've actually had that on pizza. It's horrible.
If you don't find I'm I'm not saying
that you finding her attractive makes
you copy. It's the whole you're um
It's the whole you're saying that other
people are gay if if she doesn't if you
don't find her attractive. Yeah. That's
literally copying cuz Nicolo, right?
What if you only like black women? What
if you only like blonde women?
What if you only like Scandinavian women?
There there is some people out there.
So, does that does that mean they're gay
then? Oh, does that mean they like [ __ ] then? Okay.
So, how how would that make someone gay?
I don't understand.
Really don't understand. That's just copying.
No, no. I'm using as an example.
I'm using it as an example.
That USA Izzy is looking very old
lately, Nicolo. it.
So you get £1,200 a month.
Yeah, I made 14 this month because of
the football bets.
It's not loving life, bro, on that
amount of money.
But it is good. Yeah,
you're not working. Yeah. Soon as I can
work again, I'm working every day. Soon
as I get one of these delivery jobs
again, I'm working every day.
Bam. Make £1,000 a week.
How do you remember these things, Nikolai?
You must been around for quite a while.
Oh yeah, and there was some white
knight. He says, "Oh, I don't think it's
a good idea you touch her boobs and
stuff." We was kissing. I was like, "Why
don't you mind your own business, you
little white knight?"
Yeah, there was a white knight from Poland.
She just broke up with her boyfriend.
She wanted dick.
I kind You know what? I kind of missed
that O'Neals. You know, that's where I
met all the army friends.
Yep. You are back on YouTube again.
You've just commented.
Yep. You're on YouTube. Yes, you are.
Do you know who I've not seen for ages?
You know that Ryan Hansen?
That one from Sunderland that used to
come on the um
that used to come on um the Hangouts,
the the one from Sunderland.
His name was Ryan Hansen. Sure someone
will remember him.
Well, it doesn't matter. You're still on
[ __ ] YouTube, so
doesn't matter, mate. Go off YouTube
just like Ryan Hansen. Not see I was
thinking about that the other day.
Yep. Yeah. And I'm seeing you again.
Bye-bye. I'll get rid of you.
So yeah. Oh, it's on its way. Yay.
So yeah, I've not seen that Ryan handsome.
So what? Nicolo, you want me to go
Cardiff on? You want me to go Cardiff next Saturday?
Could give it a whirl,
but I'm not booking a hotel.
That makes me sound skinned. I'm really
really [ __ ] not.
Like the whole idea is you go out. You
Yeah. And I told him I said, "Yeah." I
said, "Fuck off, you simp." I said,
"Yes, I am bothering her. What the [ __ ]
are you going to do about it, you [ __ ] s?
The whole idea is
Yeah. Do you remember? Do you remember
that American guy?
Yeah. Um, do you remember that American
guy as well? He said, "Don't talk to." I
said, "I'll talk to who the [ __ ] I
want." Silly y thinking you're going to
come to my country and tell me who I can
talk to, bro. You're you're [ __ ]
you're you're trying trying to take
liberty. Talk to who I [ __ ] want.
They used to get smashed up, bro. Every
week they were Americans in their own
hills cuz they used to fight with the
army people. So they had to stop letting
the army people in cuz obviously they
couldn't discriminate Americans because
obviously some of them came over on holiday. So
um they used to get [ __ ] up. Yeah,
bro. They they Yeah, they they try to,
but then when you tell them about
themselves, they can never finish it.
Now, I'd actually respect one of them if
they could actually finish it.
They start, but they can't finish it.
That's what they do. I would respect one
if they could actually finish it.
Anyways, the idea, Greavesy, is you go
to Cardiff or Birmingham or wherever you
go and then you do an all nighter, you
get drunk, you get numbers, then you get
back to you get back to um
you get back to um the nest calls
at like [ __ ] 8:00 in the morning and
text the little numbers and then you
wake up to some lovely replies.
Yeah, I don't know why they do it, but still.
Yeah, that guy that was when I was when
I kissed that one from Kenya, that was
definitely jealousy. Definitely,
because they're scared to do it themselves.
I remember when Tam watched me do an approach.
I remember Tam Tamley's friend watched
me do an approach. That's how we started
arguing, me and Tam.
You know, Tommy was he watched me in the river spins.
But what about what about going to leads
to do an all nighter, Nicolola?
Go to Leeds next Saturday, do an all
nighter and come back. You do it every
week, isn't it? Just go do an all
nighter somewhere and get the the first train back.
What What do you think?
What do you actually think, bro? That's
sick, isn't it? Nah, I don't know about
leed, bro. Oh, I don't know about leads.
I don't know about that. [ __ ] that. That's long.
You should do it like one week
Newcastle, one week leads. No hotel,
just straight in it with a Well, I don't
have a I'd have to renew the rail card. Um,
yeah. One sec, bro. Leads, Newcastle,
Scotland. [ __ ] You'd be [ __ ] bro.
You'd be shattered when you come back.
You'd be shattered, in it.
Yeah, you'd be [ __ ] You'd be [ __ ]
You would actually be [ __ ] The
Newcastle one would be a killer in it, I reckon.
Cardiff's quite easy. Birmingham's quite
Well, no, it's not easy. They're still
far away, but Newcastle will be the killer, bro.
That will be hard.
going all the way there doing an all
night and then coming back.
[ __ ] I don't know about that, bro.
You probably die on the [ __ ] train
back or something. Kill it. Greasy.
Yeah, you'd be [ __ ] You'd be [ __ ]
up. I know. I know the shortcuts now, lad.
Yeah, that's one of the That's the
reason why I'm thinking of going Cardiff
on Saturday, cuz at least you actually
get replies. You don't get replies in London.
So then if they reply then at least it
gives you somewhat hope. There's there's
no point in London because they don't reply back.
And if they do reply back, they don't
reply like they replied back. All of
them replied back like
with with with enthusiasm.
This is what I was saying to Monty man.
Yeah. Not Monty man, Antman. If I was if
I lived out of London, I would be out
every week. Like if I lived in another
even though it is the same everywhere
and it's [ __ ] everywhere. It's the same
England, but it's like if you get if you
got three numbers and you got free
replies. Yeah. Imagine you done that
every week for a month.
Yeah, you could test it in it. But in
London, there's no point. You don't even
get replies back. So there's no point
going out here.
You should get the [ __ ] replies when
you go out on London. And they actually
reply. They actually reply with interest
as well. That's the thing. All of them
numbers reply back with interest.
All of them. And they kept replying. So,
I mean, it's better than not getting a
[ __ ] reply in it. So,
the only And it And it's rare to get
free replies, bro. to get three replies,
three numbers, and all of them reply
like that. It's not a coincidence.
>> It's not, oh, you just got lucky once cuz Yeah.
I think when I got there there's times I
used to go out in London, bro, I used to
get six I used to get five to eight
numbers and sometimes none of them would reply.
Sometimes none of them would.
Yeah. You can go out and you can get six
numbers and none of them reply.
I'm not even joking. And then you get
three and then all of them reply. But
that ship has sailed I think with London, bro.
I'm trying to think where else I've been.
But again, it's only one day. But
there's no point going out in London, bro.
It's a cockfest. Everyone's more sucker pointless. Pointless.
I can't believe them bounces though.
Nicolo, you still there? You have to go
in with a group of girls. What the [ __ ]
Why the [ __ ] would you be going into a
club if you had a group of girls? I
called him a s.
Yeah, I call him a [ __ ] S, bro. One sec.
My pizza's here. Yeah. So, I'll be back later.