[ __ ] hell.
was in Jaden. What's this?
I know, man. Yeah. I was watching Jaden
and I was waiting for her to say
something about me.
I was waiting for her to say something about me. Yeah.
I was waiting for it, bro. But she never Yeah, man.
She's a nasty [ __ ] bro. It [ __ ] It
winds me up. Yeah. Just watching it,
even though she They're not doing it to
me. They're doing it to Monty. Just like
watching it just winds me up. I swear to
God, bro. It just winds me. I was just I
was just waiting for her to say
something about me.
Trust me, you don't want to [ __ ] with me, mate.
Look what thing you got. And they didn't
they didn't even live here.
They didn't even live here, bro.
Yeah. That was annoying me just watching
that Natalie G, bro. It's annoying, bro.
Like going on a panel with them [ __ ]
snakes and [ __ ]
You know what I mean? It's annoying, bro.
It's [ __ ] annoying. It's actually
annoying, bro. Watching it.
Let me see what's his channel.
Is she actually going or what? Shard.
Get a going, man.
Yeah, Sheffield's nowhere near [ __ ]
Sheffield's nowhere near Nottingham. Madness.
You know, if somebody was doing that to
me, I would have smacked them up, bro. I
don't care if they're a [ __ ] woman,
bro. Yeah. I didn't like what I was watching.
Yeah. I I wasn't liking what I was
watching, bro. Even though it weren't
happening to me. And Yeah. Me and
Monty's had our differences in the past,
bro. I don't like [ __ ] like that. I
don't like [ __ ] like that, bro.
I told him that if she goes there, smack
her in her mouth, bro. [ __ ] her. Ain't
it? She snaked enough [ __ ] times.
Yeah. Some people need like a like the
thing is, right? Some people Yeah. Yeah.
They need They need that, bro. They need
a thick and she's one of them, bro. Cuz
she's [ __ ] with a few people on this
YouTube, you know? He's not the only
one. And no one's ever done anything.
That's what that's what need that's what
that's what he needs to do, bro.
Give him a give her a [ __ ] thick
hair. [ __ ] her being a woman. Who gives
a [ __ ] Just do it, bro. I would. If
someone's going to try if someone tells
me they're coming to my to to where I am
and they're coming to my hostel or
wherever I'm staying and you're going to
[ __ ] with me, bro, it's on. I don't care.
It's bad, bro. It's I didn't like what I
was [ __ ] listening to. And then
someone brought me up and I was waiting
for any excuse to get involved, bro. Any
excuse to get involved.
But he didn't say anything about me.
Yeah. Don't [ __ ] You best not, bro.
Trust me, with me, you'd be meeting your match.
You'd be meeting your match, bro. Don't
you worry about that. Look what happened
with that USA is that she weren't even
in this country. Yeah.
No, it's annoying, bro. I don't like it,
I don't agree with any of it.
I think it's [ __ ] wrong.
Not even funny, bro.
She's a [ __ ] proper snake, is it?
She wouldn't shag me because I I've been
with escorts. Listen, I wouldn't shag
you if you if you was the last woman on
earth, which is why I didn't shag you
when I was 22.
I would have got you I would have got
with you if you was the last woman on earth
and I was actually a virgin. That's how
bad it is.
She's a [ __ ] bro.
I don't like what I was watching.
It's bad. Is it? Really bad. Yeah. What? madness. Madness.
[ __ ] madness, lad.
You should have never met her in it, bro. Yeah. Mad. It's mad. [ __ ] bro.
That is a madness, bro.
To Monty, man. You need to do the same.
I said, "Yeah, if that Natalie G was
doing all that [ __ ] to me, I would [ __ ]
her up, bro.
I would actually [ __ ] her up." I was
watching that Jaden's live stream back.
I was watching some of it back,
bro. No one would be doing that to me,
boy. Believe that. I don't care if
they're a man. I don't care if they're
[ __ ] woman. I don't give a [ __ ]
Simple, bro. I said that if you go if
she goes there, you need to slap her up.
Yeah. I said, bro, like you need to [ __ ]
it. You need to [ __ ] her up, bro. I
swear down. That's what I said he needs to do. Yeah,
I would [ __ ] do it. Someone was
trolling me like that. I would, bro.
Yeah. And then they and then they come
to my And then they're going to come to my city
or where I'm living and come to my
hostel. Bro, that ain't happening. Madness.
And this is why I don't meet someone on
YouTube. This is why you don't meet a
woman on YouTube.
Because this is exactly what happens. madness. Yeah.
Yeah. I told him Mont wanted to come in the box. Look.
Madness, boy. Madness. Mad. [ __ ] knows.
[ __ ] knows, right?
No, she's a darling.
I was crying over some [ __ ] dead
girl. No, she's a darling.
She's a darling, love.
That's going to reply back.
Yeah, someone's going to get section
over this YouTube it. I told him you
need to get off YouTube.
I told him he needs to get off YouTube.
You need to get off of YouTube, man. [Laughter]
I told him to come in the box. You know,
somebody's actually going to get
sectioned over this YouTube. Yeah.
Yeah, I spoke to him earlier, bro. Madness. What's up,
Watch that come.
I'm laughing that belly, bro.
I think it's [ __ ] out of order, me.
I think they're all [ __ ] That's what I think. Yeah.
What a [ __ ] What a nasty [ __ ]
[ __ ] it up.
Is she actually going that N?
I was just thinking. Yeah, when I was
watching that live stream, bro.
Um, when I was watching that live
stream, I I was um I couldn't stop
thinking of like Tom and Jerry like this
is mad, bro. The [ __ ] that's going to go
on this [ __ ] what's going to go on
this community today is the same website
you can watch Tom and Jerry on.
You know, the same website you can watch
Tom and Jerry on. The same [ __ ]
website a [ __ ] child can go on.
You know, anyone would think it's just so innocent,
you know, needs to be shut down. This
whole YouTube thing, you know,
this whole YouTube thing needs to be shut down.
It's bad, bro.
Yeah, it's not nice. It's horrible, bro.
I wish you done that to me, bro. I'd
give her a [ __ ] slap across her [ __ ] face.
I was waiting for her to talk [ __ ] about me, bro.
I actually I was waiting for her to talk
[ __ ] about me cuz someone brought me up,
but she didn't say anything about me cuz
trust me, she would meet her match with
me, mate. Trust me.
Like even watching it is annoying, bro.
Seeing how much of a snake she is. Yeah.
I don't even like watching it,
you know? But because obviously it's not
about me. I can't do anything. But trust
me, she she'd meet a match with me, bro. Trust me,
that [ __ ] USA did and she weren't
even in this country.
Yeah. I said to him, if if you see her,
just slap her up.
She's [ __ ] with you on the internet.
She's purposely going out of her way to
[ __ ] with you and she's not leaving you
alone by coming to where you are. [ __ ]
her. Just slap her across her face.
That's what I said to him.
Yeah, go on.
I'm not I'm not just saying that, bro.
Like, I'm being serious.
She's actually going out of her way to
[ __ ] with him.
You know what I'm saying? And trolling
and trolling him on channels. You know
what I'm saying?
I said just if you see her, slap her up.
That's what I said. Wait at the train
station and just slap her up, bro. 100.
It's bad. It's out of order, man.
I bet Antman's glad he got off this [ __ ] in it. Yeah.
[ __ ] hell, man. I can't believe that
belly is still on YouTube. Yeah.
Message me on Facebook.
If that's the real you, ring me.
That's not the real Monty.
Just a pizza.
That's the real you. You can you can ring me.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Mad
[ __ ] Madness, bro.
This YouTube's supposed to be innocent. You know
how do you reckon this YouTube thing is
going to end, Astron? I think someone's
going to end up dead on here.
I actually think someone's going to end
up dead on here, bro.
Some end up dead on here, bro. I can see it happening. Is that
that good vibes stalking me. Look at
that. Good vibes only stalking me.
You're a [ __ ] weirdo.
Ah, what a weirdo, man.
Stop stalking me. Good vibes, you little coward.
Oh, he's stalking me. He goes on my
channel. He's a stalker. Creepy old men.
This community is full of creepy old men.
You [ __ ] creep. You creepy bastard.
Why are you watching me, you [ __ ] creep?
That good vibes only is a [ __ ] creepy old man. Creep.
[ __ ] creeps, man.
How the [ __ ] can you compare me to
[ __ ] nons legs?
How the [ __ ] How can I be compared to
that [ __ ] nod legs, man? Come on.
My [ __ ] Virgin has a channel reacting
to me every day.
reacts to me every day of his life. How
the [ __ ] can you [ __ ]
How can you re um me to that virgin?
Bro, this is crazy, man. [ __ ] hell. M
I told him he needs to just get off of YouTube.
I'll be back later anyways. Yeah, I'm
going to go onies.