Yo,
well, he said go live.
Yeah, I don't know.
I want this to go live. So [ __ ] hell. Come on.
Who's going to turn up?
Molly asked me to go live. I'm waiting
for him to join.
I didn't know that Penny Bunny watches me. about it. 25
I remember going to Sheffield.
It's the It's It's West Midlands, isn't it? Sheffield.
Yeah, I like Sheffield.
It's in the West Midlands, isn't it?
King's Cross. Is she a [ __ ] [ __ ]
Think I'm on the train. King's Cross. Is
she a [ __ ] [ __ ]
What the [ __ ]
King's Cross is [ __ ] London, you
Nah, she's got to be trolling. Don't be that stupid.
Nah, bro. Is she actually that she can't
be that thick?
What the [ __ ] King's [ __ ] cross.
It's [ __ ] London. Nah,
no one could be that stupid boy. No way.
She got to be trolling, bro.
She's not going to be having sex with
me. I'm not [ __ ] meeting her. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, when you're watching me, good
vibes, you little freak. Stop watching
me, little old M. You [ __ ] old man.
You sad skin little old man. You little Laur [ __ ]
You fat ugly old man ain't got a life.
You fat ugly old man that sucks that
sucks LJ's dick.
Why do I not have him blocked on these things?
Yeah, I don't know why I don't even have
him block. You [ __ ] old man. Bye-bye
now you [ __ ]
Fingers crossed. What the [ __ ] How the
[ __ ] can you end up there? Jesus Christ.
She [ __ ] is a [ __ ] [ __ ]
She is a [ __ ]
Praise her. Praise her done that once.
Got no friends. I got more. Oh, you're
blocked as well. by [ __ ] I don't
entertain keyboard warriors. So, I just
saw that [ __ ]
that name. I was actually going to
entertain it for a second.
Yeah, I don't entertain um obsessed keyboard warriors. [ __ ] nerds.
She has to bang me. I'm not banging her.
I will never bang her. If she was the
last woman on earth, I'd never [ __ ]
bang her. [ __ ] that.
He has a huge talking about yourself.
These aren't established accounts.
Yep. talking about yourself. Come up
with some new comebacks. You repeater.
Anyways, um yeah, I just block these
repeaters, bro. Soon as I see them, like
that coward red star, I just block them.
I don't even entertain them.
So, you going to join or what, bro? You
asked me to go live. Are you going to
join or what?
Are you going to [ __ ]
join or what, bro? You asked me to go
live. What the [ __ ]
Yeah, all of them skint comments, bro. I
just ignore them because they're just self projecting.
I don't react to these projected idiots,
these low life nerds on YouTube, man. I
don't react to them.
Like, we've said enough about them a
million times. We don't need to say the
same stuff over and over again. I don't
react to these idiots. These projectors,
idiots. I didn't play Black Ops for a
while, bro. Might play that later.
Maybe maybe she she's just never traveled before.
But I I've traveled a lot, so I know
like everywhere. But that's how I knew
the train and train station to go Birmingham. Good luck.
We not flown before by myself as well. Strange. Yeah.
>> Yeah, it's fine. Soon as she turns up.
Yeah, she's getting arrested. I've
already told the staff. The staff
already know. So, it's not going to be noon.
Money. She's got the wrong train. Is she?
>> Yeah. She's got the train to London.
Yeah, it's fine then, is it? It [ __ ]
[ __ ] She's going to get arrested anyways
because of all these little clowns in this community.
>> That's it. I'm done with N. I'm done
with her. I'm not crying for that woman no more. >> Yeah,
>> I'm getting this tattoo covered up on my
arm and I'm going to put women a blackarted. >> Yeah,
>> that's what I'm going to do. Get a
tattoo covered up and put women are
blackarted. I'm going to get it colored
all in black and pop women.
>> That's what I am going to do. That's
what I'm going to do.
>> And my mom said if she comes down say
she's going to get my cousins down to
kick her [ __ ] head in. >> Yeah.
>> So either way, she's going to get killed
if she comes down here. One way she's
going to get arrested or battered. Not
by me, by my cousins.
>> She's on the way. Well,
>> that's a bit thick, is it?
>> She ain't [ __ ] coming to me, Shag.
I'll [ __ ] I'll [ __ ] kick her in the [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm not going out with that, man.
She's a [ __ ] psycho, man. She's
[ __ ] up, mate.
>> I don't want a woman like that. Really,
I don't. I don't.
>> You don't. This is why you don't date
women off YouTube, bro.
>> This is why
>> that's why I always used to say like
remember you always say that, bro.
>> Yeah, but I thought I gave her a chance
and all that cuz she was nice. I [ __ ]
love that. I've done nothing to Natalie.
Nothing at all. But just ask ask a girl
to come come shut. Oh, listen listen listen. >> Okay.
>> [ __ ] her, bro. She's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, look. I am. I'm kicking women,
>> bro. Look at what she was doing yet on
the [ __ ] Hangouts with all of these
people. [ __ ] her, bro.
>> I am. I am. And what she done last
night, it's over. It's over. It's
completely over. I'm not going out with
a woman who exposes herself all over
internet like that. It looks like
>> Why Monty? When Monty, when did you last go Sheffield?
>> [ __ ] No.
>> No. But when No, but when was the last time? Seriously?
>> I don't know. I don't know.
>> Are you sure you've been there before?
>> Sheffield? No. Not too sure.
>> Yeah, ages.
>> Look at all these little clowns in this
community. Not one of them will come and
[ __ ] meet me. They got to go and get
Natal Natalie to get arrested. They're
using Natalie. That's what they're
doing. They're using her. I know what
the game is. That J that Jaden lives in
Sheffield, is it? Yeah.
>> J's more welcome to meet me. Any of
these old towns are welcome to meet me
if they about it. PJ if they about that lie.
>> Natalie's not even about that life. See,
I I don't whack women, but that is just
going to get arrested straight away.
>> I would get I would I would whack her.
She don't I would do it, bro. She
>> No, no, I don't whack women, mate. I
don't whack women. I'm a good lad like
that. what it is. It's not my fault that
she's [ __ ] jealous over me just
taking a girl to the shop. I was with a
[ __ ] mate. That girl were getting
bullied off a [ __ ] lad. >> Yeah,
>> she were getting bullied. So I thought
to myself, [ __ ] it. You might as well
just come with us. I've even told this
girl I've got a burn. She knew I had a
girlfriend. It wasn't like that
whatsoever. I don't even like this girl.
I just didn't want her getting bullied.
And if they can't see that, then she's a
dumb [ __ ] It doesn't mean anything.
It's trust. If you don't have trust in
the relationship, don't be in one.
Obviously, she don't have trust in me.
So, what the [ __ ] am I doing in this relationship? >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean?
>> If you don't have 100% trust in me and
she wants to threaten me and get pissed
entertain these little [ __ ]
pedophiles in this community. Yeah.
People, you are little pedos. You are.
So, you won't call me one cuz you are
the real ones in this community. Little
[ __ ] clowns. I love any of you to
come and meet me. I love you. I love any
of you. You know where I am. Workshop.
Where the [ __ ] are you?
You [ __ ] idiots, m
your faces in completely. You little [ __ ] clowns.
All of you. You all can come together.
All of you. Come on. Even the [ __ ]
three great guys. So why don't all three
of you come right now instead of getting
a woman to do your dirty work? Look at
that pier. You're working out, mate.
>> What's up?
>> Come on.
>> What's happening [ __ ]
>> What's happening you little clown?
>> How's life? How's life?
>> Fantastic. Fantastic life when I can
talk to any bird I want to. Found [ __ ] sastic.
>> We on your team.
>> Oh, don't go in that [ __ ] You little
Irish little kid little [ __ ]
>> I kicked him. We don't want N here.
>> I didn't know who it was, bro. I kicked
him. He's Scottish.
>> Yeah. Look at that. That's what you call
a workout, peeps. That's what you call a
sexy ass body. Oh yeah.
>> You know what I was thinking? Yeah. I
was thinking Yeah. This is so mad how
this is the same website you can watch
this Tom and Jerry [ __ ] on, bro. It's
[ __ ] scary, isn't it?
>> Who's coming? >> Huh?
>> No one.
>> Exactly. No one.
>> Natalie's done anyways. I'm done with
Natalie now. I'm I'm done with her. If
she wants to come and sort [ __ ] out, she
can. She can. But we need a long [ __ ] talk.
>> Watch cartoons on.
>> Yeah, I know. Entertaining these little
weirdos, man. You ain't got a life. Come on, man.
>> Come on, Natalie. I thought you were
better people. Why not? It only kicks one person.
>> Why? Because at the end of the day, we
don't want to talk to little weirdos
like you at the end of the day, to be
honest with you. Why kick people? Cuz
you're all weirdos. Why the [ __ ] do I
want to entertain full grown adults who
like [ __ ] children?
Come on. We don't entertain them.
You know what I mean? We don't entertain
[ __ ] jealous ass [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Someone someone asked lately would
would she sag me and she replied she
wouldn't sag me because I've been with escorts won't
>> yeah no it's [ __ ] worse mate it's
worse I shouldn't have even gone near
mate I just I shouldn't have I [ __ ]
shouldn't have I am getting myself
tested I am I'm going tomorrow actually
getting tested tomorrow but she did she
>> she did have black fanny flaps I'm not
just saying that mate
>> I'm just I am getting tested No, she
did. She did.
>> No, she asked. I'm not lying. I swear
down there my dead baby brother.
>> This is This is a funny comment. Yeah,
Dylan will be enjoying freshly freshly save.
>> I'm done, man. I'm done with her. I'm
done with her. I'm done with her. She
wants to play these little [ __ ] mind
games with me. Yeah, I'm done. Yeah. I
didn't even do a wrong one because a
girl on your live if you want if she
wanted to watch some shop. Is that bad? No,
>> exactly. Does that not mean I'm cheating on her? >> No,
>> exactly. Yeah. And she's getting the
wrong idea completely. This what I mean.
Well, be asked with the [ __ ]
stressiness, mate. I had it with Kayie.
I had it with Kay. Now I'm having it with Natalie.
>> Who? Who? Who's worse than Katie in it? Yeah.
>> They both are [ __ ] same, mate.
They're both the same. is because
Natalie's not being loved by your mom or
her [ __ ] dad. Yeah. And it's the same
as Kelly. Kelly's never being loved by
your mom and dad. And that's where all
the [ __ ] hate comes where
that's what not to bring this up. Yeah.
Not to bring this up cuz we both hate
the person, but that's where n
>> I don't hate Natalie. This is the thing.
I don't hate her.
>> His mom stared and [ __ ] in it.
>> Yeah. This is a thing. I don't hate
Natalie. I [ __ ] love Natalie. I I do.
I really [ __ ] do.
>> But if Natalie believe that I love her
and she's got someone who actually loves
her for who she is and actually wants to
be with her.
>> Monty, not Monty. Listen, bro. Yeah. Not
to bring the person up because we hate
them. But that's where nonsexist
weirdness comes from because your mom
starve them and [ __ ] You know what you
were just saying.
>> I'm not bothered about these little be.
Everyone needs Everyone needs like um a
mommy figure because you know a mom's
bond is stronger than a dad's bond. You get me?
>> Yeah. Of course it is. Of course it is.
And this is where Natalie gets a [ __ ]
anger from because of her mom.
>> She's feeling
>> he was like, you know.
>> Yeah. She's feeling unloved and she
thinks because her mom and them don't
love her, she thinks no one loves her. I
[ __ ] love her. Why the [ __ ] would I
get a tattoo on my hand if I didn't love
her? Do you know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> If I if I didn't love her, I wouldn't
have gotten this tattoo.
I've never done that woman in my life.
Not even [ __ ] just go and [ __ ]
find someone else, bro.
>> The thing is, TJ, I'm not that kind of
person to [ __ ] to talk to her next
girl. Maybe I've done
>> You should You should have done it with
me when we was at Birmingham. You should
have joined it, didn't it?
>> No. No. PJ N needs to understand she's
getting played by these little idiots in
this community to go and do [ __ ] so she
gets in [ __ ] Yeah, these little clowns
won't do [ __ ] theelves. Yeah, the [ __ ]
bad. You don't see L J coming to me or
you don't see that other Irish guy
coming to me. You don't see anything
from me coming. Every time I open Lord
J. What the [ __ ] is he? >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? Lord J's a little
pedophile lover who sts his kids all
over [ __ ] you. You little [ __ ] clown. M
>> you know what I mean?
>> And then you got all these little
[ __ ] idiots who go around.
>> I think Monty, I think eventually I'm
quitting YouTube eventually. You know,
>> it all herself anyway. She She really
>> What you going to do? What you going to
do, Monty? When I when I uh when I quit YouTube,
>> this ain't with it, PJ. It's not with
it. Ni should have understood this [ __ ]
I was only taking a shot to get away
from a [ __ ] bully. You know who that bully is.
>> He's [ __ ] Dillard. He's a [ __ ]
prick. And if N wants to shag him if she
can, it's not going to make me it's not
going to [ __ ] affect me whatsoever.
>> It just shows that she's It just shows
that that she's a slag and she sleep
with a [ __ ] scruffiest slag in that
place. Believe me, that lad is the
scruffiest lad in that place as well.
This growth he is. He doesn't bath. He doesn't shower.
>> I can't believe I can't believe you ate her out.
>> Well, I'm the best she's had anyways.
I'm the best she's ever had.
>> That's [ __ ] crazy.
>> Yeah, but I am the best he's ever had.
And this is
>> You was probably You was probably
licking like some next man sping.
I'm not saying what I was licking, but
[ __ ] hell. She kept on coming.
That was probably the last man's com she had.
>> At the end of the day, at the end of the
day, PJ, this woman's got a good man
here who actually does love her, mate.
He will give her what she wants. You
know what I mean? She doesn't have to
get jealous over the next girl who I'm
talking to. I'm not going to jump in bed
with the next girl. Am I [ __ ]
>> Natalie needed to understand. She's the
only one for me. I already asked that
girl to come shop. I don't regret it, do I?
>> [ __ ] [ __ ] Mongo's scared of Trixie.
That's repeating. Bye-bye.
>> Scared of Trixie. I'm not scared of
>> I had a few slices. I'm going to have
the rest later. I'm going to microwave
it. Greasy. It was lovely. It was absolutely lovely.
>> Trixie is the one who ran away from us.
I was across the road from Trixie
watching the guy. And you all know that [ __ ]
>> So, no, we're not scared of Trixie. And
I'm definitely not scared of you little
clowns in this community. Why don't you
get a bus in up here instead of getting
Natalie to do all your dirt work for
you? Natalie were pissed last night.
>> Natalie saying she's there. >> Wow. >> What?
>> Natalie saying that she's there.
>> Oh, it
is scary. in it. All on the same website
you can watch Tom and Jerry on. That's
[ __ ] scary. You can lose everything.
All over the same website. You can watch
Tom and Jerry on.
No, that's scary, bro.
That's scary, bro. [ __ ] that. I'm
leaving. And you know what? When when
when your life gets ruined
all on the same website, you can watch
Tom and Jerry on, right?
They're still going to be on there. Tom
is still going to be on there.
You know what I mean?
No, I wouldn't bum that. I wouldn't go
nowhere near her. Yeah,
it's the same website you can watch
Chucky on as well.
One second, I'll show you. Yeah, Grezy.
One second. One second, Grezy. One sec.
One second. One second.
Yeah, she tried with me before, but I
didn't want her.
She rejected Nons legs. She rejected
him. Look. Um, Grezy, look at that one.
Look at the middle picture when he's in the car.
This is the same website is kicking off
today on Look.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
December was like, you can lose it all. You know,
you should eat her out. Nah, I don't eat
women out. That's disgusting.
Especially not from like a
Yeah. No, that's disgusting, bro.
Is she there? Yeah. Oh, mate.
She said she was on the [ __ ] train to
[ __ ] King's Cross. You know,
I think what that's where Virgin Boy
gets his obsession from cuz he's had
like no mom figure. You know what I
mean? Grezy, cuz he's been solved by his mom, right? That's where
some of his [ __ ] upness comes from
because he had no mommy figure cuz a mom's uh
figure is stronger than a dad's figure
cuz obviously your mother carries you
for 9 months. Yeah. See
off is it? Just one second.
Greavvesy, do you remember Mr. G? Where
did Mr. G go? Remember the Scottish one, Mr. G?
One sec. One sec. One sec. Let me watch
this. Hold on. Hold on.
What's going on here?
One sec. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold
[ __ ] hell, Grezy.
Grezy, it's kicking off. Grezy, it's
Well, someone's going to get killed.
Someone's going to get killed.
Where's Virgin boy when all of this is
going on? Come over the [ __ ] burger.
Where's the [ __ ] rat face virgin skin can?
You're missing out on this. You [ __ ]
skin virgin living in Kent in a bed
suit. You [ __ ] virgin. Look, you're
missing this lad.
Come on. You [ __ ] virgin.
You listen to this content.
Can someone get the virgin on here,
please? He's missing his [ __ ] content.
You know what I mean? Why the [ __ ] is By
still on YouTube? [Laughter]
You know what I'm saying?
What the bloody hell is going on?
One second. What the bloody hell is
going on here?
Oh, it's not even ringing. I'm calling
him and it's not even ringing. [ __ ]
It's not even ringing.
Well, someone's been killed in it, Grezy.
All over the same website you can watch
that little doll on. Huh?
Where's the rat face virgin? Gregy and
you're not going to [ __ ] watch this [ __ ] content.
He's probably putting his benefit back
in the [ __ ] bank. The [ __ ] skin flint.
You [ __ ] skin bastard.
You [ __ ] bastard. Virgin bastard. in
a grave day.
>> Yeah, I had a few slices. I'm going to
heat the rest up later,
it was too much, bro. But I will heat
the rest up later. Can't beat a nice pizza, mate.
Nice pizza and Coke.
You can't beat a McDonald's Coke as
well. McDonald's Coke is the best.
I wonder what's going on. Yeah.
Do you reckon non-slave will ever get laid?
Do you reckon he'll ever get laid or do
you reckon I re I reckon he'll die a
virgin, mate? I [ __ ] reckon he he
will die a [ __ ] virgin.
And I don't want to see anyone [ __ ]
dying a [ __ ] virgin, mate. But I
can't be with someone cramping my [ __ ] style.
And then these people wanted me to meet
her. These people wanted me to meet
Natalie. And look what's happened.
Look what's happened. And they wanted me to [ __ ] meet her. Mad.
Every time I try and leave YouTube,
something new happens. Content and [ __ ] It's murder. [Music]
So, Grevy, if I come back in 10 years,
would it still be the same people? Do
you reckon? If I came back in 10 years,
would it be the same repeating people?
Do you think?
Would it be the same spastics? Do you like
same people every day?
Yes. Do you reckon it will be the same people?
No, but like say I went to prison or
something for like 10 years. Huh?
Then like say I went to prison for 10
years or whatever happened and I
couldn't come back for 10 years. Would
it be the same people?
Same spastics every day ain't got a life in it.
You say nobody leaves, but there is
people that left. Ant-Man left. He was
on YouTube all the time. Ant-Man left
and there's a few other people that left.
It's just the same repeating people.
See what I mean though, Greavves? You
know, these women, they ruin people's lives.
It's a serious thing. They they actually
ruin people's lives. You you you've seen
it firsthand now, haven't you, Greasy?
What these women do to people
and then you still get these little
simps that defend them? You know,
you still get these little simps that
defend them. Oh, look.
Still got these little simps that
[ __ ] defending. You're [ __ ] scared
down the [ __ ] skin flank.
M didn't it?
Women are evil, bro, aren't they?
They really are evil.
Look at my experience with USA. The
other ones, Monty's experience. They're
[ __ ] evil, aren't they?
It's horrible, isn't it? At least I
don't have to deal with that [ __ ] anymore.
I did say to Monty, if you meet a woman,
especially off YouTube, this is going to happen.
Look, I got [ __ ] abandoned for no reason.
[ __ ] look what's happening to [ __ ] Monty.
They're just too entitled, these [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] entitled, bro.
Yeah. LG was trying to say, "Oh, nobody
wants your dead girl." Cuz I was only
joking with him. I said, "Hey, she's
she's an absolute darling, babe." That's
what I said to him, Grezy.
I said, "She's an absolute babe, darling."
And I was only joking as well.
She's an absolute babe, darling.
You like that, Grezy?
See, I'm just happy with Franklin. See,
Franklin doesn't betray me. King doesn't
betray me. That's all I need is King and Franklin. You know,
when do I get to play the other
characters on GTA um five greasy? When
do I get to be the white man? Do I have
to do loads of missions or
do I have to do loads of missions first or what?
Do you have your McDonald's yet, Grezy?
You and McDonald's,
you silly case. You love your Mackey's, don't you?
Nah, he's not been nicked.
He needs to get off of YouTube.
He needs to get off of YouTube in it,
Grezy. Monty does. Please record.
Please record, please.
He needs to get off of YouTube though,
ain't it, Grezy?
He needs to get off YouTube and just
spend time with these kids now after
this, bro. I think that's the best thing
he can do. Hold down
the D-pad. What's the D-pad?
I'm on Xbox. So,
okay. Yeah. Yeah. One sec.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I can Yeah, I see it.
Now, do you believe me greasy that women are evil?
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I I see. Oh, Franklin.
We've only got Franklin unlocked at the
moment. Oh, yeah. Franklin. Yeah.
But listen though, Greavvesy, you didn't
answer my question. So, this battery,
this controller runs on battery. Yeah.
But I'm using my Samsung charger on it
and it works,
but I can't charge my phone at the same
time with it. You understand?
But what I'm saying, yeah, it's weird
cuz it runs off batteries, but if you
use a Samsung charger, it works. But you
need to keep it plugged in.
But you need to keep it plugged in. I mean,
yeah, it's weird, man. I need to get
some new batteries.
But it works. I just need to keep it plugged in.
probably use the power battery to be honest.
Yeah, I used to I used to use the power
battery when I used to do Uber. Greasy,
you should do Uber, man. You should
apply for Uber and do it every day. You
probably get like three grand in a month.
Just just just do it every day, bro.
Probably make about5600 pound a week.
You might as well. You got nothing to do in it.
You should do that Uber, bro.
Apply for it. Make three grand a month.
You could easily make three grand a
month if you worked every day. [Music] Wow.
Oh, bless you then. I think my back
sweats are not like that.
Bless you then.
Do you agree that women are evil then, Greavvesy?
They're so evil.
They are evil though, isn't it?
They don't care about anyone's feelings. They're nasty.
They're nasty bastards.
Yeah, but Grezy, they are they are evil
though, aren't they?
Okay. So, which ones are evil that you know of?
Uh, mine's USA, Izzy, Kaye, Natalie.
They're all evil, ain't it?
Them three are definitely evil, isn't it? Yeah.
They feel evil, aren't they?
Um, N's gone to Monty's and apparently they're fighting.
Yeah, there's a madness, bro.
a proper madness. Yeah.
I Cory, I I think I know why
Virgin Boy is so [ __ ]
It's lack of um I tried ringing him. It doesn't ring.
It doesn't ring. I've tried ringing him.
Um the thing is, Chloe, I think I know
why he's so [ __ ] It's lack of mother figure.
you know, where his mom used to starve
him and abuse him and his stepdad used
to beat [ __ ] out of him. I think that's
where it's all come from.
You know, the lack of mother figure cuz
obviously your mother carries you for 9
months, doesn't she?
You know, I might do a video about the
virgin, you know,
about the virgin. That's where it all
comes from, isn't it? Cuz Natalie's
[ __ ] isn't it?
It's like, yeah, my dad died, but my
[ __ ] dad wasn't in my [ __ ] life
like that. It's my mom who actually
brought me up. And that's my [ __ ] mother
who I actually still talk to. Can't be
said about him. He don't talk to his mom
cuz his mom [ __ ] starved him. Put him
in hospital. That's why he's so [ __ ]
up. Look at Natalie. She's [ __ ] you know.
Why do a little video on this, Cory?
Would you watch it? And I'm going to do
it in my favorite little pink top cuz
I'm not insecure about my sexuality. You
see, I'm not insecure about my sexuality.
So, I don't mind wearing a pink top with
a navy cap or or something like that, you know?
I'm not an insecure virgin like some
You understand, lad?
You like my little videos, don't you, Kyrie?
Yeah. I got a pink top. I got a pink fed py top.
Well, what's going on with Monty?
You still go out drinking, Cory, once a
week or I didn't go out this week, bro.
I won a football bet yesterday. 150. I
still haven't collected it yet, but
yeah, I didn't go out yesterday either.
That's I won football bets twice. Twice,
bro. Last Saturday and this Saturday.
Yeah, it's good, man. You get fed up of
the drinking as you get older, don't you, Cory? Yeah.
Yeah. You get bored of it, isn't it? I
don't really go out too much anymore, lad.
It's pointless. You speak to someone and
all they say is they got a boyfriend. Pointless.
I just chill now, man. Just chill. Yeah,
you can't even speak to someone without
[ __ ] hearing it. It's horrible.
You hate who? Women. Yeah, they're evil,
aren't they? Nasty bastards.
Yeah, I hate him as well. They're evil, isn't it?
Yeah, if you go Thailand
where uh where Ant-Man is, bro, you get
laid all the time.
Yeah. I said to him, "What what did you
hate about England?" He said England
used to depress him because he could He
said England used to depress him.
He said England used to depress him
because you can't even get laid here.
It's true though. Is it?
Yeah. You can't even get laid here
in Thailand. You get laid every night. Yeah.
It's so hot, bro. It's [ __ ] so hot.
Oh my god. [Music]
Sparking hot, man.
Yeah, there is no saers in London where I live.
You got to go central London for that.
And I never used to go sauna. I've been
to a sauna in I think I've only been in
a sauna once when I was in Scotland.
I think that was the only time, wasn't
it? I think I've only been in a sauna once.
Yeah, when I was in Scotland and I come
out the swimming pool. Yeah, I went
swimming then I went in the sauna
and then got changed, went out approaching. Yeah.
Yeah, I've been in a solder in Scotland.
That's about it.
What's good, bro?
You like tie women now. Uh,
you like tie women now, don't you? Um Cory,
you like Taiwan? Yeah,
that's good. Is it?
You don't hear the I've got a boyfriend
with them in it.
Yeah. You don't get the I've got a
boyfriend over there. That's a good
thing, is it? Yeah, man.
[ __ ] bors me that, bro. That's why I
don't really go out anymore. Cory, that
what I'm saying. I go out like every two weeks,
maybe every three weeks, maybe. It's
just pointless, isn't it?
Ah, they've all got boyfriends.
They've all got boyfriends. Wow.
Yeah. They're just not interested in this country.
Isn't that right, Cory? They're just not
interested in this country, lad.
That's what Antman said. I think he's
right, isn't it?
Do you think he's right, Cory? Yeah.
Well, obviously he's right, bro,
cuz he's in Thailand. I get the same
[ __ ] experiences along with 90% of
other people. So, obviously, is it 100%.
So hot, man. It's so hot.
So hot, bro.
I'll be back later anyways.