Hello mate. Hello M.
Yeah, Monty wanted me to show you all
something that he went to the barbers and
it cost him
52 quid. You want me to tell everyone? Yeah, man.
Bless Monty. Things are looking up for
Mob man. Oh,
[ __ ] blew up. Yeah, that's his receipt.
I see his bobber sitting off Franklin. What? Franklin,
what are you doing outside all by yourself, mama?
Oh [ __ ] Yeah. You want me to show you this?
Oh, why are you running away from Frank?
Oh, he's dead.
Sorry, get in the car.
It is banging, man.
Uh yeah, that's
uh money man got a haircut. He wanted me
to show you that it cost £52. I said to
uh money, it looks good, man. and then
you need to keep the beard and get it
shaped up. That's like his his best
that's that's his best look. I said,
"Bro, you can't go bald and have no
facial hair. You look you look like you
got cancer like that." I said that to
him as well. You you need to literally
like shave all your hair off, which you
don't, and shave the beard up like he's
done. I think that's that's your best
your best that that's basically him looks Max.
Obviously, he doesn't have any hair as well.
So yeah, see me, I wouldn't mind I
wouldn't mind being bored like when I'm
30, 40. You just rock the beard, you
know. As long as you got a beard, mate,
you're all good. Doesn't matter if you go bald.
Virgin boy is [ __ ] when he got his
bald. He can't grow a beard. [ __ ]
he's going to be [ __ ] dude. He's
actually rapidly binged.
he will be [ __ ] in it.
Yeah. I was speaking to some uh woman on
Reddit. She's such a [ __ ] she is. I said
to her, you know, when you come back to
London, cuz she's from uh well, she's
from England and she's in New Zealand. I
said, when you go to London, uh let me
know in it and let's see how bad you are
to my face and you can bring any guy you
want as well. I'm a stupid idiot on
Reddit. I said, you can bring any guy you want.
[ __ ] 80s westernized [ __ ] It was
like speaking to that [ __ ] 19year-old
again. They're such [ __ ] aren't they, bro?
I said, "Listen, I'm not your [ __ ]
mate." Yeah. I don't know how many times
I've had to [ __ ] tell you that. Stupid [ __ ]
[ __ ] really do hate them. I do, man.
I really [ __ ] do hate them.
[ __ ] [ __ ] They're wankers. So yeah. Damn. [ __ ]
Yeah, man. Message those five numbers.
Let's see if I get any replies back.
Uh, don't think so, bro.
Yeah, doubt it, mate. And I'm not going
to have time to be doing this
approaching [ __ ] anymore as well, bro,
cuz I need to be doing things now. But I
won't have time to
uh cuz that's what they don't tell you
on Reddit. You see, Joe, they don't tell
you on Reddit that you have to approach
every single day to even get a date. No
one no one tells you that.
No one No one tells you that, bro. You
You find that [ __ ] out for yourself.
Which how can people realistically do
that when a it costs a lot of money, b
where they going to get the time and the money?
Like normal people. Like it's bad, isn't
it? They make it seem so easy when it's
like one of the hard. It's the most
simplest natural things, but it's one of
the hardest things to get.
Yeah, I got five yesterday. [ __ ] took ages,
but probably not going to get anywhere
as usual. It good old England.
I think I'm going to put next week I'm
going to put 80 pound on a treble. Both
teams to score no draw.
I need to win like a couple of thousand pound meaty. >> Yeah,
I think I'll pick it just right.
Things will change. Things will never
It will never change
with women. Never. Not in this country,
lad. It will never
Oh, Franklin. How the [ __ ] did you fly
out of that car, man? It will never change.
I recorded all the approaches. I put it
on my other channel.
You know, you know me, Joe. I'm out
every week, mate. Well, not every week.
Every two weeks. I'm out every two weeks
looking for that change,
searching for that change, trying to
find it. Ain't found it yet. Franklin. Franklin shoots.
Oh, you didn't die that time. You died,
didn't you? Shilly G.
Yeah, I'm playing some Frank game.
Do you know what? Yeah, my friend had
GTA San Andreas on his laptop and that's
what we used to play on the laptop.
We're at like the 70th mission, but
obviously I don't see him anymore cuz he
doesn't he doesn't live near me. I'm
thinking of downloading the San Andreas
game again and just like trying to
complete it, but uh
I don't know about that last mission,
bro. It's about half an hour long.
That that last mission is about half an
hour long on San Andreas, but I love the
story line, bro. Nothing no story line
would ever beat it.
But obviously I'd have to I'd have to
buy on the Xbox and then [ __ ] do all
the missions all over again.
You never know, Joe. Maybe maybe one day
all of the things that's been happening
to me for years will just stop happening.
You never know.
You never know, bro. Maybe you'll stop
hearing the I have a boyfriend. Maybe
their Tik Tok batteries will fall out of
their back one day. You never know, bro.
It's like I was saying, it's like a
doll. Yeah. You know how you put
batteries in a doll? It's like someone's
unscrewed their back and put Tik Tok
batteries in it. You know,
that's literally all they ever say is
they have a boyfriend. It's [ __ ]
boring as [ __ ] bro. 2 hours into the
drinking, I was like, "Oh, I might as
well just go home, [ __ ] escort." But
I stayed out. I just stayed out cuz
Yeah, it's not even enjoyable anymore. It's It's torture. Oh [ __ ]
They don't even, like I said, they don't
even give you a chance. They don't even
go on a [ __ ] date with you. They
don't even give you a [ __ ] chance.
But then they they moan at every, you
know, every man wants sex.
You know, like they just But then don't
say that you can't find men because all
men wanted is sex. That's ridiculous,
bro. That is ridiculous.
They don't even I wouldn't mind, right?
If if they gave you a chance. Yeah.
Every time you went out, you know, you'd
get a date
and, you know, you went too fast and
then they said no. I could understand that. But
it isn't even that. So it's like, you know,
it's like they don't even give you a
chance. It's not that they want to take
things slow or they just want a
relationship. They just they're just not
interested. Like what like what Antman said,
it doesn't matter anyways, bro.
There is a lot of lesbians.
Yeah, but that's the same as women
though. Yeah, but then you can say the
same thing for women. But then know
they're trying to make it out like men
only want sex and then dump them. That's
No, no. What they mean by that is you
want to get with them to [ __ ] them and
leave them. That's what they mean. They
don't mean that you just you want to
have cuz they want sex as well in relationships.
They make it out like every man wants to
pump and dump them,
which does not make any sense because
there is people that actually want
relationships throughout their uh 20ies,
but you won't give them a chance. And
then when you're in your 30s, that's
when you're a pump and dump.
So, it's ridiculous how they don't learn
from each other. It It's mad how like
they don't learn from each other's mistakes.
It's like this woman on Reddit being a
[ __ ] She says, "Oh, I get laid." I
said, "Enjoy it whilst it lasts. It
lasts because you're going to hit the
wall now. When when you're 30, when
you're about 32, you're [ __ ] So enjoy
it whilst it lasts." Getting laid and
[ __ ] because when you're old, mate, no
one's going to want you. And if they do
want you, they're going to they're going
to use you for sex even if they do want you. So,
it's stupid really, like I said, how
they don't learn from
um they don't learn from each other.
It's crazy, isn't it? Yeah. Maybe a lot
of men do, but there's a lot of men that
don't. It's not that they would know.
They don't even give you a chance.
Yeah. There was one from Brazil
yesterday and she was like, "Oh, buy me
and my friend a drink." She couldn't
speak English to be fair. We had to
translate. And I said, "Oh,
I think I said something like cuz she
said she was going back to Brazil uh
next day, which is today." And I said,
"Oh, you want me to buy you and your
friend a drink?" I said I said, "Okay,
in exchange for a kiss, then I will." I
wouldn't have said that if she was still
here then, but I was like, "She's
leaving tomorrow. I'm never going to see
her again. So, let me try and get what I
can out the bitch." Obviously, I
wouldn't have said that if they were
staying here because
I got someone's number from Scotland. I think
I think somebody will reply later. Maybe
they might not. This is to what I mean
with London. You can get these numbers,
they don't even reply.
Maybe they'll reply later.
One, two, three. Yeah.
Oh my [ __ ] ear, man.
But look at Monty, man. I helped Monty.
He's back with Natalie. They're doing good, man.
It's mad how God don't [ __ ] repay me,
man, for my um good deeds, you know.
Well, he Well, I mean, he did kind of. I
mean, I won a football bet last week, so I mean
I mean that's good, is it?
But I need to try and win a big one. I'm
trying to think.
I need to win a big football bet, Joe.
Like just a both teams. Uh just go draw
a treble, man. That will do me 100 pound. But
no, not at all. S simps don't get laid.
The thing with simps is they women don't
like them, but they still defend them. I
don't understand why they do it. Like he
didn't get what he wanted in the end.
It's just that she doesn't have anyone
else cuz she's a bit older and you know
like he doesn't that's that's why she
went back with him. She doesn't really
have anyone else. So if it was like a
normal person with their [ __ ] together
in London, they don't care. I mean, that
19year-old kept coming back to me, but I
don't think she will now, which I don't
care about cuz I don't like her. But it
it never because I used to ignore her
and she always used to come back. She'll
be like, "Oh, I'm going block you." I
said, "Bye." And then she'd keep coming
back. So, in both cases, it doesn't.
They think sing gets them laid, but they
don't. Women don't like simps, but they
still simp. That's the whole point of
them sing because they don't get women.
And they think by sing it will get them women.
It's ridiculous. Like they don't they've
had probably less women than you. By you
I mean me. Less sex than you.
Like and they still defend them. That's
that's the bit like me and Ant-Man
always like we we scratch our heads
thinking like this is a madness, bro. We
I've had sex. I've had one night stand.
I've had kisses. No, no, no. I don't
defend women. I think they're [ __ ]
[ __ ] in these westernized countries.
And I'll tell you I'll tell you the
truth, they are [ __ ] you know, but
they seem to defend them. It's strange. It's madness. Yeah.
Well, he was, but that was his first
love, is it? I would never get like that
over no [ __ ] woman. [ __ ] that. Are
you [ __ ] mad?
I only had enough with uh
of that [ __ ]
No, you can never get me like that. If a
woman says I'm going, I'll be like, "Bye-bye, Adios. Adios."
No, I would not be begging no [ __ ]
woman back. I never begged that 19y old
back ever. When she used to say, "Oh,
I'm going. Bye." I said, "Fuck off then.
Bye." What a [ __ ] Yeah,
but I don't know why I done it with the
USA Izzy thing because I could always do
better than her. And when I was getting
women, I was getting better than her. I
had better women than her like that
whole year. But I don't know why they
[ __ ] with my head. Probably cuz all
the false hope.
You know what I mean?
So yeah uh
the bet is um
Oldman and Swinden both teams to score.
Cambridge getting both teams to score
and Colchester both teams to score. I I
should have put a [ __ ] I should have put
a both teams to score no draw on all of
them, bro. And stuck like 80 pound on
it. But I need to try and win a top the
ground, bro. Do you know what I I want
to do? Yeah.
I want to win a good football bet and
never have to like work again in my
life, bro. Like I just have no
responsibilities cuz the house was too
much responsibilities. Yeah, it was good
money and [ __ ] but I hated the
responsibility of it, man. I hated it.
Just win a nice little football bet.
Never have to worry about working again.
Imagine that. Like in the millions.
It's a dream in it. But don't think that's possible
to be honest.
But yeah, I could get better than USA.
All of the women I had was better than USA.
But I don't know. something just felt
different with her go. The kisses,
the holding hands.
But um yeah, all of the [ __ ] I've had
is better than her.
So, it's not always because it's, but
obviously mom is different.
I agree with you. I was watching the GTA
missions on San Andreas.
The last one is about half an hour long.
I need to download it on the Xbox and
start streaming GTA San Andreas, bro. I
need to buy it from the start. The Xbox
Yeah, I was watching the last mission,
bro. It's like 30 minutes [ __ ] long.
It's a good story line though, man.
Who was your favorite character in GTA
San Andreas? I think mine was Big Smoke.
A bless you.
I met a Scottish woman yesterday, Grezy.
It made me think of you.
Hey, my friends.
Yeah, some of the missions are hard
though. But like I said, I'm not with my
friend anymore. So,
um obviously to save games on these uh
things. So, I'm going to have to try and
complete on the Xbox.
Nice curry today. Me thinks I'm trying
to stay away from McDonald's. Rezy,
I'm trying to stay away from Macadox.
Oh, I actually cold approached a
McDonald's worker yesterday while speak
Oh, I wasn't I was actually just
speaking to her normally though to honest
McDonald's uniform on the little cap.
The little McDonald's cap greasy. Yeah, man.
Little McDonald's caty.
Oh, I ordered some new cats, by the way,
Grezy. You're going to see them. You're
going to see them soon.
That reminds me, how far is the delivery process?
There still not been It's still not been
items gathered. What the [ __ ]
The [ __ ] Have you ever heard of team
Grezy? It's very addicting.
Very addicting, bro.
There's no interest. See,
we heard of teamu gre.
Oh, poor Franklin.
It was so hot, man. I need a new fan.
I don't like this weather greasy. Oh, [ __ ]
It's really hot, man. Help me.
I hate the heat. I don't know about you,
G. I [ __ ] hate it.
Yeah, I've ordered some Chucky hats if
you must know Grezy. Yeah, I've ordered
some Chucky items. I ordered some Chucky
bottom uh boxes and I ordered some Chucky hats.
Yeah, I hate this heat, mate. I [ __ ]
hate it, man. I'm so glad I'm born in
October, you know, near like Halloween. Yeah,
I [ __ ] hate it, man. Yeah,
I'm out every two weeks squeezy looking
for that change.
You know they say life changes. You
never know who you're going to meet and
stuff. So I'm out there. I am out there
greasy looking for that change
you know now and again can't seem to
find it looking for that change you can
see the westernity in their eyes
we can see the westernity in their eyes
and you know the thing is I was actually
thinking you know Monty man yeah
he's actually um he's actually my um pig eating partner
Yeah, he's my pig eating partner
cuz we had like a piggy omelette. I
don't have a cow eating partner anymore,
but I've got a pig eating partner, Monty.
Yeah, man. Yeah, I have given up griev.
I just wanted to go out for a drink. And
you know what's so good though? Going
out for a drink. you meet all these new people
like you you make connections and I
don't know that's the only good thing
when you go out drinking you have like
you just meet people and have a laugh it
is fun but it's just the women it just
never changes but I will always be out
there I'll always be out there looking
for that change
looking for that change
but I'm getting old now, but I'm I'm
losing energy. I'm losing confidence
because of this [ __ ] now. So,
let me know. >> Yeah,
you can't beat it sometimes.
Yeah, but people on Reddit tell me that
I will meet someone. Oh, someone's
messaged me. Oh, thank you. I got an
update. My Chucky hats will be with me
within 5 days. Yay. Little Chucky.
>> Oh, man.
Are you I bet you can't wait to see the
Chucky hats, can you? Oh, Chucky.
I still need to go and see that
Superman, don't I?
I always sometimes like I I invite Laney
to come to the cinema with me, Grezy, to
watch a horror film and she's like, I'm
not watching those [ __ ] horror film,
so I have to go and watch them.
It's a good bet. I put Oh, by the way,
21 pound returns 140
one. So, uh, so basically I cashed out
230, right? 231. So, I just put £21 on
three teams. Saves me going to the
bookies and doing it. So, yeah. But if
it come, bro, if you had £80 on on a bet
like that, you're talking two and a half
grand. I'm going to try next week. I
think I'm going to try and get three
both teams to score, no draw.
But the thing that's going to annoy you
is you're probably going to get free
both score and draw. Telling you just
wish that you just done a normal both
teams to score. That's how it [ __ ] with
your head. But I mean, yeah, you're
talking [ __ ] two and a half grand, bro.
If if they come in it, it's it'll be
hard. But I think if you get the right
teams, you can do it, man.
Let me know. Let me know.
You remember Greavvesy? You want to go
and have a Chinese with your mama? You
know that guy that um comes on that Nicolo?
Like, you know how he like copies what I
say? Like sometimes when I'm out, I
think of him and it makes me laugh.
like, you know, typing, mocking like
what I've said in that. I don't know,
bro. It's funny as [ __ ]
Uh, it's funny, isn't it? Peter Betty
can't get attached anymore because he's
already found his mama.
Um, no, I didn't do Fleetwood.
I done Shrewsbury, Colchester,
Cambridge, Harriate, and Old and Swindon.
I was thinking I I'll give probably
Frankie a go in a month maybe. I I don't
play that [ __ ] anymore. Yeah.
Yeah. Some caps coming. Greavesy. Yeah.
Some Chucky ones.
Did you like um Did you like Big Smoke of GTA? M
>> Big Smoke, man.
Yeah, that's why I always wanted to um
try the cigars because of Big Smoke.
Remember when he used to have like the um
um when he used to smoke the cigars,
I used to be like, "Yeah, bro. I want [ __ ]
I want to be like that, bro. I want to I
want to smoke a cigar. I actually smoked
a cigarette yesterday, Grezy. Whilst I
was drinking, I found a new friend. Grezy. Oh [ __ ]
What are you doing, Mr. Muay?
I hope that Scottish woman replies, bro,
and then maybe we can meet up and have
some kids and then put baby Peter in the
little Celtic baby grow.
How cute is that?
Oh, baby pee and a little Celtic baby
grow. How cute is that?
Wiggling his little feet. Greasy. Oh,
bless her [ __ ] controller, man. I
need to get some batteries for this
controller. It's annoying to keep
switching the [ __ ] batteries, man.
God bless you. One second. Uh,
you know what makes me laugh, Grebsy?
Yeah. Is they say that these women say
that they don't uh they give up with men
because they apparently men only want
them for sex, right? Yeah. When when
genuine people come their way, they just
pretend they they have a boyfriend.
So, I mean, it's it's crazy cuz Yeah. a
lot of people only want sex, but not everyone.
That's the [ __ ] up thing is they
think, but then when genuine people come
their way, then they'll just pretend
they have a boyfriend and not give them
the chance. And then when they get into
their 30s, all the people that will all
um will be interested in them will just
want to [ __ ] pump and dump them.
Yeah. Me, other people are genuine.
I met an Australian yesterday. We were
speaking about hobbies and stuff like
that. Um, and she had a boyfriend at the
end. Like I said, no matter what nationality,
they would always be the same. It
doesn't matter where.
Um, if they're Australian, they will
talk to you, but then as soon as you try
to escalate it, I have a boyfriend.
British, just walk past. It depends
where they're from. Um,
but they they um, this woman was
attacking me on Reddit earlier, Grezy.
All because the truth hurts.
I was showing her stuck up women cuz I I
recorded five approaches yesterday cuz
this guy on my Instagram wanted to see
him. So, [ __ ] it. Let me send it to him.
I don't want outside the barber shop. And then
um he um
she was like attacking me.
She was she was um
attacking um she was basically trying to
say, "Oh, you're this. You're that."
like trying to dis discredit me all
because I showed her the truth and the truth hurts,
you know. It's sad, bro. Really? What's
the max age? [ __ ] knows 35.
If you're genuine, you wouldn't be
messaging multiple people people after a
date. Well, yes, you would to be able to
find somebody that wants to Okay. Okay.
Let's put it this way, right? Say you go
out and you approach one person and you
get a number. Are you going to stop? No.
Why are you not going to stop? Because
what if you only message if you only
have that one number? What's the chance
of that number going somewhere? That's
the whole point of getting five numbers
because it increases the chances of
finding someone who's genuine, finding
somebody that wants to date. You can't
just get one number because that number
is not going to reply.
That's the whole point is looking. It's
like a dating app. You're swiping to
find one person. You're approaching and
getting genuine to find one person to
find a genuine person.
What? So, cuz so what? You obviously get
one number and just hope that they're interested.
Like, no, bro. What the [ __ ] I mean, I
think three is enough. If you get three numbers,
then I mean, yeah, that's enough for for
the day. Yeah.
But they don't even like
they don't even give you. But I don't
think it's a good idea to be honest to
do it sober anymore cuz it just
depresses the [ __ ] out of you because
where you're sober and you can think
about it and then you just realize how
[ __ ] up it is cuz you're obviously
sober doing it. So you're like you
actually really realize how [ __ ] up it
actually is. Whereas when you're
drinking, like you're just enjoying
yourself anyways and you're drunk. But
when you're doing it sober,
when it keeps happening, you're
thinking, "Oh shit." Like, and then they
start they start making you doubt
yourself. Like, it's hard to it's hard
to explain it. That's why it's not a
good idea to do it sober.
I wouldn't mind if I was fat and ugly,
then I would love to. I would do it. So,
I Oh, yeah. I'm a fat ugly bastard. I
know why I keep getting I've got a
boyfriend. I'm a fat ugly bastard. Then
I I would have been well I know my lane.
I know what I am. But when you're not
and you keep getting the same old and
you're sober and you're still getting
it, it's not good.
That's why like you shouldn't really do them sober.
It's depressing, bro. I I remember
before when I done it I done them sober
before and it actually gets you on the
drink. Like say you went to central
London, right? And like it was it was
pissing you off. Like you was
approaching and it's pissing you off.
Yeah. You would just get on the drink.
It's so depressing that it actually gets
you on the drink. You know what I'm saying? Um
Yeah. But when I get a reply, I'll
ignore everyone else.
I I will ignore I will ignore everyone
else if I get someone.
But no one's interested in this country. Yeah, bro.
All right. You know what makes me laugh
about um Ant-Man Greavvesy? He said that
the only place you're not going to get
I've got a boyfriend is Asia.
Is he right about that? He said that's
the only place you're not going to get it.
Yeah, but do you know how stupid that
sounds, bro? He said the only place
you're not going to get I've got a
boyfriend is Asia.
That's [ __ ] I don't know. Just
something about that is just funny.
Don't know about you, man, but that
makes me laugh.
Probably. So, you copying my bet, Steven Howard?
So yeah, 20 to 140.
If it wins, I might [ __ ] out [ __ ] out of London again.
I want to try and leave London at least
once a month, you know.
Well, once a month. Not at least once a
month. Once a month.
No, it's not it's not it's it's just
both teams to score, but it's not a both
teams to score no draw. It's just a
normal both teams to score. But next
next week, I'm going to do a both teams
to score no draw. And I'm going to do
three of them, bro. I need to try win
some big money, bro. I don't want to be
like that skin tent virgin.
You know what I mean?
Nah, mate. He's on a grand a month. I'm
not on a grand. I mean, I got 1,400 this
month because of the winds and [ __ ] So,
I can actually say I'm officially not on
a grand a month yet.
You know what I mean? Grievy. But next
week, I will be doing both teams to
score no draw.
I'll do three of them.
Hopefully, it wins.
Be good in it.
to be like that little skinned virgin in
Kent, mate. [ __ ] hell.
Y'all want to be that [ __ ] skin virgin K.
You know what I'm saying? Grezy that bastard.
No, I've got three teams though. No, no,
no. I've got three teams.
No, I've got three teams.
Not two. I got three. I only put 20 on it.
[ __ ] hell. That white rum really
makes you [ __ ] man. That white rum. Oh, horrible.
Have you ever had white rum greavesy?
Oh, mate. I'm sure that's what kills
people, you know.
I'm sure that's what kills people, bro.
Telling you it's what kills people, man.
That That kills people. That
telling you that kills people, bro.
[ __ ] no joke.
Trust the [ __ ] trust the the manager
to be Jamaican.
Yeah, cuz that's where it all comes
from, is it?
Rum. It comes from Jamaica.
Yeah. Did you know it comes from It
comes from uh the Caribbean rum.
Well, you know, Filipino. What
was it? A drink or
you mean the people? Oh man,
that white rum, bro.
Oh, I had a W curly grease and some of
it went on my t-shirt, so I had to wipe
it off and there was water everywhere.
Nah, ain't that, bro? Not even.
Nah, not even, mate. Yeah, man. One second.
Yeah, it did.
Yeah, bro. I just done a big poo.
I just done a big pooy.
Big smelly poo.
It's horrible, is it? It's not wrong.
>> Yeah, man.
So, Steven Howard, do you think um think
you will ever um
do you think you will ever um lose his virginity?
Nah. Do you reckon he'll never lose his virginity?
Man, mate, I think he'll die one.
I think he'll [ __ ] die one, mate.
Never, bro. You never get laid.
[ __ ] hell. Never. Jesus Christ.
These are [ __ ] virgin.
J. Virgin Mary. Virgin Mary.
Yeah. We'll never get laid. Never.
I got with an escort yesterday.
Greavvesy. She was sucking my willie.
Yeah. I didn't get [ __ ] from the escort
yesterday, which was good.
It was good, man. Feels quite nice.
Oh, I also got some I also got some
Stitch boxer shorts as well. Oh man,
that white ramen is no joke, bro. Gives
you headaches, makes you feel sick.
It's [ __ ] horrible, mate. Yeah,
I pee in the sink. Don't know about you,
Greavves. I always pee in the sink,
mate. When I wake up, my touch is hard.
Yeah, that thing's annoying now. They're
trying to make you prove your age before
you watch porn. It's annoying.
Any everything exists on uh team
everything and anything exists on team.
You ever heard of team? They have everything.
Everything exists on there.
Uh, Monty went to the hairdressers and
he paid £52 for a haircut, so he wanted
me to show everyone.
Bro, that white rum ain't a joke, bro.
Oh my god. I'm
But I can I can still feel it in my
body, bro. It's horrible.
But it's hard to not when it's 2
pound50, isn't it, Grezy? It's hard to
not have the rum when it's 2 pound50.
Yeah, he's got no hair. How can you say no?
It's a happy hour deal. 2 pound50.
You can't exactly say no, can you?
No, bro. I'm [ __ ] I think I'm going
to have to get a vindaloo today
because I I can take it.
I've got Turkish blood in me. I've got
I've got a bit Scottish in me as well.
So, might have to have a little today
cuz I'm a I'm a man's man, mate. Some
little [ __ ] granky birdie with no muscle.
I'm not that not that kind of kind, you know.
Nice curry today, bro.
I'm trying I tried to sleep, but I can't
go to sleep. So bad. [Music]
No, you can't go sleep with your hung
over like that, mate. Yeah,
bro. I'm [ __ ] This is why I could
never go to the cinema the next day
after drinking grievy because I'd be
[ __ ] for like two three days.
Like I said, it was worth it. It's worth
it. Grievy looking for that change.
Searching for that change. But then
Ant-Man says it will never change.
I mean, it could be worse. I could be a
virgin like Virgin Boy. I mean, it could
it could be worse.
A [ __ ] kebab. What is people's
obsession with kebabs?
To be fair, kebabs are nice. Shish kebabs.
Yeah. Yeah, they are nice. Shish ones.
Shish kebabs are nice. Like a mix shish
kebab, but I've never seen the hyper me.
Oh, let's go for a kebab, mate. I'm
pissed. I've never really seen like
I think they're overrated. They're nice.
The shish the shish is all nice. Don't
get me wrong, but
it's not really for me, bro.
Saying that I might get one today
to be fair cuz maybe a shish. I might get one.
I had pizza last time, didn't I? Maybe I
will go. Maybe I will get one.
But it'd have to be a shish. And they're
quite expensive. Greasy. I don't want a
donor, man. honest. Uh,
it's not as nice as the shish.
Trust me, man. Get like a mix shush. I
can never pick between chicken and lamb
cuz I like both of them. So, I just get
both of them basically.
You know what I'm saying?
>> What are you getting? The shishon.
You don't find shovel co attractive. You're gay.
That strong homo vibes apparently. Wow.
That strong homo uh vibes.
I mean, do you think I'm gay? Greasy.
You think I'm [ __ ] gay?
Cuz I don't find several girl attractive.
I just don't see what's so special about
her. Greavvesy, what's your opinion on it?
Yeah, I'm going to have a kebab, I
think. Let me try and see.
Yeah, but that doesn't mean I'm gay
because I I'm not a copycat. Green Z.
Cuz I've got a mind of my own. So what?
That makes me gay. Because I've got a
mind of my own.
What? Because I've got a mind of my own.
And I don't And I don't follow the
crowd. I'm not a copycat.
He's a He's a [ __ ] He's a [ __ ] copycat.
What's I going to afford a kebab? You silly goose.
Of course I like it, you silly g.
So what? Because I'm not a copycat. I'm gay.
So that makes me gay. Really? Uh
where's a kebab?
I'm trying to find a No, I don't want
German Donna kebab. That's only Donna.
So what? I'm I I'm apparently gay cuz
I'm not a copycat.
He He said it so people would stop
thinking he was gay. He's a copycat.
[ __ ] off, man. He's a proper copycat. He
ain't got no mind of his own.
He's got no mind of his own. He's a copycat.
I just want to get him and squeeze his
little cheeks. You copycat.
Yeah, that is that is copying. He's a copycat.
He's a copycat. He literally is.
How can I be gay when I've [ __ ] more
women than him? I've had more women than him.
How the [ __ ] can I can I be [ __ ] gay?
How How the [ __ ] did I be [ __ ] gay?
That doesn't even make any [ __ ] sense.
What the [ __ ]
Strange, is it? It is strange. Yeah.
Why did he say that? He's got to be
copying, isn't it? He's copying. He's
trying to fit in, isn't he?
He's actually like trying to really fit in.
No one likes a copycat.
What do you think, Mie?
You can't deny she's attractive.
That's strong homo vibes right there.
I speak a bit slow like this cuz I'm a [ __ ] Um yeah, [ __ ] [ __ ]
Um right, let's see which one we get
here. Fancy £8 off. Oh,
I want £8 off my order, please.
Yeah, that sounds good.
I'm trying to think of what kebab to get. Oh
no. What could I place lamb?
Lamb shish. Uh lamb shish. No. What's up?
No no no no no no. Lamb shish kebab. mixed donor.
No, I don't want mixed donor. I want shish.
Where is it? Chicken donut.
Lamb shish kebab. Lamb.
No, there's no mixed ones.
Oh, I like that. Yeah, that's nice.
That's a raw. There's one in Stratford
in the mall. Yeah, that's quite nice,
too. I do remember that. Yeah,
it's saying though.
One sec. It has to be shish. It can't It
can't be greasy, bro, cuz it will make
me vomit. Cuz I was on the right call.
One sec, bro.
I don't think you can get a mixed one.
It's not giving you the option to get a
mixed one. Why? Chicken lamb.
It's quite expensive though.
Oh yeah, we got chicken shish and lamb shish. Okay.
I don't want any sauce. Let me um
But will I eat again later?
You get pl lamb sh.
These ones are dear though. These ones
are like4 lamb sh chicken sh 1999.
But I've got a code.
So, I should get um I'm sure wait.
One second, bro. Hold on. I need to
think about what I'm doing here.
One second, please. What? It's not giving the question. Um
Find these chickens.
Yeah, but you get £8 off of it. It says,
"Is it actually chopped up? Is it
actually chopped up brains, Greavesy, or not?"
Nah, it's not chopped up brains, is it?
They're saying that they don't have wings.
One second, bro. Where's the chicken, though?
No. No. One second, bro. Please, hold on.
Someone else wants something and they
don't have it. So, I'm going to have to
order from somewhere else. I'm not just
going to get something from me. Selfish. Um, right.
Let me try this. Have they got [ __ ] here or
So, I'd get fish, but it's too um
it's too uh greasy.
Oh, mixish £13. That's better.
What do I want? I want
Yeah. onion, lettuce. Uh,
one second, please.
Yeah, that's a lot cheaper then. That's good.
Why don't they have any chicken wings though?
I'm not just going to get something from here.
Huh? That doesn't make sense. What? [ __ ]
What did I
Sorry about this.
Uh I wish I need that rice though. a
pit of bread.
And you you fly bastard [ __ ]
Does this [ __ ] come with per bread?
Does it come with p bread?
Do you know grievy?
I'm sure it must do. Is it? It must come
with p bread.
Is it going to let you type a code in on uh
Oh, here we go. Voucher.
What's the minimum spend?
I say I've ordered it. Grely
I've ordered it. leaves,
1542. That [ __ ] cost.
Yeah, it's not too bad, bro. I can't
have anything g I can't have anything uh greasy.
No, not after drinking.
Not after drinking, mate. No. No way.
Yeah, like it's all right. Very rarely a kebab,
you know, like a shish kebab like every
6 months or something. But the way
people go on about it after drinking, it's like
I just never been big on them
like that, bro. To refer,
I'll be like, "Thank you, cunt." Ain't it, Grezy?
So, what do you reckon my mom is up to nowadays, Greavvesy?
Do you think she Do you think she went
on to have more kids?
Oh [ __ ] What are you doing, mister?
Hello, K. Yeah.
Thank you, L.
I won't eat again later hopefully.
Taking a baby away from its mama.
Do you think that's funny, Grezy?
Taking a baby away from its mama. H.
You think it's some sort of laugh,
some sort of joke?
Taking a baby away from its mama.
I think I said it in that way. Didn't I agree?
They're good like catchphrases, isn't it? Oh, Franklin.
What are you laughing at? Bezy the
taking the baby away from its mama. Oh, Franklin
signal Peter Belly's mama. Do you
remember that [ __ ] Nicolo account
keeps coming and mocking me? He keeps
teasing me in it.
Sig not Peter Belly's mama.
Sig is a woman I had a one night stand
with. She's like sig not Peter Belly's mama.
You know, like we used to
my cow eating partner.
Oh, I'm [ __ ] bro. I am actually Would
you approach women grievy if you was out
drinking with Peter Belly? Would you
would you approach women or nah? Really? Why not?
I find London very diverse.
Do you know what I mean by that, Grezy?
It's very diverse. Um,
it's hard to explain it. Oh,
I need some lamb in me,
Greg. I need some lamb in me, man.
Do you think I should go back to playing
roulette, Steven Howard? Nah. Nah, matey.
Nah. [ __ ] that, bro.
Them days are over.
Frankie. Yeah, but Frankie don't pay out.
Yeah, that's what I mean by diverse.
Like in London, you get loads of like
stuck up Indians.
Um like stuck up uh Indian heritage,
but they're they're obviously from here.
You know, what's the point of putting 20
pound in fish and frenzy? You're not
going to get anything.
You're not going to get anything with 20 pound.
I used to put 150 pound in it constantly.
God knows why I used to do it, but I did.
I remember when I used to stick like 500
pound in the fob tease, man, I was mad.
I used to just do it cuz I was depressed.
What the [ __ ] was I doing? I
I think women are hypocrites. Do you
Grievy? I think they're very hypocrites.
They go on like they don't like sex and
[ __ ] and whatever, but then they have
babies and [ __ ] They're very
hypocritical, aren't they?
What do you think, Greavvesy? Why don't
you tell us what you think, Greavvesy? [ __ ] Yeah,
I think they should be more honest like
men. What do you think, Greavesy? I
think they should be more honest like men.
They go on like they're innocent and sex
is nasty and it's weird to talk about it
and that but
then they it's just weird isn't it? I
find it weird me.
You know what the thing is [ __ ]
Steven Howard man I used to say to that
[ __ ] virgin mate I don't give a [ __ ]
what's socially acceptable or not you little can.
He used to say, "That's not socially acceptable."
I said, "I don't give a [ __ ] what's
socially acceptable. I don't want no
part of this [ __ ] society.
I don't care what's socially acceptable.
I don't want to be accepted." Who would
want to be accepted by this [ __ ]
this society? Grezy, not me. Would
you want to be?
Oh, only 12 12 minutes away. That's quite quick.
Quite a bit of [ __ ] show. It's [ __ ] [ __ ] man.
But the Chinese is also nice, isn't it,
Grievy? Nice. Nice Chinese.
Virgin boy. He's a big virgin, you know.
He's a big virgin.
He can't take the ass whooping.
That's why he runs to the police, Grezy,
cuz he can't stand the ass whooping.
that Peter Belly used to give him. I
used to literally take his trousers
down, get a ruler, and spank his ass so
bad that he had to get old Bill
involved. He had to get old Bill
involved over YouTube.
What a [ __ ] loser.
What a [ __ ] loser, bro.
You couldn't take the heat. You couldn't
take the heat in the kitchen.
We got old Bill involved. What a [ __ ]
loser. They always they they always go
to the police in the end, don't they, Grezy?
I ain't N they son.
Uh, a load of [ __ ] They wanted like
evidence as well cuz like the paperwork
through. So, this [ __ ] doesn't know what
I have on him, bro.
It's just like it's embarrassing, bro.
What I have on this [ __ ] you don't even
know the half of it. What I've got on
this little virgin. Seriously,
you don't delete your stuff quick
enough. That's all I'm saying, mate.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying, boy.
Hurry up. 10 minutes now. Yay. What's that?
Um, yeah. Oh, uh,
but it's London. It is London. I
actually was speak I actually met a guy
yesterday and he said he was from
Orington. I was like, "Oh yeah, I know
Orington and probably." and he was
trying to say it's London. I said,
"Mate, it ain't [ __ ] nothing to do
with London." I used to have a little
[ __ ] virgin used to try and tell me
the same thing. It's not [ __ ] London.
How can London be be 30? That's like
saying Readen is London. That's like
saying slow and reading is London. It's
not. They're nothing like us,
you know? And we were saying it jokingly
obviously like we were talking and
having a laugh, but I said it [ __ ]
ain't London, mate. I said it [ __ ] a.
It's nothing to do with London.
How far is that? One second.
Let me see how far it is.
There's quicker ways to get to it now.
Nah, it ain't London, mate.
It ain't [ __ ] London.
Greater London, so it ain't London. coming. [Music] Coming
It's a [ __ ] [ __ ] hole though from me
in Orington. It's like Little India.
It's [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. There's nothing
there. It's It's an absolute [ __ ] [ __ ] hole, you know.
Absolute [ __ ] mate. It's like Little India.
It actually is. It's just [ __ ] mate.
There's nothing there.
There's literally nothing there, mate.
It is a [ __ ] hole.
Honestly, Grezy, it is a [ __ ] It is a
is a [ __ ] tip. Honestly, Grezy,
what a virgin boy.
Do you remember when I done the posters? Grezy,
you laughed, didn't it? I told the
virgin, "Fuck off. Leave me alone, [ __ ]
[ __ ] it. Leave me alone, you bastard."
And he didn't believe me. I was like,
"Fuck this. I'm I'm doing it, mate.
Doing it." Do you like the posters, Grezy?
Did you like the little posters? That
That That That was good. I like the
little posters, man.
Dude, you like you like the posters, Ezy?
You liked it, didn't it?
I posted them everywhere, bro. Yeah,
but you should know, Grezy,
when it when it when it all when they
can't take no more, mate, it's the boys in blue.
It's the boys in blue, mate. It's the
[ __ ] boys in blue.
It's the boys in blue. I've just ordered
my kebab. Is it too early for a kebab, Greavves?
It's not It's not too early for a kebab,
is it, Grezy?
I just ordered mine, mix, I hope it
comes with bread.
Oh, now it's gone back to 10 minutes.
What the [ __ ]
Hurry up, you [ __ ] I'm [ __ ] hungry.
I don't think I was drinking yesterday. So,
it's not early for a kebab. Is it 4:00?
What do you think, Greavvesy? Is it
early or no? No.
Let's ask Let's ask Grezy.
And I I had a breakfast ear as well. I
paid for a breakfast ear as well. I
forgot about that.
[ __ ] Oh man.
If I get hungry again later,
that's what annoys me about the Indians.
They don't open until after 5. I hate it.
I hate it, bro. Cuz it's lunchtime from
12 and the Indians open at like 5.
I just have a pizza. I've got a picture
in the fridge.
Bro, I'm going. Yeah, I'm going to eat this kebab
and uh I I'll I'll be back later, 100%.