Oh. Oh, [ __ ]
That should should have killed him.
Yeah. Yeah, man. I'll be out today
looking for that chain.
Looking for Oh [ __ ] Almost got run over there.
Yeah, I'll be out today looking for that change.
be the last time now for like three
weeks. So, make it [ __ ] talent in it.
You know, I actually can't even be asked
today, bro, to go out. I'm actually
[ __ ] But I'm going to do it anyways
cuz I need to get some more numbers
since none of them replied. Hey, bro. I
was just watching um Egghehead and he
says, "Oh, that Red Star put up a new
video." Bear in mind, I got to watch
this loser Red Star cuz he's just
embarrassing himself on YouTube. So, I I
just felt bad. He's still stalking me.
Well, [ __ ] He's been He's been reacting
to me for months and I haven't even seen
it until now. Well, I didn't look at the
obsessed videos. It's crazy how obsessed
somebody could be on YouTube with
somebody that they don't know.
They're either jealous or they want to
[ __ ] you. They're either gay or they
want to or they're jealous of you. It's
strange, isn't it? Like they they spend
all of their life stalking me. Not Not
just like writing stuff. They actually
spend all their life stalking me. It's
insane, isn't it?
That's the joys of being better looking
than them, I guess.
Um, yeah, that's mad.
And they say that I'm skin, bro. You
spend all your life on YouTube
obsessing. That's exactly what a skin
person would do. Like these people,
that's exactly what And and the only
thing is is that even when you don't
watch their channel, they still do it.
They will literally waste like years of
their life to get about a 5second
mention. That's how that's how disabled
and lonely they are.
Yeah, they're definitely jealous, bro.
100%. Like why else would someone Yeah.
sit on YouTube 247 of their life
stalking someone? It's it's And and you
know what? Even people that don't like me,
um, they don't like that [ __ ] They they
know he's a coward and [ __ ] Like he he
is the worst for it. He is the biggest
coward you'll ever come across. He begs
um he begs them uh he begs uh Yeah,
true. He beg he begs the black man to do
[ __ ] They always do that. They always
beg the black man to do to do their
dirty work. But yeah, they're either
jealous or they gay or both.
for me. Uh, what was I saying, bro? No,
no, no. There was something else I was saying.
I forgot exactly what it was. Um,
what was I saying now, bro? [ __ ] know.
Can't remember what I seen.
I'll be out later. Oh [ __ ]
That rum really I had a McDonald's last
night. Ch. Man, I was [ __ ] hungry
again, bro. That rum [ __ ] KO'ed me.
The rum actually KO you, bro. It [ __ ]
knocks you out, man. Oh, it made me so
tired and hungry, man. No more running calls today.
So, no, I had McDonald's, breakfast, the
kebab. It was start of starving, bro.
Oh, yeah. Provident loans. He says that
I've got the worst life after Trump. I
was like, bro, I've got a better life
than probably most people in this
community. I mean, bro, wasn't you the
same guy that was showing 300 pound the
other week? He done a video to Lisa,
right? He done a video to Lisa saying
this is Huh? Yo, man.
Hey, sorry, man. I was talking to someone. [ __ ]
Um, yeah, I'll be out today getting some more numbers hopefully.
Like I said, I can't be bothered, but I
need some more numbers cuz none of them replied today.
And I'm [ __ ]
I think I'm still [ __ ] hung over, bro.
Oh, one of the matches start at 12
12:30, don't they? Yeah,
I'll be out there looking for that change.
I'm always looking for that change, man.
always looking for a change, but I'm not
bothered anyways. I'll just use escorts
into t until Thailand.
But I just want to say make sure I've
tried, you know, one last time. for a
long time. Anyways,
that one alone.
No one want to know your ugly art.
I would have brought Virgin Boy along
with me today. Maybe get him laid,
get him a date or something. But his
ugly face will scare all the women away.
I don't want that ugly face scaring him away.
You know, no one likes a rat. I know. I
have a phobia of rats, you know. That's
the only thing I got a phobia of, you
know, is is anything to do with the rodent family.
Like that's the only thing I don't like.
Not scared of heights or anything dark
like that or scared of women or any not
anything like that, you know? Nothing nothing ridiculous,
you know. But I'm scared scared of rats.
Not even scared of spiders, you know. So yeah,
I just think they're so ugly, you know, rats.
And he just looks like a rat and they're so ugly.
Can't stand even like when I look at
squirrels, they just remind me of rats
cuz their face I hate them. I do.
Oh [ __ ] bro.
Oh, what are you doing in my little car?
No, I'm not scared of spiders, man. I
just don't like rats or mice.
But yeah, Provident Loan says that I've
got I'm the I've got the worst life on
here other than tram. Do these people
realize that I'm the I'm probably like
the only one that leaves my house. I
actually go out drinking.
I actually go out socializing, something
that they don't even do. The [ __ ] bro?
Like, this guy's on there showing 300
[ __ ] pounds. He's literally on here
showing £300 to Lisa. This is my money
over the weekend.
Some money over the weekend
accent. I'm thinking, bro, what the [ __ ]
is this guy on about?
Is that supposed to be a flex that
you've got 300 for the weekend? Jesus [ __ ] Christ.
I don't understand this this disabled
community, bro. I really don't. Nope.
I don't give a [ __ ] I'm not a s. I
don't care about no [ __ ] [ __ ] on
this [ __ ] community, bro.
No, I wouldn't even watch it anyways. I don't care.
I am tired,
but I've got to get on the approaches today. Eh, sadly.
What do you think will happen today?
That boy, when I go out approaching.
Oh no, the middle one's better.
What do you think will happen? Any luck?
Yeah, I'll find the one. Yeah, they've
been saying that for three and a half years.
It's a bit hard. It's a bit hard to
believe it when you can't even get a
conversation out of someone nowadays,
but I'll take your word for it.
I mean, I done I done six approaches
sober yesterday. Uh that boy that that
boy and all I got was I've got a boyfriend.
I got five numbers and they didn't reply
which was very hard to get. But I trust
you, bro. I trust you.
Maybe this day in three and a half years,
maybe today out of all of them years
will somehow be different.
I would I personally wouldn't put my
money on it, but I mean it's worth a go
in it. It's worth a try,
you know. It's worth a try. I mean, what
would the odds even be?
One in a million, maybe. Who knows?
Probably one in a million.
Like I said, if I was a virgin, like
virgin boy, I'd probably approach like
every day until like I found someone.
But obviously, I'm not a virgin like
him. And I've been with people, so I
don't I'm not really asked, bro. I'd
rather go somewhere where it's more in
my favor. That's what a smart person
does. You see how I don't gamble on
roulette now or slot? I'd rather do
something that's a little bit more in my favor.
Which obviously makes sense, isn't it?
Oh, what did you do to the car, Franklin?
Little silly case.
I am [ __ ]
One second, bro.
Yeah, man. Sorry.
But yeah, I'll be out there today.
Yeah, sorry. I was talking to someone.
I'll be out there today looking for that change. Cari,
I'm retiring soon from this. So, you
know. Yeah. Hopefully today I'll find
that change. I'm not drinking no [ __ ]
rum today. [ __ ] that.
That That rum is lethal, mate. I hate
the hangovers. I [ __ ] hate them.
I think that white rum is the worst,
isn't it? It is.
I'm hungry again. This is what I mean, bro.
They get you for like two days, two and
a half days, then you feel bet, then you
feel fine again after two and a half
days. It really messes with me that that
white rum, bro. Like poison.
Yeah, I would have went out with Virgin
Boy Richie, but I don't want him scaring
all the birds away with his ugly face.
It's already hard enough trying to get a
[ __ ] woman in this country and then
you got someone's [ __ ] ugly face next to you.
You ugly bastard. I mean, I mean, my my
words hurt even more because I don't run
to the boys in blue, you know? I don't I
don't do that kind of [ __ ] on this channel.
I literally pull his pants down and
spank him with a ruler every time. Open
my mouth, mate.
That's why he runs to the boys in blue.
Same as Red Star, cuz I own them. Own
them in every aspect.
I Provident loans. Listen, if you're
watching this, yeah, I know you watch my
channel. I know you watch my channel
with Tim and cookies.
That silly accent that you have. Listen, you really,
really, really want to start showing
money. There you are. Okay. Show me my
10 grand that I've been asking for for
[ __ ] two years,
year and a half. Don't know why I said
two years. about 18 months been asking
for 10 grand to be shown and no one can
show me at Cory. They keep running away
changing the subject. It's ridiculous.
It's Ricky Das.
I still ain't been showing my little £10,000. Bless me.
Oh my god, bro.
I need to eat some um
I probably need to eat and probably go
sleep again, bro, if I'm going out later.
Oh, bro, it ain't a joke. I just had to
take some cucumber as well, man.
It's trying to help me sleep.
See, the thing is you get happy hour
deals on rum, Richie,
and you don't think about the next day,
you know? You don't think about the next
day. You you just [ __ ]
just just drink it cuz it's like two pound.
It's like [ __ ] two pound. So you just
[ __ ] you just drink it, you know?
So yeah, you you don't think about the
next day because why would you?
And then you just [ __ ]
I might go and get some piggies.
Nah, of course it will change. Jay
Johnny, stop being so bloody negative.
You're so negative you are, bro. I need
to start saving money now as well. I
don't get I don't get as much as I used to.
But it doesn't matter, bro.
Yeah, but bro, I want to try. What? No,
no, no. I tell you the reason why I'm
trying and I'll explain it to you. Yeah.
So when I get my haircut,
like it grows very fast and it's kind of expensive, right?
But that's why I can't just go out one
day. So I want to get my money's worth
from this haircut and then at least I
can say I tried. I got some numbers and
then I won't I won't do it now for like
3 weeks or a month. Eventually I will
just give up. Eventually I will just
give up. Trust me, bro.
Yeah, I am looked maxed, but it doesn't
it doesn't make a difference anyways.
You're still going to get boyfriend.
You're still going to get it. You're
still going to get I have a boyfriend,
bro. I looked good yesterday. I I Bro, I
come out the barbers. Listen, listen. I
was wearing my Reese clothes yesterday.
Nice after shave, fresh haircut straight
out the barbers. I don't approach by the
barbers. Sorry, I have a boyfriend.
Uh, it makes no difference if you're looks maxed.
You're still going to hear I have a
boyfriend. You could look like a [ __ ]
You could be looks maxed.
Yeah, it's not going to change ever. But
because my I have had my haircut, I do
want to just get numbers so I can say to
myself, oh, I tried my money's worth
with a haircut. So, yeah,
it's [ __ ] up, isn't it?
Lucky we don't want kids, eh?
Lucky we don't want children. Jesus Christ.
Is it a good haircut? I'll show you if you want.
Yeah, man. I know.
Yeah, a little bit. I'm probably just
going to curl the hair up. I need to go
back to sleep soon, though, bro. I'm
going out later cuz I still feel a bit
[ __ ] I'm probably going to go and eat
some piggies. See him?
Yeah, man. Yeah, I was on LJ's channel. Yeah.
Uh, it's not no luck of the [ __ ] draw at all.
It's no luck of the [ __ ] draw.
Oh, [ __ ] me, bro. It's no luck of the draw.
It will never change in this country, bro.
But I have my hair done, so I'm just
going to go out and do it again.
It's going to be [ __ ] hard today, man.
Like I said, if I was a virgin, like
Virgin Boy, I would just do it every day
until I got something. But I don't have
the time. I don't have the energy anymore.
But I just want some sort of change today. All
right, that red star is still stalking
me, Nicolo. I went I was watching a bit
of LJ and he and and that red star is
still stalking me and I've not been on
that channel for like 3 years. I think
he wants to bum me.
[ __ ] I think he wants to bum me, bro.
He spends all his life trying to make me
insecure about the way I look and it's
never going to work. Look, Red Star,
this is something that you can never do.
Show your face.
You can never show your face cuz you're
not good looking like Peter Belly. You
will never be able to show your face
with a cup of [ __ ] How does that make you feel?
You will never be able to show your face
cuz you're an ugly bastard.
You know what I mean? Must kill them
that they can't show their face,
isn't it, Nikolai?
I'm not I'm not going to leave as early
today. I'll probably leave about three or four.
So, what do you think? What What results
do you reckon I'm going to get today, Johnny?
Can't believe none of them numbers reply
back. [ __ ] man. Oh, [ __ ] me. I look
good. Oh, thank you. You, too.
[ __ ] it down, man.
Yeah, I might I might just start going
to the gym again, Nicolo, and become a
wrestler. Would you watch me on TV if I
became a wrestler?
Not one of them, bro. Not one of them.
Not even one of them.
Because we don't take no [ __ ] L's, bro.
We don't take no L's. It's like what
Antman said. He said, do you know what
Ant-Man said to me? He was like,
"When you was out there, they were
laughing at you." That's what he said to
me. He said, "When you was out there
traveling up and down the country, they
were laughing at you." He's trolling me,
isn't it? Yeah. He said they were
laughing at you. They were mocking you.
Well, hopefully it's a better result today, Johnny.
You know, hopefully it's a better result.
I find my mama. Hopefully I find my mama
today. Is it?
O, stop putting up your middle finger, Frankie.
That's very rude. I might go.
I'm hungry, bro.
You can't even get Gregs cuz everything
there is cold.
Do you know what I could do with a nice
omelette? Oh, that would do me right up.
Like an omelette. M
like a nice piggy omelette. Get a Nando.
N I don't want the shits, mate. I'm I
need to be out all day approaching. I
don't want the shits.
Oh, a nice piggy. A nice piggy omelette.
Rice piggy and mushroom omelette. How
does that sound, Greavesy?
Omelets on nice, man.
It's not greasy as well.
I mean, I could technically order KFC,
but I mean, nah, I don't want chicken
that bad. It's like I said, it's that
guy in Liverpool. He kept [ __ ]
talking about chicken.
That's why I got KFC in the morning the
other day, bro. It was [ __ ] madness.
So, what what do you reckon the results
going to be today anyways, Johnny? One second.
I know exact I know exact want an
omelette. That's exactly what I want.
Let me see if there's any places that
does an omelette.
No, one sec. Um,
yeah. But people on Reddit say that life
changes. You never know.
I know it's a waste of time today, bro.
But I have to do it. I have to do it.
I have to do it, bro.
I have to do it. I mean, it's a shame I
had that 19year-old. I could be sat here
playing GTA San Andreas, having my todd, you know.
Uh, people on Reddit said, "I'm I'm I'm
a good-looking lad. I'll be married
soon." They used to say to me, Johnny,
that, "Oh, you're you're a good-looking
chap. You'll be you um you'll find your
wife soon." They used to tell me. Yeah.
See, Gregs is pointless because
the thing is is
everything's cold there. So, there's no point.
I want an omelette, you know.
That's what I want.
That's what I had with Monty. He's my
pig eating partner, you know.
Breakfast. That's what we want.
Yeah. They don't even do any breakfast things.
CS are so expensive nowadays. Yeah.
Gregs. No, we don't want Gregs.
It's going to be hard to try and find
someone that does an omelette cuz it's
all [ __ ] allowed. It's like [ __ ]
thingies area. Virgin boys. [ __ ] Little India.
It's Little India, mate.
There's a cap here, but
was trying to find one that does the
bacon. Obviously, this is going to be difficult.
Yeah, you could get So, do you know the
best thing in Gregs is the bacon and
cheese wraps, but you can never get them
warm because no one buys them. When they
put them out, they just stay there all
day. But that's why I just get the
sausage rolls, but the bacon and cheese
wraps are way better, bro. Way better.
No, I want an omelette.
That's what I And that's what I want. It's okay.
I'll just wait.
I don't want like a full English. I want
like um an actual omelette. Oh, they do pork chops.
No, you they can't warm it, bro. It's It's ruined.
That's okay. I'll just wait.
I'll wait until it's been made.
No, it don't taste the same, bro.
Because when they put it in that thing,
it dries out. So, you can only have it
realistically 10 minutes after it's come
out. Oh, it's no good.
Yeah. Well, I don't know if you've ever
had it from Gregs. I remember I was in
Manchester. Yeah. 5:00 in the morning. I
was trying to One sec. Omelette. Here we go.
Right. Ham and cheese omelette.
Sausage omelette. Bacon omelette.
No, I don't really fancy that, bro. Cuz
I don't I think it's going to come cold.
That's okay. I'll just wait. I want a
nice piggy and mushroom omelette. I'll
be out all day today, so I'm going to
need it. And I'll probably eat it and
then go sleep and wake up and then go out.
I need to try and find a new mama. Nicolo
need to go and find a new mama today.
Yeah, I need to find a new mama.
Yeah, you take the piss out of it. But
[ __ ] mate, I used to go out approaching. Yeah.
Approach, approach, approach, approach,
approach. And then at the end of the
day, I used to just have a t-bone steak,
like spend like £100 in a restaurant.
Obviously, Virgin Boy can't afford that
cuz he's [ __ ] skin. But, you know,
that's what I used to do at the end of
the night, bro.
Come to think of it, it's been going on
for years now.
It's been going on for [ __ ] years, you know?
Yeah, I don't really want to order it
because it's not going to be warm.
Oh yeah, that Ukrainian one by the old
house. Yeah, he was cl Yeah, [ __ ]
everyone was All right. Um yeah.
Yeah. The you had the Ukrainian one by
the shop. Yeah. The Ukrainian one by the shop. Um
everyone was like, "Oh, you should go do
it. You should do it." I said, "I don't
know. I can't be bothered." And I done
it. Was talking for like maybe 3 4
minutes and then they gave their number.
They still never replied to this day to
be honest. And then they were like, "Um,
um, what what happened?" I think she said, "Um,
and then all all of a sudden I hear this
clap, like clap clap clap." And I'm
thinking, "Where the [ __ ] is where?" And
he it was on the It was in the B. It was
on the balcony.
Um, and I was like, "A funny as shit."
It gathered a crowd.
Yeah. I've got Olden, Swindon,
Cambridge, Havaget, and Shby and Colchester.
I got three £21 um and
and um £21 and
no 21 uh 20 returns 142.
But I don't know if I'm going to get three teams. teams, but
see, I'd put big money on two teams, but
I don't want to lose three, four, 500
pound. That's the thing.
I can't really If I was to put two300
pound on something, I'll just play roulette.
Cuz with football, it only takes one
team to screw you. One one team not
scoring and then that's it, you know?
I mean, I don't play with it anymore,
but you know what I mean. Like,
but yeah, I done a I done a treble
treble one this time.
I put that money away for going out
drinking, which was yesterday and
Thursday and obviously today.
Time's not as easy now, matey.
It's not as easy now, but yeah.
So, that's $142. It's just still a good
profit from 20. Yeah.
Did um the USA Izzy's friend reply? Let
me have a little look. Uh,
I bet she blocked me in it.
No, she never. She just never replied.
Maybe she quit Instagram. Eh, no chance.
Yeah, I just said your friend's an evil [ __ ]
So, I'm going to have an omelette, go
back to sleep, then um
yeah, send these approaches later.
I'm not looking forward to it, mate.
But I need to get some numbers though.
I said to Antman, "Yeah, I said to him,
hopefully I don't get I've got a
boyfriend to today." He says, "You will. It's obvious."
No, not really. Why is it obvious?
No, it's not. It's hard, bro. And it's
hard doing it sober because the [ __ ]
negative results are [ __ ]
I don't have the energy anymore, Cory.
It's It's the fact that I don't have the
energy and I already know the result.
That's what makes you just lose it
because you already know the result. And
um I just don't feel like I've got the
energy anymore for it, bro. You know,
but I'm doing it today 100%. that's
happening cuz need some more numbers. I
can't believe none of these numbers replied.
And this is what I went through for
about two years.
Um, Nicolo, before I met USA, I went
through this for about a year and a
half, two years, this [ __ ]
but I did get kisses and stuff. So, I
mean, I actually did I did get things
here and there. I must have I must have
got things here and there,
but now you can't get anything. So
is what it is.
Yeah. Not one of them numbers replied,
did they? That's unusual for Thursday one.
Who's that? One, two. Yeah.
What's the phone percent on?
I need to get some batteries, man.
[ __ ] Good night.
I need to add another notch. What do you
mean? Yeah, I need to add some more to
the [ __ ] collection today.
You reckon this football bet's going to win, Nicolo? Nah.
I know, man. I know. I know.
Bastards, aren't they? Mhm.
So, where's my mama, Nicolo?
Yeah. I need like a nice omelette to
seal the stomach, you know? Nothing
greasy, just something really nice, you know?
All of it. You just used to see how many
women's numbers I've got on my phone.
But it doesn't change. That's the thing.
It don't change. It doesn't change.
It just doesn't change, does it?
I said to someone, "Let's go to a
steakhouse." They said, "I have a boyfriend now."
That must be so Yeah, bro. Of course,
bro. Of course, today is the day, bro.
Why would you think today is not the day?
Like, what would actually give you that impression?
You know, all of this, you know, today
where it's like
it's like Undertaker, right? He had a streak for
20 well, I think it was 21 years, then
he got beat by Brock Lesnar, right?
And he was winning. And he was winning.
But that streak ended. Today is today,
bro. Of course it is. Three in a yacht.
Three and a half years of being [ __ ]
around with here. And I have a boyfriend
dealing with the same [ __ ] constantly.
Of course, today is going to be
different, bro. Today is the day.
It's It's my lucky day today, man.
Why wouldn't you think it's it's going
to be my lucky day? Just think of the Undertaker,
you know, he eventually got beat. So
today I'll eventually beat them.
Even though I'm probably about a million to one,
not not 21 to1. Or you could see the
flip side. It took him 21 years to get
beaten. I mean, I probably do more than
21 approaches a day, but you know, today
will somehow be different than them
three and a half years.
I can just feel it, you know. I can just feel it.
Three and a half years is going to come
to an end today. Yeah.
Hopefully they got them [ __ ] Tik Tok batteries in. What's that?
They're all NPCs.
NPCs, bro. I don't know where is she.
Sign not Peter Belly's mama.
I don't know where my mama is. Not sure.
No, I don't know.
Remember LT Nico
when he was born in USA? Is he? Yeah.
You remember he was warning her that
he said I didn't believe it until I saw
you boo that you actually booked it. Yeah.
Yeah. It was funny, ain't it, mate?
Oh, [ __ ] How many numbers you reckon
we'll get today? Probably like three in it.
I don't know why anyone would want that [ __ ]
I said you could go. I said you could
go. I said if you ever want her, you can
go and see her. You can go there. It
won't bother me, mate.
You remember when Virgin Boy kept texting her,
a [ __ ] got all of these people. It's
like people have a one night stand with
me, Nicolo, and then they start getting
messages from people on [ __ ] uh
YouTube. Oh, it's happening today. Oh,
that's another thing. Yeah. I need to go
to that guy's workplace.
Yeah. Oxford Circus. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm got Yeah. S. Yeah. He
works on SA. Yeah.
I'm going to be dead today. Anyways. Mhm.
So why did my mommy abandon me then? Greasy. Yeah,
there's nothing wrong with eating pork.
I think that's such a stupid I don't
agree with some of their um their things like
like circumcision. That's just child abuse.
You know, child just it's just child abuse.
No, I think I think the best saying is Yeah.
You're my mama, nobody else's. I thought
that was the best saying that I come up with.
You're my mama, nobody else's.
Grievesy, it's cute, is it? Ah, it's my mama.
But imagine having a one night stand
with somebody and then all of these
people from YouTube are messaging you.
These people don't know what they're in for,
do they? When they meet Peter Belly,
they think I'm one of these little simps
that they can [ __ ] with. Yeah. After
they sleep with or after they go on a
date with, they seem to think that I'm
one of these simps that
that they can win against. Do you know
what I mean, Grezy?
And then when they can't, they can't win
against me. Well, mate, it's the boys in
blue, then it greasesy.
They start a very good game, a very good
psychological game. But we all know when
it gets a bit tough, when it gets a bit
tough, it's the boys in blue, mate.
It's the boys in blue
or they [ __ ] report you to Instagram.
Women are cowards, man. They actually
are They're actually cowards.
They really are cowards, you know.
They really are, bro.
Them [ __ ] were laughing at us. You see,
they were laughing at us. That's why I
went to that Kenzie's workplace, bro.
Like this was like a few years ago, like
back in December, and
I just couldn't let it lie. That [ __ ]
was coming on YouTube laughing at me,
and he was actually doing it. And I I
just [ __ ] snapped.
They were laughing at us.
And then he he he tried playing the
victim as well. He told me to come to
his workplace. He was winding me up.
Literally winding me up. And then I went
there. And then he he he started saying
that I was stalking him. The [ __ ]
you know, like what the [ __ ] Izzy said,
"Oh, I don't find that funny." Yeah, you
don't find it funny because it's your
friend that I'm doing it to.
Whereas when [ __ ] Prime grabbed me,
she was she was the first one there.
When that Prime grabbed me, Yeah. she
was the first one there laughing at me.
But when I owned Kenji, you [ __ ] She
didn't find that funny, did she? No.
You dirty little mare.
I always used to call her a little fluttershy.
That's why I always used to call
Isabelle Nicolo. Fluttershy.
You know Fluttershy, don't you, Greasy?
My little pony.
I used to say to my sister as well, you
got Isabelly's hair. You look like a
little pony. I used to say to my sister,
you and your little pony hair. Yeah. Fluttershy. Uh
Yeah. Do you remember the Isabelle Times Greavesy?
That was a kathuffle, wasn't it?
That was a [ __ ] kathuffle.
Yeah. She just reminded me of a little pony.
Yeah, I remember her, man.
That's what I'm saying. I was in Monty's
position, but I was I was in his
position when I was like 21.
That's why I was shocked at his like
response because I've been in that, but
it was back when I was like 21 sort of thing.
I like, "Oh yeah, if they don't reply,
then I'm going to move on." And then
but and then I remember one day yeah I
used my mom's phone to message her and I
said oh like can you please unblock me
and then I woke up at like 1:00 in the
morning and then I got a little message
from little Isabelle and I was like oh
my god she's back. I was over the moon
and then we had a little call at like
2:00 in the morning
you know. Yeah, I I will never forget
that, bro. How can you forget, you know?
You'll never forget that.
Bear in mind, I never I was a virgin.
Like a virgin boy. Like Well, I used
escort. I mean, you know what I mean?
Like somebody that wasn't an escort. I
was I was a ver I was a virgin in that
way like he is now. And um [ __ ]
yeah, it was just nice to find someone
that actually wanted to meet you.
He completely rinsed me as well. Grievy,
do you remember that time I met Lil Isabelle,
you know, and Mr. G was online and
Triple H was online and um you remember
she rinsed my little roulette wings. I
won £300 and
it was quite a lot of well still quite a
lot of money now you know in ways but it
was quite a lot of money to me back then and
I won it on the roulette wheel
and then she completely rinsed me dry
grievy she completely rinsed me and then
got off with another man the first time
I met her and then she got on with
another man she got off with another man
Greavvesy so she rinsed all my money my hard-earned
and then left me.
>> Yeah, she was a nasty bastard.
She was a nasty bast. Yeah. [ __ ] sake.
Fingers crossed today. Egg Johnny.
Okay, Johnny, I've got I've got a
question for you. Yeah, you tell me not
to bother today
cuz it's going to be the same old result and ret.
Yeah, but people on Reddit say you have
to keep trying. It will happen.
But people on Reddit say like it will
happen. You just need to be patient and
stuff. So, how can I believe you and not them?
£200. I'm not going to spend £200, bro.
What the [ __ ] Probably about 70 80.
I know you're not even ugly and you
can't get anything. That's the worst
thing about it.
My standards are not too high, bro. They
were average looking, bro. I I
approached someone yesterday. They had
braces. I approached all different kinds
of people. Most of the people in this
country are average. They're not even
good-looking. You don't really get many
good-looking people here. Well, you
don't get good-looking women here. Not really,
bro. It's not Sweden.
It's not Sweden, bro.
Yeah. It's still the same.
It's still the same, bro. If that
football bet wins today, then I'll go to Cardiff.
But if not, then nah.
Doesn't matter who you go for, bro,
you're still going to get uh the same [ __ ]
They're they're not even that
good-looking in London, bro. They're
just like average. So So yeah,
doesn't matter who you go for, bro.
You're still going to get the I've got a boyfriend.
If I win this football bet, I'm going to
go to Cardiff today.
I'm going to do an all nighter. So, yeah.
But anyways, man, that's
Yeah, it is mad, bro. It is mad. Anyone
would think I look like Timmy Eldridge.
Bro. Yeah. No, no, no, no, no. Listen,
listen. Yes. But the only reason I'm
going out is cuz I had my haircut
and it was expensive and my hair grows
back quick. So, I need to I'm getting my
money's worth. After today, I won't try
again for probably like a month or ever.
I'm going out because I had my haircut.
So, I have to go out again. I have to
make the most of it.
Just what else am I going to do? just
sit in all day.
I'm not going to just sit in all day,
bro. You know what I'm saying?
Look, it's only cuz I had my haircut I'm
getting my money's worth. So,
Oh, yeah. He's an ugly bastard.
He's obsessed with my [ __ ] nose.
There. Nothing wrong with my little
nose. It's cute. He always talks about
my nose. I'm thinking I I told that joke.