Oh, [ __ ] Get out.
That was a That was That was a lovely piggy omelette.
That was a [ __ ] lovely piggy omnit if
I must if I must say so myself. Yep.
I'm actually tired now. All right. Time
for Betty B. Sure.
I think it's time for By
for a couple of hours.
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
I'm going out uh later. John Street.
Yeah, I'm going out for a session.
Looking for that change
to see if it changes today.
Let's see if I don't hear that
boyfriend. Bloody [ __ ]
I need to have a couple of hours though,
man. Try and get a couple of hours.
Hopefully today is the day ain't it, Grezy?
I even said if if if if I don't get the
I got a boyfriend [ __ ] I'll give you my
TV and I'll give you £1,000.
Now, I'm not addicted to YouTube. I was
off of it for like four or five days,
bro. I'm not addicted.
I just haven't done anything the past
two days, bro. I'm not addicted
at all. I think it's a [ __ ] place
full of [ __ ] Mongols. Self
projectors. That's what it is. It's not even addicting.
And like I was saying to you, bro, that
when you're actually off this, you
actually realize how [ __ ] it is.
Even more so. I mean, I don't watch any
channels, so I only go live on my own channel.
I don't I What do you watch?
I don't know if you watch any other
channels, do you? I don't watch any
other channels, bro. Cuz it's just the
same projectors. It's just the same
people every day.
So I don't I don't bother because it's
just the same people every day on LJ's.
That's why I stop watching it.
Same self projectors.
Uh they're not bad. I don't watch Mark.
I don't watch Tan Mark.
I feel I feel lucky though cuz you and
Nicolo I never see I never used to see
you and Nicolo and L J's but you come on
mine which is quite good
>> yeah I'm happy that you and Nicolo
watched me I must be quite entertaining. You know,
you watch uh
Greasy, you don't watch the um
take it you don't watch the Virgin then.
You don't watch the Virgin boy.
Probably pointless to be honest with
you, man. Because it's just all about
me. Obsessive. So, you probably don't
watch the Virgin. No.
So, it's just me, Kitty, and M. That's
all right, then.
Oh, man. My [ __ ] He had a piggy
omelette. Was tasty, Greavves. He had a
lovely piggy omelette.
It was delicious.
Franklin, why are you putting your
middle finger up, you naughty man?
Franklin is such a naughty man. Graves.
He's a naughty naughty man.
This [ __ ] is a naughty man. Yeah. One sec.
Might get a roast dinner tomorrow.
Greavves. I'm not sure yet.
Football start soon. One of my matches
start soon. Let's get one out the way.
And then we've only got two, don't we, Greavves?
Is that okay with you, boss?
Nah, this bet ain't winning today. To be
honest with you, I probably won't even
sleep to be honest with you.
Nah, to be honest, I probably won't even sleep, lad.
I'd like to, but we got some approaches
to do. Otherwise, we're never going to
see that change.
We're never going to we're never going
to see that change. Greavvesy,
what do you think about it? Just looking
for that change.
You know, you like that little saying,
my eyes are [ __ ] bro. Oh, man.
That's what happens when you get on the
old RMI calls. Greavvesy.
When you get on the old Ramy calls, I'll wait.
You'll You'll wait. Yes. Until it's been made.
Until it's been made, eh?
Rocket laughing it. Yeah, man.
One sec, man. [ __ ]
Oh, you know what? Yeah. He He You know
what Monty's just done? He's blocked me
just for saying that he's he's [ __ ]
living together with Natalie.
He said he just sent me a voice not
saying, "Oh, bro, no one knows where
you're [ __ ] living firstly and so
what if I mention that?" Yeah, what the
[ __ ] bro? It's not like I've gave the address.
[ __ ] him anyways, bro. I don't give a
[ __ ] Simple, man. Don't come crying to
me again when [ __ ]
you know, it all goes wrong. You see
what I mean with people? Greasy. What?
Because I said one thing that you're so
what, bro? Everyone knew you was
together. The [ __ ] How you going to see
each other if you're not living with each other?
The [ __ ] He's an idiot, man. Well,
good. You can block me all you want.
That's fine. I don't give a [ __ ]
See, you see what I mean, Grezy?
It's the same thing, bro. Like, you know
what I mean?
Cuz he's a [ __ ] idiot, bro. [ __ ] it, man.
Yeah, Monty. He's like, "Oh, he blocked
me because I I said that, oh, he's
living with Natalie." Anyone would think
I [ __ ] doxed [ __ ] address. Yeah,
he can block me. Good for him, bro.
Good. Don't come crying to me. This is
what I mean, bro. With these with with
with people. Would you understand
about telling your [ __ ] what that you're
living with someone? Anyone would think
that I doxed you. [ __ ] him anyways, bro.
I don't care.
Don't come. Yeah, it is silly. It is
silly. [ __ ] him anyways, bro. Cool. I
don't give a [ __ ]
Oh, why are you telling people my [ __ ]
What? Because I said that you're living
with Natalie. So what, bro?
Why are you even on YouTube listening?
How would you know that if you weren't
on YouTube? Think of it, Grevy. How
would they know if they weren't on
YouTube? Think of it.
[ __ ] idiots, man.
So what if I [ __ ] said that?
So [ __ ] what? Huh? You know,
you you said you said that you wanted
everyone to know that you're with her.
Yeah. And I just said that you was
living together. So, and how would you
know that if you wasn't on YouTube? Let
me let me ask you that, Grezy. Yeah. How
would you know that if you wasn't on YouTube?
Answer me that, bro. How how would they
know if they weren't on YouTube? Think of it.
Bro, that guy, he would have been literally
[ __ ] without me, bro. You understand?
This is what I mean with these people,
bro. [ __ ] them. This is why I don't like
I don't bother with people.
Yeah. Well, no, there is people that
leave though. Ant-Man has actually left.
He doesn't watch anyone. No, there is a
few people that have left and they don't
watch for real.
No, there is there is people there is a few people
telling people your [ __ ] You literally
told everybody that you was back with
her. You understand
what happened [ __ ] with what happened
to bros before hoes, man? Seriously,
[ __ ] hell, man. He's [ __ ] in his
head, bro. Honestly, he is [ __ ]
He actually is [ __ ] in it.
Oh, there's no point calling me, Monty.
I'm not speaking to you, man. You block
me, you can block me again. Let me
listen to this again.
And I also never said where you was
living either. So try again. I didn't
actually say where you was living.
So what? I said that you're living with
someone. Where, bro? Where were you
living? Anyone would think I actually
docked where he was living. What the
[ __ ] bro? Anyways, [ __ ] it, bro. I'm
not I'm not listening. I'm not listening
to your voice notes either.
The [ __ ] man. [ __ ] him, bro. I I can't be bothered.
Why are you watch Why are you on YouTube anyways?
Uh why are you on YouTube, bro?
Uh why are you Why are you on YouTube, man? Oh,
yeah. You can keep sending me voice
notes. I'm not listening. [ __ ] me.
Yeah, you get a job. Yep. Same same to
you then. I've seen you on LJ's.
You get yourself a job, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] Yeah, same to you as well. sat
on large J's up people's ass, you little
jobless bastard. Yeah, same to you. You
You get off of YouTube. You're on
YouTube every day. You get yourself a
job, you [ __ ]
Yeah, tell yourself that, [ __ ] boy.
And I don't sit on YouTube every day.
I've got a life on like you. I don't sit
there and watch people I don't like
every day like you, you sad bastard.
Yeah, that's that's another thing. You
literally are on YouTube every day cuz
I've seen you.
Yeah, you get yourself a job, you
[ __ ] spasticated bastard.
Disabled [ __ ] Yeah, same same advice
back at you. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
bastard. On LJ's licking ass. I've seen
you on LJ's licking ass. Talking like
you all slowing at. Shut up, you jordy
[ __ ] You know,
you're another one on the list that goes
quiet when people go to your city.
You're another one.
You're just another one.
Isn't that right? Um Grezy is another one.
I don't sit on YouTube every day. I can
get off of YouTube unlike you. You can't
take a day off of YouTube.
Not even one day.
You literally sit on YouTube all day,
every day. You [ __ ] disabled bastard.
That's why if you ever catch a L's live
stream, same disabled people every day.
You know what I mean?
Same to you, man.
And to you, Monty, as well.
I don't know, man. Ask yourself that. I
said one thing, Monty. What are you on about?
I said one [ __ ] thing. I didn't say
where you [ __ ] lived.
Did I even say that? Anyways, I don't
know, bro. Ask yourself,
you'd have to ask yourself that question
and you'd find out the answer.
It is it is it is entertaining. Yeah,
sometimes this is, bro.
You You are gay and you have Tourette's.
So ask yourself that question, you
little self projector.
It's not too late, man.
Oh [ __ ] this starts in 30 minutes.
Why are jobless bums that ain't got a
life telling other people to get a job?
Jobless spasticated people telling other
people to get a job. It makes me laugh
that does it make you laugh. Grezy,
should they be getting themselves a job
before wondering about other people? Yeah, man.
Uh, I don't know. Treble both teams to score.
I'm going out later to smash these approaches.
I'm going to do a lot of them sober as well. Yeah, man.
No, no, no, no, no.
Uh, I put £2120 on it and it pays £142.
So, quite a bit from 20 odd pound. The
first match starts uh in 12 minutes. So, yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. It's good return really afy. Matey.
Oh, they all stalk my Yeah, bro. They
They all do it, bro. Like you'll tell
them a bet. Yeah. This is what they do.
These little spastics on here. Yeah. Say
you do a double and you put 80 pound on
it. They'll be like, "Oh, what what's
the teams?" And then you'll tell them
the teams, right? And they'll literally
stalk your bets. Like they don't even
worry about their bets. They're so
they're such weirdos on here, these
little mongos that they that they
literally will stalk your bet, right?
and watch to see if it loses and then
when you lose they'll be like h you lost
80 pound like 80 pound anything to me
because obviously they're skin so yeah
that's why like I told you this one
because it's 20 pound and I don't give a
[ __ ] I done it a few days ago but in
future I'm not I'm not telling my bets
because of these stalkers these stalking
spastics so in future you're not going
to know if I won and you're not going to
know if I lost.
Yeah, they literally stalk your bets.
That's how obsessed they are. And they
do their own football bets as well.
That's the That's the That's the thing, bro.
It's cuz they're weirdos on here. That's why. Weirdos. Spooking weirdos. Yeah. Franklin. Franklin shooting.
Do you like Franklin? I like Franklin's
little name. I think it's quite cute. Franklin.
Yeah, it's cute. Punch. punch.
There we go.
Oh, [ __ ] police just killed me, man.
So, what are we predicting for today's
outing then? Uh, Greasy,
what are we predicting for um today's outing?
What kind of result?
How the [ __ ] does he kill them with one punch?
He punches Franklin punches these
people. Yeah. And he and he kills them
with one punch. How the [ __ ] do you kill
someone with one punch? The [ __ ]
You know, I could go [ __ ] mad at
Monty if I wanted to. [ __ ]
introducing me to that [ __ ] virgin
that won't leave me alone. But you know,
I you don't see me getting [ __ ] mad about it.
That [ __ ] virgin, bro. [ __ ] virgin [ __ ] you know?
Don't see me having a [ __ ]
I do say that sometimes. I can't believe
you actually introduced me to that [ __ ] virgin.
[ __ ] stalking little ratfaced weirdo.
You can't get laid. Never been laid in his life.
Oh, I just done that. I just came from
the beach actually. Oh [ __ ]
Oh, that Joe F is a troll, isn't he? Grezy.
Yeah, that Joe F's a troll, ain't it, man?
Virgin boy scared of escorts,
dude. Who Who do you dislike the most?
Yeah, but he is a bit slow. You know
that Jo, he's he's a bit slow though, ain't he?
He's a bit slow at times. He is a bit
slow at times. I'm sure you've noticed
that as well.
He's a bit slow. He is a bit slow. I
guess it's old age, isn't it?
What about Virgin Boy?
What's your opinion on the Virgin? H
I don't watch that.
It it's very stupid what that's why I
done that video to Joe cuz I was trying
to help him understand. I don't know if
he's stupid or he was just trolling. He
says, "Oh, they do what they do for
reaction." But I was trying to explain
to him that they are reacting to me. For
them to be wasting all that time every
day doing videos and stalking me, that
is reacting. That is taking time out of
your day. So that's where none of it
makes sense. But he didn't understand
what I meant. So I mean slow people be
slow in it.
It's like the whole you don't react to
get a reaction. You write things. And
what I was trying to explain is they're
actually reacting. Like if you go on
that red okay let me give an example.
Right. If you go on that Red Star
channel, how long has this [ __ ] been
stalking me and how often do I ever
mention this [ __ ] I mentioned it today
cuz L went on about it. So I thought,
let me go on the channel. It's been a
couple of months. So it doesn't make it
what he's saying doesn't make sense. So
you're reacting every day, being
triggered every day, embarrassing
yourself every day on YouTube to get a
reaction once every 3 months. Okay. And
then so you reacted to get a reaction
and now what?
It doesn't make sense. Do you
understand, Greavves? It doesn't doesn't
make any sense.
And that's the whole point of it being a
disabled community, you know,
cuz it is a disabled community, bro. It
is very disabled. [Music] Yeah, man. Yeah.
You having a McDonald's? What? What?
What? What's for dinner today, Grezy?
Oh, no. Franklin. Franklin's on the beach now.
What's for your dinner today?
What are you having for tea or supper?
Oh, bless you then.
You know, I have a McDonald's. I had
McDonald's yesterday. I'll probably have
a McDonald's when I come in later.
on the big night out, you know.
Oh, I like Franklin.
Oh, bless you. Then you're not going to
go you're not going to go until the 10th
without having a McDonald's.
I got two [ __ ] on me. You know,
I'm beating them both up. Franklin,
you're not going to you're not going to
last until the 10th. Grezy, don't be
such a silly goose. You love your
McDonald's. Oh, the police are after me.
No, Franklin, get in the car. Get in the
car. Get in the car.
Oh, I died. Oh.
Oh, I'm so tired, bro.
But unfortunately, I have to go out
today, bro. I need to find a candidate
for baby Peter Grezy.
He's not going to find it. It's not
going to find itself, is it?
I can't believe that woman on Reddit
yesterday, man, like just attacking me
because she can't handle the truth.
All I done was show her some like approaching videos.
It's like they're such simps that they
anything that shows women in a bad
light, they they they go all in denial
and defensive about it. Like, no, you're
a creep. recording it, which is not even
weird what I record, Greavves. I only
record a conversation,
you know? I don't show any faces. I
don't put any personal details out
there. Like, there's some channels they
actually show like their faces and stuff.
Um, and they don't like it because it
proves everything that they say to be
wrong about women. like, oh, they give
people a chance and they like confidence
or all you need to do is approach or
whatever it is. It proves them wrong.
Your videos show what it really is like.
And because they don't want to put women
in a bad light, they just go and they
just go on defensive mode,
which is ridiculous really if you think
about it. Cuz say I didn't record these
videos, Greavvesy. Yeah. No one would
believe me. They'd be like, "Yeah, mate.
You need to need a personality. You need
to be confident. No, no one would
believe you. You'd be like the boy who
cried wolf, never believed, which is
what helps these videos show what you're
dealing with in in where you live, you
know, when you when you're trying to
when you when you go out and you approach.
The truth hurts, man. That's all you can
say in it. What's your opinion on it, Grezy?
I don't think it was that bad recording
some approaches I've done, you know,
over the years.
It shows your um future in this country
when it comes to dating and stuff.
It's like what Ant-Man says, it's the
same [ __ ] just different characters.
Same start and same ending.
When he watches these videos,
it's just different characters.
Franklin just fell off and died.
Same start, same ending. It's just
different characters. Griezy, would you
agree on that one? It's just different characters.
I don't know if I can be bothered to go
out today, bro. I'm [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
But I'm going to have to, bro.
I'm going to have to, man.
Yeah, I need to go out today, bro, cuz I
need to get some some numbers and [ __ ] So,
yeah, I'm [ __ ] tired as [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, there the swindling game is
playing now. So, hopefully the first
match don't take that don't completely
[ __ ] the bet up. I don't think I will
sleep. I can't believe I'm doing this [ __ ] again.
happened to go out again. [ __ ]
madness. I went out yesterday.
I I I'd invite Virgin Boy with me, but
his ugly face will scare them away,
Nicolo. He's his ugly face.
That [ __ ] ugly face will scare them
away, mate. So, best not go with a virgin.
I am so tired, bro. I think I'm still
hung over slightly, you know?
or there's something that's not right.
But once you had a few beers, you'll be
all right, I'm sure.
Virgin boy ain't coming. He will scare
them away with his [ __ ] ugly face.
Who's that righty? Mhm.
I am shattered, mate. Absolutely ugly face. Yeah,
ugly [ __ ] Just like that red star.
They're both equally as ugly. That's why
they're going about me because they're
jealous that I'm better looking than them.
Yeah. Like, think about it, bro. Who's
who's going to be sat on YouTube all day
today? them two virgins. It ain't going
to be me.
It ain't going to be me, mate.
Oh, I'm tired, bro. I need to get some
sleep, bro, before going out. I think
100%. We got all day anyways. So
So what's in Glasgow for me, Nicolo?
There's nothing in Scotland for me.
That's why I've never I didn't go back
to Scotland because there's nothing
there for me.
Yeah, there's nothing in Scotland for me.
Well, there's my dada.
My daddy's in Scotland
where the [ __ ] he lives. But uh
I got a Scottish number yesterday. Did
she block me? Let's see if she blocked me.
No, she didn't block me. It's good if
they didn't block you, bro. It's all
right, you know, if they didn't block
you because statistically, right, even
if you message these numbers and they
don't reply and you collect a few of
these numbers, you can always message
them in two weeks and
see like if they want to meet up in two
weeks or something. So it's not it's not
the worst thing because you can still
sometimes they do reply
if you just say oh you want to go out
and [ __ ] So sometimes they
they do you know it has happened. It's
happened a few times.
So where's Tam anyways Nikolai?
Well get out of the car. Franklin you're
going to kill us both.
Come on old Swindon. We need you to both
score and then we got two other matches.
Yeah, pretty much. Yeah,
but a lot of them just don't block. She
just didn't reply. The Scottish one just But
she didn't block me though.
Yeah, can't even be bothered today, bro.
I really can't.
But I'm going to have to, bro, sadly. Oh,
they probably have a roast dinner
tomorrow, I think. Yeah.
Yeah. Swindon's already scored. Come on,
hold him. Get scoring, son. Oh, come on.
We're in the fifth minute.
Come on, hold him.
Score. So, then we got two left.
I say two left, it's still even if they
do score, two is quite a lot to [ __ ] get, bro.
Yeah. Do you remember that one? Yeah. Yeah, man. Yep.
So, now we need old That's why I always
bet on Swinden, bro, cuz they always So,
now we need Olden. And then even if they
both score, then we still got another
two games. Shsbury, Colchester and
Cambridge and Harriut, which again [ __ ] um
we need to um
That's quite hard, bro. Even two is quite hard.
But I'm sure this will both score. If
Swindon's already scored, I'm sure Olden will score.
What do you think, Nicolai?
Yeah, that's 20 to 140. It's a good bit
of money, is it? Really extra drinking money.
What? All three of them's going to come
in. [ __ ] off. No way, bro. Nah,
taking a baby away from its mama.
I mean, I don't even know why I'm
bothering going out today. I mean,
they're not [ __ ] interested in this country, but
you know, I don't have anything better
to do to be fair and um
yeah, I got nothing better to do. So,
so even if that one wins, I mean, I
still got two more games. Yeah,
remember the only way Virgin Boy will
ever leave me alone is if he's dead or in prison.
That is crazy, isn't it? Imagine that,
bro. Somebody would have to be dead or in prison
to leave someone alone. That's [ __ ]
madness, isn't it?
But I weren't even that way towards my mama, Nicolo.
You know, my sister's boyfriend said to me once,
he was like, "Um, you're going to win a
football bet one day and you're going to
wish you had more in it."
Was he Was he right, Nikolai? Yeah.
You're going to wish you had more on it.
Is it? Yeah. It's true though, is it?
Cuz I had a 75 to one before.
Yeah. 75 to1. I must had more. You're
going to wish you had more in it, in it. Yeah.
Yeah. You're going to wish you had more
in it, mate. Yeah. But you're not going
to put £500 on 75 to one. Maybe like 80,
but not. You're not going to put it on
that, are you?
Yeah. But you're not going to put £500
on a 75 to1. But yeah, I'd be m I'd be
minted in it.
75 to one it was. And it I only had a
[ __ ] quid on it.
Even if I had 100 Even if I had [ __ ]
I was 19. Even if I had 20 pound on it, 17 fucking50,
it would have been it would have been 1450.
It's still a lot of money, bro, for when
you're 19, you know, even if I had like
20 quid on it.
I'd play online roulette, but
it's too rigged. The online roulette is
just too rigged. So there's not even no
point playing it.
It's rigged in it. The um
the roulette in it
online roulette is defo fixed. That's
why I don't play it, bro.
There's people that put £500 on 75 to
one. Yeah, but they probably wouldn't
even pay me.
Nah, I wouldn't I wouldn't do it. I
wouldn't risk that money on that. I
would never do it.
Doesn't matter how much money I was
getting, I would never do it.
I would never put £500 on a football bet. Nah,
I would never do it, mate. If I was to
gamble£500, I'd go on roulette.
Two300 pound. Anything more than 100, I
would just go on roulette. So that's no
point. They wouldn't have come in, bro.
What? Like£500 on like a 75 to one.
N [ __ ] that. No,
that's how I was able to pay for USA
Izzy steak Nikolai
from the little house mouse.
Trying to think how I can get more
money. I need to start the delivery
applications again on Mon. I'm just
going to say that I live in Stoke on
Trent. Then they can't say that they've
got too many drivers if I just change my
address to Stoke on Trent.
And if that doesn't work, well then I'm [ __ ]
Yeah, she was a nasty old [ __ ]
See, why would I have dessert? She was my dessert.
If you get what I mean, Grezy, why the
[ __ ] would I want dessert when she was my dessert?
You know, do you get it? Huh? No. She
was like, "Are you not having any dessert?
Come on, old. Get this [ __ ] game out the way."
75 to one, £500. Yeah. Sick, man.
Should have used the milk to put in the
cups of teas in it. Uh Nicolo,
that Red Star is such an obsessed little
bastard, isn't it? You just know that
he's like some just complete bully
victim in real life. Probably 40 still
living with his mom probably in it. Yeah.
Big boobies, eh? The Albanian one have
big boobies as well.
Yeah, imagine that though. 75 time 500.
But they probably wouldn't pay me out.
They'd probably make it so hard for me
to get that money I get. I bet you any
money, bro. They'd make it so hard, isn't it?
Yeah, I know. He's He's a sad bastard,
isn't it? He's such a stalker, is he, bro?
He's He's the biggest coward as well.
Like, even people that don't like me,
they even say it as well. He's a coward.
Everyone says it, bro. He's an actual
like he he spends his whole life stalking
day in day out. Oh, I mean even Tramodo
gave up in the end. I mean certain
people just gave up in the end. Year in year out.
Yeah. Yeah. Um year in year in year out,
right? Like non-stop. Year in year out.
Year in year out. year in year out tries
to get the [ __ ] black man to do
everything. It's always a black man they
try to get to do things as well. But he
will never ever meet anyone.
This is this is what I don't understand.
He will never ever meet anyone ever. He
will never say anything to anyone's
face. He will never say where anyone's
from. He will just sit on YouTube all
day in his mommy's basement
and never meet anyone. It's mad, bro.
That's why I don't go on the channel. I
went on it today cuz LJ A brought it up,
but that was the first time in three
months. Think about it, right?
They're saying that you're bald in your
skin, you're this, you're that, but
listen, they're wasting their life every
day stalking you and being obsessed with
you. So, I mean, think about it, bro.
What What are they? They're talking
about themselves, obviously. You know,
I've never seen someone so dedicated as
well. but such a little [ __ ] in real
life. It's mad, isn't it?
If I had a channel on that London
Taylor. Yeah, let's just give me an
example. Let Let me give an example.
Let's just say I was trolling London
Taylor while stalking London Taylor
every day. I would meet him, bro. I
would just be so pissed off in the end.
Yeah, because you know what I'd be? I'd
be like, "Okay, well, he's asking me to
meet him." Then I keep stalking. I was
like, "No, [ __ ] this. I've got like
let's just use him as an example because
let's just say he's the biggest on this
community. Yeah. Goes to the gym. I
would meet anyone, bro. If I was
stalking them for years and years and
years and years and years and I had
people keep coming back and saying I'm
this and I'm that. I'd be like in the
end I'd be like, "Fuck it. Let me just
meet this [ __ ] and embarrass them."
Think of how much respect you'd get as
well. But he can't because he's a fat
[ __ ] disabled [ __ ] sitting in his
mama's basement every day. I'm telling
you, that's why he doesn't meet no one, bro.
No, no golf.
Yeah. Whoever it is, it's a [ __ ] cow.
They're a coward.
Just like LT said, whoever it is, it's a coward. So yeah,
even that All Night Spaz gave up. Even
sometimes I see that All Night Spaz
doesn't even mention me anymore.
And he used to be he used to be one. He
used to be another one as well. And then
eventually he just gave up.
Madness, isn't it?
But then when you're in their country,
they don't say anything. I think it's
funny, isn't it?
But yeah, if I put £500 on 75 to1 Yeah.
How long do you reckon it would have
take me it would take me to get that money?
Be nice to win a nice little football
bet in it.
Retire early, eh? Retire.
It' be good, bro. never have to worry
about working again or money again. Eh,
yeah, he's another sad bastard. He says
that I'm I've got the worst life on here
after TR. I was like, bro, you're
showing £300 to an old woman. Is that Is
that supposed to make anyone jealous?
This is my money for the weekend.
Okay. Your point is, so you showed
you showed £300 and that's your money
for the weekend. Okay. Um, and what
what's your point?
I don't understand these people, bro.
So, you're showing an old woman £300.
team the weekend team.
>> That's how we talk with be [ __ ] bmy accent
and then you're showing £300 to an old woman. Okay.
But you know what I noticed, Nicolo?
No one showed my 10 grand, have they? I
still ain't see my 10 grand.
Yeah. No one still showed me this 10
grand. I'm undefeated.
Yeah, cuz they ain't got a life, bro.
Yeah, it's cuz they ain't got a life.
They're all skin. They all stay at home.
They ain't got a life, bro.
And you know the thing is they talk
about Ant-Man. Yeah, but at least
Ant-Man changed his life. At least
Ant-Man went to Thailand, living in
Thailand, off this place. But then they
talk [ __ ] about him, which is mad. Like,
at least he turned his life around, bro.
Swindon squad again.
Come and hold him, you bastard. You know,
[ __ ] sake, man.
But how long do you reckon it will take
to get that money? Get 75 [ __ ]
Nah, bro. I'm good. No, it's not even
that, man. No, it's not even that.
Um, so basically, yeah.
Yeah, that's 70. That's 7,500 times
five. But no, it's actually more than
that because all the pounds add up as
well. The pounds and the pences also add
up as well because obviously it's times [ __ ] 500.
So all the pences and the pounds add up.
Yeah, it be a lot of money in it.
How long do you reckon it would take for
them to give you the money though? If
you want to bet like that probably like
all you got to do, bro, is do a correct
score of nil nil and you're already
winning. Just hope none of them score.
Just hope none of them score in it.
Yeah, just hope none of them scar.
That's all you got to do is Yeah. Just
hope none of them scared it. Yeah.
So, if you if you I'm going to try and
do a correct score, bro.
I think I could do like a correct score. Yeah.
It's like if you had a million to one
and you put Fiverr on it, you're not
going to wish you had more on it because
5 million you're set for life. If you
have if you had5 million pound, yeah,
you're set for life. So, you're not
going to think, "Oh, I wish I had more
on it because 5 million is is enough."
You know what I mean? So,
yeah, they asked me for it. No, not
source of Yeah, the UK casinos. Yeah,
but the foreign ones don't ask for that.
The foreign ones don't ask for that. Yeah, mom.
Yeah, the the the foreign ones don't ask that, bro.
But I don't even play online anymore cuz
it's just all rigged. All the on all the
roulette is just rigged. So
they used to blame blame the poor house
Edge poor [ __ ] He used to get the
blame for everything. He's only [ __ ]
two He's only [ __ ] 2 months and seven
days. 2.7. And he used to get blamed for
the He used to get blamed for
everything. That poor [ __ ]
Do you remember the house Edge? only two
months and seven days old and he gets
blamed for everything.
Poor house Edge.
It's [ __ ] madness. Poor [ __ ]
[ __ ] a baby practically a bubin and
he's getting blamed for these magnets and [ __ ] Poor [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, I heard in Ireland they've
still got like arcades where you can gamble. Like
I remember I tried to get into a casino
in Scotland and they still didn't let me
in cuz I self excluded and I thought oh
cuz it's like a different country
technically they let me. But
yeah, you can gamble£100 spins in the
arcades, can't you? In Ireland. Yeah.
Yeah, man. Come on, hold him, you bastard.
Score a goal
or two or three.
Do you think you can win big on roulette
anymore online? I don't think you can.
As soon as you start putting 20, 30
pounds on numbers, they just start rigging it.
That's what I noticed. I never really
hit big online.
No, I'll never play the Euro minions
because the chances of winning is just
nil. So, there's no point even doing it.
It's a waste of time. Yeah, man. [ __ ] >> Yeah.
Do you remember that time I went casino
with 150 and walked out with 4K?
[ __ ] hell, mate.
I was pissed as well. Couldn't believe it.
Mad times, is it?
That's not that much, bro. You need to
win like thousands to be set, you know? It's hard.
But yeah, online as soon as you start
putting like 3040 on numbers, they just rig it.
You know what I mean? They just rig it.
So it's pointless. Pointless, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. It was a lovely site, wasn't it?
I can't believe Virgin tries to tell
people that he shown 40. Do you know
what he tried saying before? virgin boy
that he had 100 grand from inheritance.
He tried saying that he had 100 grand before.
It's mad. He's
He literally thinks he's got money. Me,
I don't have lots of money. Me, I've got
probably about 1,400 [ __ ] pound left.
Probably bought this TV and [ __ ] I
mean, I don't need to lie and pretend
I've got money, bro.
Yeah. He used to say that he had 100
grand like we when I used to meet him
but but the thing is I don't obviously I
understand that like people don't
not everyone likes designer clothes but
why are you well how comes you ain't got
a bed how comes you've never been abroad
why do you live like a skint person if
you got all of this money I generally
thinks he thinks he's I actually think
that he thinks he's [ __ ] Elvis, mate,
he ain't got he ain't even got assets.
Like he's got like a few cheapy cheap
like shitty guitars like them cheap ass
guitars, but he literally doesn't even
have any assets. Like you would think, right?
You would actually think that someone
that's got all of that like, okay, with
me in the house, yeah, okay, I could
have had more savings, but you know,
I've got designer clothes. I traveled.
You know, I was drinking every [ __ ]
Um, you know, a lot of the time, three
times a week, I was still living the life.
Why? How? You've got all this money, but
you you're skint [ __ ] skip thing. I understand, mate.
Yo, yeah, he lives in lives in Little India, mate.
Little [ __ ] India.
Like older mates go yet.
I think this is the one where we lose today.
That's all right though. It's only 21 pound.
He's skinnier than the [ __ ] skin. Yeah, man.
Peter Bell's had a better life than him
and I'm and I'm a few years younger.
He's older than my sister as well.
I've got more life experience.
You've got more women experience.
I used to say to him like all women are the same.
And I used to just say and he's like,
"Oh, you don't know all women." And then
you could ask him this as well and I
used to say I [ __ ] know more than
you. I [ __ ] met more than [ __ ]
you. That's for sure. But I used to just
say it cuz I just used to say it.
But now like I actually mean it. Well,
it might change today. You never know.
When I go out later, maybe. We'll see in it.
Yeah, I remember that.
Yeah, man. Pulled his pants down,
matched his ass with a [ __ ] ruler.
So, we couldn't take it, so we ran to
the boys in blue.
Boys in blue. Yeah.
Yeah. What a loser, man. What an absolute loser.
I told you to leave me alone. You [ __ ] virgin.
I feel sorry for the police to be honest
though. I feel sorry for the system
because you got this little virgin
crying like a [ __ ] when he can give the
heat but can't take it and then they're
actually like thinking that he's a
victim. It's mad, isn't it? And then
there's probably people out there
getting stabbed and [ __ ] raped.
People that actually need the police or
some [ __ ] getting their [ __ ] phone
snatched and then you got some [ __ ]
virgin on the internet starting [ __ ]
with someone and then when they
retaliate they run to the police crying.
It's madness, isn't it?
and they they actually and they actually
think it's winning but it's not winning
because it just makes them look like a loser
which they don't care about or they are
a loser but if they don't care about
that though you know it doesn't matter
they have you know you got to understand
with these people they ain't got no shame so
you know if you put £500 on a both
double both teams the sky Nicolai. It
returns about 1,500
which is not really a good return is it?
It's a lot of money to lose on a
football bet in it. Yeah,
that's not really a good return, bro. Yeah.
Well, obviously if you lose, then you lose £500.
I'm going to, like I said, I'm going to
do a treble both teams to score, no draw,
and hopefully one of them come in. But
that's the hard
three teams both score no draw. But
so why did So why did he keep saying if
you don't find this sh attractive you're
gay? What was what was your opinion on that Nicolo?
Did Did you remember what why he done it?
Yeah. Obviously, you just put £500 in
the machine, isn't it?
Yeah. You just put £500 in the machine, is it?
Do you know what would be a good bet?
Yeah. Betting on the WWE, like a Royal Rumble. Um,
you know, like the WWE Royal Rumble,
that would have been a good thing to bet
on if you could even bet on it. I don't
even think you can bet on it, maybe.
But yeah, if you could bet on like the
Royal Rumble, that would be good. That
would be like the Imagine that, bro.
like betting on it and then just
watching it. That would just be a lovely site,
but obviously I don't think you can bet
on the WWE.
I'm sure you can't. Maybe in America you
can, but I don't think you can here. Oh,
yay. They scored. Yay.
Just two more now, [ __ ]
Just two now. More. Just two now. Two
more now. You [ __ ]
See, I told you about this swindling
game, bro. We already got one.
There you go.
We got one. We got an early one. There
we go. We got it in the first half as
well, didn't we? Yeah.
That's what you call bittersweet as
well. I told you about this swindling, bro.
They're good at scoring and they've got low defense,
so you know, but the other two's not
going to come in.
I don't think the other two is going to win.
Who was better, USA, Izzy, or um
Oh, the Albanian? Nah, not today. I had
one on Thursday, bro.
I'm not [ __ ] rich anymore, mate.
Can't be doing them things.
I still got two teams.
I had a good escort on Thursday, man. Yeah. Yeah, man.
You actually think this bet is going to come in?
So, we got Haywards, Havit, and
Shrewsby and Colchester.
Nah, one of them is going to lose 100%, bro.
One of them is going to [ __ ] probably
end nil nil.
I can just see it happening, bro.
Well, if it does come in, then I can
safely say I've done good on the [ __ ]
football bets this month, is it?
Yeah, I I turned 80 to 280 and then
[ __ ] lost 50 on that [ __ ] pissing frenzy.
[ __ ] stupid Frankie, man. [ __ ]
Well, if it does win, then
it's good, is it? It's 120 profit along
with all the other [ __ ] wins I had.
Yeah, it'll be a good win, man.
You know the best show is when you if
when you need one more team. Yeah. And
then the and then the dot starts do
starting when they got a penalty. You
know when the dot goes like dot dot dot dot dot.
Now I'm going to start off in central
then I'm going to go somewhere else.
I'm going to start off there and then go
somewhere else. I'm not saying where I'm
going though because of these little
grasses on here. But
maybe if the football bet wins, I'll
just go to Cardiff.
You know, I done an all nighter in
Cardiff that Friday. Yeah. Then the next
Friday, I done it all again. I don't
want to go fabrics. It's too expensive, bro.
[ __ ] when I went there last time,
they were asking for like £35. I was
like, I am not paying that.
35 [ __ ] pounds to get in.
Nah, it's pointless, bro. £35 to [ __ ] get in
somewhere. You're [ __ ] having a wank.
I think it was £35, bro. That's madness.
Just to hear I have a boyfriend. Imagine
that. Paying £35 to get in somewhere
just to hear I have a boyfriend.
It's a madness, isn't it?
That is actually mad. Eh,
could you imagine? You get you get lots
of Americans that go there, too. Yeah.
You know, people on Reddit, Can I ask
you a question, Nicola? Why Why do they
make it seem like if you go to like a
pub or a bar or a club, all of a sudden
you won't get the I've got a boyfriend?
They make it seem like
like you won't get it there.
Don't know if you notice that as well.
They make it seem like you're not going
to get it there.
I don't know if I'm the only one that's
noticed that, but you [ __ ] do get it.
[ __ ] you getting that [ __ ] Simmons as well.
You try to speak to anyone in a [ __ ] Simmons.
You get it, bro. You definitely get it.
You get anywhere you go.
It's horrible, isn't it?
Yeah, I know, bro. I just have two left now.
This will be epic if it comes in, but I
can't see it coming in. 142.
Yeah, that'll be enough for a night out. 142. Yeah.
Horrible, horrible out.
Yeah, if it doesn't come in, it don't
come in. It's only £21. But
be nice if it does come in cuz then I
can just use that money to come out.
15 140 150 is enough, isn't it? Yeah, man.
What do you reckon is going to happen
today when I go out approaching? Hope. Yope. Go.
Yep. Go. Yep. Go.
What do you think, W? Anything good?
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ] I need to put my t-shirt on, bro.
But I done good this month anyways. I
went to Birmingham, went out a few times and so
still do good considering I'm not on
that income anymore. So, think I still
do good. And I just love it, bro. I just
love not having that responsibility
anymore. Yeah, it sucks about the money, but
I had some money that I kept from it. So,
maybe, bro. Maybe. Maybe today
is the day.
Maybe today is the day
you stop hearing. I mean, so what what
what do you think will happen then?
If I go into a club and start trying to socialize.
Yeah. If these two if these two win, bro, then
Yeah, same. It's been the same for years.
I remember one month I spent about £500
on escort one month. In one month £500.
Yeah, I remember £500 I spent. Yeah, true.
All that happens when you go out and you
just make new friends. Before that happens,
before that happens is you make new
friends and [ __ ]
That's it. Is it? Oh,
I really can't be bothered today. I
can't lie. I can't be asked, but I'm doing it.
I think this football bet's going to
come in, bro.
If this one comes in, that's three in a row.
Oh, yeah. Do you remember that time I
done it in Brixton? I done it on the I
done it on the street, bro. On the
street. I was by I was by the I was by
the motorbike. I kept like getting this
sexy frustrated. So I was like, "Oh,
it's like 4:00 in the morning. The club
closed and I was next to the motorbike
and then a guy come and he thought I was
trying to steal his motorbike and he he
started like grabbing me and that and I
was like, "Oh, like it was that was
actually a true story, bro. I swear to God, bro.
I'm not even joking."
Yeah. I'm not even joking. That was
actually a true story, bro.
Yeah. I was lying on like next to the motorbike
having a [ __ ] having a bank, bro. And
then he comes and he's you trying to
steal my bike? He thought I was trying
to steal his bike. And his friend was
there as well. And his friend was like,
"Leave it. Leave it. Leave it." He
wasn't. I could have got I could have
got beat up, bro.
Especially if there was two of them. I
was only having a little bang for the street.
Yeah. Well, not on the street. I was
lying down under something, not on the
street. But yeah, I've been through some tough times, you know.
But today, I'll be looking for that change, you know.
I should start putting these approaching
videos up on my channel again.
Yeah, I should start putting on my
channel. with that. Oh, I need this
football bet to win, bro.
I'm ruining I'm rooing for this football
bet to win.
Oh, what the [ __ ] is this? Keep
messaging me. [ __ ] off.
Yeah, that's what I love about not
having this [ __ ] house anymore, bro.
Is no responsibilities, none of these
little pricks. I mean, yeah. Yeah, you
might have lost some money, but I mean,
I won [ __ ] £300 this month, so it's
still near enough 1,400 and I had no responsibility, so
it could have been a lot worse. And I
got some money from the house as well. So
that's that's why I'm like I wouldn't
say I'm not asked. Obviously
I don't know how to explain it. Like I
didn't like the responsibility. I didn't
like it, bro. Like this that's
I don't know how to explain it, bro. Like
the best thing you could have probably
done in that situation is like what you
said, put £500 on like a 7 to one or try
to win as much money and then just kick
them all out and then just have the
house to yourself. It's not fun, bro.
Trust me. And I'm still dealing with them.
No, not really. She didn't have no boobies.
I said to her before as well, yeah. I
said, "Oh, if you don't pay," I said, "I
won't charge you the rent." Yeah. For a
month if you give me a [ __ ] She
says, "No." But yeah, she she do it she
do it for a black guy for freezy.
So I used to hear her [ __ ] black guys
and stuff. Yeah.
Badness, isn't it? No, I'm actually
being serious. I actually sent her a
voicemail asking. Yeah. I wasn't bad, bro.
That's what they push you to do. Yeah.
And she was like, "Oh, no, no, no."
Well, she'd give it she'd give it to the
blacks for free,
you know what I mean? Yeah. I didn't
like her. I just thought, why not? I'm
in a position to do it. But like then I
had to like pretend I was joking. It was
awkward. Yeah. [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, I should have. Yeah.
She said she going to get her boyfriend
on me as well. I said, "You can get go
get who you want. I don't give a [ __ ] mate.
But then I see this black guy go around
approaching him. He gets the same [ __ ]
I have a boyfriend. So it's like what?
Who the [ __ ] do they want? Like Tik
Tockers and [ __ ] big YouTubers, it seems.
Yeah, I should have told her about L2.
You remember Antman? He used to say,
"Get the pain out." Is it? Get the plane
Get the pain out. He used to say, "It's
funny, isn't it?
This bet needs to come in today, bro.
could do the extra bit of money in it.
Yeah, it's nice not having the
responsibility to be honest.
It is nice.
It's so love. It is so lush.
Cuz say you was abroad and something
happened with the house, right? Say you
went to America somewhere and something
happened with the house and you're not
there. It's just a buzz kill. Like when
I used to go out and be like, "Oh, fuck."
That there there's a problem with the
house. Oh, it's it was just a buzz kill.
I remember. Yeah. My mom was on holiday.
Yeah. And I was in the I was in a club
in it. I think I was in the O'Neals. And
then the the the I think the housing put
stuff on the [ __ ] on the door saying
that they're going to repossess the
house and [ __ ] in it. And they were
[ __ ] themselves. And they were
They were absolutely [ __ ] themselves.
themselves, bro. And then they said,
"Oh, what what's going on with the house
now? What's going on with the house?"
It was funny, bro. Like, what's going on
with it? I I don't know.
And then my mom's on holiday as well. So
yeah, I just don't I don't miss that responsibility, bro.
I really don't.
They're [ __ ] annoying. That one
person's okay. Maybe even two. Yeah.
And the other team starting what?
Two hours. Just under two hours. So
yeah, you better [ __ ] win today, you stupid [ __ ]
Yeah, man. You better [ __ ] win.
You better win, eh? I'm shat chatted.
Franklin, what are you doing in the car?
His little mates. Franklin.
Was that cute little Franklin?
We out today looking
just looking for that change, you know,
searching for that change.
Looking for it. Looking for that chain. Yeah.
How's it going, Eggman? How's it going?
I said calm down before you before you
start doing something silly again. You
know we know you and your little ways.
You remember that one bread.
That's how it turns you, bro. You racing
for [ __ ] crazy birds.
Oh, I'm I'm happy in my little nesticles
today, but I have to go out, bro. You
know when you stay in bed for too long,
like a couple of days, and you don't
really go out much, Grezy. Your back
starts hurting. Your body starts aching.
Mine My body's aching.
I've got a feel
I think this football bet's going to come in.
Don't know about you. Yeah,
you might as well just get an escort.
Yeah. Keep seeing an escort trying to
bond and then just have kids with an
escort. I think you got more chance of
doing that 100%.
Cuz that that Chinese is he said that
she would have my baby and stuff.
Think about it, bro. They want money.
Yeah. They're trying to make a living,
right? But like what a porn saw is. If
you play it the right way, it would it would work.
It would work, bro.
It would work. Yeah.
Yeah. It would be a Chinese me, wouldn't
it? Be a funny looking baby. I bet you.
So, how do you know USA is my mommy
anyways, Nicolo? Is it the eyes and the hair? Scary Berry.
Do you know why I laugh about you,
Nicola? I don't see you on any You wait
for me to go live to mock me. I never
see you on L's. I never see you on
anyone else's. Only mine.
Same hair, same eyes, same interests. And it
take after my mama.
Yeah. Take after my mama.
Yeah, cuz Laney doesn't like horror
movies. You couldn't pay Laney to see a horror movie.
Yeah. You know, the door was kept
getting um shut today by the wind and I
had to keep opening it cuz all I kept
thinking about was that Australian
horror film that I watched. So, I had to
keep opening the door.
That woman kind of scared the [ __ ] out
of me, bro. Don't know if you've seen it yet.
Yeah, I get you, man.
Yeah. Sometimes you watch like a horror
movie and then the door shut and then
you realize like, yeah, I need to open the door.
Some of them horror films can really
[ __ ] with your head, but I wouldn't
change it for the world.
I always tease Ley. I said, "I'll come
watch a horror film." She says, "Nah."
She doesn't like them.
Right. Did I get any replies from um her friend
Why did you say is his friend not
replying to? Have you noticed that these ignorers, right?
As soon as you send them a picture, it
changes, Nicolo. Like it will say sent,
sent, delivered, delivered. And as soon
as you send a picture, it will say
scene. It all changes, isn't it? Yeah.
It all changes, doesn't it?
They click on it straight away. Or if
you say something negative, they're there.
But normal nice messages,
nowhere to be seen.
They're nowhere to be seen.
Nowhere to be seen, eh? Yeah, man.
Do you remember that? Do you remember
that Ricky Milling? Nicolo. Ricky Millington. [Music]
I'm sure you do.
Yeah, I'm sure you do, don't you?
If you're watching for a long time, you
should know about that account.
Ah, you remember, don't you? You
remember, don't you, mate? Yep.
Yeah. But what if if it's a nice message, Michel?
What if it's a nice message?
Do you not remember that Ricky Milling account?
And I always say like the reason I put
the videos out there is because I'm open
for constructive criticism, but I just
don't want to be compared to others
cuz it's a waste of time comparing me to
another person. You know, they tell you
that you shouldn't compare yourself to
others and [ __ ] and ret you can give
constructive criticism, but I don't want
to be compared
cuz it's a waste of everyone's time. And
people always say that you should not
compare yourself to others.
And I and I and I stick by that.
The Indonesian guy wants to come out
today. I'm not [ __ ] going out with him.
Why am I going to go out with a scaredy-cat?
I'm not going out with a [ __ ] I'm not
going out with a [ __ ] scaredy-cat,
bro. Are you mad?
Yeah. Yeah. And I'd always say to
Antman, why don't you ask them how they
do it? He's like, oh no, that's weird.
That's weird. Not really. And even if it
is weird, who cares about being weird
once if you're going to get the answers
that you want, right? Why Why not ask? I
would. I would if I generally if it was
bothering me that much, you know, other
guys do it. I would ask them. I honestly
would ask them,
but he was so anti it for some reason.
Even though it would control his mind like 24/7,
you know, it's like what what do you
mean you're not going to you? Like there
was a brand that I was looking for
before, you know, the All Saints bug.
And I couldn't find it to save my life.
And I was about to ask somebody who was
wearing it, where did you get it from?
Because I couldn't find it to be, you
know what I mean?
Shut the [ __ ] up, you old man. You jog
on. You [ __ ] old sad bastard. Get a
life. E Vapor. You sad old man.
You [ __ ] sad old wrinkly bastard. Get
off of YouTube and get laid. Get a life.
You [ __ ] wrinkly old bastard. Keyboard warrior.
Yeah. How could How could anybody forget
you? You've been on here years [ __ ]
repeating. You old wrinkly old man.
[ __ ] stupid little [ __ ]
Why do I try to sound like a road man? I
don't try to sound like a road man. This
is what you call the Queen's English.
That just goes to show how you got no
life experience. You know, funny enough,
right? Yeah. I was asking these people
uh two days ago, where do you where did
you think I was from? And they don't
even ever guess London because I don't
sound like a road man.
I sound like a normal person.
A nor a normal southern person. You You
think I sound like a road man?
You have no life experience. If you
think I sound like a road man, don't
even use the slangs, you know? Yeah.
I'm not I'm not afraid of saying where I'm from. you know.
Yeah. No one guesses I'm I I'm from London.
No one guesses I'm from London, man.
Virgin boy is ashamed to be from Kent.
You shouldn't be ashamed of where you come from.
It's like KSI. He hates the fact that
he's Nigerian. He hates the fact that
he's African. So, he tries to use a
nickname. It's crazy, isn't it? Just own
it, bro. You're from Africa.
Like, the [ __ ] What's wrong with that?
You know, own where you're from, bro.
He hates the fact that he's African.
You can tell as well, bro. Like, he
tries to like um
shortcut his name and [ __ ] like, "Oh,
you're from Africa." [ __ ]
You are a sad bastard. You're on
YouTube. You've been doing this for
years, mate. You've been doing this
since I was 22. You are a sad bastard.
You're a sad sad middle-aged bastard.
You are. You've been on here for years.
That that in itself makes you sad.
You've been on here doing this for
[ __ ] years. You're a sad bastard.
Kids, no kids, grandkids, no kids.
You're a sad bastard.
Yep, that's him. Yep. You are literally
a sad boy. That makes you even sadder.
That makes you even more sadder.
Oh, middle. Oh, you're an old man then.
Well, you're an old man. Yeah, dude.
Just browsing. This guy's been on here
for years, bro. doing this
[ __ ] years, years and years and years. Yep.
And before you say I don't want kids,
never wanted kids.
No, I mean what I said more sadder. I
said what I meant and what I I meant
what I said what I just said. I I said I
meant what I just said. More sadder.
It's my little word. You got a problem
with it? Deal with it.
It's like when people correct my yaw.
They said yaw. I said no. I said y in
that way cuz it looks better. Just to be a nic
move. Come on.
Why do you come in the hangout to have a little chat?
Why does that KSI hate being African, bro?
What the [ __ ]
Why are you so ashamed of where you come from?
Silly, man. Is it? There's nothing wrong
with being from [ __ ] where the [ __ ]
you're from. I'm sure Franklin's
African. Just like there's nothing wrong
with being from Kent. Do you know what I
mean, Nicolola? What's What's wrong with
being from Kent?
Nothing wrong with being from Kent,
mate. There's nothing wrong.
Nothing wrong with being from Kent.
Don't know what the problem is. You
You're just from Kent. Nothing wrong
with Kent, mate.
You're not insecure, are you?
You're not ashamed. What are you ashamed
of being from Kent for you know?
Well, actually it's not um it's not
tent, you see, cuz uh back in the uh 19s
um it actually
uh was um it comes under London.
Come come come under London. It's It's
literally It's literally southeast London. Yep.
Yeah. They all talk like this. London.
Um, so actually
it's like this
is this is southeast London.
That's what it sounds like.
like a bit like like bit like this with
a bit like a spack up. Yeah, man.
Just having fun. Fun in the sun. Fun in
the sun. Fun in the sun.
Oh, that's repeating. That is mate.
That's repeating. That's when I was 21.
You are a [ __ ] repeater, aren't you?
Yeah, I'm single. And so are you single? >> Mhm.
>> So are you single and all of the other
people in large age are all single? Fat, ugly bastards.
Yeah. And you're single as well and
lonely and skint.
Yeah. Self projecting. Still talk. And
you're an old man as well. You say you
got a wife. If you ain't got no [ __ ]
wife, a wife, but you're sat on YouTube
every day, prove it. Prove it.
Prove what you got in life. Come in.
Come in the hangouts and prove what you
got. That's That's a good way to end it.
Let's show everybody your wife that doesn't exist.
Mate, you people in here are not just
single. You're actually [ __ ] virgins.
That's how sad it is. You probably never
even seen a woman naked. Do you know
what I'm saying?
Single skin, lonely
bully victims. That's why you come on
here doing what you do year in year out
cuz you all get bullied. You probably
tried to like leave your [ __ ] house
and you just get bullied every time you
tried and then you just come back on
YouTube just repeating yourself again
like the spastics that you are. But
let's see your wife anyways.
Be a bit odd though in it cuz she don't exist.
She don't exist, mate. You all the you
people are I'm I'm the only one on here
that's been seen with women.
No, you haven't. I don't want to see
your kids. I just want to see your wife.
I just want to see your wife, please.
She doesn't exist. That's the thing. She
But I do feel sorry for you, man. You
know, coming on here for years, doing
what you do. You must have it must have
not been easy, you know, the bullying
that you received as a child
in your younger years, man. I mean, to
come on here for years and years. I I
feel, you know, it's to a point where
you're actually to be pied,
you know, you you people on YouTube are to actually
to be pied.
That's that that's that's how it how it
ended up. You know,
you're actually someone to be pied just
like Virgin Boy, just like Red Star.
You're actually something to not even I
I wouldn't even say you're anything to
even laugh at anymore. You're something
to feel sorry for, you know?
It can't be easy being you.
You know, there's an account that says,
"Is it hectic being you?" Greavves. I
don't know if you've seen it. Type that
same person has been saying that for
about 7 years.
No joke. They say it must be hectic
being you, right? And I'm telling you,
bro, that person has been saying that
for about seven years on this community now.
Yes, they have.
Yes, they have, bro. It's like, is this
even a human being or is it a [ __ ] robot?
Oh, bro. Like, I don't know if you've
seen it, but there's an account that
says it and they'll be like, "Bloody
marvelous." Yeah. Have Have you se you
you've seen that in it? And they've been
doing it for like seven years. They've
just been repeating themselves for years,
mad. Why do they keep repeating
themselves like that? Are they just like [ __ ]
They must be like alcoholics, isn't it?
You think they're like alcoholics or what?
I think they're also they've got to be also.
They've got to be alies, bro.
They've got to be also.
Jesus [ __ ] Christ, man.
Yeah, you to be fair, you got me into
the macadox to be honest, Greavves. E,
you got me into the [ __ ] macadox. Yeah,
you got me into the macadox.
I don't like McDonald's really, but it's
something to get. I'll probably be
having one later this evening, Grezy.
later this evening.
You remember Do you know what used to
make me laugh? Yeah.
>> Timmy's done his bollocks. Dimmy's
done his bollix. D. Oh,
I used to love that on Timmy sometimes.
I used to like that. Oh [ __ ]
You remember when I had a fight with
that tiger and Timmy Grezy? They got defeated.
I defeated them.
Okay, I'm going to watch the football
then and then um have a shower and then
get ready and go.
Wish me luck today, Grezy, cuz uh
I'm going to [ __ ] need it, matey.
Yeah, I went in that mattress because I slipped,
bro. I slipped.
If you ask Greavves, uh if you ask
Tiger, he'll even tell you that I won. Yeah,
I slipped, bro. And then I come back and
I punched him in his face. Did you see
how the freedom pass um slipped?
I don't I can't believe he actually
thought he was going to beat me.
He actually thought he was actually
going to beat me.
Like one of his punches didn't even do anything.
Like he's [ __ ] what? His punches
didn't even do anything, bro. Like he's
[ __ ] weak. That tiger.
He is [ __ ] weak, bro.
Yeah, it wasn't my It wasn't my pass
either. It was my mom's. I don't have a
pass. It was my mom's. But yeah. Yeah.
Do you know what we should do, Grezy? We
should have a tea party.
Me, you. Oh [ __ ]
Thank you. Uh, me, you, Stitch
just going around having a little tea
party. What do you think?
Man's tea party. Oh, mate.
I don't want to meet your [ __ ] kids.
What the [ __ ]
Yeah, we can have a little tea party
today, man. Come on. Just get more teams. Oh,
it's going to be a lovely day today,
bro. There's going to be a pro session,
es school and McDonald's.
Well, I'm not going to do the school and
if I win, but
yeah, Reddit's full of nerds
just like you. You're a nerd. Bye-bye now. Mhm.
Anyways, I'm going now. Yeah. Uh,
I'll be back later.
Life hate you. Nah. Why? Why would I say that?
Why would I say that, man?
Nah. Why would I say that?
Nah, I don't say that. I just said these
people have been bullied since they
since they they come out of their mom's vagina. Yeah.
No, I used to say life bullies you.
That's what I used to say. I used to say
life bullies you. Ah
yeah. I ordered some Stitch underpants.
I ordered some Stitch underpants, Grezy.
You know, like underpants.
Yeah, man. I ordered some Stitch underpants.
Yeah, they were just like a pack in it.
I got some Chucky ones, Stitch ones. You
know what that means? Underpants.
So funny. It underpants.
That sounds so funny calling it that. I
call them boxer shorts. Boxes. And
Antman Ant-Man calls them um underpants.
Where's my underpants?
You grow up, you silly goose.
You grow up. My underpants. Oh
yeah, he has to change his underpants
cuz he shot himself in it.
I'm saying [ __ ] underpants.
I can't find my underpants.
Yeah, I can't find my [ __ ] underpants.
Who the [ __ ]
bro? Who actually calls it that? Who
actually calls it that? Seriously, [ __ ] underpants.
That is a madness.
Who even calls it that at that age? Underpants. [Laughter]
That just makes me laugh. I don't know why. [Laughter]
I need to stop laughing. But honestly, I
got the giggles.
Right. I'm going anyways yet. So, I'll
be back later.