Oh, [ __ ] hell, man.
I think they're going to [ __ ] me hard, bro. Here.
>> [ __ ] I think they [ __ ] me last time
to be honest.
Oh, all they need is a little penalty,
but it doesn't look likely. I don't
think they're going to score. to 168.
Oh man, it would have been nice to get
my first three, but
I don't think Shbury is going to score. No,
I just need choose to score now for
[ __ ] this money, but I don't think
they're going to score. And they got a red card. No,
that would have been a treble. Both
teams to score, but I don't think Sh's
going to score here, man.
Yeah, I'm going out in a bit anyways. undressed. So,
I got [ __ ] anyways. Um, come sure.
Nah, they got 10 minutes to score. [ __ ] hell.
Almost, man. We'll get three teams one day.
We'll get three teams one day. Don't you worry, man.
I don't think I've ever been a goal off
three teams before, though.
[ __ ] hell, man.
We know you got a red cord, but
yeah, man. I got 10 minutes for this
[ __ ] team to score. I don't think
they're going to score.
A lot of teams got a red car to be fair.
Come on. Get a penalty, man.
Get a penalty or something.
Yeah, man. [ __ ]
Let me see. No,
all they need to do is score one [ __ ] go.
I don't think they're going to score. Matey, matey.
Well, at least it's not let down for a
big amount to be fair. It could be worse.
Uh when they
they [ __ ] me a few times. They have
jeally [ __ ] me a few times.
Anyways, I'm going. Yeah, I need to go out. So,
what's that? 21 and Yeah.
Yeah. I am gun.