[ __ ] Shrewsbury.
[ __ ] me right up, bro. Ruin my whole
day. Jesus Christ. Oh, damn.
Yeah. I mean, I expected to lose, but
not to be [ __ ] over by one goal. So,
yeah, I can't go out when that's on my
mind. So, change of plans. Just going to
chill and play Franklin.
Oh, I needed to [ __ ] win some money
for me to even make it tolerable.
Nah, [ __ ] that.
No way, Jose. Am I [ __ ] going out
doing all that [ __ ]
I was all dressed up as well. I just had
to have another [ __ ] shower.
No, I'm good, bro. [ __ ] that.
I could have done with that extra money,
you I could have done with that extra money
and a number replied back as well. So, yeah.
Yeah, man. [ __ ] [ __ ] been [ __ ] by
one [ __ ] goal. [ __ ] bastard,
you know. Yeah, that was only 21 pound
on it as well. So
yeah, I won't get mad or saying it was
rigged. It just just a buzz kill.
There's there's nothing else you can say
about it. It's a buzz kill
cuz I literally would have just paid for
basically the whole night
and it would have been for free. I'm not
getting paid to do deal with this
[ __ ] You know what I mean? But
yeah, [ __ ] shoes be bastards. They
done it last time. Well, not last week
or the week before that.
Can't help how I feel, bro. I'm not
moaning about it, but if it's ruining
your whole day, then just don't go out.
I'm not going out.
I won't go out now. Simple.
Yeah. If I lost like got [ __ ] then
I'd be like, "Yeah, okay. I lost." But
not losing to one goal. [ __ ] that. There
weren't even a big amount as well
cuz you get you you know you have a
shower, you get changed, you do your
hair, and then you just
it's not good if you're trying to go
out, bro. Just before you go out. It's
just a buzz kill. If it wasn't I was
just about to go out, then I wouldn't
really care as much. But
yeah, [ __ ] losing to one [ __ ]
bastard girl. Can't [ __ ] off.
So yeah, I'm ordering some food, bro.
Yeah, bro. I'm not going out now. I
literally got changed and everything.
Put my after shave on or styled my hair
up. Literally waiting for one goal.
One goal and they couldn't even do it.
Could have done with [ __ ] 40 quid.
You know what I'm saying? So, I'm not
going. And one of the numbers replied as
well um from Scotland. So, I don't get
paid to deal with their [ __ ] I'm
not doing it. [ __ ] right off, bro. I'm
ordering some food and just chilling.
Yeah, I just wash my hair and then Yeah.
No, I'm not saying it's rigged, bro. I'm
not I'm not having a tantrum. I don't
care what it is. Just ruin my whole day. Simple.
Just ruin my whole day. No shouting, no
just not going to go out now. Don't want
to go out.
So, wouldn't be worth me going out.
It ruin the whole mood. could ruin the
whole vibe. It's literally like a buzz kill.
It's like a vibe killer.
Yeah, I ain't going out. [ __ ] that, bro.
I mean, I don't care if I don't go out
again for the whole month, to be honest.
I don't care anymore, bro. I'm done
here. I was dressed up nice and that,
bro, as well, but nah.
No, bro. Just a football bet. Uh, Grezy,
man. No, just a football bet I done the
other day. Uh, I put 21 pound on. I put
21 pound on. It made me think of you the
other day. You know when I won the
football bet and I got it two three
I won the one two three one. Well, I put
21 pound on the football bet a few days
ago. Literally done three teams. All I
needed was Shrewsbury to score and they
couldn't even score. Literally got back
in the shower and got in my little
shorts and t-shirt and I was like, "Fuck
this. I ain't going out." It ruined my
mood. It just ruined my mood, bro. I
weren't shouting or saying it was
rigged. I don't care what it is. It just
ruined my mood.
Yeah, it wouldn't have. But it was
because I was so close to winning.
It It No, no, no, no, no. I tell you why
it affected me. Because I was so close
to winning. I could have done with that £140.
Not that I needed it, but I could have
done with it.
Yeah, I could have done with it. I could
have done with a [ __ ] 140 quid cuz at
least the [ __ ] that I'd be putting
up with today would have been paid for.
And yes, I have my own money, but it's
not the [ __ ] point. Simple. I'm going
to get a nice big takeaway instead, I think.
Yeah, it ruined the whole vibe. If it
was just like I lost, then I'd be, oh
well, I lost. Or if I was already out or
But one [ __ ] team, all I needed was
them to [ __ ] score and they couldn't
even [ __ ] score. on our fault. [ __ ] that. Yeah, man.
Probably get an Indian to be honest.
Come to think of it, I shouldn't have I
shouldn't really gamble to be honest. If
if and I won two times. I just wanted to win
treble both teams to score. It was so
[ __ ] close. Why the [ __ ] didn't they
just [ __ ] score?
For [ __ ] sake, bro. I just wanted to
say, "Oh yeah, I've done three teams.
Why, man? You know, they had enough [ __ ] time. So, yeah.
Yeah. And it was only £21 out of like
the money I won
the past two weeks.
Yeah. And I went out Thursday as well
and I got numbers and one of them one of them replied,
"I've done my balls in again." Well,
that word on the street is completely
wrong. See, this is what people don't
understand, Greavesy. Yeah. It's like my
mom and other people, they think, "Oh,
it's only £20." It's not the point. It's
literally, it doesn't matter what the
amount is. I don't know how years later,
bro, they um they don't understand. It's
not about how much you lose. It's not
about what you have left. Losing is just
losing in that way is just so [ __ ] annoying.
And I was about to go out as well. I was
about to go out. So now, you can't go
out like that, bro. Simple.
Because don't forget, I have to deal
with these the women's [ __ ] as well.
And I'm up £300. When I said I'm up £300
in the past two weeks, that was
including that football bet that I just done. 280. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. That's what I'm saying. And
if it just got destroyed and I'll be
like, "Okay, I lost." Yes, it come to an
end. The street come to an end. It's the
way I lost. All it needed was one
[ __ ] goal. And it weren't even like
it was a double. If it was a double, I
be okay, maybe. Yeah, it was only a
double. But it was a treble, bro. A
[ __ ] treble, you know? So that's why
I just ruined my mood. Killed the vibe.
So just get a nice binding instead.
Almost though. I was close. Very close.
I was like, if I win this one three
times in a [ __ ] row, but nah, it
would have been too easy.
Yeah, it would have been too easy.
Then I have to deal with the [ __ ] from
women. I was like, nah, I can't be
annoyed with all that. I'm speaking to
someone in Scotland as well, so I got
enough numbers. I went out Thursday. I
went to Birmingham. I you know I don't I
have nothing left to prove here, man. So yeah.
So yeah, bro, I'm getting too old for
this [ __ ] anyways. So
why couldn't she be just score, man?
One day we'll get three teams one day.
That's the dream, you know. Three teams.
That is the dream, man.
And I was thinking to get doing free
both teams to score no draw. That's
never going to come in, bro. [ __ ]
hell. Why didn't they just score, bro?
What the [ __ ] They're playing home as well.
Stupid [ __ ] [ __ ]
So yeah, I'm 280 up actually. 280 or 300
the past two weeks, including that bet.
It was only £2120 on it. Still couldn't
even win. [ __ ] dirty [ __ ]
dirty [ __ ] bastard in it. Uh,
you can't go out like that, bro. You
can't go out like that. And you know the
thing is, Grevy, you know, when I used
to go to the casinos, that's let me tell
you this. This, yeah, which I probably
haven't told you. That's the only reason
I could tolerate it going out because
I'd win about 80% of the time I gambled
in them casinos. That's probably why I
never done anything silly.
because I'll be like, "Oh, well, you
went out, but you won money, so it's
like you got paid to go out, so you
can't really moan." That's why that's
probably one of the reasons I probably
tolerated the [ __ ] for so long.
Come to think of it, yeah, it it makes actually sense
now. And by win, I'd mean I' I'd go
there and win about 700, 800, 1,000,
which no one makes in a [ __ ] day. So
it's like, well, you can't really moan.
I mean, and then it was the same cycle
for years and years and years
cuz there was times where I'd lose
and then um I just go straight back
home. You know, it could be £100 and it
would I just go straight back home cuz I
couldn't bear staying out. And obviously
cuz I'm inside the house, I'm not going out. So yeah.
So that's probably why I didn't do
anything like beat a s up or
I don't know done something. [ __ ] knows.
It was probably cuz I used to always win money.
So it's like well you want money. Who cares?
You're waking up to money. That's that's
what it was. Thinking of it now. That is
probably what it was. You know,
at least that Scottish one replied though.
And I'm already speaking to one person,
so it's whatever. It I just don't have
the energy anymore.
I don't have the energy for it anymore, mate. So, yeah,
that's enough to put anyone on a down I
make. It weren't even a big amount, but
it was enough. 140 is 140, bro. Time
with the other, it's enough for like a
night out. It's pretty much 150
for a piss up in it.
Yeah, I think I was pushing my luck with
three there, man.
I think I was pushing my luck there.
I don't like the clo I don't like being
that close. Do you know what I'm saying?
I rather they just all nil n.
It's a good thing I don't play that
[ __ ] roulette anymore, isn't it?
Yeah, man. I just lost a [ __ ] 21
pound football bet that I done the other
day. Giving me severe No, not it's not
giving me mood things. It's just a buzz kill.
No, they're not mood swings.
It's why I don't gamble, bro. I was
changed, ready to go out. Just literally
just done a U-turn.
Just literally done a U-turn. And I
thought, you know what, Grezy?
Having an Indian and playing Franklin is
just a better idea
to be honest with you. I think that's probably um
why I went out the past two weeks is cuz
I probably won money and I felt like at
least I was getting paid. It felt uh
it's hard to explain this, bro,
but I felt like I was getting paid. So
either even when I paid it, it work out my pocket.
Yeah. Shrewsbury let me down for £141
both teams to score. Yep.
Yep. So, I was ready to go out. Yeah.
Done my hair, dressed smart, put my nice
after shave on, just on a just just
didn't go out. Just went back and went
had a shower. It just ruined my whole
day, my whole mood. I can't go out like
that and then deal with this [ __ ] from
women on top of it. I can't do it. So, I
just went I just had a shower, got in my
clothes, chilling. I'm just going to
order some food in a bit. Yeah.
I don't like um
Yeah. I just can't be bothered.
person in it. Yeah,
I can't go out on the [ __ ] drink. I
happen to think of that.
I went out Thursday anyways.
So, there's no way I can go out like that, bro. Yeah.
Nah. Nah, no, no, no. I can't be
bothered, bro. It does get you down
because it's annoying. It's a buzz kill. It's annoying.
No, it doesn't turn out the best, bro.
You're still going to get the same [ __ ]
from women. I have a boyfriend. I have a
boyfriend. I can't be asked with it,
bro. And I shouldn't even drunk. I I
drunk rum on [ __ ] Thursday. It made I
still [ __ ] feel like [ __ ] because of it.
You don't get It's the same [ __ ] with the women.
I don't have money to be wasting going
out now. You know, I already went out on Thursday.
This [ __ ] hunting bastard. [ __ ] annoying.
You know, the only reason I could
tolerate all them years is cuz I used to
win in the casino. That's the only
reason I could tolerate the the the
[ __ ] in this country, you know.
Yeah, maybe, bro. I mean, it's not
happened in three and a half years of
going up and down the country, going out
in London a million times, but yeah,
today it might have just been different.
Yeah. Yeah. Maybe. Maybe. Maybe. Yeah.
three and a half years of [ __ ] up
and out the country [ __ ] But maybe
today might have been the day where all
of the stuff that's been happening to
you for years stopped happening.
I personally wouldn't put my money on
that, but I mean, everyone's different.
If it was going to happen, it would have
happened by now.
There's I don't think that has any
argument to it
really to be honest with you. So,
we're beyond that, bro. We're actually
beyond that. We're beyond all of that
[ __ ] now. So, yeah.
I don't have the energy for it, man.
What the [ __ ] How the [ __ ] are you? Uh, yeah.
We're beyond that, bro. We're beyond that.
Yeah, bro. Maybe. Maybe. Yeah. Cuz
suddenly, like, one day you'll go out. Yeah.
And women are not going to not be
interested and they're not going to
pretend they got boyfriends cuz cuz one
day Yeah. You'll just like go out and
that [ __ ] will happen in it. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, it never happened anywhere. It
never happened in London. It never
happened anywhere else.
Don't believe it, bro. I don't believe it.
Yeah. I don't think so, bro.
Well, it's not happened for me and I'm
almost 28 and I've tried more than
anyone in the world. So, uh,
yeah, put it that way.
Yeah. [ __ ] going out, lad. It happened
to you. Well, good for you, man. I'm
happy for you.
You want a medal? Which one do you want?
bronze, silver, gold. I mean, I'm happy
for you. Congratulations.
Just like I'm happy you won your football bet.
I mean, good for you.
Now I actually understand how I dealt
with all of that [ __ ] with them for years.
is because most of the time whenever I
used to go play roulette, I used to win.
That's that's what it was. Cuz I could
have ended up in prison like Ant-Man. Maybe
that's what I think a lot of it is, you know? Like,
come to think of it,
I've tried more than anyone in the
world. So, I mean, you must be speaking
to somebody else like Greavvesy
cuz I've I've tried more than anyone in
the world. I mean, I tried on Thursday.
I tried two weeks before that. Go went
to Birmingham. I've been up and down the
country numerous times trying. So, I mean
I mean you must not be talking to me
because I've tried more than anyone in
the world. So, you must be talking to
Greavvesy. You must have like someone
like me and Greavvesy mixed up.
Like more than anyone in the world. No,
no, no, no, no. Backtrack, bro. More
than anyone in the world. Yes. And that
might sound delusional, but it it's the truth. Um,
so, okay. So, let's go by your logic
then. So, how many more years do you
have to keep dealing with their [ __ ]
Okay, let's just say that you're right.
So, how many more years do we have to
keep going out and dealing with their
[ __ ] Because it's already been
three and a half years. So, how many
more years do we have to keep doing this?
How many more years on estimate? Because
it's already been three and a half years.
You know, everyone's seeing all of the
traveling videos, everyone's seeing all
of the [ __ ] How many more years do
we have to keep dealing with their [ __ ] you know,
another three and a half, another 30, another 40.
So, how how many more years is the first
question? And B, how come this already
happened by now?
And come back to me when you got the answer. You know, you know.
Oh, and if you keep trying, then what?
And what? It's suddenly going to change.
So, if you keep trying, it's suddenly
going to change.
Okay. Well, it's not changed in three
and a half years. So,
maybe one day. Yeah. Maybe, maybe, maybe
So, you're going to go up to someone,
right? And they're not going to do all
the things that all the other women have
been doing for years. I don't believe
it, bro. Like, you need you you need to
sell yourself to me, bro. You can have
an argument. We can have a debate, but
you you're not really selling yourself,
you know? So, you're not really convincing
because I've got I've got experience
and I've got like it's like having um
it's like going to court, right? And
I've got a jury. I've got a defense. But
you don't really have one because you're
just saying keep trying when I've tried
more than anyone in the world. And
trying hasn't changed anything. I've got
It's like I've got a jewelry. Yeah.
With a defense, but you don't really have one.
So, you know, the judge is going to take
my side. You know, I've got experience.
I've got, you know, it's I' I've got a
jewelry. I've got a good case. You don't
really have a any. You don't even have
an argument. Not literally, but So, I
mean, how can anyone take your word for it?
You literally said, "Don't try and never
change." And I've just told you I've
been trying for years and it's never changed.
So, it's like, what the [ __ ] It doesn't
even make any sense.
You need to leave the country. That's
what you need to do. You need to give up
and do other things such as leaving the country. Oh,
bro, you're an idiot. You're an absolute
Yes, I always used to win every week,
but I've been doing this women's [ __ ]
for years and I've still not won. Would
you go to the casino if you've been
losing for three and a half years? No,
you wouldn't. I
I'll give you a good example actually.
You want to know why I stopped gambling?
By gambling, I mean fishing frenzy,
roulette, and all of that stuff. You
want to know why I gave up this is a
good analog analogy here, right? Do you
know why I gave up the fishing frenzy
and the whole roulette [ __ ]
I did. You know what I did? Because I I
wasn't winning for like 6 months. So,
would you keep going to the casino if
you won if you was losing three and a
half years? No, you wouldn't. Cuz after
6 months, I just gave up.
You ain't done it more than me. You No,
no, no, no. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
You doing the woman [ __ ] is not the same
as me doing the women [ __ ] Okay. Okay.
Did you go out in London four times a
week approaching? Did you go to Wales
two times in a week approaching? Did you
go to Birmingham? Did you go to
Newcastle? Did you go to Scotland? Did
you go to Bristol? Did you go to Leeds?
Did you go to Sheffield? Did you go to Middlesbrough?
Did you do any of that [ __ ] for years? I
I I'm guessing you didn't because I
don't think any normal person has. So,
if you want to go by an analogy, right,
when I wasn't winning on them slots and
I wasn't winning in in on the roulette
for 6 months, I packed it in. I gave it up. So,
Oh [ __ ] Franklin, man. So, I I can
actually say like Yeah.
So you went to all of them places by
yourself approaching like I did. Really?
So you done it for years? Okay. Well,
how many how many people would you say
you approached in years?
You've not tried anywhere, bro. You've
not tried 1% of what I've tried. No one
in the world has.
And it's not even anything to be proud
of, to be honest. It's actually disgusting.
But somehow you think it's going to
change. You're [ __ ] delusional. You're delusional.
You are delusional.
You've not met nowhere near as many
women as I have. Nowhere. Nowhere.
Nowhere near. Bro, I used to I didn't
work for three and a half years. I was
getting three grand a month. What do you
think I got up to in in all of them
[ __ ] years when you was probably
working like a normal [ __ ] person?
You've not tried more. No one's tried
more than me. And it ain't anything to
to be proud of that, oh, I've tried more
than anyone. It's just how it is. So, yeah.
Well, I I I'm telling you my experience
and what I've dealt with. Like Thursday,
for example, right? I approached five
people sober. I have a boyfriend. I've
got a boyfriend. I've got a boyfriend.
I've got a boyfriend. You think I really
want to be going out dealing with the
same [ __ ] today after losing a football
bet? I don't give a [ __ ] if it was only
20. Do I want to go out? And And it's
not even that, bro. We're not even We're
not even talking about that. We're
you're you're delusional. Okay, put it
this way, right? Do you do you have a
mother, right? Do you have a mother,
right, that does the lottery? Do you
have a father that does the lottery? Cuz
my mom does the lottery. And guess what?
She ain't won in years. And the next
time she does it, she ain't going to win.
She ain't going to win. Just like most
people that do the lottery, they don't win.
That's that's another way you can see
it. So at the end of the day, if you
ain't got anything in three and a half years,
you know, leave. Simple.
But you're talking about yourself there.
Yeah, you're talking about yourself
there, mate. I've literally had sex on camera.
Um, you literally are the virgin. Uh,
yeah, talking about yourself.
Anyways, end the conversation. Let's
just agree to disagree.
You don't really have a argument. You
don't have a defense. So, there's no point arguing.
You just keep repeating the same [ __ ]
over and over again.
So, yeah. Simple,
right? Let's move on, bro. Let's just
agree to disagree.
I'm still a virgin. I've had more sex
than anybody on this [ __ ] community.
[ __ ] escorts. No escorts. It's not
the [ __ ] point. I'm not dealing with it today.
I should never have to deal with it for
the rest of my life.
Yeah. And I'm and and and and I'm
telling you what's happening to me,
right? And I'm telling you what's
happening to me. So, I think we should
just agree on that everyone's different
and just leave it. Everyone's different.
I think that's what we should agree on
that everyone's different and we both
got different experiences. End the story. So yeah,
I went out on Thursday. I got I got a
boyfriend about five times.
[ __ ] it was winding me the [ __ ] up.
So what you So okay. So what what what
do you think is going to happen if I
went out today then?
Let's just let me let me let me let me
ask you this this this question. What
will be different today than all the other [Music]
I don't know how many times let's just
say that the other 2,000 times you've
been out. What would make today so
different? Why today? Why today of all
of them 2,000 times before that you've been out?
No, no, no, no, no, no. Tell me what the
likely is. I I I know what would happen
if you don't. You'll save a lot of money
and you won't be depressed because you
already know the outcome. That's I I I
know as well. If you don't, then you're
saving yourself mental torture and
you're saving yourself money. That's
what will happen if you don't. So yeah,
that's what will happen if I if I don't
go out today, which I'm not going out
today. I'm going to save money. I'm not
going to get me. I'm not be going to be
dealing with the I've got a boyfriend
[ __ ] and I'm going to have a peace of mind.
Well, I don't sound depressed at all.
I'm just [ __ ] arguing with you.
That's what will happen if I don't go out today. Yeah. So, yeah.
Plan to leave, I guess. Yeah.
And it's not even about the I've got a
boyfriend [ __ ] bro. Really? You know,
you're going to get numbers and they're
just going to play games like they
always do. It's never going to change.
It's always going to be the same, you
know, but that's just like part of it.
What are you going to do? Get numbers
that mess you around.
Yeah, I'll be single. Okay, bro. Yeah,
good for you, man. Good for you.
Yeah. Well, I've got I've got a defense.
You don't have a defense, so Yeah, man.
It might be the same.
I mean, it might be. It might be the same.
When I've met women, I've not been
uh I've met a lot of women that's wasted
my time. Um I've not been on a date for
about 3 months.
So those were nothing to to to even to
even say about cuz a lot of them wasted
my time that and it made me more
depressed. There's a lot of them I
didn't even get a kiss from. So you have
no argument. At the end of the day I've
not been on a date in about 3 months and
God knows how many times I've been out.
Tells you all you need to know. Tells
you all you need to know. And also, even
if you meet a woman,
unless you've done something with them,
it doesn't even count. Unless you've
done something with them or you've met
them more than once, it don't even
count. It's just a time waster,
you know? I remember the last day I went
on, I wish I [ __ ] never met them. And
it makes you more depressed and it makes
you more hopeless.
So, and I'm not even chatting [ __ ] with
that one. I'm actually being deadly
serious. Where the [ __ ] are they now?
You're talking about these women that I've met.
Where the [ __ ] are they now, bro?
Where the [ __ ] are they now?
Does that mean you never will again?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. 100%.
Yeah, 100%. Where were these women now
that you speak of? You brought them up.
Where were they now?
Where are these so-called women?
Because 90% of them were bad
experiences. So, do do you want to keep
talking about that?
You should be in a relationship by now.
You should be lying in bed with someone
by now. No, it's not absolute bollocks.
No, it's not absolute bollocks at all.
How the [ __ ] would you know? Was you
there when we met? The last day I went
on was that Italian wasting my time
that you know
bad experiences are better than no
experiences. Uh no it's not. Uh no it's
No it's not mate.
No it's not. I'd rather have no experience.
I messaged that USA Izzy's friend. um
the other day as well. She still hasn't replied back.
If I ever see her, bro, I'll slap her
around her [ __ ] face. You understand
me? I'll slap the [ __ ] around their
[ __ ] face. Does that sound like it's
better than no experience?
Uh, stop asking stupid questions.
I'm not answering stupid questions.
So, stop ask stop asking stupid questions. So yeah,
like it's just the same old.
Yeah, man. You can't go out like that,
bro. When you've lost a football bet so
close to winning.
Nah, you can't, bro. You can't go out
like that. I can't. Nah, it doesn't
matter how much money I had in my bank
or have in my bank. You can't go out
like that. No way.
So, you've lost a football bet and then
you have to deal with the [ __ ] from
women. No thanks.
I'm good, bro.
Well, I'm sure if something was going to
change, it would have changed by now in
3 and 1/2 years. 3 and 1/2 years is a
long time. Like I said, when I stopped
winning on gambling, I gave up. After 6
months, I gave up.
So, I mean, the evidence is there. I
mean, you can't lie.
You know, you're saying that it's not
going to be the same old forever, but it
it is looking that way. The experiences
are looking that way. And I know that me
and Greavesy, we don't um agree with a
lot of things, but I'm I'm sure he would
even agree with me on this one, you know. Yeah,
it is going to be the same old. It will
be the same old until you leave England.
Until you leave. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no. Until you leave this westernized
country, it will never change. It will
literally never change. I mean, what's
what's your opinion, Grezy? You know,
let's have a let's have a third opinion.
My my I I'll tell you what my point is.
This is my whole point, Greavesy, before
you and then he has his point. what I'm
going by the fact is
I've been trying three and a half years
more than anyone in the world and it's
the same old and it continues to be the
same old and my question was is how long
does how long more does somebody have to
keep trying for
and I think that would that would stand
a good argument in court um if you if
you was arguing with somebody in court
that defense in itself
proves that you're Yeah.
So, it's a good defense. It's probably
one to I mean, yeah, you can say, "Oh,
you don't know what the future holds,
but they probably said that to you about
3 and 1/2 years ago as well." 3 and 1/2
years, you're still in the same rut.
So, I mean, we probably Well, we heard
that 3 and 1/2 years ago. So, I mean, yeah. Yeah.
I think it's a good argument.
I don't know what your opinion is, Grezy. Okay. Right. Okay. Yeah.
Okay. Yeah. Yeah.
No, they're just not someone for
everyone. I don't know what people's
opinion is on that. I just think they're
just not someone for everyone.
I just don't there's just not someone for everyone.
Literally, there isn't.
So, but you keep telling yourself that. Anyways, yeah, one sec.
Yeah, man. I'm getting too old. Like, if
this was like 3 years ago, Greasy. Yeah.
I'd have been like, "Oh, I'm just going
to go out anyways. [ __ ] it." But as you
get older, you know what's going to
happen. You know, it's okay going out
two times a month. And it's not money.
It isn't money. Um, you might think it
is, but it isn't. But it's more you kind
of know what you're going to get.
So, there's just like not really a point
in going out now for a while. So, yeah,
you make yourself worse when you go out as well.
It's one of them where you're just
damned if you do, damned if you don't.
I mean, you want to put yourself in that
position again, you know?
You know what I mean? Like,
and then the football bet just killed
the vibe anyways.
So, so that's how I dealt with it all
them years is winning from the gambling.
That's that's how I will say it to um and Antman. Yeah.
How will it change? By leaving England
and going to a country where they're interested.
That's that's how it will change. It
will change when you change. And by you,
I mean me, which is leaving this country,
you know, be Asia, be South America,
something like that.
Nah, bro. I'm good. I'm staying here.
I'm playing Franklin. So, that's how it
changes. It changes when you change.
When you leave this country and you go
to Asia where people are actually interested
or South America or Colombia. But that
is self milk. But that's the only way it
will ever change.
Will it change? Well, I mean, Ant-Man's
been in Cambodia for two weeks and he's
had three people that want to be his girlfriend. So,
yeah. I mean, he gets laid every night.
Um, he gets women interested on dating
apps. Don't know, man. I think so.
and any other white westernized person
that's gone there.
Yeah. No one's ever gone to Thailand and
said they couldn't get laid.
So, I mean
I mean that's how it will change. It
will change when you leave. So, yeah.
And I'm not drinking rum again. I need
to get a curry. Right. One second. Hold
on. Let me order this food a second.
They're just not interested in this country.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
Let's get some nice Indian food. Yeah,
it will never change. It's [ __ ]
depressing dealing with [ __ ] for women
your whole life. Your whole life. It's
not a life though, is it?
Yeah, this sounds like a better idea.
I got five numbers and only one replied.
Well, I'll be sat here chilling.
I'll be sat here chilling. Right.
I'm going to get a venderoo lamb vindaloo
and some rice.
Yeah, I'll probably just watch some WWE later or something.
I don't know how you think it can
change. I'd love to know that.
Well, I am.
>> Yeah, there's no point going out to get
more numbers. I don't reply. I only had
one [ __ ] reply out all their numbers. So,
you need to you get to a point where you
realize that there's no one for you in this country.
You need to you you get to a point where
you realize that there's just there's
just not someone for everyone. You know,
I mean saying that
I mean saying that if we weren't if
there was no social media then you know
you would have found someone. So I mean
who would really know you know
but I don't know Grezy I mean
I mean yeah I've started getting into W
well old WWE. Yeah.
Yeah. Going out today, getting rejected.
It ain't no life, is it?
It ain't no [ __ ] life,
is it, Grezy? Ain't no life, really, is it?
It ain't no life, mate.
Oh, 57 minutes.
I just ordered the food.
I mean, who what do you think about this
whole dating thing, Grezy? You didn't
really give like a sensible opinion.
My logic is it's never changed because
it's not changed for years and it
continues to be the same old if not worse.
I think I've got a good argument,
but people still somehow think it's
going to change one day. [ __ ] I'd
love to know how it will change. Every
time you go out, it's the same thing.
Like, it's not even similar. It's
literally the same thing.
But somehow you think it's going to change. Wow.
You really are a believer, bro.
You really are an optimist because Yeah.
You seem to think one day all of a
sudden you're going to meet someone.
You're crazy, bro. Crazy. [ __ ] crazy.
Yeah, I went on a date three months ago.
I wish I never. It knocked my confidence down.
Yeah, it knocked it knocked my confidence.
I went on a date um 3 months ago. Greasy.
Yeah, it [ __ ] my confidence up.
That's all you're doing when you're
going out. You're just you're just torturing yourself.
55. You're You're just torturing
yourself every time you go out.
But somehow you think one day it's going
to change. Yeah. Madness.
No. No. No. No. Uh yes, that's what but
this when this guy is saying that you
don't know what the future holds and retin
bear in mind you know my history. No, I
don't care about it. I mean that's why I
mean that's exactly why I didn't go out
today because of the football bear and
the fact I didn't want to deal with the
[ __ ] again. I mean that's I mean that's
exactly why I didn't go out. That's
exactly why I'm not going out today.
That's the exact reason why I'm not
going out today.
I dressed up, done my hair. I was ready
to go, but I was like, "Fuck this, bro.
You because you've not tried nowhere
near 1% of me. You have not tried
nowhere near as much as I have. So,
if you was going to meet I don't even
like talking. It just winds me up
talking about it to be honest. I don't
even like talking about it, Grezy. It
just it just winds me up,
you know? Like, think of it like you're
wound up enough from the football, the
[ __ ] and then you're going to go
out and deal with even more [ __ ]
Uh because I've got more experience than
you. Because I've gone out and I've
tried more than you. I've got more
experience than you.
That's the whole point. I've got more
experience than you. I went out on
Thursday. I got numbers on Thursday. I
got one person that's replied back.
I went to, you know, I I did go out on
Thursday as well.
I don't uh Yes, I do.
Um Yes, I do.
Every time you go out, it's the same.
Bro, listen listen. Let me let me let me
I knew you was going to bring this up,
bro. Listen. You know when you're saying
that you've been in a relationship? Yeah.
You're in a relationship with one
person, right? I was going around
meeting all kinds of women and they're
all the same. They're all the [ __ ]
same. They've had a bird friend's house.
Uh, bro, what have I told you about
talking about yourself?
Smoking the time. What have I told you
about talking about yourself, man? It's
not going to change the fact that you're
all of them things yourself talking about me.
Why do you constantly come on here and
talk talk about yourself like that?
It's not good for your mental health.
I've told you this many times. All of
the things that you're saying that I
don't have, I've already shown a million times.
I've literally shown a million times. I
think your disabilities is getting
yourself confused with me again.
Like, you're a [ __ ] [ __ ] All of
them self-projecting things that you've
you you've just wrote is literally every
single thing that I have actually shown on here.
You're you're actually talking about yourself,
you know. Jesus Christ, bro.
And another thing is, right, um, you're
saying about, uh, you've been in a few
long-term relationships. That doesn't
mean you know more women than me, bro.
It doesn't matter. You being in a
relationship doesn't mean anything.
They're individual women. That doesn't
mean you've got more experience. And
yeah, I I kind of have been in a
relationship with someone. That does not
mean you know more about women. You have
not gone up and down the country meeting
different women. I have.
So just cuz you've been in a long-term
relationship, that doesn't mean [ __ ]
I've got [ __ ] sisters. I've got a
[ __ ] mother. I was up and down
[ __ ] you know.
No, I'm talking about this smog on the
[ __ ] time. He's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
He's talking about himself. Never
worked. Yeah, I've never worked. you're
talking about. Why are you sat on RJ's
um live stream every day as well? So, yeah.
And it was it was actually dep and I
tell you another thing up girl when I
went out on Thursday, it was actually
depressing as [ __ ]
I wasn't talking about you when I done
them five approaches. It was actually
depressing me every time you you you
Yes, I have had a job.
Yes, I've had a few jobs.
Even you know the thing is it's [ __ ]
depressing. I went out on Thursday. Even
I got a boyfriend [ __ ] It's [ __ ] depressing, bro.
It's [ __ ] annoying and it's [ __ ]
Every time you go out, you lose more and
more hope. I think that's the way to put
it, Grezy. Is it?
I think that's the way. I think every
time you go, the more you go out, the
more you lose hope. The more women you
meet, the more you lose hope.
Nope. Because the thing is, Greavesy,
all of that comes to an end when you try
to speak to a woman and they keep
pretending that they've got a boyfriend.
Well, you keep telling yourself, "Well,
well, I' I'm giving up." How about this
one? Let's just both agree to disagree
and I'm giving up.
You want You've not had the same thing as me.
You've not had the same thing as me,
bro. I've tried more than anyone in the
world. What do you mean you've had it
more than me? What? Because you maybe
went out every week with your friends.
That's not anywhere near the amount I've tried.
What the [ __ ]
You're talking [ __ ] Absolute bollocks.
It's like what the [ __ ]
You're [ __ ] full, man.
I think I've still got that rum in my
system, you know. Greasy.
I mean, you're like I said, you're an
optimist, bro. More than me.
You think one day you're going to go out
and it all of a sudden changes? [ __ ] hell, bro.
You're crazy, man.
You really are crazy.
So what happened in them three and a
half years, man? [ __ ]
Well, lucky you. Lucky you.
But I've given up 100%. I've I probably
won't go out now for probably like another month. Yeah, man.
So, my sister said, "You don't need to
go out more than once a month." I was
like, "You're crazy.
No, it's all right, man. It didn't make
me mad. It was just a buzz kill.
Yeah, I'm not happy either. They [ __ ]
me up for £140. I could have done with
that money today. I was just about to go out.
I was just about to go out and do some
um approaches and [ __ ] but it just
ruined my mood, so I never
Yeah, they [ __ ] me up as well, mate. I
could have done with that, Molly. I
could have done with it.
Yeah, whatever, bro.
That's why I didn't go out today, bro. I
I literally dressed up to go out. I done
my hair and everything. Uh Steven Howard
and I literally just went back in the
shower and got changed and ordered some food.
Uh, bro, we're not talking about my looks.
If you if you want to talk about my
looks, at least show your face.
And I'm nowhere near 30 either.
And you're gone. Bye or by now. It's basic.
Yeah, I don't want I don't want my money
back. I don't care about £21.
I just wanted to um Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, I got a right idea, man. Yep.
What car did that come out of? Yeah.
So, yeah, I'm [ __ ]
I'm pissed off now. Anyways,
yeah, I'm I'm glad you're on the
whiskey, bro. It ruined my whole day.
That [ __ ] football bet.
Yeah, I'll probably go sleep and hope I
don't wake up.
It didn't make me mad or anything. It's
just a buzz kill.
Just a [ __ ] buzz kill.
It's annoying, bro.
You have to deal with this [ __ ] for
women year in year out, year in, year
out, and then you got to deal with
[ __ ] shitty [ __ ] one-off [ __ ] goals.
The [ __ ] man? Like, what the hell? This
life will never change.
Never, bro. Never. Yeah,
it's depressing, isn't it, Grezy?
This life is [ __ ] bro. It
I wish I'd never done that football bet now.
How much did you lose, Stephen Howard? I
wish I'd ever done that football bet
makes you want to kill yourself in it.
That along with the bad experiences,
it's a fuel for negativity, isn't it?
It actually is a fuel for negativity.
It does fuel negativity, doesn't it,
gambling? Yeah. Might
as well just eat lots of [ __ ] food and
be and become depressed now. It
>> Yeah. What was the return? Mine was 142.
It will never change. Never change.
Hopefully I just have a sleep and die in
my sleep. Have a heart attack or
something. It'll be nice.
Never have to think about this [ __ ] ever again.
It will never change. Never. Same old.
No, I do the odd football um now and then,
but it looks like I can't even do that
to be honest with you. I do the odd uh
football bets. I won two times in a week.
um one go off [ __ ] £140
[ __ ] I was about to go out and
everything. I was changed. I was like I
can't go out with that on my mind being
[ __ ] over by one goal.
So even though I didn't need the money I
could have done with the money even
though I didn't need the money but still
it's still money in it.
So, just to press now, you can always
count on gambling to ruin the day.
A one-off goal. Yeah.
And I won two times in a week as well.
I haven't gambled responsibly as well.
That's the thing.
I guess it's not a form of Did anyone
ever tell you this? Any of these
streamers tell you that when you gamble,
you become depressed.
It makes me depressed. I don't know
about you. And mine was only £21. That
was some of my winnings. I don't know
about any of you, but it makes I don't
know about any of you, but it makes me [ __ ] depressed.
[ __ ] gets me [ __ ] down. That's why
I couldn't go out today. I have to deal
with that and the [ __ ] from the women.
Nah, I'm good, thanks. Yeah, man. Yeah.
Could have done with that [ __ ]
[ __ ] 40 odd pound.
Let's put it straight, bro. anyone could
have done with it. You know what I mean?
Like [ __ ] hell. How many [ __ ]
hours would you have to work for that?
I can't believe they didn't score.
I actually can't believe they didn't score, lad.
They had enough time to score.
They had enough [ __ ] time, didn't they?
Yeah, they had enough time to score, didn't they?
It's depressing, bro.
My Indian should be here in a minute. Yeah.
But it's good that I discovered that
thing today with the money
and that's why I dealt with this [ __ ]
for so many years
without like doing something drastic. I
think that is that is a part of it to be honest.
Get bad experiences, win money cuz you
knew at the end you have money and
you're going to get laid at the end of
the day no matter what. That's probably
why I dealt with it for so long.
That obviously it makes sense.
Obviously. Yeah. You know what I mean?
You know, you live in London, it's [ __ ]
even like before you you tried. Oh [ __ ]
I won £800. Well, no matter what happens
today, got a couple of numbers and I'm
getting laid. So win-win.
That's that's why I didn't do anything
for so all them years like you do a madness
and I had too much to lose as well that
you know what I'm saying? So
I'll tell I'll tell him about that later. Um, man. Oh [ __ ] So yeah. [Music] Yeah, mom.
Anyways, I'm going to um eat eat the
Indian. I'll come back later.
I'll definitely be back later. Anyway, so yeah.