Wait till that little [ __ ] [ __ ] goes
live, bro. I swear someone someone's
getting it today, bro. 100% someone's
[ __ ] getting it. I swear to God.
Oh, Milton Kees broke boy. Smokey B, why
don't you come and join the hangouts?
I'm going to go on that live stream at
7. By the way, I'm going to meet this
little [ __ ] today. Yeah, the little
Milton Kees wanker. Milton Kees boy,
bro. I swear to God. Same with Red Star.
Yeah, put up where you are and I will
come and meet you tomorrow. Yeah. I'm
not even going to do a video. I'm even
going to go live. I've titled your
[ __ ] names. Yeah. Milton Kee, broke
boy. You're another one. Yeah. I'm going
to put the link out when more people
join. Right. I want one of you to come
in like the cowards that you are. Yeah.
And um Yeah. Show me where you are and I
will come and meet you. Um [ __ ] Boy,
Red Star, and then uh Smokey B. I want a
time. I want a time that you're going to
meet me and Milton Kees. I want you to
join the hangouts. I'm going lie today,
bro. [ __ ] this. Yeah, [ __ ] I've had
enough of these people, bro. I swear to
God. I've actually had enough of these
people. I Milton Ke broke boy pretending
that he gambled away three grand. Right.
Let me put the link out cuz I know you
watch me. [ __ ] this, bro. [ __ ] this completely.
Oh, you little Milton Ke M. Mm. You
little M boy. Come and join the hangouts
right now. Yeah. No, I'm not going to go
tomorrow, bro. Let this little [ __ ] come
in and agree to meet me before I go and
waste my [ __ ] time. Yeah, simple,
bro. And that red, I'm calling you both
out. Yeah. Now, now I'm actually calling
you both out and I want you to show me
where you are. Come on, Milton Kings
boy. Come on, Northampton boy. Come on.
Come on, [ __ ] boy. That ain't London.
Come on. You know, you you you want to
keep winding people up. And guess what,
bro? I'm going to come in at Hangouts at
7:00. Yeah. I'm gonna come in that
hangouts at seven and I'm just going to
keep talking about how much of a [ __ ]
you are and now you're never going to
meet me. Yeah, you [ __ ] stupid skint
little melting keen skint boy on £300 a
month. Yeah, that's what you are about.
You've stop [ __ ] going on people's
hangouts pretending that you've gambled
three grand. You've never gambled three
grand. You've never seen three grand in
your life. You little Milton Kings boy.
Yeah. So, trust me, I'm going to be
going in that hangouts at 7. I'm going
to be bullying the [ __ ] out of that
Milton Keen guy. And watch what I'm
going to talk about as well. I'm going
to keep talking until he meets me. I'm
going to keep taking the piss out of his
Milton Keen accent. I'm going to take
the piss out of him and his voice.
Watch, bro. And you will see this guy
won't dare let me travel to him, bro. He
will not dare let me travel to him. The
Milton Ke [ __ ] boy on£300 a month ain't
going to meet no one. Yeah. Yeah. I'm
not even needing to bring anyone's
[ __ ] names into it now. The little
special needer, the little run boy
hiding in Milton Kees is not going to
meet anyone. Yeah, that's what I'm going
to do. I'm going to join the hangouts.
Yeah. And and I'm not going to argue
with any of them until he joins.
Yeah. Simple. And after today, I'm
coming off, bro. I'm coming off again
after today. Yeah. I'm [ __ ] sick of
all you [ __ ] spastics. I don't even
know why I come back, bro. I hate all of
you, bro. You don't understand. Except
the few people that come on my live. I
hate all of you, bro. Yeah. And if I
ever see one of you, I'll smack you on
the [ __ ] road. Yeah. Just like I
called [ __ ] Prime out. Yeah. I called
In Birmingham. So, let's not talk about
that anymore, bro. Yeah. Let's not even
talk about that anymore. Yeah, bro. I'm
going to join it. I'm going to join. I'm
going to tell him to join. If he's not
going to join, I'm going to leave.
There's no shouting. There's no arguing.
Let's see what the Milton Kings little M
boy pretending that he's got three grand
is going to do today. [ __ ] pretending
that he's he's gamble, bro. You don't
have free grand. You don't have money.
You know what I'm saying, bro? You don't
have nothing. You're You live in Milton
Kees. You're a Milton Kees boy. Not a
London boy. You're a Milton Kees boy. Do
you know if he's got Bro, do you know if
this guy's got kids or anything or like
a family? I'm just going to start taking
a piss out of his family today. I'm
going to keep taking a piss out of his
family today and everything. Yeah,
I'm going to start taking a piss out of
his mom and I'm going to I'm going to
his mom and his dad. Yeah, that's what
I'm going to do is watch watch, bro.
When when he goes live. Yeah, I'm going
to start taking a piss out of his mom
and his dad and everything, bro. Watch
watch, bro. I'm going to I'm I'm going
to be the [ __ ] center of attention in
that live stream. Yeah.
Sorry, bro. This is why you don't see me
on here anymore, bro. Because of these
retards. S, bro. Like, after today.
Yeah. I don't really come on here
anymore because of these retards.
Because, you know, they're geeks, bro.
Like, they would get slapped up in real
life, bro. You think someone from Milton
Kees, a soft Milton Ke, a little soft
boy who sucks his dad's dick, could ever
say anything to me, bro. That's like the
insult. Some stupid little reject for
Milton Kees. Like, do you know how much
of an insult that is, lad? Like, some
stupid little reject from Milton Kees is
going to start typing about me, bro.
Like, did you all forget a month ago
when I come out the gym and I said to
him, "Let's meet today." And he bottled
it. Do you remember that? Do you
remember I literally said that and he
bottled it? He's some little Milton Ke
reject, bro. The M would get slapped up.
He is a Milton Keen boy. And I know that
annoys him because he ain't from London.
You're trying to be from London, but
you're not from London. Bro, that's the
that's the annoying thing is cuz these
people, bro, they would get slapped up
in real life. These ugly fat people,
these skin fat, ugly life losers would
get slapped in real life. It's not even a joke.
Like, bro, you've seen how they all act
when people in Birmingham. Like, allow
it, man. You know what I'm saying? This
is why I don't come on here anymore, bro.
This is exactly why I don't come on here
anymore. You don't see me. This is
exactly exactly why I don't come on here
anymore, bro. Now you see exactly the
reason. They're all [ __ ] retards. You
know what I'm saying? They're all skin
[ __ ] ugly people on benefits. And the
difference is, bro, I will say it to
their face. You know, I'm not trying to
sit here and say it to them. Yeah.
I'm not trying to sit there and say it
behind the keyboard, bro. Like, I will
say it to his face. You know what I'm
saying, bro? I will say it to his
[ __ ] face. Any one of them, brother,
if they want to meet me today. It's why
I don't come on here no more, bro.
You know what I'm saying?
You run up your mouth online. Even
seeing their stupid little comments
annoys me, bro. When I'm trying to
[ __ ] when I'm arguing with someone
else, you would get slapped the [ __ ] out
of you stupid Milton Ke, bro. They're
talking about my looks, bro. I'm better
looking than all of you ugly people. Why
do you think you're sat on YouTube every
day? Skin ain't got a life. Yeah.
Friday, Saturday, you're all on [ __ ]
YouTube. Friday, Saturday, you're all on
YouTube. [ __ ] Skintter than a [ __ ]
skin. All talking to each other. All
lonely, bro. Yeah. Let's start talking
about this, bro. No, no, no, no, no. I'm
not going to I'm going to go in today
and I'm going to start talking about his
family, bro. Yeah. I'm going to start
talking about his family. Has this guy
got kids, bro? Has this guy got kids?
I'm going to make this [ __ ] meet me
today, bro. Yeah, I am going. You've got
me reacting now. Yeah, I'm going to
start talking about the Milton King soft
boy who sucks his dad's dick. That's
one. No, no, no, no, no, no, bro. No.
You wanted a reaction. Now you've got a
reaction. Now I'll finish it. Now I'll
show everyone what the Milton Ke boy is
always going to be about. Yeah, that's
it, bro. That's it. I'm going to [ __ ]
show that Milton Kees [ __ ] buyer on
£300 a month pretending that he's gamble
three, bro. I'm going to rip into him
today, bro. Watch. As soon as he goes
live in two minutes, I am going to
[ __ ] rip into them, bro. Every single
one of them. This is why I don't come on
this [ __ ] anymore, bro. Yeah. You got a
reaction. I've reacted now. I'll finish
it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Exactly, bro.
Yeah. No, I just hate these people on
this community, bro. Yeah.
You know, you little Milton Ke M boy.
Little skint boy in Milton Kees boy.
Yeah. I'll tell you all about your
fuckingelves today. Sat on YouTube every
[ __ ] day. You ain't got no money. You
ain't got no life. You're all skin ugly
bully victims, bro. Yeah. Do you know
what I'm saying? You're all skinned,
ugly little bully victim YouTubers. And
I'll meet any of you today, bro. This is
another thing. I'm going to meet any of
these people. Listen, bro. You didn't
want it last month when I come out the
gym when I said, "Listen, you Milton
Kees boy, [ __ ] boy. She called you
every name under the sun and you still
wouldn't let me meet you. You little
rejects. You little geeks. Yeah. You
make it [ __ ] impossible for anyone to
meet you. You think some little geek,
little nerdy little virgin in Milton
Kees, some little [ __ ] ass could ever
say anything to my face? Okay, well,
we'll see you in 2 minutes then, won't
we? Yeah, come in the hangout and let's
talk properly and arrange the fight
properly. Yeah. Or tomorrow. Yeah,
simple, bro. That's it, man. You little
dirty [ __ ] geeky little virgin nerds.
Little low lives on benefits. Yeah,
that's what you all are. Most of you,
bro, of that L's channel. You're all
little benefit bums. You're all little
fat ugly life losers. You want to talk
about taking Oh, it's everyone else's
fault that you're in your 40s and you're
on benefits. Oh, isn't that funny?
Everyone's a [ __ ] everyone's a fat
ugly mant, isn't it? Because you are in
your 40s, all ugly on benefits. That's
everyone else's life. That's everyone
else here. That's everyone's else fault
that you're all ugly and you're all on
benefits. And you can't stop coming on
YouTube talking about your fat bun ugly
selves. Yeah, that's what you are, bro.
You all talk about your [ __ ] ugly
selves. Get off of YouTube, bro. What
are you doing? Get off of YouTube. You
know, I was off YouTube for four or five
days. Yeah, come on. Get off of YouTube.
Come on. You're nothing, bro. You'll
never come off YouTube. It's your lives,
mate. It's your [ __ ] lives. That's
what it is. It's your spasticated lives.
You talking about yourselves, trying to
call other people what you are is all
you've got in your life. And I love it,
bro. I love it. It's the truth, bro. You
hate You hate what you ate, love. That's
what you are.
You're sad little mas. Sad little a sad
little Milton Kings m. And let me tell
you, do you know what I want to I want
to meet this guy for? It ain't even so
much that I'll smack him up, bro. No.
Gambled. No, I don't gamble anymore,
bro. Do you know what? Do you know what
it is? I want to show everyone the real
manta. The fat ugly manta. the ugly
people on YouTube. You know, it's not so
much that I know I'm gonna beat them up.
I just want to show their ugly looks,
the fat, ugly Milton Kings boy. I want
to show the [ __ ] boy that pretends he's
gambled three grand. He's never seen
three grand, mate. That's what I want to
do, bro. As I'm beat him up as well. I
want to show everyone. These are the fat
ugly bunters that can't get off of
YouTube. Let's make a Let's make a book
of it, bro. Some [ __ ] Milton Kees, boy.
Please, please. Come on, you Milton Kees
boy. Come on, you Northampton [ __ ]
[ __ ] You little Northampton geek. You
little Northampton geek. At least if
someone's from [ __ ] Manchester, bro,
or [ __ ] London, you can actually take
them a bit serious. But a [ __ ] Milton
Kees boy. A Milton Kees boy. I don't
know if any of you have ever been to
Milton Kees before, but yeah, it's a [ __ ] man.
Milton Kees is a [ __ ] It's got one
shopping center and loads of
roundabouts. I don't know if you've ever
been, but imagine a little farmer boy, a
little town boy thinking that he could
ever he could ever try it with me. Bro,
please meet me so I can show everyone
how ugly you are. Please, come on, man.
Let's not be a keyboard warrior. You
know, let's not be a keyboard warrior,
man. Come on. Let's not be a key. I will
go anywhere. Same thing to Red Star as
well. I will meet you anywhere tomorrow.
You said all of these. All do you know
what um do you know what he said? Um do
you know what Red Star said Joe? He's
jealousy got into it, bro. He gave
himself away. Yeah. Somebody was asking why. Um
um what was he saying? Um
why are you doing all of this? And he
said stop what he said, bro. He said
it's because I sublet and gambled and I
was flush. I told you it was jealousy.
They don't like anyone that's not fat
and ugly and old like them. I told you.
I told you exactly what, bro. I told you
what it was, bro. He even said it
himself. Not in that way, but he
basically said it. I knew it. Yeah, you
got more money than them. You're better
looking than them. Yeah, they It kills
them, doesn't it? It actually kills
them. It really does, mate. I need to
get a McDonald's coke in a bit, mate.
Yeah, I'm starting to think it is as well.
well, bro. To be honest with you, I'm
thinking it is too
because of um because of uh
um because of the things he's talking
about like acid attacks. Yeah, I was
starting to think that too. Either way,
it's a coward. Whoever's behind that
account, they're a coward. This is just
exactly like what LT said. Just like
that Smokey B, just like all of them
from that L J channel, they're all
spastics. I don't know how anyone can go
on that channel, you know?
You know, I I I
know what I mean.
Yeah. Well, if he doesn't let me in, he
doesn't let me in. That's That's fine,
bro. I'll just talk about on my channel.
It's fine. If they don't let me in, they
don't let me in.
I swear to God, if I ever catch one of
these people, bro, swear to God, I would
love to I will [ __ ] Simone spite
them. And you know what I want to do to
that to that [ __ ] smoky be that red
shot? I would just slow and spike them.
Have you ever seen what a Samoan spike
is? I'll just Samo and spike him once,
bro. That would be it. Just just a Samo and spike.
Yeah. Straight through the throat. That'
be it, bro.
That that that that be it, bro. Just a
nice Simone spike.
Just another one of LJ's [ __ ]
followers. I don't know how Joe goes in
there. It's full of spastics. It's the
same [ __ ] It's the same people every day.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
But we all know why these people do all
of this [ __ ] bro. Is they're all
[ __ ] fat and ugly, in it. They're all
fat and ugly, mate. Now he's not all
right, bro. And if he ever comes back
here, I'm going to slap him up. Whenever
he comes back to London again, I'm going
to slap the [ __ ] out of him. Bro,
you do not understand what this Lord Jay
does. I don't think you understand, bro.
I don't like any of them. Do you not
understand what this L J does? He goes
for people that he deems weaker than
him. Do you not understand what he does,
bro? He goes for people like Timmy. Then
I have to end up almost in court for
what I say to him before he goes and
then he avoids LT. I don't like him.
He's a [ __ ] You know, that's one of
the reasons why I don't like him.
Yeah, I did tell Bro, I told you I did.
Bro, I told you I did. I don't lie about anything.
Yeah, I told you I did. Yeah, I've got
to make a new channel now cuz these
little spastics discovered me, in it.
Yeah, they discovered me. That's how
they keep discovering me. That's why I
don't like that LJ. Anyways, that's why
I don't like that LJ. If he actually met
that LT, then I'd say, do you know what?
I could actually kind of tolerate him.
But he's a [ __ ] He's an opportunist.
No, I didn't go back in the barbers.
I already had my haircut. No,
I think they were looking, but Yeah.
Yeah, I need a McDonald's coke, man. [ __ ]
I can't exactly order one cuz it's too
expensive. It's like £7.
Quite a walk though, bro.
But yeah, you see what I mean? Nicolo.
But yeah, I think that's Pat as well.
That red star to be honest with you. I
think so as well. Yeah.
Yeah, I think it is as well to be honest.
But yeah, anyways, this is why you don't
really see me on it, bro. I'm going to
make a new channel and then um I won't
be on for like a week.
This is why I don't come on here anymore, bro.
Cuz someone on here is going to annoy me
and I want to get them, bro. I want to
get them. You know what I'm saying? I
want to really hurt one of them, bro.
And you don't understand. And because I
can't get them, you know what I mean,
bro? That's why you don't really see me
on here much.
Do you remember that though, Nicolo? Go.
Where have my little legs take me?
Where have my little legs take me? You remember that?
They took me all kinds of places.
Yeah, that [ __ ] that Red Star is
jealous, bro. He said because I used to
sublet the house and win money from
gambling, that's why he goes for me.
That just goes to show that he's jealous
of money, bro. I knew it, man. I knew it.
These people are on benefits, bro. I'm telling you.
These people are on [ __ ] benefits.
I'm telling you, man. Don't Don't listen
to end. These people are these people
are [ __ ] skinned, bro.
Yeah. Do you remember that, Nikolai? Yeah,
I sure did.
I need a McDonald's drink, man.
But if I order it, it's like seven quid.
I'm pay I can't pay seven pound, bro.
I really fancy a McDonald's coke. It
doesn't taste the same, bro. Unless it's McDonald's.
Um, and I'm not hungry cuz I just ate as well.
Quite a walk as well. About 10 minutes. 15 minutes. Um um
so take you saw the approach today Nicolola
you like him good in it
still can't stop hearing that I have a
boyfriend [ __ ] bro you still can't stop
hearing it now I'm just going to have a
car I already I already went out for twice today.
Yeah, you you can't stop. Uh
yeah, but I went I walked twice today. I
went out twice today.
Yeah, I go to the co-op as well.
Yeah, you can't stop hearing the um
Yeah, I've got a boyfriend. [ __ ]
Oh, [ __ ] One second, bro. Yeah. One sec.
Yeah, exactly right.
Oh, did you see all the videos there?
Yeah, they just say that they're not interested.
Yeah, they're not interested, but people
still tell you that you're going to meet someone. Yeah.
Oh, yeah, man. The video where I was
like wearing a hat and [ __ ] Yeah.
Oh, did you watch then? Yeah.
Yeah. It's happened a few times, bro.
Sometimes you just approach someone and
they'll say straight away you're not um
they'll say straight away that they're
not interested and then um
um what will happen is um you'll then
show it to people on Reddit and then
they start attacking you, which is
basically what I had today. I had a
woman attacking me and being personal
and [ __ ] All cuz I showed her videos
where women weren't interested. All cuz
I took their advice. Yeah.
Yeah. It's happened um three maybe. It's
happened a few
Yeah, it's happened a few times.
Yeah. You can't get anyone in this
country. It's impossible, bro.
So now you've seen it for yourself.
It never changes. That's what I mean,
bro. Like, yeah. So, you've seen it
yourself now. I don't care who's seen in
the videos, bro. I'm not insecure. I
just don't want people see me, do it.
Like, Red Star, I don't them I don't
want to keep I don't want to give them little weirdos
um ammo. You see, that's the only
reason. But I don't care, bro. I'll just
start a new channel now.
So, yeah, bro. That's um that's the thing.
They treat you like you're ugly and
there's nothing wrong with you just like
there's nothing wrong with like any
other people that's right and then they
wonder why people get depressed. So
yeah, this is why like I feel like the
best the best um approach is just to give up.
Um, which is Shouldn't really have to do that. But
yeah, I wish I recorded it, but I never recorded it.
It's no life for anyone, bro. Really, is it? But
then people say that you that it
changes. How how can it change?
They say life changes.
You know, I was reading, Nicola, I was
reading uh I'm not um people talking
about dating like 19 days ago and
people's like, "Oh yeah, I got friends
with I don't know how they get friends
with benefits." I think they were in
America, but I don't know how they even get laid.
You can't even get a date. So, how
people how they get laid? I I shall
never know, bro, to be honest.
I don't know how they do it. I actually
messaged a few of them after ask them.
Not wondering how they do it because
obviously it's not going to change my
situation, but basically wanted to show
them because there's no point me
wondering how they've done it cuz it's
not going to make me do it. So, not I
didn't mean it in that way. I meant it
like this is how it is in London. What
the [ __ ] you know?
Yeah. They say it's hookup culture.
Yeah, but how?
You can't even get a conversation, let
alone a [ __ ]
what the [ __ ] You can't even get a
kiss, let alone anything else. But yeah,
yeah, they say it's hookup culture. Yeah,
that's what I I don't understand, bro.
It's like people say stuff online,
right? And then that was the whole point
of that channel. Do you like the name of
my channel, Nicolola? The whole point
was to show the reality of like dating
for someone that's like normal looking
or this is the the reality of it.
This is the reality when you try to try to date. Yeah.
So, this is the reality when you're
trying to date in these westernized countries.
Um, so I'm not sure where you would go.
You know what you would do. Anyone would
think you look like I might as well been
born. What the [ __ ] This guy should I
might as well have been [ __ ] tip born Timmy Eldridge. Yeah.
I have to put all them videos up there
again. [ __ ] sake. Going to take ages now.
Yeah, I don't want any of them on my
channel or following my [ __ ]
Yeah, they're just not interested in this country.
So, what are you saying? That they're
not interested in this country or
something? Is that what you're trying to say?
Yeah. I'd say I'm like decent looking.
Yeah. Decent beard, decent face,
decent hair. Well, even though I was
wearing a cap. Yeah. I think I just look normal.
And I can't get I've had it before where
they've just said not. I've had it. I've
had it a few times. It doesn't happen
all the time knowing it, but it it does happen. Yeah.
They're just not interested in this country.
Oh, I just run over a [ __ ] dog, bro.
That's why I don't think it's a good
idea me going out doing it again, bro.
Because the same thing's going to happen
again. You remember we said, "Oh, yeah.
let me not do this for like 2 weeks.
Um, let me do it for 2 weeks. And you
said you'd probably end up killing
yourself. That is what will happen. You
can't do it, bro. Because what what's
going to happen is you're going to do
about five of them and then you're going
to keep getting the same [ __ ]
right? And then you're going to think,
well, whoa, [ __ ] this is [ __ ] up. How
can you be normal looking or station
looking or whatever good looking
whatever the [ __ ] it is and then um
and then um you know you can't even get
anything and then it's going to play on
your mind and then it's just not worth
doing it. You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. Do you like the approaches then? Yeah,
I done more as well that I didn't put
up. I've got some more recorded I didn't put up.
Yeah, I got a lot, bro.
Yeah, it's bad, isn't it?
It pretty much shows that you're helpless.
But I'm not I'm not even going to do a
football bet next week because there's
no point in me winning because I'm not
going to be going out. So yeah.
So hopefully that gets you more of an
insight, bro, of um how how we're
dealing with how how it's like dating in this country.
It's [ __ ] up, isn't it?
So, what would you do if you was me?
Yeah. I mean, imagine I was a virgin.
Imagine how bad that would be if I was a virgin.
That would be bad, isn't it? And I mean,
even if I even if I just had escorts
only. Imagine I just had escorts only,
which to me is still a virgin. Even if
you just [ __ ] their schools. I mean,
technically you're not, but you know,
you cheated then. Like, imagine I was a
virgin. Imagine how worse that would be.
I think I would have probably end up
probably doing someone in, bro. I'm not
going to lie to you. It's depressing.
It's like, think of it, bro. Like, you
know, these simps, I've had more women
than these simps would ever have, and it
still depresses the [ __ ] out of me, you know?
I don't care about society norms and I
don't care about what's socially
acceptable. I used to say it to the I
used to say it to the virgin. I used to
say I don't give a [ __ ] what's socially
acceptable or not. You little virgin. I
I I don't want to be accepted by society,
you know? I don't care what's what's
acceptable by this [ __ ] up society,
you know, Tik Tok and that. I don't want
to be accepted by a [ __ ] up society.
You know what I mean? So,
I don't want to be [ __ ] up. I don't
want to be um
I don't want to be accepted by a [ __ ] up society.
Yeah. Well, I don't give a [ __ ] what's I
used to say to the little virgin.
I don't give a [ __ ] what's socially
acceptable or not. I don't give a [ __ ]
That's what I used to say to him. You
silly little [ __ ] Don't try and [ __ ]
manipulate me, you silly wanker.
Cuz what they do is not socially
acceptable. Because the thing is it No,
no, no, Joe. Because what they do isn't socially acceptable.
What these some of these people do ain't
socially acceptable? So you need to
practice what you [ __ ] preach.
Is what they do socially acceptable? Ask
them is what they do socially
acceptable? No, it's not.
So yeah, bro. I don't know. I'm still
figuring out what to actually do, bro.
They say it's a hookup culture.
Let me just make sure I can I've got all
of them videos. Yeah.
But yeah, it is impossible to get laid.
Yeah, it's impossible to um
Oh, is it impossible other guys?
Because realistically, yeah,
you need to watch out for the other guys
cuz the other guys do it.
So, what do you think I'm normal looking then, Nikol?
Where's that one? The island. One
second, bro. I need to
One second. Where's I hope I I ain't
I ain't uh
deleted it. No,
I have to delete a lot of my videos, man. But yeah,
this hookup culture. Yeah, we've seen
that as well.
I'm not trying to get validation, bro.
They they found my channel, lad. If I
was trying to get validation,
right, I wouldn't be on a community like this.
I mean, these people will bring you down
no matter what you are. So, I mean, if I
was trying to get validation, lad, I
wouldn't be on here on this community.
But where's that [ __ ] other video I got?
Yeah, this is why
that's why I don't really come on here anymore, lad.
You know, you can't even get laid.
It makes you suicidal, doesn't it?
You can't even get [ __ ] laid.
It's mad, isn't it?
But somehow people think that one day
it's going to change.
How is it going to change? Yeah.
How's it going to change?
How is it going to change, bro?
It will never change, mate. Never change. Yeah,
I don't know what to do, bro. Honestly, um,
give up with life. I don't know, bro. It's depressing
being treated like you're Timmy Eldridge.
Imagine being treated like you're
[ __ ] Timmy Eldridge. H,
being treated like you're Timmy Eldridge.
I'm being treated like I'm Timmy Aldridge.
Oh, here we go. Lovely.
Got it, mate. Lovely.
Yeah, it will never it will never change.
Never change, mate. Never change.
Yeah, it will never change. So my little
my little um channel was just basically
to spread awareness.
I don't think I was any I was doing
anything wrong doing that. Was I?
All I was doing is like spreading awareness.
But then you got to watch out for the other guys.
I'm a kind, isn't it?
I'm just like spreading awareness,
Greasy. I don't think there's anything
wrong with spreading awareness.
Is there anything wrong with spreading awareness? No.
taking a baby away from its mama.
Where's the one with my hat on there? I
think I deleted it. So, I had to Yeah.
Yeah, they're just not interested in
this country. Cory,
how's it going to change?
It will never change, mate. Never change.
Never change, mate. Never change.
How's it going to change?
Yeah, it's depressing in that. Oh [ __ ]
Yeah, it will never change.
I'm looking for that change. Now I need
to make another [ __ ] account now
because of these stalkers
[ __ ] trying to call me a m. These
people are the masers sat on YouTube
every day doing what they do cuz they
ain't got a life. I'm off tomorrow for
like a week or two. So
yeah, these people can't get off of
YouTube. Cory, you see they can't get
off of YouTube. It's all they have.
I've proven that many times. >> Yeah.
They're repeating themselves again. Repeating.
Yeah. Hey, look. Whenever you go on Lord J,
it's just same repeating people.
Same repeating bully victims. They ain't
got a life. Sorry, lad. This is why I
don't go on here anymore, bro.
I know you miss me. I know you love me,
bro. I know you love me, but sorry, man.
These people are stalkers.
Yeah, I know what you mean, bro. Yeah,
they're actually stalkers, lad.
There actually are stalkers on here.
This is why I don't bother with this
anymore. Um, Cory, lad. You know,
this is why I don't bother with it anymore. They're stalkers.
They never stop. They're stalkers, lad.
It's mad, man. Is it? Yeah. I'm off
tomorrow anyways. Stay.
They're just weirdos. They're just
little bully victims. If they weren't,
they wouldn't be on YouTube every day
doing what they do. They're just people
that have been bullied in life. You
understand that? They're just people
that have been bullied their whole life.
sat there waiting for their little 400 pound benefits.
You know what I mean, lad? Yeah.
Right. I'm going to join. Yeah.
And I'm going to tell you exactly what's
going to happen. Yeah. I'm going to try
and call this
L J. All right.
and not RJ just smoke your be out. I'm
going to join the hangouts and what's
exactly what they're going to do?
They're going to talk over me. If they
let me in, they're going to talk over
me. They're going to shout over me and
then they're going to um kick me. Shout
over me and ask me questions. They do
the same [ __ ] It's the same atmosphere
on here. This is why you don't see me on here, bro. Look, Link,
you people don't ruin no one, lad.
You people don't ruin no one. You're
just pathetic. So, put the link up.
Let me let me own these people, bro.
Yeah. No talking over people. Let's
actually meet today cuz you all say that
people are not about it.
Listen listen, let me join. Anyways, I'm
going to say to them, right, all of you
people, why don't you all come and join
the hangouts? You all come on here for
years and years and years. You got more
followers than me. Uh, you can't show
your face, bro,
because you're all [ __ ] fat ugly
virgins. What? I'm going to own them.
Yeah. Well, I'm going to own them, bro.
No shouting, no nothing. He's not
putting the link up. That's it, bro.
I'm going to own them, bro. Watch.
Right. Go and Lord J.
One second, bro. I'm going to come back.
One sec. Go ahead.
That is exactly why I don't join. I told
you exactly what they would do, bro.
That is exactly why I don't join. Same
atmosphere, same thing. I told you what
they was going to do before they even
done it, bro. They just shout over you
and talk over you and change. And that's
exactly why I don't come on here
anymore. And people miss me while I'm
gone. And that's exactly why I don't
come on here anymore. Every single time
I try to meet, they all change the
subject. They all shout over me every
single time. They do it all the time.
That's why I don't join. This is why I
don't bother anymore.
Right. Should we try one more time? see
if the Milton Kees boy is going to meet
anyone today. We'll try one more time
and then if that's not going to work
then I'll come back.
They're going to do it again. We'll try
one more time. Huh?