Bro, they got proper [ __ ] owned it, man.
Got proper destroyed. He led I destroyed
all of them, bro.
They got [ __ ] ruined, mate. Like,
even though Yeah, they're trying to
[ __ ] like start with me, bro. They
got owned, bro. Everything I said, they
didn't really have anything to say back.
Was it eperoids or something? These
people got a bro. Yeah, they tried to
all stick up for each other. They got
bullied, mate. But they got they got literally
Yeah, they got boyed off, lad.
They got [ __ ] boyed off. And then
that Jesse tried coming in, bro. Why is
he talking? I told him to come to London
next week. They got owned, bro. They got
only that said, "Bro, you're 41. You're
skinn. You got no friends, bro. He's an
old man, bro. He's about to have a
[ __ ] heart attack. Why am I Why am I
argue with a [ __ ] old man?"
You know what I'm saying, bro? This is
what I mean though, with these people,
bro. Like, it's just the same [ __ ] with
them every time. The sad little [ __ ]
little virgins. It's the same [ __ ] with
them low lives every time, bro. I
shouldn't have really joined to be honest. But
bro, he must have used the word skint
about 10 times yet. And I asked him to
show money and he couldn't even do it.
That's what I mean, bro. Like this. They
just Bro, honestly, bro, they're not
even worth entertaining, lad.
Yeah, man. They're not even worth
entertaining, bro. They got bodied. I
just bullied them, bro. You have to
shout cuz they talk over you.
that Lord is the skintest
bastard ever. And listen, hold on a
minute. You're saying that people come
on my chat. Yeah.
And they take the piss out of me, bro.
You think I don't know that? Yeah. It's
called a wind up. Obviously, they're
taking the piss, bro. Of course. Well,
what is your followers doing, bro? How
many times have you been to different
cities in England? And how many times do
these people meet you? They never meet
you. So, what are they doing to you
then, bro? What are they doing to you?
And what are they doing to you?
You know what I'm saying? And what are
they doing to you when you come to all
of these places? They don't meet you,
lad. They don't meet you.
No, I'm not triggered at all. You people
are triggered. That's why you come on
YouTube every day self-projecting
because you are triggered. Triggered
little virgin low lives. I told you all
about your little virgin selves. You all
are. You all are triggered.
Of course, mate. You're all triggered
yourselves. You little virgins. That's
why you come on YouTube every day, you
[ __ ] idiots. All triggered to the
eyeballs every day.
They're [ __ ] fat ugly mongos, bro.
Yeah. Do you like it, bro? I whoop their
ass in it. Like, whoop them, man.
[ __ ] an old man with a bad back.
goes on like he's got all this money,
bro. He ain't got no money, mate.
He gets about honestly
probably gets about £400 a month.
He pro they probably get like £400 a
month lad. I told him come to London
next week. I'll meet you bro with you
and your kid.
And I was actually bringing his kid up
cuz I was basically saying that your
child wants to look at you and your
followers and not want to end up like
that when they're when they're 20 when
they're 40. You know what I'm saying?
When they're [ __ ] 40 odd years of
age. They don't want to be like you
people. [ __ ] they are losers. You
know them people on that chat, bro.
Yeah. They are the biggest losers that
you'll ever come across. What do these
people do? Sit online every day calling
people that they don't know cuz they're
fat ugly mongos. They need entertainment
on YouTube, bro. Cuz they ain't got a
life. Without this, bro, then they'd
have no entertainment at all.
You know what I mean, bro?
That's what I should have said to him as
well. You're saying that my followers
take the piss out of me. Okay. They take
the piss out of me. Okay. And your
followers don't even meet you when you
go to their location. So what about that then?
Cuz they've all got anxiety. They've all
got social anxiety. Do you understand?
You know what I mean, lad?
But yeah, I'll be off here tomorrow
anyways, lad. So don't expect me back for
like a little while, lad.
It's just the same [ __ ] every time, is it?
And they don't let you talk. That's
another thing. They don't actually let
you talk. They don't do question by
question format because you're I'm too
intelligent for them,
you know. So, and then you and I was
going to say before you bring up the
like Prime thing, where was Prime last
week, two weeks ago when he was being
called out? Uh uh uh where was he? When
I was actually in his city and I was
giving him the chance to move me from
his city. Where was he? Where was he?
Oh, so you can't even use that anymore,
can you, bro? Cuz he actually got
violated in his own city. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, he's with his family. Oh, that's the
excuse, wasn't it? Yeah. This is why I
don't bother with these people, lad.
They're just self-reflectors
cuz they they say something. Yeah. You
try to end a conversation. You try to
end a conversation. Yeah.
And then they just
like they can't do it. You're skin.
Okay, I'm skin. Show me money. Oh, I got
money. Same [ __ ]
You can't have like a a conversation
with them. You can't have um an
intelligent conversation with them or anything. But
that's why it's [ __ ] pointless, man.
You just end up shouting over me, man.
Annoying as [ __ ]
He says that he's got all of this money,
bro. But you know that LJ is the
skinnest person. He's just like nons.
They're all skin.
They really, really are all skin.
They really, really, really are. Bad, bro.
Bad is it? This is, like I said, bro,
this is why you don't see me on there much. Yeah, man.
Then they're stalking like channels and
[ __ ] It's [ __ ]
It's mad, is it?
SW Come on, lad. SW Come on, mate. Yeah.
It's [ __ ] low lives, isn't it, bro?
On here. [ __ ] low lives.
And I said to the kids, "Yeah, you can
say what you want, but listen, bro. Your
dad got offered to come here next week,
and he ain't about it. So you can say
whatever you want, but your father
got offered to come here with you next
week, and he shot it.
These little [ __ ] bongos. I shouldn't
even be on here with these [ __ ]
spats, bro. That's the thing. You come
with it for a while. Yeah. Just chilling
that." Yeah. And you get dragged into
the same thing with these mongos because
they're so [ __ ] disabled.
Yeah, I'm already Yeah, really? How did
I do that then? Really? How did I do
that? I literally owned you and you kept
talking over me. Yeah, you saw me
running. Was I running two weeks ago
when Prime weren't meeting me in
Birmingham? Yeah. Was I running then?
Yeah. Was I running when I was in
Birmingham two weeks ago? And we was
calling every [ __ ] out. Yeah. Yeah. Was
I Was I running then as well? Okay, man. Yeah. Listen,
you you we let me let me let me tell you
something, bro. You we we your spastics.
You all low life fat, ugly skin mongos
that can't get off of YouTube. Let me
rip into you right here, right now. You
little sad little disabled people. You
ain't got a life. You all muners sat
there on your little benefit money,
disabled to [ __ ] every day doing what
you do cuz you're all a bunch of [ __ ]
sorry ass 40year-old little muners.
That's what you people are. Sorry ass 40
year olds losers. That's literally what
you are. Lonely, fat, ugly, rejected
little losers. And that's why you can't
get off of YouTube. You bully
yourselves. Listen, mate. You people in
your 40s, you got no friends, no life.
Your family hate you. You're all ugly.
That's why you come on YouTube every
day. You're all skint ugly little
victims. And you can't meet anyone cuz
every single time you people get called
out, you don't do nothing. You're
nothing but skint ugly little alcoholic
little bullied little muners. You say
you bully me. Okay, come meet me right
now then. Yes, Lona. Okay, Lona. Come
and meet me right now then, you little
spacker. Come and meet me right now
then, you little [ __ ] Okay, come in
the hangouts then, you little skint
bastard. You little virgin. Go and suck
your mro. Listen, you people have been
on here for years and years and years.
You've never had women. You've never had
money cuz you're all skint. You're all
ugly. You're all lonely. You got no
life. You got no balls. You can't come
on anyone's door because you're all
[ __ ] ugly moners, spasticated little
bully victims. And I love it. Yeah. I
love the fact that you can't do nothing
to me. You lonely, ugly, skinned people
get laughed at every day, bro. When you
people come on YouTube every day
embarrassing yourselves and getting
bullied. I love it. I love it when I see
you on YouTube and you can't get off it.
I love seeing you people pipe your life
away with no money and no misses. I love
it. And I also love the fact that you
know where I live, but you still do
nothing. It gives me a boner. I love
seeing you little losers. I love seeing
what I don't want to end up like. ending
up like you little 40 year old lonely
skinned people that ain't got a life. No
one wants to end up like you spastics,
bro. You people might as well you people
might as well be dead. You are what I
don't want to end up like in my [ __ ]
40s all alone scared to go on someone's
door. You're what I don't want to be
like. I don't want to be like you
40year-old losers on YouTube. Thinking
about it, Cory, bro. How old are we,
lad? We're in our 20ies, bro. We're in
our 20ies. These people in their 40s,
they're all old, ugly, lonely people in
their 40s, bro. I love it, man. They're
all lonely little 40-year-old fat ugly
people. I love seeing them on YouTube
cuz it shows they got nothing. Every
single time these little loners come on
here and self project, I love it. I love
seeing them embarrass themselves talking
about themselves. Come on, bro. Keep
calling yourself a loner. I love seeing
you bullied 40year-olds. I love it. I
love seeing you little bullied
40-year-old loners. Yes, you are a
loner. Yes, you are. Keep talking about
yourself. You're a loner. You're ugly.
You're stint. You can't meet me. You're
in your 40s. Yes, you are. Keep typing
about yourself. I'm not even going to
block you. I'm going to let you keep
embarrassing yourself and I'm just going
to keep playing Franklin now. Yeah, you
keep talking about yourself, Lona. Yeah,
keep embarrassing yourself. I'm not even
I'm not even going to, bro, Cory. I'm
not even going to kick them. I'm going
to let these people keep embarrassing
themselves. I'm going to let these 40
year olds keep embarrassing themselves
and showing themselves up. I'm not even
going to kick it. I'm going to let them
keep embarrassing themselves behind the
keyboard. Let these little monties keep
embarrassing themselves. I love it. Let
them keep talking about themselves.
Anyways, Cory, uh, what are you up to
today, bro? I need to go to the [ __ ]
gym tomorrow, lad.
Yeah, I need to go to the gym tomorrow,
man. Hopefully it's not too hot. Hopefully,
bro, I need to get on that grind again,
bro. I actually need to get on that
grind again, lad. You know, I was making
like some serious gains. Yeah, I'm like
I said, bro, I'm ignoring these people
now. I'm going to let them keep
embarrassing themselves. I'm going to
let them keep wasting their life
projecting and embarrassing themselves.
Doesn't it bother me, lad? I'm going to
let them keep embarrassing themselves.
Bro, they can't even leave their house,
Cory, lad. I'm just going to let them
keep embarrassing themselves.
Just let them keep showing themselves up on YouTube.
Yeah, bro. I need to um made them games
again, Cory. Lad. Yeah, man.
Let these people keep embarrassing
themselves every day. Uh yeah,
no Steven hour today.
>> Oh [ __ ] What's up?
Do you have any nieces and nephews?
Do you have any nieces and nephews, bro?
Do you have any like nieces and nephews?
Not not in a weird way, bro, but do you
have any nieces and nephews?
I'm saying if if you do, then what you
want to do is
I wouldn't say bring them on this
community, but you need to show them
these people what they don't want to end
up like in their 40s and 50s. is they
don't want to end up like these ugly
people on YouTube. This is a prime
example of what you don't want to end up
like at these people's age. I'm
thinking, bro, we're we're in our 20s,
Cory. Well, you maybe just got out your
20s, bro. We're in our 20s, bro. We're
good-looking. We got more money than
these people. They're sat there
projecting every day. They're wasting
their life away, bro. Embarrassing
themselves. They're literally on YouTube
every day embarrassing themselves.
That's why I don't block them. I lead
them to it.
I let these people just embarrass
themselves and show them up. Show themselves up
cuz all they do is talk about themselves.
Saying that they probably won't get
bored, mate. I look like a Turkish down
syndrome. Oh, that's nice, bro. Coming
from somebody that that's scared to show
their face, that means a lot, bro. That
means that means a lot, bro. Coming from
somebody that's probably a bold, ugly,
white, pasty [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I know, man. That means a
lot coming from somebody that's scared
to show their face.
Yeah. Yeah. It means a lot, bro.
But again, I'm not the one scared to
show my face. You are. And that speaks
volumes, lad. That speaks volumes.
One second. Oh [ __ ] I need to call someone.
I was talking to someone.
No, no, no.
You people still embarrassing
yourselves. You're not bored yet? Jesus Christ.
You're not bored yet. You little selftor. is
No, no, no, no.
You little Mont is still typing. Yeah,
right. 5% now. Yeah, it's fine, bro. What's that?
Sorry about that, man.
I was saying to Monty, come on here and
he don't want to come on here anymore. I
don't blame him, bro. I shouldn't even
be telling him about YouTube. I
shouldn't even be telling him about you, Mongos.
about you [ __ ] mongos
to be honest with you, man. Yeah,
I'm trying to sort myself out. Yeah,
to be honest, I I shouldn't even be on
here to be honest. They are [ __ ]
mongos on here. They actually are, mate.
Yeah, it's right 100%. What am I doing, mate?
Yeah, bro. Stop talking about yourself,
man. Stop calling yourself a [ __ ]
virgin [ __ ] It's not nice to talk
about yourself like that, bro. You're
making me feel bad.
Stop talking about yourselves. Because
thing is, right, like I said before, you
are the ones that sat on YouTube every
day of your lives. Not me. You're the
ones that are sat on YouTube every day
of your lives. Can't get off of YouTube
cuz you ain't got nothing. Not me, mate.
So if I was you, I would just stop
talking about myself. If I was you
people, stop talking about yourselves
like that. Stop bullying yourselves.
Stop bullying yourselves every day. Should
you not do you not get bored about that
talking about yourselves?
Do you not get bored of talking about yourselves, man? [ __ ] hell.
Jesus Christ. I feel sorry for you
little bully victims.
Yeah, you was rooting for me. I own
them. I own every single one of them.
I've shown more money than you. Show
more women than you. I beat all of you.
I got nothing left to be on here for.
You know, I'm not on YouTube every day
like you little bongos. Can't get off
it. I'm going to show you people from
tomorrow what you little [ __ ] virgins
can't do. And that's get off of YouTube.
YouTube's all you got. I'm gonna prove
it to most. But you you fat ugly people
can't get off it. Can I ask you a question? Right.
Why the [ __ ] are you people on YouTube
every day if you got all this money and
you got all these friends?
Yeah. Bye-bye. Bye-bye. Enough. Yeah, man.
Talking about yourselves. Banger barking
up the wrong tree. Yeah, for real, man.
Yeah, I just said to Monty, yeah,
whenever something goes wrong again,
just don't come crying to me. Yo, Yeah, man.
I just told Monty basically.
How could you tell me to [ __ ] grow up
when you're the one that was crying over
someone you [ __ ] barely even knew?
You know, like you can't really tell me
to [ __ ] up, can you?
How the [ __ ] did it almost [ __ ] your
relationship up? What relationship, bro?
You weren't even with them. What?
So you're blaming me for you and Natalie?
How how are you going to try and blame
me for me? How the cold approaching
almost [ __ ] you and that you wasn't
even with her. What the [ __ ] bro?
How the [ __ ] is he going to try and
blame me for that?
That is a madness, bro.
When you have pe Oh, sing over women
again. Why is there so many simps? When
you have people stalking women, that's
[ __ ] up. That's PJ behavior. Wow.
Why do they defend women so much on
this? I'm just reading this.
The only thing P's up to is saying
everyone is old. He's almost 30. I'm
nowhere near 30 and I've got a better
life than any of you. He's absolutely
ski. Probably got 2K max to his name.
2K. If I had 2K to my name, that's more
than what you would ever have. This is
what I mean with this community, bro.
But at the end of the day, you know, Monty,
don't [ __ ] try and blame me for Natalie
about how that almost [ __ ] up your
relationship. Well, you weren't in a
relationship. What the [ __ ]
Like, I get the whole YouTube thing, but
you can't blame me, bro. What the [ __ ]
This is why I don't bother with people. Madness. The madness.
But I get the YouTube thing, boy. But like
you don't. Yeah. And like I get the
YouTube thing, but [ __ ] him, bro. I'm
done with Monty, bro.
Why? What, bro? Why is there so many
simps like on that L J channel and even
like Virgin Boy?
Like, why is there so many simps?
Like, I don't I don't understand why
there's so many simps, right?
It's Yeah, I deleted all the cold
approaching videos cuz I don't want you
[ __ ] mongos [ __ ] following me.
Yeah, maybe that's why cuz I don't want
you [ __ ] ugly people following me and
you people know who you are. So yeah, I
deleted it. Yeah.
Uh no, most people do not have a
girlfriend. Yeah, surprise surprise.
Skint Robbly conked it. Bro, you're
still repeating to have all the quins
code on his secret channel. Why delete
them? Because I don't want because I'm
making a new channel. I don't want you
[ __ ] mongos [ __ ] following me
around. Made up statistics over there. I
don't care what Google says. If a woman
has a boyfriend, do I I care, [ __ ] And
why are you even writing stuff, bro?
You're with a [ __ ] [ __ ] You're
with a the wolf. You're still a [ __ ]
virgin. Why are you butting your rat
face in people's business? You're a
virgin. You're with a disabled girl.
You're a disa. You're with a disabled
girl. Why are you defending women? Why
are you even talking about this? You
should be hating women. They don't want
you. Just like Britney didn't [ __ ] want you.
And you're defending them. Yet you're
with a disabled girl. You know what's
worse, bro, than probably being single
and being a virgin is being stuck with a
disabled girl. I'd [ __ ] I' I'd be
[ __ ] raging. I'd be a [ __ ] raging
incel if I was stuck with a disabled
girl. The last thing I would be doing is
defending women like these. There's so
many simps. I swear to God, there's so
many simps, bro.
And then you're talking about other
people. I'm not having this
conversation. And you are a loser, you
little [ __ ] You're the one that
runs to the police, you [ __ ] skinny
little rat loser. Yeah. You [ __ ] ugly
[ __ ] with your disabled girlfriend.
Yeah, you skint disabled benefits [ __ ]
bro. Like, stop writing your stupid
little videos. Remember, you was the one
that was running to the police, scared
to leave your house with your ugly girlfriend.
With your ugly dwarf girlfriend that
can't talk. Yeah, you were scared to
leave your house, you loser. You little
tent loser. Don't [ __ ] start [ __ ]
writing [ __ ] [ __ ] about me with your
[ __ ] girlfriend and your autism. You
understand, bro? Cuz let's not get it
twisted. You understand? You are the
biggest [ __ ] loser. Yeah. You suck
your dad's dick for a bit of money.
Yeah. And then you're showing your
benefit money off like you got money
when we all know you in a bed sit with
no bed. You have You don't even have a
penny a pot to piss in your skin. Look
at what you wear. You [ __ ] Do you
think I You You could pay me, bro, to be
going around rolling in some trampy
clothes with some greasy [ __ ] hair
like you. You understand?
You understand, bro? And then you got
[ __ ] bro. [ __ ] Monty, bro. Trying to
say, "Oh, that almost [ __ ] up my [ __ ] relationship." You know,
and stop writing this [ __ ] you [ __ ]
skinny [ __ ] lanky loser behind your
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] You understand?
With your ugly rat face, with your
rodent face, your pig face, bro, you
ugly [ __ ] with your [ __ ] girlfriend.
I mean, if bro, no one would be talking
about [ __ ] what I know and me not
[ __ ] meet them.
And then you got him trying to [ __ ]
blame me for he's [ __ ] He said, "Oh,
me got going cold approaching with you
almost [ __ ] up my relationship." Hold
on. What relationship? You wasn't in a relationship.
And then we got this [ __ ] Kent virgin
skint boy with his [ __ ] disabled
girlfriend. The Kent wanker that sucks
his dad's dick. [ __ ] who I actually
met because of [ __ ] Monty. You know,
I should be having a [ __ ] go at Monty
meeting this [ __ ] lanky virgin
through [ __ ] him. You know,
you know what I mean, bro? What the
[ __ ] You know what he's trying to say,
Grezy? Yeah. I said I had to listen to
you [ __ ] crying and you're telling me
to grow up. Bully victim. You people are
the bully victims. You get bullied every
day. You are the muners. I'm better
looking than all of you. That's why you
can't show your faces cuz you are them
runters. You said that right. And do you
know what he's trying to say to me? He's
trying to tell me to grow up because I'm
Cuz I told him to come on [ __ ] YouTube. You know,
I said to him, "Bob, you was the one
crying over someone at 35 years of
[ __ ] age. Don't come running to me
when it goes when it goes [ __ ] up
again." I just told him, "Don't come
running to me again." Simple.
Simple, bro. [ __ ] him, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. And I'm recording that as well. One sec. You
You know what I'm saying, bro? You're
the one who's a [ __ ] loser. You lanky
[ __ ] You ain't even got a bed, you
[ __ ] virgin. That shitty [ __ ]
virgin thing, bro. You and that little
[ __ ] virgin [ __ ] in Kent. Not even
being able to get your rocks off. You
know why I'm saying that? You're a madness, bro.
>> Sat in that little [ __ ] hole in Kent
being a virgin all your life at 31. [ __ ]
out of here, bro. You're a [ __ ]
[ __ ] sucking your dad's dick for an
extra money, but still being a virgin at
31. You know what I'm saying, bro? [ __ ]
him anyways, lad. And [ __ ] Monty as well
cuz he actually got me back on it last week.
So you get me back on it and you [ __ ] run away
just like you introduced me to that
[ __ ] virgin in a [ __ ] I Kent. You
know what I'm saying, bro? You don't see
me [ __ ] saying all of this [ __ ]
Think about it. I would have met that
lanky [ __ ] loser. that [ __ ] lanky
shitty virgin loser if it wasn't for him.
You understand, bro?
[ __ ] should show me a bit more
respect. What the [ __ ] Bad, bro. Madness.
Is this the [ __ ] thanks I get?
We got some [ __ ] Yeah, I'm done with
him anyways. No, I'm not doctoring, bro.
[ __ ] him anyways, bro.
And then we got this stupid little
[ __ ] lan. I can't be bothered, man. I
just said to him, "Just don't come
running back to me." Basically, I can't be asked.
We got that [ __ ] loser in tent
sucking his dad dick for an extra bit of
money. Sucking his disabled dad dick.
[ __ ] you know what I mean?
for an extra bit of [ __ ] benefit
money [ __ ] writing [ __ ] on YouTube.
You got someone that [ __ ] betrays
you. [ __ ] [ __ ] him, bro.
Yeah. Anyways, I'm done with him, bro.
You should have kept me blocked, bro.
You're not going to keep me blocked
because you know once you [ __ ] off,
you're not going to have anyone else.
That's why he unblocked me. Know what I
mean, bro? That's why he unblocked me.
That's why he just unblocked me cuz he
knows deep down, you know.
No, I'm not going to own him, bro. Do
you know why I'm not going to do any of
that [ __ ] Because I don't want to be
like someone that didn't do anything
when I was face to face with them and
then start doing it now. They're not
here. I'm not like that, bro. I'm not
coward like that. I'm not like that
[ __ ] Kent Virgin with a rat face, the
ugly face. I'm not like that, [ __ ] You
know what I mean? I'm not going to start
saying stuff now. If I want to meet him,
I'll just say meet me.
But I'm not I'm not doing that, bro.
That's cowardly, bro. That's what the
virgin does. You understand? That's what
the virgin does.
That [ __ ] Kent virgin does.
You know, I particularly didn't really
want to come back on here to be honest
with you, bro. But he kind of got me
back on here.
You know what I'm saying? And then what
he's he's telling me to grow up. How is
he telling me to grow up when he's the one [ __ ]
when he's the one crying over [ __ ] Natalie?
You know what I mean? Like he was the
one crying over Natalie
and then he's saying I need to grow up
and he's like 35.
Yeah, I never and and oh, I'm the one
that got his kids strip searched. Oh,
I'm the one that done this when I
didn't. I got blamed for all of this
[ __ ] bro. But who's the one that
went to Birmingham to go and see him
when he was crying?
Who was the one? Cuz it weren't Haley.
It wasn't [ __ ] his friends in
Manchester. It wasn't [ __ ] any of his
friends on here.
You understand? It weren't [ __ ]
Virgin Boy and Kent who he [ __ ]
introduced me to.
Do you know what I mean?
[ __ ] cringe cold approach. Listen
here, virgin boy with a rap face. Never
in my life have I ever dated a disabled
girl. And I never will. Yeah, I never
ever will date disabled like you. If I
was you, mate, I would be hating women.
The fact that I'm still a virgin, the
fact that Peter Belly's had more women
than you, the fact that you're stuck
with a disabled [ __ ] that can barely
talk. You should be hating women, mate.
You know what I'm saying?
I would be hating women if I was stuck
with a disabled person.
You know, you can't even approach you
[ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] [ __ ]
you know, with your [ __ ] string of
piss [ __ ] ugly body, with your ugly
face, with your ugly arms [ __ ]
talking all of this madness. But you
weren't saying nothing when your [ __ ]
when your dad when your [ __ ] stepdad
had you up against a [ __ ] wall. You
weren't such a [ __ ] big man then, you
[ __ ] virgin. Was you? Was your big
man? You weren't a big man then when he
had you up against the [ __ ] wall and
had you screaming for your [ __ ] life,
you lanky [ __ ] Yeah. Why don't you show
everybody your arm? Show everybody your
arm that needs twisting back. Show
everybody your [ __ ] arm that needs
[ __ ] twisting back. Yeah. Show
everyone your arm. Go on. Go on. Don't
show everybody your [ __ ] arm. You
[ __ ] lanky [ __ ] Go on. You lanky no
muscle [ __ ] Show everyone your arms.
Show everybody your [ __ ] arm, bro.
They need snapping back into place. You
[ __ ] virgin [ __ ] Go on.
Go on, mate. Go on, you [ __ ] skin
virgin. Go on.
No, you can't. Can you, mate? I know
about your arm. I've seen your arm. Show
everybody your [ __ ] spasticated arm
that needs You know when I don't know
what exactly it was, but his arm, right?
You know when your arm gets I think it
was his hand by his arm. It needs
twisting back into place. His arm needs
twisting back into place. You know when
you get like an injury, he needs it
needs to be like twisted back. It's no
joke, bro. Ask him to show you his
[ __ ] arm. He's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
mate. He's sing. He's actually on these
channels singing, but he's with a
disabled girl and he's still a virgin.
[ __ ] bro. Think of how many [ __ ]
[ __ ] I've been with. And I'll never
be a s. Never.
Simp is not in my [ __ ] DNA, bro.
Maybe Monty [ __ ] simps.
Maybe Virgin Boy simps.
You know what I'm saying, bro? But that
ain't me, bro. That ain't in my DNA.
Cold approach might be in my DNA, but
that ain't in my DNA.
You [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] little bongo.
Look at who you're with, bro. That's why
you're stalking the women that I've been
with, cuz you're jealous. Yeah. Oh, I'm
happy. You're not no [ __ ] happy, bro.
You're sat there [ __ ] stalking all
the women I've been with, but yet you're
sing. You ain't been with [ __ ]
And all the people that you've you
you've met two times before, they're all
fat and ugly, and you're sat there
defending women. You sad sad bastard.
What do you mean? I don't like He talks,
bro. Listen, bro. Let me let me let me
tell you something. Yeah, Cory. Yeah,
I've had a big mouth in the past. Yeah.
And I've said some mad things in the
past, but bro, this guy has got a
disgusting mouth for somebody that's
such a little [ __ ] Yeah, I'm telling
you, bro. For somebody that is such a
lanky little [ __ ] that will not say
anything to anyone in real life, his
mouth is is like a toilet. You
understand, bro? Do you understand? He
is like a toilet. And in real life, bro,
listen listen, bro. Have I took some
L's? Yeah, I took some L's, bro. But
listen, here's the thing. I've met
people. I've defeated people on this website,
you know. I've actually defeated people
on here. You You just [ __ ] run your
mouth every [ __ ] day. Try to get
other people to do your [ __ ] dirty work.
You know what I'm saying about [ __ ]
about why delete them when we already
have them saved? Because I don't want
you follow me around, you [ __ ] bongo.
Which is why I blocked you on
everything, you [ __ ] [ __ ] And he's
like, "What a loser, bro. You are the
definition of a [ __ ] bro. I'm going to
end up doing a video on this [ __ ] You
know that, bro. You know that. I'm going
to do and when the if the police I'm
going to show them all the what this
[ __ ] stupid little lanky [ __ ] has
been doing. This string of piss. This
string of yellow [ __ ] piss.
Seriously, bro. I swear to [ __ ] God.
Yeah. Who the [ __ ] are you about I don't
care what Google says? Shut the [ __ ] up,
you little virgin. About you don't care
what Who the [ __ ] do you think you are?
You autistic [ __ ] Remember you was you
literally weren't saying nothing, love,
when you was scared to leave your house
[ __ ] yourself for two weeks. Yeah.
When you did not go to Laten Stone cuz
you were [ __ ] your pants for 2
weeks. Yeah. Don't come here saying you
don't care, you [ __ ] virgin. Who is
Bro, this this [ __ ] was [ __ ] himself
for [ __ ] two weeks. He wouldn't even
leave his house. Yeah. Does it does
everybody remember that? Do you know
what I'm saying? This virgin was
[ __ ] it until the coastal was clear. >> Yeah.
[ __ ] little [ __ ] bro.
[ __ ] obsessed. Why are you so
obsessed, bro? You're with a disabled [ __ ]
You're with a [ __ ] disabled girl that
don't give you sex. What the [ __ ] do you
care what I do, you little [ __ ] What
the [ __ ] do you care what I do?
You're with a disabled girl that doesn't
give you no sex. Shouldn't you be
worried about your [ __ ] self?
I would be worried about my [ __ ] self
if I was [ __ ] you, mate.
Why is he talking about boyfriends and
not boyfriends? He's a [ __ ] absolute
[ __ ] isn't he?
And also when he's saying that he's most
of his friends, what did he say? He says
he says most of his
and most of his male friends have a
girlfriend. That's not true. Bro, I have
got so many friends that are single. So,
but well to be honest with you, probably
most of your male friends are in a
relationship with other disabled people
like you. So, say that you actually
could be telling the truth there. Yeah.
Because they probably play on disabled
youngans like what you do. That's
probably why they have got a girlfriend
to be honest with you.
Yeah. Do you know what I'm saying, bro?
So, actually, yeah, they probably do cuz
they probably prey on [ __ ] disabled
people like you do.
Why is he obsessed?
[ __ ] you know what I mean? Why Why is
he so obsessed, bro? [ __ ] You know
what I mean?
Like literally most people are single.
Most people are single. Most of the
people I know are single. I know
bartenders. I know chefs. I know
tenants. I know people. I know normal people, bro.
I know a lot of people in different
cities and guess what? Most of them are
single with all different kinds of
personalities and all different kinds
of, you know, I mean, I know people that
are in relationships. Yes, they are.
There are people in relationships, but
not most people. No, they're not.
You know what I'm saying? You're talking
out of your [ __ ] ass.
You know what I mean?
Like you're talking out of your bloody
ass, bro. Like Cory. Yeah, I know like
no other but I know so many people and
honestly most of them are single. Most
of them are are single, bro. You know,
you know what I'm saying? Most of them are single. Like for real,
why why does it matter anyways? Why are
you Why are you even talking about that?
We all know they lie. They got
boyfriends. Why? Why? Why does it
matter? Does it matter?
I mean, what what's what's
it why does the conversation drag on and
on and on and on and on and on and on
and on and on? Why does it drag on, bro?
Why does the conversation drag on and on
and on and on and on?
I mean, I don't know what your opinion
is, Lea. Like, I've got men that are
friends. I've got male friends. And
trust me, more of them are single than are single.
Yes, he was. Yes,
bro. Like I said, you can try and call
me what you want, all you want. You're the one
that can't show me. Okay. Okay. Listen,
bro. You would know what you'd have to
do to really trigger someone, but you
can't do it cuz you ain't got it. You
ain't got 10 grand, bro. Under the skin
one. You showing 14 grand. Well, can you
show me 10 grand then?
Mate, you're sat in a bed sit with not a
pot to piss him. Yet you coming on it.
You're the same as L J.
What? You're making fun out of me. What?
For what reason, bro?
cuz I said I had £1,300. Well, I'm a
realist. Yeah, I've got £1,300 or what?
I don't pretend I've got money like you and Laur
is that even if you had money, your
lives were equally [ __ ] Even if by the
very slim chance you had more money than me,
you know, and you don't have more money
than me, bro. And even even if you did,
bro, your lives would still be [ __ ]
You're doing everything but showing that
[ __ ] six grand, aren't you, Virgin
boy? 10 grand. Sorry.
Do you know what? I'm going to make it a
little easier for them. I'm going to ask
them to show me six. Do you know what?
I've come to the realization. Yeah. That
uh I've come to the realization, lad. I
don't have money, Peter. Well, Trevor,
I'm not going to pay attention to you
because I went to Middlesbrough and you
didn't show up. So,
I mean, you you shown yourself up there,
kid. You made me travel 5 hours to you
and you didn't even come out. So,
because I'm not going to get this 10
grand, I'm going to ask you to show six
grand and then you you know that's what
it is. There was no proof of that. Yes,
there was. Everybody saw the video. You
are all the same, aren't you, when you
get owned on here. Yes, there was proof
of that. I had done a video and
Middlesborough is a very small town and
you were still making excuses. Yes,
there was. There was a lot of proof of
that when I was in the shopping center.
Nice try, boy. See, the thing is Trevor
Dawson, you need to be very careful
because the thing is is that we know
that you live far away, bro.
Middlesbrough is [ __ ] long from
London. But the thing you got to
understand is that we're not all like
you. You understand? We're not all like
you, bro. Scared to leave our cities,
scared to leave our towns. So, you need
to be careful who you're [ __ ] with,
bro. Because we all seen you in middles,
bro. And you didn't come up. You didn't come out.
Come on, man.
I would lost a day in T-side, brother.
I've been all over the country. Up and
down Middlesbr. You didn't come out.
I'm going to do a video to this loser. Nothing. But
I'm trying to think, bro. Honestly,
Cory, I don't know about your friends,
bro, but most of the friends that I know,
they're all single.
They're all single, lad. All of the most
of the friends that I know are single.
I'm trying to go through my lists,
but I've got a better life than you will
ever have, mate. You're the old man.
You, bro, your lives are over. Your
lives are [ __ ]
But I'm looking at some people
and all the people that I know, most of
them are single. Anyways,
I'll be back, Roy.