I woke up with a [ __ ]
[ __ ] some mad news
yesterday. Some [ __ ] mad
news. Some dirty [ __ ] [ __ ] mushrooms. I
think I find these women so evil and so
hypocritical. That's what I find
them. So evil and so hypocritical.
Imagine that. I have to [ __ ] go to
bed think about it in the morning. Had
to wake up as well to do these
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying, bro?
[ __ ] pissed me off. I [ __ ] hated
my [ __ ] kids. Yeah, you don't know
what I felt like [ __ ] doing
yesterday. I felt like God madness, bro.
I swear to God, bro. I swear to
God. I said to man, I'm going to end up
doing what you're doing, bro. I swear
I'm going to end up doing that. I swear
to God, they're pissing me off. These
stupid [ __ ] women, I [ __ ] hate
them. Watch what I messaged them all
today. They're [ __ ] evil. discover
the earth. Funny funny how that funny
how that person's got it has no opinion
of what they've done to me and their
behavior towards me. Oh, as soon as you
say one bad thing, you're the villain.
You're the villain against Robin Hood.
Isn't that fat? Isn't that funny? But
they got no opinions of what they do to
you. Just like most people in these
[ __ ] nightclubs. [ __ ] off, you know?
[ __ ] off, you [ __ ] scum of the earth.
That's what they are. They're scum of
the earth. They man their kids. I hope
them man their kids get raped. I was
saying it yesterday as well. They were
pissing me off. I'm just lying in bed
[ __ ] chilling. You and your [ __ ]
stinky little kid. Yeah. And I [ __ ]
sent them a [ __ ] video of me getting
a [ __ ] [ __ ] as well. [ __ ] scumbag.
[ __ ] know what I'm saying? [ __ ]
mold. Took me [ __ ] ages to get a
[ __ ] sleep when I finally did. I woke up
[ __ ] so hypocritical. They're [ __ ]
dumb, bro. They are. They're so
hypocritical as well. You know,
hypocritical little [ __ ] try to sit on
the internet. Right. This is what makes
me laugh about these [ __ ] Yeah.
They try to sit on the internet, right,
giving you advice about dating, yet
they've had everything given to them on
a silver spoon. I've literally got a
spoon in my tea right now. And they've
been given a silver spoon lining towards
their mouth all their [ __ ] life. They
don't have to work for anything. They've
never had to work for themselves.
They've never had to improve themselves.
Yet, they know all of this [ __ ] about
dating. Yet they've never ever had to do
anything but have everything given to them, you
know, tried to give [ __ ] people advice, you
know. Keeping [ __ ] off. Suck my dick.
How about that one? Keep crying your
mug. How about that one for [ __ ] keep
crying your [ __ ] stupid little
mug? Do you know what I'm saying? [ __ ]
off. You've never had to There they've
never had to work in their life. They
they've had everything literally given
to them on a silver [ __ ] spoon. Just
think about how [ __ ] up it is, bro.
Think about how [ __ ] up the dating
game is as a as a woman you can go on a
date at with a filtered photo being a
solid four or five out of 10. You get
5,000 likes in an hour. [ __ ] off. Don't
[ __ ] try to give me [ __ ] advice, you [ __ ]
mug. I [ __ ] hate these women. I hope
they all get raped and acid in their
face. I hope all of them get raped and
they get acid attacked right up on their
nostrils. [ __ ] mugs. I swear to God,
bro. They're evil. They're evil [ __ ]
Horrible evil [ __ ] Hypocritical, devious,
evil, you know. And And here's another thing is
Yeah. Um, actions speak louder than
words. Actions speak a lot louder than
[ __ ] words, bro. Remember that.
I said, "Fuck you. [ __ ] your boyfriend,
mate." Yeah. If he wasn't dumb, he
wouldn't be doing a 9 to 5 [ __ ] job
like I would never have to do. You know
what I'm saying? [ __ ] off, you mug. You
know, so lucky there's laws in this
country, bro, cuz I would have done
something a long [ __ ] time ago. I
hate these [ __ ] women. I hate him. I
hate him with a
passion, you know. But unfortunately, we
can't all go out and do things like
Ant-Man because what happens? We end up
in prison and they get even more of a
laugh. I [ __ ] hate them. I hate
them. You understand? And and I you know
what I'm saying,
bro? I [ __ ] do. I hate them. They're
[ __ ] scum. Them and they're ugly
kids. They're [ __ ] ugly kids is to do
with [ __ ] them as well. I [ __ ]
hate them, bro. You
know, [ __ ] hate them little
hypocritical little [ __ ] Yeah. They'll
sit there, give you all this advice in
the world like they know about the
struggles when they don't know about the
struggles. Then all of a sudden, they're
in a relationship. Oh, but guess what?
They've never had to try. They've never
had to travel around the country. [ __ ]
off. [ __ ] right off, you [ __ ] bug.
You know, you don't know the abuse that
I was giving them yesterday, bro, on
this [ __ ] Reddit. [ __ ] off, you mug. You
know, you've been given everything on a
silver spoon for just existing. Imagine
that. Having a [ __ ] in between your
[ __ ] legs. You get everything given
to you for just existing. And you want
to try and give me advice. And you want
to try and tell me to keep trying. [ __ ] off. You
know, stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] You
know, [ __ ] hate him, bro. I [ __ ]
hate them. I absolutely hate them, bro.
You think I was trying [ __ ] when I said
I'm not going out for a month. I [ __ ]
hate them, bro. Watch what I'm going to
text these numbers today. I'm going to
text them some madness. I'm going to
send them my [ __ ] me get my dick
sucked. Watch. Watch, bro. You watch.
Yeah. Like I've got the [ __ ] numbers
to do it. [ __ ] them, bro.
Oh, you it doesn't matter. As a man, you
should respect a guy. How about you suck
my [ __ ] dick? How about they show a
bit of [ __ ] respect and sort their
[ __ ] attitude out, [ __ ] Why don't
you say something about
that? Why don't they sort their [ __ ]
attitude out the [ __ ] silly [ __ ]
before [ __ ] trying to tell people how
who they need respect for? [ __ ] off. You
know what I'm saying? [ __ ] right off,
mate. You need your [ __ ] mouth
washing out with [ __ ] washing up [ __ ] liquid.
And that's [ __ ] facts, bro. I [ __ ]
hate them little rape victim [ __ ] with their ugly
kids. You know what I'm
saying? [ __ ] hate them, bro. It
[ __ ] pissed me off. I had to go sleep
thinking about it, bro. As well, you're
going to sit there and give me [ __ ]
advice about how I need to do this. I
don't give a [ __ ] if you're in [ __ ]
New Zealand. I don't give a [ __ ] how you
need to do this. You need to do that one
month later. Oh, all of a sudden you're
in a relationship. I guess let me just I
bet you didn't have to travel the whole
world world. [ __ ] off you silly
[ __ ] You know, [ __ ] off you silly little
[ __ ] I hate them. I [ __ ] hate them.
You watch when I get this passport. I'm
[ __ ] out of here. Yeah. You watch
when I get this passport, bro. You watch
when I get this passport. I'm [ __ ]
out of here. Yeah, I [ __ ] mean it,
bro. [ __ ] this. If I end up seriously
[ __ ] doing something, it ain't a [ __ ] joke,
bro. [ __ ] doesn't matter who the [ __ ]
you really are, bro. Does it? You
know, you know what's so [ __ ] mad is
I should be given money for all of the
effort I've tried. £50,000, I'll take
it. Yeah. With the amount of effort I've
tried, I should be given money. I should
be given [ __ ] a golden medal and
[ __ ] 50 [ __ ] grand at
least. You know, you got these [ __ ]
[ __ ] on there trying to tell you that
you need to keep trying. [ __ ]
off. You know what I'm
saying? I [ __ ] hate them. I hope they
all get raped and acid attack them and
their kids. Literally, they man their
[ __ ] kids. I hate
them. I actually [ __ ] hate them, bro.
I swear to God, I hate them.
I'm always up early, mate. Sick of [ __ ]
women. I'm sick of them, bro. I went to
bed [ __ ] thinking about it with mood
swings and I woke up with mood swings. I
was so tempted to go out and do madness
last night, bro. I'm not even joking. I
was going to I was going to go and do
something, bro. I'm not even
joking. I finally fell asleep. I woke up
thinking about it again. These women are
just so hypocritical.
That's what I find with these women is
they'll sit there and they'll try to
give you advice on, oh, you need to do
this. Oh, you need to do that and keep
trying when you've tried everything and
then a month later they're the one
that's in a relationship because they
have had everything given to them on a
silver spoon. On a [ __ ] silver spoon
that I'm looking at right now, they've
had everything given to them on and
they're trying to tell me how I need to
keep trying, but they can get in and out
of relationships. [ __ ] off, man. Watch
when I get this [ __ ] passport. I've
got out of here. And I'm not coming
back. How about that one? I'm not coming
either. You know, I'm sick of them, bro.
I'm [ __ ] sick of them. I hate them.
Hate them. Do you not
understand? I went out last week cuz I
had to get my passport renewed. I had to
get my hair done.
Yeah. I hate them, bro. Even ones I've
not met, I hate
them. Trying to give you
advice like they know anything. trying
to tell you you need to change our
pictures on dating apps. Huh? Is that
mad when we put a filtered photo up of a
woman, she gets 5,000 likes? [ __ ] off.
Just admit it. The the dating the dating
game is rigged against ma men. End of
end off. End [ __ ]
off. You know what I said yesterday as
well? I said to this [ __ ] person in
Scotland, I feel like going out and
killing someone. And they said, oh, I
need mental help. Help. But they have no
opinions on what they do. They have no
opinions on the disrespectful things
that they do. They're only interested in
your ex your overexaggerated reaction.
They're not interested in anything that
they [ __ ] do, are they? You know,
they don't care about their attitude and
their piss taking. Nah, that's
completely fine. But then when you react
to it, [ __ ] off, man. Get out of it, you
[ __ ] Hate them, I do, bro. And yeah,
Travel, you can send letters to my
neighbors again. I hope all women get
raped and acid attacked them and their
kids raped acid in their face. Go send
posters on me, bro. I don't care.
Yeah, them and their [ __ ] kids on
their beak. Yeah, go send [ __ ]
posters of me, lad. I don't give a [ __ ]
You're not moving me out where I live. I
tell you that for [ __ ] nothing. Go
and do it again, bro. No one cares. I
love it. I get a boner. No, I'm just
pissed off with [ __ ] women. Nothing's happened, bro.
I just hate him, mate. I just [ __ ] him.
Passport. No, I'm off Thailand,
bro. I'm not trying to get this
passport. I shouldn't get this Saturday.
I'm going next month 100%. I'm looking
at this month. [ __ ] this. [ __ ] this for
a game of [ __ ] soldiers, mate. You
know, there's other benefits there as
well. I'm not having this, bro. I'm not
having this anymore. You know, don't
[ __ ] sit there on Reddit giving me
[ __ ] advice about women when you're
the one that's in a Isn't it funny how
these are the same women that can get in
and out of relationships, but they're
trying to give you advice. Never had to
struggle. Never had to work for
anything. When you're born with a [ __ ]
in between your legs, I don't think you
understand how life is on easy mode. You
don't have to work for anything. Get
everything given to you. You can get any
man just by existing. But they want to
sit there and give you
advice, bro. The only bad thing that
they have is having a period every month
and that stops when they're like in
their 40s. What the [ __ ] would they know
about working or [ __ ] keep trying?
What the [ __ ] would these little [ __ ] know about
anything? Nothing, mate.
Nothing. Yeah, they they because they're
they're white knights. Trouble. Do you
not understand? They're white knights.
We get them in London as well. They
don't have a bad word to say about
women, you know. They don't have a bad
word to say about [ __ ]
women. Yeah. That's what they're like,
bro. I I said to someone in Scotland,
"Yes, I feel like going out and killing
someone." Yeah. And then they were like,
"Oh, yeah, you need professional help."
"No, no." I said, "Oh, but you got no
opinion on what women do." You know, and
maybe white people feel like this. No,
you ain't got no opinion on that, do
you? [ __ ] idiot, mate. Listen, if
anyone went through half of what I went
through, they would be in jail by now
and they would kill themselves. Facts,
bro. They would kill themselves or kill
someone or done something like what
Antman done. They would not be sat here
on a table telling you the same
[ __ ] They would be in prison, bro. Or
they would be dead. They'd be dead.
They'd either kill themselves or they'd
be in prison. End the story. If anyone
went through half of what you went
through, somebody would end up doing
something. So, you can't be that
mentally ill, can you? And trust me,
they [ __ ] would have. Trust me, they
[ __ ] well would have. How do you
explain that one
then? Yeah, they're just they're just
scum. They're just [ __ ] scum of the
earth. They're just [ __ ] scum of the
earth. And and you know the thing that
annoys me, bro. I tell you the [ __ ] that
annoys me is how easy they have dating.
They have dating mode on easy. Annoys
me, bro. That even just that they they
can get any man they want, get in and
out of relationships, but then they want
to give you advice.
They want to give you advice, you
know. Yeah. And these people have never
been in your shoes. Isn't that madness?
They've never been in your [ __ ]
shoes, you know? Is that mad? They've
never been in your [ __ ]
shoes. I hate them. I do. I [ __ ] hate
them. I hate them. That's the nice ones.
Anyway, so I was telling that bad about this
yesterday. Yeah, just like you, Harry.
You'll be single for for the rest of
your life as
well. Yeah, you'll be single for the
rest of your
life. Yeah, you'll be you'll be single
for the rest of your life, too. the free
musketeers. Nothing. What is he saying?
He's in Thailand living
life. So, so what what do you expect me?
Yeah, you're saying something. But of
course you are. Of course you are.
That's why you're on YouTube every day.
So what my question is, Tro, what what
do you expect me to do? Go out every
single week spending
£300?£300 trying to meet someone? See,
I'll give you an example. This is I'll
tell you the difference between dating,
right? A woman has just got to go on a
dating app and get any man she wants.
She can say that they only want them for
sex, but that doesn't ring right because
there's loads of women and men that want
relationships. And she can jump on a
dating app and get any man she wants. As
a man, you literally have to go out
every week dealing with [ __ ] upon
[ __ ] upon [ __ ] up in attitude.
Make believe boyfriends, [ __ ] after
[ __ ] after [ __ ] after hundreds
after hundreds after hundreds just to be
in with a chance. And you wonder why
people are so bitter about the dating
game? You wonder why people are so
bitter about it? Listen, bro. You What
are you supposed to do? Go out every
week spending hundreds of pounds to be
in with a chance? Why do you think
people are so bitter? We know what we're
in for by the Tuesday.
Do not think you'd be asking women out
to hang out too soon. Um, stop being
stupid. I've shown my messages, bro.
Listen, whatever you say, I've tried it.
You you you might think I'm coming on
here being awkward, but I'm not. Yeah, I
got some messages. Um, they're not
interested in this country. It's like
what Ant-Man said. There's no trying to
analyze do this right, do that right,
it's this, it's that. They're not
interested in this country. End of. You
know, some people it take pe, you know,
unless you want to keep going out and
trying and trying and trying and trying
and hoping one day you get lucky. That's what it
is. Just these [ __ ] women. That's
what made me trigger. These [ __ ]
women. Obviously, I haven't gambled
since the football, so it's not that.
Yeah. But that's how it is. You know, it
annoys me how they can get anything that
they want when they want.
It's annoying, bro. And then these same
women that are giving you advice are the
same women that would never get with
you. Talking for a couple of months.
Hold on. I just read that. Talking for a
couple of months. You don't talk to a
woman for a couple of months before
asking them out. What the [ __ ] How are
you going to keep somebody entertained
for a couple of
months? But anyways, it it doesn't
matter. No matter how you conduct this
or what you look like. Yeah.
know. Yeah. You've also seen me not
asking him out the very next day as
well. You've also seen that as well as
as around how we seen it. Yeah. It's
just another excuse. Just like when you
used to say that I live with my
mom. Yeah. Just like when you say that I
live with my mom. Yeah. It's just
another excuse. Yeah. Remember that time
before? Oh, you live with your mom. You
live with mommy. That's why you can't
get a woman. Oh, mommy. And then when I
moved out, well, we're still having the
same problems. It's just another
excuse. Take things slow. You're too
fast. It's just another excuse. You
know, the problem with this day and age
is they don't have a bad word to [ __ ]
say about [ __ ]
women. Mate, you can be an attractive
man and you still won't get nothing.
You could be an attractive man with
money with decent clothes and you still
wouldn't get nothing. How's about that
one? You're still You could go You could
go to a club, bro. Yeah. And you could
get a,000 You could wear a,000 suit,
£1,000 Hugo boss suit all tailored and
you're still going to get I've got a
boyfriend. Unless you're like [ __ ]
seven foot and you're like [ __ ] 10
out of 10. their standards are
unrealistic. That's where the problem
stems from. The problem stems from
because of these simps on social media
inflating their ego, right?
Um yeah, it might be your negative
mindset. Nice try. You're not going to
get a reaction. We've already been over
that before. Yeah, nice try, buddy. I've
so and this and this is
exactly when people used to ask me why
do you put approaching videos on your
channel? Why do you put approach videos
um channel explain the girls who can't
get laid? Every girl can get laid. Every
single woman can get into a
relationship. Don't even try that. Don't
even [ __ ] try that. No, you're you're
negative because of your negative experiences.
You are negative because your neg your
negative experiences with women change you
negative. Round and round in circles we
go. There is no such thing as a woman
who can't get laid. Mate, I literally
put up a four out of 10 last year as a
woman on a dating app and it got 5,000
likes. Suck my [ __ ] dick about
there's a woman that can't get laid in
this in this country. There is no such
thing. There is no such woman in this
world that can't get [ __ ] laid, even
if she had Down syndrome. Stop talking
[ __ ] I come from the dating game. I
know these [ __ ] things. How many
experiments do you think I've done? [ __ ]
off. And you're negative because of
them. They're the ones that make you
negative. Their [ __ ] stinking
attitude and their arrogance. They're
the And and it's funny how you say, and
here's another thing. It's funny how you
try to say about Yeah. Yeah. You
definitely [ __ ] Okay. What about all of
the numbers that I messaged first and
they didn't reply in? What was the
excuse with that
one? What was the excuse with that one?
What was the excuse that one that time?
Because you seem to have no matter what
you do, people always make excuses for
them. So, I play along with
it. If someone with downs gets in the
relationship, that proves it's not a
right, I'm blocking it. I know what
you're trying to do and it's not going
to work. You're not getting a reaction.
Bye-bye. Um, yeah, you guarantee it.
Well, you guaranteed wrong because I've
got loads and loads of messages where
I've messaged first and they don't even
reply. So, stop talking [ __ ] out your
ass crack and stop making excuses for
women. It's embarrassing, mate. We're in
2020 [ __ ] fired now. You
know, listen. And you know what's so
funny, right, about people that talk
about attitude, you are probably too
been too full on Yep. It's always an
excuse, isn't it, Nibla? It's always the
man's fault. Yeah. It's always the man's
fault, is it? It can never be the woman.
You don't have a bad word to say about
women. It's never women, is it? And you
know what's so mad? Yeah. Here in
London, well, people say out of London,
they talk about how you've got a
negative attitude, mate. There's women
here that have got the most disgusting
attitude and they're very, very easy to find. You
know, they've got the most stinking
negative attitude out there and they
can't get off their phones, but men are
told they're negative. Double standards.
Double standards. They think by
defending women, women will get with it.
They think by defending women, women
will get with them. It's [ __ ]
embarrassing. All they do is simp. They
got a bad word to say about women.
Yeah. They just [ __ ] defend them.
It's [ __ ] embarrassing. All they do
is defend them. They ain't got a bad
word to say about him. It's [ __ ] embarrassing,
bro. You know what I'm saying, bro? They
ain't got a bad word to say about
them. It's [ __ ] It's a madness, isn't it? You
know, but yeah. Like, what are you
supposed to do? Go out every week and
spend 30 like
£250? No. Well, I'm talking about them.
Well, I'm talking about them. You can be
talking about me, but I'm [ __ ]
talking about them. So, yeah, you're
wasting your time. I'm talking about
them. So, you can be talking about me.
I'm talking about them. They're
horrible. I hope they all get raped.
Them and their kids.
Simple. So, them and their [ __ ]
kids. But on a real travel, that's what
you would have to do to get a date in
this country or get a woman in this
country. You would have to go out every
week. I'm not going out for a month. So,
I'm [ __ ] because I'm not going out for
a month. I'm not wasting any more money
in this country. I don't even have a
passport anyways. So, until like
Saturday, [ __ ] off. How about that
one? Go [ __ ] off. How about that? [ __ ] off, you mug. So,
yeah. Um, so what are you supposed to
do? Yeah. Well, no one's going to give
me a slap. Yeah. Yeah. Well, no one's
going to give me a slap. Let me ask you
this. If you go to Liverpool City
Center, how much do you spend in a night
out, Jay? Muhammad, how much do you
spend in a
night? How much do you spend in a night?
When you Liverpool City Center in
London, mate, you spend hundreds. So,
what am I supposed to do? Go out every
week spending hundreds. Tell me that's
fair. Tell me that's fair that I have to
go out every week getting my hair done, spending
hundreds. Yeah. Nice try, nibbler.
You're not going to get a reaction. This
is not Monty Man's channel. This is not
Timmy's channel. Stop making excuses for
women. You're not going to get a
reaction. 100. See, in London, you're
talking about say 2 250, right? So,
let's say for argument sake, right? You
go out, say for example, you go out,
right, every week, and you spend just
over 250. Bro, you're spending over a
grand a month. Imagine that, bro. You're
spending over a grand a month on
drinking. You know what I'm saying? What
is someone supposed to do that every
week to find someone? You see how it's
not fair? You understand what I'm
saying? You see how it's not
fair. You know the [ __ ] people have to
go through to get anything in this
country. It's disgusting and it's not
spoke about and I think it's wrong and I
think it does need to be spoken about.
It's not normal. It's not normal, bro.
It's not normal. All jokes aside, you
you can tell people that they need a
slap, whatever. You know they you know
and and the mad thing is that even when
you go out you still don't get
nothing. Yeah. I'm the problem why you
can't get women. Yeah. Okay. Good for
you simp go away. Yeah. Go away. And
these people trouble that say about oh
it's not women's fault. Ret these people
don't even leave their
house. These people don't even leave
their house bro. They don't know what
women are like. And if they do leave the
house, they probably live in some
[ __ ] Glasgow. These people don't live
in London. They don't know what women
are like in this society. They're scum.
They really, really are scum. I've just
explained to you what you have to do
every week. There's no mixing it up.
There is no nothing new, Harry. The only
thing you've got, the only thing you've
got is approaching, and that could be
anywhere. Dating apps and that's all
you've got or you go Thailand.
The only thing that you've got is
Thailand approaching. That could be
anywhere. Nightclubs or Thailand. That's
the only thing you've
got. That's the only thing you got,
bro. Anyways, I'm blocking you now. Bye-bye now,
[ __ ] Yeah, but you get what I mean.
You Yeah, but you get what I'm saying.
And also, the women that they probably
speak to are in their 40s, 50s. So these
women in their 40s and 50s are nicer
people. You come to London trying to
deal with women in their 20s, they're
[ __ ] mate. They are absolute [ __ ]
And French people as well. Go and do it,
bro. Go and do it. I'd love one of you
people to go and do it. But you've only
got approaching dating apps or leave
this country. That's all you
have. You can't go speed dating because
that's rigged against men.
Yeah, but mate, at least it's Yeah, but it's cheaper
there. It's cheaper there and you'd have
a better You know what I'm
saying? Yeah, but what I'm trying to say
to you, bro, well, in this country,
Okay. Okay. So, in this country, the
only thing you've got is dating apps and
approaching. That's all you got. And
none of them work. Well, approaching can
work, but you have to get extremely out this world
lucky. Yeah, I know that. Yeah, it is.
Yeah, exactly. It's 10 times cheaper. But you know,
so yeah, I know what you're saying. I'm
not denying that. But bro, it's not even
just about the women in Thailand. Better
weather. Gambling is illegal. So
wouldn't you rather be somewhere else than
here? You know what are you supposed to
do, bro? Go out on the street every day
approaching. You know, when I found that
19year-old, I was out approaching every day.
Yeah, but you're going to be in Thailand
for like a month, two months. So, but
yeah, I was approaching like three times
week. That's what And that's literally
what you have to do in this country.
It's disgusting, bro. It's disgusting. I
used to approach like Wednesday to
Saturday. I'm not even joking.
It's [ __ ] disgusting what people have
to go through in this country. It's
disgusting. You know, it is actually
vile, man. When they just get to get any
man they want. Look at this, bro. I
traveled all over the country and that
was basically for women. No one's
traveled. Yeah, no one has
traveled. I'm not going to run out of
money, though, Harry. I'm not going to
run out of money. But yeah, if I went
out every week, maybe I would run out of
money, you know?
I've got money. I've got more than
enough money. But if I went out every
week, probably in three weeks, I' I'd
probably be low. If I'm spending £300 every [ __ ]
week, if I'm spending £300 every [ __ ]
week, then eventually, mate, I I
probably would, like most people would.
No, I'm not going to run out of money
cuz I'd get paid when I'm out
there. You wouldn't run out of money.
You get flights like 500 quid indirect
flights. You wouldn't run out of money,
bro. once you get the flights out the
way. I just hate them. I just hate these
women. I hate the way the dating game
is. I hate I just hate
everything. But it's not even just about
the women, bro. England sucks for
different reasons. Gambling, women,
weather, government, everything's
backwards in England. It's not just the
women. You can stay for a couple of
months. My friend stayed for like 3
months. He's on for like 3 months. He
was there 3
months. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
You wouldn't go there, but it's
Something's got to be better than here,
bro. Something has got to be better than
here. Something has got to be better than here,
lad. I'm going to message all of them
numbers saying a load of [ __ ] bro. I
don't give a [ __ ] I don't
care. I hate
them. So, this is what we're dealing
with in this
country. This is what we're dealing
with. Next time I go out, I don't think
I'm going to try and get any
numbers. No, they won't grasp grass me
to who, bro. How many times have these
people tried stopping my money?
They wouldn't grasp me because they
wouldn't know when I'm going and they
wouldn't know where I was. They can't
grasp me for what, bro. You know, they
how many times you can cuz you send
letters to Thailand. You can do you
would know where I am. But that's what
I'm trying to say. You You
Bro, these people have tried, you
know, I'm probably just going to be in
bed today [ __ ] depressed.
Hope you people have a better day,
man. So, when I go out, when I go out
again, I can't go out for a month
now cuz I'm saving. [Music]
So, you know what I
mean? Maybe try pursuing on the spot.
Maybe. I don't think there's point of getting
numbers unless it's on the street.
But why should I have to keep doing
this, bro? Why should people have to
keep going out and doing this? I can't
do it for a month. I need to save money.
I've got travel plans. I'm supposed to
be going to the [ __ ] gym today. I
can't go out every
week. You know, it's [ __ ] disgusting
this country. You might as well, you
know what you need to do? You should
just give up and stick with escorts.
That's what you, you know, the best
thing you can do in your life, right, is
give up, go to the gym, and just travel,
bam, and just use escorts. That seems to
really be the only way you can find
happiness. Yeah, escorts are never going
to be the same, but bro, you're never
going to meet anyone, so what? It's
better than nothing, can
it? Well, I don't see any other other way
out. I don't really care about cream
pie. I only like [ __ ] I haven't
[ __ ] in months, bro. I just have
[ __ ] all the time. I don't even [ __ ]
them. I just get
[ __ ] Yeah, you'd have to go back there, is
it? But somewhere it's got to be better than
here. Yeah, you can't queen cream pie then,
but I don't really have I don't really
care about the sex.
I just care about the [ __ ] I don't
really care about
sex. And this woman who was trying to
give me advice, yet she's the one who's
got a boyfriend of a month. I said, "Fuck off,
mate." That's what I said. I said, "Fuck
off. Go suck your [ __ ] boyfriend's
dick rather than anyone else's, you
[ __ ] scumbag." And I was sending her
me getting a [ __ ] and
that. And then she's trying to say,
"You're barely traveled." I was like,
"Bro, I've been to France, Belgium. I've
been to the Netherlands. I've been
Scotland. I've been Wales. I've been all
over England. Just because you've been
to a few countries." Yeah. Doesn't mean
you've traveled the world. Barely
[ __ ] traveled, mate. I'm 27. Why do
you think we're doing [ __ ] this [ __ ]
year? [ __ ] off. You can't. So,
yeah. I can't even go to the cinema.
Well, to be fair, I never used to even
be able to escape it even when I went to
the cinema, to be fair. Cuz even when
you go to the cinema, there's always sex
scenes. So you can't even escape it in
the cinema most of the
time. Nothing comes out to the 28th. So
I'm just going to be sat here
bored. I'm just going to be sat here
bored like a dog for a whole month. Can't do
anything. Sucks, isn't
it? Yeah, it sucks. [ __ ]
it just be sat bing out my head.
I'm not wasting any more money in this
country. I'm not wasting any more money
in this country, lad.
No. Why is it gone cold again as well? Yeah. You
know, they're all scumbags. It's like
Antman said, it doesn't matter where you
go, you see the same men with the same
attitude, the same women with the same attitude. That's
facts. No matter where you go, it's the
same people with the same attitudes.
I've noticed that as
well. I noticed that as well. It's the same
people. How was money? I don't give a
[ __ ] I don't compare myself to other
people. It's irrelevant. I don't care. I
don't compare myself to
others. Yeah, it is a
r. But seriously, all jokes aside now,
[ __ ] all of this ragging [ __ ] Where
where do you go from here?
Oh, do you know this is another thing as
well is also when you go out drinking,
you're like [ __ ] for like three days.
When you go out drinking, you're [ __ ]
for like three days. I think I've just
got over the hangover on Friday. So, you
have to go through all of that just to
be able to get
someone. Oh, it's a laugh, is it,
bro? Downies, bro. No one joins.
But how this person does this, how this
person does that, it's comparing. And comparing is
irrelevant. You know, there's no such
thing as if this person can do it, so
can you. That's not the way the world
works. Unfortunately, we wish it worked
like that, but it doesn't work like
that. It doesn't work like that because
the whole thing is is there's not
someone for everyone. So, that would
answer your question. There's literally
I don't believe in that saying that
there's someone for everyone. There's
people that are just not compatible with
no one, you know, especially in this day
and age as well. I never believed in
that saying ever. Never have I ever
believed in that
saying. Never have I ever believed in
that saying because it's [ __ ] It is
bollocks. Cuz think about it, bro. If
they ever summoned for you, you'd be
with them. You'd be sat here with them
right now on this live stream. The
amount of traveling and trying you've
done. End of. I'm not going to bore you
with it all, but that's
it. What do we do? Go out every week and
approach? Is that what we're supposed to
do? Go out every week and approach and get
depressed? That sounds like a great
idea, isn't it? Go out and get depressed.
M yeah, spend £300 a
week. That's how much it is to go out in
London. 300 pound a week. [ __ ] hell.
Sorry, bro. That's funny.
Uh £300 a [ __ ] week,
eh? I mean, I'm guessing it would be
around that. About £300.
Yeah. It's not even like a little£100.
You can't go out out with a little£100.
Go out, send it, spend100 pound. You
can't even do
that. Exactly. That's why we're not
doing it. And that's why we're not doing
it. That's the whole reason why we're not doing
it. Oh, you could join the pool
industry, but that's not as easy as as
that. Yeah. Well, you wouldn't spend 300
a week. That's what I'm trying to say.
But I'm saying if you was to go out,
that's how much realistically you'd be
spending. By the time you've got your
haircut, you're easy spending over £200.
So why would you do that, bro? It
doesn't make sense when all you're going
to get is, "Oh, I've got a boyfriend.
I've got a boyfriend. I've got a
boyfriend." So it's [ __ ] stupid, isn't
it? When we all know that they don't
have boyfriends because it's [ __ ]
How can I have [ __ ]
boyfriends? It's going to be nice not
hearing that for a month. It's going to
be lush not hearing that for a month.
Piss me off, bro. Oh, that used to
[ __ ] piss me
off. It pissed me off on Friday and I
weren't even going out to get
women. It was just pissing me off
constantly. Pissing me off,
bro. A point of it. Yeah. pisses you off
where you want to just go out and keep
selling it and not stop or and then
another part of you wants to just give
up when we all know realistically giving
up is the only option but when you're
stubborn like me it's hard to you know
but I'm not wasting any more money bro
I've already wasted enough [ __ ] money [ __ ] you
know getting an only fans why would I
get an only fans be [ __ ] stupid I'm skint
Hey, I've got some money to show you.
Actually, I've got some money in my
pocket. One sec. [Music]
Yeah, bro. Got some dough yesterday,
lad. I can get out of ground if you
want, but we'll start with this. Can we
this? There we go,
Timmy. Little bit of bum change for you.
you. A little bit of bum change for you,
buddy. You want me to take out another
two grand? Got five of there for you,
too, mate. If you
want. Yeah, Timmy. It's only upstairs,
bro. By the way, bro. So, I haven't uh
got got any out of my bank, but plenty
more where that come from, buddy.
See, at the age of 40 years of age, I've
warned you to not talk about people that
you don't know, buddy. You
know, I've warned you to not talk about
people you don't
know. You know, you're not showing the
grand. You just been show shown more
money. You still don't show
anything. You must really be the good one.
Um, I'm not addicted to approaching.
No, cuz I don't really do it anymore. Yeah. Oh
m look at this
cash. Look at this
cash. But I'm saving for love anyway. So
yeah. Yeah, man.
man. Get no car, no house, no woman.
Talking about yourself there. To me, I'm
in a house and I've got more money than
you and I've had more women than you as
well. So, stop talking about yourself.
You're 40, you're skin, and you're still
a virgin. Remember, remember what you
said to me? You said that you get £500 a
week, but by the time you've paid your
bills, you get £200 a week. Mate, do you
think I could live on £800 a month?
Escorts don't count. I've showed many
women that weren't escorts. Nice try,
buddy. Yeah, I've showed more money and
I've shown more women than anyone on
this community. So, you can keep calling
them escorts to make yourself sound
better, but make yourself feel better.
But yeah, escorts don't count. Even
though I've shown loads of women that weren't escorts.
Okay. Yeah, buddy. You you you get £300
a week. I couldn't live on £300 a week.
I couldn't live on £200 a week. I literally
couldn't. I could not live off that a
week. I swear. I'm not even joking. I
could not live off that a
week. I'm not even chatting [ __ ] I
swear to God. I swear to God, I could
live on that a week.
So, my crypto wallet. Why do you want to
see my crypto wallet? What the
[ __ ] [ __ ] crypto wallet, bro. Have a
[ __ ] word be your [ __ ] self,
man. Yeah, I couldn't live on that
above, bro. [ __ ] 300 quid. That 300 quid a
bub. Nah, [ __ ]
Yeah. So, yeah. Yeah. To me. So, yeah.
me, I need to do some serious serious
saving. Some serious saving,
lad. So, I'll be bored this month,
but is what it is.
No escorts, no
nothing, which is good to be fair. I
mean, you shouldn't be wasting all that
money on that anyways if you think about it. But
yeah, when I'm off to Thailand, when I
get my passport, which should be on
Saturday, I'm out of this country, bro.
I was getting these mood swings
yesterday. Truth talker. This woman was
trying to tell me what I need to do and
able to get someone. And guess what?
She's had a boyfriend for a month. Is it
mad how all of these women that give you
advice are the same women that are
[ __ ] someone else and can get any man
they want? I [ __ ] hate them, bro. You
don't know the stuff that I was saying
about their kids yesterday and
everything. I [ __ ] hate these women.
I hate women. I hate them. And I've had
more women than anyone on this this community, lad.
Yeah, I hate them, bro. I actually I
generally hate them. They're scum. They
really are scum. Trust me, they're scum of the
earth. You know, they they sit there and
give you advice, truth talk about how
you'll find someone and but this person
is never them, is it? Why is this person
them? Why is this person never these
women? But they'll have no problem
[ __ ] someone else. See, my
experiences with them has made me hate
them. It's it like they hate you and I
hate them. You both hate each other.
Your My experiences with them has made
me feel this
way. You know what I'm saying? How much
are the flights? Like £500. So,
yeah. Yeah. I'm not giving you a link.
I'm going out in a bit. Yeah.
Proof talk. I went out on Friday
approaching women, but most of them have boyfriends
apparently. They got boyfriends
apparently. Same old [ __ ] in the same
England. Same old [ __ ] in the same old
England. Hey, isn't that madness? Same
old [ __ ] in same old England.
No. No. direct to.
Yeah, you'll never hear that in
Thailand. You never hear it in Thailand
because adman's been three times and
he's never heard it. And the people that
say they have boyfriends and the and the
women that say they have boyfriends
don't tell you they got boyfriends, so
you never hear it. In England, you hear
it all the [ __ ] time. I was pissed
out of my head on Friday, but I [ __ ]
definitely remember hearing it. You
definitely hear it in Thailand. You
[ __ ] definitely hear it in
Thailand. You definitely hear it in
Thailand, mate. I tell you that
much. And I know that. And I know that for
nothing. Because my friend's been there
three times. Why would people go there
if they hear
it? There we
go. Yeah. And and London is full of
stuck up [ __ ] I think they're better
than you with bad attitude problems.
Timmy, the only virgin is you. You are
the virgin. Stop calling yourself a
virgin. There's a video of me getting a
[ __ ] [ __ ] There's a video of me
in bed with two different women. The
only virgin on this community is you and
Sean. You are you are both virgins and you'll die
virgins. You are a virgin. You little
virgin. And what what I don't understand
with this community is why do you come
on here calling people things and then
even when they prove to you that they're
not, you still call them the same thing.
Like for example, you call people a
skinned virgin. They show you money,
they prove they've had sex, and then you
still call them things. It's because
you're talking about yourselves. It's
the same thing as Sean, the erectile
dysfunction virgin. He will die a
virgin, but there's 10 years between you
two. Why do you do that? You call people
things and then even when they show you
that they're not, you still call them
it. It's cuz you're one
yourself. It's cuz you're a virgin
yourself. It's like what I said about
Sean. He's a [ __ ] virgin. He said I
was watching these videos say he said
something a virgin would say. I said you
are a [ __ ] virgin. You never stuck
your dick up. Nothing. You've been with
a woman for 3 years and you've still not
[ __ ] her and you're still a
virgin. You know, people that talk about
these things are ones
themselves. Virgin skin. They're talking
about their own projecting life. These
people are fat, ugly losers that have
got nothing going for
themselves. Yeah, it
is. My mom's messaging me,
lad. Yeah. You said, mate, you said big
nose about a million times. Can you stop
repeating yourself? It's boring now.
This is why like you're killing the
chat. Big nose. Big nose. Big nose. You
sound like a
5-year-old. Yeah, you're boring now,
mate. Oh, here's another thing. You said
that you you you're with your woman for
3 years, but you've spent the past hour
stalking me. That's because Sarah don't
give you no sex. You will die a virgin.
Sean, you're going to die that virgin.
I'm telling you, you're going to die a
virgin. Is it mad truth talker that he
says that he's with his girlfriend and
he's got a woman, but he's on YouTube
every day stalking me. Go figure. How
can you have time to have sex with your
disabled woman, right? You can't get
him. He's a He's He's a crafty [ __ ] You
go to his area and he runs to the police
like a little [ __ ] but he comes on
YouTube like some big man. He can't get
got. He's a [ __ ] coward. Little rat
face. Little virgin. When you go to his
area, he doesn't come out and he runs to
the police screaming he's not a fighter.
He's a YouTube warrior. A lanky string
of piss ratfaced little YouTube warrior
that spends every single moment of every
day stalking Peter Belly cuz he wants to
be me. But he spends time with his
girlfriend apparently. [ __ ] off. You
[ __ ] her. You're a virgin. Typical
virgin. Just like when I first met you, you little
virgin, you know. And you will [ __ ]
die a virgin. You diagnose autistic
disabled lanky stringer piss skinny
little [ __ ] They'll go and [ __ ] up and
suck your disabled dad's dick. You rat boy. Rat
face. His girlfriend is disabled and she
doesn't give him sex. This is why he
comes on YouTube every day triggered.
He's a sad bastard. Sad little bastard. Yeah,
bro. Didn't want to reply and stuff. Uh
no. I need to go, bro. I'm gonna come back later.
Yeah, I have stuff to do, bro. I need to
get coke. Why does this [ __ ] thing
keep spamming? I'll be back later. Yeah.