It sucks [ __ ] [ __ ] How the [ __ ]
did in Colchester [ __ ] score? [ __ ]
a load of old botics.
Oh, it's [ __ ] They didn't even [ __ ] score.
Gold didn't even score today. It's a
[ __ ] over our bollocks.
It's absolute [ __ ] I won't be gambling again.
That was like my last bet. [ __ ] load of [ __ ]
It's a load of
It's a load of our bollocks.
It's rigged to [ __ ]
There's only two both no draws in that
whole [ __ ] league. [ __ ] off. It's [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah. Well, I won't be gambling again
anyways. Just ordered some food.
So, I was speaking to Morgan's friend
all day, so I was busy. [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] [ __ ] I won't be doing it again.
It's such a wank how they don't score.
How one day they score and then the
other day they don't score. It's a
[ __ ] load of old wank.
It's a load of old wank. That's the last
one I'm ever doing anyways.
Well, since I gambled out there, I might
as well just put a football bet on. I'm
done. It s [ __ ]
Imagine you actually did want to go out
today. Imagine trying to go out with
that on your mind. Nah, it's not even possible.
No, it's irritating. It's depressing. I
don't think you'd be able to, to be honest.
It's [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. It's [ __ ]
a load of old wank. I would have lost
anyways cuz I would have done
Coldchester in Swindon and Colchester
didn't glass though. It's [ __ ]
It's a load of old wank. Trust me.
It's [ __ ] [ __ ] Mhm.
This [ __ ] in it, bro. Bollocks, mate.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] depressing. How are
you supposed to do a quiz when you got
that in your [ __ ] mind? It's
[ __ ] I'm not doing them again.
It's depressing. I'm not doing them
again, bro. It's too depressing. I hate
it. It's [ __ ]
I feel like going out and starting like
a fight with someone or something.
Yeah, it's depressing, bro. Very depressing.
Very, very depressing. Mhm. Yeah. Depressing it. [ __ ] depressing.
That's 50 g going down the drain.
But it's just entertainment, so they say.
So they say. It's just entertainment, so
So they say, huh?
Just ordered some food, by the way. Yep.
So they say
It's a madness there.
It's a [ __ ] madness.
Yeah, I was talking to um
USA is his friend for like 5 hours on
the own Steven Howard. Yeah.
Five [ __ ] hours.
Can't wait till I'm out of here, lads.
Can't wait till I'm out of here.
Looks like I'll be able to work soon, so
I'll be off here.
I always pick Colchester.
She said if I went there, she was going
to get like seven people to shoot me and [ __ ]
I'm not going to lie, bro. Yeah, like
even though we were on good terms, we're
talking and [ __ ] we was on the phone
for like 5 hours, I was kind of like
when I was hearing that yesterday, but I
was kind of like I kind of want to call
their bluff, mate. You know what I'm saying? Like
kind of want to call their bluff cuz I
I'm not scared of no guns. I'm not
scared of no [ __ ] [ __ ] But we
weren't arguing or nothing.
You think me? You You think, bro,
someone that goes all the way there
would go all the way there if they knew
they were going to lose.
If they knew they were going to lose,
they wouldn't go there, would they?
No, they wouldn't, bro. Why would
someone go somewhere to lose? It don't make sense.
No, they actually thought I was going to
go and like kill people and [ __ ] I was like, no.
But yeah, she's [ __ ] She's [ __ ]
We was talking.
We was talking for like 5 hours. Um,
yeah, on the phone, bro. That's why I'm tired.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ] One sec. Listen,
that football was depressing, bro.
Oh, she's not born nuts to me, mate. Trust me.
I said to her, she met my her match with
me and I didn't meet my match with you. Trust me.
She's a nutty bastard.
We having banter and [ __ ] but you're
not going nuts for me. Trust me.
If I get this thing soon, I can be out of here.
Told you I going out today. I'm done.
Done, bro. When Peter belly says he's
done, believe he's dead. Done, bro. Mhm. Yeah. Yeah.
This situation like
is that the real you Kieran? This is
another reason the pay was 438 from 50 pound. But
even though I was speaking to her friend
and [ __ ] and you're speaking for like 5
hours like this is one of the reasons
why you need to leave here leave this
country. Well, you don't need to leave
the country but you need to give up with
women from the west cuz do you know how
serious this actually is?
Go along with the I've got a boyfriend
[ __ ] The same old boring [ __ ] that
always happens. like you. This is part
of the reason why you need to like think
about what you're really doing here.
Yeah, I lost the football bet. I had a
double both teams to score.
Uh no draw. Got completely [ __ ] with it.
Yeah, I got completely [ __ ] bro.
this [ __ ] Didn't win on Frankie the
other day. Don't win on roulette. It's
boring. this this life here, bro. It's
boring and depressing.
Just waiting for my food to come. Yeah,
that's like an indication of why you
really need to think about what you're doing.
I was willing to actually call her bluff
yesterday. Like, you're going to It's
the way she was saying it. Even though
we weren't arguing that,
you know, like
trust me, I will go there and I will
take one of you out before you take me
out. Trust me. You know what I mean?
This is all madness. This is, bro.
Yeah. So, I can't choose you over my
bestie. I said, "Yeah, you can.
This is madness, bro."
Yeah. How you I don't go out like
I don't go out anymore doing the
approaching kill. I've been out for a
couple weeks, lad. I can't be asked
anymore, lad. I can't be bothered with it.
Have a nice vendal now. Oh, wait.
I want I want out of there, bro.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I'm done with the football, bro.
I'm not betting on it again. And it's
not like, oh, I would have won anyways
cuz I would have lost cuz I would have
done cold chest and swindon.
Uh, you skin.
I think I've got like maybe 900 left, I
think. Oh, [ __ ]
But I need to be careful cuz I'm
leaving. So, I can't be I can't afford
to be wasting any money.
I should have this job soon. So, where's
this [ __ ] thing, bro?
What you skint? Yeah. I just can't be
bothered with it anymore
hearing lad like the whole I've got a
boyfriend and [ __ ] like but we were
having good conversations on the phone
me and me and her friend and that. Um
she told me some stuff I didn't know.
Like I'm not going to get into it but
[ __ ] up [ __ ] that I didn't even know. So
yeah, she told me stuff that kind of is
like okay yeah should stop now. Like,
well, I stopped anyway, but [ __ ] bro. Like,
yeah, you skin, bro. Yeah.
I mean, it's hard to come by nowadays. I
won I won I won two football bets in a row, lad.
Um, one week and the week after, but
there's no point me uh
there's no point me gambling, bro, cuz I
don't I don't like losing. I was on the
FBI um day before yesterday and that was
the last time in like months and months and months.
Yeah, I don't really do it anymore. Like
I don't I don't do it because of I don't
like losing. So if I don't like losing,
why do it?
So you've watched some of my videos, but yeah.
Yeah, I've got about like 900 or something. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. I stopped months ago, bro. I
was I was bored of the same old cycle.
I was bored of the same old cycle, lad.
You know, you're not bored of it. Like
well my mine wasn't going skimp but it
was like obviously like the mood swings and [ __ ]
Bro should have quit a long time ago my
man. What the [ __ ] Whether it's the
moods it's [ __ ] you with or you ended
up skin whatever it is like [ __ ] all that.
And like the double both teams to score
is a good way to win, but you got to put
a lot of money on it. Like 500 pound minimum
and that returns like 17,800. But
obviously if you lose then bro Yeah, you
can't. I stop cuz the mood swings.
Yeah. No one plays them anymore, bro.
Cuz they're all [ __ ] rigged ever. The industry's finished.
I've not been skinned for like three
years, lad. I've [ __ ]
Yeah. Stop doing it, bro.
You're in a cycle. You don't even
realize you're in a cycle. You need to
break the cycle. It might seem hard at
first, but it's worth it. It's what I
done. Like, I would go out and keep
hearing this [ __ ] I have a [ __ ]
boyfriend [ __ ] getting them [ __ ]
me around. Then I realize it ain't never
going to change. So that's why I've
booked what I've booked. You know what I
mean? Similar with gambling. It could be
anything, bro. It doesn't need to just be gambling.
Mine was like with the women thing and
and gambling as well. I ain't going to
[ __ ] run in circles all my life.
You know what I mean?
So we actually skip now until what? Next week.
Yeah, I've got like 900 pound, but I'm
going to live off like 50 a week
thingy soon. So
yeah, I'll show you my bet if you want.
You want to see my bet? I'll show you
mine if you want.
[ __ ] starving I am, bro.
I think that's just my food that's
pulled up. I'll be back live later. Anyways,
yeah, that's my football. But [ __ ]
better be my dinner.
Better be my dinner.
Oh, it is. Yeah, man.
Oh, don't wake up this window.
Come on, K.
You already know what I'm going to say. M virgin vanilla
I was telling Morgan's friend about this.
Yeah, I was telling Morgan's friend
about this. Yeah, she was telling
Morgan, "Oh, yeah. I was speaking to him
on the phone and he seems normal. He
seems chill, man." She said, "Really?" Yeah.
Go to my bathroom. She been on the phone
for about 5 hours. This boy can't
his ass would be on fire.
A lovely Indian, mate. A lovely Indian.
I was on the phone to USA is his friend
for um about 5 hours. We [ __ ]
that is delicious.
Yeah. All of our bets got [ __ ]
You want to see me b
You want to see me bite a bit of love?
You want to see me bite a bit of lamb, lad?
Yeah. One second.
I've been eating all [ __ ] day.
I've been eating all [ __ ] day, man.
The vindaloo, mate.
And I'm vindaloo saying made for the
weak. The weak virgins
[ __ ] guy [ __ ] bro.
M. That is lovely for this. Oh m delicious mate.
I'll be back in a bit.