Yeah, man. Bam. Wonderful.
What's good? Nothing.
There's nothing good about this life.
It's [ __ ] depressing.
There's nothing good about this life. It's depressing.
Well, lucky you. Changes my mood. Gives
me mood swings.
Yeah, stop trying to troll me, bro. I'm
not Monty or Timmy. I don't know how
many times I've had to say that. I'm not
Monty, man or Timmy. So, don't talk to
me like I'm one of them.
Facts. Literally facts. So yeah,
stop the trolling, bro. It's not going
to work on my channel.
Yeah, you are trolling. Well, you're
trying to troll. You're not trolling,
but you're trying to troll.
That's what you're doing. You're trying to draw. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't even know what we're playing today.
We're playing some Franklin Grey B out
my [ __ ] head. Yeah.
What up my [ __ ] matey? Nah,
I'm too lazy.
Too lazy, mate.
Is this life going to end? It's the same
[ __ ] every day,
you know, despite people saying, "Oh,
you don't know what next week holds. You
don't know what could happen the next
day." It's been the same [ __ ] for years.
So I mean [ __ ] you kind of do you
have a good uh inkling what it will be
like tomorrow and then next week and
depressing country to live in you know
horrible is it horrible way to live in this country Yeah. So is [Music]
stupid [ __ ] idiot on Instagram was
like, "Oh, just approach next week.
Clean state and forget about your
experiences." I said, "Fuck that. Are
you [ __ ] mad? I'm not [ __ ] going
out there like a [ __ ] doing it all over
again when we already know the result.
You're trying to get me more [ __ ]
depressed. Jesus Christ.
[ __ ] crazy. These people grievy the
[ __ ] they're [ __ ] crazy. They are
It's [ __ ] depressing, mate. I hope I
die in my sleep. I'm getting closer and
closer and closer and closer and closer
to wanting it to happen. And when you
get these people giving you stupid
[ __ ] advice, it's even more depressing.
You know, they know what you've been
through already and they're still and
they're telling you that you need to
[ __ ] I'll just end up blocking this
[ __ ] Like it's straight off the bat. I
would just end up just blocking the [ __ ]
Like straight, bro. It's best thing if
people giving you,
you know, you know your experiences, you
know what you've been through with these
people and they're still telling you to
go and approach. They know what you've
been through already with these people,
you know, like [ __ ] last week, the
[ __ ] [ __ ] me, bro. The week before
the last week, they they know. Why are
they telling you to go out and do it again?
Are they trying to get you depressed or
something or what?
like even more depressed.
It's not a clean state. It's not forget
your experience, you No. No. Remember
your experiences as to why you should
never try again,
you know? You know, no, remember it.
Remember your experiences.
[ __ ] that. Why' you forget them?
Remember them. They're [ __ ] terrible.
It's a reason why you shouldn't [ __ ]
do it ever again.
I keep hearing that I got a boyfriend
[ __ ] [ __ ] off. I'm not listen I hear it
enough when I'm watching other people's
videos when it ain't even me doing it.
Even that [ __ ] annoys me. It gives me
a [ __ ] headache. I need to take
[ __ ] code. It gives me a [ __ ] headache, bro. Yeah,
I can't wait till I die
to be honest.
I can't wait till I drop dead.
depressing life here. >> Yeah.
Well, I think the best way is to die in
your sleep to be honest. I think that's
your best your best bet is to probably
die in your sleep.
I don't give a [ __ ]
I don't give a [ __ ] This life is depressing.
It's a [ __ ] It's [ __ ] depressing.
This life being miserable and frustrated
every [ __ ] day thinking about your [ __ ] experiences.
It's [ __ ] hell living. It literally
is hell living.
Frustrating, annoying from the time you
wake up to the time you go to bed. It's
annoying thinking about it. It's annoying, mate.
You know, even speaking to USA is his
friend yesterday was annoying me, bro. I
haven't spoken to her today, but even
that was annoying me.
All of it. All of it annoys me. All of
it does, you know, and show it and so it
[ __ ] should do, you know.
I'm not answering questions where you're
bringing up that virgin. So, there's no
point mentioning that virgin on my chat.
Stop mentioning any relevant virgin on my channel.
Giving him air time.
Stop asking stupid questions as well.
Same problem every day. Women, bad
experiences, [ __ ] Having to think
about your bad experiences, just the
usual [ __ ] Being in this country,
every everything's depressing. Every
everything's depressing when you're in this country.
Everything, the women, the everything. I
hate this country.
It annoys me from the time I wake up to
the time I [ __ ] go to bed. It [ __ ] annoys me.
So yeah, that's what the problem is. Nope.
No, I don't.
It's just annoying being in this
country, the bad experiences, the
[ __ ] what happens when you approach
and you got someone telling you that you
need to approach.
The [ __ ] Why the [ __ ] would you do
that? To make yourself more down, more depressed. So yeah.
It's [ __ ] depressing it is. So yeah, tried it.
Try it. Tried it already.
Tried it already. Tried everything.
Never mind. I've approached more than
everyone in the world. So, I mean, I
ain't just saying that when I say it.
Nope. I've seen it in America as well.
This guy was approaching this uh fat
woman and she said to him, "Oh, I've got
a boyfriend." Yeah, they're even doing it now.
Yeah, I've I've seen on videos as well
on Instagram. I watch these like
approaching videos, these R channels.
It's getting worse.
Generally generally generally getting worse.
Generally is getting worse.
bad. Really bad.
I was watching some last night.
It's depressing, man. It really is.
It's depressing life. Is it?
It is a depressing life. Really is. Congratulations Congratulations.
Want a cookie?
Do you want a cookie?
Cheated on you in the end. Sounds about right.
Yeah, that sounds about right.
Yeah, sorry about that.
Do you want a cookie or something?
This country is depressing. Really,
really is depressing. Slow. Waiting
around for everything. Oh, it annoys me.
Does England annoy anyone else?
The people, the women, the government, [ __ ] everything. Everything.
Full of absolute [ __ ]
That's what it is. It's full of absolute
[ __ ] this country. One sec. Mhm.
depressing place to be.
You can get banned. You weirdo. Weirdo.
This life ain't the one.
Nope. I've already ate chicken and chips.
No. Wish you could just fall asleep for
like a year
and then just like wake up or fall
asleep and never wake up or fall asleep
and like wake up when you want to eat
and then just go back to sleep. Life is
pointless, man. It's [ __ ]
It really really is [ __ ]
And there you M the funniest thing about
life as well.
It never changes.
Despite what people say, it never changes. Mhm.
Never changes. Same old [ __ ] Same [ __ ] Different day. No change. Yep.
[ __ ] life in it. [ __ ] life.
It's your [ __ ] life.
It's horrible living like this.
Anywhere like England, America.
It's depressing to live in one of these countries. Canada Yeah.
So, I'm going to watch the Oreo man
later, I think.
Yeah, I'm going to go watch the Oreo, man.
You should watch some greasy Oreo, man.
Funny off, funny off watching them kind
of people is better than watching
um people on here. Yeah, man.
I like that depressing depressing talk
and [ __ ] I love it, man. It's better
than getting false hope and shitty advice
from people. You know what I mean? Yeah.
No, he's still upload. She's got another channel.
>> Yeah, he has he has another channel.
Yeah, I just watch him
even like some of the older videos. Yeah. [Music]
What's your opinion in Grezy? Do you
think the past
dictates the future? I think the past
dictates the future. 100%. Mhm.
Past dictates future.
Yeah, I I would say the opposite. People
say past don't dictate the future,
but it does. Definitely does. Past
definitely dictates the future.
Teammates hang. What the [ __ ] Uhoh.
Oh man, these headaches Anyway, [Music] some think
Yeah, still live. Coming up in a bit.
This message Bquest. I lost his number. So, [Music]
Yeah, I lost his number cuz my WhatsApp got deleted.
Yeah, man. There he is.
go to sleep now, but I don't want to
wake up too early, bro. That's the problem.
No, I'm good. Thanks. I'm all right in bed.
No, I'm all right in bed. Thanks.
I sleep now. I'll probably wake up late.
Just haven't seen what's the thing, bro. Yeah.
Anyway, I'm going go and see you later.