Sorry, I was going to go live. I've
already talk about this, but
some of us actually have a life. So, yeah, So yeah,
cuz I went on my other account and I saw
it cuz I got people blocked. Hey,
I'm telling you that red star is just
some 40y old virgin that lives with his
mom. Facts, bro. Facts. I didn't even
clock it until I went on my other account.
You just know he's just some [ __ ]
40-year-old virgin sat in his mommy's
basement all day, every day. You know
it, bro. it, you know,
100%, bro. 100%. You just know that he's
just some loser sat in his mom's
basement wreaking a jealousy every day,
but too scared of a too scared of a little [ __ ]
He's a [ __ ] proper [ __ ] in it.
He's scared, bro. He's a scared [ __ ]
How can you do this? like, "Can you do a
video?" Well, saying that you're too
scared to talk, so I mean, that's not
going to happen.
He He didn't spend 350. He didn't spend hardly anything.
London is much more expensive than Belfast
because you cuz this community is full
of sad retards. I mean, look at what
that red star does. Sat on YouTube every
day stalking men for free. I mean, you
are in a sad community. I mean, what the
[ __ ] do you expect? It's a disabled
community full of the bongos that ain't
got a life. So, I mean, I mean, what do you expect
on YouTube? I I don't know how like this
Red Star can do this like for years. Sat
on YouTube stalking but
not do anything to anyone. I don't know
like how somebody can be triggered every
day of their life like that. I I don't
understand it, bro. I think I would just
get bored and think, "Right, [ __ ] this."
But I could never imagine being like
some of these people,
you know, every day.
100%, bro. 100%.
This [ __ ] has been doing this for
absolutely years. And don't forget about
the people that he's begged to do stuff
to me like um this coward. Don't forget,
yeah, this little virgin coward has
begged like London Taylor to do stuff to
me and other people which needs to be
added on, bro. You know, he's sat there
stalking every day and he's blocked.
Like, the only reason I saw his comment
is cuz I went on my other account and I
went on L to see who was talking about
me. That's the only reason I saw it,
bro. He's sad as [ __ ] Imagine being
that jealous of a person. It's crazy.
But to them, it's normal cuz they're
disabled. But yeah, but to them it's
normal cuz like I said, they're
disabled. They ain't got a life. So
really weird. And and the and the
maddest thing about it is he doesn't get
paid for any of this [ __ ] That red star
does not get paid for any of this. He's
wasting his life away. Yeah, I'm the
skinn one and I'm this and I'm that,
right? All the things he tries to call
me. But he's been doing this for years,
begging the black man to do [ __ ]
begging other people to do [ __ ] sat on
his fat ugly ass on YouTube every day
and he doesn't get paid for any of it.
Like not even a penny. Think think of it, bro.
He's a proper proper loser.
No, that's what you need to do as well.
Like when you see him comment again, oh,
but you beg the black man to do this.
You beg the black they beg the black man
to do things. You'll notice that he
cowards like Red Star will beg the black
man and the [ __ ] can't even talk
on video. He's that scared. He's that
much of a victim. It's [ __ ] up. These
are people are really weird.
I have no energy in real life. It's mad.
He is a coward. Everyone knows about
that coward now, bro. Just some fat,
ugly skint virgin. Just like nonslegs.
They both That's why they both get along
cuz they're both [ __ ] low and they're
both [ __ ] skint as well. Yeah.
two skinned [ __ ] go together. You know
what I'm saying? It's mad, isn't it? I
don't go on the channel anymore. I just
saw it on Lord J because I went on my
other I didn't realize I was logged on
to my other account. That's the only
reason I saw it.
Yeah, they beg the black man to do stuff.
Yeah, they they they love going to the
black man and because he's a coward.
Because, bro, he doesn't do anything
himself because he's a fat, ugly,
disabled [ __ ] You know what I mean? At
the end of the day, he is a fat, ugly,
disabled [ __ ] What can he do himself?
What the [ __ ] can he can't, bro? He
probably can't even make it down the stairs.
That's why he's sat on YouTube every day
embarrassing himself. It's free of charge.
That's why he comes on YouTube and
embarrasses himself and doesn't get paid
for it because he's a [ __ ] he's a disabled bastard.
[ __ ] madness. He is crazy, bro. Yeah.
And yeah, you don't that's that's that's
the thing is they don't even know us.
Um they don't even know me and they
don't get paid for it. Imagine sat there
stalking someone you don't know every
day that you're never going to do
anything to. You're not going to get
paid for and you don't even know them.
It's jealousy. It's clearly it clear as
day is jealousy with these people.
It's clearly jealousy with these people,
bro. Come on. How long we've been doing
this now? Come on.
No, we're just talking about Red Star the loser.
Yeah, he's the [ __ ] losers. Think of
it like like if they Sorry, bro. If they
have to do this every single day, then
bro, they're clearly jealous of something.
So, you know, just just
how she wouldn't do it.
I think it's Pat Mustard. Me that
account. I think that's Pat Mustard. Yeah.
Yeah. Oh, Virgin boy will never
approach. That's why he will die a virgin.
Oh, mate. That's why he's going to
[ __ ] die a virgin. He's never going
to get laid. I said that a million
times. I told you he would die a virgin.
I know him better than than he knows his
[ __ ] self. He will die a virgin, mate.
Yeah. Just same old same old [ __ ]
Yeah. But again, it is a disabled
community, so I mean, what do you expect?
They're [ __ ] mongos, so I mean, what
do you expect from a from a bunch of mongos
sat on [ __ ] YouTube every day
stalking for free?
[ __ ] hell. Imagine that on your
deathbed e in many years to come that
you spent all your life stalking on on
the internet. Stalking someone you don't
know and you didn't even get paid for it.
>> Take that [ __ ] L, [ __ ] Take
that [ __ ] L.
That is a big L, bro. It
take that L.
>> Yep. Someone on Reddit. Oh, another
thing is they also stalk me on Reddit as
well. They literally will wait for me to
post stuff. That's how obsessed they are
with me. They literally stalk me on
Reddit as well.
Yeah, they stalk me on Reddit, lad.
They're [ __ ] stalkers.
You don't even stalk people like that
when you're in love. That's what I find strange
is that they say that they're not
jealous of someone and you're this and
you're that and you're this and you're
that. But think about it. You wouldn't
even stalk somebody like that if you was
in love with them. Think about it for
one second. Say you actually knew
someone and you actually knew them and
you was actually in love with them. You
wouldn't stalk them the way these people
stalked me. So something's not quite right there.
something's not ticking right, you know,
if you ask yourself this, you know, it
doesn't make sense
cuz I know if someone's skin and they're
all of these things, I wouldn't be doing
videos on them every day. I wouldn't be
stalking them every day.
So, I mean, it goes deeper than that,
like it goes a lot deeper than that.
It goes a lot deeper than that, bro.
you know. So, yeah, they stalk me on
like forms as well. I mean, have you
seen what that Jamie Thompson looks
like? Fat and ugly. Bomb. Fat and ugly.
Huh? Fat and ugly. You get me?
So, it seems to be like um a thing, you know.
uh, yeah, bro. Just same old [ __ ]
Didn't go out last. I didn't go out uh
this week. Ghost.
Yeah. K. Uh, yep. Graycat as well that
used to talk about Kaye. You're quite
right. Gray Cat, Bomb, Pat. Uh,
they're all self-projecting fat ugly people.
So, I mean, yeah. Uh, yeah. I didn't go
out this week ghosting. I just can't
wait to leave now, bro. Can't wait to leave. Yeah, bro.
Hope you had a good uh bank holiday weekend.
I'm glad you did, bro.
I didn't do a bet um on Tuesday. I
didn't do a bet.
Oh, just a Thailand, bro.
Yep. They're all fat and ugly, bro.
What? You can't believe someone's been
to Vegas four times. Why would you
believe someone's been to Vegas four
times? It's not hard to go to Vegas, bro.
And he's got a girlfriend. He's got a
wife. And has Has has anyone seen what
his wife looks like? No, we haven't. So,
that answers your question.
What goes to Vegas, bro? It's It's not
hard to go to Vegas. There's There's
nothing mad about it at all. The [ __ ]
You've got to be trolling me, right? And
he's got a wife who's probably uglier than him.
No, that Jamie Thompson, the the fat
one. The fat ugly one. The one that stalks me.
No, we were just talking about ghosting
that as like, you know, if you was in
love with someone. Yeah. You wouldn't
stalk them the way these people stalk
me. But these people say that you're
this and you're that and you're this and
you're that. But put it this way, bro.
Say you was in love with someone. You
wouldn't stalk people the way these
people stalk me. So something's not right there.
You know, we're just saying something
isn't I don't know about you, but
something is not right there. Do you
understand? Like me, when I used to [ __ ]
with that USA, Izzy, it used to be like
once a month or so, it wouldn't be all
day every day like these people.
And I had actually well I wouldn't say I
known them but I actually met them.
Uh I'm overweight. Bro, listen to me.
When I'm when I start getting as fat as
you people, I will start worrying about
it. You're talking about yourself again.
Bro, you're trying to say that I'm
overweight. Bro, no one can be as
overweight as you people. Worry about
your own weight and your own looks first
and then start talking about other
people. So yeah, something's not right
there. ghost him. Something's not right there, bro.
Think about me. Yeah. Say, say I was to
argue with you. Yeah. For example. Yeah.
Talking about yourself. You asking, "Go
self-reflect on another channel." So,
let's just say they tried to call me
fat. Have they seen themselves? [ __ ]
hell. So, say for example, Yeah. I I I
say that for example ghosten you are a
manta you are skin you are this you are
that. So am I going to leave you to your
sad pathetic [ __ ] life or am I going to
stalk you all day every day and not get
paid for it?
You see what I mean? Like let's just say
we use that analogy. Yeah. You can see
it doesn't make sense. You clearly have
something in their life that they want
where they have to come on here
triggered every day
and because they hate something that you
have that they don't. But obviously
there's nothing that they can do about
it because they can't meet anyone. So
they beg the black man to do [ __ ] So
you got understand it doesn't it doesn't
look make sense, does it?
No. No. I know. I'm just using that as
an example. You know
how they can like No, to be fair. To be
fair, bro. Like, I think it's mad how
they can just do they not get bored of
being triggered every day. Like, imagine
being sat on YouTube from the time you
wake up to the time you go to bed
triggered like Red Star. Like sat on
YouTube triggered every single day.
You've got all this energy and all this
anger, but you're not going to do
nothing about it. That would that would
I don't know about you, that would wind
me up. that would generally generally
wire me up that I was such a coward that
I could have energy behind the keyboard.
Um, but I and then I'd have to beg the
black man to do [ __ ] cuz I couldn't do
anything myself. Would that not wind you
up? That would wind me up if I was them,
bro. I think deep down they're wound up. Yeah. Uh-huh.
Yeah. They're all ugly, but I'm better
looking than all of them.
I'm better looking than all of them. Yeah.
Do you remember when he was trying with
USA? Is he? USA is he rejected his ass.
He thought he had a shot. Virgin boy
thought he had a shot because I met them.
[ __ ] hell, man. Virgin boy thought he
had a shot, bro.
I joker. Virgin boy thought he was going
to get in there. No, mate. They don't
get with virgins like you. Sorry. Yeah.
Yeah. I feel sorry for that red star, bro.
And I feel bad cuz he actually wants to
do something, but he can't cuz he's too
much of a disabled coward. He wants to
do something is why he That's why he um
how I ended up on this community because
of [ __ ] Timmy.
Yeah, he stalks me all day, every day.
But I'm the skin mon apparently.
Remember that ghost? Yeah. One sec. Um,
yeah. He's the one that stalks me all
day every day, lad.
No, no, no, no. They don't do it for
reaction. No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. One sec. One sec. One
sec. One sec. Firstly, I don't watch the
videos, right? I only know about it
because I logged on my other account by
accident and I went on Law J's. Firstly,
they don't do it for reaction because
even if they don't get a reaction, I
tried explaining this to Joe a million
times. um they will still do it and they
are reacting for reaction in the first
place which then goes that which then
goes which then misses the whole point
because if I'm calling someone a fat
ugly manta I don't want a reaction from
them and I certainly wouldn't react for
a reaction. So no because even if they
don't get a reaction they will still do
it cuz they will literally do it all day
every day for like 10 years. Even if
they didn't get a reaction, even if they
didn't get a mention, they will still do
it. And what are they doing for a
reaction? They are reacting.
So it doesn't make any sense.
You know what I'm saying? Like it's all
it's all disabled. This is what I'm
saying. It's all it's all disabled.
Anyways, I found this community. Sorry.
Because of Timmy. I found this disabled
community because of [ __ ] Timmy. Yeah.
It was because of the fobies and um Timmy. Yep. Yeah, man.
But even if they don't get a reaction, then
they would still do it.
And let's just say they did do it for
reaction. So, let's just say they Okay.
Okay. Let let's just say that they
spent 6 months stalking you all day
every day for a reaction. Okay? So they
wasted all their life and time doing
this all day every day for a reaction
for 6 months. Let's just say for
argument 6 months. Yeah. And then after
that 6 months you reacted for like 2
minutes. Okay. Then what?
Okay. So what? You're going to do it
again for another 6 months until you get another reaction.
So it's uh it doesn't make any sense. So
let's just say okay they do it for
reaction. Yeah. And then you react every 6 months.
That says more about their life than
they're will that they're willing to sit
there and do this all day every day.
It's it's cuz they're fat ugly people
that ain't got a life. That's why they
do it. They do they do it for they
they're fat ugly people
that ain't got a life. That's that's
what it is.
So no, I stay in the community to speak
to like the decent people. So
it is a [ __ ] community though. For
real. It is. It is a [ __ ] community. One sec.
But what I love about this [ __ ] is when
they when these fat ugly people
try to say that you're gaining weight.
Like you'll see these fat ugly people
trying to tell you about your weight.
That's what that's what makes me laugh.
That's the thing that makes me l [ __ ]
l mate. As soon as I get to about 1% of
you people best believe I'm hitting that gym,
I don't commenting for hours at a time, bro.
I don't really do much nowadays
ghosting. I don't go out drinking
anymore because of the women [ __ ] So yeah.
Oh [ __ ] sake.
Yeah, they don't do it for reaction. It
makes me laugh when people say that.
Yeah, you're talking. Yeah, you're
talking about yourself again. Bye-bye.
I beg the black man to do your dirty
work again, you coward. Um,
but they don't do it for a reaction
because even if they don't get a
reaction, they Okay. So, okay. Okay.
Okay. Let me let me use this analogy,
right? So, you're saying that they do it
for a reaction, right? So if I posted
every single day, going casino, approaching,
right? Or just like normal [ __ ] Say you
daily vlog on this channel. Yeah.
And I didn't react for 10 years and I
went back on one of these channels in 10
years. I guarantee you even in them 10
years they didn't get a reaction, they
would have still been doing it every
day. So that completely misses the point
of they do it for reaction because they
don't do it for a reaction.
They don't do it for a reaction. People
that do stuff for a reaction types and
then you know they don't do it because
why would you be reacting for a reaction?
That doesn't make any sense. Why would
you react for a reaction?
Can someone else help me out here? Cuz I
don't I don't understand it.
Let's just say I could get Timmy,
right? Let's just say I could get Timmy reaction. Yeah.
Oh, he's he's a [ __ ] virgin, mate.
He's never going to get laid. He's never
going to get laid, mate. Say like I
could get Timmy to react, but I'd have
to do videos on him every day. [ __ ]
that, bro. Keep your [ __ ] reaction.
You understand? Something's not right
there, bro. I'm telling you.
Something is not right there. I'm
telling you, something is not right there.
Yeah, Virgin boy is never going to get
laid. He's going to die a virgin. Yep.
Confirmed by the psychiatrist actually. So yeah. Yeah.
Not just the doctors
cuz why have I had normal women and he hasn't?
Ask yourself that question.
USA is he well they're not normal but I
mean they're not disabled. Um
and then obviously you got loads of
other people there. Why is virgin boy
only ever got with disabled? Virgin boy.
I say that to myself sometimes, bro,
when I'm in the shower. It's so catchy.
Boy, you're [ __ ] burdening. I know.
It's just like a catchy thing. You know
what I mean?
Yeah. He is 41.
My birthday is April, Nicolo.
Yeah, my birthday is April. April 7th.
[ __ ] hell. He actually is full. Yeah.
Yeah. My birthday is April, isn't it, Joker?
No, that's not my birthday. Nah,
the best month is April. And no, not not
because my mommy's born in April. Well,
March and April is the best month.
And no, like I said, it's not just
because my mommy's born on them months,
that month, you know?
I don't know. It's a good month, isn't it?
I forgot Isabelle's birthday. What was Isabelle's birthday?
I can't even remember.
No, it was April.
Nope, it was April the 12th, actually.
So every year it's like an anniversary.
No, it was actually April. It wasn't
March. It was April.
Taking a bubin away from its mama.
Taking a baby away from its mama.
Yeah. No, it was April, bro. Oh, [ __ ] Yeah, April.
I can't get over Fraser, bro.
Oh, I know that guy. He looks like a He
looks like a [ __ ]
crackhead. Yeah, that's the day I met my mama.
That's that. Do you know when I met that
USA? That was my f It was the first day
I bought the Stony and it was the first
time I wore the Stony. It was my first
Yep. It was my first Stony, bro. Yeah. Yeah,
I still got the stony where I at my
where where I met my mama.
Yeah, is the green stony. Yeah, I
thought Let me flash the cash a little bit.
Good times. Hey, Zippy. Good times.
It was good times, wasn't it?
Oh, you going flying, Franklin. Yeah,
that's where I found my I still got the
approaching video. Nicola,
I can't believe she told her friend like
straight after like she met me. I think
I just done something bad. I gave this
guy my number. I thought he was cute.
Uh, I am cute. Oh no, Nicolo.
Stop mocking me, you [ __ ] Stop [ __ ]
mocking me, bro.
All you do is mock me, man. Mhm.
All you doing is more.
Where's Monty now? Nowhere to be seen.
This is why I hate people, man. You
know, they just use and abuse you.
Yeah, it makes me laugh when people say
they do it for a reaction.
That's just [ __ ] that they do it for
reaction. That is [ __ ] cuz I don't
watch any of them anymore
cuz I actually don't watch any of them
anymore. I just realized I weren't on my
main account. That's how I saw the
comment. I don't [ __ ] watch them.
So that's [ __ ] that they do it for a
reaction. That is bollocks. Cuz think
about it. Yeah. If someone winds Timmy
up, well you you they he used to make
like four or five videos.
So they don't get a reaction.
Yeah. I feel like going out and doing
something really dark. I hope I go and
lose all my money.
I hope I go and lose all my money.
That's what he said. Is it
about doing something really dark?
Yeah, that was funny as [ __ ]
I like number two.
I like number two. That's where you said it at. Yeah.
The [ __ ] life in it, bro. We're born
then and we die.
But then you should look at people like
Red Star and then your life is perfect.
If you look at people like Red Star and
[ __ ] like and Virgin Boy, your life
actually your life's actually Their
life's actually perfect compared to
theirs. They have to sit online stalking
men every day and they don't get paid
for it. Think about that. >> Yep. Yeah.
They do it for free. Nico,
they react their life away for free.
So they get a reaction then what?
No. No one answers me that. No one
answers me that at all. Okay. They do it
for reaction. Okay. So let's just say I
agree. So they do it for reaction.
they stalk you for six BS. They react to
you every day for 6 months for reaction.
Okay. So then you do So then you react
and then what?
Okay. And then then what?
H then what happens?
See, they're [ __ ] disabled, bro. They
don't even know what they're talking about.
That's not good, is it?
Bro, they're fat, ugly skin people. They
can't even go out and go to the pub and
have a drink. hear that skin,
bro. It's not even that. If they could
leave their house and they weren't
skint, they wouldn't be doing this. They
can't even go to the pub and afford a
[ __ ] drink. That's why they do all of
this [ __ ] every day, cuz they're they're
fat, ugly, disabled people that don't
even leave their house. They got no money whatsoever. So,
yeah, that's why they do all of this
Yeah. stalking [ __ ]
Legit, bro. That's why they do all of
this stalking and
[ __ ] that they do, cuz they ain't
got a life.
They got no life but YouTube.
It's all they have. Think about it.
They wouldn't be sat on YouTube every
day stalking if they weren't skin, bro. Yeah,
they've never had a woman ever.
Do you remember you're better looking
than them, you got more money than them,
and you got a better life than them, and
it kills them. That's what Ronald Pomp
said to me.
It stayed with me that little comment
cuz I think it's just right cuz why else
would people still be doing this [ __ ]
now up to today?
Well, I don't have loads and loads and
loads of money, but I got more money than them.
And obviously, you know how they kept
losing the and you know m you remember
how they kept losing the money game as well. So yeah,
it's true though, is it?
If you think about it,
I think that account's right.
Well, I think that counts right, Nicolo. Do you?
Yeah, sounds accurate to me.
And it kills them. And it kills them.
Get off of YouTube and live your life now, buddy.
I ain't seen that account for ages.
Must have took his own advice.
Yeah. Virgin boy. Virgin boy ain't got no money.
Virgin boy ain't got [ __ ] all.
He ain't got [ __ ] all.
[ __ ] all, mate. [ __ ] Cool.
>> Yeah. When he comes on here, I'm going
to have a go at him. I think that's Mark
Samson. Yeah. Like he was he was trying
to be a snake on LJ saying, "Oh, if
that's P uh imagine being scared of PJ." So um
so when he comes back, I'm going to say,
"Well, you're scared of me, you little
bitch." And I'm going to start slating
him and I'm going to call him out as
well. So when he comes back on here, if
he dares, he's getting called out.
Little snake [ __ ] Just like that Ricky
Villain doing. Hey,
they're all they're all, you know, like,
you know, the thing is with this year is
that they're all like pretty similar.
All snakes, all self projectors
like that. Ricky Milling does it as
well. He's a projector.
Says that people have got no money, no
future. They're literally talking about
themselves. Especially when you're
living in somewhere like Hull and you're
like 40 years of [ __ ] age.
I'm surprised these people didn't get a
[ __ ] um degree and talking about themselves
like an actual master's degree and
actually self projecting. They're
they're the best at it, you know,
talking about themselves every day.
surprised they didn't get a [ __ ]
degree in it to be honest. They're so
good at talking about themselves. It's
fun to watch.
No money, no car. That's literally you.
But you need to put your you need to put
your name in front of it. That's why you
are sat on YouTube every day stalking
because you ain't got a life. Yeah. No,
he's with that hoe. So, he's not coming
back on there now.
No. Nowhere to be seen, buddy. Nowhere
to be seen.
Hello. What should be seen? Not
People on Reddit said getting laid is easy. Nicolo,
they should just use Tinder.
Just use Tinder.
Just Just go on the apps.
Nicolo, just go on the apps.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
They say just go on the apps, Nicolola.
Just go on the dating apps.
When have the dating apps ever worked?
Well, other people. Well, it worked for Other people.
Other people. You say,
other people. It's always other people, isn't it?
Very lazy, you know, comparing you to
other people. It's very
what's the word I am looking for?
It's very lazy.
What do you think?
I think it's very [ __ ] lazy. Really?
It's just lazy.
Yep. I've showed them videos. I've
showed them dating apps. And they still
just resort to making stuff up. I don't
know what more I could show them. Yeah.
Other guys do it. Other guys that aren't
you, but they they say that you
shouldn't compare yourself to people. So
why are they comparing you to strangers?
They compare you to strangers,
but oh, they
but they tell you that you shouldn't
compare yourself to people, but they
compare you to strangers. So, I'm not sure.
Doesn't really make a lot of sense, does it?
No, it doesn't make a lot of sense, does it? No. Bam.
I'm so glad I gave up, though.
I'm happy I gave up, bro. Ready to leave now. Yeehaw.
I was so happy I gave up.
Was a long time coming by.
Don't get any replies from the numbers. Somebody involunt.
disagree with you on some stuff. I said,
"Bro, you can agree, you can disagree.
It doesn't really matter if you agree or
you disagree, to be honest. Evidence
doesn't lie. Videos don't lie. Text
messages don't lie. So whether you agree
or whether you disagree, it doesn't
really matter because we've got the evidence.
You know, we've got the actual evidence.
So, it doesn't really matter if you
agree or you disagree. Evidence don't lie.
If past doesn't If past doesn't dictate
future, why has it been dictating it for 4 years?
I don't think I got I don't think I got
an answer. Why is every week a replica
of the last week?
You know what I'm saying? So Other
guys do it.
Watch out for the other guys.
They're quite scary. Nicolo man. Other
guys do it. Other guys.
[ __ ] other guys, bro.
[ __ ] other guys.
Other guys do it.
[ __ ] other guys do it.
Compare them. It's not nice, is it?
It's not nice, is it? Being compared, [Music] Dip. Stop.
I'm out of that [ __ ] off.