Still can't find this
[ __ ] Been trying to find this [ __ ] I
still can't find him. I've been at it
for like a [ __ ] hour, mate. Still
can't find him, bro.
They're [ __ ] up.
I'm going to find this [ __ ] even if it
takes me all night.
Bro, I've looked up like Edinburgh
University and everything. For some
reason, I can't find this [ __ ] Welcome.
him if his number was
linked if his um number was linked to um
um if his number was linked to his
Facebook, I would have found him by now, bro.
But his Facebook's obviously not linked
to his number because I had his
number. See this woman in Scotland who I
was kissing two weeks ago. I found
her. I'm trying to find this guy from
Glasgow, man. I've been at it for like
[ __ ] an hour, bro. It's [ __ ]
hard, you know? I'm trying to find this
[ __ ] Tam from Glasgow.
I've been looking up Edinburgh
University cuz I remember he said he
went to Edinburgh
University. It's very difficult trying
to find this [ __ ] I
believe I [ __ ]
tried. You know what I mean?
His number obviously wasn't linked to his
Facebook. No, I need to find Tom, mate.
That's my dada.
I need to find my daddy,
mate. I need to find my daddy, bro.
Sorry. This is serious.
And he's not even live anyways. two hours
ago. I will find this [ __ ] bro, if it
takes me all
night. Stop calling yourself a skin m,
bro. It's not good for your mental health.
It's really really not good for your
mental health to talk about yourself like
that. Well, I can't find it,
bro. Yep. I'm trying to find this Tam from
Scotland and I can't find
him. I've been trying for the past
[ __ ] hour. I'm going to find this
[ __ ] today, bro. If it takes me all
night, cuz it's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
Yeah, I'll find this [ __ ] [Music]
software. Where else would I be going,
bro? I don't know.
It it it's like John in England. I'm
going to find him, bro. His name is Tam
and he went to Edinburgh
University. I remember he said that when
I met him. He said he went to Edinburgh.
Actually, I lost my phone. Ben, but
obviously there's a load of people on my
Facebook who I've who I who comes up
because of the number like this woman
from Scotland two weeks ago. There's
loads of people that come up but he
doesn't come up. So I take it his number
was not linked to his Facebook or he
don't have Facebook. But if you don't
have Facebook then there's no chance
finding him because if he's got
Instagram the chances are his Instagram
is not Tam.
So yeah, bro. Um,
yeah, I'm just going on Facebook list
after Facebook list after Edinburgh,
after Glasgow. It's [ __ ] long, bro.
But I I'll find this [ __ ] today, bro.
Trust me. By about 3:00 in the morning. Watch.
Yeah. So, it's a very
uh it's a very common name, huh? John's
not John's not coming that much
anymore. Let's see what he's live. Yeah. Mhm.
What's going on,
man? Oh, I'm [ __ ] knackered,
man. Been a long time, Ben. Hey, what do
you reckon the chances of me finding
this [ __ ] All you've got to do is look
at the people who's gone to Edinburgh
Uni, type his name on Facebook, and
hopefully he's got
Facebook. I found some guy before. It
took me about 3
hours. But it was dedication, bro. [Music]
Yeah. I don't know, bro. Just just
funny, isn't it? It's just
fun. Life is too short, but it's it's funny, isn't
it? It is funny. Yeah.
I was with a Scottish woman two weeks
ago because I don't have his number
anymore because my phone got stolen
obviously. Did you not listen? My phone
got stolen. So when I got a new phone I lost his number. Uh
bye-bye. Obviously, cuz my phone got
stolen, so I lost the cunt's
number. I was looking on what I've sent
my friends as well to see if I've sent
Nah, cuz I've used to do that with
people. That's how I found people
then. He said, "In good faith, I think
you need to talk some things through to a psychiatrist.
That may be it
off. No, bro. You don't even know what
the conversation was about,
bro. You don't know what the Do you know
what the actual conversation was about,
Ben? Right. It was the Celtic day. Yeah,
it was last year. It was It was when
Celtic was playing before the Euros.
Remember a couple months before the
Euros? And obviously load loads of
people from Scotland come down and take it.
Okay. And then we're talking and [ __ ]
He said, "Oh, he's from Glasgow." He was
in the Weather Spoons party in the
Weather Spoons. No, I didn't go. And
then he's like,
"Uh." And I said, "Oh, I've been
Edinburgh. I'm not in Glasgow." And then
his friend come over. I said, "I'm going
to send it, lads." And um I went and
spoke to these these women and she said
she had a boyfriend. And I went to him.
I said, "Oh, I'm sick of them saying
they have boyfriends in these social
environments. They can't all have
boyfriends." And he was like, "Oh, well,
they do." I was like, "Well, they don't,
you know, and then it turned into like a
little disagreement and I got his number anyways." And
yeah, no, I got a cheap membership. I
get a cheap membership. But yeah, you
don't need psych. You need to speak to a
psychiatrist for what's saying that,
bro. It's common [ __ ] sense, man.
Like, it's England. You know what I
mean? Yeah. When I lost my phone, I lost
all the numbers. But
yeah. Yeah, bro.
I'm not drinking or going out for a month.
Ben, it's going to be hard, but I'm
going to do it, lad. I'm going to [ __ ] do
it. Okay. Yeah, I will do it, bro. Watch
me. Watch me do it.
Yeah. I don't want to meet him. I just
want to find him.
But I think it's
impossible. Yeah, Ant-Man's in
Thailand. Yeah, I'm just tired. That is
Yeah. Yeah, he will want to fight me.
Yeah. No, I actually um I actually did
message him um a few months ago. I said,
"Oh, how about we meet up in Glasgow and
have a little drink?" And he was like,
"It depends who's asking." I said, "It's
your old pal PJ." And he never he never messaged
again. That was before I got my phone
stolen. He said that entirely depends on who's
asking. Oh, that was ace, is
it? That was ace,
bro. [ __ ] Scottish prick. K. Wads. [Laughter]
Yeah, I love it, bro.
lad. You know, Ant-Man goes to Thailand,
Ben, because he says that the women in
this country just aren't
interested. He said they're just not
interested in this country.
That's what Ant-Man says.
Yeah, he's right. Obviously, they're not
interested in this country. I've got I
renewed my passport. I should get it
Friday, Ben. I had to renew my passport,
lad. It doesn't matter,
mate. They're not interested in this
country. That's what he said. That is true.
True. But at least you don't get I've
got a boyfriend over
there. You don't get over there, mate.
You get it here. But you don't get over
there. Yeah, I renewed my passport on
Saturday while I sent it off for renewal.
So, I might get some nuggets. You
know, I'm supposed to be saving money as well,
but I need to eat.
actually some nuggets and some
coke. Some nice McDonald's coke or maybe
like a burger or something. I don't
know. Cuz I went mad when I lost money on the
football. But I control my gambling a lot now,
bro. No, I still got two grand. I've
still got 2K. So, you know, obviously I
have I sent 600. I got like two grand.
So, yeah, I kind of control it
now. Have to in it, mate.
Yeah. How people live on a [ __ ] grand
a month, I shall never know, Ben. A grand a
month. [ __ ] grand a
month. You're [ __ ] wanking me off,
lad. A grand a month.
I think you should talk some things
through to a psychi with a psychiatrist.
He said in good
faith. But think about it, Ben. Yeah.
These people that say this stuff like
it's your attitude ret. Think about it,
bro. These people have not been in your
shoes. These people have not been in
your shoes. So what the [ __ ] would they
know? Think about it, bro. That's real what I'm
saying. What I'm telling you, bro. What
they know. They've never had to walk a
mile in your
shoes. Don't judge a man unless you've
walked in his shoes. As Eminem
said, remember when I lost that woman in
America? [ __ ] it was I couldn't find
her. I gave up in the end because that
was [ __ ] America. But I think we
could find Tam. I actually think we
could find him,
bro. Him and his little graduation pitch
with his little kilt. I still remember
it. Him and his little kilt. Oh, bless you.
Like that's what I think, Ben. I think
it's that as well, bro. I think it's
that as well. I got with some Scottish
women two weeks ago, but that's what I think it
is. That's what I think it is, bro.
Because I've got a friend. Yeah. He's
like the same roundabout, the same looks
as me, but he's white, but he looks tan,
but you can tell he's white. And he gets
like no problems.
like he has no problems and he's not
better looking. We're like the same, you
know, obviously, but I've got a beard,
but he just cleans up on these dating
apps. I can't get
nothing. But I'm not the worst. The
least desirable race is
Indian. Um, and then like Chinese like,
but yeah, that's obviously that is what it
is. You know, these people that would be
attracted to you like Syrian, Albanian,
and all of these people, they don't
obviously use dating apps. It's it is
the race. That's what I was thinking as
well. I was thinking the same thing cuz
it ain't the way you [ __ ] look,
bro. I don't know,
man. Cuz sometimes I watch Glasgow
videos and it's annoying knowing that he
lives in that city and I don't know
where the [ __ ] he is. But
uh yeah, they are racist. Yeah, they're
all racist because you get a 6 out of 10
white guy and then you get a 6 out of
10 ethnic guy, which is what I look
like, and you see who does better.
That's what it is, bro.
Definitely. And I look [ __ ] I got a
beard in it. Uh yeah
[ __ ] Why do you think I got with
Morgan? Cuz Morgan was Syrian.
I could only get like Syrian, Brazilian, um maybe
Albanian, anything but white basically.
Yeah. Why is he so obsessed with me? Cuz
he wants to be me, lad. He's jealous of
me. Yeah. Tam Tam the Celtic
fan. Doesn't matter if she wasn't she
was she wasn't into me long term. I
still had sex with her, mate. I got what
I wanted. So that's a W on me. So
yeah, don't give a
[ __ ] And the [ __ ] lived in another country.
So, how was that going to
work? Would I do well in Scotland, Ben?
I'd probably get [ __ ] killed. They're
probably that racist over
there. Yeah, Spain. I I do good with
Spanish people. Yeah, Portugal. I've
been with a I've been on dates with a
Portugal woman. Yeah.
Um, it also
depends what they were meant to be long
term. They lived in another country.
What did you think was going to happen?
They're just a [ __ ] bro. Would have
been the same with anyone
else. I've been to Edinburgh. I'm
talking about Glasgow. Yeah, I've been
to Edinburgh. Ed No, no, no, no, no.
Edinburgh is the same as London because
I've been to Edinburgh. I've been to
Edinburgh and we was talking about this earlier.
Um, we was talking about this earlier as
well, bro. That Edinburgh has very
Londony vibes. It is very much like
London. Like, it's all built on money.
They're snobs. I don't think they said
they had boyfriends when I went there,
but it is it is Londonly. Yeah, I got
that vibe, too. But the good thing about
it is it's very much cheaper than London.
Double rum and coke, five quid. You
ain't getting that in London anywhere,
mate. But it it's good. I like Edinburgh
because it's it's nice and it's cheap.
But in terms of like the people, yeah,
it is very um touristy. There was
Americans. So obviously if you lived in
Scotland, it' probably be better to live
in Edinburgh than just go to Glasgow for
drinking. They were only like 40 minutes
apart in it. Not that I've been to go,
but I could imagine, you know, saying
similar to like places in London, England, you
know. Yeah, it's
it's it is good though cuz it's cheap,
but it is very Yeah, it's proper like
London. I I found that as well when I
went there and everywhere s cuz I
thought it was going to be a lot better
than it was. I found Newcastle was better than
Edinburgh. I thought, [ __ ] it.
Like I thought, [ __ ] it.
Uh, you know, you go to Scotland
drinking. It's known for drinkers.
Drinkers in Scotland. I'm going to have
a well of a time. It was good, but I
thought it was going to be
better. I literally went all the way
there to [ __ ] escort and come back.
That's why I ended up doing [ __ ] an
escort and then coming back. I remember
it. I remember exactly what happened.
Yeah, I'm probably going to go in Miami
in the summer. That's why I need to go
to the gym soon to build this body.
Man, we're going to have fun with this passport, lad.
Yeah, but the women there were very easy
because I've met Scottish women and
they're they're quite
easy here in
London. Tam the Celtic fan and he's
Scottish mate with a beard.
It was very [ __ ] tall. That's another thing with
Scotland. That's another thing with
Scotland. Their [ __ ] ceilings are
[ __ ] tall as
Yeah. Did you notice that when you was
in Scotland, Ben? They're [ __ ] Bro,
that ceiling was Oh my god,
man. Yeah. I couldn't live on a grand a
month, Ben. Who's going to pay for the
little stonies and baby Peter's baby
grows and the little nights
out? You know, I'd have to start selling Peter's pork
chops. No, that was in Newcastle. We're talking about Scotland.
Yeah. Yeah. They look very industrial as well.
Yeah, I should have, but I didn't really know the
volley. I'm doing a few countries this
year. We're doing America again. We're
doing Dubai and we're going to do Thailand as
well. I might go Amsterdam as well in the
summer with a friend. So yeah, we're
doing some fight [ __ ] this year, man.
[ __ ] got nicked. I know, bro. It was
bad. I know. It was mad. It was mad,
bro. No, you just booked the flights.
Yeah. Which is like
£500 and then No, it's not 2K for
flights, bro. Ant-Man went there once
was £900 and the other time was £500.
No, you can get indirect flights for £500.
And man went three times last year and
his last flight was £500. I think it was400 and
something. Yeah. And the hotel. Yeah.
But bro, all you need to really worry
about the flights. I get enough money,
you know. I don't that I'm
saying. Yeah. I got nicked the next day
and I went to Scotland for like two
hours then come
back. Oh, it's crazy. Is
it? Yeah. Was a crazy come back then.
I should have stayed another
night. Yeah, that's the one, Ben. Yeah,
bro. It's still cheaper than America,
though. America's going to cost like
[ __ ] four grand just for a week for one
person. [ __ ] grand a month,
eh? How can you live on a [ __ ] grand
a month? That's [ __ ] depressing,
bro. It's [ __ ] expensive. Living's
expensive, you know. [ __ ]
expensive. No, I've got money, but it's
I've got money. I've got like 2K, but
it's if I choose to go out and that,
it's going to dribble
away. No, not even that. It's just if I
was to go
out. And here's the thing. Yeah.
No, here's the thing as
well. Like I said, I had
£620 in one account.
Yeah. And um I got my passport on, got
my hair done, went for a few drinks. I
had 150 left. Mhm. Just that money.
Obviously, I've got other money, but I'm
saying so how can a grand a month do it?
Cuz Yeah. Okay. It was a one off, but
still. So the passport was like £88
something. Haircut was 35. Drinking. I
swear down I had about 150
left and I didn't even pay any bills as
well. Yeah. It's funny, bro.
Yeah. See, I get over three grand a
month, Ben. And I find the money still
can go very
fast. Over three grand a month. And I
could still go very fast. And I don't
have a rent or
anything. Maybe because I had to do my
passport this month or
something and I haven't really carried
much over from the second month. But
yeah, maybe maybe that's why.
Yeah, that's like [ __ ] three times
the amount, bro. You
know, no. Uh-uh. No, Ben. I got um I
tell you that £300 I lost was a loan.
That was an extra £300 from a loan. So,
out of my own
money this month, I've probably gambled
about 50 quid, 60 quid out of my own
money, which is over three grand because
that £300 was a
loan. So, it was like an extra bit of
money. So, that weren't even out of my
actual own money. That's what I'm trying to
say. But yeah, probably was Frankie from
like the last month gambling like 600.
If you stay away from it for a month
now, you've only lost 50 pound. You'll probably
think you seem to have a lot of money next
month. I've still got money. I've still
got like two grand in that. But I'm just
saying, you know, going out in London's expensive, so
yeah. Yeah. Tom went to [Music]
um university in
Edinburgh, he said.
Ben, he's a
[ __ ] That's what he's a [ __ ] [ __ ] [Music]
had to stop some gas electric up 50 as
well. Yeah, but I think you hit the nail
on the head. I think it's my
race, Ben. I think it's my race.
Defo cuz I've never been with a
white woman like proper white I don't
think I think I have once actually but
yeah they've they've either been Italian Colombian or
yeah maybe I'll just go out approaching
people that look like me. That's one
thing I still have not
tried. Oh yeah, she was American white.
I mean, she sucked my dick, but I mean,
yeah, she was she was freckled and white
with blue eyes, but
yeah, I fingered only anyway, and she sucked my
dick. It was a
madness. But I found my daddy all along.
He's in Scotland,
Samuel. Tam, my
dada. So, USA is my mommy and Tam's my
dada. Oh, what a lovely combination.
Yeah, it is hard.
Yeah. Yeah. I think it's my race. I
definitely think it is. as well.
Yeah. But what I'm saying, Ben, do you
reckon if I lived in Glasgow for all
these years, 27 years, looking the way I
did, you would have found someone there?
Yeah, I think you would have found
someone there. Defo, because there's
less competition there. That's another
thing people don't understand with
London. They seem to think, "Oh, yeah,
London's easy because there's loads of
people, but there's also loads of
competition." This is what people don't
understand. You know, when you go to
places like Newcastle
or Scotland or somewhere else with a
smaller population, they can't be picky
because they don't have many options
there. Do you
understand? You know, when you go and
you approach someone in London, 2
seconds later, someone else is doing it
or they beat you to it. that will never
happen out of
London. So that's a that's a major
factor as well is is is the
competition. But people don't understand
like it's like when you go to Newcastle,
there's probably like four women to one
man. In London, it's about [ __ ] six
man men to one woman. So that's another
thing. People think London is easier cuz
there's more people, but it isn't. It
[ __ ] isn't, bro. Trust me, London has
type. Yeah, you would definitely if you
live somewhere like Scotland
or for long enough. I'm not saying
you're going to go there one day and
then you're going to find someone, but
if you l if you lived there long
enough, you would have found someone
somewhere over London. But I'm telling
you cuz it's probably semi difficult for
white people as
well. And obviously I'm not [ __ ]
white like or I don't look white. You
know what I mean?
Yeah. Now I'm just sick of these women,
Ben. You know, I went out on Friday. I
got a few
numbers. They messaged back and then
stop me. Well, the bartender messaged
back. I was talking to her earlier,
but yeah, she said she'll meet me next
week. Well, we'll see, won't we? But yeah,
man. It's [ __ ] isn't
it? Yeah. Madness, isn't it?
I love that. That's
cute. Yeah, they were white.
Yeah, they were white. Of course they
were. I'm a
Welsh. I think that the other day was
the first time I actually skit I kissed a Scottish
woman. No, it's not actually. I kissed
one a few years ago from Edinburgh
actually, but they were from London. And
they kept saying I said, "Why don't we
meet up?" She's like, "Oh, I'm in
Scotland." And I was like, "I'm in
Scotland now." I didn't go for her
obviously, but I messaged her. I said,
"Well, I'm in." She said, "I'm in
Scotland, buddy." I said, "I'm in your
country now. Why don't you come
out?" But no, I have actually kissed one
actually before, but that was few years
ago. But yeah, I've only kissed two actually. Wow.
It does matter if I look foreign because
they probably kiss me because they're
drunk, but the next day they don't
reply. The foreign ones have
replied. They're the ones that have met
me. Albanian, Brazilian, Portuguese,
Syrian. They're the ones that have
actually met me sober. So, it does
matter, bro. Because anyone can kiss
anyone. That doesn't really mean anything. you
know. Yeah. Does that make
sense? I tell you the worst city to fall is is
Manchester. I would say Manchester is harder than
London. Yeah, Manchester is harder than
Definitely. I like Manchester, but it's
not the place to pull. I don't
reckon the It's another thing that gives
me London vibes, bro. It gives me London
vibes. It's a smaller London with [ __ ]
transport. I like it. I do like
Manchester cuz I know some people there
and that, but in terms of like pulling, nah.
What would baby Peter from Scotland look
like, Samuel? With his little stone
island baby growing his little kilt. Oh,
what a lovely
sight. That's a lovely sight. Imagine
that, Ben. His little kil in his little
pipe. That's funny.
Yeah. Yeah. Sean's never been to another
country or even Scotland because he's
skinn. That's just cuz he's skinned it.
Like that just
happens. I'd call a baby Tam
Junior. Tam Junior.
some junior in
it. His friend was like a big guy with a
beard and a hat. I wonder how they met,
Samuel. How weird is
that? Wonder how they met. H.
Yeah. You want to
[ __ ] ground up?
What do you think of that Samuel grand a
month? Yeah. But the thing that pissed
me off yesterday was how
like I was saying it's
rigged. No, his friend was actually
being all right. He said we got to get off now. Yeah.
You said enjoy your
trip. Them Celtic [ __ ] were laughing at
us. That's why that's why I had to
[ __ ] send another message, mate. Them
Celtic [ __ ] were laughing at
us. Them Celtic [ __ ] were laughing at us, man.
Yeah. And I just [ __ ]
snapped. I just [ __ ] snapped.
Ben, I don't know how I'm ever going to
find him realistically. He doesn't have
Facebook. Imagine just going to the city
center and he comes out.
But yeah, I hate it how like the dating
app dating game is rigged against men. I
hate it, bro. How women can just get in
and out of relationships and get sex
whenever they want. I hate it, bro. I
it. I hate how they don't suffer like
us. I really [ __ ] hate it, bro. That
pisses me right off.
Yeah, his friend was actually all right
though to be
fair. It It could have got dirty though.
It was It might have turned into a punchup. You
know, he was squinting his eyes at
me. Ah, you in your little ways. Yeah.
I love it,
bro. No, I'm going to find this time,
bro. Like, we could bury the hatchet
over a nice good oldfashioned piss up in
Glasgow. How does that sound, Samuel? A
good oldfashioned piss up on me.
H, a good oldfashioned piss
up. And I remember his WhatsApp
emoji. His WhatsApp emoji was a Scottish
flag. I'm going to find this gun, bro.
Watch. Come on, McDonald's. What's
taking you so long? [Laughter]
He was being a
[ __ ] Was he being a [ __ ]
I'm going to come off.
Yeah, I just said to him, "What's your
fuck?" I just said to him like, "What's
your problem?" I didn't start cursing
that. And he said, "In good faith, I
think you need to talk some things
through to a
psychiatrist." Then he blocked
me. I should have just messed him normally in
it. I don't like the way he was
squinting his eyes at me and being a [ __ ]
who was just trying to be a
[ __ ] and it's like he's in a
relationship so he doesn't know what
it's like to deal with women. That's
what was the problem is like you you're
not in my shoes mate. You live in
[ __ ] Glasgow where everyone's
probably [ __ ] friendly. Yeah. You
probably been in a relationship for
about [ __ ] 15 years. Respectfully,
what would you
know? So before like buttoning your
[ __ ] have some [ __ ] sympathy, you know, that's
over. Yeah, his friend had a cap on and
beard. What do you reckon the chances of
finding this? Uh,
Samuel, I was actually going to go there
and call him out, bro. When I had his
number, I was going to go there and call him out.
Oh, no. He was slim. He was slim.
What do you reckon the chances of finding
him? I'm trying to see if I've got that number
anywhere. I've looked at my friend. I've
not sent it to him either.
Yeah. So Sammy, why can't Sean um go
abroad and get Stone Island and that?
Why can't he get these things?
M. So I don't have either of my parents.
Tam my is my daddy who left me and my
mommy in America abandoned me.
So I'm pretty much an orphan. I don't have a
family. Why do you think I don't see
Elaine anymore? I've been adopted by a new
family. I've been adopted by a new family, lad. That's my
mama and that's my daddy in Scotland.
I've got I've got Scottish in me. You
see? You reckon I'll find this
[ __ ] I don't know how you're going to find them.
I'll try my
best. There's something to do with it. Yeah.
Yes. I'm going to knock his [ __ ]
bullets in. That's what I'm going to
do. I'm going to be like I'm in guard
guy. All right, you little [ __ ]
I mean, the population is only 600,000
and something. It can't be that hard to find this
[ __ ] See, London is 9 million. You
know, if if they're in London, you got
no chance. But Glasgow, you you have a
chance just like that, you know. Bye-bye, weirdo.
Uh, it's like that woman in America. I
couldn't find her for the life of me. I
had to give up in the end. I was never
going to find her cuz I think I forgot
what state she lived in and I didn't know her
name cuz I think it was it weren't
Massachusetts. I think it was Missouri
she lived in. So you got a whole state,
millions of people. I don't know her
name. You're not finding them, mate. Had
to have bought it in the end. But with
this Tam, I'm sure there's a good chance of finding him. Yeah. [Music]
What do you reckon the chances of firing him? Samuel
5050. Defend said that he's got a misses
in in Madrid.
That doesn't even make any sense. So,
you live in Scotland, but you got a Mrs.
Spain. That doesn't make no sense,
bro. Yeah, but she doesn't know him cuz
she lives in Edinburgh. He doesn't live
Edinburgh. Yeah. Going to Scotland to find Tam. Yeah.
Yeah, I feel probably ghost, isn't
it? Yeah, we was talking about I was
talking to Tom's friend about the three
Scottish people with Tourette's. Well,
two of them were
Scottish. He was like Johnny Davidson.
Oh, bro, that was mad funny. Do you
remember them three people with
Tourette's? And then me being Scottish
made it funny as well. Oh, that was funny,
bro. And it was Scottish as well. Two of
them were Scottish.
Remember? Chopper Daisy's pubes. Ginger. Remember
that? That was ace,
bro. Right. My food's here. One second.
Be right back. 58 56
56 58 56
Which what what Sean are you talking about? [Music] The virgin one.
Imagine we couldn't find USA Izzy Samuel. Like
imagine imagine we could never find USA
Izzy and she was another one who got
away. We didn't get her number or her name or
anything. That would be taking a baby
away from its mama.
taking a baby away from his mama, [Music]
man. I'm saying
Well, I'm going to go and watch some
money and then
um find this tang guy
hopefully. He's such a virgin.
Yeah. Well, Snapchat. Yeah. I couldn't
find I can't find Tam
man. His number must not be linked to
his Facebook cuz I found most people
else but him.
Um, that's how I found some other
people. So, when my phone got nicked,
the number was still connected to my
Facebook. So, all the numbers I lost. I
just messaged them on
Facebook or Instagram. I can't find this [ __ ] Tam,
bro. Where you going, Tam? He's probably
so bad ranting around Samuel.
Samuel, you've been stalking me for over
a [ __ ] year and a
half. If he's not on Facebook, mate, we're
[ __ ] We can't find him then. I know
he's got Instagram cuz he told me he had
Instagram, but yeah, we're
[ __ ] If you don't have Facebook, then we're screwed. Never [ __ ]
them. I've been trying to find the
Scottish guy for the past [ __ ] two
hours, mate. I can't find
him. That's my
dada. That's my daddy.
dada. So, I don't have any parents now
because my mommy and daddy left me. Sucks. Brian Sta.
Huh? I've got two grand left. That needs
to last me, bro. Two grand. You reckon
two grand can last?
Greasy? Yeah, but what if his
Instagram's not Tam? That's what I'm
trying to say. If his Instagram's not
[ __ ] Tam, then we're [ __ ] We're never finding
him. We're going on Edinburgh Edinburgh
University. Um cuz that's my
daddy. Cuz I've got Scottish in me, you
see. Even though I cuz I'm wondering
where the Scottish heritage come from.
Um Grezy, I'm wondering where the
Scottish heritage come from.
I knew my grandma had Scottish, you
know, cuz I've got Scottish in me and I
don't know where that come
from. So, they're my parents. Yeah. Yeah.
Nope. I lost his number. He's got my
number. No, I don't.
No. Well, tough [ __ ] I want to speak to
him cuz he's my
daddy. Well, I want to speak to him.
Tough [ __ ] and what I what I say
happens. I just want to know that he's
safe. I just want to know my daddy's
safe, you know.
Samuel, does that not annoy you though,
Grezy? How easy women have the dating
game? That [ __ ] pisses me right off.
does. Yeah, I don't think I'd ever find him again. Impossible, bro.
Impossible. But yeah, lad.
Yeah. Anyways, that's that's what annoys
me. How easy they have the dating thing
busy. That's the [ __ ] that pisses me
off, bro. Not even this
situation. They get given everything in
life just for having a [ __ ] [Music]
Do you think two grand will last,
Samuel? What do you reckon, Greasy? Do
you reckon two grand will
last? I become obsessed with everyone I
meet. No, just my mommy and
dada. Two grand should last a little
while, ain't it,
Greasy? I paid all my bills,
so we're not doing Frankie again this
year month. We're saving some money up, bro.
Yeah, only my mommy and da. Is that right, Grezy?
Yeah. Yeah. I was going boogieing, lad.
Yeah. So, out of that £750 Greavesy, how
much do you save a month?
I'm not in my late 20s. I'm actually
just past my
mid20s. So, I'm kind of still in the middle.
grand a month is [ __ ] [ __ ] mate. I
get over three grand a month and that's
just about enough for Peter
Belly, which I don't understand how it
is. Nah, it's not that good, bro.
It depends, is it? But I eat out and
that because I have no choice at the
minute, but who knows?
E should be able to save loads out three
grand a month.
But it isn't though, bro. Because I paid
Listen, I had 620,
right? I had 620.
done my passport, had a drink, done my
hair. I had 150 left and altogether I've
got like just under two grand. That can
go very easy,
bro. So, not
really. So, you still have to kind of
save for another month before you start
seeing it. You know, it takes sometimes
two months to build your money up, bro.
Even if you get [ __ ] like three
grand. It's hard to explain.
Um, what do I have to
pay? I don't pay rent. I stay with my
friend. Well, I pay £100 if that's what
you pass. So, £100. Then I've got my phone bill
and yeah, just my phone bill. So all of like 180.
Yeah. I know. Not much to pay out for,
but it still seems to go. The money
still seems to go. What's it going on,
bro? It's not going on [ __ ] gambling,
obviously. Because that we only gambled
extra money this month.
Yeah, I've got just under 2K 1.9 I
think. But I had to fork out for that
passport, didn't I?
So, and I did go out and I did go out
having a good old piss up.
So if I went out every week, I'd have no
money by like the third week,
basically. It is a lot of money.
Obviously, 1500 two grand is still a lot
of money, but I think it's where I'm
used to having thousands and [ __ ]
so you know what I mean. Yeah.
Yeah. You can drink that amount alone,
mate. When you're in London, you can.
You can in London. You really, really
can. You really can in London, mate. I
remember I went out one time. I think I
bought one person a drink where I spent
£250. You can, mate. Trust me. When
you're on a detox, you
can. And I bought food as well. Hold
on. You can, bro. You can. No, not not
like £400, but 250. You
can. You can, bro. And they were buying
me drinks as well. Well, one of the guy
was buying me drinks as well, and then
we was like sharing it. So, you
know, you can 250 you can. I've done it
before. I don't know where the [ __ ] the
money went. That 620, bro. Passport
hair. [ __ ] knows. [ __ ]
knows. But yeah, it went anyways.
So yeah, it was good times, bro. But the
madnesses have still not stopped. The
money's not dried out yet. So it's still
good, bro. It's still good.
Yep. There was one I was fingering in the
O'Neals. Good old O'Neal's time. Hey,
Samuel. Good old O'Neal.
Eh, isn't that right,
Zippy? Isn't that right, S? Yeah. Oh
yeah, you could go out every week and
save. You would just have to pre You
would just have to pre-drink.
you would just have to pre-drink and you
could probably spend about450
maybe. But the reason I didn't pre-drink
on last Friday is cuz I wanted to to
give it one last big hurrah before renewing the
passport. I wanted to give it one last
hurrah. before redoing the passport. One last Yeah,
bro. [ __ ] it out.
No, I haven't done that for a while to be honest.
No, I will be doing that when I go out
again, which I'm not going out for a
month. Like I
said, I need to go to gym tomorrow. I
really need juice to start going to this
gym if I'm going
[ __ ] Miami and [ __ ] bro. I want to
have that summertime body, you know what I mean?
or like any hot
place. We should just be done with the UK,
lad. But yeah, it's what Ben said. It
definitely is your
race. Definitely is your race. I was
thinking that as well. I was actually
having this conversation with my friend
cuz he looks tanned and people think he's from
Australia and he looks like proper white
and that whereas I don't.
I'd actually put my passport picture up,
but I look like a [ __ ] terrorist. So,
yeah. Yeah, that
Yep. So, we'll see if this bartender
meets me next week.
How much money do you think Tam has,
Samuel? Do you think Tam has a lot of
money? Well, I went to the Euros last
year, he told me.
Yeah, I'm coming to the
pub. I said to her, "Do you want £500?"
She replied straight away. I said, "How
about some kissing and holding hands and
that?" I don't
[ __ ] soon as I mentioned the £500. [Music] No, you
graduated. Yeah, I messaged that one on Instagram from
Brazil. She blocked me on everything. I
don't know why these women do that. I
don't know why they waste your time and
their time. They always know they're
going to block you in the
end. So why do
they why do they do it? I don't
understand why they why would they go
out with somebody and
and sort of kiss them or have sex with
them or do these things if they're just going
to just go cold after. I don't even know why they
even I think they do it to pass time.
That's what I think they do it to. They
do it to pause
time. You know what I mean? Is
it? Why they do it? I don't understand
some of you. Why they even do it like [Music]
A grand a
month. You're in a grand show.
Oh, I do have a I've got a phone bill
and I paid towards some gas and
electric. So, let's say £200. So,
yeah. So, yeah, man.
Still goes though, mate. It still goes.
Takeaways, drinking. It still
goes when you go
out. Still goes,
mate. Trust me. Even when you you're on
a higher amount, you'll
see. But this month should be a good
month when I get money again. Yeah.
So, how much are you left with at the
end of the the end of the month? [Music]
See, and I probably get more than you a
month cuz I don't even
work. And life's still depressing
without a sex
life. I think I get like 3.3K.
And life's still depressing without a
sex life. Could you imagine? I actually had to
work. I'm lucky, bro. I get to get that money and
and basically have most of it to do with
what I want with
it. But life's still
[ __ ] Life is still [ __ ] lad.
I never said I get it all on
benefits, but that's what I get. That's
what Rice said. He said that he gets it
on benefits. No, he [ __ ] doesn't.
Nope. But that's what I get, bro.
Believe it. Don't believe it. That's up to
you. Peter B. He's got his money making ways, lad.
But believe it or don't believe it, bro.
That's up to you.
Oh, but you don't get just on benefits.
No. Rice trying to say that he gets 2.9K
on benefits. No, you don't. No, you
[ __ ] don't, mate. Especially not in
Glasgow. He's talking
[ __ ] Yep. And I'm not going to tell you
them other ways cuz that's Peter Benny's little
secret. That's Peter Belly's little
secret. Why did I say secret?
Secret. Yeah, man. But that Reese does
not get 2.9K a month on
benefits. No way, mate.
But life is still [ __ ] without a woman,
bro. And sex and stuff. Yeah. Well,
uh, I'm not going to get into it. Yeah.
But I'm telling you how much I get.
Believe it or don't believe it, that's up to
you. I'm not going to get into it, bro.
I'm tired. Believe it, don't believe it,
that's on you, bro.
I'm not going to educate you on anything
or educate these people on anything. You
believe it or you don't, bro. That's up to you. Yeah.
That's up to you,
dad. Cuz guy on YouTube used to get 40k a month,
Samuel. 40k a month. [ __ ] hell, bro.
Imagine that. 40k a month. E
Bro, I'm not educating you on anything.
I'm done with the I'm done with the convo,
lad. I'm done with it now. I'm not
talking about it no more.
Yeah. I'm not educating. I'm not
incriminating myself. I'm not
nothing. Yeah. I wasn't born
yesterday. I wish I made 40k a month on
YouTube. Yeah. Well, never your mind,
bro. I've got my ways, don't I? So
that's all you need to know,
lad. [ __ ] 40 grand a
month. 40 grand a month. Do you think he
was chatting [ __ ] when he said that he
was earning 40 grand a month on YouTube?
He had like a million
subscribers. Do you believe it,
Chris? £40,000 a
month. [ __ ] me. [ __ ] me,
mate. That's a lot of money a month
now. 40 grand a month. He's got no
savings. He's an idiot. He has no
savings. He doesn't get that anymore.
You should have invested, man. He was
making 40 grand a month. Yeah, you could
have easily invested.
But that's a lot of money a month
now. What the [ __ ] 40 grand. Wow.
Do you know who the side men are,
Chris? Do you know who the side men
are? You might not know who they are. side
man. Yeah, they used to be good. Now they're
boring. There is no point in
life. I don't even see my mom anymore.
She messages me at that, but I just
never see her. I just don't go around there,
man. Yeah, they are [ __ ] boring, bro.
I like the smaller
channels. I think they've got a more of
a point to prove. I like smaller
channels than bigger
channels for various different
reasons. There's this guy called Wendell
and he's got like 127,000 subs. He goes
around like America and different
places. It's quite uh educational. Uh yeah,
December, just before Christmas.
Yeah, I can go there anytime with that.
I just haven't bothered, bro. I just on
my own life, you know. Yeah.
I mean, Peter Bell is independent nowadays. Eh, old
school. I'm old school, lad. link.
Yep. I do everything
myself. I clean kitchens and [ __ ] So I
know I don't
need No, I didn't have to
leave. But I got kicked out be well
before all the
posters. And actually, no, I left
because of the gambling and just shouting and
[ __ ] So, it was all like different things, you know. Hello.
Hi. Who's this? I'm me.
Okay. Who's me? Just die. Hey,
just I I'm just me. How are you?
Never never heard of you. Yeah, it's good. Yeah. Yeah.
Are you a [ __ ]
Well, some people would call me that. Yes.
But I take it as
Are you a [ __ ] No. You're not?
No. You're really not a [ __ ] Yeah. Really?
I doubt that. I don't think you are to
be fair. Where are you from?
I'm from Birmingham, bro.
Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You got to
have a Brummy accent.
That's cuz I'm posh.
Okay. Yeah. Yeah.
That's nice. That's nice. Yeah. That's
So, how did you find my channel?
Well, it just came up on my
um what do you call it? like when you do
the shorts and it just came up. I don't
know. Sorry. I'm not really techsavvy. Okay. So, what
what are you doing tomorrow?
Well, what you doing tomorrow?
Probably staying in bed. Yeah. Are you ready?
Why didn't you come out and meet
me? Come and meet you. I'm all right. I
don't like Birmingham.
You don't like Birmingham?
No. Oh, that's a shame. It's quite a
scary place to be.
Yeah, it is quite scary to be
fair. I mean, I wouldn't go out in
Birmingham if I didn't have to.
But sometimes you can't out
I just go to like random like venues and [ __ ]
Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to the
West Midlands um soon. I'm going to Blackpool,
right? So you're going to Blackpool on when?
Uh next week. Oh, next week. What date?
Like what? Um Friday.
Friday. I know that's that's that's near
Birmingham. You could come up. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Well, it's really fun talking to you.
So, are you going to come or I'll come
to I love Birmingham. No. Blackpool.
Blackpool. Blackpool. Yeah. Blackpool.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm not. No, seriously. Do you want to
come next week? I'll come to Blackpool.
Are you paying? Yeah. It's not far from
Birmingham, is it? Well, yeah,
it's it's far. It's far enough. I
thought it was only up the road. No, no,
no. It's far enough to be fair, but you know.
No, it's only up the road. Don't be silly.
What? What makes you say it's far?
Well, it's like far.
What? Up the road. Yeah.
Oh, well, just just just come next Friday,
eh? Well, I'll trust you. Okay.
You good anyway? Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, fine.
Yeah. Just chilling.
Yeah. Good. Good. Good. Good. Just
recovered from a hangover. I went out on
Friday. Got smashed. Oh, did you really?
Yeah. Yeah. I just came across your
channel. Like it just came like on
um Yeah. I just came across. How old are
you? How old am I? I'm old enough, bro. How old? 38.
Oh, okay. That's That's all right.
So, what part of you live? Huh?
I was trying to find
Tam Steven Howard from Glasgow again,
but I still can't find a [ __ ]
Here. I don't know what you want to buy. I'm sorry.
I said, "Where in Birmingham do you live?"
Oh, um by um the B rang not far from
there. Yeah. Oh, okay. You sort of
basically the city center.
Yeah, pretty much. Yeah.
Oh, fair enough.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's good. So, you Muslim?
H how can I go on a Celtic film? There
the the the Celtic form. There's so many
[ __ ] There's so many Tams in Scotland,
bro. I went to the Edinburgh University
trying to find the TAM.
I could go on a Celtic football team on
Instagram. I'll be worth a
while. USA is my mommy and Tam's my
dada. Steven Howard, they're my
parents. Taking a baby away from its mama.
taking a baby away from its
mama. There, that's my mom and that's my
dad. And they both told me that I need help.
So that's my real family, you know. Yeah.
That's why they disappear cuz they
didn't want me finding out that they're my
parents. Do you remember the first time
I said that to Steven
Howard? Taking a baby away from its
mama. That was so funny. The first time
I said it in it, Steven Howard
taking a baby away from its
mama in it, bro. The first
time taking a baby away from his
mama. That was slow age,
bro. Everyone copy me in
it. Yeah. Go on a Celtic form. I reckon
you can find him on a Celtic form. Yeah.
taking the baby away from his
mama. Is that why I cried? Steven Howard. Hello. [Music]
You all right?
Can you hear me?
Apparently a mongaloid has been left in
charge of a baby.
What? I hate women.
What's your opinion on that?
Oh, hi PJ,
huh? Uh, you PJ? Yeah.
I actually quite like you.
Do you like me? You don't know me. Well, yeah,
whatever. Get over yourself, bro.
How can you like someone you don't know?
Well, how can you like fall in love with
somebody that lives across the Atlantic
that you want to stalk?
Um, because they gave me their booby
milk and they left me without nutrition
when they left me.
But it makes any sense, does it? Really?
Of course it makes sense. is taking a
baby away from its
mama. How does that not make sense? That makes perfect sense. Yeah. She's
gone. [ __ ] her.
I hate women come
Joe Tman USA is he's my my parents and it's Steven
Howard I don't know who it is heat. That's my
mama. He's already found his
mama. Yeah. Why? I said to him, "Why did
you even have me if you were just going
to abandon me?
Why have me if you didn't want me? It's
the same with
Tan. Why have a child if you don't want the
child? It makes no sense.
Huh? Doesn't make any sense.
Do you remember USA is
Steven? Good times, eh?
Yeah, I'm Tom. That's my daddy. My d?
Yeah. And his friend had a tap on with a
beard. Like um one of them caps with a
beard. They looked nothing like each
other. I wonder how they met Samuel.
Tamy's mate. His mate was all right, but
he was a
[ __ ] A beard and a cap.
Yeah, it was strange, bro.
It live in Glasgow now having fun without
me in it, Samuel.
Yeah, that woman in America I couldn't
find like [ __ ] four years ago. It
pissed me off,
bro. I couldn't find her,
mate. The one that Sean kept stalking
four years ago. Hello.
You okay? Are you okay? Yeah.
Well, that's all that matters.
Maybe when we meet up we can maybe I
don't know make love.
I Well, maybe really.
Are you up for that? Yeah.
But if I give
consent or not concerned?
What did you say? If I say it's like not consensual,
well, you would have to let me know.
So, what's the safe word then?
Just say Yeah.
Yeah. Is that okay with you, boss?
You're calling me boss. I thought you
were the boss.
Yeah, I am.
I know you're a troll.
You know I'm a troll. Yeah. How?
Just guessing. So, what color are you? White.
I am white. Yes.
Are you fat? No. Really? Really? Yes. [Music]
I'm stinking. Yes.
I' I've never claimed to be anything
other but but
you're stinking. Well, how bad is it?
Not that bad. Okay.
Not bad enough that you
know you find yourself on here with me anyway.
Are you drinking? Yeah. you.
Nah, you're drinking on a
[ __ ] Tuesday morning. A [ __ ]
Monday night. Say Monday cuz it's it's
just turned. Well, I had a day off.
Okay, for [ __ ] sake. I'm allowed to
have a drink on a day off.
Do you know Tradal? Who? Tradal.
I don't know what you mean. I'm sorry.
You know, Lord J,
I literally came across you in my um
thingies. You know, when [Music] What? Interesting.
Kick me. Kick me. I don't care. Have you
got any kids?
No, I have no kids.
Yeah. I push nothing out of my
funny. I bet that makes it feel better
for you, doesn't it? Like, you know, I
mean, I pushed nothing out of my funny.
When was the last time you gave a [ __ ] Oh
gosh, now you're asking. I don't even
remember. I don't like keep track on
things like that.
Yeah. Like when was the last when was
the last time you gave a
[ __ ] PJ? Come on. Well, I never gave a [ __ ] Exactly.
Why would I give a [ __ ] when I'm not gay?
Well, I don't know. People do weird
[ __ ] don't they? No.
When was the last time you had sex?
I probably four months ago.
[ __ ] How do you lost?
Cuz I'm not a rampant little rabbit like oneself.
I think it's I think it's impossible to
live without sex. Me you.
Well, it kind of like is, but it isn't.
Like I I think you I think you'll
survive without it. I mean, like, is
there the possibility that you could
possibly go out and shoot up a school
because you haven't had sex?
Potentially. Like, do you know what I
mean? I'm not going to lie.
Yeah, that's my logic.
Yeah, I agree. Yeah, you agree.
I'm evil. I'm evil. Yeah, I'm
evil. Okay. No night. You are. Yeah. No
night, PJ. Love you. Huh? Love you. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I know you love me. Hello. Hello.
Who's this? Natalie Nat's karaoke channel.
Oh, I think I've spoken to you before. I
thought you I've thought I heard your
voice. Sound a bit like lemons.
I sound like Lemons. Yeah, you know
Lemon Drops. Yeah, the guy that don't
leave his house. Yeah, you sound a bit like him.
Where are you from? Um, Nottingham.
Oh, nice. I've been to Nottingham a few
times, actually. By the way, Rock City.
Oh, and Rock City. Rock City. Yes, Rock
City is very Oh.
Um, do you know Sean PJ? Yes.
Yes. Well, he actually quite fancies
you, by the way. Yeah, I know. He He's
been stalking me for years, man. It's
just one of them things, is
it? Yeah. What account do you normally
use, Nat? I don't think I've spoke to you before.
Um, batty natty. I'm using my It should
say um slippy goggle goggles, but yeah,
I misspelled it
wrong. I made a channel so nobody could
find me cuz I was God bless
you. Bye PJ. Can you hear me?
Yeah. Yeah. End of the day, you're a
woman abusing that's a [ __ ] rat that
likes to [ __ ] abuse and pray on other
vulnerable women. And yeah, English, please.
You You will be gone. Hello, cheeky
monkey. Hi, cheeky monkey. Hi. Yeah. Oh
my god. You can't even get your words
out. You're that drunk.
I'm not drunk. I've been sober for 23
years. No, not you. Her
I like her fuzzy hair.
Who's fuzzy? Mine. Yeah,
it's cur. It's meant to be curly. It's a
bit dry today.
That's all right. That's all right.
You got any plans for um tomorrow?
Just meeting up with a few people.
Oh, bless you.
I think I'm just going to chill to be fair.
Yeah, Rock City is a good nightclub, but
I think we're too old to go there now.
Well, it's it's gone a bit downhill. It
used to be all rock music and now it's
they play 70s nights and Yeah. The last
time I went to Nottingham was I think it
was last a I think it was last April
last May and I I got a um yeah one night stand.
Oh right. That's the last time I went.
You got a message in the back.
People saying that you could be my new mama.
It's tram. Tram is in the back.
You're not let you're not coming in TR.
You're boring as [ __ ] bro.
He ruins everything.
Sends letters to people's neighbors um
trying to get people killed and [ __ ]
I don't think he really wants to do
that. He's already done it. Oh, has he?
Okay. Yeah, he's a [ __ ] He's a
horrible old [ __ ]
Oh, I just think he's joking sometimes. So,
um, how old are you anyways? 42.
You're old then, are you? Well, I'm quite
old. 42 is nearly 50.
I think you're old when
you're 50. 50. 55. I think you're old.
Well, I've got eight years to go. There you go.
I know a girl who's called Sunflower.
Her name's D and she's over 50 and she
looks she looks younger than me.
What happened to that Sunshine from
Manchester? Does anyone remember her?
Never heard. Used to be You remember her
in it, Steven Howard. Her name was
Sunshine. She was from Manchester. We're
going back like four years ago. I wonder
what happened to her. Strange. You used
to be on this um community. Yeah,
I haven't been in this community that long.
It's the worst community you could ever
have come across. What do you think of
King of Belfast?
I think he's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
You think he loves himself?
Yeah. Are you okay? You seem like you're
you you're crying. Are you all right?
No, I'm not crying. I'm just I'm very
I'm detoxing. I've been 23 days off alcohol.
Oh, so you was you an alcoholic? Yes. Okay.
And now I'm clean.
Yeah, that's good.
Every time I go out drinking, I I get
hung over for like 3 days, man. It takes
me like three days to get over it. It's bad.
The cheeky monkey is still here. It's
still a chicken cake. No, she left. All right.
Yeah, drinking is just
bad. It will kill you. That will Yeah, I
saw you. I've only just subscribed to your channel.
Yeah, we basically do
um damning videos, approaching women
videos and stuff and yeah, it's just
that kind of stuff. Oh yeah.
Oh, Sunshine still trolls Timmy. Oh,
I've never heard of it. Yeah.
So, do you know about my main channel? No.
Link in the the private chat or
something or in the public chat. Yeah,
I've just got over a thousand subs now
on my channel, so I've got reason to
celebrate. The trolls are upset because
they tried to take me down. and they
didn't. I've had
not all the trolls. Some of the trolls are
supportive. I get good ones and bad one
bad ones. The good ones are okay
and very supportive. So, I've got kind of
like a safety net. Yeah. Yeah.
I have a lot of good friends around me
that support me.
Have you ever been Have you ever been to Blackpool?
Um, not since I was 16 years old. So,
it's been years.
Yeah. I've never been.
Yes. When I went I went went in this
hotel and it was a bit shitty.
I was thinking maybe we could go to
Blackpool and go to Coral Island. Coral Island?
Yeah. It's a casino.
Oh, right. I don't really gamble and I'm
married. No, you could just watch me
gamble. Yeah, but I'm married, darling.
Yeah, we could just be friends, you
know. Oh, there's nothing nothing wrong
with that. Yeah,
it's not it's not too far from you, you know. Seriously. Oh [ __ ]
Go do a club. Not is PJ. Say again. Why
are you religious?
No, I'm atheist. Oh,
what are you? Um, I believe there's
God, but I don't know. Are you a pork lover?
Um, I like pork. Yes.
Yeah, same. I'm not Muslim.
Yeah, I'm I'm atheist. Yeah. So,
I've always been spiritual into spiritualist beliefs. Yeah.
Yeah. I used to have a Ouija board.
Yeah. Yeah. I bought one because I
always wanted to try one.
and tarot cards. [Music]
I used to give myself tarot readings.
You look like you're really um struggling.
No, no. I'm
just It's It's probably the medication
I'm on. Yeah. Well, what are you on? Coconut?
No. Anti anti-abuse. It's um this fuller
I can't pronounce the word this
full can't pronounce
it like that. It's like basically
anti-abuse. It like if I have a drink
it'll make me very ill. Yeah.
Yeah, stay away from that alcohol. It's
evil, man. I don't know about you, but
whenever I used to drink, I used to get
really depressed the next day.
Yeah, it's it's a depressing. That's why.
Yeah, it's all right going out and
having fun doing it, but you have to pay
for it a couple of days afterwards.
Yeah. Hangovers, feeling thick.
It's a shame cheeky monkey left. Yeah,
cheeky monkey coming back up. Yeah, come
back. Let's go sleep. I'm [ __ ] knackered.
Have you ever been to Glasgow?
Probably. I've been to Edinburgh.
Yeah, I've been to Edinburgh, but not
Glasgow. Did you like it?
Yeah, it's pretty all right. They have
nice hotels up there. Yeah, they do. I
stayed in a nice one. Yeah, it was good. Big rooms.
Big ceilings as well.
Yeah, high ceilings. Yeah.
Oh, are you in your little N accent?
Oh, do I sound like I've got an accent
to you? Um, a little bit.
Yeah, I remember when I first went to
Nottingham the first time and I was
hearing these people talking. They were
like, "Hey, up duck." You sound a bit of London.
Yeah, I'm from London.
Yeah, that's what I thought. London.
Do you ever use that dialect a up duck?
Yes. A bless you. I use darling as well.
Darling. Yeah. Yeah. That's normal.
That's like what what what a lot of
people say, you know.
Well, as you can tell, my voice is a bit Yeah.
at the moment. But I used to do karaoke
on my channel, so that's what I did on
my channel. Oh, nice. So, I'm going to
wait till my throat is better.
I can do karaoke. You You know Cosmic Kitty?
Um, yes. Yes. She doesn't live too far
from me, does she? No.
No. I know Becky Docks as well. She
lives even closer to me.
Let me ask you this question because you
would know. What's the difference?
Because I don't know. What's the
difference between a noting accent and a
lesser accent? Is there Can you tell the
difference? Not much. No.
That's what I thought. Yeah. Not much. Right.
The worst accent in the UK is the
Birmingham one, I reckon. What do you think?
What the Brmy accent? Yeah, it's [ __ ]
annoying. That is God, that's [ __ ]
Glasgow can be quite hard to understand
as well. Which one? Welsh. And Welsh.
Oh, yeah. Welsh. Like when it's outside
Cardiff. Yeah, that can be annoying.
Yeah. Do you know somebody called Rice?
Yep. He lives in
He's got a Welsh accent, hasn't he?
Yeah. It's [ __ ] bad, is he?
from my channel cuz he rerses you.
Yeah. And the Belffor one's bad, too.
Yeah. He's a bit of a knob. He turned
nasty on me because I wouldn't go out
for a drink with him. I didn't say yes.
Say again. He went nasty on me because I
didn't say yes to going out for a drink with him.
No. King of Belfast. Yeah, he's King of
Belfast is just um he's just a s. He
just he does it to every single woman he
can talk to on this community. He tries
like licking their ass to to get with
them. It's quite pathetic really. Yeah,
he's a pathetic.
I think he's a god.
What do you rate um LJ King out of 10 a two? [Laughter]
Oh, I don't like face tattoos. I don't
like I don't think a ginger hair should
be a baldheaded person. Would you rate
me out of 10?
Well, I gave you a higher score than B
house once. He asked me and I gave you
Yeah. And he probably put the worst
picture up of me as well. Yeah.
Yeah. That's me.
Oh, was that your girlfriend?
No, it was just some vacation fling. Oh,
yeah. You got quite broad shoulders in
you. Broad shoulders. You do weight
liifting? Yeah. Huh? Do you do weights?
No, I haven't been to the gym for ages
to be fair.
No, I just come back to it to be fair. Is
Muhammad? Can't even say that.
That's weird. He asked you out for a
drink when he doesn't even live in
[ __ ] England. That is pathetic, man.
He was on about coming over to see me
and Becky. God, he's such a sad bastard.
I know. Imagine going all the way from Ireland.
That's crazy, bro. Meet women.
It's a bit sad, isn't it? Can't even
find one in
Is it really? Do you know in Nottingham?
Is it Is it Is the rent quite cheap?
Don't know. My My ass is about hundred over £100.
Uh well, a week. Yeah,
it's not too bad
then. Yeah, that is pretty sad. I have I
wouldn't go to another country to meet
someone I've never met before. That's
pretty pretty weird. I'd be scared to be
honest going in a different country. What period?
Like if I if like somebody offered to
pay for a holiday from for me from
England to the States, I always a bit
dubious about that.
Did you do it? No, I didn't.
Would you go to another country by yourself? No.
It just feels a bit weird.
And then when you come back, you got to
readjust as well. It's quite a brave
thing to do, eh?
Yes, it is a brave move. move.
Anything can happen to you, you know.
Do you get many people?
Not in bed. Don't know. I'm not tired. I
don't sleep early.
Yeah, I heard Cosmic Key almost had a
mental breakdown. She did. She's in
hospital, isn't she? Mental ward or something.
Was it all over YouTube?
A lot of people said, "I don't
know. I don't know much about it. I
stick to my own streams usually." Yeah.
I haven't hopped on many panels since
I've stopped drinking. Yeah.
Trying to keep away from
stress treat. Yeah. What What got you
into the drinking? Do you reckon
depression or did you like the way it
made you feel or what? I like the way it
made me feel.
Yeah. that you
and it gave me confidence braver.
Yeah, I get you.
You just make a fool of yourself when you're drunk. [Music]
M. It's fun when you're out listening to
music doing it, I guess. You know. Yeah.
Did you ever hit the city center and get
on a drink or not for years? No, I used
I used to drink at home.
Yeah. In the
warmth and done pub crawls in years.
Yeah. I'd always go out if I was to to
do it in it, you
know, trying to, you know, meet new
people and whatever.
I take it you get porn bombed a lot.
That's why you're very cautious with
your battle. Damn right.
Well, you have to come on mine sometime
and get used to my channel. Yeah, I'll
come. Yeah, you can get used to me. Then
you know I'm not going to porn bomb you.
Have you ever been to London?
Um, yes. Quite a few times I went to go
and see Kid Rock.
Yeah. Lots of lots of stuck up women in
here in London. Oh, is it? Yes. It's not
noise. They're [ __ ]
I'm not that sort of woman. Randy man.
Yeah. Stop being
perverted. There's so many perverted
people in this community, you know.
Yeah. It's like you can't talk to a male
being a woman like them. Yeah. They're
just jealous. Induendos. Yeah.
So, what's your channel called? Nati's
karaoke channel. Natty karaoke channel.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's easy.
Yes, I've never done karaoke before.
Should give it a go. Lots of people.
Good do. Yeah.
I don't just do karaoke. I play Jackbox games, too.
Yeah. And sometimes he wants to be a
millionaire. Um, Family Feud, words on
stream. Just try and find things to do
and I play music some streams.
Yeah. Well, I can't do karaoke at the
minute. I've been trying to figure out things to
do. I need to go sleep though. But I'll
be back on tomorrow definitely. And I'll
I'll check out your channel as well.
Yeah. Yeah. All right. Have a good rest
in a bit. Bye again.