Love this new charger, man. [ __ ]
Why do you never have any [ __ ] ammo
in a [ __ ] gun on GTA? I don't get it.
One second. I'm speaking to someone. Interesting.
Yeah, man. I got a good football bet on
for um Saturday, bro.
I decided like
not next week, maybe the week after I'm
going to get on the Guinness, man.
I was bored today. I had to do some
stuff. But yeah, I'm getting the
Guinness craving again.
I got a good football bet on.
I might go fabrics. I ain't been fabrics
for ages, man.
Might enjoy fabrics. I'm not sure.
Another thing I another thing I was
thinking of, bro, is maybe trying to get
that 19y old back. Well, she's actually 20 now.
I might try to get her back, but I'm not
going to lie. [Music]
I'm trying to think what we're going to do for
I'm not approaching every single day.
I'm not going out to approach. I'm going
out to drink.
I'm not interested.
And I'm not going to go out once a week.
I'm going to go out like once a month.
Once every twice a month, maybe.
No, [ __ ] that. I ain't I ain't doing
that, bro. I've tried enough.
No, I've tried enough.
I'm not interested, bro.
I'm not interested. I'm going out to
[ __ ] drink. I'm not interested.
Yeah, I know how it all works, bro. I
know it all works. I've been doing it
for four years. I get it. I know what
you're saying, but I'm not interested.
That's the whole point I'm trying to
make. I ain't interested just like they aren't. So
obviously if I was a virgin like virgin
boy then I would but no
who cares building momentum you can
[ __ ] go and do it bro you can go and
[ __ ] do it you know you can still do
it even if you feel uncomfortable it
doesn't mean anything
I'm not interested the game's dead here bro
I ain't interested I just want to Go and
get [ __ ] in that brewery place. Oh [ __ ]
Yeah, I ain't interested, bro.
You're the only fans one that used to come. Nicola,
if I weren't leaving the country and I
was a virgin and [ __ ] then obviously I
would do it every day. But it's a waste
of my time.
No, I only walked about 2 miles and walked back.
No, I don't think you understand. I'm
sure you obviously are trolling. I ain't interested.
I'll get her back. Don't worry, bro.
See, the thing is, right,
she's going to be [ __ ] though, cuz
she's going to want like she's going to
expect loads of money and I just don't
have it anymore like I used to be Joker.
So, she's probably still going to be
thinking that I can gamble all of this
money and win all of this money.
Obviously, I have more than enough money
and I'm not skin like Virgin Boy, but
you know, the money I used to spend when
I used to go out with her was ridiculous
and I just don't have it anymore.
You know what I mean? you give. But like
I can get the [ __ ] back, bro. Don't worry.
So I can get her back, bro. Don't worry. But yeah,
she's almost skinn virgin boy. [ __ ]
hell. I spent £140 today just walking up
the road. Had to pay someone. And I put
a football bet on. [ __ ] had to buy a
lead. £140 I spent today, bro. [ __ ]
just walking down the [ __ ] road. [ __ ] me.
That is a [ __ ] madness, bro.
But yeah, I'm going to get on the piss
at some point. It ain't going to be this
week. Even if the football bet wins, I'm
not doing it this week.
But yeah, I'll try. I [ __ ] get her back, bro.
I missed the [ __ ] and [ __ ]
There was there was these people I was
speaking to on social media and they're
like, "Oh, yeah, but you have to keep
trying." I said, "You do realize I've approached
about 4,000 people." I guess it's about
4,000 people. I I'm sure it's got to be
about 4,000 people. So it's like, yeah,
you need to really think about what
you're like doing. You know what I mean?
You need to think logically.
You're not approaching every day, bro.
You're not approaching every day. You
can barely do three or four sober
without hearing that [ __ ] I've got a
boyfriend [ __ ] You're not [ __ ]
If it worked, then I would do it, bro.
But I'm not interested. Um, I feel like
100 years old, bro. I'm not interested,
I ain't interested. But I I'd get But
I'd get back with that [ __ ] bro. 100%.
She She's been shown like a lot of money
and [ __ ] and you know, so she's not
going to be able to find somebody that
can. That's why she kept coming back to Peter Belly.
That's a lot of money to anyone, let
alone someone that age, you know, when
you're just winning spending 700 pound
on nights out. You know what I'm saying? Like it's
if you got it, bro, then you know,
good times e um
maybe. I don't know, bro. London's quite big, but
you probably see a few of them.
Yeah, probably. Probably. Yeah, depends.
Well, I do want to get on a piss at some point, bro.
I really want to starve myself from it
so I enjoy it more.
See, that's the that's the whole point.
cuz you're supposed to be going out to
to get [ __ ] which is what I'm doing.
I'm not going out to try because I can't
be bothered with it. Um, what's happening?
I don't know. Football bet for Saturday.
90 on the football
returns 324. So,
oh, Franklin smash his face. Go on. Oh,
now I got shot. Yeah.
So, maybe two weeks or something, bro. I
just want to go out and get [ __ ] I
don't want to try like Yeah.
No, I haven't won. It's for Saturday. I
thought there was football playing
today, but there isn't.
It's a double both teams to score. Nah,
it's not a no draw, bro. [ __ ] that.
I won't do them for a while. But even if
it wins us, I'm still not going to go
out Saturday. It's I'd rather just chill
at home and play some Franklin, bro.
And I'll just get [ __ ] in two weeks
because I want to go and get [ __ ]
Remember, it's all about breaking the cycle, Joe.
It's all about breaking the cycle.
I mean, yeah, but it's not the league
that I bet on. I mean, yeah. Yeah,
you could try every day for like another
5 years. You could try, but then what
happens if you're like 34, 35 and you
still ain't found somebody?
Yeah, I was younger back then, bro.
That's when I had hope back then. I used
to do a lot of crazy things, spending
7800 on a night out.
So, I'm just going to try and get that
19y old back.
Think I'm going to try and get her back.
if she doesn't come back to me first.
But you need to make sure you're going
out because you actually want to get
[ __ ] and not because you're trying to
get women because you're an idiot if
you're just going out to try and get
women because we know how we know how
the sad song always ends up
cuz think about it like this, Joe. Yeah.
You know how you were saying the I was
talking to a few people about this
earlier cuz I found them on these
approaching videos. You know how you say
the past don't dictate the future? Huh?
I bet people were saying that to me four
years ago before I tried the first time.
I bet you when I tried the first week,
two weeks and I was complaining when LT
told me to go out and drink and [ __ ] I
bet you them four years ago people's
telling you exactly the same thing as
they're still telling you now.
It doesn't matter madness. They're
probably telling you the same thing as
they were telling you back then
when you first started off.
Think about how mad that sounds.
Do you not know how mad that actually is?
I don't know. I'm not entirely sure, mate.
I'm not entirely sure when I'll go out
again. just can't be bothered with it, bro.
Always like I have a boyfriend, all that
[ __ ] I'm not sure, bro.
I need to really
really forget all of the [ __ ] that's
happened like with the bounces and [ __ ] Yeah,
but like I said, I'm not entirely I'm
not entirely sure, but I'm doing it.
It's been two weeks. Anyways,
it's more that you've had opportunities
and blew everyone. No, I didn't. I blew
everyone. Okay. Okay. Let's go through
every single opportunity. Right. USA
[ __ ] me over.
Um, she [ __ ] me over.
Even speaking to her friend the other
day was annoying me. It was It was going
to make me end up doing something, bro,
that I probably would have regretted.
But that's one of them. Then we have the
one that I went on the date with from
Italy. She was happy to hold hands and
flirt and then when I tried to kiss, she
didn't want to kiss after 3 hours. Okay,
strange. Um, there's been loads of dates
I've been on.
And they claim they don't feel the vibe
when I've done everything perfect.
So, I mean, no, not really, bro. Not really.
Yeah, but this is this is when it was
possible. I mean, but that's when it was
possible. It's not possible anymore.
Yeah, it's not possible anymore. You see,
but another thing you got to understand,
Nicolo, is that if you was to go on a
date with a woman now, it'd be
pointless. It's pointless you even
um it's pointless you even going on a
date with a woman. There's literally no
point you even going out with anyone.
Like, there's literally no point. Cuz
when I was speaking to USA's friends,
she's like, "Oh, yeah, she's she's she
he's she's gone out with guys and then
she's not like them." And I was like,
"Well, hold on a minute. One second." Right.
It goes to show you what multiple
people. So, at the end of the day, they
have this unrealistic expectation in
their head that remains unfulfilled.
And everyone that you meet is going to
have the same, they've got the same unrealistic expectations.
cuz I can tell you, oh [ __ ] dates that
I went on and I done perfect to a tea
and they still made excuses not to see
me again. So there was nothing I could
have done better
and they just make excuses. So
just full of time wasters as well.
That's another thing you need to, you know,
and dates are not expensive as well.
Dates are not cheap as well.
Yeah, I had a homemade curry today. But
but yeah, like I said, even even
speaking to USA Izzy's friend, the whole
thing was just annoying me. Like it was, bro,
it was annoying, bro. Cuz
all the reasons why you should give up,
but at the same time, I do want to go
out and have a drink. So, I mean, not
not this week. Not next week. But
I will, bro. Trust me, I will again.
But it doesn't matter. But now it's impossible.
Now it's impossible. The reading one was
a [ __ ] Wait, hold on. The Reden one.
The Red one was a [ __ ] was a [ __ ]
[ __ ] I just read that. The reading
one was [ __ ] She had [ __ ] issues.
What the [ __ ] Have a charge for that.
Probably the best one I had a chance
with is probably that that Portuguese one.
That's like when I came back from
Belgium. I feel like that's the only one,
you know, but you got to understand that
a lot of these people are time wasters.
Like that Italian one, she was just
wasting my time. Ukrainian one wasting
my time. You you know, you get a lot of time wasters. So
now you get a lot of time wasters. And
you speak about the 19y old, bro, I
didn't have money to keep giving. I
didn't have money to keep [ __ ] giving
people. But to be honest with you now,
if she comes back, I'll probably just
take her to be honest.
She's better. She's She's more than
better than anything to be honest. I
mean, it's not like, oh, she's better
than nothing, bro. She's probably better
than most people's [ __ ] girlfriend.
For [ __ ] sake. There's not even
anything wrong with her.
you know. But yeah.
Yeah. She was scaring me, bro. Oh, bro.
I'll never forget that one. That one
used she scared the [ __ ] out of me, bro.
And the maddest thing is it was like I
remember this. It was like I think it
was like 7:00 in the morning, bro. I was
trying to get an Uber back home and
there was no Ubers. I was like, I need
to leave this house, bro. She scared the
[ __ ] out of me. And there was no
directions. I had to I had to get out
cuz it was in a village and I had to
knock like other people's doors for directions
um for directions to um to the train
station. It was bad, bro. She scared the
[ __ ] out of me. But that Portuguese one
was probably um
yeah, my best bet to be honest with you.
But now it just seems impossible.
It's mad. It just seems impossible now.
You know, I was thinking earlier the
good days, you know, like the house
party days before Tik Tok, before
Facebook when it was actually possible.
Now it's Good luck to you, mate. It's
all I can say. Good luck to you.
Good luck to you. And then our only fans one disappeared. H
yeah, the only found one disappeared. Strange, eh?
How do you remember that Reden one?
That's a bit strange.
You must have been under another
account, Joe. How the [ __ ] do you
remember that red one? That was years ago.
Yeah, I don't even care, bro. She sucked
my dick so many times. I [ __ ] her so
many times. I only fans one, bro. It's
fun as [ __ ]
Yeah, but how do you remember? You must
That's what I'm saying. You Yeah, you
must have been around back then, though.
That's what I'm saying. Yeah,
I should have stayed with that
Portuguese one to be honest.
She weren't ugly. She weren't ugly either.
No, I know what I've done. I know
exactly what I've done. But I'm saying I
didn't know you was around back then. I
didn't know you were watching it. I know
exactly what I've done.
You are the You are the ones that seem
to [ __ ] forget what I've done. I I
know ex one second. Joker will love me
for this one as well. I know exactly
what I've done. You are the ones that
seem to forget what I've done. Show
money. Show women. Turn up to places.
No, I know exactly what I've done. But
you are the ones that seem to forget.
You remember what suits yourself.
I know exactly what I've done from start
to finish. You don't. You are the ones
with these memory problems, not me. You
know, so yeah, I know. I know exactly
what happened. I was live. That virgin
Mark Taylor was saying, "Oh yeah, you
need to get your dick out. You should go
next to her and get your dick out." Yes,
I remember everything.
I remember exactly what happened, bro.
What the [ __ ] How can I forget memory
like mine? I remember everything.
But yeah, I guess it was kind of more
possible back then.
Now it's just like
it's just not possible anymore.
It's just not possible anymore
for some reason. I don't know what it is
cuz like I said, if I was 6 months into
this, if I was a year into this [ __ ]
right? and you know, you might have got
one one night stand or you got kisses
and you got dates and someone said,
"You'll find someone." I'd be like, "You
know what? Maybe you're right." You
know, a year's nothing. You know, you
can go through the whole year of what
you had and um you can be like, "Okay,
well, it's only been a year, man." Like,
[ __ ] you know, you have some hope,
but now you ain't got no hope
because it has actually seeming it has
actually got worse.
No, it is. You You should have grabbed
it by the horns whilst whilst you
basically could cuz now you're never
ever like you're probably never ever
going to find anyone.
Like that's that that's probably what it is.
So like when I got USA that whole year I
was getting [ __ ] but now you can't get nothing.
Yeah. She come back to my house when she
said she didn't feel the vibe. I think
one of the tenants was making noise or something. But yeah.
Yeah, it gets worse and worse every year, bro.
But I remember being on a dry spell for
like two years. Then when I came back
from Manchester, then I got USA Easy.
Then I got like a couple of one night
stands, which was a good year. That year
was a good year, you know.
And then the year after that, it wasn't
as good. Obviously, I had a lot of money
in that, but I only had one person.
So, I only got laid once that year that
wasn't in escort. So, it does it does
get worse and worse. It does get worse
But, I need to really be like mature
about this. I really need to get it in
my head that it's never going to change.
I need to accept it just like most
people like Ant-Man and be mature about
it. But, I can't, bro. It just affects
me. I can't do them sober cuz every time
I do them so sober, it just affects me, bro.
Yeah, I think next year will be worse,
bro. I think next year by next year I'll
be [ __ ] completely skin and I won't
have anything ne by next year to be
honest with you. So, nah. But yeah.
Yeah, it does seem to get worse every
year. USA is a year was the best year.
That was the best year. Then there, that
was the best year, bro. The best best
year. And then the year after that,
which was last year, it wasn't as good.
Now you can't even get anyone.
So has it has actually got worse every
year, hasn't it?
I got a one night stand on my birthday.
I got a [ __ ] one night stand a week
before my [ __ ] birthday. I was fingering people.
But now you can't get nothing.
Nah, you can't. They're not interested.
She just wanted to waste my time. She
weren't that hot, bro. Jesus Christ.
She wasn't that hot. She was like a
[ __ ] sixth. What the [ __ ] bro? She
like a six, seven. She wasn't that good.
But no, she was just another time waster.
I think so. Anyways,
cuz it's hard to believe, right, that
somebody would have just [ __ ] you or
somebody would have just started kissing
you if they were acting like that on the first date. So,
I don't think so, bro.
I [ __ ] whole escorts and that bro.
What the [ __ ]
Yeah, they should have kissed you, bro. They were
Well, no. What probably would have
happened if you didn't tried to kiss
them? They probably just wouldn't meet
have met you again.
What do you think? I think they wouldn't
have I think they probably just wouldn't
have met you again. Cuz
don't forget there's actual people I've
kissed and I've not met again.
>> No, she blocked me. No, no, there's a
reason why she blocked me. But I kind of
[ __ ] that up myself.
So, and it's not strange. If that
actually happened, why would that be
strange? Nothing what they do is
strange. It's just a normal. It's just
what they do.
It's not strange. It's what they do. Are
you shocked by it, bro? What the [ __ ] I
know. I kind of [ __ ] that up myself. So So,
but yeah, what would have happened is
they would have met you and then they
probably would have met you again. So
that's what they do a lot of them.
Yeah. But that's not strange, bro. Some
need to look at what USA done. You think
after that you can call any of these people strange?
It's just what they do, right? You know,
you have to get used to it now. It's
never going to change. Sir,
what I think is so [ __ ] up, how they
make dating seems so easy when it's
there's nothing easy about it. Like, oh,
just go on Tinder, you get laid.
Just go on Tinder, you get laid.
That's what that's what they tell
people. If you go on Tinder, you get laid.
Well, I go to bars and clubs, they
really don't understand how hard it actually is.
They said, "Oh, yeah. Just just talk to people."
Yeah, it was all right.
I prefer [ __ ] So, yeah.
So what if I didn't approach then
Nicolo? Do you reckon I would have met
somebody through a friend or something?
And I don't know where they get this
[ __ ] from because it ain't easy in America.
It's not easier in America at all. I've
sh cuz let's say most people on Reddit
are American. It's not easy in America
at all, bro. It's probably worse there
because you got the you got the entitled
westernized [ __ ] and then they think
their country is better than everyone else's.
>> Like you don't know, bro. Like I'm
saying to you, I keep saying when I was
speaking to that USA Izzy friend. Like I
was like 1% away from calling her bluff,
bro. Just like, oh yeah, you wouldn't
[ __ ] with me. Like I've got I've got
relatives in prison. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. Ah, you I've got
relatives in prison and like does she
know like I don't give a [ __ ] about that
That was annoying me. I'm not going to lie, bro.
You know what I mean?
If you stop approaching,
if you stopped approaching, you'd be
able to save money
and actually go to Thailand and actually
be able to get what you want instead of
wasting your money here approaching and
still not getting laid. But
I think it's good to summarize it. If
you approach now, you're not even going
to get a date.
So, you've only got two options. You use
escorts or you go to Thailand
or you try to rekindle
people that you've met before.
Maybe that's literally all you have, man.
You keep trying here. You're not going
to get laid.
You're not going to get anything.
It wasn't even worth delays. I did get
[ __ ] four one night stands in [ __ ]
four years. It's like one every year. Yep.
Did you like that? Only fans won Nicola.
Here's another one that loves the money. Is it?
They love Peter Belly's money. Yeah.
Yeah. It was good times, bro.
I must have used her like four or five times.
She used to come up and then Laney was
in the downstairs of the house. So,
Laney was on the bottom when I was doing
it. It was so It was so weird. It got
like so weird in the end. Yep.
But it's still not worth it. It's still
It's still not worth it.
Why do they make it seem so easy?
Imagine Reddit was honest. What do you
think they would say? What? What? What
do you think they they would say if they
were honest, Nicolo? Like say they were
to give uh honest advice on Reddit. What
do you reckon it would be? My my opinion
is that okay, look,
these westernized women are very very
stuck up due to these simps on
Instagram. So, I would probably advise
you to go to a non-westernized country
where the odds are more in your favor.
But if you do want to try here, you're
more than welcome to, but you're playing
at your own risk. And I think like
you're you're set straight there. But no
one no one ever says that [ __ ] And it's
probably very very unlikely you're ever
going to meet anyone. But no one says
that on Reddit. Never never heard
anything like that.
Strange, isn't it? It strange how you
see stuff on Reddit,
you'll close your phone, and then what
you experience in real life contradicts
everything they say.
But that's probably what the honest
honesty would be, I reckon.
Don't know what what do you think? Would
you agree or Yeah. Yeah,
horrible, bro. Horrible.
But like I said, I should have gave up
after that USA easy thing to be fair. Or
maybe the year after to be honest. Yeah.
Yep. I remember, bro. I remember.
You get what I mean though it
so I'm not sure and that woman using her
living in Liverpool as an excuse which is ridiculous.
I don't know why they waste your time
and their time and then moan about it. I
just don't understand why they give
numbers, reply, keep replying, and come
up with some [ __ ] excuse. Like, why
not just not reply? What? So,
yep, they do that a lot, bro.
It's all the same. Once you've met one,
you've met them all. Why do you think
I've not been out for a while, bro? I
can't be asked. Once you've met one,
you've met them all. That's what I'm
saying. They all do the same thing. They
all have the same mannerisms.
They all do the same stuff. Yeah,
they're all NPCs, lad. Yeah,
they're all NPCs.
Yeah, there we go.
But yeah, that underage people, they've
been doing that for years.
>> Yeah. You know what makes me laugh? When
you meet like a 34 year old and she
says, "You're too young for me.
You're too young for me." They also do that.
Yeah, they do it when they're um when
they're older than you as well,
which makes me laugh cuz people say, "Oh, um
oh uh yeah, you know, there I'm trying
to get this one in Scotland to meet me."
Um they be like, "Oh yeah, go for milks,
go for older women.
I don't know, bro. I probably won't go
out in two weeks saying that.
Dude, this is how your your mind plays
tricks on you. It's nothing like Michael
Jackson. Like, Michael Jackson used to
[ __ ] me up every [ __ ] week. Come on,
PJ. Try again.
But now it's not Michael Jackson. It's
like, oh, should we just go out? But
then when you actually think of it,
there's not any real point in actually
going out cuz
it's been the same [ __ ] for years.
Michael Jackson don't [ __ ] me anymore,
bro. But that was more when I was a bit
younger cuz I still had some hope there.
But yeah, they are they're just [ __ ] here, bro.
They are just [ __ ] here.
Hey bro, I got a football bet for
Saturday, man. Put 90 pound on it.
But yeah, that's the only way to
describe them really. They're just [ __ ]
Really? They're just [ __ ]
I don't think I bother to be fair.
Yeah. Yeah. I got 90 pound of returns. 324.
Yeah. Cambridge versus Newport and
Barnett versus Colchester.
No skin people on this [ __ ] channel, lad.
No [ __ ] skin people on this [ __ ]
channel. Know me Nolan.
Might eat up some more chicken curry,
man. I'm hungry again.
Hungry again. Hungry again. door, man.
>> Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, I won't be out for a while, bro.
That's why the money thing don't bother
me. Like the loss of the Well, obviously
it does bother me, but I kind of got
used to it cuz I was done with like the
going out already. I was done with this
country and I was done with the [ __ ]
So that's why it's not really like
affected me as such and obviously I had
savings as well. So I was just back to
reality when I gave up. So I mean yeah
that's why like obviously like it's
still [ __ ] obviously bro you've lost
money but like you know what I mean?
I won a couple of football backs last
month as well, so
kind of even itself out. [ __ ]
No, I've got a curry cooked for me. I'm
going to microwave it, add some. I'm
going to have a bit more. Yeah, man.
Do you think 100 pound would be enough
to go on the piss nic
fabrics, weather spoons?
another club. Do you reckon £120 would do it? >> Yeah.
So, I go to the swan, but
yeah, she is a [ __ ] bro.
I don't need that energy. I was like,
bro, if I was coming to your country,
I'd shoot every single one of you, bro.
And I was telling her, "You're so
lucky." I told her like the whole thing
like about the first time when I was
like me and that 19year-old, I said,
"Bro, you was going to get your ass
whooped. You don't realize that." Like,
and in the end, I actually did get some
money back from it from the bank. So, at
the end of the day, like people was
just, "Oh, just allow it. Just allow it.
Just allow it." Then I was in a good
mood. Obviously, I won that four grand.
So, I was like, "Try and get some money
back here." And that's why, bro, the
first time you got lucky.
You got lucky, bro. Like,
I don't give a [ __ ] about all that. I've
done all that already, bro. I don't give a [ __ ]
I done all that, bro. Already.
I'm not ask about all that. I've already
done all that. I'm leaving in November
anyway, so I ain't asked.
I'm not asked at all. Wink wink. Yeah.
Yeah. I've done all that [ __ ] though.
I think I know it's it's a waste of time
in this country dating. Yeah.
Yeah. Her friend is a [ __ ] though.
Really is a [ __ ]
I wonder if I'd be able to get into them
casinos ever again.
Probably not, bro. And I wouldn't anyways.
I wouldn't anyways, bro.
But I prove my point enough times, you know.
It was fun rinsing them, but I used to
take them to the cleaners, bro.
I used to take them to the absolute
cleaners and back, bro. [ __ ] me.
I'm sure they used to hate me, bro.
I'm sure they used to hate me, lad. Yeah.
I think of some of them gambling times
sometimes though. They were they good
they're good memories to look back on.
But I wouldn't do it all over again. I'm
old now, bro. I feel I feel like a hundred years.
Yeah, she's not going to do anything.
She's not going to do anything.
I I'll just say Yeah. Why don't you come
outside? Why don't you come with your
gun? Shoot me with your gun. Face to
face. Let's see it. Come on. You with your gun.
This got seven siblings. I said, "Why
don't you come?"
You know what I mean, bro? Yeah.
Yeah. She blocked me on Instagram.
Imagine having a [ __ ] friend like
that, bro. Jesus Christ. Imagine that.
So, do do you think this football bet
has a good chance of winning?
>> Where is it?
>> Yeah. 90. Yeah.
Warn it. Colchester, both teams to
score. Cambridge News to score.
90 returns. 324.
That's a That's a pretty good return, isn't it? [ __ ]
That's quite a good return from 90 quid.
That's like the same odds as the first time.
[ __ ] hopefully it does. Yeah. One second.
That's a good return of 90.
Yeah, that is a good return.
I should say to her friend, "Yeah, give
me your address and I'll come with a
[ __ ] gun and we'll see how big you are then." Yeah.
She said she was going to be the one to
come and shoot me with your relatives.
Really? Oh, man. That's funny, bro.
That is really, really funny. Come on.
You're not about that life, man.
No one no one in Boston's about that life.
You know what I mean, Nicolo? No one in
Boston's about that light.
But you see this this [ __ ] right is all
caused from cold approaching. This this
[ __ ] is caused from approaching. Do you get me?
So you know what they're like. It's not
about them anymore. It's about you. It's
like what Ant-Man said. It's not about them anymore
about you, bro. It
cuz we can blame them all we like, but
we know what they're like. So if we're
not going to do anything, then you know still
that's all you really got in England is [ __ ]
a cinema football
coming out. Scared B.
You scared [ __ ]
That's funny as
you control me, mate. Do you? Oh. Oh, that's nice.
That Ricky Milling is a snake joker.
And you know the maddest thing about
that guy is he's probably still a virgin.
He's probably in his late 30s, 40s,
still a virgin.
I've had le less [ __ ] than me, but
then he still defends women. Autism alert. Autism. Ohism. Uh,
I'm going to heat this chicken up in a
minute. I'm starving.
Starving more than I am. Even though I
had it a few hours ago,
lady didn't make it for me.
Lady didn't make it for me.
You never have a
lady didn't make it for me.
I love cheese at all. [ __ ] me. Yeah.
Yeah. I can't win them casinos again.
But I would have probably stopped
gambling by now anyways to be honest.
What was you going to do that every
Thursday for the rest of your life?
That was like God telling you. Yeah.
Like every time you used to go out
Thursday, right? And you used to win.
Bit like these football bets. I
personally believe it was somebody in
the sky telling me, "Leave, leave,
leave, leave, leave. It's never going to
work here. It's never going to work
here. Leave. Leave. Leave."
That's why I personally think it was a
sign, bro. In still is in some ways.
You won two football bets in in a row,
bro. What the [ __ ]
They're normally not as easy as that to win. So,
you're about to come to an end anyways.
You couldn't keep going on like that for
the rest of your life.
going out, winning money, approaching, getting nothing,
going back home.
You know what I mean?
Was fun though. It was fun.
Right. One second. Anyway, we could just
be back few seconds.
the first time. Yeah, especially when I
won that four grand. Especially when I
won that four grand the night um the
the night before.
Yeah, the night before. You know, I won
on the Wednesday. I was supposed to go the Thursday.
I was supposed to go the Thursday, but I
won on the Wednesday.
I never I remember I remember when I
told the um the N I was like, "Oh yeah,
you know, I've got to go America and
[ __ ] in it." Said, "What?" I said,
"Yeah, got some uh unfinished business
over there." She said, "You [ __ ]
what?" I said, "Yeah." Mhm.
See you [ __ ] I was like, "Nah,
I'm being serious."
I know. I was being serious, bro. One
second. Let me hit this car up and come
back. I'll say
Yeah, I used to tell everyone.
Yeah, I used to tell everyone though I
thought m I was just get my food.
I used to I used to tell the dates as well, Joker.
Oh man, I used to tell everyone
they used to think I was [ __ ]
A lot of people would be like, "Oh,
leave it. Leave it. Leave it." And some
people would say that. And a lot of
people was like, "Oh, they'd go there
and shit." Some crazy punk said they would, but
they just tell the bartenders and [ __ ]
There's this guy I got friend lives in Australia. Well,
and when he was here, I told him his
name is Jackson. And uh
I said, "Oh, you remember the story?" He
said, "Yeah, yeah." Mhm. Yeah.
Of course I remember, bro. I remember everything.
H I said to LT earlier,
I should have a baby Peter. So my baby
and your baby can watch WWE together.
My Bubshin and your Bubshin
can watch the WWE. We can take them to the WWE,
right? One happy family.
Yeah, I got him laid as well
for them [ __ ] Yeah. Yep.
Yeah. I told everyone about my mama.
Are you sure it was my mom and Nol or
maybe I got the wrong person?
This car is quite nice.
Yeah, must have.
Now, I still talk to him occasionally,
but he's a he's a good guy.
No, he didn't say that. He didn't say
I think I might try and get Virgin boy
by laid, but he couldn't go somewhere
like Fabrics. He'd get [ __ ] knocked
out. [ __ ] Lanky Virgin.
That [ __ ] If that [ __ ] was stealing
Fabrics, mate, he'd get me [ __ ] glossed.
[ __ ] virgin. It Mhm.
You're going to be [ __ ] You get me
beat up. Just beat him with the [ __ ] virgin.
You know what I mean?
How can you not go on about your mama?
What she done was really cruel.
Yeah. Fem was like, she said, "Oh, this
cute guy approached me." I gave him my number. Yeah.
And maybe winning a football.
Like I said, that's what kept me doing
something crazy all them years is
probably winning the money at the casinos. Yeah,
I honestly think if it wasn't for
certain things, you'd see me you'd see
me on the news.
You would have probably saw me on the
news. I'm not even going to lie, bro. For real.
Cuz you know when I used to win money,
right, a lot of the times it used to be
before I used to go out. I was like,
"Oh, whatever happens there, I want
money and I'm getting an escort." Yeeha.
So nothing to lose from today. So
if you think about it, right? Um, no.
But if you think about it, Gambling
saved my ass a lot of times, bro. Not
cuz I needed the money. Just you want
money in it.
It was good, bro.
It could have been a lot worse, bro. You
could have not had the house for three
[ __ ] three and a half years. You
could still be a virgin like virgin boy
and you would have never really known
the truth. You know the truth at 27. Now
you need to leave, which is what we're
doing. Like it could have been a lot
worse. It could have been a lot [ __ ]
worse, bro. Trust me.
It could have been a lot worse than than it is.
could have not had a house for three and
a half, four years. You could have had
that money, so you wouldn't have known
what it's like to go out and get laid.
Could have been a lot worse.
Trust me, we were lucky in in a lot of ways. Nope.
one of my other friends.
But we got lucky in many ways, bro.
You know, it could have been a lot
worse. Even though it's bad, it could
have been a lot worse,
right? Cuz if you didn't have the house,
you would have been able to with money.
You wouldn't have been able to go out. But you probably
there's probably a chance you could have
met a woman that way, but it's not worth
[ __ ] up the business for. I'd rather
the money and take it away from my work.
That's what makes me laugh when people
say I'll meet people through work.
Yeah, but the thing is is
I'd rather just a money bro and and just
try away from the house and not get
things like, you know, mixed up and
[ __ ] you know?
But yeah, I've had it all. But I've had
money. I've gone gym. [ __ ] I've done
it all and never made no difference.
But only one thing to look forward to now.
That was lovely. That was Yeah.
Yeah. We have some piggies tomorrow.
And if I didn't have the house, I
wouldn't have been able to go out with
that 19-year-old. I wouldn't have been
able to meet USA. I wouldn't have been
do it, get the sex, and know that it's a
waste of time. And um now I need to
leave. I feel like 100 years old now
compared to how I did like [ __ ] a few years ago, you know?
I need to get that roll back, bro.
I miss [ __ ] sucking my [ __ ] dodger.
[ __ ] it felt good, bro.
[ __ ] good. It was
Who Who do you think I was meant to be
with? All of the people that I met,
Nikolai, you know, all of the people
that I met,
who do you reckon was
who do you reckon was the one out of all of them?
All of the people that I met
saying that it's [ __ ] waste of time
coming on these [ __ ] dates now, is it?
[ __ ] why do I feel 100 years old?
Yeah, but how how do you know?
Yeah, but she would have blocked me and
run away if we were meant to be together.
If we were meant to be together, then
they she wouldn't have run away and left me.
If that was the case, you know,
so who how can that be my mom if Lane is
my mom? Nicolo Lane is my mom. So, how
can that be my mom if Laney's my mom?
Yeah, I got Laney a birthday card. Need
to give it to her at some point. It's
her birthday soon. Yeah.
Yeah, but obviously she wasn't my mommy.
Obviously Laney's my mom. Obviously,
isn't it, Nicola?
No, I didn't get obsessed with [ __ ]
crazy, bro. You're a [ __ ]
Right, I need to get some more coke. Two seconds. Oh [ __ ]
Almost fell up the [ __ ] stairs.
So Laney is my mommy, isn't it?
I say to Laney all all sometimes on the
phone I say to Laney like,
"Why do we not look like each other? Why
do we have different taste buds? Why
this? Why that?
You You're not my mama.
Then Lane just laughs and then we kind
of this goes up this goes off like
subject. You know,
you know what? It's funny you mentioned
that those two are the only ones that
have actually come on to me.
Uh she also lied to her friend,
which is the same lie that she she lied
to uh LT
saying, "Oh, she wasn't feeding me. He
wasn't feeling me, bro. I had to tell
her friend what she done. They're
[ __ ] such liars, aren't they? These
I swear down, bro. They're such liars.
Then she's trying to tell Then she's
trying to tell LT that she's never gone
to the police. She [ __ ] has cuz her
friend Cuz her friend,
right, her friend told me that she's
gone to the police twice. I knew she
went to the police, bro. She'd have grass.
I knew I knew she'd went to the police.
She'd have [ __ ] grass, lad. [ __ ]
see what I mean?
Yeah, she has gone to the police, bro.
She went to the police twice.
So, if I go back, if I go there, they're
going to be they're going to be watching me, bro.
They're going to be watching me.
What the [ __ ] What? What? Oh, we can't
do anything because they don't live in
America. That's what they said. What the
[ __ ] do you expect What the [ __ ] do you
expect them to do, bro?
What the [ __ ] do you expect the police
in America to do? You know
what? Come to England and arrest me?
Like, what the [ __ ] do what do they actually expect?
You know what I mean?
Nicolola, what the [ __ ] did I actually expect?
Yeah, but white women don't know how to cook.
She used to come around and suck my todder.
It was good, man.
Good time there.
Yeah, good times.
She used to hate doing it though,
but she did do it.
I know. I kind of like the Only Fans
one, man. She was a dirty [ __ ]
Dirty [ __ ] are better.
When I kissed USA, it kind of it tasted
kind of stale. Nicolo
can't explain it. Like her mouth tasted
kind of stale.
Why do you think that is?
Like kind of stay off. If that makes sense. Huh?
It's mad, isn't it?
It's nice to have a good detox
cuz the next time you go on the piss
when you have a good piss up next time.
Ah, it be lovely. Would it wasn't that? What? What's lacking?
Virgin boy. Never.
What does that mean? Lactating.
No, but her mouth. Her mouth tasted kind
of stale when I was kissing. It
tasted kind of stale
about she wasn't feeling me. That's a
load of [ __ ] bro.
[ __ ] friends trying to [ __ ] troll
me on Instagram.
Who speaks to somebody on the phone for
like 5 hours just to block them?
What a loser, bro. But don't forget it
is her best friend. So,
I mean, who else would actually associate with that? Yeah,
Franklin's in the car.
You were sitting with some guy and
Yep. I was wondering what what happened.
I thought I said one I said to the I
said to the teller Yeah.
I was saying like hold on a minute. One second.
Where's Where's this person's picture?
Cuz I was just about to message them
asking if they got home. All right. and
their pictures disappeared. I was like,
"What? What's going on here?"
Then I thought maybe, you know, their number was um
maybe their number um
just um maybe because they were in
Germany, they got a new SIM. I don't
know what to think.
I thought something had happened to to
their phone or something cuz like what
the [ __ ] How the [ __ ] are they going to block me?
We got intimate. We got naked.
Nicolo, how the [ __ ] could have you
>> Yeah, that's bad, bro.
We listen to Eminem.
Yeah, damn right.
You know, for a while I had to stop
going I had to stop walking that way.
You know, I used to go central London
every week drinking or twice a week. I
had to stop going that way
cuz of um
um obviously it would make me think
about it and obviously how can I forget
it when I'm keep going cuz it was like a
certain spot you had to so I had to sort
of when I used to go to the O'Neals
I had to um go like a different way but
always coming out it would be like
you're reminded of it because if you go
to the right it's obviously where you
met your brother
it was hard to avoid because it was one
of the ones where you saw Pat Ja. That's
Yeah. It's where I met my mama, you know.
So, why did my mommy abandon me anyways, Nichol?
Why did my mommy abandon me?
I bet she wouldn't have blocked me if I
was mash tag Brady.
I bet if I was mash tag Brady, she
wouldn't have [ __ ] blocked me
cuz he's got lots of followers and stuff.
Hashtag # Brady. Yeah.
So, what, Nicolo? You honestly don't
think them them you big YouTubers can
get anyone they want? I think they
could. Maybe I'm wrong. I reckon they
could get anyone they want. I reckon
they could just go on Instagram and be
like, "Yeah, [ __ ] Come around and suck
my dick." And then they would do it.
I feel like they I feel like it would work.
I feel like anyone like them could could
get any could get lots of women
>> because of their status and [ __ ] You
know what I mean?
But maybe not. Who knows?
I reckon if you was someone like
Mashtag, you probably could just get anyone come.
I don't know. But I don't know.
Depends, isn't it? It just depends.
Do you reckon? Yeah,
those were the sad times, Joker. Yeah,
that's what I would do. If I was like
Justin Bieber, I would just bang B. I
would just bang bands and [ __ ] If I was
someone like Justin Bieber, I would just bang fans.
I wish, you know, I would actually like
kill to be in some of their positions.
Like, well, maybe not as much now, but
you know, when Justin Bieber was like really famous,
not even for the money, just like the
status, you could probably get anyone
you want. Get sex whenever you want. You
know what I mean? Nah, bro.
Saying that though, a lot of his
audience were younger, weren't they? So, young followers,
you know what I mean?
What do you think?
Yeah. Now, Only Fans would always make
excuses why she couldn't meet me. Oh, do
you want to buy pictures? I was like,
no, but I'll give you money if you if
you [ __ ] me. And then after that
and after that Nicolo,
do you remember when I used to do the
good morning approach?
Do you remember them approaches when I
used to say good morning? Do you
remember them approaches?
LJ wish he had it in him to do that. I
was I was a crazy [ __ ] back then.
Do you remember them ones? The good morning approaches
and on the [ __ ] train as well. Oh my
god. I don't know how I done that, bro.
What the [ __ ] Do you remember having a
good morning on the train and everyone looked back?
Oh, mate. I don't know how I done that. [ __ ] mad.
Oh, [ __ ] They were looking back at it.
Do you remember they looked back? Hey.
Yeah, I loved it. They all looked,
didn't it? They all looked.
Yeah. Good times, man.
I don't know how I had the confidence to do that, but
I don't anymore. I feel 100 years old now. Yeah.
Do you think I'll ever be reunited with
my mama? Nicolo.
Do you reckon I'll ever be um reunited
with my mama? I
Yeah, good times, bro.
When do you reckon you slow down from
the drinking and [ __ ]
Could they? You never know.
Imagine you going to a ball that she's in.
Imagine I go to like a ball that she's
in. I would say you what you [ __ ]
[ __ ] What the [ __ ] you saying now?
Whereas little Isabelle, I would just
leave her. Little Isabelle. But her, I I
would stick on her, bro.
I would stick on her. The only thing
that annoyed me about her is like, who
the [ __ ] does she think she is? Entitled
[ __ ] She's like a [ __ ] four out of
[ __ ] 10, bro. And she thinks she's
[ __ ] better than people. She thinks
she can go around being a [ __ ]
I was saying,
"Yeah, I was." Yeah. He thought he hit
the jackpot. You know that time you come
in the house when I was in Nottingham,
he said, "Oh, you're going to I'm going
to come tonight." And um I don't know
where I ended up. But I didn't go back
to that house. And then he went up the
stairs. He's like, "I've hit the jackpot here."
And then he lifted the um cover up and
it wasn't me. It was some other poor [ __ ]
You know, a life could have been ended that night.
I would have been like, "Oh, mate, I'd
be rubbing my hands."
I know they say that you shouldn't hit
women, but I'll be real with you. I I
wouldn't be able to help myself.
I generally don't think I'd be able to
help myself. That's that's that's like
honestly I wouldn't I wouldn't be able
to help myself.
I throw a drink over a [ __ ] face as well.
>> Yeah. And I'll shut them up. Send it to our friend.
Yeah, could do. Could do. Yeah.
And she's in Miami. I said to her
friend, "Oh, she's gone to Miami now."
She, "Oh, no, she hasn't. She wants to
go there." I said, "Yes, she [ __ ] has.
Of course she has." Cuz it's everywhere,
bro. Everyone knows where she is, you know.
Stupid [ __ ] bro.
The one trying to [ __ ] use living in
Liverpool as an excuse. [ __ ] Liverpool.
Oh my god. Trying to use that as a [ __ ] excuse.
That is insane, isn't it?
Yeah. I'm done with these [ __ ] here,
bro. Generally think I am.
Did you like the look of the Only Fans one, Nicola?
Did you like the look of her?
Like, would you bang her, do you think?
The only fans won.
She wasn't brown. She was white.
No, she wasn't. She was white, bro.
She was white. She wasn't brown.
Maybe she had tan or something, but
Yeah. Yeah. But you'd [ __ ] her though, wouldn't you?
Yeah. But you'd [ __ ] her in it. Obviously,
she sucked my Willie god knows how many
times, bro. A lot. Sometimes I run [ __ ]
to that video where she's sucking my dick.
It's hot, bro. It Yeah,
but that Italian one, she was wasting my
time. She wanted to hold hands and all
that, but didn't want to kiss.
But we all know that she wouldn't have
met me again. Anyways,
yeah, I'm just going to go out to get
pissed cuz I want to get pissed when I
go out again, bro.
And obviously, I'll do approaches when
I'm drunk. But I don't know. I don't know, man.
I might just go out with that Indonesian
guy. I just want to go for a piss up.
That's how much I don't care anymore,
you know? I don't care anymore, bro.
That's why I might just go out with an
Indonesian guy and just go on a piss.
Yeah, but Virgin Boy would never say
that because he's a copycat. That's why
they go on That's why they say if you
don't like Chev Cole, you're gay cuz
they're copying each other.
They do on Instagram as well. They've
got no mind of their own. She's not even sexy.
There's nothing sexy about her,
but people will say if you don't like
her. Yeah. So, I might just go with an
Indonesian guy. I'm not even outside of
pool anymore, bro. I can't be asked.
That's how you know when I'm hanging
around with him. That's how you know. I
just just don't care. I just want to go
for a drink, you know?
Yeah, it's not it's not my problem, bro.
It's your problem.
It's your problem now, lad. You should have left.
Yeah, I'll just go out with him.
The Indonesian guy, bro.
Maybe I'll get him on camera next time
we go out.
Cuz I only go out on my own when I'm
trying to like pull and [ __ ] Yeah. Yep.
The 19year-old was good though.
Yeah, the 19year-old was good.
He was good at giving [ __ ] as well.
You think USA is yet has ever gave a [ __ ] Nicolo?
Nah. He never gave a [ __ ] has she? Never, bro. Never.
Nah. Not everyone does it, you know. Nah, bro.
What do you think, Joker? [Laughter]
Ah, not everyone does it.
Can't be sure, you know. Yeah.
What makes you ask that?
Yeah, but she might have never gave a
[ __ ] You don't know.
She didn't give me a [ __ ]
But not every ONS I have has. Sorry.
Yeah. Yeah, it does.
But you don't know. She might have never
gave a [ __ ]
You don't know that for sure, though, do you?
You don't know that for sure, do you?
She wanted me to go down on a scancast
[ __ ] but [ __ ] that. Uh
yeah, she was trying to say I grabbed
her and all of this [ __ ] when she's the
one that come on to me, but okay. Yeah,
she's the one that come on to me, bro.
And then she was saying to her friend
she wasn't feeling me. What the [ __ ]
That is [ __ ] bro. She's the one
that [ __ ] took me back to [ __ ] her hotel.
But I didn't even ask to come back, bro.
I didn't even know. She the one that
[ __ ] took me back to where she was staying.
Yeah, she tried to make Yeah, she's made up. Yeah,
they're mad in their head, bro.
That man is [ __ ] sending me voice.
Now he's drunk. One sec.
I've already had that burger.
But yeah, she was trying to make it seem
like that she [ __ ] she uh
that she um she didn't come on to me.
She [ __ ] come on to me. The [ __ ]
[ __ ] What the [ __ ]
He was grabbing me. [ __ ] idiot. Oh, Franklin.
No, it was longer than 6 months. It was
like a year.
No, it weren't 6 months, but it was like
a year he done it for.
>> No, he done it for a year, lad.
Yeah, it was more than 6 months, bro. It
was like a year and he didn't even do anything.
See, if I got a hold of [ __ ] virgin
boy, it would be more than just a [ __ ] Sorry.
If I got hold of that [ __ ] virgin
cancer, you know, [ __ ]
It' be more than that.
Just like if I got a hold of any of these people.
Yeah, man. Yeah, it was like a year,
bro. It was like a year.
He's a sad bastard.
Sad sad bastard. And not to mention, he
had my address as well. He knew where I
lived, which doesn't make any sense.
Like, he knew where I lived as well.
I did all that talking for a year just
to really just to basically do nothing.
But catch someone off guard and make
them say sorry. That's crazy, bro.
badness. It makes you wonder, doesn't it? Scott Gbert. Scott Jbert.
If I ever see her and her friend,
imagine her and her friend was in
[ __ ] London together. I've smashed
them both up. You know,
I literally like would smash them both
up and there'd be nothing they could do
cuz there's no guns. They don't There's
no guns here. So, they'd be [ __ ] Why
do you think these Americans always lose
over here, bro? They ain't got no guns.
They're [ __ ] weak.
That's why they always lose without guns.
You know what I mean? I've smashed them
[ __ ] both up. Imagine that. Yeah.
Just like that Red Star online stalking
men every day. He's been doing it for
years and he he doesn't get paid for it, Nicola.
He doesn't get paid for it. Yeah.
Well, I don't care how many SS there is.
I'll smash her in their [ __ ] face.
There can be a million simps and I'll
smash them in their [ __ ] face.
I'll beat her and her friend up just
with one hand. Yeah.
You get me? Oh yeah. But
yeah, that red star does this [ __ ] every
day and he doesn't even get paid for it.
What a loser.
He's a loser.
That red star is the biggest loser I
think I've ever come across in my life. Oh man.
Yep. For sure. Um
That red star is a sad bastard, bro.
Imagine waking up here every day to
stalk someone all day and not get paid
for it. What a sad bastard.
I actually live in his head rentree.
But do you know what makes me um laugh
Joker is when they say um
oh they do it for reaction. No, they
don't do it for reaction.
You know when they try and say, "Oh,
they do it for reaction." Well, they
don't do it for reaction. That's [ __ ]
I don't I don't know why people say that
they do it for reaction because they
don't they don't do it for a reaction. Middle finger.
They do it because they're obsessed and
jealous or something. They don't do it
for reaction, bro. What the [ __ ]
They don't do it for reaction.
You know what I mean?
That's [ __ ] lame, bro. That's a lame excuse. Yeah.
Why do you think um USA tried blaming me
for everything, Nicolo?
What do you think that was all about?
Have to have the fan on all day, man.
Have to have the fan on all day.
I've reported you five times to the
police. Don't make me do it again.
When times get a bit tough
and they get all out on their [ __ ] it's
the boys in blue, mate.
You should already know this, Nicolo.
You know when times get a bit tough and
there's no fight left in them, it's the
boys in blue, mate.
Virgin boy is guilty of that. Tradal
[ __ ] USA is he
when it gets a little bit tough and
they've got nothing left in them on
their deathbed. Shattered. Shattered. No
hope. It's the boys in blue, mate.
It's always It's always the last it. The
boys in blue.
It makes me laugh, bro.
Imagine getting owned so hard on social
media you need to call old Bill. That is mad.
I own I owned Virgin Boy so hard you had
to call the police on me.
That's how bad the ownage was
cuz Virgin Boy
can't beat me. Virgin boy
can't beat me on in insults and
arguments because I was saying the truth
about him. He couldn't take it, so he
ran to the police. He's a little [ __ ]
You can give it, but he can't take it
cuz he gets owned.
They get owned so badly they have to run
to the police. What a loser. Yeah. [Music]
>> When it all gets a bit tough, there's no
fight left in them. It's the boys in blue, mate.
Is Barqu Quest a snake? Nicolo.
Is Barqu Quest a snake or no?
I've not heard from here.
Oh sn it
is money, man. They're all snakes.
Why is there so many
Why is there so many snakes on here, man?