[ __ ]
>> No, bro. That is mad.
What's up? What's up, bro?
One second. Oh, here we go. Hello.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] mental. They be mental on YouTubes,
>> bro. I'm not going to lie, bro. I I was
actually like thinking of like just
stopping this [ __ ] They're just all
weirdos on here, bro. I can't lie. Like,
>> no, he's just gone [ __ ] up. completely
[ __ ] up. You got Rice and Kayie
getting arrested, but I reckon that
Kay's getting sent back home now. But
I've got I've got a theory
that Rice is going to go back to Kay's
house. That's what I'm thinking of now.
>> The thing is, why did he get arrested though?
>> Because he's a [ __ ] pedo, isn't he?
He's a Nazi. I don't know why he got arrested.
>> I don't know why he got arrested. I
haven't been on shoes, but the [ __ ] he's
been saying and the [ __ ] he's been doing and uh
that's why you got to be careful of of
the stuff you say on social media.
>> They're just weirdos on here though.
Like, and it is funny. Like, it is funny
like the rice thing and that. Don't get
me wrong, it's funny, but they're just
all weirdos on here.
>> No, I knew it was coming with Kelly as
well with them all.
How do you know?
>> Obviously, of course, Kelly's just
gullible only. Why they like Kelly did?
Because she's got a crack in between her legs.
>> But since he's gone to rice and
>> Are you sure? Are you sure he's been
arrested and not just escorted?
>> I think he's been escorted to be honest
with you. That's what I think. Cuz if if
he did get arrested and then he would
have been put in the back of the fan at
the very back of it, but he didn't. He
got basically put out the side of the
fan. So that was telling me that none of
them's being arrested. Only what's going
on there is that Rice has been affected
from that property. He's not allowed
back at that property now. So
>> he must have been saying he must have
been saying bad stuff about kids then is it? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. So only where Rise can go now is K
back back to Kay's house. Like that's
it. And as soon as everybody knows that
he's at Kay's house, what's what's going
to stop everybody turning up to Kay's
house? Everybody knows where Kay lives.
>> I've already told Natalie soon as Rise
where Kay is, I'm going.
>> [ __ ] hell, bro.
>> I bet you I bet you I bet you laughed
when Billy got arrested in it.
I was laughing at all of it. Belly
getting arrested to rise and Kelly
getting transported to the train
station. That's what's happened.
>> They're being transported to the train station.
>> They will just go straight to Kay's isn't it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Now they will. Yeah.
>> So what do they do? Do they contact his
landlord or do they send letters? Like
what do you think? He
>> sent letters to his council, didn't
they? And video clips and that to the council. clock
>> and that's what's probably done it with
the police. I don't know about the
police being there. Yeah,
>> who's got the police involved there, but
all I can say is [ __ ] that none of
them's being arrested and
that now clearly
is getting called and m by everybody in
real life include gone as [ __ ] >> Yeah,
>> life. Oh [ __ ] Like
today my mom sent my mom the video. My
mom seen the video. See when mom's even
said you landed on your feet you make
you done good for yourself better meaning
>> yeah can you hear me
>> yeah I can hear you yeah
>> yeah just hope just hope they don't do
it to you and it then you'll be [ __ ] up
>> they don't know where I'm living anymore
they don't know where I am and they're
not getting me a dress and I'm not
switching my camera on or going live or
anything anymore. I'm already here now
to just say this is all [ __ ] up.
All the all this YouTube [ __ ] is
just gone [ __ ] up completely. Me and
Natalie's just been sat there watching
sat there watching. That's it.
>> It's the same. It's the same low lives
on here though is it?
>> No, it is the same low lives. [ __ ]
great five guys and Kelly thought she
was in with the great five guys. >> Yeah,
>> he thought she was well and in there
with him, but she's not.
>> You need to realize that you're wasting
your time like even arguing with these
people cuz the thing is with these
people on here, bro, they're just
disabled. Like there's not even no point
arguing with them. That's what I
realized in the end.
>> No point arguing with them.
>> They not they're not disabled, PJ. Well,
some of them will be. Yeah, obviously.
Course. Yeah, but it's to do with loneliness and depression and
>> everything else in this community.
That's why they do it do what they do to other people.
>> It's just a self It's just a
self-reflecting community. That's all it is. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I can't be bothered with it
anymore, bro. You know,
>> that's why that's why me and Natalie's
quit. That's why we quit.
We don't you don't see the point of it.
They found out where we live this was.
They found out that I moved back to my
old place again.
>> But now they don't know where I am.
>> Do you think V will be let out?
>> Yeah. Yeah. They only can keep him in
for 24 hours.
I can keep him in cluster for 24 hours
and be out.
But it depends what he's done to him for
him. They can keep him in, but it all
depends what he's done
and how bad the crime is, what he's
done. But Rise and Kayley, they would
have been picked up by the police and
moved on because if Rise didn't get arrested
then rise on the last life, isn't it?
>> Hey, me. Mhm.
No, not really. Cuz that means if he
moves down to here, then I'm going to
have to snap his legs, isn't it?
>> Talking about my daughter.
>> Yeah, Lester's not far from you, is it?
>> Lester? No. If if Kaye if Kaye if Kaye
if Kaye is done with if say Kaye gets
done with him then he is [ __ ] Like
where's he going to go bro?
>> I kind of feel I kind of feel I kind of
feel bad for him. You know
>> I feel bad for him.
>> Now why don't anyone go for cuz why
don't these people go for like actual
actual pedophiles like nons legs and
[ __ ] They No one Have you noticed that?
No one ever goes for that nons. Have you
noticed Have you noticed that with this community?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I do. I do because she only
licks the ricees. That's why,
>> you know, but obviously I'm not saying
like Rice hasn't, but you know, there
was actual other pedos on this community.
>> No, what it is what it is is because we sit here
>> and we call these back and they don't
like it when you call him back where
Sean sits there with a laugh on his face
and don't call them back.
>> That's still Yeah. But yeah, but if
somebody done something like they done
with rice to him, then he would, you
know, do you know what I mean? [ __ ]
they're still calling people skin
everyday Monty. Nothing's changed.
>> Oh, nothing will change, PJ.
YouTube. Nothing will change. That's why
I've left this community. There's
nothing good in here no more except for
people trying to [ __ ] my life up. >> Yeah.
And yeah. Yeah. You can see with belly
and [ __ ] rice and [ __ ] in it.
>> Yeah. Lucky enough that weren't me. It's
not even that Kay even got called a M by
the people there as well.
>> Just M. That's what someone said at the
end of the video.
>> What have you done? If that mob was
saying that to you, you would have
fought them in it. >> What?
>> If that mob was saying that to you, you
would have fought them in it. Yeah.
>> Oh god.
Or would have you run away?
>> I want to know why why he's got afflicted.
>> That's what I want to know as well.
>> That's what I want to know. And it's
plenty funny that Kayn's involved in
that now and she's on the video.
>> So I never ever argued with Rice. He was
always right with me. So like, do you
know what I mean?
>> It's not like that. These videos can go viral. Viral.
>> Yeah. Cuz it's not the community
recording it. It's actually the public
recording it, not the YouTube community.
We just said that would be me one day.
Nah, cuz if a if a mob come for me, I'm
I'm going outside it. I don't care if I
get my ass kicked. I'm going outside.
You know what I mean?
You didn't even know what an angry mob
was, did you, Monty? Before then, of
>> course know what angry mob is, PG. Yeah.
>> There's a lot of angry mobs in the
Simpsons. They used to do it in the
Simpsons, isn't it? Yeah.
>> Yeah. You got a lucky escape.
>> Yeah. Still laugh cuz I'm not coming
back on YouTube. I'm only here because
of what's happened. That's only why I'm back.
>> It's cuz what's happened with R and K
and F. That's why I'm really back for
now, but I'm not back.
It's just [ __ ] up. What do you think
about that? that
>> and rice and fell.
What do you think about it all?
>> Natalie said it's her own fault. Oh [ __ ]
>> You know why he was hoping that?
You know why they got kicked out?
>> No. or saying that he's a nons and that
got picked out for being a n
sisters. You don't know where I am,
Monty. These people think they know
where I am and they don't.
>> Yeah. Don't Don't even clues, man, where
you are. Don't even
>> They don't know where I am. They'll
never know where I am.
>> Well, me and Natalie, we're not even in
Birmingham anyways. Let's just put it
that way. You know what I mean?
>> Me and Natalie's moved out of
Birmingham. We're not there no more.
We we we do live together,
but we don't live in Birmingham anymore.
We got a private rent in house now. P. Yeah.
>> That's good, man. Is it? That's good.
>> Yeah. Is it is Oh, yeah. Me and got our
own private trying to find out where I
live so they can send posters. It's not
going to happen. They're never going to
know where I live. So crack on it.
>> But they're going to be goed when
someone finds out where they live and it
happens to them and they're going to be
[ __ ] crying about it.
>> It will happen.
>> Look at Pat Mustard. He was he got found. >> Mhm.
>> You know what I mean? And he thought he
was invincible and he got found. So, you know,
>> yeah, they're never invincible forever, bro.
>> No, they look
rise and clearly got I believe.
Yeah, but they didn't get arrested
though. That's the thing. And Rice did
not get arrested.
If they got arrested and then they would
have put been put in the back of the
police, they didn't get put back in the
police. They got put in the side of it.
That means they got transported away
from the away from the place.
>> It's bad. Very bad.
>> No, it's good now. Rice is homeless.
>> You feel sorry for
>> you all need to get Kerry out as well
now. You all need to send that to K's
house in get Kicted.
I don't feel sorry for Rise. No.
>> Why am I going to feel sorry for someone
who's who's weak pen for my kids? >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? I'm not a [ __ ] Kie.
>> Pete, your sister one second. Bonnie,
let me read this. Pete, your sister
deleted her Facebook confirms uh you
don't know where I live. I've said this
about a million times. I I can promise
you right now, Monty. And them, they
don't know where I live. Crack on. I
said crack on.
>> That doesn't confirm anything. If your
sister's deleted a Facebook or not.
>> Yeah, just crack on and do what you said
you're going to do. Crack on. No one's
bothered. You don't know where I am. So, crack on.
>> Your sister could have deleted a
Facebook for any reasons.
>> The letters are being sent. You can send
whatever you want. No one's bothered.
Like, literally, nobody is bothered. You
don't know where I am.
>> Screenshot all this, PJ. Screenshot it all.
>> They don't know where I live. Honestly,
they don't know where I live money. I
swear to God they don't. Promise you.
>> Yeah. Just screenshot what they write
and then you've got them writing what
they're going to do. Then then what they
going to do then when you got >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean?
>> Where I am.
>> Yeah. You keep stop talking and do what
you said you're going to do. Stop
typing. No one's No one No one's asked.
You know what I'm saying? No one's asked
what You know what I'm saying? That's
what I just said to them.
No one's asked about what these little
[ __ ] retards do, bro. You know what I mean?
>> Rick Rock. >> Yeah.
>> Ask Rick Rock where do I live?
>> He doesn't even know where I live.
>> You can put heads up. No one's bobbing.
Stop wanting. Am I right in what I'm
saying? Stop typing and saying what
you've done and what you're going to do
and do it. That's how I know that.
That's how I'm telling you. They don't
know where I am. I'm telling them to do it.
>> Yeah, they even say you're at your mom's.
>> I'm not at my mom's either.
They don't know where I am. That's what I'm saying.
I'm not at my mom's and I'm not at my
sisters. No one knows where I am.
>> Yo, Rock, why don't you get a life
instead of um trying to [ __ ] ruin
other people's lives? Rock.
>> Bro, come on, man. Do you think these
people could ever get a life? these fat ugly people.
>> Brock, why don't you meet PE's here for a fight,
>> bro? He can't even leave his house. He's
a fat ugly bongo.
>> [ __ ] hell. Just let him do what he
said he's going to do, bro. Let him embarrass himself.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. Well, stop. Okay. I'm
I'm going to ignore that now, buddy.
Anyways. Yeah. So, just stop talking
about it. Yeah. Listen, the last thing
I'm going to say to you Yeah. is do what
you said you're going to do and do it
cuz you don't know where I live. So, now
anyways, Bonnie. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Just block him. >> Byebye.
>> And and they and this is how you know,
Monty. Listen to me. Yeah. That these
people are the ones that are scared.
They ain't got life cuz they wouldn't be
doing this. Yeah. They sat on YouTube
[ __ ] every day doing the same [ __ ]
every day. All the way through summer.
>> All the way through summer.
>> Yep. All the way through summer. Don't
leave the house. Nothing. You know, I'm
not going to do good for myself. I got a
perfect good woman that here. You know what?
>> What would you do if they found What
would you do if they found out where you
live and done that to you what they done
to Rice? What would you do? Like, what
would you actually do?
>> Well, it's not hard to find somewhere
else to live, PG. How many houses have I lifted? >> Yep.
>> Getting back with Kay. Am I getting back
with Kay? First time I heard about that.
Talk to that man. I'm never get back
with Kayie. Never ever ever would I get
back with Kayie. Never.
There's only one woman I'm sticking with
and I'm getting married to her. I'm
going to make her a step stepmomage to
my kid and that's Natalie.
Yeah. Going to make Natalie the proper
stepmom over what my kids actually need. >> Yeah.
Yeah, just it's just good you didn't
turn up like you didn't turn out like
rice isn't it? You would have been
[ __ ] then in it.
>> She said, "Mark, I'm good." Me, lad, I'm
>> You would have been [ __ ] in it. >> What?
>> If that if you were right, you would
have been [ __ ] up in it.
>> Why do you all these people that I'm in
a tent as well? Why do they all think
that I'm still living in a tent?
>> Cuz they're mongos.
>> They sit on YouTube over there calling
other people's skin.
Give me some.
>> What's that comment say? The bottom
comment. Give me what? PV.
>> Sorry, I'm not a fight like you.
>> Money, you like these.
>> I don't like these people. How is SPD?
>> Oh, SGD is fantastic.
>> You know, the only thing Yeah. I regret
about is [ __ ] I met that [ __ ] nons
through you, bro. That's the only thing.
>> You never met him through me. You met
him through the [ __ ] community.
>> I met that [ __ ] virgin through you,
mate. Don't bring Sha Long Legs on me,
PJ. Never bring him on to me like we do.
>> You know, still not getting a job,
[ __ ] What's the excuse this time? Like
>> same excuse you got the bottom. You
wrote that comment. Why the [ __ ] have
you got a job? Why the [ __ ] are you sat
on YouTube every day, daily talking
about other people's [ __ ] indoctrining
other people's address, and making other
people like hell?
>> Why is that? Why ain't you got a job?
>> Same [ __ ] in it.
>> Yeah, of course it's the same [ __ ] It
It feels like these have got [ __ ]
memory loss or [ __ ]
>> I was saying the same thing earlier. Yeah.
>> Where you only can write only one
sentence. Your skin,
get a job. It's just the same [ __ ] with
>> Monty. You know, Monty, but you know
that I'm not skin. I've met you. I'm not
skin. You know
>> you're the ear, >> huh?
>> Yeah, the you're the skin skinned one here.
No, I'm only messing all these are skin.
Oh, [ __ ] you're making me blush out there.
I don't wear pink. Don't peek.
You people are [ __ ] proper
disabilities. We write it proper mongos.
Any p anyway PJ. So yeah, that's the
news. What what you all wanted to read.
So rise did not get arrested. They've
been tough at the train station. No [ __ ]
So they've gone back to Kay's house now.
And that's where they've gone back to is Kay's address.
You ever worn pink? Pink? Have you ever
seen me in a pink? No, >> babes.
Have you ever seen me wear pink?
>> Sorry about that. I've never worn pink
in my life, have I? >> No. EJ.
You hear me?
>> Yeah, I can hear you.
>> Yeah, I said no, you haven't.
>> It's all Yeah. [ __ ] idiot.
>> No. Yeah, it's all Why do these people
money? Why do these people go for me
every day even when I don't talk about them?
because they know you're going to react to them.
>> Yeah. But even if you even if you Yeah.
But even if you don't react to them,
they will still do it. You do realize that?
>> Yeah. So they until they get till they
get a reaction.
>> Yeah. But even if they don't get a
reaction, they will still do it. That's
what I'm saying.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Until they get one
until they mention it's name. It's to do
with the name. So you read their comment
out their name.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Put Okay. Put
like this. Right. Okay. So, say I was
ignoring someone for six months, right?
And they were like trying to get a reaction
>> out of me every day. And then let's just
say that I gave them a reaction 6 months
later. Okay? So, they got the reaction
and now what? Okay. So, what?
And doesn't make sense, huh?
>> I think these people generally I think
these people are disabled. I'm not going
to lie, bro.
They just come out. They just come out
their mom's [ __ ] ugly. That's all.
>> They what?
>> They just come out their mom's [ __ ]
ugly. That's all.
>> You like them though?
>> Some of them are all right. Not all.
Then the rest of them are just tried to
copy of the five great ugly guys who are
not even that clever.
>> Maybe one day. But maybe what maybe one
day they'll get off YouTube. Is it?
>> No. These people are at peace here. You
don't understand with these people. >> What?
>> These people have not got no life at
all. Meaning that the basically YouTube
ridden basically ridden to YouTube every
day and day out. You can't get
>> and I know why they keep calling me a
manta monty. They need to stop repeating
Lord J because you can't get a bird. But
I'm sitting there laughing at Lord J cuz
he ain't even got a bird himself. Mhm.
>> And I've also I've also shown them birds
I've had in the past, Monty.
>> Yeah. It doesn't matter if you have
birds or not. It's just [ __ ] weird
when people mention other people's
business or people's lives. >> Yeah.
>> People haven't or had add in life
>> and people reacting self-reflect on you.
>> [ __ ] can you please just get a job for
[ __ ] sake? So you will have
>> you get a job.
>> You missed me. You missed your feet. Byebye.
>> Listen, stop asking women to get [ __ ]
undressed on YouTube. You little [ __ ]
weirdo. American Yankee.
>> Who is Who is it? Who is it?
>> Who would that thingies? Get him back up. PJ.
>> Okay. If you He left back up the day.
Like Yankee [ __ ] incest [ __ ] Oh yeah.
[ __ ] Mitch the Yankee [ __ ] [ __ ] I
don't even know the Yankee bastard.
[ __ ] [ __ ] in his mouth. Dirty [ __ ]
Is it leg? Okay.
>> One second. Hold on. I'll be back.