Yeah, s what they doing?
They've been obsessed for years, bro.
No, these fat, ugly people been obsessed for years.
That's nothing new.
Yeah, it's nothing new, bro.
Just like the women [ __ ] never changing.
It's nothing new. It's something we don't know, you know? Yeah,
they're all skin on here.
Yep. All cell projection.
All self projection. Yeah.
I just come on here to complain really.
complain about women to be fair.
I don't really do anything else. I only
come here for
What are these people saying about how
me I've gone live four times? These
people on YouTube all day every day.
They can't get off it. They've never
ever took a day off of YouTube. What the
[ __ ] And they're talking about other
people. Yeah, I've just went on it.
These are the [ __ ] fat ugly people
that can't even take a day off of
YouTube. [ __ ] four times live or no
[ __ ] live. Who the [ __ ] are they to
talk about anything, bro? They're sat on
their fat, ugly old asses every day,
can't leave their house, sat on YouTube,
talking about other people being on
YouTube. Are you mad, bro? What the
[ __ ] These fat, ugly people that sit on
YouTube all day, every day, year in,
year out, not one day off of it, and
then and they're telling me that I've
been live four [ __ ] times. So [ __ ] what?
What the [ __ ] bro? Madness.
What we got on there, bro? It's just
full of nerds.
That channel's just full of fat nerds.
[ __ ] disabled people. They ain't got a life.
Bye-bye now. Yeah, bro. There's no point
um entertaining these nerds.
That's all they are. Low life nerds.
It's all about me. Madness.
I don't know how many times
I've had to say to these women, I'm not
your [ __ ] mate. I think I probably
said that three times in the past 3
weeks. I'm not your [ __ ] mate. Which
is what I've said to about
God knows how many times like when
people say it to me, I say I'm not your
[ __ ] mate. Yeah, you don't know me
from Adam. Do not call me mate. It
sounds horrible, bro. I don't like it
when people call me mate. When a woman
tries to call you mate, they all do the
same thing. They say the same stuff.
They do a lot of the same [ __ ] for
people that aren't the same. But given
that, they do a lot of the same [ __ ] and
do the same stuff for people that aren't
the [ __ ] same. Isn't that a madness?
But when when you have one when you have
a conversation with one of them, it
reminds you of the other conversations
you've had cuz it's the same [ __ ]
Same conversation, just different people.
Yeah. Same conversation, just different people, different characters.
Oh, they do that all the time, bro.
Older or younger. Yeah, they do that all the time.
They use a lot of excuses.
They use a lot of different excuses.
Yeah, they do it a lot. There's always
excuses with them.
They're just [ __ ] That's what they are.
Yeah. When you lose on gambling, you
actually feel like you've been raped.
It's horrible, bro.
Yeah. It actually feels like that when
you lose on roulette or the Fox. It
actually feels like you've been [ __ ]
raped. It's disgusting, bro.
You actually do like, you know, it's I
know it sounds funny. It sounds mad, but
it's actually true. You actually do feel
like you have.
I'm not reading that. Got to make another account.
Soon as I saw life for the fourth time,
I blocked you. So, you just wasted your
time. I make another account. Sad.
Sad bastards. They talk about me being
live four times a day. They sat on
YouTube all day, every day. Can't get
off of YouTube.
Sat on YouTube all day, every day, and
can't get off of YouTube. Isn't that funny,
dude? I can't remember, bro. Probably. Yeah.
Yeah, actual [ __ ]
What's the day tomorrow? Yep. Um,
nothing. Just chilling. I'll probably go
to sleep today about 5:00 in the morning
again, 6:00 in the morning.
Just start thinking about your negative experiences,
how it's never going to change,
you know? What the [ __ ]
It's horrible. It's a horrible life.
I wake up at like 11, bro. I'm a lazy [ __ ] nowadays.
That's what happens when you got nothing
to live for. You just give up the life.
Yeah. You legit just give up the life,
bro. I should have done a long time ago,
but I just always thought it was going
to change, but it never changes. Nothing
changes in this life.
I keep trying to watch man before I go
to sleep. But
hope I don't wake up. But somehow I
always wake up. Yeah.
That damning thing was funny, isn't it?
What I don't understand with these
people, it's like that that guy from
Italy I said, right? Like how they
forget so quickly. It's like you tell
them like your experiences or say
they've got experience in it, right? So
they know the situation or like you tell
them this situation and they'll wake up
one day and they like, "Oh, you going
out today?" Like, "Well, no, considering
it doesn't work in this country and
nothing worked in this country." It's
like they it's like they have memory
loss. It's like they wake up, it's a new
day, and then they forgot all the things
that they got told and all the things
they got shown, and now they think
somehow this time it's going to be
different. Not going to be different at
all. It's never going to be different.
Oh, you know that one I was shouting at
at the park? I messaged her on Facebook.
She come up with Facebook. I said, "Oh,
you you're the one that shouted at the
park." And she just blocked me.
nu just on my second channel right on my
second channel was enough like I've got
so many approaches but yeah
true true but bro that take him like
[ __ ] years to watch but you get the
gist of Yeah. Um, oh, it's Peter Griffin
in a strawberry.
It's just something for Family Guy.
But I've got enough like approaches on
my main channel to like to show that's
enough. You know what I mean? Yeah.
But no, but the Italian guy has done it.
Like the Italian guy has done it
himself. He's been out with me about
four times. I said, "What do you mean
it's going to change? You know, of all
people, it's not going to change. You
know it's not going to change. So, why
are you saying it's going to change? And
I said, "Good luck to you, cuz you're
going to need it. Cuz I ain't doing it
anymore. I should have to do it anymore.
I shouldn't have to waste any more time,
any more money doing this again." So, yeah. Uh,
I said it's strange because he's
actually been out with me doing it. So,
how he thinks one day it's just going to
change is beyond me. But each their own
things like that don't change otherwise
it would have by now. So that's that's it.
They still give advice about this.
that French almost.
>> I just stayed in bed just like every day.
Stay in Stay in bed. Uh,
I went to get some coke, but apart from
that, I just stayed in bed. Yeah.
That's what I do every day, bro. When
you give up your life, what the [ __ ]
When you give up your life, you're done,
bro. That's how it is. Should have gave
up a long time ago,
to be honest. I just thought things were
going to change, but never changes.
Yeah. Yeah, that's the way it is. Nope.
No, I already got a takeaway today. I
had a vindaloo today. Yeah. Um, just depressed.
I went out the house once today to get
some coke and that's it. Probably be in
bed all day tomorrow again. I'm just
waiting for this life to end. Me and
[ __ ] Savvy Guy.
Oh, did you just realize that? [ __ ] hell.
But yeah, I should have recorded everything.
Both, I think.
I think both to be fair. Yeah.
Be in bed all day tomorrow again.
What's the point in trying in life and
you know it's never going to change and
you're just going to get tormented?
[ __ ] pointless. You might as well
give up. It's easier that way, you know?
It's [ __ ] easier that way. It's never
going to change, but never going to [ __ ] change.
So, when this if this football bet wins,
like I said, still not going out. Still
not doing anything but putting it
towards thingy. So, yeah, I'm dead
serious about that as well, bro. I'm
dead serious, bro. [ __ ] this, you know.
Yeah, I wake up at like 11.
There's this guy here that I used to go
out with, Joe, from Italy.
Um, oh yeah, I show I sent some women
dick pictures, Joe. Surprisingly, they
reply back. Obviously, none of them were
from England because obviously they
could they could go to the boys in blue.
It's a bit harder to do that when
they're in another country. And a lot of
them replied back to negativity. I was
like, "Oh my god, it never changes, does
it? This is the same old [ __ ] we're
hearing. Same old conversation with
them. Same old boring despite them all
being different." So people claim same
old [ __ ] [ __ ] you know? Yeah.
It got a reply though. It got some replies. Yeah.
They ignore normal messages but reply to negative ones.
Strange, isn't it?
Very, very strange. But they reply to negative ones.
That is very strange that it um
so yeah, that French one was trolling me
hard. Why are they such trolls them
[ __ ] French [ __ ]
She said, um,
she said, "Oh, it's it's small. I'm a
bit disappointed. I thought it was going
to be bigger or something. [ __ ] off."
Yeah, they they affect your mental
health. They're them. They're the
problem. They're the problem. Them [ __ ]
They are the [ __ ] problem. Them
[ __ ] [ __ ] Oh, anyways, I met this guy.
I met this guy from Italy. Yeah. Oh,
sorry. I used to go out with this guy
from Italy, Joe. No one really knows
about him. And I told him basically what
what was what yesterday and he said,
"Oh, it's going to change one day." And
I was like, "You of all people think
it's going to change. You of all people,
you're second best to me. You've done it
with me. You've gone out approaching
with me. How the [ __ ] is any of it going
to change when this [ __ ] has been going
on for [ __ ] years now?"
And then he was trying to say like then
he kind of turned into like a s in a
way. I said you of all people know
this is never ever going to change. Never.
Um he said tell exactly what he said. I
said bro you of all people you've done
this with me. You know it's never going to change. He said
exactly what he said. said
I told him
I told him oh I sent I I said I hate I
messaged them I hate them to see how
quickly they reply said I think if you
stop hating them and just try to feel
more positive towards women things will
change I said you of all people think
it's going to change you're delusional
he says I love women I don't hate them I
said mate he said oh I was trying to
meet some interesting women and I told
him like bro we've done this a million
times It never changes. So, yeah.
I think maybe where he's not done it for
so long, he's forgot how bad it is. Cuz
it it's possible. You know, I I you
know, like a year and a half ago, I
thought it was going to change.
But it's not negativity, it's reality,
though. It's not negativity, it's
reality. That's the difference. There's
a fine line between negativity and
positivity. That is reality. What I'm
saying, what I'm showing is reality.
That's not negativity.
Negativity is something that's not
happened. It's just a negative thought.
This is real. What is happening?
And um then I had like some numbers that
never replied. And as soon as I said I
hate women, they replied back being a
[ __ ] being an awkward, wannabe, smart
like we're still going through this at
[ __ ] 27 years of age coming on 28. So,
and it's like I'm not being negative.
I'm being real. Otherwise, I wouldn't
say it. If I didn't believe it, it's
like if I went out tomorrow, it would be
the same old. I could bet money on it. I
could bet all I have on it that it would
be exactly the same. So, where if
there's truth in it, how is it negative?
How is it negative is if it's the truth.
It's not negativity. It's reality.
Your experiences are negative. If
there's truth in it, it's not negative.
Stop talking about yourself. Stop
putting yourself down. I told you this a
million times. Stop sing.
Am I like the only one that knows the
like the truth or something?
They generally are the problem.
Otherwise, I would be out trying now. I
wouldn't have [ __ ] booked these
[ __ ] expensive ass flights if I
didn't think that. You know what I'm
saying? I know they are the problem.
It's clear as day they're the problem
from what I've experienced, from what
I've seen other people experience. Um,
and here's a question, Joe. You know,
these people that give advice, what do
you reckon they would have done if they
were in my shoes? Because it's very easy
for these people to talk when they're
not in in your shoes. What would have
these people done if they were in my in
my booth? They would have [ __ ]
probably killed someone by now.
That's another thing you need to
understand is these people that give
advice, they've never been in your
shoes. That's that's also another thing
because if they had been in your shoes,
they would have ended up killing someone
by now. It's obvious they would have or
yeah, they would have done something. So I mean,
it's all right for women. They get sex
whenever they want. They can get a
relationship whenever they want. How
would they feel if they if they were not
given a relationship, could barely get
sex or never had sex or whatever, and
they can't find a relationship? They
wouldn't be positive. Nobody would be positive, you know.
So what what would they be like if this
was happening to them? What would they be like?
Cuz I'm telling you, it's like, you
know, when these people sit there saying
that you're you're mentally ill and that
Yeah. What they don't understand is what
these people don't understand is your
experiences are very uh an exception for
someone that's tried so much. So
actually, it's actually quite normal
because anybody else would have just
killed someone by now or ended up in
prison. Somebody would have ended up in
prison. Trust me, I'm telling you right
now. Or they would have just they would
have killed someone or they would have
done something other than what I'm
doing. So, how they can sit there and
try and say, "Oh, well, it's not
normal." Well, it [ __ ] well is cuz
how else would they feel if if it was
them and not anyone else?
You know what I'm saying? No, I'm not
having some positivity, bro.
You know, I was going to start on LT
today. I was messaging him saying like,
bro, like I was going to I was going to
start on him, like proper start on him,
bro. And I would and I would have
finished it. I don't give a [ __ ] Yeah.
See, a lot of people don't understand
that. Like, I had to not do certain [ __ ]
because of certain things. People don't
understand that. But, bro, you got
nothing to lose, then [ __ ] it. In it, I
don't give a [ __ ] And I'll see it right through, you know?
I just start being a [ __ ] to people,
bro. Like, it's simple. Yeah.
Yeah. It's not It's not funny.
Just like just random people, bro. Like,
yeah. Look what I was saying to that diamond, you know. So, yeah.
So, how else would anyone feel if they
were me then?
Imagine you could you could put it all
on a high drive hard drive and put it in
their brain. Imagine that. That's
another thing. These people have not
tried as much as you. So, what the [ __ ]
would they know?
You know, you're not new in the game,
bro. You know what I'm saying? But this
Italian guy, bro, he really I feel sorry
for him that he they he actually thinks
that there's a chance.
I really feel bad for him, bro. And I've
gone out with him like four times.
And he says, "Oh, you'll find someone
like it's" But again, he's probably not
tried as much as I've tried, so who knows? You know,
it's crazy, ain't it?
But I used to be like that. Did you
remember, Joe? I used to be, "Oh, next
week's going to be different. Michael
Jackson's calling me. Come on, let's go,
man." Now, I don't get any of that. Now,
I'm just looking forward to leaving cuz
I know it's never ever going to change her.
So, I don't even get that anymore.
I don't even want to drink anymore. I
just want to leave to be honest. That's
how it is. Yeah.
Guess I gave up years ago.
You're boring. Bye-bye.
You're [ __ ] boring, bro. Bye-bye now.
So, yeah, that's where we're at, basically.
Yeah, there's no point responding to
these people like Virgin Boy and that
because all they're doing is self-p
projectioning because they want attention. So,
I wrote I saw Virgin Boy's post uh
yesterday and it was just all of it was
just self-p projecting. So, there was
like no point me even like responding to it.
Good, bro. Just chilling, man. How are you, Charlie?
who I've met once before.
So, yeah, that's how it is.
But at least I get to go to Thailand in
November. That's good, man.
Yeah. Can't wait. Finally get out of this [ __ ]
I can't wait.
When do you think I should have gave up?
Um, Joe, I think I should have gave up
after the USA thing. maybe six months
after that. I think I should have gave
up by that time.
You know what what what do you think?
You know, I can't believe this. You
I can't believe I've traveled all over the country.
This is This is This is crazy. What the [ __ ] bro?
No wonder my bones are so [ __ ] old
and [ __ ] [ __ ] at 20 fucking7. I
[ __ ] see why now, bro.
Where's the best city in terms of what
I like? Newcastle.
That's my favorite, I think. But overall, uh
I don't know. I quite like Edinburgh, so maybe Edinburgh, then maybe Newcastle,
and then maybe Nottingham,
but then Birmingham's quite good for
like the food and that. Uh my second
favorite is Edinburgh, I think.
Oh, I know, bro. I have to watch um
certain porn sites because of it. Yeah,
they're doing it on everything, bro. Yeah.
What's your What's your favorite um
What's your favorite city, Charlie?
I like London. Well, my favorite is
London, obviously, but in case if you if
you mean not London.
If you mean just for nights out, then
I'd say Newcastle. Yeah.
Amsterdam's a [ __ ] holder to be fair.
Where would you rather go, Charlie?
Thailand or America? Thailand. Any day,
bro. [ __ ] America.
[ __ ] America. [ __ ] them, bro. [ __ ] them.
Do you remember Damon?
No. [ __ ] America, bro. You remember Damon, though?
you keep telling me to find God. I don't
believe in God.
Why did you and mommy break up? Did you see that?
I just don't like American people.
Simple. Don't like them. Never have, never will.
Yeah. You can't even get laid here, Charlie.
Like, London, England. [ __ ] bro. You
can't even get [ __ ] You can't even
get laid, lad.
Why did you and mommy break up? Did you
see that grievy? What I said to Damon?
And I wouldn't like Australia because
obviously you can't get laid there
either. But I mean it's more tolerable.
I'd prefer Australia than than America. But yeah,
but the coward would do it himself. But
the coward wouldn't do it himself.
That [ __ ] [ __ ] is emailing me, by
the way. that Jade. She needs to stop it
cuz I'm just going to end up going on
her [ __ ] door. Don't try and involve
me with your shitty stupid little games
with LT cuz I'll just come on your door,
bro. I don't give a [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] was emailing me, bro.
[ __ ] why, you know? [ __ ] off, man. You know
there is no God.
Yeah. And I and I spoke sense as well.
Why did you and mommy break up?
I said it was my dad. Is it?
There is no God.
God. There is no God, lad.
There is no God, bro. God don't exist.
God don't exist, bro.
I'm sure I'm going to get the Xbox and
the Smackdown game at some point, Grezy.
Show you all the glitches on it.
I just don't see no point in even
getting out of bed, even trying.
It's a depressing life, bro. Depressing [ __ ] life.
It is, isn't it?
Yeah, that's why I quit the gambling on
the slots and that because um I used to
feel like you I feel like I'd been raped
every time I lost.
It sounds funny, but it's [ __ ] It
does make you feel like that. It's
disgusting, bro. You actually feel like
you've actually been raped. It's horrible.
and robbed at the same time.
I know it sounds funny to you, but it
ain't. It's [ __ ] It actually makes
you feel like that.
It actually does, though. Like, it
actually does. If you could imagine it,
that's how it actually feels like.
So what you say, Nicola? I'm like
Chucky. They can't get rid of me. So
yeah. Well, what do they do with Chucky?
They killed him, right? So if they
killed me, I wouldn't come back, right?
You said I'm like Chucky, you can't get
rid of the [ __ ] right? Yeah. So what
if what if what if you what if I get killed?
Yeah, this one kills me then I can't
come out now. Can I? You know
You can't get rid of me once you meet
me. Is it?
It's like that woman on Reddit. I said,
"I'm your son now. You're stuck with me."
Literally, you're stuck with me, bro. I
was given that Italian abuse earlier,
the one that I met a few months ago. I
said, "You're all the same, you [ __ ]
dirty, slaggy little [ __ ] cunts." Yeah,
I was sticking it on all of the numbers, bro.
I [ __ ] hate the idea.
Yeah, I think that's a fair point.
What would have these people done if
they were in your situation?
If these people's in your situation,
what would have they done? Yeah.
You just going to get rid of the [ __ ] Yeah.
I can't believe I've tried more than
anyone in the world. I'm sure I've
actually broken like the Guinness Book
of Record here.
Went up and down the country. Tried a
million times. Money I spend doing it,
but people still seem to think it's
going to change.
[ __ ] me, bro. They're [ __ ] delusional.
So, yeah. Oh yeah. We have
[ __ ] this life. Infinite mic.
[ __ ] this life, lad. You know,
you need to find God.
My phone might die in a minute. Yeah.
>> Yeah, I did. She was with my momad, but
she was of age and she was in a club.
I approached a girl with her dad before
on the street.
He's like, "Oh, you're barking up the
wrong tree." I said, "No, I'm [ __ ]
not. I'm barking up the right tree."
Yeah. I used to uh I used to get into so many madnesses.
So many, bro. Nah.
Not at all.
It's never going to change.
And when you go out and you try, it
winds you up as well.
I don't know how it doesn't wind people up. [Music]
The whole I've got a boyfriend thing. I
don't know how it doesn't wind people up.
Probably because they not tried as much
as me to be fair.
They're all the [ __ ] same.
I said, you know what I'm going to call
you? I'm going to call you Rudy Roof
cuz you're rude. So, I'm going to call
you Rudy Roof. Is that
all the same?
It's like what Antman said. They say all
the same stuff. They do all the same things.
crazy. They're not all the same, but
they do all the same things. They say
all the same things. They have the same mannerisms.
They do a lot of stuff the same for
people that aren't all the same. Stay
must think, who the [ __ ] is this guy
messaging me? Imagine that, Nicolo. You
must think, who's this guy messaging me?
Who's damning to me, Nicolo?
Just some random guy there.
He's just some random.
Yeah, cuz everybody knows everyone need
needed to know about that that witch.
Everybody needed to know about that witch.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
Do you remember when he was sending voice notes?
Yeah, it's funny that
everyone knows. Yeah, everyone knows
the witch. The evil witch.
The evil [ __ ] Yeah.
I wish I never ever approached Nicolola.
Nicola. I wish I never ever approached lad.
I wish I never ever approached.
You know that [Music]
No, I would have met I would have met
someone through friends.
Yeah, but I might have met someone
through my friends or when I wasn't
looking for it by what people on Reddit say. [Music] No. Yeah, sure.
I might have met someone on a dating app
or something, you know. Yeah.
Okay. What about the dating apps?
Yeah, but people say you get laid on Tinder.
They say you go on Tinder.
Yeah, but that's what they say. If you
want sex, you go on Tinder. Yeah.
I mean, what do you reckon most people
would have done in my position,
Greavves? I think they would have ended
up in prison. So, in in ways I am very
normal because most people would have
ended up in prison. Most people would have
ended up killing someone or something.
So, in a way, you actually are very you
are actually very normal
if you think about it.
No, they wouldn't have dealt with it. So
you're telling me if somebody went up
and down the country, man or woman, and
they can't get anything, they can't get
in a relationship, they had to deal with
this [ __ ] every [ __ ] day for 4 years,
they would have dealt with it. I don't
think so. I don't think so. Somehow
we're never ever ever ever ever
going to we're never going to know
either. That's the thing. We're never
going to know. But I don't think so. I
don't think people have the patience
that I actually have. See, the thing is
you say I act like a baby and I'm a sore loser,
but I've actually got a lot of um
um Yeah, but I was trying to find a
candidate for baby Peter.
So, I mean, no, no one's forcing them,
but I mean, you're trying to find a
candidate for baby Peter, so what?
Yep, I've heard that one before. Yeah. So, yeah.
No, if anyone else was like me, they
would have ended up killing someone. I'm
sure of it, bro. Ended up in prison or
they would have just left a long time ago. Yep.
Think of it, Grezy. You got [ __ ]
around your whole life by women. You
wasted time. You wasted money. And it's
still going on. How would you feel?
How the [ __ ] would you feel? How the
[ __ ] would a woman feel if it happened to them? You know,
it's [ __ ] depressing. It is. Mhm.
So what if I went out tomorrow approaching Nicolo?
I always ask Grezy when's it going to
change? When's it going to change?
And he just gives me [ __ ] answers. Yep. >> Yeah.
Yeah. That theirs isn't about men. Do
you know why Greasy? Cuz they can get
sex when they want.
They can get relationships
when they want.
Yeah. They give them the goodies.
They give the drug dealers the goodies
and the scumbags the goodies.
Don't you find it funny how everyone's
got an abusive ex?
You know they're Isn't it funny how
they've got all got an abusive ex? You know,
you see they all got
an abusive ex.
You know what? Have you you ever watched
that Oreo man video, Nicolo, when he
said, "Stop compliment." He said, "Stop
telling me that I [ __ ] look handsome.
If you [ __ ] tell me that I look
[ __ ] good again, I'm going to go
[ __ ] mad. Stop telling me I look
good." Oh, I don't know if you ever
watched it, but Oh, it's Ace.
Oh, I don't know if you ever watched it, bro.
No, it's Ace. He said, "Stop telling me
that I [ __ ] look good. Stop playing
with me now. You tell me that I [ __ ]
look good again. He's going mad, bro. Literally.
I might put it on, bro. It's funny as
[ __ ] I might put it on.
Yeah, I might pull it on, bro. Yeah, man.
He makes raps about himself
cuz we both think the same about women.
I'll link you the video. Hold on. One second. [ __ ]
Who is it?
It's called Stop Complimenting.
What is it?
He does raps about himself in a negative way.
Where was it now?
Maybe I shouldn't give the channel. actually.
Where the [ __ ] is it? It might must have
been from years ago.
I like watching these people. I relate
to them even though I'm not a virgin. But
this would obviously be a good channel
for Virgin Boy as well cuz he's never
actually been laid, has he? So
where the [ __ ] is that? No, it can't
have been from 9 years ago.
Where is that?
Maybe it is. But
Oh, here it is. Here it is. Oh, mate.
Watch this. This is ace.
Yeah, it's here. It's here.
I love it, bro. I love that video even
to this day. It's ace. He's like, "If
you're not going to break your ass for
me, [ __ ] Stop telling me I look good."
Yeah. I love it. Yeah. [Laughter]
Cuz he's already found his mama.
I hate you people. You mock me. You
know, without me. Yeah. You people would
actually be [ __ ] You wouldn't have
got all of these sayings that I come out
with in it.
You wouldn't have, you know, Virgin Boys
never come out with him. L's never come
You'd be [ __ ] You, you know what I'm
saying? Grevy, who would you [ __ ] watch?
like what? Check that video I sent you, [ __ ]
I'd like to try and get some have some
hope, Greasy, but there is no hope.
I've been up and down the country and
I've approached thousands of women. So,
there is no hope for me.
I don't know how people can still say
there is hope when there is none.
That's what makes me laugh when people
think there's hope when there's
literally no hope. cuz it would have
happened by now.
>> Yeah. A bit, bro.
I just spent all day on Reddit just
swearing at random women. We usually
like just starting [ __ ] with them
cuz they're all evil little [ __ ]
Little [ __ ] westernized hypocrites.
Just starting on them, you know? water.
How come you never watch the virgin
greasy? I know it's never see on Virgin boy channel. H
Yeah, I hate gambling Mike here cuz
every time I lose I feel like I've been
raped. It's horrible, bro.
Tomorrow staying in bed.
Yeah, I'm staying in bed.
Yeah, he's so obsessed with me. Why
would you go on your channel, right? Cuz
you watch me anyways.
Yeah. I I always used to feel like I've been raped,
you know? Might be bad, but that's my
life now, bro. So,
literally, bro, it's horrible.
Feels like you've been raped in it
when you lose. I don't know about you.
No, I've already lived my life, bro. I
don't give a [ __ ] if I drop dead. I
No, I'm all right, bro.
Oh, the fatty with no life.
I stopped gambling. Well, I did the football.
I've been biting my nails a lot, which
is strange cuz I'm not anxious or anything.
No, bro. Listen, I've not played roulette in
Well, no, actually I went on the FBI
last week. That was like the first time
in months, bro. And I don't gamble
online. So, I mean, I've stopped. That
was the first time in like 6 months,
bro. I don't I don't play roulette. I
don't play slots. I only do the football.
I don't really [ __ ] with that anymore
because of the mood swings and [ __ ] I
had to stop because of the mood swings.
Yeah, I had to stop because of the mood swings. So,
no thanks, matey.
Bed's a better place, isn't it, Grievy?
It's more safer for me. Yeah,
it's more safer for me in the neester, of course.
No, I just don't like losing.
I'll show you my football bet again. Oh, [ __ ] Um
yeah, I got B at Colchester. Both teams
have score. Cambridge Liverpool, both
teams have score.
I put 90 on it and it returns 324. Yeah.
So, it's a good return of 90. I normally
put £80 on them, but I just put 90 on it. Yeah.
You reckon that's got a chance? That football bet. Yeah.
You think it's got a chance that
football bet? Um, Mike, I think it does, isn't it? Got
a good chance, isn't it?
I've won so many both teams to scores.
Both teams to score.
Could do with it winning, mate. I need
the extra money to be fair,
but if it doesn't, it doesn't obviously. Yeah.
I wish that time that 75 to1 I wish I
had 500 quid on it, bro. I won a 75 to1
when I was 19. I wish I had like £500 on
it. Oh, [ __ ] hell, man. Yeah.
I wish I had £500 on a 75 to one.
Imagine that, Mike. 500 on a 75 to one. Jesus Christ.
It' be good in it.
out. I'm going to have to meet you, bro,
and smash you up, bro. I'm going to have
to do it. I can't lie.
Yeah. I bet you wish you had more in it,
in it. I bet you wish you had more in Typical, eh?
Bet you wish you had more on it.
Well, I might I'm going to have to meet
you out to have to show everyone who's boss.
Yeah, I only had a pound on mine. I only
had a pound on mine. I wish I had more on it.
20? Yeah. Well, at least you still had
20 pound on it. What is it? 990. Uh,
sorry. 9920. Yeah. Yeah. Still good. I
only had a pound on mine.
Yeah, I only had a pound on mine, bro. [ __ ]
This damn keeps [ __ ] telling me to
find God. LT, what the [ __ ] is that all
about? Find God. Only God can save you. [ __ ] God.
Tell me to find [ __ ] God. What the
Only God can save you. Oh, mate.
No, I'm not a keyboard warrior. They're
a keyboard warrior. They're the ones who
run into the police, bro, from across
the pond. Not me. The keyboard warrior,
bro. I'd slap him up with one finger,
bro. I'm not the keyboard warrior.
They're the keyboard warriors. Yeah,
think of it, bro. You're not even in
their country. Who's the one running to
peace? And don't say they haven't both
cuz I've spoke to their friend. I've
spoke to their best friend on the phone,
bro. Yeah. For 5 hours.
So don't try and [ __ ] tell me they
haven't, bro. Like they're the keyboard
lawyer, bro. They get slapped up. You
know what I said to him? Yeah. I said to
him, "Tell me where you have any
relatives in England. Do you have any
relatives at all?" And then if he said,
"Yeah, I was going to just go in the
door, bro, today. [ __ ] it. I'm not in a mood, bro."
There's nothing keyboard worry about me.
No, he's a bro. I call him a I call him
a fat ugly Puerto Rican [ __ ] mong.
That's what I call him, bro. You don't
know what I call him on my voice, bro. Yeah.
And I've seen people, bro, I've seen a
video of some Irish guy calling someone
a black bastard five times and the guy
done nothing. You probably saw that
video as well. And he done absolutely
nothing, bro. Absolutely nothing. It was
some Irish guy in a van.
No, it No, it's not ages ago what I
said. Yeah, I said something new to him
earlier. Yeah. And also there was a real
of some Irish guy calling someone a
black bastard five times and the guy
done nothing, bro.
So, it's also not every black guy.
It's not every black guy that's going to
do something. What the [ __ ] Yeah.
Cuz I don't I don't need to try it in real life.
I don't need to try it in real life, bro.
I don't need to say. I'm telling you
what I've seen. Rob, you know.
So, yeah. I'm telling you what I've seen. Yeah.
No, I love the [ __ ] all of you.
No, I have the all of you. I' I'd even beat you.
I'd even beat you, bro.
If crunch comes to crunch, I'd actually
beat you. Yeah. Mhm.
I'd even beat you, matey. Yeah.
Know what I'm saying, Rob?
I'll [ __ ] put you in a [ __ ] pile
driver above. That's what I'll [ __ ] do. Yeah,
the other day on [ __ ] Reddit.
No, that black guy's a keyboard warrior.
That diamond's a keyboard warrior.
Who the [ __ ] goes to the police in
another country? Who does that, bro?
Come on, man. Who goes to the police
over someone in a different country?
Like that's just pathetic, isn't it?
Bro, if you think about it, how pathetic
is that? And I'm not saying they went five Oh [ __ ]
I'm not saying that they went five
times, but they they have been not five
times though, but they have been
cuz their friends told me who goes to
the police over someone in a different country, bro.
Who Who even does that, bro? That's crazy.
That is crazy [ __ ]
That is a bit mad, bro.
They only went twice, but still. That's
[ __ ] crazy, bro.
This is why these people need to stop
playing around with people, bro. You
know what I'm saying? They need to stop
playing around with people. It's [ __ ] ridiculous, man.
And then crying to the boys in blue.
What the [ __ ] Crying to the boys in
blue. Another a certain other person
likes to do that, don't they?
To the boys in blue.
I notic a lot of these riches do that.
They go crying to the boys in blue. What
is that? What is all that about? >> Yeah.
So you were trying to cover up for the
[ __ ] scare LT trying to say, "Oh,
she's never gone to the police."
[ __ ] she's [ __ ] has, mate.
[ __ ] pathetic, mate. [ __ ] pathetic.
Yeah, we need to really get revenge on
these [ __ ] you know, bro. I'm
telling you, we need we need to get
legal revenge on these [ __ ]
You know that? Like actually.
Yeah, we actually do, you know.
[ __ ] god, man.
You know what annoys me? Men that defend
women. That's what annoys me. You know,
I know I know it annoys people like men
that go for women. But do you know what
annoys me even more
is when men try to stick up for women.
[ __ ] hate that [ __ ] Even if they're
in the right, I [ __ ] hate that [ __ ]
bro. [ __ ] hate it, babe.
Watch my [ __ ] channel.
Imagine that, Greg. Someone actually run
into the police in another country over social media.
You know, I think that's a bit madness. Yeah,
you're not about nothing, man.
Not about nothing over there. Yeah.
Yeah. I've just been [ __ ] with people
all day. Really, Grezy? Yeah.
I need to make myself some cola. Yeah, it
So, I've got to type something. Yeah.
Would you say you're depressedly since
you don't really go out much?
Yeah, the person is quite dangerous. You see, Greavves.
It makes you start people for no reason and [ __ ]
And obviously it's not good when you've
had bad experiences like me. When you
put it all together in one, it's not
good, is it?
If I didn't have such a long history, I
think I'd be okay. But because I've got
such a long history of this, I'm kind of
[ __ ] Like there's no hope. Like you
can't even be positive about it cuz of
obviously your history and having more
money when you did you do now. And like
if it kind of ain't changed then it
ain't going to change now thing. So
you've got like you got a history of this.
You've got a long history
which is the concerning thing about it.
You see? So
there really anything you can do but leave badly. Uh
I don't know, guys.
I just watch like incel [ __ ]
I just watch like incels and
go on Reddit and [ __ ]
I used to pray for better days,
but um then I realized that there's not
ever going to be any better days.
So then the next thing is you hope you
die and you hope there's an afterlife,
you know. So that's what I pretty much knew. Yeah. Hey
Now, do you believe I'm not agobic music?
Oh, do you believe me, Greavvesy?
I You never know. I could be agrophobic.
I obviously live alone now, so like I
don't um have people that I live with anymore. So um
see the thing as well I used to live
with people and [ __ ]
I always used to spend time with them so
we just used to take the piss out of
each other so we couldn't know you could
never ever get depressed but now I just
feel like isolated and but even then
like there'd be times where I'd come
back and I smacked the whole place up
like you could ask them like
I kept getting the I got a boyfriend I
got a boyfriend. I remember one that day
I smashed the Superman mug.
You remember when I smashed the Superman
mug up and pissed all over the floor
during [ __ ] Ramadan season, bro?
Pissed all over the floor, bro, in the
kitchen. I mean, what? But but to be
fair, my mental health was a lot better
there than it is here.
Cuz um you wouldn't you wouldn't feel
isolated here. You feel very isolated.
It's hard to explain,
but that was only like a That's a rare. Yeah.
Here you feel just left and forgotten about. Greavves.
just left and forgot about, you know.
Um, because I like to come on YouTube
and complain. How comes you come on
YouTube all day, every day, and you
can't take a day off of it?
I answered your question, now you answer mine.
I just come on here to complain about
women. really. I don't get involved in
dramas or anything. Yeah.
See, I used to snap out of it after like
a day cuz there used to be hope. But
there's no hope now. So, I'm [ __ ]
Basically, it's not like, "Oh, try again
tomorrow. Try again Saturday." Cuz we
already know what happens when you try.
So, we ain't we ain't got no hope.
it's bad that I got this history. I
might do a video about this. I might do
I don't know.
I'm sure you watch all my videos, Gre.
I think that's the sad thing is that
there's no hope.
I don't know. I just say I'm going to
leave and I just complain. I just come
on here to complain, you know,
complain about this last
This life that's not changing. Once
you've met one woman, you've met them all.
Once you've met one, you've met them all.
Even at 28 years of age,
I'll be 28 in two months. And there's
been no changes, Reezy.
No changes at all.
Pour myself a glove. I think I'll be
right back. Oh, nice going on.
Yeah, my teeth are getting all nasty
now. I don't even brush my teeth most
days to be honest with you. Horrible.
Oh, I was just talking and I don't think
you heard me. I said I don't even brush
my teeth nowadays. My gums are getting
all nasty in my [ __ ]
Oh, you did hear it.
Yep. That's what happens when you give
up a life, matey.
That's what happens when there's no hope.
The only thing you can hope is when you
die, there's an afterlife with all the
other dead people. Maybe I'll go to
heaven with Michael Jackson and [ __ ]
other people that's died and [ __ ]
We all waiting there.
Get all in.
I'm housebound. G we
just wish there was some sort of hope
but there is none.
There is none.
I think there is no hope at all. Well,
there is no hope. I'm no longer living
in the moment now. So, I can take a step
back and actually see it for what it is.
This ain't never going to change. Things
are never going to change. Women are
never going to change. Never.
It's never going to change, bro.
I'm no longer living in the moment like
I was for three and a half years. Not
just basically saying that I give up
with life. Bit like we all give up with Yeah. Yep. in it.
BD. What's What's a BD?
No, she wouldn't. I don't like the [ __ ]
I hope she gets cancer and dies.
Oh no family. [ __ ] [Music] What life
gives you? What hope is there?
There's no change.
Yeah, they call me USA stalker. Like her
friend and [ __ ] They they just know me
as the stalker.
That's Q in it.
Yeah, what a life, eh?
So, I need to save up a couple of
thousand probably for them two weeks
that I go away, which shouldn't be too hard.
It will be harder, but it's possible.
What do you mean? I don't know what you mean, bro.
Oh, so basically, you know, like when
you write to me mocking me, like when
I'm outside and you see like old people
walk past, I said, "Oh, this could be
this Nickelo account." And no one would
ever know. Just going home every day
with a bit of popcorn and coke coming on
my live stream mocking me. Think
about people that died.
What are you talking about? No.
You know, Antman said to me, Grey, he
said, "It doesn't matter what people
say. You know what these women have been
like for years. You know what they're like."
Is he right? He said, "You know what
they're like. I know what they're like."
It's true, isn't it?
He said, "When you was traveling around
trying your best, they were laughing at you.
mocking you. I was dead. He said they
were mocking you.
I was dead, bro. That That is trolling. Yeah.
Rape victims. A lot of them. You
remember when I used to call him D? Yeah.
You know, imagine LT with his boys doing
what you're doing. Imagine LT sat there.
Yeah. After a night out. Yeah. Doing
what you're doing. Like writing stuff
like comments to eyebrow and then just
laughing about it with his little mates
like all sat at a table. Yeah. on
YouTube typing as I typed by trying to
patronize me. Imagine that gloozy.
Do you remember they used to keep
blaming the poor edge poor [ __ ] House
edge poor [ __ ] only [ __ ] two months
old and seven days. Two months and seven
days and they used to blame that [ __ ] for everything.
See, I had the best I had the best
sayings, you know.
Leave that [ __ ] alone. Don't you even
dare try and blame that little [ __ ]
It's only a newborn, you know. That was
a banger as well, it
poor [ __ ] Always getting the blame
about losing number seeker.
Do you know what used to make me laugh?
See, it's like Mark had some good
sayings. Do you remember Greavvesy? It
looks for what you ain't got.
I remember hearing that years ago when I
used to play the machines. He said it
look for what you ain't got
cuz he covered the pool. Yeah. Mhm.
Yes, Ali could be here with his little
friends on YouTube doing what you're
doing, Nicolo, mocking me and trying to
patronize me and trying to egg me on.
All sat there laughing. Imagine that.
Someone's going to get hurt or sectioned.
What the [ __ ]
They were laughing at you. Is that true
grievy? When I was going up and down the
country, they were laughing at you.
Is Antman a troll?
Greavves, you do think that Ant-Man's a
troll? Yes, sometimes he has to be in it. >> Yeah.
There's different characters.
Um, well, answer this question, Grey,
then. Why do if women are not all the
same, answer me this. Why do they say
the same things, act the same way,
victimize themselves the same way, and
have exactly the same mannerisms, and
play exactly the same games? If they're
not all the same, why do they all do this?
cuz they're not all the same. Surely
they wouldn't do all of that, right? If
they weren't NPCs.
They're [ __ ] NPCs, bro.
They give you that westernized look.
I think it's Tik Tok, isn't it?
They were laughing at you.
Well, I don't I don't I don't seek to
get into their knickers as well, but
they still tell me they've got a boyfriend.
Maybe I want a relationship.
Maybe I want a relationship, but they
keep telling me they got boyfriends.
So, I mean, I never knew I was just
trying to get into their knickers.
I wouldn't be friendly with them.
They're [ __ ] evil [ __ ]
Maybe I want a relationship. Who knows?
Good luck to you.
Good luck to y'all.
Good luck to you, mate. You're going to
need it. Just like what I said to that Italian guy.
Cuz even when you get these people
numbers, their numbers, they say they're
not interested in dating right now. I've
had a lot of people say that, Grezy. But
people on Reddit say that you're going
to meet someone. But everyone you meet
un isn't interested.
So I mean
it goes against guidelines it you know.
Do you want my number?
Do you remember that approach? Um
fast enough to reply to negativity.
I really want you, but I don't think you want me. I do.
Probably she said that to me. What the [ __ ]
Yeah, I said that French woman my dick.
She said, "I thought it was bigger." Dot
dot dot. So small. I'm a little disappointed.
Why are they such trolls, these French
women? This is like the third one that's
done this, bro. I'm a little disappointed.
In real life, they never acted like
that. They acted quite shy and stuff,
but then on here they're [ __ ] trolls. Yeah.
He's another [ __ ] that blocked. He's
another [ __ ] that played games. Yeah.
Yep. You remember that? So, I've been
trolled by three French people now.
I'm a little disappointed,
but yet they act like they don't speak
English. They speak English fine when
they're trolling people.
I'm from France. This is what these
French will do. Nicolo,
they will um be nice to your face and be
like, "Yes, you on my my number." in
their little French accent. I'm from
France. That's what they'll say. And
then then they give you their number,
right? And then they lead you on.
They lead you on.
They're laughing at you the whole time.
They're laughing at you. Yeah.
But they never say they've got a
boyfriend, which is strange.
Why are they going to say they've got a
boyfriend? They'd rather give you their
number and [ __ ] with your head.
They [ __ ] with your head, wouldn't they?
They'd rather do that. Yeah.
them [ __ ] were laughing at us. Mhm.
I really want you, but I don't think you want me. I do.
Hey, I got a story about a Scottish
woman um that I approached Greavvesy,
right? So, I approached her and she's
like I said, "Oh, let's meet." And in
two weeks uh two weeks after she said,
"I'm not in London." And I was trying to
get a hold of her.
I voice noted and I sent one more
message. And she just wasn't clicking on
the message to for love nor money. As
soon as I said I hated women, that all
changed. She was on the message straight
away. Nicolo, I was trying to get a
response for [ __ ] god knows how long.
I had to [ __ ] follow up. She was
nowhere to be seen. But as soon as that
negative message got sent, she was there before before [ __ ]
before before you could say Jack [ __ ] Robinson. it. Yeah.
Right. Makes you wonder, don't it? Makes you wonder.
Rudy Roof's gone quiet.
Rudy Roof has gone quiet.
Yeah, I still talk to Chinese is he? >> Yeah.
She calls me dear. She says, "Dear, I
can't speak English." That always that
always makes me die. She has to
translate the language. She says, "Dear,
I don't speak English, dear." She calls me dear.
Chinese calls me
calls me dear. Yeah.
Women are disgusting. Greasy. [ __ ]
disgusting. They are disgusting [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] disgusting.
What they put people through
keeping them alone and single. Disgusting. It disgusted it.
So anyways, Greg, I want a relationship.
So how do I get a relationship? Yeah.
Do you remember that Portuguese one I
went on a date with?
But Greg, every time I try to speak some
to somebody, they say they've got a boyfriend.
It's like they prog you a sex life. Uh
they pres they beg you changing your malro status.
It's horrible. They keep you single and
alone. It's horrible, isn't it? Really horrible.
It's so bad, you know.
I think giving up was the best idea. I
think that was the best thing to do, bro. You know,
cuz what you're not what you're not in
can't hurt you, right?
You know what I mean? G uh Grezy.
But then I don't like using escorts cuz
I feel like using escorts they if you
use escorts it's like they win.
I mean even going Thailand they win but
I mean it's like a holiday at the same
time sort of thing, you know? It's sort
of like you're going on holiday as well. Oh yeah. Yeah. >> Yeah.
So, what about Franklin? Where will
Franklin be, Grezy?
So, Greavvesy, you're saying that you
could go to America in four months if
you saved your money?
Really, Grezy? Really?
No, you couldn't.
So, you could save up four grand in 4 months.
Don't be silly.
Don't be a silly goose.
Don't be a silly goose, lad.
So you could say about four grand in four months.
So it' be about two grand for the flight
hotel and 1,500 spending money. Yeah.
And you you could do that in 4 months. Yeah.
be hard it would be hard.
>> You'd be hard, huh?
See, I find it I find it hard living off
£1,100 a month, but I I won like £400
last month on the football, so that's
why it's sort of even itself out.
It's not hard to live off, but I mean,
you won't be able to go out drinking and
[ __ ] a lot. It's nowhere near as bad as
these people make out. It's not bad, but it's like
you won't be able to like
you can get short very quickly, but it's
nowhere near as bad as these people make
out. But these people are fantasists,
right? All in all, it's like 1,400 last
month cuz obviously the football bets in
it. So, it's all even itself out.
So obviously if we win this football on
Saturday it's we be at the same again
which is obviously enough. So you go in.
Yeah they were mocking you. Yeah.
It's not nowhere near as bad as these
people make out like 1100 pound a month.
It's not as bad as you'll just run.
You'll just be short if you went out
drinking a lot and [ __ ]
Like I said, it wasn't £1,100 last month
cuz I won the football twice. So,
I'll probably have to start this job soon.
I need to get extra money, but I can't
be asked, bro. I don't want to I don't
want to deal with people.
Yeah, you could do it in four months, Grezy, but
you wouldn't be able to go out.
You wouldn't be able to go out though. So yeah,
you've not been out since what? You've
not been out of the house since, mate.
out drinking you silly goose.
Yeah, we got to that age where we don't
do it much anymore.
It's never going to get you laid. Anyways,
I need this football bet to win on
Saturday, bro. It's a nice little
winner. 324, it was quite nice
for 90 quid.
with a nice return.
They were laughing at you.
I'm knocking you. Yeah. Barnet, Colchester,
Cambridge and Newport.
I think it's going to win, bro.
Cambridge, Newport, Bonnet, Colchester.
And I put 90 on it.
We have a new lucky number, you know.
How much you doing on it? I put 90 on it.
Yeah, do it's a normal both teams a
score. It's not a both score no draw.
Even though I probably should have done
both team both scar no draw.
Why is it risky, bro?
I just said both teams to score.
your boyfriend, man.
Yeah, I got 90 pound on it.
The first game we won at the season was
good, bro. 80 return 285. That was good odds, man.
And then we won the second week as well.
That was good, bro. Good.
Yeah, we lost the third one.
Yeah, we we won. We won two, didn't we? Yeah.
Women are disgusting. Yep.
I always used to feel like USA laughed
at me when I was losing.
Do you reckon USA loves me? Nico,
she thought, "Let me just block this
[ __ ] That'll be the end of it." Is it
like Chucky, bro?
Yeah. 90 on the [ __ ]
It's nice. It's nice over 300 lb win. That is
quite a good return.
No, I couldn't because she blocked me. Yep.
You remember that G? You remember that
gay one I was arguing with?
The first one paid well. 80 return 285.
It was a good return. So yeah,
you remember that Birmingham date I went
on Niko though? You're trying to get me
to pay for the food and the drink,
and I w to [ __ ] get any
get any get anything in return. Yeah.
No, I thought that
Oh yeah, I do actually remember that
actually. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, I do. Remember
when I used to have dreams of USA is There. Yeah.
You remember everything, don't you?
Why does Reddit keep banning me? Why
does the mods keep banning me, Nicolola?
They keep banning me, bro. Yeah.
Yep. You remember, don't you, Nicolai?
You remember everything. Yeah.
Why does the mod keep banning me on Reddit, Nicolo? Yeah, literally
they also defend women.
They love defending women as well.
Virgin boy likes defending women as well.
Even though he's still a virgin, he's
going to probably die a virgin. Virgin boy Yeah,
hair's greasy. I feel dirty, greasy, but
I don't need to shower since I've given
up a life. So, I don't need to do anything.
When you give up life, isn't it? Give up on life.
Sorry about that. >> Yeah.
It will never change. It will never Sad. Level. off.
Yeah, I hope I die in my sleep.
Yeah, I'm a phobic, isn't it? Uh, we I'm aophobic. Yeah.
So what if I go out tomorrow approach him?
Yep. Probably about 5, six, maybe even 7.
I didn't think I was actually going to
get to sleep to be fair.
Yeah. When the birds sing,
you know that new, you know, that
[ __ ] New Year's Eve I went out, I
must have approached about
probably a hundred [ __ ] women that
day. I'm not even joking.
I'd like to know where these different women are.
I'd like to know where these women are
that aren't the same cuz I've never
found one. Don't know about you, I've
never found one.
the Indian pond. Which what?
Not sure what you're talking about. pond. [Music]
What were you on about?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I remember.
That's when Venom come on here, it
weren't on. He weren't on it, was he?
He weren't on it, was he? He weren't on that [ __ ] No.
Nah, he weren't on it, was he, bro? No.
What do you reckon my funniest highlight
to YouTube has been?
What do you think the funniest highlight was?
I think the Izzy thing was funny in it.
The Izzy thing was funny. Do you
remember Virgin Boy when he saw me meet
Izzy and the first time and he got
jealous. He's like, "Nah, you didn't
[ __ ] her. You didn't [ __ ] her. You
didn't [ __ ] her." Cuz cuz he's never
[ __ ] anything and he's still a virgin.
He hates the fact of anyone getting sex
cuz he's still a virgin.
Have you noticed that?
Cuz he's still a virgin.
He's going to [ __ ] die a virgin as well.
Nah, bro. No one's interested in this [ __ ] anymore.
How much do you think you really
realistically would spend on a night out of drinking?
I'd say probably about £100.
Probably about 100. 70 to 100.
Yeah, cuz he's still a virgin. That's why.
Yeah, it's cuz he's the virgin. He said,
"Oh, no matter how many times you say
I'm a virgin, it's not going to convince
people." I'm not trying to convince
people. I'm telling you what you
literally are. You are a virgin.
I'm not trying to convince anyone
anything. I'm telling you what you are.
It's only just me and you. I don't care
about other people. I'm [ __ ] telling
you what the [ __ ] you are. [ __ ] stinky virgin.
You know what I'm saying? Greasy. Virgin
[ __ ] who's never had it. I win.
If I don't believe it, I wouldn't say it. Yeah.
Is this football back going to win or not?
[ __ ] better win, mate.
You're a [ __ ] better one. Yep.
Literally, I'm going to do it all day here.
Calling them evil, disgusting [ __ ] cuz
that's what they are. Evil, disgusting [ __ ]
You remember the one in the park? She
got [ __ ] scared, isn't it? You're not
so big when you got someone in your
[ __ ] telling you about yourself, are
you? Just not even in your face. You're
not so big then, are you? You [ __ ]
You're not so big, are you? You can't
tell I was in your face cuz I weren't
even in your face. I weren't anywhere
near you. You're not so big then, are
you? You [ __ ]
Nah, you're not so big then, are you?
You weren't so big then, were you?
No, I weren't so big then.
Yep, they are. Yeah. Yep.
Oh, is that it? It's a bit small. I'm a little disappointed.
That's what the French one said about my dick, Nikolai.
They're such [ __ ] trolls, isn't it?
See, I'm a little disappointed.
I find it so mad how they only reply
back to weirdness.
So, when that Twitter thing come about,
I had so many messages. It was quite
actually felt popular.
I felt popular, you know.
Yeah. How do you remember all of these
things? You're a weirdo. You are. That's
definitely Joker. That Yeah.
You know how I know I'm a YouTube
legend? Cuz Greavvesy only goes on my
chat. Nicolo only goes on my chat and
Steven Howard only goes on my chat.
That's how you know I'm a legend. Yeah. So yeah,
I'll be slagging off women all day
today till like 6:00 in the morning.
Wake up, do it all over again. Yeah.
Yeah, you like my little live streams
and that is it. LT sat there with his
little mates mocking me on YouTube.
Imagine that. Grezy
sat there before a night out laughing at
me around the table with his little
friends putting me up typing messages.
I already done Barnet. No, they don't hardly score.
They scored [ __ ] last week.
[ __ ] Swindon that [ __ ] me up or someone else.
No, I got Sweden. I got a bonnet.
You know I got Bonnet, bro.
They got to score. They scored last time.
Born going to score. Nicola.
Do you reckon Bonn's got a SC?
What do you think about Bonnet, bro? Do
you think they're going to score?
They beat Swindon last week.
Like, do you think it's a good football
battle, Nicolo or N?
I almost got [ __ ] freed [ __ ] two
weeks ago, man. I just needed one more
goal. I almost got a [ __ ] treble both
teams to score.
Almost got a treble, bro.
Just one goal away. Oh,
I was one [ __ ] goal off. 140 from 20 almost.
What do you think? Do you think Blet's
going to score? Okay.
Okay, that's cool. Yeah.
I just asked for dating advice on Reddit. Um,
uh, his name is Virgin Boy. What's his name?
Uh, Virgin Boy. His name His His name is
literally Virgin Boy.
That's his name. Virgin Boy.
So, anyways, Nicolo is born. It got a score. What
are we doing?
Is Born going to score or not?
Yeah, he lost. He lost it.
So, do you reckon that bet has got a
good chance of winning?
I think it's got a little while. Yes, sir. Yeah.
Yeah. I would give it a little while.
Poor damn getting messages in it.
Poor damn getting messages, bro.
Fine god, little man.
Can't believe she went to the police
over [ __ ] social media. Nicola.
Uh, just an ex of a one night stand. I
had Yeah, I had a one night had a
holiday romance and then she [ __ ] me
up. [ __ ] me over. Then I had to start
like messaging her exes and [ __ ]
Yeah, I was going to do crew and
swinden, but I didn't like they were I
didn't like the fact they were playing
at 12:30. So, yeah. Yeah.
Why would I message her exes? Just
funny, isn't it? Something to do,
ain't it, Nicolo? Something to do.
Yeah. So what?
Just some just funny, isn't it?
Why did you mommy Why did you and mommy break up? 7 hours.
No, he's not a virgin.
Is the bet I done good, Nicolo, or not?
Is the bet I actually done good or what? Yeah,
it's your lucky day. The slower the better.
I remember I told my friend Yeah. what
she was saying to me. Her friend was
pissing herself laughing.
What? She did that? Yeah.
Yeah, she said that.
What the [ __ ] Yeah.
But is my bet actually good, Nicolo, or not?
Is it a good bet?
It [ __ ] better come in, mate. >> Yeah.
I mean, but what am I going to do if it
comes in, bro? I'm just probably going to [ __ ]
I'll probably go cinema, to be honest.
Something's coming out soon, is it?
Oh, one second
on Rainbow. Um, Grezy. Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ] Remember,
do you remember he was like, "Oh,
bungle, you dirty bear." Oh, yes.
You dirty bear. Yeah.
Feels like you've been [ __ ] raped. It does.
I don't even think you can play. You
can't even play on roulette anymore, is
it, Nicolola? cuz I'm on GameStop and
them other sites are dodgy. So I don't
even think you can play like online
roulette any um fair roulette anymore,
can you? So yeah,
the channel is wrong in media if you
want to see it.
Yeah, if you want.
Look how desperate you are for a grass.
You really need to get laid.
You really, really need to lose that vcard.
I'm telling you, son. You're doing
anything just to try to get someone
nicked. You need to get laid.
You know, you know what you're saying
about what people think and what people
don't think. You need to literally lose
your virginity. I'm telling you, forget
[ __ ] anyone watching this. I'm
telling you, you're a virgin. I don't
care what people believe or what other
people don't believe. I'm f I know you
better than you know your [ __ ] self.
[ __ ] you [ __ ] virgin tongue. How
do you think I know about this and that
and this and that? It come from me.
Tilly the Dalmatian
[ __ ] you know Philip Campbell from
Leeds. Who knows all these things? I do.
I know you better than you know your [ __ ] self.
You're [ __ ] virgin. Can't you
virgin? And yeah. Yeah. Want
to make a cup of cont.
Where's my mater?
The belly can't get attached anymore
because he's already found his mama. Yeah.
I need to go in a bit. Well, actually
Yeah, I believe in hitting women. I
believe in hitting women, greasy, cuz
they're not supposed to defend
themselves. You know how people say,
"Oh, they can't defend themselves." But
they're not supposed to.
When were they supposed to really defend
themselves? They weren't supposed to defend themselves.
If a woman's being a [ __ ] slap her
around the face.
They're not supposed to defend themselves.
You know, they're weaker. Good for them.
I mean, you know, they're not supposed
to really defend themselves.
The point is them to get is to get a [ __ ] slap.
I believe in it. I believe in it a lot,
actually. You know,
if I see that USA is
I would do if I was in front of that
USA, I'd give her one bang. She wouldn't
even get up. I would do it.
Generally would do it. I've never been
in a situation where I've had to. There
was one time I was about to, but my
friend pulled me back. Yeah. Yeah,
but I would definitely do it 100%. I've
spat at a woman. I've spat at a woman if that counts. You know,
I've spat at a woman in Nottingham. Yeah,
she was being a [ __ ] so I spat her. Not
like straight in her face, but I spat
her. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yep, it certainly did.
The [ __ ] [ __ ]
I believe in hitting women. If I saw
that USA, I'd smack her one across her
face. It wouldn't even be a beat and it
would just be one punch and that would be it.
Uh, the spit did hurt her. I'd literally
just said that about a million times.
Bro, you're [ __ ]
Stop trying to bait me as well. Stop
trying to be a weirdo and trying to bait
me. That's what it seems like you're
doing. Why you asking the same thing
over and over again? I spat at the [ __ ]
I know what you're trying to do. It's
not going to work. It's obvious what
you're trying to do,
bro. I spat at her. End of story. [ __ ] me. So, yeah.
Yeah, I believe in hitting women. Yeah, defin
maybe not your mom or someone, but I
definitely believe in it.
None of you have actually seen this. Uh,
that's because you don't see every
second of every day of my life.
So you wouldn't see it because you're
not with me every second of every day of
my life, whatever I do.
So yeah, and you're banned. Bye-bye.
See you later, weirdo.
I need to brush my teeth greasy cuz I'm
getting like a not an absess but um a root canal
from all the sugar that I eat
eat and drink and drink.
They will never change.
It will never change. Yeah.
Oh, stop me.
I haven't drunk for ages, Cory.
I haven't drunk for ages, man.
I can't be bothered, bro.
What if I go out tomorrow and do some approaches? Cory,
what would happen? H
what do you think would happen?
Are you sure? What makes you so sure?
Cuz it never happened two weeks ago. It
never happened before that. It never
happened before that. What makes you so sure?
I don't believe you, bro.
No, I can't, bro. These women have to pay
these I need some sort of revenge.
I need some sort of revenge, bro, before
I can do that.
I need some sort of revenge on them.
I need to meet one and ruin their life
or something like that, bro. I need to
do do a madness, you know?
I don't know what I'm going to do yet.
I'm not sure.
I don't know what I'm going to do yet. Grezy
Grezy will turn his little telly on his
42 in telly and see me on the news.
I don't know what I want to do. Yeah. Right.
I'll be back tomorrow. Yeah.