Yeah.
[ __ ] finger. [ __ ] bro.
Whoa, actually ate. I haven't even ate
today. [ __ ] Oh [ __ ] Well, I was about
to and it taking too [ __ ] long.
Yeah, it was taking too [ __ ] long.
So I didn't. So yeah. Yep. Even
One second. Why is that not working?
Hey, I didn't eat today, Greavves. I
went to the Chinese. They were trying to
make me [ __ ]
wait [ __ ] half an hour, bro. I
thought, "Fuck that." And I went into a
shop. Had to buy some milk. They were
taking ages. I was going to walk out
with it. I was about to [ __ ] walk out
So, I probably won't eat today, to be honest.
I don't think I've been a day without
eating for years. Yep. [ __ ] years.
So, I probably won't eat today. I had a
shower and that though. I changed, but I
don't think I'll eat today, bro.
I'm too depressed to eat thinking of my bad experiences.
I will do a video on it later. Bless you. Good.
Yeah. I'm just sat here. Did you eat?
You know, I used to sometimes just
starve myself for like a day or two
just cuz it was funny.
Like doing something dafted. Felt like
You know what I mean?
Just doing something really dafted. Yeah.
I'm kind of hungry, not going to lie. KFC, maybe.
Haven't ate all day.
Maybe get some KFC. Maybe.
Yeah, I'm not angry as angry today, but
I'm still depressed as [ __ ]
which something I'm going to probably
have to deal with for the rest of my
life. How I've tried more than anyone in the world,
so best get used to it.
It's [ __ ] depressing, isn't it?
All right, let me get this anyways.
She don't want to know you.
That seems a lot cheaper.
Maybe I got to deal with something. Yep.
Life is [ __ ] Hey, I'm speaking to this
woman in Canada, Greavesy, but I'm sure
she's going to disappear at some point. Yeah.
[ __ ] I don't even like going up the
road now in this country. I hate this
country. It depresses the [ __ ] out of me, bro.
the experiences with women waiting
around for things. I told you it wasn't
just one thing. So yeah.
Yep. I had another woman today on
WhatsApp say, "I have a boyfriend."
Again, they all do and say exactly the same stuff,
you know. They do and say exactly the same stuff,
but they're not the same. Well, at least
I didn't go out today, ain't it?
Until you lose hope, you're [ __ ]
That's the thing, Gre. Until you lose
hope, you're [ __ ] The only way you'll
break the cycle is if you meet someone
or you lose hope. And obviously, I lost
hope. So, if you don't lose hope or meet
someone, you're basically [ __ ] because
you're in the same cycle forever. It's
horrible way to live.
Horrible, horrible way to live.
There is no hope. There is no hope whatsoever. Oh [ __ ] So yeah,
got the football back tomorrow. I don't
even care about this life.
>> You know what, Greavves? You know what a
lot of people never done? And this is
what I'm going to say in my video. I
feel like a lot of people never gave me
credit. Like I feel like a lot of people
like you know obviously some people can
agree, some people can disagree, some
people can even feel sorry for you, but
I felt like no one ever gave you credit
for all the times you tried and the [ __ ]
that you went through with these women.
I I I generally feel like no one ever
ever gave me the credit any credit or
you know I noticed that. That's one
thing I was actually noticing. No one's
ever really done that, have they?
like any anyone would think you never tried,
which also is a good point to add on
your video as well. Like it's not like
you you never tried. You [ __ ] tried
more than anyone. [ __ ] me.
So it's not like um
you know when I got stung by the [ __ ]
reality beat. I I I realized this.
It's like I literally got stung by
reality beat when I weren't living in
the moment anymore. And and I noticed
that no one ever ever gave me credit for
trying, did they? They just called me
names. I noticed that as well. Yeah.
Odd. Very [ __ ] odd.
No one ever gave me credit for trying or
cuz God loves a try. You know what? Why?
Anyone that tries something should be respected
even if it's your enemy doing it. I
know. I noticed that.
I definitely noticed that.
That's what makes all of this so [ __ ] up.
That's what makes this whole situation
so [ __ ] up, you know? So, yeah.
That's what happens when you're not
living in the moment, bro.
You have a You're back to reality. You
you you think of all the things that's
happened to you and all the things
you've tried. I'm sure if this was
anyone else, they would have ended up in
a mental hospital. I swear to God, bro,
no one's as patient as me. You know, you
can say what you want. Oh, um,
you can say what you want, like, oh
yeah, you're a s loser or, "Oh yeah, you
got ADHD." But can't deny I've got
patience dealing with that [ __ ] for
[ __ ] how many years I did, you know,
with them [ __ ] So [ __ ] you can't even
take that away.
Nothing. I just ordered KFC.
Yeah, Chinese was taking too long, so I
had to I bought that. So, yeah. Yeah, man.
Didn't go out today. I won't be going
out tomorrow. Even if the football wins,
I'm not interested in this country anymore.
Simple. I ain't interested.
So, I'm not interested in games and im immature people.
So, I've got like no numbers now I can try with.
And I am not going out doing this again.
No [ __ ] way am I going out doing this
[ __ ] again. You You can [ __ ] right off.
It ain't about the I've got a boyfriend
[ __ ] Grezy. It's about everything.
Cuz think about it. What if we went out
today? We're not going to get it all
day, are we? Yeah, we're going to get it
a lot. But it's the other thing that you
get. It's not one thing.
It's not [ __ ] one [ __ ] thing, you know?
Yeah, I just I don't have no new numbers
now, bro. Like, I just [ __ ] with them
all cuz they were being [ __ ] So
So what are you saying about what I
said, Grevy? You know I'm right, don't
you? No one ever gave me credit in all
of them years of trying, going
Manchester a million times. No one ever
gave me credit for that, did they? I
noticed that. No one ever gave me credit.
Am I lying, Grezy? Did you give me credit or
am I lying?
No one ever gave me credit. They just ridiculed me.
I think that amount of dedication and
trying should be respected to be honest, you know. So yeah.
So, no new numbers now. Yeah,
it's bad. Is it Greasy? Very bad.
So, you don't think there's any truth in
what I'm saying? Yeah, [ __ ] well is.
Yeah, [ __ ] well is, mate.
You're probably going to have to go to
[ __ ] therapy, bro, after all of that
trying and getting nowhere. I think
that's like a that's an issue you're
probably going to have to go to therapy
for to be honest.
All that trying still nothing. Still
getting the same advice.
What do you think? It's mad.
Well, Grezy doesn't care cuz it doesn't suit him.
It doesn't suit him.
My experiences don't suit Grezy, Steven
Howard. We're very aware of them, but
they don't suit uh Greasy.
Yeah, my experiences don't suit Grezy.
Yeah, they don't suit you, do they?
I can't even keep still, bro. I was out.
I wanted to punch someone in the face.
There was some [ __ ] fat woman that
called me mate. I say if anyone calls me
mate again, I'm going to start again.
Bro, if anyone calls me mate again, I'm
going to start some mad [ __ ] bro.
It doesn't suit you that I've tried more
than anyone in the world.
Doesn't suit you.
What? What do you think of that? I've
trib more than anyone in the world. I
should be respected.
You know, I'm surprised no one's
respecting me for all that effort that I
put in. Wow.
That's crazy, isn't it? Madness.
How do you work that one out?
Well, you're wrong. You're completely
You are completely completely wrong.
I said that's what I'm going to start
doing to give them back what they've
gave me over the years. [ __ ] being
you know. So, I said I'm going to go out
and just get them and use them for their
body to [ __ ] with them. Yes. Because of
what they've done to me over the years.
Yes. Yes. Cuz they're [ __ ] Yes, I did say that.
Yes, because they were being [ __ ]
What the [ __ ] They started it. So yeah,
I feel like I've got like a big reality check, lad.
You know, I feel like I've um I feel
like I got a lot like a reality check
when I lost this house. You know that?
Like not [ __ ] but I feel like I know
now, you know?
Well, they all seem to do exactly the
same thing, Greezy. I mean, they all
reply to negativity. They all say the
same stuff. They all do the same [ __ ]
They all say the same [ __ ] I feel like
every single conversation I've had with
one, I've had with [ __ ] many others.
I actually get flashbacks of ones that
I've had with other people. I mean,
like I said, for them to not be all the
same, they do a lot of the same stuff.
I'm not saying anything, bro. I don't
I'm just saying for people that are not
all the same, they do exactly the same
stuff as each other, which is a bit
suspect, do you not think? Two people
that don't know each other doing exactly
the same thing.
Acting entitled, saying the word mate,
pretending they got boyfriends, all it's
so many different things. It's not even
just that. Same strange. It seems
strange, isn't it, for people that
aren't the same, you know?
It's they they they do a lot of they
have a lot of similar similarities, you know,
they have a lot of similarities and the
fact that they all reply back to
negativity as well, which is what do men
do that? Men don't [ __ ] do that. So
what? I don't know any man that's got
similarities to me.
Ain't no man that's the same as me, bro.
I can safely say that.
So, bro, they like I said, for people
that aren't all the same, they act they
sure act all the same. You know, you
want to meet halfway, little little bud
fist bump. We'll meet in the middle
because I feel like I've had the same
conversation with different women where
they try to be entitled, take the piss,
be [ __ ] It seems a lot of them are
like that, bro. Even people that are in
their 30s, it seems like that a lot.
piss taking, you know, trolling,
flaking. They do a lot of the same
stuff, bro. I give you, you know,
saying that they've got a boyfriend on
WhatsApp as well. That's another thing
I've had about four times where someone
don't message back and then they message
back saying they got a boyfriend over WhatsApp, you know. So, So yeah,
I never ask for their number within 30
seconds. And and in the numbers is when
I've got numbers. I had one French one
to say, "Oh, look." She's like, "Oh, I
have a boyfriend. I have a boyfriend."
I'm sick of [ __ ] hearing it, bro.
I've heard that a million times now. And
I'm not talking about approach. I'm
talking about numbers. I You know them numbers,
them replies I got from them numbers
were all similar. I have a boyfriend. I
have a bro. I swear to God, three of
them said they had a boyfriend out of
all of them. That like it's [ __ ]
over these WhatsApp numbers. They all
say the same stuff.
Influenced by Tik Tok, brainwashed by
Tik Tok. They say and do all the same
stuff. Cuz let me tell you something,
Grezy. I didn't travel all around the
country wasting my own money to say I
told you so. That's ridiculous.
I didn't do all of these things to put
my [ __ ] thumbs in my earlobes waving
my hands around with my tongue out
saying that I [ __ ] told you so.
I never [ __ ] done that. So
tell you that for nothing, mate. I can
[ __ ] tell you that for nothing.
They do exactly the same stuff.
They're like NPCs, bro. [ __ ] madness.
If I was if I was in Canada right now or
somewhere other than America, I'd be out today.
I'd be out today. If I was somewhere
other than here, Canada, even though
it's westernized country, like say I
just happen to live there or somewhere
other than here, I'd be out
generally would be out today drinking. Yeah.
So, you know,
they do all the same stuff.
This French one was like, and they all
tried to reverse the psychology to like victimize themselves. Um,
so I I feel like it's just best to just
call it a day. We
generally feel like it's best to just
call it a day here.
So I generally feel like
that's that's it. Yeah.
I feel like I' I've proved what I wanted
to prove, you know? So, but I wasn't
trying to prove anything. I was trying
to [ __ ] find someone. That was the
whole [ __ ] point of doing this was
actually to find someone, you know? It
wasn't actually to prove anyone right or
wrong. it was to actually find someone. So
that's why I don't go out most days. I
just stay in. It's too depressing.
Like it's too depressing going out.
I just went out for like [ __ ] half
hours. Just too depressing, you know? So
Look, there's one here, bro.
There's one here. Please, can you stop
texting me? I said to her, "No thanks."
I said, "Otherwise." She said,
"Otherwise, I'll block you." I said,
"Why do you give your number and you
ignore?" She said, "Because I have a
boyfriend." [ __ ] Doesn't have a
boyfriend. I said, "Why you give your
number?" So, she said, "Stop." I said,
"Yeah, right." I said, "Fuck your
boyfriend and show him my big dick."
That's what I said. Yeah. [ __ ] off with
your [ __ ] stupid boyfriend [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] off.
Yeah. People [ __ ] stop approaching to
stop hearing that [ __ ] We're still
[ __ ] hearing it. [ __ ] right off, mate.
Cuz I'll make you and your boyfriend
suck my [ __ ] dick. I'll [ __ ] you
both. Both of you. You know what I'm
saying? I'll I will [ __ ] both of you,
bro. You know what I'm saying?
I'll go to France and [ __ ] you both. You
know what I'm saying?
And put on [ __ ] YouTube. I'll [ __ ]
you both, mate. Yeah. One second.
They're all trolling bastards. That's
another thing, Grevy. They're all trolling bastards.
But I'm sure if I went out today, it was
going to be different, wasn't it, Grezy?
Yeah, it would have been different today. Yeah.
Yeah. It would have been completely different today.
Yeah, it would have been so different
today. It wouldn't have been been Yeah.
So different today.
Do you know Stephen Howard? If I went
out today, it would have been so
different. If I went down to the brewery
today, it would have been so different.
That brewery that I wanted to go down,
it would have been so different today, you know.
Yeah, it would have been so different.
Didn't you know it would have been so
different today, Grezy? Yeah.
Do you want to do another bet, Grezy? Do
you want to do you want to bet?
Do you want to bet? Do you want me to go
out tomorrow? We bet some money
and I will do everything you say. Do you
want Do you want to do a bet tomorrow?
I'll get a haircut, everything. I I'll
make it fair. I bet you tomorrow I will
go out and all I get is I have a [ __ ]
boyfriend and numbers that take the piss.
You want to bet, Grezy? Come on. Come
on. I'll bet you, bro. Fair. Fair and
square. We'll do the bet fair and
And you tell me how many people you want
me to approach and where.
Do you want do you want to have a bet?
Come on, Greasy. Let's bet. Come on.
Come on, Greasy. What are you scared of?
Come on, Greasy. Come on.
No, I'll go to bars and pubs. I'll go to
I will go to bars and pubs, bro. I won't
do it on the street. I'll do whatever
you want. Wherever you want me to
approach, I'll do it. You know,
I feel like if you didn't find anyone
four years ago, you're kind of [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying?
If you didn't meet anyone them years
ago, you're kind of [ __ ]
But I I'll approach. But bro, I'll do it
in the pubs, in the clubs. I won't do it
on the street. I'll do it wherever you
want me to do it
and I'll say whatever you want me to
say. Does that sound like a good deal? Yeah.
Yeah. That's all you ever get.
If I And you're saying long distance
don't work. Greavves. If I find someone
in another country, when I come back,
I'm going I will leave again.
I will leave again. I will leave. I will leave, bro.
But not America. But I I will leave.
I'll go Canada and make a make a new
life for myself, bro. I will [ __ ] relocate.
Oh, that was yummy, Grezy.
Oh, Grezy, I scuffed the absolutely I
I scoffed the absolutely lot. Oh,
that was delicious. Oh, [Applause] yummy, yummy. Hey
m I already finished it. Yummy. I
gobbled a lot. I had some chicken strips
and a piece of chicken. Chicken strips.
Piece of chicken and some chips. M yummy.
Oh, that was yummy.
Wow, that was yummy. Yep.
Oh, do you know what? Do you know what
Virgin Boy used to say, Grezy?
When I used to meet him, he used to say,
"That's not socially acceptable." I
said, "I don't give a [ __ ] what this
[ __ ] up society sees as acceptable. I
don't want no part of it." That makes
you laugh, in it,
I don't give a [ __ ] what's socially
[ __ ] acceptable. What I done what I
done up the road was was probably not so
today probably wasn't socially acceptable.
You know, I don't give a [ __ ] what's
socially acceptable. [ __ ] society.
What do you say about that, Grezy?
I don't give a [ __ ] what's socially acceptable. You know
who's with me.
I don't give a [ __ ]
So, but but but getting with a 16y old
is socially acceptable. A 42y old man
with a 14y old is acceptable.
Nons's dad and non legs his mom. But
that's socially acceptable, huh?
But that's socially acceptable.
[ __ ] So, I don't give a [ __ ] what this
I I stay in cuz I hate society. Greasy.
I don't I'm not If we done what was
socially acceptable, we'd be on our
phones. We'd be glued to Tik Tok. Is
that socially acceptable? Being glued to
[ __ ] Tik Tok and being a [ __ ] NPC.
Is that [ __ ] Is that Is that what you
class as [ __ ] acceptable?
[ __ ] off. I don't want any part of this [ __ ] society, you know?
about that's not socially acceptable,
you [ __ ] virgin. [ __ ] try and tell
me what's socially acceptable, you [ __ ] virgin.
You like it when I say that, ain't it, Grezy?
You You love it when I own Virgin boy. Ain't it?
Who? Everyone or just me?
Nah, not really, bro.
It's just I won't going to let that
Polish pig bouncer try and tell me who I
can and can't talk to in my own country,
which is also um a lot of the reasons
why I don't go out drinking anymore. Um
because of um you know what I mean?
Yeah. Just that, you know, that's like
yeah, I just don't want to deal with the
negatives of like going out drinking
anymore. That's why I don't bother no
more. It's just negative.
You get what I mean?
Staying home and playing Franklin is
just so much better. Staying home and
playing Franklin is so much It's just a
better idea, isn't it, Grizzly? Yep.
Do you reckon Virgin World ever get laid, Grezy?
But I don't think Yeah, I should have
got a lot more credit for all of the
effort I put in over the years dealing
with their [ __ ] you know?
You know what I mean?
But I'm going to do a video about this
dating anyways cuz
I need to send it to my friend. It's so
weird. Like sometimes these people wake
up and be like, "Oh, you're going out
today?" Like it's suddenly going to
change. Like all of this [ __ ] is
suddenly going to change
because they've never tried anything and
[ __ ] They seem to think it's going to
change for you when it never will ever.
You get what I mean?
But they seem to think one day it's
going to change. [ __ ] Yep.
We would you say that I've tried more
than anybody in the world? I'd say definitely 100%.
I don't think I'm ever going to find Mrs. Right.
I'm going to do a video about Mrs. Right.
Searching for Mrs. Right.
That's what the title of the video is
going to be. Heater betties give up hope
on trying to find Mrs. Wright.
Have you never heard that before?
Greavvesy. Mrs. Right. Greavvesy. You
never heard that before.
Looking for Mrs. Right. Huh? Where?
Oh, they run away. But yeah,
imagine if people actually wrote that
[ __ ] and didn't [ __ ]
you know, weren't actually trolling. Huh?
When do you think it's going to change,
Stephen? How with this whole dating
thing and [ __ ]
It will never change.
It will never change ever.
It's kind of tormenting to be honest.
What do you think, Grezy? It's
tormenting, isn't it?
Sat there laughing at you. They were
mocking y. Ain't it greasy? These
[ __ ] were laughing at me, mocking me.
They were laughing at you. That funny.
They were laughing at you. M.
It will never change.
Where's Joe this evening?
We're We're awaiting Joe. Grievy.
Yeah, we're awaiting Joey.
Wonder who that Joe F account is.
It's definitely some [ __ ] is it? [Music]
Messaging worldwide is what are you talking about?
Who's worldwide? Is he? Huh? You know.
Yeah. But there's only two is these though. Greavesy.
There's only two, right?
Do you feel sorry for Damon Grey? All he
wanted to do is be in a relationship and
now he's got someone messaging him from another country. Huh?
That's cute, isn't it, Grezy? All he
wanted to do was be in a relationship, ain't it?
And he's got someone messaging him from
across the pond. Grem