Wow, man. So many simpletons all in one place.
I need to get off this [ __ ] soon. But
100%, man. I swear to God.
These people give me [ __ ] brain damage.
I swear to God, these people give me
[ __ ] brain damage, bro.
They actually give me brain damage. Here we are. Five. Six.
Yeah, these people are [ __ ] retards,
man. In this community,
they were laughing at you. They were
[ __ ] mocking you. That's what they
were [ __ ] doing.
I was going to do a video talking about Yep.
This makes me laugh. And you know,
people say, "Oh, you know,
trying to convince people. Who cares
what these people think? They they've
been proven to be biased a million
times. Who cares what they think?
Who gives a [ __ ] what these people
think, bro? Who cares?" You know,
that's why I say it anyways. Yeah,
some [ __ ] right here. Yeah.
people need to [ __ ]
you know what I mean? Like I need to uh
grow up. I think
I got some [ __ ] in my ears. It's like Yeah,
good football that bro. Yeah, I was
going to do one virgin boy by version.
Virgin boy. They were mocking you and
they left you in that [ __ ] bed
sitting skent. Still bedsitting Kent
still a [ __ ] virgin. They were
laughing at you when you when you was
defending them all these years and
you're still a virgin at 31 years of
age. They were laughing at you. You know
what I mean? Yeah. I was going to do a
video like virgin by virgin. when you
have to end up with a [ __ ] disabled
[ __ ] that can't [ __ ] talk. They were
mocking you, laughing at you. I don't
want to [ __ ] um
Ant-Man. Yesterday I said I said, "Oh,
but while you when you committed that
crime and you was in prison, they were
giving the drug they were giving all the
drug dealers the goodies.
They were giving them the goodies. While
she was in prison eating [ __ ]
[ __ ] probably pot noodles, they were
giving they were giving the goods to the
drug lead to the drug dealers. They were
laughing at you.
They were laughing at you. You love the
heart of the um Yeah. I'll give him a
taste of his own medicine, didn't it?
When you was in prison, they were giving
up the goods.
They were giving up the goods to the to
the drug dealers and the scumbags.
Yeah. They give him a taste of his own medicine. Nah.
Nah, not at all, bro. Not at all.
That Jo really is a simpleton, isn't he?
He really is a [ __ ] simpleton. That
Joe F. Hey,
I need to go for a drink at some point,
bro. [ __ ] I've not been out for ages. I
don't need to go for a drink, but I
can't be bothered.
Maybe next week.
Maybe. Nah. Don't know.
Oh, he's just showing like his money
again. I was like, "Bro, stop this [ __ ]
now. Come on."
I like it's waste of It's a waste of
time, bro. I'm not getting I'm not
getting into it with these people anymore.
They're all biased. I don't give a [ __ ]
bro. I'm not getting into it with these
people anymore. You know what I'm saying?
Showing money and no, like you proved
what you're about multiple times.
You know, [ __ ] it's pointless. You
lose every single game and you don't
admit it, so there's no point with you people. Yep. So yeah,
you don't find Sho attractive your gay.
You remember that one? They were mocking
you when that when that trend when you
was trying to copy the crowd, Virgin
boy, you were trying to fit in the women
were laughing at you.
You know, actually when I compare it to,
you know, this, you know, the maddest
thing is, right? This situation is so
[ __ ] up. Yeah. But when you actually
compare it to like Virgin Boys or another Simpucked
up it actually is. It's really really
bad. But then when you compare it to
Virgin Boy, it actually makes it seem really good.
You know what I mean?
No, I can't I can't do his accent. But
if you compare it to Virgin Boy or like
L J or any other simps, it actually
seems really really good. We actually
got off lightly to be honest. That's how
[ __ ] they actually are.
You know what I'm saying? That's how
that's how bad it is. You know what I
mean? Cuz when you're comparing your
experiences to these simps,
it doesn't even seem bad. Even though in
reality is [ __ ] up, it is really bad
to like a normal person. You know how
mad that is?
You know what I'm saying? Is it? Yeah.
He thought by defending them they would
sleep with him. You know when someone's
a s when they start saying like women
don't owe you anything and [ __ ] like
that. That's how you know they're a
simp. There signs there like little s
words like that. They don't owe you
anything cuz they use it in the wrong
context. So it's simp to me that's simp because um
yeah of course it's simp
about they don't owe you anything. They [ __ ] do.
They [ __ ] well do. Yeah man. [Music] Yeah.
Oh, I fancy going down a brewery today,
but and then I need to get a haircut and
[ __ ] I'm not doing that. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm not doing that, bro.
I know, bro. That's why I had to give up
in the end.
That's why I had to give up in the end, lad.
No one ever gave me credit either.
That's what I found strange. No one ever
gave me credit. And I mean no one generally.
But they still tell you that you're
going to meet someone. It's mad, isn't it?
And I I have actually given up.
That's that is the is the bad thing. I
actually have given up. Cuz
since getting this new phone,
I've only been on like two dates. Is it
two dates? Three dates. Three dates. And
I've had this phone since December.
And I've only had three dates stone.
And we are August.
So reading that what you will. So, I
basically got three dates in almost a
year. That's disgusting.
That's [ __ ] disgusting, bro.
That is absolutely disgusting.
Really, really, really disgusting if you
think about it.
I'm [ __ ] telling you. You're not
telling me. I'm [ __ ] telling you cuz
I'm [ __ ] living it. I'm telling you it's impossible.
I was watching Oreo guy, Oreo man yesterday. Um,
and he was saying it better than me. He
was saying about how this is why women
don't this why men don't approach
anymore because women are narcissistic.
And he was saying they're all the same
and that and it was a good presentation
and he says like they they don't like
people for for they can just like you
for no reason. They can just not like
you for dumb reasons. Like there was
some guy some woman didn't like him
because he didn't read because he read.
Sorry. So because he read books that was
the reason she didn't like him [ __ ] years ago.
Yeah. Years ago.
Three years ago, man.
It's not possible anymore
like it used to be,
which that's why I obviously had hope
because you used to actually be able to
get stuff, but now you can't get
anything now. So
that's not socially acceptable. Do you
remember who used to say that? Um, Nikolai,
that's not socially acceptable.
That's not socially acceptable.
I said, "Aren't you [ __ ] trying to
tell me what's [ __ ] socially
acceptable in your [ __ ] bed? You skin cunt."
You like my accent?
That's not socially acceptable.
I don't want to be accepted by this tick
tock brain society. I want to [ __ ]
live with the [ __ ] penguins in Antarctica.
You know what I'm saying? in [ __ ]
Antarctica, bro. I don't want to be
accepted by this [ __ ] up society. I
hate even being out in [ __ ] public.
What's your [ __ ] normal? Sat on
[ __ ] Tik Tok all day, every day with
your [ __ ] head glued to your [ __ ]
phone. I don't think I don't think that's acceptable, [ __ ] [ __ ]
you know? But that's not totally acceptable.
And you know that thing. Yeah, when them
black guys was throwing water at him.
That actually happened. I never [ __ ]
made that up at all. Why would I make it
up? He looked back and he said, "Oh,
them three black." I said, "No, they
threw water at you." Why would I pretend?
Why would I literally say, right, that
they did when they didn't when we're not
arguing at this point. They probably saw
some [ __ ] weird lanky virgin in their
area and they probably didn't [ __ ] like it.
And he says that I don't know how to
speak to women yet. He's never ever
called a woman in his life. That's what
makes me laugh. He's never ever pulled
anyone. If you keep if you compare me to
him, my my experiences are actually
good. And that's saying something.
That's actually [ __ ] saying
something. You know, you don't realize
how good you have it until you you had
it until you compare yourself to someone
like them. That's how [ __ ] they really
are. You know what I'm saying? That's
like obviously it's bad. We know it's
bad. All of it's [ __ ] up. But when you
compare it to someone like LJ J or
Virgin Boy, it's actually really good.
You know what I'm saying?
That's that shows how much [ __ ] they are
than you. Do you know do you understand?
I've never resort to disabled.
And I've kissed a few masers when I was
drunk, mate. I've kissed a few muners
being drunk back when it was possible. Um, so yeah,
never have I resorted to disabled. Never
One second, bro.
Yeah. And I don't know how many times
this guy has to try and say you got a
big nose. He's not making anyone insecure.
You know, he's not making anybody insecure. So yeah.
So yeah, but [ __ ] that, bro.
I'm not going out today. I probably
won't go out next week either. Football
better win or not. I don't think I'm I'm
going to go out, bro.
You could probably like go back to
approaching, but it'd probably take you
a very very long time. You'd have to do
it for so long you you'd have to forget
all of the things that's happened until
you do it again and then the same [ __ ] happens again.
But like a year maybe, probably like a year.
Oh mate, he wasn't saying any of that
[ __ ] when he was running to the police
crying, was he? Something that a lot of
people also pretended to forget as well.
It's funny, bro. The band is funny, but
in terms of getting into anything
serious with these people. Um,
yeah, that's what I'm going to do. I'm
say I'm just saving it towards like the
time. Exactly. Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
But I will have to go out at some point
again to have a drink just because I
want to just go for a drink. You know
what I mean?
Not and obviously I'll approach when I'm
drinking, but I'm not going to do any
sober because I'm drunk anyways. [ __ ]
it. Maybe someone might approach me.
I think I'll have to be drunk to ever do
it again, bro. Like, and it's not going
to be for a very long time.
Like it's not going to even be next week.
Yep. It's not even going to be next
week. It's not though. Even if it wins,
I don't I don't know when. But it's not
going to be anytime soon.
But you could even meet someone on the
internet and then obviously you could
just go to their country. I mean that's
the thing, you know. We've got no
responsibilities, nothing's we have no
ties here. You know, when we come back,
we have no ties to this country, so we
can leave as well.
You probably got more a chance of that
than [ __ ] actually approach him. So,
Yeah. And then she [ __ ] me about.
I was going to go [ __ ] Manchester,
weren I? The same week and then she
[ __ ] me around.
Nah, it's not. You barely get any
replies, but I mean, you can go on
Reddit and [ __ ]
I was I was speaking to somebody in
Canada, but they
stopped replying, so Yep. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm not going to do it, bro. I'm
just probably going to go cinema or something.
Hopefully the [ __ ] bet wins,
but even if it does, I'm not going to go
out anyway. So So doesn't really matter
if it does or doesn't to be honest. I'll
just get a nice takeaway and play some Franklin 324,
which probably last like three days in in Thailand. So
spend the £24. What am I going to get
with £24 or like a takeaway or something? [Laughter]
Something like that, bro. Yeah. I mean,
you get a takeaway in it. that boyfriend.
You had a boyfriend.
That's what I might do. Go out and do
that. Where is he then? I won't be going
out anymore, bro. Don't you worry about that.
All that [ __ ] years of wasting money
and trying to find Mrs. Wright.
But at least we actually it was actually
possible back. It was more possible back then.
No, not even a sausage.
Not even a [ __ ] sausage.
Not even a Cumberland sausage. Eh,
you got a boyfriend. There we are.
Where is he then?
Well, where is he then?
Yeah, I think my body's [ __ ] from all
of the approaching from all of them from
all of them years, bro.
100, bro. I think it's [ __ ] That's my
I think that's why my feet are [ __ ] and that
what I used to do, bro, is no joke.
But like I said, if I was in somewhere
like Canada, I'd be out today.
Not America, though. But if I was
somewhere like Canada. Um,
no. It's not pure luck. It's not pure
luck at all.
Not at all. At all.
is a world.
No, that was that's back when it was possible.
No, no, no. That's that's back when it was possible.
That's that was years ago. That was like
four years ago. That's when it was
possible. Yeah. It was luck when it was
possible. Now it's not possible.
I mean, yeah, it was luck then cuz it
was possible then. It's not possible
now. I don't think we used to complain
back then, did we, Nicolo? Did we? We
did. I don't think I ever complained
back then to be fair. I was too busy
complaining about USA, is I don't think
I complained back then.
It's only when you look back on it,
you complain now cuz it's impossible
now. And it doesn't matter, bro. Listen,
listen, listen. I My body count should
be about 100. I should have been in
about 50 relationships. So, at the end
of the day, bro, even all of that stuff
wasn't worth it. For you, you're not
understanding, right? There was this
woman I was speaking to. She's lesbian.
She, oh, I'm in the same position as
you. I can't I haven't had anything for 4 years.
And she was like um
she said um
and I said yeah. She said oh you've had
more than me. I said yeah I've had more
than you cuz I've approached about 6,000
women. So that's probably why I've had
more than you. So nah nah it's not right
women right time.
Yep. pretty much. Nicolola,
what what the [ __ ] are you talking
about? But yeah, back then it was
possible. It's not possible now.
And also, you know, before I met USA, I
tried for about 2 years and I didn't get
anything for two years. You know, I went
through a period of trying for two years
and I didn't get nothing. Then I went
Manchester, then I got laid, then I came
back to London and met USA. So I
So I didn't get anything from that July
to that April.
So it's disgusting. No matter what way
you look at it, it's all disgusting. All
of it's disgusting
to be honest with you.
Don't know who you're talking about. Oh, her
Yes. What about her? Yeah, she turned
out to be a [ __ ]
So, what about her? She was Yeah, she
was a [ __ ]
Yeah, she turned out to be a [ __ ]
but it was actually possible back then.
No, she was a [ __ ] No, she was a [ __ ]
You remember when I used to go on dates,
Nicolo and tell them about USA is
swear if another woman calls me mate,
I'm going to smash them in their face.
You know, there's this woman on Reddit
that says mate. Why do they all say the
same thing if they're not all the same?
Mate, mate, mate. I said, I'm not your
[ __ ] mate. I had to say that to the
[ __ ] 19year-old, bro. Nicolola, I was
actually I was down the road the other day, yesterday,
and she was like, "Oh, excuse me, mate."
I said, "Bro, if someone calls me mate
again, I'm going to say something, bro.
Stop. I'm not your [ __ ] mate."
It sounds horrible, bro. When women call
people [ __ ] mate, I'm not your mate.
[ __ ] mate, bro.
Yeah. Do you remember that Nikolai?
And she wasted my time, but oh, I won money, so
Yeah, I won money though, so yeah.
Yep. No, I don't. I'm not your [ __ ]
mate. Don't call me mate, bro. I said that to get.
So, what you're saying never try here
again, is it? Nah. No way.
Yeah. She used to suck my willie, Nicolola.
>> She used to suck my willie. She used to
come to the old house and see all the
tenants and [ __ ] >> Yeah.
I I had to own that [ __ ] uh girl
tenant. I was like, it's so funny. Like,
she's 100 times better than a girl
tenant. Like thinking that you're
keeping me sexless and then you see that
I've got a friend that's better than
you. Way better than you. [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah,
some of them did. Yeah.
Yep. Some of them did. [Laughter]
It doesn't change, does it? No changes. Yeah. Yep.
So, I mean, even even if you think about
it, right? Four years. What did you get
in four years? What? Five lays? That's
disgusting. You should be getting laid
all the time in your prime. Dates, sex.
You know, if I didn't have that house, I
probably would be like, "Oo, man.
I probably would be like, "Oh, your
man's um 36 now." I would I would Well,
I wouldn't be like him, but
I would be I wouldn't be like him
because I would have left and but I
would have left a long time ago and I
would have used an escort,
which is but in terms of like finding
someone normally, I if I didn't have the
house, I'd be like him. There's no doubt
about it. I'd be like him.
Well, saying that, I went to Manchester.
I didn't have the house when I were in
Manchester, but I would I would be like
[ __ ] like in
only cuz I didn't have to work for 4
years and [ __ ] So scary [ __ ] in it, bro. Scary. Yeah.
No, it's not six. It's about five.
Maybe even four actually
cuz I could have [ __ ] one of them.
Virgin boys at zero.
Virgin boy is at zero.
What do you think?
Virgin boy can't get late.
Yeah, but I didn't [ __ ] them two, so
it's still disgusting.
A woman could get that in a day on Tinder.
Yeah, a woman could get that in a day on Tinder.
That's bad, is it, bro? Really bad.
Really bad, isn't it? But it still
counts as a [ __ ] in it. So
yeah, the not one. Yeah,
I really [ __ ] up with a lot of people
cuz of that USA, isn't he? You know,
she was laughing at me the whole time.
What's disgusting, Grezy?
I really [ __ ] up with like a lot of
people, you know.
because of that [ __ ]
I'm mad. But I did do a lot of thing and [ __ ] So
that that that year was so good, man. Oh
my god. That year was so good. And it
never it didn't matter that I had I
didn't have six grand in cash cuz I was
still getting three grand a month. So it
doesn't matter what you got, it's what
you got coming in. That's what it's all
to do with. It's, you know,
>> yeah, I feel like I'm 100 years old now,
Greg. I just want to have a baby Peter. So yeah,
my life is YouTube and Reddit. Really?
Is it actually?
Is it actually, bro? So I didn't travel
a lot in three and a half years. Yeah.
Really? So, I I'm the one that's coming
on YouTube every day saying, "You're
skint, you're this, you're that, you're
this, you're that." Bro, do you know
what I don't understand with you people
yet? You sit there and say, "Oh, you're
back on YouTube. Oh, you're back on
YouTube." But, bro, like, you can't even
take a day off YouTube.
So, I don't understand why you're
pretending that you're not on YouTube.
Why do you do that?
Yeah, but some of them were [ __ ] because
you can't even some of them I couldn't
even [ __ ] properly cuz um where I'd
wanked cuz the thing is you never know
when you're going to get laid. So you
could masturbate three times in a day
and then oh [ __ ] you get laid and then
when you get laid
you don't have any come left in you cuz
you didn't know you was going to get laid.
So obviously [ __ ] that in it.
That's the That's the thing.
Yeah, I banged one of them more than
twice as well. So you don't see me sing
anyway. So why why is Virgin boy sing?
Why is he sing?
If I want to moan at women when I've
tried everything more than anyone in the
world, why don't he leave me to it? Why
Why is he defending them?
That's the bit that doesn't make sense.
Why is he actually defending them?
All of these people that defend them.
Yeah. You remember when Antman said
before I met her, he was like, "Oh, um,
I've not smelt a woman in years."
Yeah, I remember that not evening when I
was supposed to come back on the Sunday,
but I come back on a Monday cuz I booked
a hotel with her and that in it. So, she
just sucked my dick cuz I couldn't [ __ ]
her cuz she was on her period. So, I was
like, "Okay, whatever. Yeah,
but it's just the same shit." And then
you message them again and then I have a
boyfriend. It's just annoying, bro.
It's just annoying. They're all the same.
We just have to accept here that it's
impossible now. So that's it.
So what if I didn't have the house? What
do you think would have happened? Huh?
What do you reckon the body count would
be? If I didn't have the house, then
I don't know, bro. One or two?
It Yeah, it does count. It still counts.
No, it does still count. It does still
It does still count cuz either way Well,
I didn't pay for all of them. I mean,
Sig didn't pay nothing. The Manchester
one I didn't pay nothing. And the one on
my birthday I didn't pay nothing. If
anyone they paid if anything they paid for me
cuz they one of them Sid bought me chicken.
She bought me chicken.
Yeah. Yeah, I could have. Yeah, I would
have found a way without the house
anyways. I would have found a way.
But I I always think that's what stopped
me um going insane is because oh yeah,
it's [ __ ] but you get more money than
everyone else and you don't have to
work. So I think that's what stopped me like
I was in a I was in a different position
than Ant-Man, you know? I always had
money and you know, I was always winning
money and [ __ ] So you know, if you have
money, all of your problems go away. You
know what I mean?
Cuz like say you got a house and you
knew you was getting £500 in two days.
Like you're better off than most people.
You know you're getting money. You know
you got money. So it was always
something to look forward to. But
obviously when you don't have that
obviously it was still [ __ ] It it it
was still [ __ ] but I don't know. I
always feel like that's what saved me
doing something crazy, bro.
But I'm sure I would have found a way
without the house anyways. would have
just got used to it, I'm sure.
Um, but if it was very money driven, if
you think about it, go out, win money,
get nowhere. Like, it's it was very
associated with money, wasn't it? If you
think about it,
cuz why would you care that you went
out, got numbers, and they didn't reply?
Worst case scenario, and you won money.
No one cares. cuz you would have been in
anyways. You're laughing. Do you know
what I mean? So
when you don't
have that anymore, it's um
and it's like what Sid used to say. She
says, you don't know how lucky you actually are.
You know, like you're not working.
You're getting 3.3K a month. You're
laughing, mate. You know what I'm
saying? You're [ __ ] laughing. you
know, even that money that I had, you
know, it doesn't matter what you had,
it's what you was also getting. So
really, like you you you you can't
complain. Really, if you think about it,
how many escorts do you reckon I've been
with? USA is friends as I say 200 maybe.
I think I've been with at least 200.
If that becomes um that becomes a um
addiction as well.
Pick my in Thailand. Yeah.
No, you couldn't. No, you couldn't.
No, you couldn't. Uh-uh. No, you
couldn't because the house wasn't
refurbed. No, you couldn't.
Trust me. The house wasn't in a perfect state.
Trust me, you couldn't. Not five grand. You couldn't
because if you had work done to it, you
could. But the the rooms weren't
perfect. They weren't nowhere near
perfect. The only reason you got a lot
of money from them is cuz they were in
London. You wouldn't have got five grand
a month. Unless you unless you got it
refurbished and you put money into it,
then you could. But no, you could have,
bro. The house wasn't perfect. So,
bro, I'm telling you, I've put it up
I put it up for a lot more money and no
one was interested, so I had to lower
it. But either way, like, yeah,
it was good. But I didn't like the
responsibility from the house.
I'd still be there now. I'd still be in
that room, big room now. I don't give a
I wouldn't give a [ __ ] if there's people
living there. I prefer that area. The
area is a lot better. It's better for
your mental health as well. I found that
area was a lot better for my mental health.
And obviously living with people,
laughing, you're near everything.
It was just a better area. I thought it
was better for like my mental health and
[ __ ] as well. So So
the only thing is I didn't have a
[ __ ] bed. That's the only thing. I
slept on a [ __ ] mattress on the
floor. Yeah. I was sleeping in some
guy's room for like six, seven months.
Yeah. Sleeping on the mattress on the floor.
Yeah. the bed. I slept on a mattress. I
don't mind sleeping on a on a mattress
on the floor.
Uh I don't know for like 7 months.
I can sleep on a mattress on the floor,
but I can't sleep on a on a couch. Nah.
You wake up with like [ __ ] neckaches and [ __ ]
Yeah, man. I slept on Yeah.
Yeah. Me and the tenant went clubbing.
Me and him went clubbing.
Yeah, he was getting the same thing out
of a boyfriend. Yep. Yeah.
Yeah. It was good. But at least I lived
the life for 3 years.
You know, if I if I still had that
house, I would just be leaving. So, I'd
still be I would just be leaving. I
wouldn't do anything else but leave. You
know, I've still got designer clothes
and [ __ ] And
you know I mean I lived the life for a
very long time, bro. So I mean
now I just need to find something now
where I can get probably back up to like
1.82 grand. That would be enough for them.
Um I won two in a row then I lost two.
Yeah, I lost uh both teams to score
treble. I put three teams and [ __ ]
one team let me [ __ ] down. One
[ __ ] I done three games and one team
let me down. The [ __ ] could have done
with that 140.
I could have done with that 140, mate.
Could have done with it.
I could have done with it, Nicolo. I
could have done with it.
Virgin boy couldn't show them 50s, could
he? Nicolo. Virgin boy couldn't show
them 50s, could he, mate?
I need to do some delivery thing on the
bike soon, but I'll do it when I'm ready.
Literally, we'll just do it when I'm ready.
I should be able to make some money on
that. So, yeah.
Virgin B. Virgin boy by can't show 50s. Hy
Nicolo. Virgin boy by can't show 50s.
Do you think I would still be with,
Nicola? Who Who do you reckon I'd still
be with out of all of them women if I
didn't [ __ ] it up? Maybe Sig.
Stig was like, "Oh, she wants a
relationship." and no no and she doesn't
want sex. But then she's the one that
approached me and wanted to [ __ ]
And then we went back. She's like, "I'm
not going to [ __ ] you and that." I said, "Okay."
And then she was like playing with my
dick and that.
I was doing like foreplay and then she
just jumped on my dick. I said, "What
the [ __ ] You said that you didn't want to [ __ ]
but then she said she wants a
relationship. How How does that work
then when you're you you [ __ ] somebody
you first meet?
I'm not sure.
Can't remember now.
It's like she was trying to resist the
Peter Betty, but then she couldn't.
I don't really like being touched and
stuff. I said, "Oh, okay." So, I just
went upstairs and then she's like, "Oh,
where have you gone? Where have you gone?"
And then she started like kissing me and
[ __ ] and that. I was like, "Oh, wow.
What the fuck?"
That's probably why you can't find a relationship.
Do you know what I mean?
Yeah. She lived in like the south area.
So I was east and I think she moved to Tutin
which is nowhere near me.
Yeah. I used to be a really good kisser
but not anymore because I don't kiss
anyone anymore. I can't even get a kiss
anymore. I can't even get a conversation
let alone a [ __ ] kiss.
Yeah. I used to be like really good cuz
I practiced my skills on different
people that I do it with. I used to kiss
so many people in the O'Neals. Oh my
god. It was crazy, bro.
But you can't even get that anymore.
What about the Nottingham? Was she my mama, Nicolola?
Was she Was she my mama?
Yeah, it could be.
This could be it.
That wasn't her in the background
picture. That was her mom. I've said
I've said this a million times. It
wasn't her. It was her [ __ ] mom, bro.
Holding her as a child. That wasn't her.
That was her mother.
What the [ __ ] I told Lar a this about a
million times. It wasn't even her.
I really want you, but I don't think you want me.
Bro, I don't give a [ __ ] if she was
brown. She's got a mouth and she can
suck a dick. It's good enough for me.
Nothing wrong with Brown.
Nothing wrong with Brown at all. Yep.
If they've got a mouth, they can suck a
dick, can't they? So that's it.
A lot of these Brazilian women are [ __ ] brown.
It's so much effort going to central
London now and drinking in it.
Oh, I'm tired of it, bro. I'm too old
for it now, bro. You outgrow this [ __ ]
You know what I mean? [Music]
Not sure, man.
I believe Sig was from New Zealand.
That's funny, isn't it? Yeah, she moved to Tutin,
which is nowhere near me. We all know
about tootin, don't we, Nicolo? If
you're a longtime watcher, you should
know all about tootin.
What happened in tootin?
Yeah, they're not my ends, bro. They're
[ __ ] And no, the other one that sound
was in tootin as well, but that's not my
ends, you know. Nothing to do with me, mate.
But you know, you know about toing, don't you?
What do you know about?
I don't anymore, bro. That's why I don't
do it anymore.
So, you might think, "Oh, it's just
about the money." But it's not about the
money, bro. Cuz I have money to go out.
And even if this football bet wins, I'm
still not going to go out. You know, it
gets to a point in life where you need
to move on to, you know, better things, bro.
You know what I'm saying? So,
but I I don't, bro. I don't. And it's
worse though, bro. Do you know what used
to be worse? If you would do it on a
Thursday or uh uh a Sunday to Thursday,
you'd have to get the night bus back and
it would take like an hour.
It would take like a [ __ ] hour.
Yeah, it used to be hell getting that
bus back. I remember that time I won the
four grand. I had to get the night bus
back. But do you think I gave a [ __ ]
I've got like four grand in my [ __ ]
hand, bro. So,
like, yeah, it used to be hell, bro.
Getting that uh getting that night bus
back. It used to be a [ __ ] A lot of the
time to be fair, I would like go casino.
So after like all the places closed at
like 4:00, I'd probably just go casino
until like 5 and then just get the bus
back. I get the train back. Um
and just get the train back.
So what happened in to then anyways? I'm
Nicolola. What happened in two and do you remember?
>> Do you remember what happened?
Yeah. Do you remember what happened in
something to do with a hospital? Yeah.
Well, I think Sig would have been a good
candidate for baby Peter.
I think she would have been a good mommy
to baby Peter. I do think Nikolai Uh
the tenant had a problem with his dick
and we had to go to um the hospital. I
didn't go in with him, but he wanted
support because maybe he doesn't like
hospitals and uh yeah, I had to uh I had
to go with him. [Music]
Yep. That's what [ __ ] Virgin boy
needs to No, it wasn't any erectile
problem. His dick was actually broken.
But I remember Virgin Boy having a
problem with his little dick before. Um Yeah.
Yeah. I remember Virgin Boy having a
problem with his little dick before. Oh,
he sewed like an X-ray, which is
probably why he used to project his
virginity onto me for all of them years.
Yeah, virgin boy had a problem with his
little [ __ ] autistic dick.
I remember seeing the X-ray. I'm not
even joking, bro.
That's why he used to call me a virgin,
cuz he's one. Cuz he is a virgin.
Think about it. If none of the things I
said was true, why did you go run into
the old bill?
No, it was another one.
Do you remember when LT smashed the window
and he thought he hit the jackpot? Yeah.
Yeah. And and I paid for him to get And
I paid for him to get laid as well. I
paid for him to get laid, too.
We me and him went through a lot of
stuff together, bro. Um
Yeah. He went out for my birthday on a Thursday.
Yeah. He He almost got killed. He almost
got [ __ ] killed. He did. He I
remember him running to the back of the
garden now. It's not funny. It's not Yeah.
No, another one. It was another one.
How's it going? How's the approaching going, Adan?
They've all got boyfriends. [Music]
in WWE yesterday. Like I watch it up until 2011.
Yeah. Up until Yeah, he did. He had a
piping hand. Yeah. You remember
everything, can it, Joker? I was
watching WWE Royal Rumble yesterday
until like up until 2011.
I don't think it I don't think they make
as much money nowadays. I don't think
the kids nowadays
are into WWE. I don't think because
obviously it was at its peak back back
in my day when you know the the
Undertaker and that obviously most
them's retired now. So I don't think
it's at its peak anymore where kids are
into it like they used to be. Yeah,
I don't think so.
You know what? I was actually watching
some of the Undertaker stuff and it
makes me laugh now. Like, it's just
funny to me
how he doesn't laugh the whole time.
Like, I'd be laughing, mate. If I was
trying to play a character like him the
whole time, I'd be laughing.
And the way he would just lie down and
just sit up.
You know where he just lies on the floor
and then just sits up.
Do you remember when Izzy was doing my
um makeup? Look at that. Yeah.
Yeah. Everyone go remember my name. Oh
yeah. I was watching that the other day
as well. Yeah.
See you around, officer.
Everyone can remember my name.
But he doesn't get mentioned in any of
the other ones. Oh, Franklin and his little dog.
Yeah, she was trying to use me for my
little money, Nicolo.
And then when I said no more drinks,
Isabelle, she started stamping her feet.
She started stamping her feet.
Yeah, she was having a tantrum.
just everyone go remember my name. You
know that last mission is hard, isn't
it? It's like half an hour long. Yeah. Yep.
Do you remember that one? Do you remember Kenji
when he looked he gave me the eye and
Monty knew straight away. I said, "You
know what he was thinking when he looked
at me?" He was like, "Yeah, free." So,
we was about to go in. Yeah, we was
about to go in, right? We was about to
go in and um
she said, "Oh, you can both come." And
he gave me the eye in it. And I said to
Monty, "Do you know what that means?"
She said, "Yeah, freom."
He gave me the freom eye in it.
Yeah. Cuz I wanted to cop block him in it.
Do you remember that kid J?
He was pissing me off, bro. Yeah.
My little Isabelle.
What do you reckon would have happened
if if I never cut ties with her?
She was like, "Oh, sorry. I
sorry I uh
sorry I um
sorry I um"
She said, "Sorry I stripped in front of
you. Do you still like me after that?" I said, "Yeah."
I said, "Do you still like me?" She said, "Yes.
She was doing my makeup. Yeah,
she didn't have any boobies.
She didn't have any boobies. So, no.
It's about these movies.
I think the Albanian one had the best
one to be honest.
Pretty sure. And Sig as well. Yeah.
Do you think Isabelle would ever meet me
again, Nicolo? Oh, do you remember them
people that were getting so jealous when
me when me and um me and her was playing
roulette and holding hands? Virgin boy
was getting so jealous
cuz you always thought you was going to
be a virgin like him, you You know, and
obviously as you got older, you you
become better than that virgin and you
[ __ ] you actually lost it. You
Unlike him, he never lost it. You understand? Yep.
Yep. You know it. Yeah.
Yep. Everybody was like, everybody was
congratulating me. Mr. B, uh, sorry, Mr.
G, Triple H,
um, everyone. LJ didn't show his face
then. Uh, Pat Mustard, even someone that
used to [ __ ] with me every day. And he
was like, "No, you [ __ ] [ __ ] I was
like, hold on a minute. We've just met
here. It's not all about [ __ ] fuck."
I was like, "What? What are you talking
about? No, no, no, no. Me and Britney,
mate. Me and Britney situation. No,
mate. No, no. Literally, there was like
[ __ ] even Craig Goodston was loving
it. Everybody was cheering except that
[ __ ] virgin. And you think I give a
[ __ ] that you show me you with a [ __ ]
disabled girl? That proves you've had
sex? [ __ ] Right off. That doesn't prove
anything, mate. Anyone could be seen
with a disabled girl and say they're in
a relationship with them. You know what
I'm saying? Like no no no
[ __ ] mate. [ __ ] That's how we know
he's a virgin.
That's how you know. All of these things
proves that he is a virgin. And like the
the the the the extent that he goes to
stalk these women, it goes to show he's
a virgin. I don't care if he's in a
relationship. I don't care what other
people think. I know him better than he
knows his [ __ ] self, you know? You know,
it he is a he honestly is a [ __ ] virgin, bro.
And I think Bomb's a virgin as well
cuz only a virgin would do that.
Only a virgin would do that. You know
what I mean?
He tries to get information out of women
because he wants them to say that they
didn't [ __ ] you. So he thinks that
you're a virgin like him.
See, he doesn't meet me anymore because
I'm an adult and I smash his [ __ ]
face in, you know? People like that can
only do stuff to like kids 17, 18. It's
a [ __ ] kid to me, you know? And then
when you get older, none of these people
want it anymore. Just like these
Americans, like Virgin Boy, they don't
want it as soon as someone becomes an adult.
It's weird, isn't it?
You know, but as soon as like if I was
17, 18, he'd probably try and meet me
and take a piss out of me.
So they go for
No, sometimes I even still message them
Americans and say, "Fuck you. [ __ ] your
mom." Cuz the [ __ ] they used to say was
vulgar, bro. It was nasty. It was nasty,
bro. And then as soon as you get a bit
older, they don't want it anymore. Yeah. Simple.
But now when you when you're older, like
you're a grown man, they don't want any
of it. They run to the old bill
cuz obviously I didn't know a lot back then.
So I used to think I would have met him
and said, "Look at your [ __ ] virgin
self, you skint [ __ ] You skint lanky
bastard." Cuz he knows that's what it
will be if I ever see the [ __ ] You know
what I'm saying? But like obviously back
then you're you don't have a beard. You
you're skinny. You don't know much about
life. you know, you're not as developed
as you are now. I'd say you're a [ __ ]
dirty, stinky little [ __ ] and [ __ ] off.
That's what I'd say to him. And I'd
record it as well. You know,
these people can only act big to kids.
People used to do on Skype as well, bro.
They used to do on Skype. These
Americans used to do it on Skype as
well, bro. They did. They [ __ ] did.
I eat all of them up now, bro. I'd eat
all of them up. Why do you think when
USA, for example, does this [ __ ] she
plays victim? When you give it back to
her, why do you think she plays victim?
Cuz that's all they can do. You understand?
Strange, isn't it?
Yeah, they all cowards, bro. Even them
people on Skype,
dude. They used to make fun out of like
dead relatives and [ __ ] Yeah, bear in
mind they were like 18, 19
and I was uh maybe 15,
you know, and then they used to do all
of this madness, bro. And then I
messaged one, I think it was like a year
ago. I said, "Oh, you little [ __ ]
German immigrant. Little Yankee 911
[ __ ] What you [ __ ] saying now, bro?
What are you saying now, you little 9/11
little bastard? You little German
immigrant." That's what I said to him.
Yeah, you little Nazi bastard. What the
[ __ ] are you saying now, [ __ ]
Then he said like one thing that he
blocked me. I said, "Yeah, that's what I
[ __ ] thought, bro." You know? Yeah.
Yeah. But karma got this one guy, this
guy was in, this guy in America, he
always used to make fun out of dead
relatives and he ended up losing a baby.
So that's karma. I mean, that right
there is karma. Um, not I don't think he
had the baby and then the baby died.
No, I haven't heard from him for ages. I
got his number, but don't talk to him. Yeah.
>> You know what makes me laugh is when
women say they don't like dick pictures.
If they find dicks ugly so much, why do
they [ __ ] them? Why do they suck them?
They're so They're such hypocrites, isn't it?
They're very, very hypocritical, aren't they? Women,
men admit they like sex and whatever,
but women, they pretend they they find
dicks ugly. And if you found something
ugly, you wouldn't put it in you. You
wouldn't put your mouth around it if you
if you found dicks ugly.
I mean, I find [ __ ] vaginas not to be
the best looking, but
it's not as bad as these people make
out. What the [ __ ]
If it's so weird, you wouldn't you
wouldn't [ __ ] a dick. You wouldn't suck
I don't know if you ever noticed that. Oh [ __ ] Yeah.
How do you feel about that?
And this guy said, "Oh [ __ ] the
football starts, dude. [ __ ]
Yeah, it was. But her boobies wasn't.
So, yeah. Nicola, why do they pretend
that dicks on Ry and dick picks on Ry
when they're the ones that suck it?
When they're the ones that put dicks in them.
I I've never understood that. Never. Never did.
Never did. Never did.
Cuz if you found something nasty like dick [ __ ]
you wouldn't put a dick in you. You
wouldn't suck a dick. I just don't
understand. I think people need to be
more open, you know?
I don't know. It just seems very odd to
me. Maybe it's just me.
Do you think it's hypocrit? Do you think
it's hypocritical? Um, Grezy.
I think she's very hypocritical.
Hopefully this football wins get a nice Chinese Yeah,
right. I'm uh I'm gone anyways, so I'll
be back later.