Oh [ __ ]
Oh yeah, man. Went to the [ __ ]
>> fat. What a lovely stroll. You know, I
think some of these fat [ __ ] should do
this, you know, every day. Then they
won't be so fat.
Yeah, I got to double both teams to
score. I put 120 on it. Bad ass over here, bro.
[ __ ] mate. I put 40 pound on the FBI as well.
[ __ ] better [ __ ] win today. These
[ __ ] lower leagues though.
You're not saying the teams cuz of um
stalkers obviously on here. St like to
st my bets. So I'm not saying what the
bet is, but yeah.
Not going to say if it won or lost
either. Another thing I need to stop doing.
>> Yeah, man. Yeah. I don't know.
I withdrew 160. I put 40 on the FB Ty
and then [ __ ] I put um
yeah 40 on the FBY and 120 on a football
bet. Double both teams to score. [ __ ]
hell, bro. Returns over 380. So hope it
wins in it. Yeah,
it'd be sickening over wind.
Um yeah, £40. I got one spin out of 40
pound on the roulette.
Just gets worse, isn't it, bro? It just gets worse.
[ __ ] one spin out of [ __ ] 40
[ __ ] quid. Oh my [ __ ] god.
One spin out of 40 [ __ ] pounds.
That is [ __ ] in [ __ ]
[ __ ] bro. Oh my god.
That's insane, bro.
So, I spent one I bought some burgers
I'm going to cook later.
Don't know, man. He's gone
somewhere. Well, I don't [ __ ] know, but yeah. Um,
yeah. Hopefully this football bet wins,
bro. 380. Good. Isn't it good from 120?
It's a good good win. Oh, [ __ ] 120. Oh
[ __ ] Some [ __ ] tea, man. Yeah. So,
guess where we're at. Yeah. [Music]
Do you have flies coming out of your
fridge or is that [ __ ]
You actually have flies coming out your
fridge, man. That's crazy. If you do,
that's [ __ ] crazy, bro. If you do,
why do you have flies coming out your
fridge? I was in the supermarket just
now and [ __ ] most of the [ __ ] there
looks [ __ ] off. I just got some
burgers. Going to make some burgers
later. Qu out now for a little while. I
need to save, bro.
Otherwise, there'll be no [ __ ] holiday.
There'll be no [ __ ] holiday, mate. Yeah.
Slim. I went to the bookies. Yeah. With
you 160. I put 40 on the roulette. Um,
one [ __ ] bar, bro.
I hit one. Um, I got one spin out of 40.
Then I put 120 on a football bet. Returns 38 something.
But hopefully that football bet wins.
be nice, isn't it?
If not, then we're [ __ ] even.
If not, then I think yeah, we're pretty much even.
Obviously, I won on the football like
past few weeks, so I'd say then we're even. Yeah.
Well, that's mad, isn't it?
Yeah. Evens. Then we're even
saying the teams although
because of um the stalkers on air.
So, I'm not saying the teams cuz you get
these autistic weirdos like stalk your
football bet. Uh I'm not even going to
say if I won or lost. So, which is
something I should on the last few times
cuz these people actually stalk your
football bets and they'll try to think
that you're like them, that you're skin
like them and then like it gives them
ammo. So, I'm not even saying. Bro.
>> Yeah. Otherwise, I would, bro. You know,
you know, I'm like, "Yeah, I got one
spin out of 40 quid." Yep.
8 weeks. Is that all? I didn't do it for
like 4 months. What the [ __ ] 8 weeks is
nothing, man. That's only two months,
but I just thought, yeah, just try some
extra money and [ __ ] But
yeah, and I just done some food
shopping. Well, I say food shopping. I
just got some burgers.
Like I said, I need to save now. So, you know,
bollocks. I said I done four months. I
never said I done 12 months. Open your
ears. I said I done four months. It was
even four or five months. Good, bro.
So yeah, I could just put 120 on three teams.
So yeah, [ __ ] sake, man. [Music] Yep.
One second. Yeah,
they should be Yeah.
>> So, yeah, man. Hopefully this football
bet [ __ ] wins. Who knows? Could do
get [ __ ] maybe next week. Oh my god.
Let's wait. Let's wait. So good.
What is this?
But yeah, what do you think it is with
these people on Reddit anyways? Cuz it's
not any better in America. We know that
for a fact. We know that with the dating
scene, it's not any better in America.
So why do you think they simp?
Why do you think they simp?
Interesting. Is it bro? Very interesting.
They go on like it's so easy, but it's
like there's nothing easy about it,
which is strange cuz they live in
America. So why would they think
dating's easy when they're [ __ ]
Yeah, I got a football bet. I put 120 on
the football and I put 40 pound in the
machine. That's 160. So if it loses,
I'll just be evens
this month. So
I bought some burgers I'm going to cook
later cuz can't keep having takeaways.
If obviously I'm going away and thingy,
so I won't be able to afford to keep
having takeaways and [ __ ] know what
I'm saying. Nah, I won't be able to do
it, bro. But this this [ __ ] football
bet returns 380 which is good for 120.
It's more than three times the amount in it. So
got one spin out of 40.
What the [ __ ] bro? One spin out of 40 [ __ ] quid.
Imagine that greasy. One spin out of 40.
That's a madness.
That is a bad boy.
Yeah, I'm not telling you who I bet on,
you [ __ ] [ __ ] Don't [ __ ] come
on my [ __ ] chat trying to lick my ass
as well. Never you mind who I bet and
you're not going to know who I've um if
I've won or lost. Yeah, you little
[ __ ] I've seen you on Lord Jay's
channels trying to say I'm a monster,
brother. Listen to me here now. Yeah,
I'm better looking than all of you would
ever be, bro. Yeah, that's why you can't
show your face. That's why you can't do
the most easiest thing there is to do.
Don't [ __ ] come on my chat trying to
lick my [ __ ] ass, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Like, I'm not [ __ ] seen you on L's.
Was it last week? Was it? I think it was
last week. You little [ __ ] [ __ ]
about the manta. You are the manta.
Don't suck my [ __ ] dick after you
suck your [ __ ] dads, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] I've seen you on Laura J's, you little [ __ ]
Stop talking [ __ ] bro. Stop [ __ ]
talking [ __ ] on [ __ ] L JS and comment
on mine. And yeah, you asked me a
question and I answered you. None of
your [ __ ] business.
Yeah, who I bet on is none of your
[ __ ] business. How about that one?
That's an answer for you.
That's a nice little answer.
You like that little answer?
That's a nice little answer. Yeah. None
of your business.
Yeah, I haven't had a bet yet. You keep
telling yourself that. Yeah, I haven't
had a bet.
>> Bro, you're not you don't don't worry
about what teams I've done.
Ever you mind what teams I've done? Cuz
I know why you want to know the teams.
Cuz we know what you little skid little
losers do. You little bongos. You
[ __ ] stalk my [ __ ] bets and then
you all start getting happy when it
loses when I don't give a [ __ ] about
120, bro. We're not all skinn like you.
You understand? You people are the skinn
ones. That's why you bring up money all the time.
Yeah. And like I said, if you got
anything to say, say it to my face.
Don't say it behind the keyboard on
someone else's [ __ ] chat. Yeah. these people.
Yes, cuz I don't like losing.
But the only people that are skinn is
you people. That's why you call people
skint every day cuz you people are skinn.
Bro, I [ __ ] spent about £300 on
[ __ ] Sunday. I just spent [ __ ] 160
in the [ __ ] bookies for [ __ ] sake.
You people call people skint is because
you people are skint. It takes one to no one.
So what? Yeah, I got mad cuz I lost 90.
Oh yeah, that's another thing I didn't
add. Yeah, I lost 90. Yeah, I did lose
90. Yeah, and and your point is what? I
don't like losing.
But today I'm going to have to get used
to it if I lose. So that's it.
You people call people skin every day
cuz you people are skinn. That's why you
go on about money all day long, bro. Cuz
you're talking about your [ __ ] delves.
Like, for [ __ ] sake, man.
Just stop it now, bro. It's It's
embarrassing. You've been doing this for
years now. You know,
calling people what you are yourselves.
It's bad. Really bad.
Yeah. Yeah. You're not skin. Yeah. Okay.
Of course you're not skin. Yeah. You
people are 100% skin. That's why you
call other people skin every day cuz
you're skin yourselves.
Yeah. You call other people skinned cuz you're skin.
proof in it takes one to no one just
like virgin boy skinned and then a skin flin sking
skin flame that's what he is skin a
[ __ ] skin flint you can even say
fuking or [ __ ]
bro if none of you's none of you was
skin then you wouldn't have run away
when I showed you all that money time
and time again
nothing but I just went to the bookies I
went to supermarket. I'm just chilling,
man. I've already been out.
I'm [ __ ] hungry, bro. So, yeah. Uh, basically Yeah.
>> So, that's where we're at.
That's where we're at, bro. Unfortunately,
where we're at. I need to start working,
bro. Probably within the past couple of days.
I need to get loads and loads of money,
Cory. I don't want to be skinned like
these people. I need to get loads and
loads of money.
But like I said, I'm not going to go out
until next week regardless.
Regardless of what happens, I'm not
going to go out till next week or maybe
the week after.
Doesn't matter if I win, if I lose, cuz
it's not about affordability.
Well, it is in terms of like I need to
save for holiday, but in it's not like I
can't do it. I can do it if I want, but
rather not. So,
you get what I mean. Anyways,
yeah, bro, I need to seriously make some
money, bro. That's where God no.
Yeah, I spent 160 just in the betting
shop. [ __ ] hell, man. November,
why do you talk [ __ ] behind people's
backs on L's? Let me ask you a question.
Why do you and this Ricky Millindon,
right, talk [ __ ] about [ __ ]
people behind their back and then you
try to speak about women? Like, bro, you
none of you know more about women than I
do. I know more about women than you'll
ever know cuz I've been with women.
You get it's the same thing with that
Ricky Milling. Why do you do this [ __ ]
Talk [ __ ] behind people's back. You
don't even know me, bro. Why do you
What's the point of wasting all that
time and energy on people you don't even
[ __ ] know? how mad that is. You want
to talk about people
meeting people only once. How about
this? You've never met me. You've never
met the people that you waste your time
on every [ __ ] day. [ __ ] So, yeah. yeah, basically um to Yeah.
What's the day tomorrow? Wednesday, then Thursday.
Weeks go by quite quickly, don't they? Could
do with that 380 though, mate. Yeah,
good. Do with it, mate.
So, that's where we're at. But yeah, the
machines never change, do they? It's
nice to know the machines never change.
[ __ ] they never [ __ ] change, do they?
[ __ ] one spin out of 40 quid. What
the [ __ ] man? You go to supermarkets,
most of shit's [ __ ] off. You can't
even find a decent [ __ ] joint of
[ __ ] pork. This country's gone to the [ __ ] dogs.
They're trying to kill us all off, man.
They're trying to kill everyone off. I'm
telling you, they're trying to kill everyone off.
They are trying to kill [ __ ] everyone
off, man. I'm telling you. [ __ ]
That's how you know the country's down
bad, bro. When you go into a supermarket
Yeah. And you can't even find meat
that's not even not off.
The the the meat, bro, most of the meat
was off. And even though like the pork
said it's in date for like 2 days, I
said, "Bro, you know, pork goes off
before it says it goes off cuz it's pork.
Like if someone buys that tomorrow or or
it's not going to be no good, even if
they buy it today.
I don't live near a butchers anymore.
And that's not the point. People
shouldn't have to go to a butchers.
People go to butchers out of preference.
Not it shouldn't be mandatory that
people have to go to the [ __ ]
butchers to get meat that ain't off.
People go to butchers because they've
got more money to go butchers or they
prefer meat from the butchers. You
shouldn't have to go to a butchers to
get something that's not off. That's
[ __ ] And I don't live anywhere near
butchers anymore. So yeah,
that's [ __ ] insane, bro. It's
happened a few with a few of them
Morrison. It's happened. It's happened
in sainsburries as well. You know, you
go Morrison's all the [ __ ] meat is [ __ ] brown.
Literally, bro. So, I had to get beef. I
got one bit of beef, but still, what the [ __ ]
They're trying to kill us all off, mate.
They are trying to [ __ ] kill us all off.
It's [ __ ] madness, bro. Yeah,
that's where we're at.
I got four numbers on Sunday. I'm still
talking to two of them, but I don't
really care or expect anything because I
know how it is here. But it's it's
[ __ ] in it
trying to kill us all off, matey.
120 on a football bet. What a crazy
bastard I am, eh?
I'm [ __ ] starving, bro.
Yeah. So, it should come in, shouldn't it?
I owned him so bad he went to the police.
Imagine being so Imagine being owned so
hard on YouTube that you have to run to
the police. Imagine being that much of a loser,
you know? Can't imagine it. Don't Don't
know if any of you can imagine it. Just
imagine you you got owned so badly you
had to run to the police and then you
come on YouTube and act like you've won.
That's funny, bro. It's sad at the same
time. It's funny, but it's also sad.
Imagine being that much of a [ __ ] loser.
Only losers do that.
That's how you know everything I say is
right because you wouldn't have ran to
the police. If everything I said was
wrong, you wouldn't have ran to the
police when I say that you're a virgin
and your skin cuz you are and you know
you are. That's why you run to the
police cuz you can't take it.
You are a skin little virgin. You know,
I saw some of your [ __ ] from [ __ ]
last week booking an 8 8 900 [ __ ]
holiday. [ __ ] me, bro. I was doing that
[ __ ] when I was 23. And I'm 28 in two
months. Less than two months. So yeah.
So yeah, it's only it's it's only just
over two one bet. Yeah. So then it
should win then, shouldn't it?
Be nice to get an over 300 payout. I
don't think I have before on a football bet.
But I realized this is obviously not the
way and I'm going to have to start doing
something else. It was just a bit of fun today cuz
I realize it's not sustainable, you know,
cuz obviously you're not always going to
win. I mean, for [ __ ] sake, I put 40
in the machine and I got one win out of [ __ ] 40.
No, sorry. One um one spin out of 40
quid and the bar was on like [ __ ] 30%.
I'm 28 and I've had more women than you
would ever have. You're in your 40s and
you're still a virgin on YouTube hating
on people you don't know. Look at your
life. And yes, I have had a girlfriend
actually. So, try again.
And even if I hadn't, bro, you're in
your [ __ ] 40s on YouTube every day
talking about people that you don't
[ __ ] know. Yeah. Look at your life.
Look at your life being older.
You're older and you're on YouTube and
you ain't got a [ __ ] life and you
don't even have a woman and you ain't
even got any money. Think about your
life. Your life is much worse. You know,
everything you get shown, you deny it
anyways. Every single time. is why
people do not waste people don't waste
their time on you little mongos anymore.
You little 40-year-old losers, we don't
waste our time on you anymore. Cuz every
time you get shown [ __ ] you just deny
it. No one cares what you think. You
think we care what a bunch of [ __ ]
40-year-old losers that don't know us
think. Not even the slightest.
[ __ ] meeting once is bad enough, but
you've never even met the people you're
hating on. What a life you have, you know.
And [ __ ] having never having a
girlfriend. You've never even had sex.
You know, I'd say a lot of these people
on here were [ __ ] virgins, bro. I'm
I'm not even going to lie to you. I
think a lot of them are.
You know, I think a lot of these people
are virgins on here, bro. I'm not even
just saying that. Yep. Definitely. But
I've shown more money than them, more
women than them, that I'm better looking
than them, and they still come on here
and talk [ __ ] every [ __ ] day. That's
why people don't waste their time on
these losers, bro. Like, it's pointless.
I can't be [ __ ] with them, man.
You kind of have an opinion, but but
it's not an opinion because you said
that people are skin. People have shown
you more money than you would ever ever
see in your life, which I have done.
I've shown I'm better looking than you
and I've shown I've had more women than
you. That's facts. That's It's not an
opinion matter. It's actual facts what
you've seen. I can never show money
again, bro. I can show money whenever I
want to. But I don't want to show you
money because I know what's going to
happen. You will run away. You asking on
benefits. Yes, I can show you money
whenever I want. I just I I just done [ __ ] 160
um today in the bookies, bro. I've got
plenty of money to show you. But I'm
never going to show you money because
you people never show money
because I know what you do. That's why
people don't show you money because
you're self-reflecting. You're skipping
this onto me. I don't waste my time on self projectors.
I don't waste my time on skint people
that talk about themselves. It's a waste
of time. Waste of [ __ ] energy. You
have been shown money time and time and
time again and you all run away. We've
seen what you do. So there's no point
wasting any time on it. There's no point
wasting time trying to meet people. Um
because we know what you are. The
evidence is there with you mongos. What
you do, you fault you old virgins. We
know what you do. That's why people
don't [ __ ] with it no more. You want
people to show you money because you
ain't got no money. That's why you talk
about money all day cuz you are skinn.
That's why you're on YouTube every day
hating on people that you don't know cuz you're skin.
You're skinned 40-year-old mongos
self-reflecting bully victims. No one
cares about any of you. No one cares
about you [ __ ] ugly 40-year-old
spastics that come online every day cuz
you ain't got a light. You're something
to laugh at now.
It got to a point where, you know, well,
actually, you're not even something to
laugh at. You're something to pity.
You're not even anything to laugh at to
be honest with you. You know, you're 40
year olds and you failed in life. That's
why you come on YouTube with your anger,
calling people what you are, skin,
you're this, you're that because you're
40y olds that failed in life. You're
something to to not want to be like. You
know what I'm saying, bro? Like, yeah,
bro. Why do you think that is? Why do
you think I come on here for more?
Because none of you people do bully anyone.
You bully yourselves. You embarrass
yourselves every day coming on YouTube.
All you do is embarrass yourselves. You
don't bully no one. You embarrass yourself.
If I got bullied so much, I wouldn't be
on it. I literally would not be on it.
Like, I'm sure if people get bullied in
school, um, they run to the teacher. You
fat, ugly, mongaloy, disabled people
could never bully me. You can't even
come on my [ __ ] door for [ __ ] sake.
All you do online is embarrass yourselves.
You know what I'm saying? All you do is
embarrass yourselves for the 40-year-old
virgin skinned bastards that you are.
That's all you do. Embarrass yourselves.
That's why most of the time people don't
even block you. You know what I mean?
[ __ ] disabled [ __ ] ugly bastards.
They ain't got a life.
Want people to show their money cuz
they're [ __ ] skint themselves.
And you go. Anyways, back to some if if
9K is nothing, doggy, why did you run
away when I showed you that money then?
This is this is part of the reason this
this community is very disabled.
It's a very very very disabled community
um for the disabled people. Okay, bro.
If if 9K is nothing and I never showed
9K. I actually showed 5.7K, which I've
never shown 9K in my life. If that if
it's so nothing, why did you run away then?
Think about it. you'll run away for like 18 months.
Why is that then? If all of this money
is nothing, then you got all of this
money. But they don't understand it
because they're disabled. So when you
ask them a question, there's no point
cuz they're just disabled.
No, you just said that 9K is nothing. I
never showed 9K. I showed 5.7K and you
all ran away.
You know what I'm saying? These people,
what they do, Cory, is they talk about
their own lives. They sit there and got
no money. I could sit there with 300
pound in my bank and I'd have more of a
life than them
sat on YouTube being spastics all their
life. You know what I'm saying? Like,
[ __ ] hell. Crazy.
It is crazy, man.
They talk about themselves. Don't know
how people can sit there and talk about
themselves so much every day.
It's insane, bro. Their mental health
must be so [ __ ] So
these people don't bully anyone. They
bully themselves by embarrassing
themselves. It's quite sad to watch actually, you know.
[ __ ] madness, lad.
4K from what, bro? Nice. Nice, man. Oh, [ __ ]
Right, I'm gone. Yeah, I might be back
later or something.
Is that okay with you, boss? Yeah.