Yeah, [ __ ] yeah, mate.
Yeah. So, I've decided right after
today, I'm coming off this [ __ ]
weirdo place full of bongos. Ain't got a life. Yeah,
good [ __ ] bongos. Ain't got a [ __ ] life.
They ain't got a [ __ ] life, mate.
Shout on [ __ ] YouTube every [ __ ] day.
Some [ __ ] good exercising today. I
did these people on [ __ ] YouTube
talking about themselves probably every
day. It's what they do for a living. Yep. [Music]
Yep. Just ordered some lush food.
[ __ ] starving. Haven't ate today.
Welcome back. Yeah, bro. But guess what?
I'm not going to be on here tomorrow,
but you people will be.
Yeah, thanks, man.
I never said I'm leaving. I never I
never said I was leaving. I I never said
I was leaving at all.
So yeah, I never said I was leaving.
I never said I was leaving, bro. I'm
leaving, but I'm saying it now. I'm
leaving [ __ ] tomorrow. Yeah. Here,
little mongos. Ain't got a life. Can't
get off at your gym. You know what I
mean? It's all you [ __ ] have, you know?
[ __ ] food. Better hurry up. I'm
[ __ ] starving, mate.
[ __ ] starving. I am. Yeah.
I was going to do some approaches today, you know,
but I didn't. I saw some people. I was
going to, but I was like, nah, I can't be asked.
literally it's going to be [ __ ]
So yeah, what I'm saying now I'm leaving tomorrow. So
the question is will you people be on YouTube? That's the
that's the main question. Will you
people be on YouTube?
Will you people be on your job?
I think you will.
I think you will be on YouTube. Me, won't you?
[ __ ] won't you?
I think you'll still be on YouTube
though, won't you, lad?
It's just a [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] place
full of mongos with people that ain't
got a life.
It's just just a sad spasticated community.
People that just argue and start on
people that they don't even know cuz
they're clearly jealous of something in
life. So just a weirdo place, you know?
It's [ __ ] full of weirdos.
I'm convinced a lot of you. Yeah, I was
skintless [ __ ] virgin boy
in a [ __ ] bed sit with no bed in it.
Something's telling me you are, mate.
Something's [ __ ] telling me you're
acting skin in a [ __ ] skinny face.
Don't [ __ ] lie to me, mate.
Do not [ __ ] lie to [ __ ] me. Yeah.
Skint than a [ __ ] skint flint.
Try and shag Natalie J. No thanks. She's
not my cuppper.
I got uh chicken fried rice and some beef chowine.
The reason I got two is cuz I'll
probably leave some for later and heat
it up. cuz I didn't eat today. Oh, I got
some chicken boards as well.
Yeah, I went out to collect the money.
Um, I saw some people, but
was going to do some approaches, but I
couldn't be [ __ ] Yeah. N
can't wait to eat. I'm [ __ ] starving,
bro. No, not showing anything, mate. The
only thing I show are curries cuz it
reminds me of Virgin Boy when he shot
himself the first time I met him. Not
showing no Chinese, not showing no money, right?
Not showing nothing.
Look at You can look at yourselves.
Joe's not been around, has he? Greasy.
Yeah. Must be skin. Skin like you
people. You talk about skin every day
cuz you are skin. Takes one to no one.
It's just like Joe. He's so skinn. You
know that Joe F. Yeah. He's so desperate
to convince people that he's wealthy.
But in reality, he's just [ __ ] skin,
you know? It's so obvious. Just like
Virgin Boy on his little shitty 800 pip
holidays that was done at [ __ ] you
know what I mean? So, um,
them little cheap holidays.
Oh, nothing, Stephen. I just went to
collect the winnings earlier and went
for a walk.
Nice winnings. It was
just under 400. That's good, man.
You ready for the next piss up in? Probably never.
I don't know, bro.
3 weeks minimum.
It was [ __ ] raining today as well.
No, didn't play any of the machines. Nope.
Imagine I put that on a both score no
draw because it was an act. It was
actually a both score no draw.
It actually was a both score no draw.
[ __ ] me, bro. That would have been sick.
But I'm not complaining, bro. Like
money's money in it. So [ __ ] But it
would have been sick, bro. If that was a
both score, no draw. [ __ ] hell.
You can get a both score no join them
leagues easy I think
but I'm not I'm not bing
still good we won some football bets
last month as well
so I won three out of five yeah
I need to Uh, cinema Friday. Hurry up,
food. I'm [ __ ] starving, man.
Starving, man. I'm [ __ ] I'm starving, bro.
Yeah, I was speaking to that woman from
Canada, but I think she's playing me. Grievy.
I think she's playing Peter Belly.
playing me for a fool, I think. Nah, bro. Hello, [ __ ]
You all right, [ __ ]
I want food. I'm [ __ ] hungry.
Do you like beef chowine? Do you like
beef chowine? Greavvesy.
Yeah, I've done a lot of walking today
and I walked on an empty stomach because
I don't want to become fat.
So, I'm going to have to do that every day now.
I walked maybe four or five miles, I think.
No, I'm getting try I'm getting Chinese.
I've already ordered it.
Beef chowine and chicken fried rice. I
didn't get a spicy this time, but
sometimes it's good spicy. that extra
bit of like kick to it. Nah, I'm bored
of Indian at the moment. I'm I'm
preferring Chinese at the minute.
Sometimes I like chicken fried rice,
sometimes I like beef chain. It depends
what I'm in the mood for, you know?
They do a chicken chain, but that just
doesn't sound right.
Or sometimes I get like a Chinese curry. Yeah.
>> No, I've not had I've never had duck. I
was thinking of trying duck the other
day. It sounds nice.
My legs went far today, mate. Saw some
women in the mall. I was going to do
some approaches, but could be [ __ ] I
was contemplating it, but I was like,
nah, it can't be asked.
This could be asked, mate. I done enough Sunday.
when I spend where I spend all that [ __ ] money.
>> Yeah, I didn't do any. Could be [ __ ]
Went to collect the money and just
walked in the mall.
I'm very hungry, matey.
I'll save some for later as well.
Yeah, I had them chicken nuggets for
McDonald's last night, but just makes
you constipated. Them nuggets just make
you constipated. Them [ __ ] spicy nuggets,
they just give you the [ __ ] So, I don't
know why, but they just do.
Do you know the best curry is lamb ticker curry?
When I get a bindaloo, I get like a lamb
ticker one. So, there's chicken, chicken
ticker, lamb, and then lamb ticker.
Um, yeah. So, there's chicken, then
there's chicken ticker, then there's
lamb, then there's lamb chica. The lamb
ticker ones where it's at, man.
Obviously, virgin, but I can't get that
cuz skin and uh
couldn't be able to can't take that spice.
Why does that always go on about money? Strange, bro.
He always goes on about money. That joke.
I think they're in denial about their
own finances or some [ __ ]
It's it's it's crazy, bro.
I mean, I used to do that [ __ ] and then
when I realized and then I realize that no one
no one ever plays the game back, do they, Grezy?
They invent a game.
They invent the They invent a [ __ ]
game, right? And then when you play the
game, they they run away. So, what's the [ __ ] point?
>> Yeah, I have.
I made some homemade burgers yesterday,
Grevy. They were [ __ ] delicious.
I made them on the [ __ ] I made them
on a George Foreman. I bought a new
Oh, homemade burgers, eh? Can't beat
them. Can't beat them, mate.
Nothing even compares. No other burger
compares, you know?
Maybe GBK, but
Burger King's okay. Like, at least with
Burger King, it doesn't taste plastic,
but it's still not
It's still nice. It's still yummy, but it's not, you know,
it's still it's still nice, but it's not
as good as homemade.
Peter belly tired.
The weather's made Peter belly tired. Grievy,
it's my birthday next month.
Come on, food. I'm so hungry.
So hungry. I was going to go Nando, but
just figured it was too expensive.
How you going lose it, Virgin boy?
Oh, you're going to lose it, V boy.
Yeah, it's overpriced. That's why I didn't go.
That's one for Chinese.
Come on, food.
Oh, is it raining?
Oh, I can hear that all the way from here, Grezy.
Huh? I feel sorry for that poor delivery driver. Oh, mate.
You don't know where I am. You'll never Oh jeez.
An school. Why did you do that, Grezy?
Oh my god.
Look at that. Le sure.
Uh, no thank you. You can go by yourself.
You can you can take yourself for a pint.
I think you're gay, Greavvesy. Does
anyone else think Grievy is gay? I think
Greavves is really gay.
He doesn't find Chev attractive. He must
be gay. [ __ ] gay. Greavves is gay.
Who do I sound like?
What? What? What? What? What copycat do
I sound like?
Nah. Sorry, mate. I can't leave the
house. I'm agoprophobic. Sorry, bro.
Nah, I'm agrophobic, bro. I've got
anxiety. I can't meet you. Sorry.
Who Who do I sound like? Grievesy,
Greavvesy, you're [ __ ] gay. You don't
[ __ ] share a co attractive. Who Who
do I sound like?
Who do I [ __ ] sound like when I'm
saying that? Who do I sound like, bro?
No thank you.
[ __ ] some [ __ ] skin [ __ ]
disabled virgin trying to [ __ ] talk
about other people's sexualities
in his [ __ ] shitty medit by the
council. [ __ ] off, mate.
[ __ ] right off. You know what I mean? Come on. I'm hungry.
Yeah. I'm going cinema fried gravy.
We're going to have some hot dogs, some picker mix.
Nah, sorry mate. I'm not meeting you.
You go for a [ __ ] pint on a Wednesday.
To be fair, I've drunk on a Wednesday before.
That's the day my mommy replied to me on
Snapchat. Grievy, if you remember
correctly. If you remember correctly,
that's when my mommy replied to me on a Wednesday.
Yeah, but not in this weather, mate.
Yeah. Uh, midweek piss up, but not in
this [ __ ] weather. [ __ ] hell.
What the [ __ ] I think I've been out on
a Wednesday maybe twice. Maybe
you always seem to meet the best people
on a Wednesday. I know it's strange. Yeah. Virgin boy. [Music]
You like that, Grezy?
Hey, [ __ ] You all right?
You're right, [ __ ]
You like that, Grezy? You're You're right, [ __ ]
My belly is rumbling now.
I can get attached again, Greavvesy. I
can get attached again.
Do you believe that now, Greavves? I can
get attached again.
Why could I get attached before Greavvesy?
You don't even remember the reason. Oh,
you don't even remember the reason, do you?
Because you already found your mama.
Where? Where did I find my mama then? Grezy.
No, I don't tip them.
Where did I find my mama?
Oh, did she? That's nice. Nice.
That's not what her mom said last night.
That's not what That's not what her mom said.
Why is it with you people and money
every day? You must be really really
skinn. I think you people must get like
£300 a month or something
if that. Or you probably or you might
not even get any money. You constantly
always talk about money.
I really I really want you, but I don't
think you want me.
I was on the phone to this Canadian
woman yesterday and I told her like we
was talking about our sexual
experiences. I said, "Yeah, there was
one. I got a [ __ ] in the alleyway and
she was like, "How did it stop?" So I
said, "Basically, I approached somebody
in the pub
>> and um we're talking for a bit and then
they got like turned on, didn't they?"
And she was like, "I really want you,
but I don't think you want me."
And I said, "I do, but we just can't do
it here. You know, people are watching,
people are looking.
You know, you're causing a scene.
Do you know what that means, Grezy?
You're causing a scene here. So, I just
Yeah. took her to that anyway. Oh, and
the bouncer tried cop blocking me as
well, even though like she was coming on
to me and we both drunk, but the the
bouncer tried cop blocking me.
Yeah, the bouncers tried [ __ ] cop
blocking me, bro.
But it never worked.
I really want you, but I don't think you want me.
Do you remember the police officer when
when I was doing the Uber? Greavvesy.
What a [ __ ] idiot, man. Is it
I looked at him. What the [ __ ] I
thought he was taking a piss. Virgin boy.
I've had more women than you will ever have.
More women than you'll ever have in your life, matey.
More [ __ ] women than you'll ever have.
But you probably forgot you saw that
part as well.
I'm getting so hungry. I can't even talk
now, Greavvesy. I'm that hungry.
I won't be able to talk in a minute. I'm
too hungry to talk.
Bro, I've already had a girlfriend
before. You've never even had sex. Stop reflecting.
We don't have self- projecting on my
channel. Oh, [ __ ]
channel, Sunshine. You know the drill.
You self projectors, go back to where
you [ __ ] Go back to [ __ ] back to where
you come from. Lord Jay's, this is not a
self-p projecting channel,
bro. This is not a self-p projecting
channel. I'm not going to have you talk
about yourself like that.
I'm not going to have you put yourself
down like that. I can't see that on my
channel. I can't see you putting
yourself down anymore. It's not nice.
Don't [ __ ] Don't put yourself down, man.
Hey, stop putting yourself down.
Me and Grezy going for a KFC. Oh,
Peter B can't get attached anymore
because he's already found his mama.
He's never had a [ __ ] He's like
virgin boy. He's never had it.
He's just like the virgin.
Virgin boy. His name is
He's never had a [ __ ]
I don't even believe he has kids either.
So, I don't even believe he has kids to
be honest. I believe that's like his
sister's kids or some something
cuz how do you have all that time to
spend on YouTube if you got kids?
It doesn't make sense.
But who cares anyways?
I'm I'm I'm just caring about [ __ ] food.
Uh, you done projecting or
you still watching them GTA videos,
Grez? I watch them all the time. Things
you didn't know about GTA.
Yeah. So, that Sunday, I think I spent £300.
drinking. Gave my mom some money for her
birthday. I didn't even get a haircut. Living's expensive.
Do that a couple of times without any
wins, mate. You'll be like [ __ ] Virgin boy.
Skinn up 800 pound holidays. [ __ ]
skinny and a fy skit face.
You'll be [ __ ] skint like him, mate.
I'll never be [ __ ] like that, [ __ ]
No, I won a bet yesterday.
I won a football bet yesterday. No,
I had £7. The bet was actually 387 that
I won. I was going to put £7 on like
one, but can't be asked.
I want to go cinema and have some
popcorn, but I can't go until Friday. I
like going cinema, greasy, and having popcorn.
Come on. I'm [ __ ] starving.
What happened to Timmy? Did he lose all his money?
He's going to be like V one day. He's
He's going to be like Virgin boy one
day. Skin in the bed. [ __ ] You [ __ ] watch, mate.
You [ __ ] watch mate.
You'll be sking a [ __ ] bed sit one
day on that virgin. Yeah.
Why is the weather like this, bro? What
the [ __ ] man?
Greavvesy will never do that Uber thing.
Even if it wasn't for your back.
You wouldn't do it.
Yeah. I don't think you got the minerals
to do it, Greavves. The food delivery.
What are you going to do every day? You
wouldn't be able to do it every day. You
get fed up of it.
What would you do? You wouldn't
You wouldn't be able to do it every day.
What are you doing, Greavvesy every day? No,
that was some [ __ ] graph. That
[ __ ] thing on the bike, bro. It was hard, man.
Nah, it was hard, bro.
Nah, it's [ __ ] hard, bro. Trust me.
So what, Greasy? You'd work 9 hours for £80.
You'd work 9 hours for £80, wouldn't you, Greasy?
Yeah. You'd worked 9 hours for £80 on a
little bike, wouldn't you, Greasy? Yeah,
Greasy. 9 hours for £80 on a 90 on the bike.
It's like £10 an hour. You You earn £10
an hour basically. Well, unless you do
on a Sunday, then you you earn like6 an hour.
So, what do you Would you work for £10
an hour, Grezy?
Yeah, it's about £10 an hour.
Would you work for £10 an hour? crazy
just a little bit less.
But I mean,
if you got in a rhythm of it and you
done it every day, then you'd make a lot
of money at the end of the month,
wouldn't you? Minimum wage or no [ __ ]
minimum wage. If you think about it,
see, I'm too lazy to work, bro. I'm too [ __ ] lazy.
I'd rather chill and play Franklin.
Oh, yeah. That's what it is. It's a [ __ ]
Well, that's what it is. It's a side
job. It's not supposed to be
a main income. [Music]
I worked 8 hours before for 50 quid.
>> Yeah. It's not my food. No. Yeah. I'd
rather just chill and play Franklin.
Yeah, Greavves. I would just chill and
play Franklin, you know. I prefer that better.
So, how what what how much do you reckon
you could make a week doing it? If you
done it every day, Greasy, like honestly,
if you done it every day, how much do
you reckon you could make?
Say you done like eight hours a day,
maybe 500 maybe.
What do you think?
I made like 170 in three days.
If you're done Saturday, if you're done
Friday, Saturday, and a bit Sunday, then
maybe you can make 250 maybe.
But I'd rather just make it on bets, bro. Cuz
I can't be bothered working. I'm a lazy [ __ ]
I'm a [ __ ] lazy [ __ ] man. I'm a lazy
will never lose it. >> Yep.
I'm [ __ ] hungry.
Virgin boys really really skint
showing [ __ ] Amsterdam holidays. What
a [ __ ] skin flint. I'm telling you
that [ __ ] is skint [ __ ] skin.
He's a skint bastard.
They can't show me the color of their
money. You remember grievy? Remember
when I used to own them at the money
game? Yeah, which I still could. I could
still own them, right? But I just, you
know, they don't show you anything every
time you do do it. But the thing is, I
said, I want to see the color of your
money. I want to see some pinkies. And
he couldn't show me any cuz he ain't got
none. Know what I'm saying? Yeah. I
said, I want to see some 50s. Some juicy
50s with a man on it. I want to see your
shitty little 10 pound notes. Couldn't
show me nothing cuz you don't have it.
He's a skinned bastard. Oh, Franklin.
Oh, Franklin. Come on.
He's a skint. He's a skint [ __ ]
You skint bastard, mate.
He's a skint [ __ ] bastard. They ain't
got no money. Yeah,
I wish I put all my money on that
[ __ ] bet yesterday, mate.
I'd be laughing, mate. Put all my money
on that. But even even at 40, I lost on
a roulette. I wish I put that on it as
well. That would have been like 40.
Yeah, like over 500
or 160. [ __ ] sake, man.
But I never knew if the roulette was
going to pay out. That's why I just put
40 on the property. See?
>> Oh, [ __ ]
How do you know he is?
I'm [ __ ] need some food, man. Where
the [ __ ] is it?
[ __ ] starving, bro.
I'm [ __ ] hungry. Grooy, I feel like
[ __ ] nonssgs when his mom [ __ ] starved him. [ __ ] sake.
I feel like the [ __ ] virgin when he
got [ __ ] starved by his mama.
See, my mommy never starved me at the beginning. Grezy,
she abandoned me. She didn't starve me.
She just abandoned me. Grezy,
don't say that. I don't want that
[ __ ] virgin delivering my food. Don't
[ __ ] say that.
I'm [ __ ] saying I don't want that
[ __ ] skinned virgin [ __ ]
delivering my [ __ ] V with his skin self
with his shitty guitars and his skin
ugly face with no money.
I used to tease them a lot, didn't I? Easy. >> Yeah,
it's funny, bro. It's funny as [ __ ]
Funny as [ __ ] I am [ __ ] hungry.
You got more money than them. You got a
better life than them. And you're better
looking than them. And it kills them.
Good old Ronald McDonald.
He knew what they Yeah. Because if
people don't know people, right, why
would they go at them every day? Why
would they have channels dedicated to
people that they don't even [ __ ] know
who they've never actually met unless
they were jealous? Of course, it's true,
bro. What the [ __ ]
Cuz you wouldn't waste your time on
people you don't [ __ ] know or like.
You know what I'm saying?
It's like that red star [ __ ] disabled
on YouTube every day. No life.
This weather's depressing, is it?
Boy, my belly is
really hurting me, man.
Oh, bro. I'm just going to wait for this
Chinese Yeah. and eat it and then
[ __ ] go back live.
I'm going to eat it and I'll be back. [ __ ]