Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Oh, mate, I am stuffed.
Thought I'd go live. I was going to go
live today, but I thought [ __ ] it. Let
these boring [ __ ] send me to sleep cuz
I'm [ __ ] tired now. Jesus Christ. Yeah. Hey
had a nice Chinese. Now I'm feeling
quite sleepy. So ah
these balling punts will uh
send me to sleep. I'm sure.
I'm sure of it.
Oh, it's just lovely.
We're sitting by the fan
having a little sneeze.
Can't beat it. You can't [ __ ] beat Babe,
No, even these [ __ ] uh even these
Even these fat people.
Even the fat people
and these fat people have got [ __ ] um
I've got uh what's it called? Um,
they've got attitude basically. These
even these [ __ ] fat people.
Nah, man. I was I just had some food and
I was bored, so I thought I'd come on. I
mean, I I I use this as uh therapy um
therapy sessions basically. I'm [ __ ] tired, man.
So I thought why not?
I was speaking to good LT last night. Good L.
He's He's a He's a good chap. He is, you
know, LT deep down. you know, we might
not agree on everything, but um yeah.
And if I was to be class as anything,
everything, I would actually be classed
as a misogynist. I wouldn't be classed
as an incel. I'd actually be classed as a misogynist.
That's what I'd actually be classed as,
not an incel because I've had sex multiple times.
And I mean, I have an opinion even when
I give up on the dating scene. So, I
mean, that's more of a business
misogynist, but you know, he still
doesn't seem to think that [ __ ] USA
is he done anything wrong,
which he [ __ ] did. But he still
doesn't seem to think that
which is strange to be honest because
yes they did. Of course they [ __ ]
well did. You know exactly what you
[ __ ] done. So at the end of the day
like how I don't understand how we can
you know what I mean?
And it's not about people owe you this
or people don't. It takes 5 seconds.
Literally five [ __ ] seconds.
Do you understand? You know, that's part
of the whole entitlement. That's part of
them just being [ __ ]
You You get what I'm saying, bro? Like, he's
Oh, I don't agree with him at all, bro.
Not at all. [Music]
Not saying everything I done was right,
you know? I should have just allowed it,
obviously. But, I mean, in terms of like
they obviously did do something [ __ ]
wrong. What the [ __ ] is obvious, bro? But
um so yeah,
it's kind of [ __ ] up nowadays. You
can't have an opinion without being
called a [ __ ] incel.
It's crazy, bro. It's crazy. You can't
even have a different opinion nowadays.
It's a [ __ ] madness.
I was thinking of going out. Yeah. Not
not this week, the week after, but then I thought
there's literally no point, is there?
There's no point in it.
Pointless. Pointless as [ __ ]
Oh [ __ ] man. Yo,
but yeah, the [ __ ] did do something wrong.
And that whole me and this Canadian
woman was talking about this, right?
It's like, oh, that that how that whole
like I don't owe you anything, right? is
it's used in an incorrect context,
you know, and like
you know, like um yeah, okay, people
might not technically owe people um
good man. Yeah, they might not
technically owe people something, but at
the end of the day, you know, it doesn't
take [ __ ] 10 seconds to be to be courteous.
Do you know what I'm saying? So, like,
think about what you're [ __ ] saying, bro.
And then we was talking about how like,
you know, when you approach someone and
they say straight away they're not
interested. I find I do find it rude. I
do find it rude,
you know. I I I do find it very rude.
But hey, maybe I'm just different.
Oh, I almost had a fight today on the
bus as well.
Yeah. Oh, yeah. I forgot all about that.
I actually once had a fight on the uh
bus. Typical uh English person can start
something but they can't finish it.
Crazy, isn't it? Seems like it it really
never changes the country with the kind
of people that are in it.
Oh, yeah. I forgot about that on the way back.
Craziness, isn't it? Craziness.
All of you guys. All of All of you guys.
Who are you guys?
I'm more English than you.
I'm more British than you. What the
[ __ ] Are you okay, bro? I mean, I'm I'm
literally more British than you are.
What would give you the impression that
I'm not? I'm literally more English than you.
What the [ __ ] Are you a [ __ ] or something?
Are you an absolute [ __ ]
Do you know how much [ __ ] white I've
I've I've got in me?
Why would I get deported when I'm more
English than you?
What the [ __ ] I'm literally more
English than you, bro. I have the
slightest bit of Turkish in me and
that's it. Nothing, Mike, man. I [ __ ]
I want to [ __ ] double both teams to
score the other day, bro. 120 return 380,
but I lost 40 on the roulette. That's
why I don't I don't touch them machines
anymore, bro. I was just bored.
Yeah, I just went out today, walked the dog.
Some [ __ ] [ __ ] tried starting
[ __ ] on the [ __ ] bus on the roulette.
Nah, the football bet was good though. I
got 380 from 120.
So, I mean, it's good return, isn't it?
I done five football bets in the past
two months, bro. And I won three out of
four. Three out of five.
Yeah, I won three out of five.
300 on that. [ __ ] man.
What? Online or?
Yeah, I want I've won three bets.
Yeah, it's getting hard everywhere. You
can't win anymore, bro. The only thing
you can really win on is is the football.
That's what I won on. So, cuz I spent a
lot of money on Sunday, like £3400, and
I wanted to sort of win some money back
cuz I don't have loads and loads of
loads anymore, you know? So, so yeah,
the only thing you could probably
The only thing you can probably win on
is like probably the football now, bro.
To be honest, it's all [ __ ] fixed.
I used to go casinos on Thursdays. I
used to win like nine times out of 10. I
used to clean them, bro. But um
yeah, [ __ ] that. [ __ ] that roulette
Yeah, I played a I played a spinning
one. I wish I just put the 160 on the
[ __ ] bet and not the 120. I I wish I
put the whole 160 on it now. Yeah,
I wish I just put the whole 160 on. It
would have been quite a bit better in
it. So, still money in it.
Yeah, I win some I win some good
football bets, Mike, you know, and then
double both teams to score.
I want some the [ __ ]
want some good ones on them, bro.
Yep. You need to pack that [ __ ] in, bro.
What the [ __ ]
Why are you still doing that, man? It's not good.
I'm kind of bored of it. Me, bro. I've
gambled like so much in my life, bro.
Like probably I wouldn't say more than
you. Yeah. But maybe on the same level
as you. Cuz bro, I've gambled. I used to
gamble [ __ ] three times a week.
Trust me, bro. I used to be in them
casinos more than anyone, bro. Like the
past two and a half years.
Never done my bollocks in for like 3
years. So yeah, I just bet on the
football for the extra money, bro, that
I need nowadays. when I need extra
money, I just like lump on a football bet.
It seems to work a lot of the time. So
that's the only reason I sort of do it
at the minute, bro. Too lazy to work. So
it's nice when you win a double both
teams to score, bro. You know, you don't
get you understand the buzz, you know,
when you're waiting for one team to
score and then you you watch the
penalty, bro. Like, [ __ ] me. It's so
good, bro. The buzz is so good
when it's like dot dot when it's like a
[ __ ] red dot and it's beeping. B.
Nah, bro. Just a football
when I need when I try when I need the
extra money. Or I could do with the
extra money. But yeah,
it's [ __ ] ace, man.
Yeah, I won three football bets the past
few times I hit
80 to I put 80 in, got it to 280, put 80
in, got it to 230, then I put 120
and then got to 380. So yeah, I don't
touch the roulette or slots, bro. I I
literally only do the [ __ ] football cuz of
Yeah, I'm not working at the minute. So
yeah, stop talking about yourself. No
self projecting on my channel.
Um, but yeah,
no self projecting on my channel. Nope.
I don't play any of that [ __ ] bro.
None of that [ __ ] Nah,
not at all. At all.
I never used to like slots until I played Frankie,
but I'll be stopped working soon anyway,
so probably won't even do the football anymore. So,
you lost 300 on roulette. That's not
good, is it, matey?
I bet you was kicking off on that, ain't it?
Just Thailand in November.
I'm going Thailand in November, which is
a month after my birthday. So,
[ __ ] this for a game of soldiers, bro.
Yeah, that's the only one I got.
I don't [ __ ] uh
Yeah. Walk of shame.
Oh, [ __ ] In terms of like different
cities here. Nah.
I went Birmingham to see Monty. That was
the first time I left London and
to go to a different city.
A long time, bro, in England.
No trips, matey.
Bro, I know somebody that smoked a joint
and then went back with a hammer.
They lost like a grind in the Brookies.
They come back, smoked a joint, and went
back with a hammer. That's got caught
and everything. It was a madness.
It was a [ __ ] madness, bro.
Nah, bro. I don't do that. I mean, I go
I go out in London and [ __ ] but in
terms of England, nah, bro. I can't
afford it anymore cuz I'm leaving soon.
So I can't afford to be spending
like3400 [ __ ] pounds every and by
can't afford it I mean I can't do it and
then do what other things I want to do.
Not that I literally would go skinny if
I done it if that makes sense. So
obviously yeah it's one or the other.
You know what I mean?
One or the other matey.
It doesn't matter where I'm living, bro.
Doesn't matter where I'm living, matey.
What casino did you go to? Gro.
Yeah, it's funny, bro. He lost 60 pound, didn't it?
but no, I don't I don't gamble serious, bro.
That's what these skint people do, it
skint people do, Mike. That's why they
come online every day calling people
skint cuz they are skint.
You know how it is.
They call people skin cuz they're skin.
[ __ ] hell, man.
You're mad. You are.
They ain't got nothing, bro. They sit
online all day talking about people they
don't know, bro. Arguing with people
that they don't arguing with people they
don't know that they've never met. They
ain't got a life. Literally, none of
them have got a life, bro. They're just
old farts. They've got nothing.
So, they just self-reflect cuz that's
all they really have in their life. They
just they just get laughed at, bro. You know,
yeah, they're in WhatsApp groups as
well. They're weirdos. But the only
madest thing is they'll never meet
they'll never meet each other.
Like they're actually scared to actually
meet each other, but they're in WhatsApp
groups email and emailing people. [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] weirdos, bro. [ __ ] abs.
A absolute [ __ ] weirdos, lad. They
[ __ ] are. No, I haven't heard from
them for ages.
The casinos are dodgy, is it, Mike? like
finding ways to not pay people out and [ __ ]
That's another thing that puts me off
them as well is trying to get paid out.
You know, they don't like paying out in it. [ __ ]
madness, bro. What do you mean you take
people with you?
>> Yeah, I told you that time when I had
£500 and they ripped the ticker.
But I got the last laugh though cuz bro,
like I I used to rinse them
every [ __ ] week. I used to rinse them bastards.
Qu grand 1600s.
They got [ __ ] bro. Like, yeah.
No, they didn't pay me, bro. They voided
the ticket. Remember I told you they
actually voided the ticket.
Remember that? Like, they voided they
can actually void the ticket on a
computer. So, like say you got money on
the roulette in the in the credits,
right? They could actually void the
ticket. So it means it's a void.
Yeah. Like they said to me I was banned.
Yeah. I I put £300 and I won like a,000
and I had to wait like 3 days for the [ __ ] money.
Something like that happened to me, bro.
I had to wait [ __ ] 3 days for the
money. There, oh, you're banned. And
then when I went again,
like they just voided my ticket.
There's, oh, we told you you can't come.
So, they were all dodgy as well, bro.
That's just dodgy as [ __ ]
Yeah, I had to wait three days to get
paid a thousand
in the end. But when I went again, I had
like I put I was £500 in and they voided my ticket.
So, like I lost [ __ ] £500.
Yeah. So, but I had the last laugh out
of them anyways. I I took enough money
from them time and time and time and
time again. So, what I'm saying is they
actually void the ticket.
So, what I mean is like say you put
five, say you put money in the machine,
they could actually void the ticket. Um, so
yeah, they're just [ __ ] bro. If
they didn't pay me that thousand, I
would have I would have went back with a
hammer. I'm not even joking, bro.
I actually would have went back with a
hammer. I swear to God, I would have.
No, listen, bro.
They said basically
they said, "Oh, you need to you need to
come back with ID." So, I went outside.
I gave it to this American guy. I said,
"Oh, if you cash this in, right, you can
have some of it." Like, I said, "Oh, you
can have like£60 70." I weren't asked
like I could just go to another casino.
Then he was texting me saying that it's
void. I was like, "What do you mean it's void?"
So yeah, they they actually voided the ticket
cuz he gave me the ticket back and it
wasn't paid. So yeah, bro, they can void
they can actually void tickets,
which is mad. The [ __ ] They let you in
there and then they they let you in
there and gamble and then when you [ __ ] win,
they don't like it.
So, it's just corrupt.
It's just corrupt, lad.
Yeah, but they won't let me in cuz they
all know me. They're all walking, but
yeah, they're all walkins.
More walkkins. Yep.
They're all walking, bro.
I don't know, bro. I don't really give a
[ __ ] about gambling anymore, to be
honest, bro. I don't even know why we're
talking about it.
You shouldn't even still be doing it,
bro. to be honest with you after like
with all the [ __ ] that's happened, man.
You should try to give that [ __ ] up.
Really, to be honest with you,
I'm done with it, bro. Like, like I
said, I only done the football cuz I
needed the extra money. You know what I
mean? Cuz I had spent a lot.
But I'll be working soon anyway, so I
won't I won't even need to do that anymore. So,
well, to see how much money I can make. So,
yeah. But I've not been skinned for like
three and a half years.
I gave up cuz of the mood swings it was
giving me. That's the reason I stopped doing it.
I stopped doing it because of the mood
swings that it was giving me, not
because of like me being That's why I stopped doing it
cuz I do like 150 150 150 and the [ __ ]
just all adds up. That's why I stopped
doing it and it just gives you mood
swings as well, like proper mood swings.
So that's why I stopped doing it. But I
learned the football the other day cuz I
needed the extra money.
That's why I stuck 120 on two teams. It
returned 380. It's just under £400 in it. So,
I needed the extra money, bro. So, yeah.
Like I said, I spent a lot of money on Sunday.
That's the thing. You go out.
You go out once.
You go out [ __ ] once. Yeah.
And you're spending like [ __ ] two 300
[ __ ] pound just drinking and [ __ ]
you know? You're [ __ ] done for, bro.
That's that's a problem when you go out,
you know. So, yeah.
Uh went out on Sunday to do some
approaches, done some drinking,
load of [ __ ] Same old. Um
put 120 on the football bet, 1380.
And yeah, man.
Same same as [ __ ] really.
>> Yeah. Went out approaching on Sunday,
but it was just the same old [ __ ] as always is. Yeah, man.
You've seen this episode before. Well,
bro, I've seen this episode for [ __ ]
6 years. you people coming on YouTube
every day calling people skin.
So, I mean, I've seen I've seen you
self-reflected for the past 6 years
before I could even [ __ ] um
uh before I could even go facial hair.
So, yeah, bro. They're all projectors
ghosting. All of them are self projectors.
All of them are, bro.
Like when they call people skin and
Yeah, bro. No, they're all self
projectors. All of them, man.
You know what I find so mad, ghosting,
is they they argue, right, and obsess
over people every day that they don't
even know, that they've not even met.
How mad is that?
Think about that, bro, for one second
that they don't even know.
It's so mad. Even that Red Star account
sat on YouTube all day every day
stalking. It's madness. But they don't
understand how mad it is because they're
disabled, right? A lot of these people.
Um, no, it's not about a reaction. This
is another thing I I forgot to tell you
as well before you left the other day.
It's not about a reaction because even
if you don't react to them, they will
still do it.
Even if you ignore them, right?
At the end of the day, even if you
ignore them, they will still do it. So,
it's not for a reaction because they
don't get a reaction. They they don't do
Even if they don't get a reaction, they
would still do it. Yeah. They call me
skin cuz they're skin,
bro. That's why I laugh at it, man.
Like, when they sit there and say, "Show
me money," and they try to show me like
a proxy, thousand pound. I just laugh at
them, bro. Cuz they know they've lost
the money game time and time again.
I don't give a [ __ ]
I mean, think about it, bro. Even if
they done it for reaction. Yeah. Okay.
Let's just say that you're right and
they do it for reaction. Okay. So, say
So, say you you react six months later.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Think about this. Right.
Yeah. Well, they've been I've shown them
more than £1,000
and I could show them more than £1,000
now, but I'm not going to because every
time you show these people money, they
run away. So, I'm not playing their
silly games again anymore. And another
thing is listen,
what I was saying is listen listen
even if they do it for reaction. Yeah.
Okay. So, so let's just say they're
stalking you all day every day for
reaction, right? So let's just say
they're doing it all day every day for
reaction. Yeah. And say you react to
them after 6 months. Okay. So then what?
So okay. So you reacted for like what 5
seconds. Okay. And then what what's the end goal?
So you waste 6 months of your life to
get a reaction and then after you get a
reaction then what? See it doesn't make
sense. They don't they don't do it for reaction.
They do it because they're jealous of something.
That's that's why they do it, bro.
Because they wouldn't do it otherwise.
So simple as that.
What do you mean? Do something about it.
Well, they're never ever going to stop.
Yeah. They will never ever stop. Even if
you didn't react to them, they're jealous.
Of course, they will never stop.
Yeah, they will never ever stop.
they're never going to stop the lads.
Never ever ever. Even when they're dead,
they'll never stop. They ain't got a
life. They're skinn and they ain't got a
life, bro. What else do they have to do?
Okay. Yeah. One sec.
But yeah, it is funny when these people
try to um
play the money game and show you le way
less than what you've turned in.
Yeah, that's Jamie. Yeah.
Why is he an idiot? Oh, I just had a
nice Chinese ghost in. Oh, it was lust,
man. It was [ __ ] lush.
>> It was [ __ ] sending me to sleep, man.
[ __ ] tired as [ __ ] I am, man. >> Yo,
>> you all right?
>> Yeah, man.
>> I can't stand.
>> I tell you what I be doing. No, I'll
tell you why. Yeah,
>> you are right on one thing. It is
jealousy while they do do it.
>> M it is jealousy is because you're
younger and them. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> You're not as fat as them. Yeah. And
you're not as over the years. Yeah.
>> And you got more money than them as well.
>> About the money, but even if you didn't
have money, it's to do with the voc
get if you can get laid or if you can't get laid.
>> Yeah. anything to do with all that
>> and you can actually go out and like
what I mean by that money yeah is it it
doesn't matter about the money but it it
does in a way where like you can
actually go out and a fool to go out
they can't does that make sense like yeah yeah
>> no of course of course but it's more to
do with that really and what money is
because everybody really gets money
either way benefits or not these people
won't be living now do you know what I mean
>> yeah but I mean look at belly he gets
300 00 a month. Look how
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I know that.
Just just about a slip off that. Do you
know what I mean? So
>> these will probably come out with a
little bit more in order about the same.
Obviously they come out with more what
does because these people pay pay people
money on YouTube. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? So these people do
pay people out on YouTube. >> Yeah.
>> But it's not that what they really
really jealous is what you look like and
how old you are and
>> Yeah. You know what I mean?
>> Yeah, man. And that's what I think it is
to be honest with you.
>> It is. No, it is that because if it
wasn't that, Monty. Yeah. They wouldn't
do this all day every day. Like, think
about it. They don't even know you.
They've never met you. Think about it.
You know what I'm saying?
>> Yeah. Look at George. If you want to
know who George is, it's John West. Look at him.
>> So, it's the same with that red star, isn't it? >> Yeah.
I didn't I didn't know that [ __ ] John
West we call George
>> Jamie Hager beast
all of the beasts in this community is
used man. Yeah, 100%.
>> I was just I was just busy today, Monty.
I don't have time to be on here, you
know, all all day like them.
>> I haven't even been on all day, me
either. I'm just Come on.
Had a nice Chinese me. Oh, lovely.
>> Was it nice with it?
>> Yeah, it's nice Chinese, isn't it?
>> Oh, no. It depends. I like my car's me.
Kerry's are pretty nice
>> from where
>> from takeaway shops. Kyot is
>> Yeah, Indians is nice. Chinese is nice.
>> Jamie Hag is a [ __ ]
>> Well, you must be a big [ __ ] me on
YouTube all day. This bastard can get
laid and you can't. And that is I
[ __ ] love it.
>> You can call me what the [ __ ] you want.
So would you like a lamb co in it?
>> I like any kind. I look
>> you can call me whatever you want
please. But you 10 times worse than what
I am in life. Come on man. Have you seen
Ben? Have you seen Ben my dick's misses?
What [ __ ] Not making fun or nothing
like that but walk [ __ ] down. Ben my
dick. Your birds are [ __ ]
That's [ __ ] who he's going out with.
>> Have you seen my dick's girlfriend? >> No.
>> Yeah, I send you a picture. I'm not
[ __ ] around, PJ.
I'm not [ __ ] around. He's
been my digest girlfriend.
>> One second.
>> I'm not [ __ ] around either. Look at her name.
That's been my biggest girlfriend. No [ __ ]
>> Are you friends with um are you friends
with Rick's mace?
>> No. I'm a [ __ ] Why?
>> Just wondering.
>> No, I'm not m with Rick.
I'm not m with anybody on this community
who I don't know in real life. PJ,
>> kick this loser. Nah, Monty's all right, man.
>> Kick this loser.
Dave, why don't you come up on the panel
then and talk and I will go if you come
up. Yeah, I will go. You're basically
giving PJ no one to talk to. So,
>> yeah. So, if you come up Yeah. Yeah. I
will go. Yeah. Oh [ __ ]
Ask him to count to 30.
Hey, that's easy. 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10
11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23
24 25 26 27 28 29
There you go. You [ __ ] clown.
>> It's [ __ ] weird this man.
>> Yeah, it's closely count. You don't
ignore me on here, do you? When I c
usually when I do [ __ ] up, that's me
[ __ ] up on pushy clowns.
That's me doing that [ __ ] on purpose.
>> Have you ever had
you ever had a beef chowine?
>> No, I'm not too sure.
>> From the Chinese.
>> I think I'm not too sure. Oh, that's so nice, man.
>> He's the biggest clown I've ever seen in
my life. Take your cap off in the show. Ask your
>> Well, if I'm the biggest One, one sec.
But if I'm the biggest clown in this
community, what the [ __ ] are you doing
on YouTube? Repeating yourselves every [ __ ] day.
Usually a bigger clown than what I am
by repeating the same [ __ ] count. Add
somes shake off. Look how bored you are.
And I'm about as bored as your mom's
[ __ ] lad. And I love it.
>> Your mom's [ __ ] N is N is Mongo's carer.
>> N she's not even my carer. It just shows
how much you actually know. It shows how
much you are fuckups in life, doesn't
it? It really shows how much they really
know PJ cuz Natalie's not even my car.
Natalie is not a Kayie a money grabber.
Like Kay is a racist carer. Jesus Christ.
>> Are you
>> Am I a money grabber? No, I don't like
money to be honest. Peia,
>> you're a money grabber.
>> What a money grab it. [ __ ]
>> We need to go for a drink again. >> N.
>> Yeah, I know.
Yeah, she gets paid to look after [ __ ] Jamie.
>> Oh, she does she? I didn't know that.
You must be the [ __ ] for making up
all that excuses what you don't know.
>> Oh [ __ ]
>> This community is all about money, isn't it?
>> Yeah, of course it is. That's only what
they think about is [ __ ] money. What
What are you jealous if Natalie is my
carer? Obviously Natalie isn't my carer.
But if she is, you'd be jealous cuz he
coming out more with more money than you
then, won't you? And at least
>> you're not you're not coming in, Lord J, you [ __ ]
>> Yeah. No, don't let him up. Don't let the self-reflector.
>> Yeah, he's a selfreflecting bastard.
>> [ __ ] [ __ ] Talk about everybody else
what they do on YouTube, but don't talk
about the own [ __ ] he does. Yeah,
>> the [ __ ] mongos, man.
>> Yeah, the skin PJ and then they call you skin.
>> You like it though?
>> I don't like it, mate.
>> I think it's weird.
I think it's weird as [ __ ] Come on up my lad.
>> If that's only what these entertainment
these people go, it's not entertainment
to me. It's just pastified.
It's just looking for attention. What
these people are not getting off mommy
or daddy attention
or they're coming on YouTube looking for
attention of people like us
because mommy and daddy didn't give
these attention in their part time.
And that's what HP. Yeah,
>> it's just creep. It's [ __ ] weird.
Damian's mates with nons legs. Yeah, I
hear that though.
PJ, this is why I [ __ ] you off all the
time. Thinking amazingly [ __ ] nons
legs and [ __ ] like that. You better
[ __ ] sort that [ __ ] out, PJ man.
This is why I [ __ ] you off cuz this
is your fault why people think amaz.
You're a [ __ ] freak, PJ.
>> Don't ever put me on [ __ ] shows, mate. PJ,
I'm not the one who's [ __ ] met
[ __ ] Sean. Never put me on his
[ __ ] level, PJ. Never.
I started coming for you, PJ. Like, I
will start [ __ ] coming for you.
Keep on putting me on Sean's [ __ ]
level, saying I'm his mate and all that.
Look, you're a [ __ ] weirdo, PJ doing that [ __ ]
I'm not the one who's [ __ ] met that longlegged [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but you you [ __ ] knew him
before me and you [ __ ] made PJ, you
[ __ ] prick. Does it mean I [ __ ]
chilled with him like you did?
>> Yeah, I didn't know. Yeah. Did I know what you
>> I told you they were like on
PlayStation. I told you it was a [ __ ]
big ass nons, but you were like, "No,
it's not. No, it's not. No, he's not.
He's all right. Sean on lens. He's all
>> Yeah. Yeah. Cuz I felt sorry for him.
>> Felt sorry for announce.
>> Yeah. I didn't know that until I [ __ ]
met him. Obviously.
>> Everybody told you. Everybody told you.
>> Ed told you he was announced back on PlayStation.
>> Nons and Mark Taylor. Three online
predators, bro. Two are actually online predators.
>> Who are? [ __ ] Mark Taylor and Nons,
but they're trying to say you're a
predator as well.
>> I might [ __ ] a predator. It was Mark
Taylor. Matt Taylor who went for Make
sure you clowns. Not me.
It was It was Matt Taylor who done [ __ ]
with Emma. Make sure. Not me. I've done
nothing. Have I ever Peter, just tell
the truth. Yeah. Have I ever dated
anyone younger than myself except on PlayStation? No.
There you go, you [ __ ] clowns.
Only person who dated on PlayStation for
proper relationship was [ __ ] Kay. You
were the youngest person I've been with on PlayStation.
>> You [ __ ] idiots.
And Shy Longlegs was never my mate.
So stop putting [ __ ] on me. What's not
my [ __ ] You [ __ ] idiots.
>> That that Britney thing was so weird, man.
I told you about Sean or PJ. So stop
putting Sean on me saying he's your mate
PJ. I didn't mean to change it to Sean.
American [ __ ] did. I don't know. But
it weren't [ __ ] me.
>> Okay. Now
it's just [ __ ] weird.
>> Well, it's weird you putting up my little me.
Listen PJ [ __ ] is in Fat Dan and Valley
stream 24/7. He's a snake.
>> Okay, I'm in Fat Dan first.
>> Yeah, I used to be in Fat D. I'm
checking Peace out.
>> Launch Legs [ __ ] and M Taylor all the
same. And you know it PJ.
>> Yeah, PJ knows about about M being
showing legs. Why do you mean why do you
read these things? What you already
know? You know what I mean?
>> Cuz you read it as well.
>> I don't read [ __ ] It's your reason she
out. And this is why Natalie doesn't
want to meet you. It's cuz you're a prick.
>> You read out. I don't even want to know.
That's funny. Is it?
>> I won't read anything then. Okay. I
won't read it.
>> But you know what you're doing is you
send me some shitty pictures you send
me. Oh, look how people like like
[ __ ] Lord sending me. I show Yeah, I
show you Timmy cuz it's funny as [ __ ]
>> Why is it funny?
>> Cuz he's making a [ __ ] of himself.
>> [ __ ] weird about your mate. You won't
be s You're taking a piss out of me.
What you reading comments? What? Don't
What What don't make sense, PJ?
>> Okay. Well, then don't come on YouTube then. Simple.
>> Simple. You're the one who got my ass on
YouTube. You don't remember that?
>> Okay. And now I'm I'm going to try and
get you off of it.
>> You can't get me off it, can you?
>> Well, there you go. Nobody shitty
community page here because of you got
mentally shitty thing.
>> Oh [ __ ] man.
>> Yeah, it is funny. Timmy making a tit of
himself. It's funny. That's why I send
you. It is funny. It's funny as [ __ ]
>> No, but PJ, think about it. These people
these people are sus
on YouTube [ __ ] lied calling other
people pedals when you don't even have
the proof on that [ __ ]
Do you know what I mean?
They don't have approve on [ __ ] all but
they sit there and call people penos.
Why don't you Google me? Ro stay on me
[ __ ] ro stay on grave you. Yeah yeah
Google me you clowns.
Oh watch all the old videos on YouTube
of me taking piss out of being a nons. Yeah,
>> you people are [ __ ] Mongs in this
community thinking of me and Mitchell as
well done [ __ ] No, people with me and
Christy Mitchell, not Emma. Emma M to do
with M [ __ ] clothes. >> Yeah,
it's just weird. All right,
>> it is [ __ ] weird, TJ. But you make it
more weird is when you start agreeing
with these people against me. This is like
wait. I haven't agreed with anything.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. [ __ ] show this,
mate. Yeah, he is.
>> I'm not
for you, but that doesn't make me his [ __ ] mate. You know,
>> that doesn't make me his mate for knowing someone.
You know what I mean? Would I now go out
and meet Sean in person? No. What a
[ __ ] Unless I'm going to smash his
[ __ ] head in putting all this [ __ ]
all over YouTube.
Now I've done [ __ ] with Emma. Who's
Emma? Emma's [ __ ] kissed his sister.
Who have I done [ __ ] with? Kirsty. Who's
my Taylor done [ __ ] with? Kirsty. I mean Emma.
>> Yeah. Ny's been a prick to me as well.
>> DJ did not think you're a prick. No, I
think she's a prick because she was
going to make me go all the way there
years ago and she weren't even going to
meet me, she said. So, I think that's a
bit of a prick
if you ask me.
>> PJ, that was ages ago back then when I
went there. Yeah, but what if I actually went there?
>> Then I would have been
>> I think she still met you PJ. Come on,
lad. I think
>> Well, she told people she wouldn't. So,
but how what am I supposed to believe?
Well, I don't know what you're supposed
to believe, but that's not me, is it?
>> No, I know. No, but that's You said that's why.
>> That's not me, is it? >> Yeah.
only met you because Natalie met me. I
don't know why she met me. She not likes
me for a long time.
Natalie's even told me she's liked me
for a long time, but she couldn't say
anything to me cuz I was in a relationship. Yeah,
>> it's the same as um
when I got this card through my door. I
got I got a card through my door off Natalie,
>> but it won't open. It was about It was
to do with cosmic kitty Snickers
>> when I got through my door with Cosmic
Kitty Snickers. Yo, I'm going to jump
anyway. My guys here, so I'm going to
jump. Yeah. All right. In a minute.
always takes it out of [ __ ] me, man.
I didn't even do anything wrong.
Always an art with me.
You know what I mean? [ __ ] um
this Tinder is a [ __ ] joke, you know.
No, I'm not saying that stuff.
He takes things too serious. I send him
Timmy Elder stuff cuz it's funny.
[ __ ] two out of 10 with [ __ ] attitude. [ __ ] Crazy, man.
Absolute bat [ __ ] Crazy, bro. Oh my god. Crazy.
Let me try and get him back.
He blames me. Yeah.
He's the one that comes on my live and joins, you know.
He always [ __ ] blames me, man. Sick of it.
He always blames me. Always. [ __ ] sake.
No, there's a lot of people jealous of
Peter Belly on here. Red Star is the biggest one.
That [ __ ] stalks me all day, every day.
Time he wakes up to the time he goes to
bed. That red star is a [ __ ] stalker, man.
Imagine that. Sat on YouTube stalking
someone every day you don't even know.
That's a madness. That's a madness, bro.
That is a [ __ ] madness. B, bro. Mhm.
Oh man, I'm [ __ ] tired, bro.
That [ __ ] Chinese. Oh,
put me in the food coma, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Chinese again. 20. It actually
come to £31.
Jesus Christ. We're not all skit like a
certain virgin army.
We're not all [ __ ] skit like a
[ __ ] certain virgin, are we, mate?
No, man. We're not all skin in a [ __ ]
bed [ __ ] are we, mate? No,
we're not all [ __ ] skin like a
[ __ ] like a [ __ ] burden in the
[ __ ] bed, mate. Are we not mentioning
any [ __ ] names here? You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. So, stop [ __ ] [ __ ] shy on
me, PJ. Yeah. [ __ ] man.
>> Now that [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah, but now
that [ __ ] is [ __ ] obsessed with me
for the rest of his life now, bro.
>> That's your fault. I already told you
back on PlayStation what he
what he used to do.
>> [ __ ] weirdo, man.
>> Oh my days, man. And now he put his
[ __ ] [ __ ] on me. [ __ ] madness.
It's a madness, bro.
Oh, these people are [ __ ] weirdos,
man. Why Why did you get me into this
shitty community anyway, Pet? Why?
But if if you think about it, it's
actually made us closer.
>> No, no, not exactly. Because it's making
me also hate you, Pe.
>> Yeah, but we met and stuff, isn't it?
>> No, no. Just the [ __ ] you just said,
your natural saying that I'm Johnny
Long's mate and all that. Look,
>> no, mate.
But basically, you're putting me on. Oh,
you like him. Why don't you go a drink
with him all the time and that? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. But then you get people in here
who would believe that [ __ ] You know
what I mean?
>> It's a joke, but he like obviously.
>> So, it's okay for you to have a joke,
but not me.
>> No, I would never [ __ ] sit there and
say, "Look at you, man. You you was a
pedo mate." Obviously, you you were
yours mate back then. Yeah. But I want
to sit there and put that back on to you
like you do it with me. Oh, look at you.
Why don't you go out with a drink on
your understand? Do you not understand
that? I actually felt sorry for him
before like you know before I met him
and [ __ ] He used to get bullied. Yeah.
So I I thought like oh someone's just
picking on this this this weird kid. You understand?
>> Yeah. Yeah. But do you understand why
you were getting picked on now?
>> Now but back then I didn't. You don't
understand. Back then I didn't.
Yeah. And it's same as that Jack the Ripper, right?
>> Even you know what you told me about
Jack I was just about to say that yet. I
didn't know any of this [ __ ] before
meeting him. Obviously.
>> Okay. Now,
>> you know what I mean? I didn't know any
of that [ __ ]
>> The community what I got you w to on you
on PlayStation PJ with rude girl lights
and all that back on PlayStation. All
them to choose to show long legs. I got
introduced to Shy Longlegs myself
through all them myself. >> Yeah,
>> I don't know shy long legs and proper
myself. I've never had Shy Long Legs on
my friend list on PlayStation. I've
never talked to him. I used to do a fat
down thing to him where I sit on his
panel and call him to [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean?
And that's what I used to do. >> Yeah.
I used to sit in my bedroom day in and
day out every day in back in Manchester.
Never went out cuz I used to get a lot
of [ __ ] by the police
like you already know. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? I never went out.
I stayed in.
You know what I mean? So [ __ ] That's
how I got to know his long legs.
>> He's just a weirdo, man.
But the youngest girl read I'm not
reading out your comments.
>> No, don't read them. PJ reading them.
>> I can read them myself if I want to, but
I don't read the self-reflecting comment.
I'm not being funny. John West's real
name PJ. What is it?
>> What is it again? I don't know.
>> It's John West's name's called George.
>> Is it? >> Yeah.
And that voice he puts on
is it's not his like fake voice.
Basically, it's his real voice, but he
put it makes it more [ __ ] fake. >> Yeah.
>> You know, it's clipping.
>> Yeah. Clipping is a weird it.
>> Yeah. That's who John West is clipping.
>> Oh [ __ ] So, is is Guinness your
favorite drink now?
>> I don't drink really pee. Yeah,
>> it's too good, isn't it?
>> Yeah, but it takes you a while to get pissed.
>> Yeah, obviously. What? What? What? Any
drink is it?
>> No, not any drink. No, some drinks. It
depends really how you are. See, I don't
even get pissed off proper because I
don't drink it proper. So, I don't
exactly get pissed. If I have Guinness,
I think I'm like drunk after the second
one. It starts hitting me, bro.
>> Doesn't it? >> Yeah.
>> Like when we had no drink on the into your belly.
>> Yeah. [ __ ] that. Is it?
>> It's all right cuz you get it get you pissed more.
>> Yeah. The longer you go out, like if say
you haven't drunk for like two months
and then you go to drink, you get pissed
quicker. It depends how like long you go
about it as well. I mean
>> these days they die. Why don't these
people come up on the box PJ? Because
they know if they come up on the box.
Yeah. They're just going to get ripped
into stay in the comment race. They
write [ __ ] to piss you off from there. >> Yeah.
>> That's what they do.
That's what I tell you. Don't read the comment.
>> I'm not reading it. I'm not reading it. >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] not. If you want yards to
change, you don't read them. You're [ __ ] idiots.
>> Yeah, I won't read it. Don't worry.
>> You know what I mean? I'm [ __ ] not
self-reflecting anymore to these people.
You know, I've got a lot on at the
moment. What these people don't even
know about. Now, they does.
What do you mean?
>> I'm not saying [ __ ] all to you either,
PJ. You're the biggest on YouTube.
>> I could probably guess what it is.
>> You can't keep a secret at all.
>> I could probably guess what it is. You
make it so obvious. >> What?
>> I probably already know what it is.
>> Go on. What is it?
>> I'm not going to say, but I probably can
tell on it.
>> Go on. What is it? Just check. If you
know what it is, just say
>> babies in it.
>> Nothing to do with babies. No,
>> you don't know nothing. >> What?
>> You don't know what I meant by that, is it?
>> Yeah. Natalie pregnant.
>> Yeah, I see.
>> No, Natalie's not pregnant.
>> Oh, no. Nothing to do with that.
Anyways, even if she were pregnant or
not pregnant, I won't be saying [ __ ]
about that on YouTube either way.
>> Yeah, cuz you know what they do it obviously.
>> Yeah, of course. And if Natalie is
pregnant, none of you will see me again
on YouTube. I'll be gone.
>> No, I think you'd still come back.
>> No, no, no. I'll be gone. I'll be [ __ ] gone.
>> Really? Forever?
>> Yeah. Forever. I won't come back on YouTube if
I will never ever come back on YouTube again. Never.
>> Yeah. I'm alive.
>> Have you Have you and Money Mike squash
the beef now?
>> Money m's going to get his nose bed back to normal.
>> No, I only sent you the Timmy [ __ ]
Yeah, cuz it's so funny him making a tit
of himself. Like, it's funny to me.
>> We're both making a tit of theelves.
Money Mike's jealous because I'm going
out with Natalie. That money Mike wants
to go out go back out with Natalie. But
Money M doesn't understand.
He cannot get a woman either way because
he's a short ass c with a small [ __ ]
You know what I mean? He's got a small
dick. What woman's going to go out with
a man with a big peanut dick?
>> Do you know what I mean?
>> Yeah. Um, peeps, I definitely do not
have a peanut dick.
Definitely 100% don't.
>> Why do these people just constantly try
to call other people? It's weird as [ __ ]
>> Cuz because these people are [ __ ]
ugly as [ __ ] PJ. They rather sit there
and and put other people try and put
other people down where they are. That's it. It's
It just makes more sense than anything.
skeleton and hate and
>> but what you can be it doesn't matter if
you got money even if you're better
looking than them they hate it. >> Yeah.
>> They hate it is because you got the
balls to go out cold approaching and
these can't go out cold approaching.
They hate it. >> Yeah.
>> They hate it because they go out and go
on go and actually try. They don't like
it cuz you you go out and cry. They
don't like it at all.
>> Yeah. So they sat on YouTube sitting
there making up themselves by calling
you to [ __ ] like they do with everybody
else. One thing I'm definitely not is
not a [ __ ] pedo 100% on that. But
these people put people out as one of
them is because
>> it's to do with ugliness and hate. Yeah.
>> It doesn't matter if these people are
old and skinny because they skinny hold
men in as well. Look at John West. He's
a skinny ass little run.
>> You think you think I'm ugly, Monty?
>> I just I just look normal in it.
>> To me, you I'm a man in it. So to me,
yeah, you just look normal. You're a man
like me. I look normal to man. I'm not
I'm not going to sit there and say PJ.
Yeah, man. You sexy bastard. You know
what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> But you're not ugly. For [ __ ] sake.
You know what I mean? You're not ugly. I'm just
>> These people are ugly. Is it? These
There's a lot of other Yeah. Course.
Course. Because why are they on YouTube
for calling people? Like you said, for
calling people who they don't know. >> Yeah.
>> Trying to put other people down. You're
not putting me down.
>> They They don't put me down, Monty.
>> Maybe I'm bold people, but I love being
bold. You can sit and take piss out my
boldness. I love being bold as PG.
Being bold gets you laid.
>> I can show my face right now, bro. Look.
Yeah. Wait, let me get inside. I [ __ ]
nearly doxed myself.
I'm not doxing myself and then turn my
camera on outside.
>> I just need to go as >> Yeah. Look, look.
Oh, look. T see that. But look, I turn
my command over the camera. See, I never
do myself again.
There you go.
Oh, bless you.
>> And that's what the challenge of what
other people look like. Peeps here
with Baldhead. How you doing? Still
better looking than usual bald head. M.
And that's what the PJ
is so weird, Monty, cuz even PlayStation
was never like this. No,
>> no, they weren't it weren't for the
repeaters and it weren't for the jealous people either.
>> No, back then it was all it was all
banter back then.
>> Yeah, of course
>> it's all it was all banter but every
people get some flipping out and it >> Mhm.
>> I was the most cockiest bastard on the
Is that Is that Red Star fat and ugly as
well then? Yeah.
>> Red Star's not really jumped on me like he's on.
>> Yeah, but the same the same thing still
applies though is it if they're doing the same.
>> That's the thing though. I can't call
Red Star. I'm not like that. You know
what I mean? He's not done nothing. He
hasn't really done [ __ ] to me. He hasn't
not what I've seen. Do you know what I mean?
>> Mhm. It's mainly you.
>> I don't know the guy. I ain't
know. Yeah. Is weird. Yeah, it is weird that that
>> he's jealous cuz he's jealous cuz I'm
better looking than him and I've got a
better life than him.
>> These people can have a good life. It's
not about money what these people put at us. Life
>> money doesn't make the world go around.
Happiness does. That's what I think anyways. >> Yeah.
>> Why do you think I'm always happy sometimes?
Why do you think I've always got a smile
on my face? Never really get down. I
don't take life so serious like you people do.
>> Yeah, it's true.
>> I really don't take life so serious.
So, I don't give a [ __ ] what these
people say about me. Nothing what these
people say about me is true either way.
You know what I mean? So all of these
two it really you think about it Natalie
G has been watching me you from the
start of me being on being on YouTube. Yeah.
>> So if Natalie G Natalie G knows
everything what's going on on YouTube
with Pat mustard
with all this [ __ ] on YouTube with
me. She knows it's all fake. She knows
it's all bollocks. Why would she be with
me? Why would Natalie be with me? >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> If it was all true, she wouldn't be with
me, would you? >> Yeah.
>> There you go. So, Natalie even knows
it's all [ __ ] All this [ __ ] on me
on YouTube. Natalie's met my family. She
met my mom. She knows [ __ ] why we
moved. Actually moved out of Manchester.
Definitely not for being a Nazi either. We're pubs.
It's just weird all of this.
Yeah, they are weirdos.
Yeah, they are.
They are weirdos.
Do you know why you think to yourself?
Do you think why why these don't go out?
I do sometimes. I think that some of
these are actually on the people hunting websites theelves.
>> Probably. Yeah,
>> that's what I'm saying.
>> L own them both. L could never own me ever.
>> Peeps. LJ just sits on his panel talking
to himself about other people. That's it. >> Yeah,
>> that's it. LJ is to be yourself
reflector in this community.
Little goat calls everybody pedos when
that man sits there and puts his own kid
up on YouTube to randomize men.
>> That's a bit weird to me. >> Yeah.
and sits there and calls every [ __ ] else.
And Lord is scared of me anyway. Peace.
L is terrified of me.
>> Hey, I stopped going on Lord J's um live
because it was always the same talking, isn't it?
>> Yeah. He kept on kicking me every time I was
>> I mean I'm I'm saying the comments are
always the same.
>> Yeah. Yeah, it is. You know when you
answer a question and that
>> No, no, no. What they No. What he what
they do Yeah. What they do is Yeah. You
join the hangouts and then they shout
over you and then they put like stuff up
and then it's pointless even joining. >> Yeah.
>> That's what happened. That's why I don't join anymore.
>> No. No. You're right. You're right.
No. No. No. Rather PJ's panel. We What's the point?
So you people YouTube up.
>> What happened yesterday people?
Nobody was alive whatsoever yesterday.
Whatsoever. YouTube this community is going dead. >> Yeah.
>> You know what? Do you know what got you
know what made it dead though? It's the
repeating is it?
>> The repeating getting people affected
from the properties and stuff like that. >> Yeah.
>> Rice. I'm not Rice and Kelly. I don't
give a [ __ ] about them two either way.
But look at them too. They left YouTube.
I've left YouTube. He only jump on your
panel now and again.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Natalie's left YouTube. She only
>> is right not on back now. No,
>> right. She's at K's house. Does everybody listen?
>> Saying is he back on YouTube?
>> He's still on YouTube. They still watch.
>> Yeah. Nobody live. But no, nobody goes
live no more.
>> Yeah, it's cuz of these people, is it?
>> Nobody goes live. Yeah. Only the person
who was live yesterday was that Natalie
Bible Basher singing and that's it. And
nobody was there was she only had about
what 10 watches. 10 watches. >> Yeah.
>> Me and Natalie were watching and like
not watching. There was nobody live.
Nobody. Lo wasn't live. You wasn't live.
Yeah, nobody were
on West weren't live. Unless you went
live early on in the morning, but still
when you go off live now, that's it.
These are [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> We've only got Lord J to watch and L
ain't on 24 hours like we used to be. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? So when Lord Jane
comes off comes off and online, these are [ __ ]
>> Have nothing else to watch. Except for
music channel or old videos or repeating
videos what they've already watched
>> and that's it and that's it.
These people are complete these
communities gone and they going to what
they going to have what they going to
talk about who they going to go for now.
This is one of the best communities they
probably been in theelves like
YouTube and get a life. Well, no. It
just needs a good turn into [ __ ]
actual banter. Well, actual trolling,
not [ __ ] ruining people's lives.
>> It probably be interesting.
>> And you know when they tried to say that
your skin and your this [ __ ] it's it's
sad because it's sad to see these people
talk about themselves like that.
>> It's not talking about theelves. It's
repeating and talking about the selves.
>> Yeah. They talk about themselves. It's
bad, isn't it?
>> Yeah, of course. And this is why they
haven't got content videos.
>> But don't you think it's sad how these
people put themselves down like that?
>> Yeah. Case. Yeah. These people do it all
the time. They try and put other people down.
>> They bully themselves. They don't even
realize they actually bully themselves.
>> No. No, they do. They do. They really
do. And And they think what they said to
me is going to get at me. It's really
not. Look at me. Look at I'm not being
Have you seen that picture? What I
saying? Ben my dick's girlfriend.
>> Yeah, it's ugly, isn't it?
>> That's Ben my dick's bird.
>> She's ugly, isn't it? >> Completely.
And then you all you call meless
bastard. Not being funny. I'm not being
tight on her now. It's not her fault.
It's Ben my dick who I'm really going for.
>> You know what I mean?
>> Oh, Ben my dick. That's that um Scottish
one, is it? He's a weirdo. That's Yeah,
he used to speak to He used to speak to London Taylor.
That's these bird that that girl that I
sent you. That's these girlfriends. Yeah.
>> And if and if I'm one of these, why have
I got one of the best looking women on YouTube?
>> That's true.
>> Why have I got one of the best looking
women on YouTube? >> Yeah.
And then and then you get Ben my dick
with a [ __ ] down
don't make sense. You've all called me
to but I come up with a better bird. >> Mhm.
>> You know since after since after [ __ ]
fat way Kay
after Kay I've upgraded.
I'm I I put myself down when I was with
Kay. I was going out with gun when I was
going out with Kelly. Now I'm going out
with a [ __ ] queen.
>> Oh, bless you then. If you upgraded
upgraded, man, I've got a [ __ ]
Ferrari, not a [ __ ] Mini.
>> Oh, bless you then.
>> You know, see what I'm with. I'm with a good-looking woman, you know.
>> Yeah. what what I was with back then a
[ __ ] troll a hugely ass [ __ ]
[ __ ] But I'm glad I'm glad that these
people basically split me and Kay, but
they didn't. It was a month who done that.
>> I mean, I'm not arguing, but I'm glad
that that is over. I'm [ __ ] glad I'm with Natalie.
I'm I'm happy. So,
>> how do you know when I go on YouTube,
you get the notification, is it?
>> Well, I see you live to be honest. [Laughter]
It's funny, is it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But you Hitler
called me, you call peeves. Yeah. And
you call Natalie. But listen, peeps.
Look what you go out with. >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] man going out with a [ __ ]
completely special need.
Me and Natalie was watching one of the
videos. Sorry. What? I was just watching
like, you know, last night before I go
and sleep here, I was just watching um
GTA videos like there's some thing that
what what happens in this GTA, what
happens in that GTA. It's very
interesting, you know.
>> Oh, GTA is proper upgraded itself from
when we were younger.
>> Yeah, GTA is good, man. You never used
to like it though, ever, in it.
>> What that person said? K is what?
>> K is a psycho.
Yeah. Yeah, she is. She is. She [ __ ] Ace.
>> When are you and Natalie When are you
and Natalie going to the pub again?
>> I'm not saying [ __ ] mate.
>> Do you know?
>> No, I'm not saying nothing when we're
going to pubs and that. I'm not saying
where we're going or whatever.
>> No, not where we're going. Obviously, I
don't want to know where you're going.
>> No. No. Yeah. Yeah. Of course. Of
course. [ __ ] yeah cuz you know what?
>> That's what I'm saying. So I'm not
giving these people nothing anymore.
Like only what these people have got on
me is [ __ ] all. It's their own [ __ ]
really. And that's actually the truth.
They don't have nothing on me. Yeah.
What only what they got on me is that
[ __ ] app that's it. But that's [ __ ] either way,
you know. But that's nothing
cuz I never went on that. I tried get on
it. It wouldn't let me on it because I
was on the phone. Not actual computer.
You needed a computer to get on that app. >> Yeah.
>> So I never So I never went on the app. I
just left it on my phone. I up on
YouTube getting on it. He said that I
need a better device to get on it. I
don't know what
[ __ ] either way. Thank God. >> Yeah.
>> So I I won't even let these people
bother you anyways keys. Yeah,
>> they don't bother me. These little
mongos don't bother me. Are you mad? >> No,
they do. They bother the shelves. I want to know.
>> They're just little retards.
>> You know what think like what these
people actually want in life? What do
they want? What do they want to do
instead of sitting on YouTube doing what they do?
>> I think about that every day.
>> They have they have no goals in it.
>> Yeah. No, it's like they haven't got no goals whatsoever.
>> Yeah. And that's what I think about
every day is why they YouTube every day,
>> not going out, not making actual content videos. >> Yeah.
>> And when they do make a content video,
they going to a local shop, getting a
bottle of cider.
>> It's just weird, isn't it?
>> It is. It [ __ ] is.
Obviously, you got goals, PTJ. You do
yours by going out or approaching doing
what you're doing. Do you know what I mean?
>> I went out earlier like just to go out
and that but not to approach but you
know what I mean? Just went out like
just going for a walk and that even just
something like that. These people don't
even go for a walk. You know what I mean?
>> No. No, they don't. They don't.
They really don't.
And they sit there and call other people like
you know what I mean they call other
people for what reasons for people who
goes out and enjoy theelves people who
are happy they don't they don't they
don't they don't like it when people are
happy they bring people down onto their
level cuz these people in this community
they're not happy
>> really [ __ ] not
>> and that's the honest truth why do you
think they sign YouTube day in And they
are calling other people what these have.
>> Yeah, I know. >> Just
>> trying to call people skin, but they
don't know what people have.
>> Like you were saying to there, these
people are all on Discord talking to
each other, trolling the [ __ ] out of
each other, getting people kicked out of
the houses. But these people who are
doing this with each other, they're not
going to meet each other. Yeah.
>> So, what are they getting out of this
when they don't know anybody in this community? >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean?
YouTube's YouTube. What these do on
YouTube? It's [ __ ] bullying. It's not
even bullying. It's hate.
>> It's just hate crimes.
>> And that's what it is. It's completely hate.
>> You found it funny what happened to
Rice, is it?
>> Yeah, I found it. Of course I do. Yeah,
of course. I find it funny what happened to Felly as well.
>> It's like he will never get off YouTube
no matter what happens. He YouTube is
V's life, you know.
It's It's not looking good anyways for K
because only what this community have to
do if they want to [ __ ] K's life up is
send that video to K's neighbors of K
getting It's over.
>> It's over for her. Yeah, cuz they only
had to send that video of the mob
outside Rice's house and Kay's coming
out with Rice.
>> For Kayie,
that's all they have to do for Kayie cuz
Rice is at Kay's house.
>> Yeah, but they don't know the address.
They don't know Kay's address.
>> Yeah, they do. They know Kay's address. >> Really?
>> Yeah, they've got Kay's address. They know it.
Don't forget I was there. They used to
send [ __ ] to K's address before when I
was there. Also, no address.
You know what I mean?
>> That's mad,
you know. So
what it is, PJ. Yeah, this is what it
is. If you don't because you're a better
looking than they or whatever else like
that and you get female talking to you
or whatever else like that in this
community or whatever. They don't want
you talking to female. >> Yeah.
>> They want to talk to the female.
>> They want nonsense. Not to bring him up,
but he used to do that as well. He
stalked all my like um dates and [ __ ]
>> Yeah. And this is what most do on this
community. If you're talking to a woman,
they tell jealous about it and they got
to come up and [ __ ] it up for you. >> Yeah.
>> Or whatever else like that, they don't
like it if you're talking to a woman or
if you're in a relationship. This is why
you need to be careful when you called
the approach. You don't put you don't
put names up because if you end up in a
relationship with one of these, you're
going to [ __ ] it up or going to try and
[ __ ] it up.
>> Yeah. That's the thing, is it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Cuz you remember [ __ ]
nons he he found out that girl in
America and that. Do you remember Monty?
>> Yeah. They start texting him and they
all do it on his >> Yeah.
>> Why do they think they want Why do they
think they they they done it with me and
K splitting me and Carrie up and then I get with >> N
split me and that up and when me and
that are split up they try and ruin ruin
my life. And if not, and if anyone's in
a relationship with you, PJ, they give
you a choice to [ __ ] you off or they're
going to make her life like hell. So,
they're basically blackmailing as well. Women
>> Yeah. So, it's a blackmail game with
these people as well with women. Is it funny?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It is because
Oh, they got a name now.
Oh, they got a name.
Mel. Do you remember Mel 88?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Do you remember when all
these used to go for her and pick on her
and all that lot? >> Yeah.
>> Then then suddenly they stop picking on
her for ages. >> Yeah.
>> And then they join their side because
she's got a between his legs. It doesn't
matter what the woman look like in this community. Believe
>> Yeah. Even if it's poss for [ __ ] sake.
>> You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. I get you.
>> No can get a picture or someone naked in
this community. They they're doing that
[ __ ] They want to go out and meet a
woman in this community. >> Yeah.
>> Not like me, not like myself and not
like Rice or or whatever. Obviously Rice
won't leave his front door. So that must
obviously kill it. >> Yeah.
>> But they won't go out and do that.
Do you know what I mean?
>> Yeah. They want these people in this
community can't do that. >> Yeah.
>> They can't go out and meet anyone.
>> And they're also skint as well. So they
can't even afford to go on a date.
>> It's not about being skin. If you be
going on dates, it's go it's not about
money. You still can go on a date
without having no money. You can just go
to [ __ ] go have a picnic.
>> So then why are they so okay then? If
they know that then why do they go
online and calling people skint when
they don't know them?
>> Because with some money like these
people these people are offset is a
gambling community. So the obsess with
money they spend their money on alcohol weed
[ __ ] they go gambling spending money
in gambling and they talk about people
being skinn because they spent all their
money on whatever else. You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. I'm not a [ __ ] skin peeps.
Yeah. In 3 years time, I got to have my
own house. In 3 years, in 3 years time,
I got to actually save my money up by 3
years. I could have about 30 grand in 3
years and get my own [ __ ] property. >> Yeah.
>> Just think about it. I only need one
money to live off, not my disability. I
can just put my full 790
for one side. Yeah. Block that off to
one side. Yeah. My 100 I mean my 790 to
Keep doing that every month with the 700
and whatever else every month by 3
years. Yeah. I have at least about 30
million 30,000 in my bank with all that
safe. But yeah.
>> Yeah. But yeah, but you can't you can't
live off 700 a month.
>> I can if I put my mind to it. It's keep
weed and everything else in it.
>> Yeah. If I if I if I stopped all that
then then I could I could do it.
>> You know what I mean? I could leave all
[ __ ] my normal money and put like£100
away then £30,000. >> Yeah,
>> that's what I could do. I can actually
go out and pay for my own house. I can do that.
>> But I because I've already been told I
do come out with more money and an
average working person.
>> And I'm good with that. And I'm good
with that. Do you know what I mean? If
I'm coming out with with more money and
a work more money and a average person's
coming out with
>> I can get my own house in three years time.
>> Still be sat on YouTube in a houses.
I might do that. 3 years. It's not long.
3 years I could live in my own property.
I have my own house. Not a council. I
know. I'll be laughing at these little
clowns then, won't I? >> Yeah.
>> And that's what they don't think about.
I'm not a sly skin is I spend my money stupidly. >> Yeah.
>> And this is what these don't think
about. These are the skinniest [ __ ] on YouTube.
>> It's funny, is it?
>> Yeah. I come out with more money than
the average working person does.
I'm a So I'm actually richer than a
[ __ ] wicked person.
>> That's good, isn't it?
>> It's [ __ ] funny.
And they cut me skin.
>> And And there's an account on here,
Monty. Yeah. And he calls me poor. I'm
not poor. I'm like medium.
>> Medium. Yeah, I'm I'm probably medium.
Don't know. But I come out with more
body than a wing person does. Anyway,
>> why why are they trying to call me poor?
>> I I don't know.
>> [ __ ] knows, bro. I don't give a [ __ ]
what these people think. What people
saying cuz by 3 years that could off your property.
>> You can't live on 700.
>> Think about it. It's not exactly RPJ if
you if you haven't got no hobbies.
>> You know,
>> just think about it. If you don't have
no hobbies. Yeah. Meaning you don't
drink, you quit smoking, you don't have
any of that. Yeah. Only what you've been
paying for is your rent and then your
food in your fridge. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> And freeze it. That can come out of your normal money.
>> Easy for the month.
>> Easy for the normal money. your
disability the full 700.
>> Yeah. You just put in the bank and you
just keep saving that up. You just keep
saving your disability money up. You can
live off 700 a month. It's you just got
to make that stretch. You don't treat
yourself as much. You cut down on [ __ ] completely. >> Yeah.
>> You don't go out as much. Don't don't
get as much clothes. If you're going to
get clothes, get cheap clothes.
I've been thinking about it. These old brand clothes.
Yeah. It's only a tag you're paying for
the name. The name you go to Primark,
it's just the same [ __ ] you're putting on.
>> You know what I mean?
>> So say say you go out drinking, how much
do you think you would spend that 100?
150 in it?
>> Exactly. Yeah. Exactly.
>> So how much? 150 or 200 or 100?
>> It depends. It depends. It it depends
who you're out with and how long you're out for
>> and what if you was by if you was by
yourself all night.
>> It depends if you're a lightweight or
not a lightweight but it depends on it really.
>> Some clubs can not let you in for being over pissed.
So it all depends as well. So it's not
how much he was out until like 7 in the morning.
Yeah. And then obviously you're going to
need about 150 160 at least. >> Yeah.
>> You know, but it also it also depends
when you start drinking. What time you
start drinking from? >> Yeah.
>> You know what I means? So if you go out
a lot what between what 7:00 Yeah. then
Yeah. Probably you need what 160 170.
Yeah. But if you go out between 10 to
10:00 and then you probably need what 120 130
>> but then you obviously get a takeaway in
that. So maybe 200.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Most probably.
>> Yeah. 200.
That's what I'm saying. Cuz you that
just stretch you that money what you've had. >> Yeah.
You know what I mean? And it's what I'm saying. Like
I don't know [ __ ] about money and
finances and [ __ ] like that. I didn't
even know if I save up for 3 years have
30 grand that's more will ever have in 3 years. >> Yeah.
>> Obviously 3 years is a long time but
it's also not a long time. He's really not.
>> But also, I've got kids to pay for. So,
that's going to be a lot harder for me
to save up anyways cuz it's my
daughter's birthday coming up and I got
to get her [ __ ] birthday presents and
Christmas presents and that. So, I've
got to do all that now.
You know what I mean? So, that's a lot
harder for me to cuz I give my kids 20
pound a month every time I get paid. So
my kids do get expense off me and that
and get money basically every month.
>> But I went Birmingham drinking. Me and
you. I think I spent about 200. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So yeah. No, something like
that. 100 and something anyway. Some being
about likeund and something. But we
still a good night.
>> Yeah, it was good. It was good night out on it.
>> Yeah, we stayed in that one p all night
though. So we didn't get cuz we knew we
won't get any more pubs.
>> It's still good though. It
>> Yeah, cuz you're not in one pub.
>> What you need to find PJ are the slag pubs.
>> The slag pubs. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, I know one. There's an Irish one.
>> Yeah, that's what you need to go to the
proper slag ass pubs.
the fish slate where you go to, you know
what I mean? >> Yeah.
Yeah. In London, it's like it's £7.75 a
pint of Guinness, which is a lot, is it?
>> Yeah. But you get paid more down London
because of the cost of living in London.
>> What benefits you don't?
How most benefits you come out with? No, 1100.
>> 1,100. Yeah, I come out with like just 700.
>> That but that's not my disability.
That's my [ __ ] EWP or whatever. Pay what? What?
>> That's just normal money. I come up with like 700
because I don't pay rent. I don't have
nothing to worry about. I don't pay
rent, do I? So >> yeah,
>> what I pay a month is what? 80 quid a month.
>> And that's what that's [ __ ] finger.
That's it. 8 quid a month. That's what I pay.
I don't pay council tax or nothing. I
don't pay anything like these people
would do or whatever. I don't pay
anything like that.
I only pay one thing and that's my service charge.
But that's a lot though, is it? 775 a
pint, isn't it? Yeah.
It is a lot. Is
[ __ ] Yeah. Well, me in this place, it
can save me money.
>> If you if you if you was drinking pints
of Monty. Yeah. 7. And it was £7. So 70
will get you pissed, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I I don't think so. I really I'm
not really want to talk about this with PJ. >> Yeah.
>> You know, £10 can just get you pissed.
I'll take just go out and get yourself a
bottle of [ __ ] FA, big bottle of
Coke, get yourself [ __ ] pissed.
Saving yourself money there. Go down to
the pub after when you've had that.
Clubs have already pissed out drinking
there. Saving yourself a little bit of money.
>> That's what most most people do to that,
especially in London. Yeah, they do
because it's expensive. You get before
they go out.
>> Yeah. Or even if you There's a place,
right? There's a place that was happy
hour and it's like £250 a drink and it's
like really strong. So obviously if you
have a few you can get pissed with like
£10, it spend£10 you get pissed.
>> Happy hour is every hour or not every hour?
>> No, it's until 8:00. But obviously
you'll be pissed.
>> Yeah, that's crossing time. So if you
get p So you could probably get pissed
with like 30 pound.
>> Yeah. Yeah. They did that in Birmingham, didn't they?
>> Where they did discounts of shops and
get a drink. Get one drink and you get shots. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. We had shots and everything. PG.
>> Remember when the lad bumped into me
drink by accident?
>> Yeah. Do you remember when you German
when you spilled drink all over me? You [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> It was accident, was it? >> No.
>> No. You don't know.
>> It was the accident, man. I didn't. It
was the glass me grabbing it.
Don't forget the [ __ ] climsy [ __ ]
plastic glasses. They were
>> Yeah. And a lot of a lot of a lot of the
drinks was watered down as well. >> Yeah.
>> Did you do you
>> that's when was it?
>> Yeah. The rum was not the beer, but the rum was.
>> What? No, I didn't notice that.
>> Yeah, I definitely did.
>> I did like water in rub. I thought it
would have just to the top.
>> No, the water down.
>> That's [ __ ] That that's taken away. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Is that the last time you drunk when you
was with me? Yeah.
>> Yeah. No. No. Last time I drunk you with Natalie.
>> Oh, bless you.
>> Me and Natalie had a drink last night.
Oh, bless you. But we didn't go live cuz
me and Nia are done with YouTube.
Obviously, she makes her videos a
cooking video still and that but cuz that's content,
you know, cooking
>> hook up with a
Can't you hook PJ up with a homeless
girl, won't he? No, he can't.
>> PJ can do all that himself. Yeah,
>> I've already I've already I've already
tried hooking him up with someone where
she's added him,
>> but I don't know when she be going
online with a homeless girl. She's homeless.
>> Yeah, she added, man.
Is she pretty fit? Monty,
>> not my place to say, PJ, I'm in a
relationship, so I'm not I'm not looking
at another woman. I don't tell you
nothing about another woman like that.
>> Britney rejected him, Monty. Who who who
rejected me? Britney rejected me. Huh?
>> Is it Britney's never protected PJ? Cuz
PJ's never asked Britney out or
Britney's never asked PJ out.
Not what I know of anyways.
>> No, I don't even I didn't even know her.
>> Why can't the only the only how I knew
about her is [ __ ] when nonsense kept
going on about her every time I met him.
That's how I knew about her.
>> Why can't you people just have normal
conversations and start just being
normal and that like literally
>> she rejected the open virgin. Yeah,
everyone knows that.
>> Yeah, everyone knows that.
>> She rejected Sha Long Legs.
>> No, no, no, no, peeps, you got it all
wrong. She didn't reject Shauny
Longlegs. She actually went out with Sha
Long Legs for [ __ ] years. years. >> Yeah.
>> The name split up. Yeah.
>> And then they come off sensible.
>> But she never she never [ __ ] him or
>> No. No. Obviously not. Obviously not
because it's online. Sean's immedi.
Yeah. Realistic PJ. Yeah. Sean's not
really been out with her yet because
he's never met her. He only knew her
online. And you can't say you're in a
relationship with someone. This is what
I get with people online.
Yeah, you can say you're going out with
someone, but that's the online relationship.
>> No, she reject she rejected him like
this, right? Because he wanted to go to
Canada and see her and she cut contact
with him and didn't want him. So, she
did reject him in a way if you think about it.
>> Yeah, of course. Of course. Because of the
>> they would have met, you know. Yeah.
because of the air gap and it's not that
she wanted to move to Canada and she
>> he wouldn't have been able to he
wouldn't have been able to do that cuz
he's skin and he's scared of flying as well.
>> Yeah. Either way you need a visa and a
good reason to live over there and if he
moved over there to Canada what would
he's been reasoning to the government he
would have been arrested on his boat to St. D. [Music]
So he weren't thinking on that one. And
then there's another reason, a dad.
Britney's dad would have killed him. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? Britney's dad
would have ripped his head off because
Britney isn't too young.
>> Yeah. He always used to go on and on and
on about her.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I know.
>> Weird. It was so weird, bro.
And then they call me to [ __ ]
Mitchell and me and Emma Mitch's never
[ __ ] happened. I know my M. Of course
I do. I know.
>> Yeah, sausage. I've not Yeah, sausage.
I've not gambled since the football.
>> Yeah. Why do you Why What made you come
in this community anyway? Was it Timmy
who got you on on this?
>> Yeah, it was Timmy Aldridge.
>> Okay, now
Yeah, that that plunker.
>> Why didn't you tell me what this
community were like for Pedia before he
actually joined it?
>> I did.
>> You didn't? You [ __ ] didn't. Only
what you said to me is he don't want to
argue with someone called Timmy on [ __ ] WhatsApp.
>> That's it.
>> Hi, Nicola. I was speaking to LT on the
phone yesterday. We I was talking about you.
>> Yeah, it was funny. Yeah, cuz it was funny, Monty.
>> Yeah, Nicholas a girl
>> because this cuz this community is
funny, isn't it?
>> Yeah, PJ Nicola is a girl, you know.
>> think of the name, man. Come on, Nicola.
Why would a [ __ ] girl's name?
>> So, yeah. No. Um, that's how it is.
>> Is Nicola Gay or Ray? I'm just I'm just
asking cuz it's just that name. I'm not
starting or trolling. I'm just curious
about the name. Nicola.
>> No, not there. You know
>> you know LT Nicolola. Nicolo. Yeah. He
still doesn't think that USA is he done
anything wrong when she did. She said,
"Oh, she didn't do anything wrong." I
said, "Well, she [ __ ] well did.
Oh, you prick PJ. Huh?
>> You was calling. It's Nicolo. You were Yeah,
>> it's Nicolola.
>> Nicolo. Okay. Right.
Wait. It still sounds like a girl's
name. Look. Nicolo.
>> So, how old is Britney now? She's a year
younger than me, ain't it? I remember that.
She's probably a year younger than you.
Two year younger than you. Probably in
the 20s or probably about 19. No, this
is probably in the 20s. Early 20s, I said. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I say about in the 20s.
Yeah. She is. Yeah.
She's not your age. Obviously not.
>> I I I just think he needs to get laid.
>> Who knows?
Nons legs. End the story, bro.
>> No, no, no, no. I don't want him to get
laid. I want him to be a little virgin
all day long. He's like his daddy. A little [ __ ] pedo. >> Yep.
>> Macy's dad's still alive, tell you the
truth. Maybe he is.
>> Oh, when his dad dies, I'm throwing a
party. I'm throwing a big party, bro.
Yeah. Everyone's any Everyone on you
YouTube's welcome. I'm going to buy the
most expensive bottle of champagne.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. I'm throwing a party, mate. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Me and Natalie will turn up then.
>> Cuz he likes to make fun out of the
people's dead relatives. So when as soon
as his dad dies, he might already be
dead to be honest. He might just what I
mean about his community when he wish
people cancer and all that.
>> You know what? It'd be funny. Yeah.
Because money might cause cancer on my
mom now. Yeah. It'd be funny now if his
mom caught it straight up now on
someone. It'd be funny as [ __ ]
You know what I mean? You don't risk
cancer on anybody or wish anyone
wouldn't do that to my worst enemy in
you know you know the voice chat. Yeah.
You met nons legs in. Yeah. Who else was
in it like the very first time?
>> Uh I can't really remember.
>> I have bomb. No not bomb. Um who's his name?
Who did I meet? >> Bean.
>> Bean. Yeah. Grin gr
whatever he's a couch was. >> Yeah.
>> The Grinch. No. No. What that one who
didn't like Christmas? Who's his name? >> Grinch.
>> No. The one who hated Christmas and the
three ghosts come to him.
>> The Grinch.
>> No. The three ghosts come to him. Not the Grinch.
>> I don't [ __ ] know.
>> The [ __ ] free ghost. The [ __ ] free
Holy Spirit ghost come to him cuz he
hated Christmas. He didn't like
>> The only person I know that didn't like
Christmas was the Grinch.
>> And the grudge. It was
>> Yeah. It don't matter anyways. Yeah. But
his channel were called that. It was him Dean. Yeah.
Dean got me. Do you know any log legs in
it? I don't know.
>> It's just a weird community, bro.
>> Yeah. Yes, it is.
>> Yeah. Dean
[ __ ] [ __ ] He was so ugly, man.
>> There's lots of ugly people on
PlayStation. There's lots of ugly people
in this community. >> Yeah,
>> but I can't. Yeah, that's not my fault.
The way these people look. That's the
mom and dad's fault. Not mine. >> Yeah.
>> So, I don't know why they're coming out on me. >> Yeah.
>> It's not my fault if they're ugly. The
mom shouldn't [ __ ] set with a [ __ ] ugly man.
>> Well, saying that, right? Too ugly is
supposed to make a cute baby, they say.
>> Yeah. Yeah, they do. They do. They say
too ugly. So, their mom must have been
[ __ ] sexy or something. These mons
must have been a mil.
>> I swear they must have been molled.
>> I don't know where Tim is. Timmy,
>> I don't to be honest with you people. I
don't give two shits about money and
Mark and Timmy. Yeah, I let them make
fools of theelf on YouTube by shouting
me out all the time. If they want me,
they know where I live. Anyways,
>> do you know what money? I'm surprised
you never ever went to Amsterdam.
>> Yeah. I'm surprised you never ever went.
>> I want to go. In fact, no one no one
with Natalie. I might actually go Amsterdam
>> cuz obviously you like weed in it. So I'm surprised.
>> I might do that then. Is it? Give my passport.
>> Yeah, it's expensive though.
>> Well, would you go and stood on Pia?
>> I've already been.
>> Yeah. You went to all the broles. You
didn't you funny bastard.
>> Do you do you remember when I went?
Yeah, but you you went to the brothel as
well as how I went to the brothel. How
do you know? >> Huh?
>> Oh, yeah. No,
>> you miss me out the brothel.
>> Yeah, but do you remember when I was
there? Do you remember? >> Yeah.
>> No, no, I didn't watch the videos. I
know. No, I don't actually because I
didn't watch it. But obviously I know
you would have gone to the bro.
>> Of course I did. I [ __ ] two of them.
Do you go to the [ __ ] strip clubs in the UK?
>> I've been to them twice. Yeah. Only >> Yeah.
>> See what's like. Have you?
>> Yeah. It's nothing. No, but it's nothing
like um over there. >> Yeah.
>> It's more shut off
over in the UK. Yeah. When I went
Amsterdam, the whole thing cost me like
£800 with spending money. 8 900. How
much did what did you get for the
prostitute there? The window shopping.
What did you get from them?
>> From the window. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. What did
>> Yeah, of course. Course. But what did
you get off of?
>> What do you mean? Oh, like it.
>> What was it? Sex or a blow job?
>> Oh, sex. No, I was into more sex then.
So sex. Yeah.
>> What? You like your [ __ ] Do you PJ?
I should have asked you for one when I
was in Birmingham, man. You should have
gave me one. >> You >> huh?
>> I don't swing that way, PJ.
>> Yeah. You remember when I pissed in the
You remember that, Stephen? How would
you pissed in the river when I was in Amsterdam?
>> Did you? >> Yeah.
>> So, PJ has pisses going through the
river, but I be at the sea now.
Yeah, I see. I'll be gone.
So, well, you going to go Amsterdam? Yeah.
>> No, because looking at the river would
just remind me of you pissing in it now, won't it?
>> Yeah, that's going to be
>> I want you to give me a [ __ ] in the
alleyway like that American woman did. Money. >> What?
Monty, I really want you, but I don't
think you want me.
>> I don't want you, PJ. Do PJ, come on, man.
>> That's what she said to me, but I don't
think you want me.
>> Yeah. Why? Why didn't you go down on her?
>> No, I just fingered her.
>> Why? Why? Why?
>> What you mean? >> Why?
>> Why would you just finger a woman, PJ?
Cuz I don't disgusting.
>> Is it? Look, look. If she If she's going
to go down on you, at least you can
[ __ ] [ __ ] please her and go down on her.
>> It's weird, is it?
>> No, it's not weird going down on
someone. Is it? [ __ ] How is it weird?
>> What is it?
>> They just posted a new video on GTA.
Yeah, I just refreshed the page and it
come up. Is that funny?
>> What come up?
>> Like a new video they put up. >> Okay.
>> You see what I mean? I like that. Tell
what it's like to do GTA and [ __ ]
>> Yeah. I'm I'm getting my PlayStation.
I'm going to get a new PlayStation and all that.
>> Yeah, we can play GTA 6 together when it
comes out if you are.
>> I'm not playing GTA 6 with nobody on
YouTube. I'm not even going live anymore
on my PlayStation. I'm not even going
back as SGT a lot anymore.
I'm keep I'm not going back as me old
again cuz they find me.
I've still got that account PD from
years and years ago, you know, PlayStation,
>> but I don't go on it no more. Well, I I
can I still know the password.
>> You doing any football bets on Saturday?
Um, how would Pip King?
>> Yeah, but I'm on it. You should try to
get into gaming again. >> No,
>> I love I love GTA 5. I like Franklin.
>> No, I'm not getting into G. He's boring
game with DJ.
I'm playing Black Ops 2 right now. But yeah,
>> Mr. Bean, I'm one sec. Mr. Bean. Yeah,
you can sit there and call everyone, but
you supposed to have money. Yeah,
>> but you like every day, Mr. Bean.
>> Yeah, probably. But I don't know. Yeah,
>> Mr. Bean's got money a DJ. Yeah.
>> So why is Mr. Bean sat on YouTube every day?
>> Cuz you know I lost all his money.
>> He had lost his money. It's just [ __ ]
weird that he's got money but it's on YouTube. >> Yeah.
>> He could actually go out
and go go and get pissed. Actually get laid.
>> So he said I can't go out and get pissed.
>> Well the thing I don't know what Mr. B
look like. All these ugly bastards on
YouTube put fake voices on. So [ __ ]
knows if we can get laid. >> What?
>> Are you trying to say I can't go out and
get pissed Monty?
>> No, you can't.
>> So why do you say why do you say he can?
Like I can't.
>> I'm just saying that he's got the money
to do that. So he can do that.
>> That's what I'm saying.
>> But he heard like compared to like these
people in it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Cuz he's got he's show
money. He's shown a lot of money. You
know what I mean?
But that's what I mean. He's your money,
but he's still sat on YouTube when he
actually can go on. The reason he's if
you look at it this way, even if you got
money, you're still not [ __ ] happy.
Look at Mr. Bean. >> Yeah.
>> So, it doesn't matter if you got money
or not. Money doesn't make you happy.
>> I can go out drinking every week if I want money.
I'm not trolling PJ. I'm not trolling
>> Yeah, but money I could go out jumping
every week if I wanted.
>> Yeah, I know. You You go out anyways, so
you don't have to prove nothing to me or anything.
>> No, he's not a clown. I like Monty's
Monty's not a clown. Monty's cool.
>> Yeah, to clown on YouTube. Let him do
that. Call me clown.
>> No, he No, he didn't call me skin.
>> I didn't call skin.
>> You know who I said that Mr. Bean's got
money. That Mr. Bean can go out. I was
even talking about PJ.
[ __ ] sake, man. I think PJ is skinn
sometimes. And I'm skint sometimes. I
think everybody get skint sometimes.
>> I'm never skin.
Yeah, load of money. I don't have loads
and loads of money, but I'm never skin.
>> No, no, course I'm never skin. I'm just
saying matter of fact is that people do get skin.
>> But either way, even when you skin,
you're still not skin.
If you need if you got everything you
need in life, if you got skin,
if you got food in your fridge,
you know, if you got
>> I spent I spent £300 on [ __ ] Sunday.
these. What is it with this community
anyway? Is it getting me on that [ __ ] now?
>> That's right. >> Yeah.
>> How can I be sc
by 3 years I could have my own house in
three years time if I save up the money.
You know what I mean?
>> About they're saying about you um
smashing the piggy bank for Fiverr.
Oh yeah, they said it's repeating. I
don't want to know to be honest with you.
You know what I mean? That's only what
they can do is repeat
and that's only what these will do is
repeat. See like gone from that to
say that I needed that for something to
back even though it were all
I don't have to sit here and explain to
myself about that. You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. All good ma'am.
All good. Always good. Is it
>> you are
bad who can't leave his house with dogs for what?
>> Did you actually do that all day
chatting [ __ ] money?
>> What? Did you actually smash the piggy
bank for five or they just talking [ __ ]
>> No. [ __ ] told me to go [ __ ] go
that we need a Fiverr
that is a fingers.
Can I go and get it?
>> Look at this comment. Yeah, he's like
you went all the way to Birmingham to
see him PJ and all he did was cry about his ex.
Obviously, because me and Natalie
[ __ ] appreciated PJ being there, but
it's not my fault that me and Natalie
just [ __ ] broke up and
you know, it weren't my fault and PJ was
there for me. And I appreciate PJ for
being there for me. And obviously,
obviously, I didn't really want to go
out cold approaching like PJ did.
Obviously, I didn't mind PJ going out
approaching, but that's different, you know. >> Yeah.
>> Okay. Now, I already had me eye on one
woman and one woman only people, and that's Natalie.
>> That's why we're talking about
>> She said, he said, "Yeah, but you didn't
enjoy PJ's company. You just cried about
it all night. How was that fair on PJ?"
>> Of course, you enjoy PJ's company.
Didn't I enjoy your company? And did I
was I crying about it all night?
Not all night. Not all night. Only when
we went live.
>> Only when we went live. That was only
the time we started crying about Natalie.
>> When we was off live, I didn't say
nothing about Natalie. Not really. Anyways, it's
>> [ __ ] weird, isn't it? This community, man.
>> It is. Anyways people, so
no, I'm not even saying [ __ ] At least
I'm with Natalie. Even though she has
done some crazy [ __ ] on YouTube, I'm not
bing no one for that.
>> What about the girl Jamie was speaking
to? Jamie wasn't speaking to a girl.
>> I was only speaking to one girl. Well,
yeah, one girl really, and that was me
and PJ. when me and PJ was walking down
the street with them two girls and
that's it. But it weren't like
>> good in it. It was good fun. >> Yeah,
>> I enjoyed it. Me. Did you?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, we were. It were good.
>> They was [ __ ] not my age. They were too young.
>> She stole my hat. I had to take it back off her.
>> Yeah, I know. I know she did. Try
getting mine for me being bold. I told
you to get yours.
>> Cute little hat in it. >> Yeah.
>> Self-reflected in this community completely.
>> You You must m You must have thought I
was mad doing them approaches doing them
approaches. Isn't it?
>> No. Yeah, of course. I'm not being funny
with other you people in this community,
but how many people have tried getting with Natalie?
>> I'm just saying a lot of people try
getting with Natalie.
>> Know what I mean? And yes, and they
don't like it. So if I was ugly like you
people, I won't be with Natalie.
>> It's all right. If Natalie thought I was
one of them, she won't be with me, will
she? She being in this community from
the beginning. Natalie is one of the
only people on here I've not actually met.
>> I don't think so to me to be honest with
you. I don't know.
But you know what I mean? I think I've
met loads of people. You, Toasty, Mike,
Tiger, Unworthy Clock, Timmy, [ __ ]
LJ, you name it.
No, Natalie never tried again with me.
No, not Natalie.
N played P not not playing him but
tried to get PJ to meet her but N
weren't going to show up.
>> Yeah. So she's a prick then. That's what
I was saying to her earlier.
>> I should I should kick her in the [ __ ] for that. >> No.
Okay. She didn't She's ugly. >> What?
>> She's ugly. She's nice. Natalie,
>> she was But she was going to stand me
up. That's not nice.
>> Yeah. Come on, PJ.
If I was a woman, I wouldn't even
[ __ ] meet you.
>> No, but she was she was getting me to go
all the way there and then she weren't
going to meet me.
>> Yeah, I would have probably done the
same. But you you never done the same though.
>> Yeah, I know I didn't mind. But if I was
a woman, I probably would have done the
same to be honest.
>> So I'm going to have to kick her in the [ __ ]
>> This is why a woman won't make you cuz
you want to kick him in custo. Yeah.
Natalie just said you were ugly and know she never
um Yeah. Ghosting listen. Yeah. Why why
is it as soon as you you have a
different opinion on women that people
call you an incel? Like if you don't s
they call you an incel when I would
actually technically be a misogynist not
an incel but they call me an incel like
[ __ ] bro. Anyway PJ these should
actually praise this community because
if this went to another community Yeah.
he would actually talk to him in the
background and just get kicked.
>> Yeah. You know what I mean?
>> So why don't they appreciate us either
way? Cuz we give them a platform to talk
or not really a platform up here but we
let them right. We let them say what
they want to say but they don't you know
we answer them and [ __ ] like that or
>> there's so many simps ghosting isn't it?
I went out on Sunday. Yeah I spent about
like 250. I just fancy going out
drinking on a Sunday. Got some numbers
didn't really go anywhere but it's just
it's it's so expensive just going out
now. ghosting, you know, even for a
drink. It's expensive as [ __ ] bro.
Lucky I won on the football on Tuesday.
I won a football Tuesday, luckily.
>> No, she's not better than USA, is he? No
way. Is Natalie better than USA? Is he?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I think she is. Natalie,
I'm happy to be to be honest with you.
Yeah. people. I've always like Natalie.
I've always had a thing for Natalie.
Even when I was calling Natalie to put
back on YouTube ages and ages ago when I
were calling Natalie, I had a thing for
Natalie. Oh, is that?
>> Yeah. It's expensive um drinking,
ghosting, is it? Um no, she's not better
than USA is he
USA is my mama. Monty,
why don't you meet us here then?
I already have. She's my mama.
>> Yeah. Why don't you meet her again then?
>> Cuz my mommy abandoned me.
>> Well, I [ __ ] abandoned you, too. All
the [ __ ] you bring to her. >> What?
>> All this [ __ ] you bring to your mom.
>> What do you mean?
>> With YouTube.
>> It's funny, isn't it?
>> No, because supposed to put your life up.
This stuff [ __ ] my life up. Of
>> course it has. If your mommy spot you if
[ __ ] your mom sp you off. It's
YouTube watch done that if you really
really think about it.
>> I can't get attached anymore cuz I
already found my mama.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying. So that's
what I'm saying. If your mom's watch
think he is he lost his kids because of
YouTube. What's he on about? I can't
cope with him. Exactly. Over YouTube.
Nothing else. Over YouTube.
>> I'm reading out comments that like are
not I'm reading out comments that are
not actually trying to start [ __ ]
between us and that. I know which ones
comments obviously not
>> I know which ones to read, you know.
>> You just answered your question yourself
over YouTube or the people on YouTube.
>> So yeah, YouTube basically. So basically
YouTube had to ruin your life, isn't it?
>> Yeah, of course it has. rotating accent,
but that's partly my
>> I'm being none of you, but
>> yeah, when when Pat mustard when Pat
Mustard went round with pictures of LA
and that, you know what I mean?
>> You should have just got off of it.
>> Yeah, but I couldn't because these
pictures what were going around, it were
pissing me off back then. Do you know
what I mean?
>> All these people saying [ __ ] about my
kids every day.
>> Yeah. Then me after then I'm saying [ __ ]
about these people's kids got me
reflecting back to these
madness. It's mad.
>> You know what I mean? And then I'm
saying because more more [ __ ] is being
said about my kids and it's me I [ __ ]
off and then
that's what they bring then they send
letters to my neighbors and saying that
they done the same thing to me as well.
You know what I mean? It's [ __ ] up.
And that's how it's all started.
This all [ __ ] [ __ ]
This is how it all started. Me being
called a n cuz about because of these
little clowns putting pictures up of
children and me [ __ ] sticking up for
it. Jamie got the same letters as I did.
They done the same thing to me where
they wrote like we was I was a nonsense
[ __ ] So they send it all to my mom's
neighbors. They done the same thing with Monty.
>> They done it first to me. I was the
first person. They done it to
>> They done it They done it to Monty
first, which is strange. You would have
thought they would have done it to me
first, but they done it to Jamie first
and then they done it to me.
>> Yeah. I had the same thing as you, bro.
It was [ __ ] hanging, isn't it?
>> Yeah. But they done it years after
they've done it to me. >> Yeah.
>> Not month after year, a couple of years
after they done it for you. Rice.
>> Yeah. Madness.
>> Fell just got himself kicked out.
So why? Wait, hold on a minute. So Rice
is never allowed to go back there ever again.
>> No, Rice, like I said to you, Rice is
now at Kay's house. He's living at K's
house. He ain't got nowhere else to go.
Why the [ __ ] is Rice going to be in a
[ __ ] Just think about it? Yeah. You
only get him safe out. Yeah, if you're
going to call Hey, Monty. Yeah. Um,
London Taylor wrote a comment. He said,
"Loing kids and having Squidward pump
the mother of your kids because of
YouTube is diabolical. That would mess
up my brain." By Squidward, he means rice. That one
rice will be never never go near my
children. So, I don't give a [ __ ] who
Kelly shaggy. My kids are not living
with Kayie. So,
my kids are living with my mom. So I
don't have to go through Kayie or talk
to Kay or have nothing to do with Kayie
through that. So I don't have to go
through Kelly or talk to Kayie. Kay is
not my concern. It's not my business.
It's not really
Listen, man. I don't know how you still
[ __ ] come on the phone to me and you
still [ __ ] defend that USA is bro.
You got a screw loose, bro. I swear to
God you got a [ __ ] screw loose.
>> He's destiny with that. [ __ ] girl.
>> You know what I'm saying?
>> You're actually [ __ ] bro.
>> That That's what That was years and
years ago as well.
>> Yeah, but he brought it up on the phone.
>> That's [ __ ] weird. I'll be honest with you. >> Huh?
>> Why would you bring something out from
years and years ago? It's the same as
that author is who you met. Yeah, that
was [ __ ] that was donkeys years ago.
>> Exactly. You know, why do they do that? Like >> Yeah.
You know, understand with me and Kelly.
Yeah. Because that's [ __ ] basically
new with Rice and all that [ __ ] But
believe me, peeps, I'm with Natalie.
Yeah. I'm happy with that. Natalie is my
family. I'm going to get I'm going to
probably marry N. I'm just saying in a
future time probably going to get
married to her. Okay, but it does
happen. It happens. Then Natalie will be
>> Listen, I didn't lie. I didn't lie about
anything. But you was trying to lie
saying that she didn't go to the police
when she did go to the police cuz her
friend told me she went to the police.
You know, stop acting like she's this
person. Bro, listen listen. She's not
She goes around [ __ ] with people. She
meets her match and she plays victim,
bro. What's that? That's all there is to it.
>> You know, I don't understand what So,
you know, it is what it is,
>> right? Okay. And what did I say? I was
going to beat I never said I was going
to beat up everyone, bro. Well, because
I'm not scared of them. Like, come on, man.
I had to like That [ __ ] didn't go
running to the police scared. Please,
bro. Come on. It's It's insane now.
>> He ran to the police.
>> Nothing. It's fine.
>> The mercy or the British?
>> It doesn't matter. I don't know why this
LT brings it up.
Because he's a weasel. He's a [ __ ]
weasel. That's why he brings it all cuz
he's [ __ ] This is what I mean. He He
obviously fancies his American is
himself. This is why he brings it all
up. He obviously does.
>> Yeah. I said go message her. Go have
her, bro. What the [ __ ] Like we
>> Yeah, I ain't got nothing to do with
you. That's between them two, not you. >> Yeah,
>> that's over with between you and her. So
why does she need to bring someone who's
over with you? He's got a thing for you.
He needs a [ __ ] to worry about it. Not you.
>> I I'll give you I'll give you a number
if you want, bro. Like I got a number
here if you want it. You know what I mean?
>> Give it
up for him. Give it. >> Yeah.
>> And then he's not going on about it for
you. Give it.
>> I don't have so much I don't have so
much mouth online at all, bro. What are
you talking about? I've got mouth. I
don't have mouthful. I've backed up a
lot of the [ __ ] I've said. You want to
talk about that prime as well? Yeah, I
called that prime out when I was in
Birmingham last month and he was
starting saying how he was going to come
here and he was going to do that and the
[ __ ] didn't even come out. I've backed
up a lot of my mouth. I backed up a lot
of what I've said, bro. I don't know
about Monty, but I I backed up my talk.
>> I backed up my talk. You've seen me back
up my talks
with these people.
How many times have I backed up my talk
by going out with these people all the
time to go and meet them or showing [ __ ]
to these people or you you people like
to forget [ __ ]
>> You know what I'm saying, bro? So yeah,
>> I've shown these people money, shown
these people what what I can and can't
get. I've shown these people that I can
go out and meet these clowns. I've done that.
>> These only want to know why am I still
under this community?
Do do these people really want to know
why I'm still in this community? I'm
waiting till these people do the outside
of a map.
>> And that's what I'm actually waiting for.
I'm waiting until these cars actually
dock outside most of them. It's not
going to be the police knocking on these
doors. I'm going to be knocking on these
Yeah. He's going to be getting real.
He's not going to be getting caught up
in that. This shit's going to get real.
So when these people start dogsing
themselves, it's going to get real
like I'm going back to pretty soon. Not to mention
just like when I show you money, you
will run away. Just like I go go to
places and you don't show up, you know,
at the end of the day, bro, like you've
been shown money. You've been I've tried
meeting you people, you know, but you
don't get no credit on here. This is why
I don't waste my time with these people anymore, Monty. >> Yeah.
If that's only what they can be, PG self
leave them to it. That's why everyone on
here never shows up when you make me waste.
You get what I mean though. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I'm saying, bro?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Well, if these people met up, then
you would have seen me. Hey, listen,
Monty. Yeah. Did you ever
do you ever remember when I went to that
Do you ever Do you remember that old man
that um kept trying it on with Izzy and
I went to his area twice live and he
didn't come out? Do you remember that years ago? >> Yeah.
>> And he didn't come out. And if you
noticed, no one ever said anything about
that. No one ever gave me credit for >> No,
>> that's what I'm saying. I don't waste my time working everything.
>> No, no, no, no. It was someone else. But
yeah, I done that as well. That's
another thing I didn't get credit for.
But I'm talking about another thing.
This is what I mean, bro. They're just a
waste of time on here. You know, these people these people, >> huh?
Who would these people met?
>> They met no one.
>> Exactly. Well, there you go.
But you've done more.
>> Just like they don't show [ __ ] Just
like when you show money, they all run away.
>> So So you've done more than most people
in this community are. So they can't
self-reflect on that cuz who they met
what what they done. >> Yeah.
You know what I mean?
But listen, you need you want this USA
Izzy's number. You might already have
it, LG. If you fancy it, I'll give you a number, bro.
>> Cuz the way you try to act like she
never done anything wrong, bro. She
[ __ ] did. And I don't even care.
You're the one that goes on about it. I
don't I know she did, and I don't give a
[ __ ] about it. But for some reason, you
you seem to like talking about it, bro.
Like, it's weird as [ __ ]
Just [ __ ] bro. Do you know how weird it is?
>> Just give it in. Everything's just got a
chance. Give it in.
I'm not trying to show off at all. I'm
not I'm not trying to show off. Like,
listen, I'm wrong. Did I say, "Oh,
everything I done wasn't right. I was,
you know, I I I took things OTT." There
ain't denying that, bro. Like, messaging
family. Am I saying I'm all in the
right? No, I'm not saying I'm all in the
right. How you try and sit there and act
like they done [ __ ] nothing wrong,
bro. Like, you're mad. You're [ __ ]
You're I don't even know what what I
could even call you. What? What? There's
no word for it. You know
>> one minute. It's LT is LT Muslin. PG. >> No.
>> What is it?
>> I got no words for you, but honestly.
Oh, he's not.
Wait, is he white?
>> Is he white?
>> No, he's black. You know the reason why
she follows me on
everything. No wonder. >> Yeah.
>> No wonder she's obsessed with women then
if he's black then. No wonder man to
you. But you did not show off. She ran
to the police two times.
>> She went crying to the police. I was on
her phone for 5 hours. Bro, I was
talking to her friend for 5 hours.
They're not about it. The [ __ ] went
running to the police. As soon as
somebody stood up to her, she started
playing the victim. That's your girl,
bro. She ain't my problem. Yes, she did
run to the police cuz I spoke to her
friend. She did run to the police. She's
not about that life.
You know what I'm saying? I'm not scared
of her or anybody she knows. And yes,
she did run to the police cuz her friend
told me. So, stop talking [ __ ]
love. Stop talking [ __ ] She went to
the police two times. Her friend I was
on the phone to her best friend for 5 hours.
I mean, Monty.
>> Yeah. Just even look listen PJ. Yeah.
He's obviously like you have said, black
people are very obsessive for women.
Very controllive with women. And this is
what else he's doing.
Yeah. He's controllive. And that's what
he's, you know, if he wants her, go and
get her. Don't even give him his number.
PJ, go help him out one little bit.
Leave him to it.
>> You know what I'm saying, bro? And
listen, you know the only time Listen,
let me tell you something. You know that
time you come in the house, you know the
reason I didn't have Do you know the
reason I didn't do anything? Let me Let
me tell you right here now, Monty. Yeah.
I had too much to lose, bro. I was
making money on a house. I had a house.
No one's scared of you, bro. I'm not
scared of you at all. I'll put it out
there right now, bro. I'm not even
trying to show off. I'm not scared of
you one little bit,
you know? It's just I didn't want to do
anything because I knew, bro, that I'd
end up in prison. I'm not scared of you.
I'm not scared of her. I'm not scared of
her, man. You understand?
That's the only reason, bro. No one was
scared. Nobody was scared. Do you think
I was I was going to lose a house and
money I was making from that house
because of you, bro? Like,
>> why getting bothered with a girl that
you been with and he's asking who he
doesn't even know? If you had way more
to lose, Bob, you wouldn't have even
done that in the first place.
>> Yo, PJ, why is LT getting involved in
the business? What's not even his
>> Cuz that's what he does, bro. It's his
life, isn't it?
>> That's not
that that relationship with you.
>> No, no, no, no. Timmy and Tiger went on
the door. So, I went to the house to see
what the [ __ ] they were doing. I didn't
know who they were going to start like
attacking me and [ __ ]
Listen, Bomb, you've been beat at the
money game several times, just like all
of you. Bye-bye now.
>> Bomb's ugly. Oh, Connie is the ugliest
skinniest guy on Get you bastard.
>> Bob's a [ __ ] sweaty.
>> How many times you listen listen? Do you
know how many times you people Yeah.
have been beaten at the money game? It's
not even a joke. Like, do you actually hear yourselves?
>> Is that your fuckingelves, bro? Yeah.
>> Bomb bomb. The actual bomb. >> Yeah,
>> the sweaty [ __ ] fat ugly bomb.
>> You're another one I turn up to and you
didn't show up.
>> Yeah. No bomb. None of these will show
up PJ. They [ __ ] closed. My lad
closed in his community. A lot of them
are what LT will do. He is smash your
window and run off. >> Yes.
>> I don't know why why you why you're
acting like she didn't go to the police
when she literally did. They're not bad
just because they're American. They're
not bad, bro. No one's bad. You, bro.
All they can do over there is [ __ ]
get a gun and try and [ __ ] shoot
people. They ain't bad, bro. They had to
stop letting people in the [ __ ] army
in these bars cuz they used to [ __ ] up
these Americans every time. They're not
bad, bro. I don't know who you think
they are. They're nothing without their little guns.
>> Yeah, that's what made me laugh at the
Damon because he would just get slapped
one time, bro. Hey, I'm going to jump
off anyway. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Anyway, catch in a bit.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
And that's it. So,
you're an idiot, bro.
An absolute clown.
You're [ __ ] bro. Listen, all of this
[ __ ] bro, it doesn't scare me.
None of nothing you do scares me, bro.
Trust me. Nothing you do scares me.
Seriously, it really really doesn't.
You might as well try with other people,
bro, because you don't bother me. Like,
I know you get this little [ __ ]
whole, you know, I love I love you. I
know you love this little um you get
this little um frill from trying to
scare people, but bro, you really don't
scare me like at all at all at all. like
you really really don't
you know I know I didn't go crying to
you. You wanted to meet Lord Jay. That's
why I was asking you to meet him because
you're the one that wanted to meet him.
You're the one that wanted to meet him.
So I said, "Oh, go and meet him then.
You're an idiot, man."
You know what I'm saying? Where was his
mouth when I was in Stratford? Where?
Bro, listen. My mouth was when I was
making money from a house and had [ __ ] to lose.
That's That's where my mouth was. Yeah,
that's where my mouth was.
Yeah. Crying to you. Okay. Really? Yeah.
Yeah. Crying to you. You're the one that
said you wanted me to tell you when Lord
J was here. That's why I told you. Okay.
I won't tell you anything in future.
You know what I'm saying? I won't tell
you anything in future. Okay. Okay. I
won't tell you anything in future. How
about that one?
Bro, you're not worth my time. Go away.
You're not worth my [ __ ] time. Stop
it, bro. It's boring, man. You don't
scare me. I don't know why you care
about someone in America trying to say
that they didn't run to police. You know
what I'm saying? when we all know they
ran to police and we knew exactly what
happens when you land there even now.
Come on, man. Come on. You know,
I know I didn't call him to come over.
You called out Prime and you can never
do that to me. Oh, no. Oh, really, bro? Really?
That prime is a [ __ ] [ __ ] And the
only reason I called him out again is
cuz he kept [ __ ] annoying me up until
about time I went to Birmingham.
Nowhere to be seen. But I guess he'll be
back in about a month saying that he
never saw it. [ __ ] idiot.
You're a fool. You're an absolute fool.
You're an idiot.
Go and tell her I told her to go stuck
her mom when you speak to her again.
When you speak to her again, go tell her
to suck her mom.
Yeah. Tell her I said that. From Peter Belly.
From Peter Belly to you.
You're not worth my [ __ ] time, bro.
You're not worth my time.
Stop wasting my time.
Yeah, you're a keyboard warrior, bro.
Just allow it.
Yeah, you're not worth my time. You're
literally not worth my time. You're not.
Oh, bringing other people into it again.
Bringing other people into it again.
That's all you ever do.
That's what you do. You bring other
people into it again.
That's all you can do, bro. You're an
idiot. You're a waster, bro. Get out of here, man.
Yeah. You didn't You didn't violate
anyone. You didn't violate anybody at all.
Yeah. And when your friend done that
[ __ ] I weren't even in the house. I was
actually in the police cell, which I
actually proved. So try again. Try
again, bro. Try a [ __ ] game.
No one's scared of you or anybody that
you know at all. Like, not at all. At
You know, if you if you want trouble, if
you're looking for trouble, go go on another community.
You know what I'm saying?
That's it, bro.
No, it didn't violate me, mate. Didn't violate me.
Nah, nah. Didn't have me running, mate.
Didn't have me running. Trying to say
that the [ __ ] never [ __ ] ran to the
police. She [ __ ] ran to the police,
bro. [ __ ] crying. Probably made a
[ __ ] post on me. It's funny, bro.
It's really, really, really, really,
really, really funny. So, you start
[ __ ] Do you know what? Yeah. Funny. I
think we should talk about this. This
actually happened today on a bus, right?
I was on a bus today. This actually a
true story, right? And I was sat at the
seat, right? And then this [ __ ] man
come and he's like, "Oh, uh, can this
can this woman sit down?" No, no, no,
no, no. So, I've stood up
um and said, "Uh, that's a bit rude,
isn't it?" Like telling, you know,
asking people to to get up off their
seat and [ __ ] you know, I was with
someone and then he started like
chucking it. I said, "How is it rude?" I
said, "It is rude. They're not disabled.
They're not old. There's there's nothing
wrong with them. They're not pregnant."
And then he was being a [ __ ] I said,
"Let's get off the bus stop. Let's let's
get off literally right here, right now
at the next stop." If you you know, he
was trying to say I'm a prick. I said,
"Oh, am I? Let's get off the bus." Yeah.
That's what I said. I said, "You are a
[ __ ] prick, you stupid cunt."
Yeah. And then he shut his [ __ ]
mouth. [ __ ] What is it with these
pricks? You get him. You get him here as
well. You know what? I had that a lot.
Yeah, when I used to do that Uber job,
they start [ __ ] they can't finish. Why
make yourself in a worse mood and get me
in a bad mood if you're not going to if
you're not going to finish it?
What What is it with these people here,
bro? Like, same with that USA. Why Why
do this [ __ ] if you can never back it up?
What is the point of it? I don't
understand what's the actual point of
it. Why do all of this [ __ ] if you're
not going to back it up? Get off the
bus. That's what I said. You wouldn't
get off the bus.
[ __ ] [ __ ] man.
I don't know what it is with people
here. I seriously don't.
[ __ ] [ __ ] There's so many
[ __ ] in this country. It's unreal, bro. Yeah.
And it just goes to show that you doing
all of this [ __ ] Yeah.
You doing all of this [ __ ] Yeah.
Is it just goes to show that you're
lying about your life, bro?
You know what I'm saying? You ain't got
no [ __ ] kid. You ain't got no
nothing, bro. Cuz you wouldn't be doing
this if you did. It's obvious. It's so
You know, it's so obvious now. It's
actually so obvious now. You claim that
you got a good job, you got a family,
but you're trying to like meet people on
YouTube, bro. It's funny. It's really,
really, really, really, really, really funny.
And that weren't my bike,
bro. Cuz if that was my bike, I would
have got that bike back. Trust me, I
would have got that bike back. So, you
know when you keep saying about how you
took that bike, bro, you've never took
nothing from me. You've never took
nothing from me, bro. Never. Nothing.
Literally, that's not even my bike.
That's what makes me laugh when people
say, "Oh, you took your bike, bro.
That's not my bike."
You know, that's not my bike, bro.
cuz everybody would know about it if it
was my bike.
But yeah, it's obvious now anyways, bro.
You show yourself up.
You show yourself right up. Right up.
Just like that [ __ ] today did on the
bus when I told him to get off. He
didn't want to get off of it.
Bro, I didn't do anything back cuz I
told you that I had too much to lose. I
don't give a [ __ ] what you broke into. I
was making money. You didn't take
[ __ ] nothing from [ __ ] me. You
know, you literally took nothing from
me. So, I don't give a [ __ ] what you
break into some [ __ ] cancel house.
I'm subleting. I don't give a [ __ ] You
never took anything from me.
So, bro, you made just made a fool of
yourself. I was still making money no
matter how many scared per scared how
scared people are. I was still making
money, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] You know,
you know what I mean?
But it shows what you're about,
bro. Your friend done that when you knew
I wasn't even.
So, bro, no one no one's no one cares.
Literally, no one cares.
And you never took nothing from me. So,
I know I never told you that.
Never told you that at all.
Stop being a keyboard warrior. Get a
life. You said you got two kids and you
got a good job. What are you on YouTube
trying to meet people for? Come on. Stop
showing yourself up now. You're not
scaring me, bro.
You're not scaring me. Trust me.
No. No. No.
No. No. You don't. You've never done
[ __ ] Shut up. Keep defending a stupid
[ __ ] in America. It goes to show how
how sad you really really really really are.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
And you're saying I haven't been there,
bro. I didn't even need to leave the
bed, bro. And I had the [ __ ] running to
the police. I had the [ __ ] crying and
running to the police. That's what you
get for being a [ __ ] Don't go around
being a [ __ ] to people. Yeah. If you're
if you're going to cry about it, don't
go around don't do not [ __ ] go around
being a [ __ ] and then start [ __ ]
playing the victim when someone gives
you it back. You little stupid [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? Especially not
in a different country. You little
crybaby, bro. You're saying I've not
been here. I've not been there. But
isn't it funny how like
>> I basically didn't have to
even do anything. Oh [ __ ] that's
You know what I'm saying?
Don't be You should have said to her,
don't go around being a [ __ ] to people.
Don't go around being an entitled [ __ ]
to people cuz you're not about that
life. We know that you're not about that
life. Cuz anyone that's about that life
would say, "Come and do it then. Come on
then. Come and do it." You know what I'm saying?
Don't go around being a [ __ ] if you
can't back it up. You know, you narcissist.
[ __ ] little crybaby. Little crybaby.
Little crybaby, mate. Little [ __ ] crybaby. [ __ ] idiot.
I love it. Me, bro. You know that.
I really love it. [Music]
No, she never. No, she [ __ ] never.
Whoa. Something can lying for me, bro.
None of them could even touch me ever.
If that's the case, why did they go
running to the police? Why did they go
running to the police then? Cuz her best
friend told me, "Okay, yeah, come here.
This is going to happen. That's going to
happen. This is going to happen. That's
going to happen. Okay, so why did you go
running to the police?" And stop saying
that they never because their friend has
told me they have.
Who am I going to believe? Their best
friend who I was on the phone to for 5
hours or am I going to believe you? You know,
and I tell you what. Yeah. Why don't you
tell her to [ __ ] come now? I'll even
pay for the [ __ ] flights. Why don't
you tell her to come now with everybody
that she knows? Yeah. Simple. And see
what happens. Go on.
Why would Why would anyone be nervous of
me? Well, why why did you go running
into the police
like the little [ __ ] that you are? Why
did you go running to the police?
Why did you go run into the police then?
No one's scared of her or anyone she
knows. They're all a bunch of [ __ ]
[ __ ] Have you seen that [ __ ]
Damon, bro? He's some fat Puerto Rican
stupid looking [ __ ] kid. Who's going
to be [ __ ] scared of him?
I [ __ ] knock his [ __ ] block off
here then, man. It's [ __ ] funny, bro.
Her dad's talking about how he's going
to handcuff me and that.
Who talks like that? What? What bad
person talks like that?
Yeah. I've never stepped into anyone
because they kept running to the police.
Because they kept running to the police.
Glad I met them, bro. I'm actually glad
I met them. I'm really really glad I met
them. You know, I'm glad. I'm very very very glad
you know that Ali I'm very very glad I
met them. I was able to come into their
life you know
Why did you Oh, [ __ ]
How did a black guy run to the police?
Bro, she ran to the police. Her and her
dad ran to the [ __ ] police. Yeah,
you're not about nothing, you [ __ ] Syrian [ __ ]
You [ __ ] Syrian little [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
What could you do to me, bro?
What could you do to me, you [ __ ] Syrian [ __ ]
Do you know what I mean? You know what I'm saying?
What could you [ __ ] do to me? Come
on, don't make me laugh.
You know what I'm saying?
I'll [ __ ] have them all.
I'll have the [ __ ] lot of them.
I'll have the [ __ ] all of them. Me.
Even when her [ __ ] Fen was trying to
say, "Oh yeah, I've got seven siblings.
One of one of us was going to move to
you." I was like, "Bro, if that was
really if only that was really going to happen.
If only that was really going to happen." Yeah.
If that was really going to happen. Yeah. Right.
Yeah. [ __ ] right. Ain't it greasy?
Yeah. [ __ ] right, mate.
You're such a simp you are.
You know, trying to say, "Oh, it's like
when I say, oh, you can see the evil and
the Westinity in these women's eyes."
That's not being an incel.
That's not That's not being an incel.
What? Because I don't lick women's
asses. I'm an incel. Oh, well, bro. I'm
Oh, is that the new word for it now?
If they if they said that you was a misogynist,
then I'd be like, "Okay, yeah, maybe."
But they don't even call you misogynist.
They call you an incel.
All of these people that are virgins and
have had less women than you call you
incelss and they don't call you a misogynist.
Wouldn't the word be a misogynist?
I think that would fit you more more
perfect to be honest.
Bro, I've never been bullied. You've
never bullied me. None of your stupid
mates have never bullied me. Like none
of you, bro. No one's scared of you or
anybody that you know. Bullied by who?
No one can bully me.
Nobody can bully me at all. You don't
bully me. None of your friends bully me.
Trust me, you don't. Why do you think I
was kind of starting on you the other
day, bro? I was going to come and meet
you and lick you over your [ __ ] head, bro.
Cuz no one's scared of you, bro.
Literally, no one is scared of you. No
one is. No one is scared of you at all.
No one's scared of you. No one's scared
of your cousin. No one's scared of none of you.
You know, the only reason I didn't do
anything is cuz, bro, I had too much
[ __ ] to lose. Do you think I'm going to
waste my time on a loser like you?
Please, bro. Come on. You know,
bro, I'm this. I'm that. Who's the one
that has to work? You're the one that
has to work. I've never I've never had
to work. I've never had to work, bro.
You're the one sat there being someone's [ __ ]
you know? You're the one that's sat
there being someone's [ __ ] [ __ ]
every day. Not me, brother. I don't need
to get out of bed for nothing.
Think about that, bro. Think about that.
What What What What do you have, bro?
What What um
What education do you have, bro?
What education do you have? You got no education.
You got none at all.
You've got no education at all.
You know what I'm saying? And you're an
idiot. You're a simpleton just like
these people. You're a simpleton just
like these people.
You all get [ __ ] owned at the money
game. You all get [ __ ] You know what
I mean? It's ridiculous
[ __ ] pathetic you people are.
Bro, listen. You don't have anything.
The fact that you're still working at 34
years of [ __ ] age, it says it all.
You know, you weren't the chosen one.
Simple. You weren't the chosen one. You know,
you're the one has to get up from your
comfy bed every day to go to work. Uh,
I'm 28. No kids, no place of your own.
Bro, listen, I've shown more money than
you would ever have. And yes, I do have
a place and I don't need a driving
license. I live in London. Yeah, I'm
this. I'm that. Bro, it's funny you used
to say that because you're the one
that's obsessed with my sloppy seconds.
You all you do is go on about them.
You know what I'm saying? I don't want
[ __ ] kids. Why the [ __ ] would I want kids?
Huh? You've got kids and you can't even
provide for them. You're not even
financially stable. Well, you are
actually you don't have kids, which is
you you pretend that you've got kids,
which isn't even believable because
you're not even financially [ __ ] stable.
Yeah. Didn't you get Weren't you one of
the Weren't you the other ones that got
uh weren't you the one wasn't you
another one that got [ __ ] owned at
the money game as well, bro? You all got
owned at the money game, bro? You got
showed money time and time and time and
time again. And you all run away. You
all run away. I can get a driving
license in 2 months if I wanted to, bro.
I can get a driving license if I wanted
to whenever I want to. But I'm in I'm in
London. I don't need to drive.
What the [ __ ] Why would I need to drive
in London, bro? For what reason? For
For what reason? Yeah, of course it is,
bro. Well, show your car then. Go on,
And this is why you know when you people
come in here and you call people skin, I
laugh at you now cuz I know what you do.
Yeah. You all run away. You've been
shown money, bro. You've been shown
[ __ ] You've been shown Think of
this, bro. Yeah. You're you're you're
going on about some dead sloppy seconds of mine
and you're [ __ ]
you're saying how you've got this and
you've got that and you've got this and
you've got that.
Bro, you speak to the likes of Jane.
Come on. You're not that guy, bro. You
met Natalie G. You're not that guy. Do
you think I would ever go near Natalie G?
And I don't care if Monty's listening to
this. I will never ever go near Natalie
G. If ever,
[ __ ] ever. You got all this, you're
all that, but bro, you're the one sing
over dead gal on [ __ ] YouTube, you know,
just like L J. And I'm not even
trolling. I'm actually not even
I'm not even [ __ ] trolling, bro.
Yeah. Izzy, someone I actually met.
Yeah. And Izzy's better than [ __ ] that G.
She's [ __ ] stinking, bro.
She is [ __ ] That Natalie G is
stinking, bro. And I don't care if you
if Monty sees this. I'll say it. I don't
give a [ __ ]
And that's the likes that you go for.
That's why you're so obsessed with this
dead girl in America, isn't it? That's
why you're so obsessed with this dead
girl in America. And that is it. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's what it
is, isn't it?
You're obsessed with them [ __ ] some dead
girl in America. It's funny as [ __ ]
You're obsessed, bro.
Really, really obsessed. I feel bad for you. Seriously, [ __ ] me.
I I I actually feel bad for you, bro. I really do. You know,
bro, listen. If I went to America
tomorrow, we all know what would happen.
You know, I could tell you exactly what
would happen. Do you know exactly I do
you really want to know what will happen
if I went to America tomorrow?
Yeah, I could actually tell you exactly
what would happen.
They would probably get somebody to go
meet you and start chucking it to you.
And then do you know what they're going
to do after that? Then they're going to
call the police. That's what would
happen. Someone would probably meet you.
Yeah. Um and then police will get called
and then they'll bring up all the
history and I come back here. That's
what that's exactly what would happen,
bro. That is exact if if you could even
make it that far to be honest. We know
what the [ __ ] is about. We know what
the [ __ ] is all about. She ain't about
that life. I don't know why she's trying
to tell you that she's about that life
when she isn't. She really ain't about that life.
Where is she? Where's the [ __ ] now?
Miami. I could, bro. If I went to Miami
and I went in at university chucking it,
what do you think would happen? What do
you think would happen? It's not even a
case of knowing people anymore. Do you
know what? It's not it's not even a case
of knowing people anymore cuz she
doesn't even know anyone in Miami cuz
she's not from there. So, it's about
it's pointless talking about anymore
about who they know cuz they don't know
anyone there, you know.
Yeah, bro. She didn't pity anyone. I had
the [ __ ] running to the police. She
wasn't pitting anyone when she was
running to the police crying. Oh, he's
stalking me. He's messaging my family.
Oh, no. No, no, no, no. Was she pitying
anyone then? Bro, she's a coward. She
didn't even have the balls to say,
"Listen, [ __ ] you. If you're going to do
something, come here." You had to call
police in. You had to get police
involved, which means you did not want
it. That means you did not want it. You
calling the you even saying you even
mentioning the police just goes to show
that you're not about that life. You're
not about that life, bro. Cuz me, if
somebody says, "Oh, I'm going to come to
you." I'll say come then come on then
right now if you're going to do
something follow up your threat I'm not
mentioning no police
there you go so
you're not a [ __ ] about that [ __ ] life man you know
you know what I'm saying and I didn't
run from no bus driver I actually own
somebody on a bus today ran from Terry
Yeah I went to I went to Terry's area
and he didn't come out Come on, man.
It's not going to work with me. It's not
going to work with me. Come on. Yeah.
Did I run today on a bus? No. You're the
You have to get people to do your dirty work.
You're a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. You ain't
got no kids. You ain't got no kids. You
ain't got no money. Yeah. You ain't got
[ __ ] all, bro. It shows. It shows. It
shows. It shows. It shows. It shows,
man. You ain't got no kid. You ain't got
no nothing. You got [ __ ] all, bro.
You're a [ __ ] bro.
You're not far behind L. You're a [ __ ]
I feel bad for you. Me,
you don't have kids.
You don't have kids.
Yeah. My sister that that would never go
anywhere near you. Yeah. Yeah. My sister
that would never go anywhere near you.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. My sister
Well, I mean, my dad died,
so uh I mean that's that. I mean, people
die in life. But at least I ain't got
autism like your cousin.
At least I'm not disabled like your
cousin. Well, that's a good thing, isn't
it? And that's already been proven. I
mean, I could have autism like your
cousin. I could be a complete spacker
like your cousin, but I'm not. So, uh, yeah.
Yeah. I mean, yeah, people die. I mean,
my dad died. Okay. And your point is
what? I mean, when Virgin Boy [ __ ]
dad dies, we're going to throw a party. Yeah, bro.
Autism doesn't run in your family. Your
cousin literally has autism.
And your you've got some form of special
needs as well. Like I've noticed that
with you. You've actually got some form
of special needs because uh you know
when people explain [ __ ] to you, you
don't really understand it. So you I
mean you're you're the one you're the
one that's got special needs, bro.
And you're sing for someone in America,
bro. You don't get no [ __ ] You ain't
got no [ __ ] You ain't got no [ __ ]
You ain't got nothing, bro.
You have to try with people sloppy
seconds. You have to [ __ ] The only
thing that you can [ __ ] his phrase is
[ __ ] dead girl.
You're not about that life, bro. Stop
it. You're not about that life.
You know what I'm saying? You're not
about that life.
You're not about that life. And you you
know you know like you can't even make
you can't even make threats to me either
cuz you know that no one's scared of
you. Like you know that I'm not scared
of you. So you know like even you making
threats I'm just going to laugh at it, bro.
You know what I'm saying, bro? I'm just
laughing because you can't even scare
someone like me, bro. You You just get
laughed at. You know what I mean?
You know what I'm saying? I love it. I
actually love it. Yeah. I get K, bro.
You are a [ __ ] You literally are a
[ __ ] You look like a [ __ ] You
can't even get no gal. That's why you
have to s over some [ __ ] in America.
Listen, listen, listen. I made her go to
the police. I violated her. I violated
her family. And what? You're going to do
nothing about it. Show her. Show her a
real man. Show. Do you know what? Do you
know what you need to do, bro? Yeah. You
need to show her a real man in England.
You need to show her what a real man is.
cuz she doesn't really know like a lot
of people in you need to be that example
and and and do something to me, bro. You
need to show her a real man.
You need to show her a real man, bro.
No, he's not had me on my toes at all,
bro. Listen, the only reason I didn't do
anything to you, bro, is I've already
explained it. I had too much to lose.
You don't have me on my [ __ ] toes.
So, you're not going to do it then. So,
you're not going to do it then, brother.
You're not about nothing. You didn't
even You couldn't even meet Mark Samson.
For [ __ ] sake. You didn't even do
anything to Mark [ __ ] Samson. I've
done more than you [ __ ] in all of them years.
But somehow, you know, you can never
ever meet him. But why don't you show
this [ __ ] in America what a real man is?
>> I don't nothing. I was in a police cell
when he done that. We've already been
over this. We've been over this a
million times. We have been over this a
million times. He smashed the wind. His
friend smashed my my mom's windows when
I was in a police cell, which I actually
proved once I had got nicked. Well, I've
spoke about his kids. I've spoke about
his race. I've made fun out of
everything. And he's done nothing to me.
He's done nothing to me. I spoke about
his kids, his race, and he will never do
nothing to me. That's why he can't say
anything to that [ __ ] in America.
You know what I'm saying? I spoke about
his kids. I spoke about his race. He
ain't took nothing off me. I still made
money every month. I've still made money
every month. You know, I've still made
money every [ __ ] month.
No, he never said it was made up. How
could it be made up?
Are you a [ __ ] [ __ ] How is it
[ __ ] made up, you [ __ ] idiot?
What? Someone's just come and broke my
[ __ ] windows. Have a [ __ ] word for yourself.
You know what I'm saying?
And and listen, if you want to ask me
that question, why have I never met
someone? Why don't you come and why
don't you come on the panel? Why don't
we all go in the [ __ ] panel? Why
don't we all go on the panel?
You know what I'm saying, bro? You're a
[ __ ] idiot, mate. You're an absolute idiot.
Yeah. No, my mom called the police.
Yeah. So what? Your [ __ ] in America
calls the police
cuz she got [ __ ] owned. I violated
her, bro. From the comfort of my own home.
How mad is that?
You don't have no kids. You don't even
have a MS, bro. You're you're you're
living in a fairy tale land.
Yeah. You're living in a fairy tale
land. That's what you're doing, bro.
Yeah. You're living in a fairy tale land.
You ain't got no misses. You ain't got
no [ __ ] kids. Cuz you wouldn't be
trying to meet people on [ __ ] YouTube.
If you did, it's it's so obvious.
No. Uh, no. I didn't have to get a panic
button, right? My mom literally got a
panic button because she called the
police. Yes. Yes. Yes. Listen, why don't
you come and hang out, Russell?
Why don't you come in the hangouts
and stop typing? If you've got anything
to say, why don't you come on the Hangouts
and stop typing behind your little
cowardly fake account. Yeah, simple. Why
don't you come and hang out? Stop typing
behind your little fake account, I'll
put the link up right now. And anything
you've got to say, come and say it on
the [ __ ] Hangouts
since you're this big man that seems to
know everything. Yeah, one second. Let
me put let me put this link up for this
little [ __ ] and you can come on as
well if you want. No one any everyone's
welcome since you apparently know
everything. Yeah. And you want to try
and talk like you're bad. Right. Let me
put a let me put it up for you. One sec.
Yep. There we go. One sec. Should be
good. Bro, listen. Come on then. Join
the hangouts. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. There you go. If
you've got anything to say, join the
panel since you seem to know everything,
but you don't know anything at all. Come
on, you little [ __ ] Come and join.
What are you waiting for? Yeah.
You know what I'm saying,
bro? You need to, you know, these
threats here, you need to, you need to
do this with people like Jane
and [ __ ] you know, Natalie G. Don't
do it to me, bro, cuz you don't scare
me. You don't scare me at all. Like I
said, show this [ __ ] USA is he a real man.
Go and show USA is he a real man. Show
her how how people do it in England.
And why are you not joining as well?
You've got a lot to say behind a [ __ ] fake account.
Yeah. 1K a month benefit, bro. I've got
way more than 1K and I have more than
you will ever have. You've been shown
money multiple times, mate. I've got way
more than 1K. Try again and you don't
know how much I have. How much did I get
last month? And how much did I get this
month? You don't know nothing about
anyone. But guess what? We know that
every single time you got shown money,
you all ran off. That's what we know. We
know for a fact that every single time
you people got shown money, you all ran
away because you all skint skin and you
ran away. Which is why people don't
waste their time on you. You think
really realistically people can't come
and show you money? Yeah, they can.
Anyone can show money, bro.
But we all know that when you get show
money, you will run away cuz your
benefits don't stretch that far.
Everyone knows that, bro. Come on. You
know what I'm saying, Russell? I know
that I shown 5.7 grand and you all ran
away. You all went running like a
shotgun. So shut the [ __ ] up, mate. You
people can't show anything.
You've been beating at the money game so
many times that, bro, I wouldn't even
come on here if I took that many L's.
Simple, bro. Yeah. Yeah.
It was actually that bad. You got shown
5.7 grand. You weren't talking then, was
you? He was running away cuz your 300 lb
benefits don't stretch that far. You
know what I'm saying? Okay. Simple.
I've got gums worth more than your life
in one bag. You know, in this bag next
to me, them clothes is worth more than
your [ __ ] whole life.
That's how bad it is.
And no, I I wouldn't have been [ __ ] I
would have still had money. I just spent
a lot of money on Sunday and I spent a
lot of money on [ __ ] Tuesday. Yeah, I
spent a lot of [ __ ] money two times
in a month. So my [ __ ] is not your
[ __ ] My [ __ ] is not most people's
Simple. You know what I'm saying?
That's why I [ __ ] laugh, right? When
you [ __ ] you know, when Virgin Boy
shows these little 800, it makes me
[ __ ] die, bro. Cuz if only these
people knew. Yeah. I'm Bro, listen
listen. If I'm skin Well, bro, I've just
put the link there. Show us your money.
Okay, let's see your money then, bro.
The casino money. Listen, let me repeat
it again. You have been shown money
multiple times and you ran away. Yeah.
Let listen listen listen, bro. You have
been shown money and you ran away cuz
you are skint.
That's why you can't show me anything.
Because you don't have anything. That's
why you fat, ugly people sit on YouTube
all day because you ain't got no money.
That's why you talk about people that
you don't know. Because you don't have
money. You're talking about your own
life. Yeah. You fat, ugly people. You
can't even sit. You can't even go for a
walk. You know what I'm saying? You all
fat ugly. It's like this LT is an ugly
bastard. He can't get no gal, bro. Why
do you think he is still on my sloppy
seconds? You know what I'm saying?
Russell, you bro, you can't do [ __ ]
Uber Eats cuz you're Bro, listen. You
don't even leave your house. You're on
£300 a month. What are you laughing at,
bro? What could you laugh at? You're on
£300 a month. You're scared to join the
hangouts. You can't show no money.
You're embarrassing yourself. The link
is right there.
I mean, bro, the link is right there.
You can't show no money. You're scared
to come on. You're just changing the
subject now. You're just you're just
literally you're literally deflecting.
That's what you are, bro. You've been
shown money. You ran away. Can't join
Hangouts. You're embarrassing yourself.
Everything you say now, you're embarrassing yourself.
You're sat on YouTube, can't even show
money, can't join the Hangouts, and
you're typing to me. Bro, does that even
make sense? No, it doesn't.
Listen, Smokey B, let me tell you
something. Okay, let's just say that was
your money. Okay. So, why are you the only one,
LT? I've got more friends than you would
ever have, bro. More friends than you
will ever have.
You're the guy that had to move out of
London cuz you couldn't even afford to
live here anymore.
Imagine that. You had to move out of
London because you couldn't [ __ ]
afford to to live here anymore.
And you want you want to tell me about
me, bro? Listen. So, Russell, are you
joining the hangouts or not? You scared little [ __ ]
You're just like that guy on the bus
today. The one that started something he
couldn't finish. You're just like that
guy on the bus today. You're all the
same. You know, you're like [ __ ]
these London [ __ ]
Yeah, bro. You moved out of London
because you couldn't afford to live in
London anymore. You don't have a family.
Yeah, you do not have a family.
Yeah, bro. I'm getting knocked back by
every woman even though I've had more
women than you. Listen, Smokey B, let me
tell you something. These people has been shown
so much money, different amounts of
money in different times. And every
single time they have been they've been
shown money, they all run away. That's
why I don't show money anymore. If you
don't think I've got money, bro, then
think I don't have money. I don't give a
[ __ ] bro. But you know, every single
time you show these people money, they
all run away. That's why I don't waste
my [ __ ] time on them, bro. I let them
self-reflect their life away. Leave the
fat ugly people to it. I don't give a
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying?
I can never afford your old apartment in
Angel. Listen, bro. Why? Listen, why why
would you were show money? Why did you
Why did you run away as well then?
Yeah. No matter what. You've never been
disrespected like that, bro. Jane's been
taking the piss out of you for [ __ ]
years. Yeah. Jane's been taking the piss
out of you for years and you ain't done
nothing about it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And
I told her that her dad should have
[ __ ] And I told her that her mom should
have swallowed. I disrespected her back.
And no black guy done nothing to me cuz
they're all weak. All you black guys are
weak. Yeah. I remember that in Liverpool
Street. Yeah. And I told her that her
[ __ ] mom should have swallowed her
[ __ ] ugly ass. And no black guy done
nothing to me. Cuz black guys are not
about nothing. Just like Americans ain't
about nothing. Just like you're not
about nothing. Just like these other
black people are not about nothing. I
told her about herself to about a woman
in front of black guys and they done
nothing because they're weak. Weak just
like you. You're weak. Let me tell you
something. I've never had to get anyone
ever to fight my battles, bro. I've
never ever had to get somebody fight my
battles. You did. Not me. I've never had
to get somebody to fight my battles. You
have, though. You generally generally
have cuz you're not about it. You're
some fat ugly laner, bro. You're not
about [ __ ] nothing, bro. And trust
me, if that house wouldn't weren't
getting rented Yeah. and I had nothing
to lose, you would have shown you
weren't about nothing. You online
keyboard warrior. You online keyboard
warrior. You're not about [ __ ]
nothing, bro. Yeah. You don't work at no
bank. You ain't got no [ __ ] family.
Yeah. You have to get people to fight your battles.
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Go suck your mom, bro. Yeah.
You say all this, but bro, you stalk my sloppy seconds.
You know what I'm saying? You're not
about nothing, bro. [ __ ] off, man.
Get a life, bro. Go see your Makebelie family.
Go see your makebelieve family, Bob,
that don't exist.
That don't exist. [ __ ] idiot. Um.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You keep telling
yourself that, bro. Okay. Mr. Lone about
34 with nothing. Okay. Lona.
You keep telling yourself that, bro.
You keep begging women on the internet.
You keep begging, Jane. You keep begging
ugly Natalie G. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. You're 34, bro.
And you have nothing. You're an old man.
You're a [ __ ] old man, bro. You're 3
[ __ ] four. You're an old [ __ ] man, bro.
You're an old man. Oh my god. You're an
old [ __ ] man, bro. And you got
nothing at 34.
You got about nine grand to your name at 34. Pathetic. [ __ ] pathetic.
You are pathetic, mate. You got about
nine grand at 34, bro. [ __ ] hell. You
got [ __ ] all, bro.
Bro, you are 34 and you are the manta,
bro. You are m You are ma. Why do you
think you get rejected by every single
[ __ ] woman on [ __ ] on [ __ ]
YouTube, bro? Cuz you're stinking, bro.
You're ugly, bro. You are an ugly ma.
You understand? You are a [ __ ] ugly ma. Yeah.
Yeah. That's why Yeah. Exactly. Yeah.
That's why That's what I'm saying, bro.
I've still got money, but I just don't
waste my time anymore. Yeah. Yeah, they
waited for me to bank it and spend some
and then start asking me to show it
again. That's what they do on here, bro.
Yeah, that that's what I'm saying.
That's what they do on here.
I'll show him on here. One sec.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Yeah,
that's the one that they've been doing
that for ages, bro.
They ask people It doesn't even need to
be six grand. It could be any amount of
money, bro. It could be [ __ ] £700. It
could be any amount of money. And they
they ask you to show money, you show
them money, and then they run away. And
as soon as you bank it or spend it or
whatever the [ __ ] you do with it, then
they ask you to show it again.
>> Why the [ __ ] did you call Natalie ugly?
>> Well, like to me she is.
>> Like it's personal preference.
>> [ __ ] friend. You're a [ __ ] mon PJ bastard.
>> Yeah, it's personal preference. So what?
You were the one standing people going
to stand people up. So you can't [ __ ]
talk, can you?
>> I'm saying [ __ ]
>> But you have room to talk. Let's just say that.
>> Yeah, but why bring into the
conversation? Is that fair?
>> Why? Why bringing Natalie into the
conversation with these ugly people?
>> Because I was saying how London Taylor
begs every woman on your [ __ ] YouTube
cuz he does.
>> You don't beg nobody. You don't need to
beg. How's about that? He does not need
to beg. So get your
>> Have you seen these messages? His
messages have been put out there. He's
been put up there. Yes, he has been.
>> But you do need to bring Natalie into
it. Natalie So why did he bring Natalie
in with London Taylor situation?
>> Because Elie has gone with and Jane.
Yes, because he has.
>> Have you been with him?
>> No, I haven't been with him. My mom's a liar.
>> Yes, you [ __ ] have.
>> No, I haven't. My mom's a liar, PJ. I
haven't got a lie. If I did, I'd say I
do not need to lie. Well, he said he's
met you. Well, he has said he's met you.
>> No, he hasn't at all.
>> Yes, he has. Yes, London [ __ ]
>> Hang on a minute. Hang on a minute. If
Natalie has met London like like I know,
I know, I know. I think Natalie would
say she ass or she hasn't. Do you know
what I mean? Is she?
>> He told me that they have on the phone.
So, he has told me this [ __ ]
is full of [ __ ] He's full of [ __ ] Why
wouldn't Natalie wouldn't buy either
way? Cuz when me and Natalie fell out
and then Lord Jesus better in bed out of
money, Mike and Jamie, she said me
straight up. She's not going to lie about [ __ ]
>> But he told me that they haven't met. >> No.
Why would he lie? No.
>> Because why would he lie? He lies about
loads of different things on here. What
you talking about? Why would he lie?
He's already been caught to lie about
things before. Yeah. So, so what did he
do with Natalie leg? I need my mic. I
need What? What? What did he do with Natalie?
>> Well, what do you think? >> No.
>> I don't even need to.
>> You don't speak to me. Listen, Lt. Bro,
you was on the phone to me yesterday,
bro. Do you want me to put it up when
you was on the phone to me yesterday?
Stop talking [ __ ] You You call me all the time.
>> Yeah. Stop [ __ ] talking [ __ ]
>> So, hang on, PJ. So, so if he calls you
all the time. Yeah. So, why you
>> No. No, Jay. No, no, no. You beg Jane on
the internet. You've never met Jane, but
you've said that you've met Natalie G.
>> You don't even need to beg Jane PJ. [ __ ] hell.
>> She's put messages up there. She's
actually put messages up there. So, okay, whatever.
>> J it.
>> Is she on YouTube?
>> Yeah. You guys have that boss's name.
I call name. >> No.
>> Yes. She was Yes, she was begging them.
Yes, she was begging them. You was
>> You know what I'm saying? >> PJ,
>> you have met him. Why are you lying?
>> I haven't met him, PJ. Why have I got to
lie? If I met him and shagged him, I
would have said, you know, I would.
>> So, why has he said you have then?
>> Well, he's changed his message. He said
he hasn't said that to you.
>> Well, he [ __ ] has. because I'm gonna
saying [ __ ] to you then he say different
on here you then he that's the thing so
he hasn't met Natalie
he hasn't met Natalie at all
>> Natalie won't sit there and check who
she's met or who she hasn't met come on
her going out with money m was
embarrassing know you know what I mean
and she admits that you know what I mean
>> well yeah she has to well she kind of
had to admit that I They're on YouTube
together. That's what I mean.
>> Yeah, obviously. Course. But she could
always deny it either way. But obviously
she can't. But obviously, you know, but
either way, she won't she won't lie
about something or chat [ __ ] about
something to tell you she's met him or not.
She tell me anyway she met him or not. I
won't be even if she did or not. That's
why I even went out with her anyways.
But they they've never met. Unless I
must piss and I can't remember, you
know. [ __ ] it's going. Oh,
>> money. You should Well, you're obsessed,
LT. You really really really are obsessed.
>> Yeah, but you're the one who you're the
one who's giving them that platform to
be obsessed with you.
>> He's talking [ __ ] money. He's talking
[ __ ] about you as well.
>> Yeah, can talk [ __ ] about me. At least
I'm not at least I'm not [ __ ] off
with the women like he is. I don't have
to sit on YouTube like he has to and
talk about other men's women's and [ __ ]
That's called self reflexes. I'm not
scared of LT one little bit. The man's a
[ __ ] low life scum on you. You don't
got [ __ ] all going for yourself. He's
nothing to me. [ __ ] all
a little weasel. is a [ __ ] [ __ ]
You got to pop people's window through
and then run off
and then rob things and put money in
that. He's a little weasel.
Don't matter how big you are, how strong
you are, you sure can get knocked out.
And what LT doesn't understand, he can
be the world musli's man and still get
>> So anyways, LT, do you want this number
then since you're obsessed with sloppy
seconds, you freak?
>> Just blocking Pier. That's what I mean.
You You're getting yourself pissed off
with a [ __ ] someone like him. Like
literally like you said, he's black.
He's obsessed with women. All black men are
>> He's saying that. Um he's saying that.
Would Would you say to yourself? >> Okay.
>> What? What? Yeah.
>> I'm not even reading the comments.
>> Oh, don't read the comments. The self
reflect is on the uh hot [ __ ] [ __ ]
go to [ __ ] America and go shagger
then since you're [ __ ] obsessed with
the [ __ ] slag. You know what I'm saying?
>> Do you know what I'm saying? Since
you're so obsessed, [ __ ]
>> do you enjoy what they do on here? >> No.
>> So why why are you why are you jumping
on board with it all? >> No.
>> But you are you're reacting back to him.
That's the thing. You're reacting back
to them all. That's the thing.
You're sitting there. I've been in here
what a minute ago and earlier you're on
and things still going on about this
girl from America with
>> he Yeah.
>> Yeah. I know what you're talking about.
He's obsessed little [ __ ] balloon. Obviously,
>> you're just [ __ ] Now he's getting you
to stick up for him.
>> I'm not speaking up for him.
>> Calling me ugly.
>> Yeah, I know. I'm not sticking up for
him. And then you calling Natalie ugly
and [ __ ] because you're arguing in with
him. And what makes what makes you call
Natalie ugly? What makes you Natalie?
>> I'm not. I'm not I'm not I'm not
>> No, I'm not repeating your [ __ ] LT. No,
because you know what? I'm not repeating
your [ __ ] because I'm not being class.
No, he can read himself. He can read it
himself. He can read it himself.
>> And this is what I'm saying. So why are
you bringing Natalie up when you're
angry with this guy for ages? PJ battles.
>> I'm not fighting your battles, PJ. I don't like
all of the stuff that he's writing. I'm
not reading it. I'm not reading it.
>> You know, all the stuff he's wring.
That's what LT's got to say about me. LT
[ __ ] resource on YouTube. That's it to me.
He's a man.
I like the I just don't like London Taylor
like [ __ ] PJ all the time. You know
what I mean?
>> Yeah, I know what you're saying,
Natalie. It is PG course this [ __ ] on you
>> and then just dragging him forward with his [ __ ]
>> Exactly. Well then
>> start getting involved in his [ __ ]
and I know what you're saying.
>> You've not treated Monty the best
either, Natalie. So you can't talk [ __ ] about me.
>> You know nothing now. Get your facts right.
>> Hang on. Hang on. PJ Natalie's not run
my kids up or destroyed my kids.
>> I'm not talking about kids. I'm not
>> No. I'm just saying she's not done any
of that. I call
>> No. I never said that. I never said about kids.
>> No, I'm just saying it's always just
been actual trolling. But with you just
[ __ ] dragging me into all his
[ __ ] on YouTube, dragging me in, you know,
>> you know, you made him do you, you know,
you made you made him do a [ __ ] video
[ __ ] crying and [ __ ] and you didn't care.
>> That's not on, you know.
>> Only why these go for me is because
you're the one who got me into this
community. That's why I went I went all
the way to B I went all the way to
Birmingham to support Monty and you're
trying to say that I'm getting him to
fight my battles. Really? Come on now.
>> You do? Yes. What you just put where was
you an hour ago Monty?
What do you want about PJ?
>> Why would I go all the way there to help him
>> and spend time and be a friend when you
was when you didn't care? You didn't
even you didn't even respond to his
messages. You was playing with his
[ __ ] head. I had to go all the way there.
>> I don't understand like why did you
drive into all this [ __ ] in this community?
>> That's what I'm saying to you. Why get
me involved in this [ __ ] Because
>> that's why and that's another thing.
Yeah. That's why Monty will never ever
hate me because he knows I'm actually a
good friend deep down. That's why
>> PJ the thing is it's not about I'm not
your friend PJ.
You're not looking back always.
>> I don't know why. I don't know why I'm calling you.
>> I'm seeing it and Okay. So, what did I
do last month when you were replying to
his messages to PJ? [ __ ] all. That's
what I mean.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> Whatever then.
>> You know, only what it's been is word
with London Tether and myself words. But
you dragging me into this community, you
know what I mean? It's different for
PlayStation PJ. You didn't tell me what
these communities were like, what these
people do with your life or [ __ ] like
that. It's all banner to me. It's not
real. It's banner. But this community,
it's real PJ and you put my life up as
much as I put my own life up. It's your
fault really. My life's all [ __ ] up.
It [ __ ] is.
>> It's your fault. No the [ __ ] it is not.
No, it is not. How many times did I tell
you to get off YouTube?
>> You got me on to YouTube. Why would you
get me on YouTube?
>> I knew. Listen, how did I know? How did
I know what they were going to do with
you and they didn't even do it to me?
They done all this [ __ ] to you before
they done it to me.
>> The posters, right? Okay. Okay. The post
the letters to your neighbors. They done
that to you before they done that to me.
>> It doesn't [ __ ] matter. It's just the
[ __ ] knowing that if they do find your
address, knowing that they [ __ ] real
your life up or go for you or whatever.
To me, it's banter to me. This ain't
banter on YouTube. These are the people
who were [ __ ] pretent page. Yeah.
>> Listen, if I if I would if I was going
to if if it was my goal Yeah. to [ __ ]
you up and [ __ ] your life, why would I
come to Birmingham, see you, spend time
with you, and spend money with you and
and and spend time with you? Why would I
do that if I was going to [ __ ] your life
up? That don't make sense.
>> If you was a good mate or whatever else
like that, you would have got me
involved in this community [ __ ] You
would have got me involved in your
[ __ ] cuz I thought it was all just
like you PlayStation was arguing. That's
only what I thought. I didn't know they
put you up there as a nons or trying to
destroy your life as whatever. Do you
know what I mean? I didn't know. I
didn't know they target your family.
>> I didn't know that. I didn't know that.
You must have known that PJ for being as
long as you have been.
>> I didn't know that cuz I was on I was on
the community like probably 8 months
before I got you in it. Probably 8
months. Yeah, maybe
>> eight months. I've only been in this
community through lockdown. Through
lockdown. That's only 6 years. That's
long enough for me to be honest with you.
And I still haven't got a judge with
this community what this community is
about. I can't read or write or [ __ ]
whatever else like that still, you know,
but still PG, you [ __ ] my life up
completely by getting onto this shitty
community. Thank you.
>> Is there anything he lacks of all?
>> Is it ridiculous? Cuz what you're saying
is ridiculous. You have to laugh. It's It's pathetic.
Is it ridiculous? Someone's life's life.
>> Yeah. Is that ridiculous?
>> It is because I didn't ruin your life.
How the [ __ ] did I ruin your life?
>> Of course. PJ, you know, you know what
these people were doing. Pat Mustard.
>> No, I didn't.
>> So easy.
>> Okay. So, why did they do it to me
first? Why did they do it to me?
>> In this community, you were hated in
this community because you had nobody in
this community. You thought, hey, I go I
go back to SGT Ramlot because he used to
argue back on YouTube as banter. Let's
go and bring game on. Hey, yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> Okay. Yeah, you keep thinking that then.
>> Oh, so why did you get me on then? Why
did you contact me through lockdown?
COVID lockdown through all that?
>> Because you want Because you used to
like drama like the PlayStation drama. No.
>> So there you go. You just animated it.
Yeah, but I didn't know they were going
to [ __ ] your life up, you idiot.
>> I know. Exactly. That's what I only
thought it was about.
>> That's what I thought it was.
>> That's the thing, PJ.
I'm not I'm not getting involved with
your [ __ ] in this community. I'm not.
>> Fine. I don't want you to.
>> Just point saying where I should have my
back an hour ago. You know, I don't know
why you got me involved in this. My
[ __ ] in PJ's [ __ ] P. >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] not.
>> I don't think any You think this is
funny, PJ? Is that on YouTube? No, not at all.
speak to another woman today. Speak to
another woman. Try and meet another
woman, right? To, you know, just cuz
even though he never I tried to get him
to and I'm the bad one, bro. If I'm all
of this, I'm all of that. I'm all of
this. I'm all of that. Then why was I
the only one to go all the way to
Birmingham, which is [ __ ] far, you
know? Not far to me, but far from most
people spend my money that I won on a
football bet going out with you if I
done all of these things. Who else done
that? Who else would have done that? You know,
who else would have done that? Nobody.
You know, nobody would have done that.
You know, when you talk about me being
in on PlayStation snaking you when I was
a kid, when I was 16. Yeah. Yeah. I did
used to like take sides cuz it was
funny, you know. It was it was drama,
you know. Um, but you you every time any
chance that you've got to snake me, you
do it. You've done it with Traumad,
you've done it with Bomb, you know,
you've done it even with Pat Mustard.
Every single time, right, you've had
chances to snake me, you've done it. So,
we're even. So, at the end of the day, I
thought we were [ __ ] even.
You know what I'm saying? I I actually
thought we were [ __ ] even. You know,
I actually I thought I wish I had
somebody come from [ __ ] Birmingham or
[ __ ] Nottingham or [ __ ] Manchester
and come and spend [ __ ] money on me,
you know? I wish someone done that to
me, mate, when I was going through [ __ ] struggles,
you know. But then no one did. No one No
one did, bro. No one did.
You know, when Natalie wasn't even
replying to your [ __ ] messages, when
she was trolling you on [ __ ] YouTube,
but I'm the bad one. Okay, whatever.
you know, and I'm the one that [ __ ]
his life up. Well, mate, if I if I
[ __ ] your life up, then I've done a
lot of [ __ ] for somebody that [ __ ]
your life up then going all the way to
Birmingham and spending money.
Yeah, that's what I'm trying to say,
Monty. So, I mean, you got no [ __ ]
argument, man. You got no argument.
Yeah, I used to take slides on
PlayStation because it's it was funny as
[ __ ] when you're [ __ ] 15, 16. Yeah,
it's funny. It's funny as [ __ ]
You know, people take the piss out of
me, but you've you've done it a lot with
Tramodol Tra bomb. You've done it with a
few people. You know, every chance you
get to try and snake me, you do it.
You have took it. You took the opportunity.
You've done it every time, bro.
All right then, Fox. Okay, fine.
There we go.
Okay. You can't trust me. Okay. Don't
trust me then. Well, you're not coming
in the hangouts then. Simple. If you
can't trust me, I'm not letting you in.
I'm not letting you up.
Well, fine. You can't trust me. I can't
trust you then. You're not coming on. Simple.
Yeah, you can't trust me. That's good,
man. Go and have your relationship and
leave me alone then if you can't trust
me. I tried to say that I [ __ ] his
life up. I got you. I got you on this community,
right? I got you on this community.
Yeah, cuz it was funny. It was [ __ ]
funny. You know, the arguing, the Timmy
Aldrids. It was funny as [ __ ] I didn't
know these people was going to do what
they done, right?
I [ __ ] didn't know what these people
was going to [ __ ] do. No, I [ __ ]
did [ __ ] not. I was new to it my
[ __ ] self. You always [ __ ] say
that every single [ __ ] time, you
know? And if I've really really ruined
your life over YouTube, you know, why
don't you get off YouTube and get all
the things you lost back, you know? All
of the things that you've claimed you've
lost off of YouTube, why don't you go
get it all back? Get off YouTube and go
get it all back then. Nothing stopping you.
Nothing's stopping you, you know.
>> That's it. [ __ ] sake.
>> Well, at the end of the day, I'm not
even arguing with you. I would I
appreciated you coming down and being
there. I'm not even arguing with you
about that. You're the one who's
chucking that [ __ ] in my face. That I'm
Yeah, I won't even on about that. I'm
back on PlayStation. You're the one who
used to argue with me with other people
and then when we was halfway through
arguing with someone else, you switch
sides and start arguing with that person
with me on me.
>> Yeah, that's
>> Yeah. So, why would I have trust in you?
Why would I trust you?
You've done exactly the same thing.
>> You've done the same thing. EJ,
I've just [ __ ] I've never [ __ ]
done nothing to you. Not really.
>> Yes, you have. Do you remember that?
Yeah, the Discord thing. The thing disco
I'm not being funny. You're the You've
destroyed my life as well as Yeah. when
you sending scripts to my door, getting
my kids script searched. Obviously you
apologize for that but you done that
stuff like that to me and I've not even
done [ __ ] all like that to you. What
have I done to you really?
>> Have I tried snaking me with Pat mustard
and and trauma?
You've done a lot worse [ __ ]
>> You know
>> you laugh at me in this community with
these people. I've seen it.
>> No I don't. No I don't. I think some of
the things you say is funny. Yeah funny.
It doesn't really matter if it's funny
or not. He's being snaky at the end of
the day. I'm not snaky, PG. I've had
your back for a long time, you know.
>> And I've had yours as well.
>> But not really. Not when not not really.
>> a lot of the time when I'm getting
trolled on my own panel. Where have you been?
>> What do you mean?
>> Where have you been? When I'm getting
trolled to [ __ ] on my own panel. when
people up on my box calling me to [ __ ]
where have you been?
>> Uh defending you.
>> Have you? No, no, no. It's always me on my own.
>> Okay then. Whatever. Whatever you say.
>> No, you know it. Either way, you're more
about your channel. Obviously, it's your
own channel obviously. But when it comes to you,
if you're not involved in my on this
[ __ ] there, then but you you want me
involved in your [ __ ] You know what? Do
you know what I'm saying?
I was done with all this trolling
[ __ ] back on PlayStation 3 Pia. I
was done with all this. This is why I
[ __ ] you up back on PlayStation 3. I
went on to PlayStation 4. I was done
with trolling. I was done with it all. I
had my life sorted. He had my two kids.
Yeah, me staying on this community, that
was my own fault. I s got up this community and [ __ ]
look after my kids, but I didn't. I
spent more time on YouTube and that was
my mistake and I but you should have got
me onto this community in the first
place and I would have even knew about
all this community and I would have been
here now. I would have still had my kid.
My kid will be still in my life now. You
know what I mean? And that's what I'm
saying. It's basically your fault. It's
not your fault why I lost my kids. It's
my fault cuz staying on YouTube, that's
my fault. But you getting me involved in
this community, that's your fault. >> Yeah,
>> that's what I'm saying. It's not your
fault why I lost my kids. But it's
partly your fault why I lost my kids
because you're the one who me to the
community when you get me out of it,
>> you know.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Cuz I would have still my
kids. No, I didn't know what these
people's going to do. That's what you don't understand.
>> You don't understand.
>> I do understand. Yeah.
>> Okay. Let me Okay, let me put it this
way. Let me put it this way. Right. I
got nonslegs on this community. I got
Dean on this community. The same [ __ ]
never happened to them. >> Yeah.
>> Dean. Okay. Dean. No, not Dean. You
could have easily argued with someone
two, three times and left. And you could
have left. Dean left. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Only because he he was only here longer
than that. He was only for longer than
that. He got doxed he left.
>> Yeah. So he left. So that's what I'm
saying. So people Yeah. So know when to
walk away. People know a time when to
walk away. You get it?
>> Walk away. But when people are calling
your kids and you're angry as [ __ ] and
pieces growing up, you're coming on to
offender to do that. And that's your mistake.
>> You know,
>> you know what I mean? But you when
people with disabilities like me, I like
social media. Social media is a big
thing to me. But when people have got
kids, they shouldn't even be on this
community. It shouldn't be even [ __ ]
here either way. And that's my mistake.
I been here on this community having
children cuz it's no good. This
community is no good for no one. >> No.
But you're the one who's got everyone
involved in this. Me long legs [ __ ] bean.
You know why bringing the old people
back on PlayStation? I'm grown up. I'm
35 years of age. PJ. I'm not 20 [ __ ]
4, 25 anymore. Where am I going with
people like fat damn with you know what
I mean? Arguing at fat down or arguing
at Sean or argue. I'm done with all
that. I'm done arguing with these counts
on YouTube. I was done with it a long
time. I've already been sat on YouTube
trying to stick up for my family cuz the
pictures getting put up. Yeah, it's been
I'm all about banner, but this shit's real PJ,
you know. This shit's completely [ __ ]
real. I'm not scared of anyone in this
community either way. I'm just saying
putting that out there hands down there now.
But you I'm not going to go out there
fight people who I don't know who I'm
never going to meet PJ
>> and you're sadly arguing with people who
you don't know giving these people your life
>> your life and that was my biggest
mistake as well is be giving people
information about my life doxing myself
and all that that's the biggest mistake
I've done on YouTube
>> you know
>> but you s on YouTube laughing at people
on YouTube telling these people to come
to you for fights and [ __ ] like that and
all that. Look, you know, yeah, I
obviously do the same, but I do it for a
reason like money mike which encounter
my mom threatening to choke acid off for women
stuff like that. That's the reason.
But your reason, what's your reason to
be in this community? Really?
>> I just come on here now and then, money,
>> it's not about now and then. Bro, is it
PJ? It's about what you're doing on
YouTube. Who you reacting to? Who you
calling and what? What? You're not doing
actual content. You're just
>> content. I do content on another channel.
>> On another channel. It doesn't matter if
you're on another channel or not. You're
just reflecting as well as leaves on yourself.
You know what I mean? You're arguing
back with people you don't know. Why do you g
Why? Why? Why do you care what London
London Taylor thinks about this girl
from America? He's going to bring this
girl up cuz he knows he's going to piss
you off. It doesn't piss me off though.
It make No, no, it it makes him look
obsessed. It doesn't piss me off.
>> It's going to make you look more
obsessed when you're bringing this
American girl up still on your channel with him.
You don't get it.
>> Look, this person is true. Look. Yeah.
Why is Monty being too faced? He didn't
have this energy when he was in the pub
laughing with you. Yeah. Monty's always
been like that. No, no, no, no. Like I
said to PJ, appreciate that. Like with
PJ, I you know, appreciate PJ being
there, but when it's on YouTube and he's
getting me on to YouTube, do arguing
with people, getting me into fall
dragging me on to YouTube. Yeah, PJ, I'm
not saying PJ is a good l, but he knows
how to, you know, but when he's sat on
here reflecting to these people, he's
showing himself [ __ ] hope. He's
showing me up like he's my [ __ ]
supposed to be my mate and he's sat here
calling my misses dog ugly
and he's supposed to be my mate and he's
calling my misses and all that. Look,
that's not a mate when he's sitting here
calling my misses ugly.
You know what I mean? What I wouldn't if
PJ was going out with a woman in a
wheelchair, I'd be like, "Go on your PJ,
man. She's she's pretty fit."
You know what I mean? I'd be [ __ ] I I
won't bring her up and call her ugly.
>> Oh, PJ I don't know. He has to, doesn't he?
>> You know, if PJ was a mate, he wouldn't
call my Mes ugly or whatever. It's not
my fault if Natalie they don't want to
meet him or if Natalie was playing games
with him or whatever back then. That's
between them and not myself or whatever.
At the end of the day, Natalie with me
and if PJ's going to call Natalie, I'm
going to stick up for Natalie on that.
PJ shouldn't be bringing up my
girlfriend like that.
And Natalie's not ugly either way. I
reckon that Natalie is one of the best
looking women in this community to be
honest with you.
>> I bother from ugly or whatever. I bothered.
>> Yeah, I know
for you, mate.
>> That's what I'm saying to PJ. I
appreciate PJ for being there. But if PJ
is going to rub that day in my face all
the time, I just give him the money in your face.
>> Well, you do feel like you are PJ
because obviously, yeah, you will. Okay.
But at the end of the day, you know,
when you're dragging Natalie into this
[ __ ] and you're dragging me into
your [ __ ] as well,
it's not fair on me or Natalie. Do you
know what I mean? Your bullshit's your
own [ __ ] on YouTube.
>> Exactly. You get yourself into your
[ __ ] You stick up for yourself. I'll be
myself. No, PJ. You want me to be
myself? I won't be this little clown on
YouTube. Yeah. You have a normal
conversation with you. What these
people's never seen me do. But let's
have a proper conversation then. Yeah.
You know what I mean? So that that that
night. Yeah. You were there. Yeah.
>> Appreciate it. Yeah. So why would you
drag Natalie up and all this now with
London Taylor? Obviously. Yeah. Yeah.
Understandablely saying, "Yeah, you you
met Natalie." But the way you said that,
you didn't say Natalie. You called her
ugly. And why would you say would why
would you you bring another girl up with
just her name and then then you
mentioned Natalie and called her B ugly.
>> Yeah. I'm going. Yeah, cuz I I was going
I was all the women that he's begs on
[ __ ] YouTube. Is it
>> before I met you?
>> That's it. Jane. Jane. You're making
Jane. You just bring Jane's name up.
That's it. You didn't call Jane ugly.
You didn't say nothing about it.
>> Oh, no. But you didn't say that in the
conversation. You You just said Natalie.
Ugly Natalie or whatever you said. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. And so
I swear to God.
>> So that's supposed to be your mate's [ __ ] >> Mes. Yeah.
>> What? What? Why would you call her ugly
then, PJ? What What is the reason to
call Natalie ugly? Like
>> it doesn't matter what I think, does it?
point is I'm supposed to be your mate to
be called me ugly. I don't care if I'm ugly anyway.
It doesn't matter what I have your back.
>> Yeah, but it does make me think about
it, PJ. It does make me think about it.
Really? It does because one, you
supposed to be my mate. Two, you call
him my bes. That makes me of course I
care about care about it. What makes you
think that she's ugly? Why did he say
why? Why did he say it? That doesn't
matter what he said.
He shouldn't say it because that's your
mate. His mates miss it. So why would he say it?
>> I know.
>> You got to have a reason for
>> Well, you you got to have a reason for
saying it. That's what I'm saying. You
got to have a reason for saying that.
But what is your reason for calling?
That's what I'm saying. It doesn't
matter, does it? Oh,
>> it does matter. It doesn't matter. It
It does matter PJ. It matters to me. It
matters to me. Of course it does matter.
It's my misses. And you supposed to be
my friend, but then you call him my M is
[ __ ] ugly. But Jane not ugly.
>> Jane is ugly. Jane is ugly.
>> Yeah, but you didn't put it out there.
You didn't say Jane's ugly. You just said that.
>> I've said it before though. I have said it before.
>> Yeah, but you didn't say it straight up
to me. That's not what I'm getting at
either way. But what I'm getting at is
why would you call my Message ugly?
That's what I'm getting at.
>> That's what I'm saying. Why would you call
>> You get it?
>> Yeah. Obviously.
>> So that's what I'm getting at. And
that's what I want to answer. You know,
not at all.
You know what I mean?
No. No. You get cosmic kitty.
Yeah. You get who's ugly. Yeah.
>> I think I think every woman in the
community is ugly.
>> Not I can't say that every woman's ugly
in this community,
you know. But there is ugly women in
this community. Yeah, we agree. But not
every woman in this community is going
to be ugly.
I'm not going to be based on that. I'm
just going to be normal.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Go for it. I'm just going to
be normal and normal guy conversations
now. Yeah. No, I can't sit here and call
every woman ugly on this community cuz
not all women are going to be ugly in
this community. It's the same as men.
Not all men are going to be ugly, but
there is a lot of [ __ ] old fat men in
this community. That's what I do agree on,
you know. But at the end of the day,
when you sitting here calling Natalie
ugly when she's when you know 100% she's not ugly.
>> You know what I mean?
These people are saying she's ugly.
>> These people, EJ, these people [ __ ]
bing Natalie. These people, why does you
think that these people want to meet
Natalie and all that? You only call
Natalie ugly when you're in a
relationship or whatever else like that.
All the down these people [ __ ] fancy
the [ __ ] out of Natalie
and you know that yourself PJ come on.
>> I'm just saying what they're saying is it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Course but he down
they they why the people sit there and
have pictures of Naked and and be
watching her and all that lot and bust
off her and all that lot. They throw it
because they won't go out with them.
These people throw women if they don't
want them. That's why they throw Natal
and the only they like now. They look at
Lord J when Lord J when when people
said, "Oh, will you be playing Natalie
again?" And Lord J and said, "Well, if
if Natalie breaks up with [ __ ] again,"
and then they start paying her again.
But on the SL kind of thing,
me and Natalie were watching.
You know what I mean? These people have
been slightly like [ __ ] PJ. They
don't care about Natalie. They don't
care about you. They don't care about
me. They don't care about what you
[ __ ] think, PJ. Yeah.
>> Put it that way now. Yeah. They don't
care about your little cord approaching
videos. What you do? What they ask about
is you embarrassing the [ __ ] out
yourself doing that [ __ ]
And that's it. Hi, buddy.
You know what I mean?
>> Get off YouTube.
>> One second. >> No.
>> Good morning. Hold on. I'm reading something.
I wouldn't spit on Natalie G like 100
people use other way you use other one
sitting there on the channel watching
them pay get pissed that she go all lash
everybody drunk how would you all do that
obviously of course you all like it and
you all know what Natalie does when
she's pissed hate this community
>> I even know what Natalie does when she's
pissed for [ __ ] sake but all know that
you all cush Natalie to do that when
she's drunk, but you all know what you're doing.
And it's the same [ __ ] um nothing.
>> Watch when that Joe comes back on here.
I'm going to [ __ ] roast him, Mr. B.
You know that Joe account. I'm going to
roast him, bro. When he comes back on here,
>> I hate this community money. I I [ __ ] hate it.
Do you know when you're sat here
watching other people's channels when
people are live and it's sat there
arguing? You actually see things what
you what you don't see. It's weird. It's
pathetic. It's weird.
It's weird to [ __ ] Normal as adults on
YouTube or going on adults arguing like
[ __ ] It's weird to [ __ ]
>> It is weird.
>> No, it [ __ ] is. It's completely weird
to [ __ ] Arguing over what? What? What
are we all arguing over anyway? We all
aring for being all spastics and all that.
You know what I mean? I know that we all
argue about money.
>> I don't get you know what I don't do.
You know what I don't get, Monty? Yeah.
Is why do these people right type one
thing to you on a chat, they try to be
nice to you, then on another chat
channel they slag you off. That's what I don't get.
>> It's cold licking ass PJ like you do
when I'm not here. Yeah. Okay.
>> You know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> You're just like you slap Natalie off
when I weren't here. >> Yeah.
>> It's just the same like that.
>> You know what I mean?
I went here and you just called the [ __ ]
out of Natalie.
No, that that's my message. And
>> yeah, that Jo when that Joe when that Jo
comes back on here, I'm going to [ __ ]
watch what I do to him, bro. When I when
I cuz I've been seeing some of his
comments. This is why he hasn't been on
today. This is why he's not been on my
live cuz he knows when he comes back on
here, I'm going to tell him about
himself. I'm going to [ __ ] you know
what? Yeah. [ __ ] these people now,
Monty. You know, I'm going to go I'm
going to leave this community with a [ __ ] bang.
You know what I mean? Yeah. They all do
it. Especially that Ricky Mill, bro.
I've caught them out. And the thing is,
Monty, these people will never say
anything to my face. Never.
These people can think that I'm a big
ass [ __ ] in here, but real life and the
most I'm clever as [ __ ]
>> Maybe I can't read. All right, but I'm
smart. I'm nothing like I'm on YouTube.
>> Watch when that little [ __ ] comes back
on here. And you know what I mean? You
know that Ricky, he's still he's still
listen, he comes on here snaking me, but
the guy's still a virgin. He's never
even been seen with a [ __ ] woman. And
he comes on saying about what women
want, what women [ __ ] don't want. And
bro, the guy's [ __ ] probably never
even seen a woman naked.
>> Okay, just think about think about this
PJ. Yeah, I got into say like obviously, you know,
say I got into a new relationship and I
and it weren't Natalie. Yeah. And it was
someone a random ass woman. Yeah.
>> I've seen him I've seen him snake me,
bro. I've seen him do it on a few
channels. Listen, you see
>> know this, no that. What have I got? You
don't know what I've got. No, it's all
you have, Russell. That's why you hide
behind fake accounts doing what you do
for years. Listen. Listen. Right. One
second, Monty. Yeah. I've been on this
for years. Yeah. Have I Have I posted videos, Monty?
>> [ __ ] a day.
>> I've posted videos. What I've done.
Listen, Russell. YouTube is all you
have. That's all you have. That's why
you, you know, these accounts, right?
Like, come on. You know, it's like the
same three people, same skinned people,
fat, ugly people, no life. That's all
you've got. All you have is YouTube. You
people can't even take a day off of
YouTube. That's how bad it is. Don't
[ __ ] try to talk about other people.
>> Yeah. Put it this way. I'm just put it
this way, PJ. You click you reading them
comments out here. You've already read
them comments comments out ages ago. I
don't know why you read them comments.
That's what I'm saying to you. So, so
she was repeating your channel.
>> And that's Terry, by the way, as well.
That Russell will count as Terry. I just
clocked it. But yeah, anyways,
>> at the end of the page. Yeah. Yeah. This
[ __ ] It's just weird. Yeah, it's
>> This community is so weird.
>> Okay. Okay. Say this. Yeah. Just say
this, right? I just put it like this.
Yeah. Just say if I was just say if I
was in a relationship. Yeah. And it
wasn't with Natalie. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Russell is Terry by the way. Yeah. Go on.
>> Right. And it and it wasn't with
Natalie. Yeah. And it was with just a
normal normal woman. Yeah. And I was
going live on YouTube doing this on
YouTube. What would she actually think?
Lucky enough with I'm lucky enough I'm
with Natalie off YouTube so she knows.
But if I'm with a woman, you're going to
think, "What the [ __ ] is she doing? This
is [ __ ] weird." You know what I mean?
It's weird. It's [ __ ] weird.
Lucky enough, I wish Natalie Natalie's
off YouTube so she knows what this is about.
>> I'm just hoping one day I go live and
these people just don't join.
>> That will never happen. Yeah, these
people will always join. You make it off
yourself. These will people will be there.
>> These people are supposed to have jobs.
>> It doesn't matter if they got jobs or
not. Some of these probably have got
jobs. Some of them haven't got jobs. I
know that [ __ ] uh Grace.
Grace. He's got a job. He's a bus
driver. I know that he he's got a job.
That grace, he he's a I know that he works.
>> These people ain't got a job.
>> Some of them will do, some of them
won't, but a lot of them don't. A lot of
>> You know, I agree with that. And I agree
with that. A lot of them don't because a
lot of these are on 24 hours a day from
from night till morning.
Don't know what honestly I don't know
what they get out of it.
>> Most of these don't go to bed. Whoever's
live, they don't go to bed till 600 7:00
in the morning. It's like weird [ __ ]
entertainment. Wait, we're just dumb.
We're dumber and dumber. PJ just entertaining them.
>> I'm waiting for that. I'm waiting for
that job account to come back on here. Bro,
>> you're not wait You're not waiting for
no one PJ cuz no one's going to meet
you. This is where you self-reflecting
by re reflecting back to le. I'm done with it.
>> I'm done. I'm done with these now. PJ,
they draging on their own. They come on
call me what the [ __ ] they wanted, but
they getting kicked.
I'm not I'm not jumping on normal normal
panels. Not even [ __ ]
George's panel. John West. George. We're
not even jumping on these panel no more.
That's John West name by the way, George.
I'm not even jumping on his panel no
more. Why the [ __ ] am I going to jump on
anyone's panels and do what? What more?
I'm done with it. It's embarrassing to
[ __ ] I'm a 35y old man. Not on YouTube
with a bunch of [ __ ] fatties and
[ __ ] argue with you. It's not
>> But it's not worth it. Well, I am
basically you when you call him my mix, he's ugly
you know what I mean?
At the end of the day, I don't know
these people. These people don't meet
know me. They can sit there and say that
I've been kicked out of Manchester. They
can they can they can say it all along.
I haven't been kicked out of Manchester.
You know that that only knows that
they all think that I' been kicked out
of Manchester. They don't know me. P
they think that lads me on the picture
what's going around on the internet.
It's not me. You know what I mean? These
are just the idiots on YouTube who
you're entertaining. They don't know
you. They actually think they know you
and put [ __ ] up about you and that's it.
Deep down. Does that bother you? Yeah,
it does mean. No, not exactly. It
>> doesn't bother me. I laugh at it.
>> They can call me on here.
>> They They can call me and put me up as
much as they want.
They really can, but they don't know me
on here. They really don't.
If they think about being kicked out of
Rodale, let them think that. Well, really,
>> you know what I mean?
>> If if they think you're skin, let them
think you're skin. Why does that bother you?
>> Never skin me, mate. You
>> if you're reacting back to the skin
comments and going on and on and on
about what you want, that's repeating the situation. >> Yeah.
You know, you know I'm not it
if you are or not. Money doesn't make
the world go around. Happiness does really [ __ ]
money's just [ __ ] money PGA. He's
[ __ ] paper. He's just of a tree. That's it.
What's money got to do with anything?
Money's not life. Money. Yeah.
>> When Joe comes on here, I'm going to
start on him. by the way. That's
probably why he's not been on here today
cuz uh yeah, he's a [ __ ] talker behind people's back.
>> Obviously, money gets you what you need
in life, like food, rent, clothes, and
stuff like that. Yeah, that's it. Money,
money, happiness. Money, you don't have
to pay for happiness.
Happiness is free.
And money doesn't make you happy. But
when you're talking to me about money,
money, don't I hate money. Money means
[ __ ] to me. Just remember that. So when
you say all your skin, yeah, I'm proud
of it. I love it.
That's what I think about money. PJ
I You don't need money to be happy.
>> And also you said I when I was calling
Natalie G ugly, you called [ __ ] Izzy ugly.
>> I don't know. I'm
come on P.
This is not bad.
So it's all
going out with
>> Yeah, but we done stuff.
>> It doesn't matter if you done stuff or
not. You were going out with her. I
would have called her but you was going
out with me. Exactly. How can you be?
They're horrible, aren't they?
You can see the westernity in their eyes.
And when you're in a relationship,
>> and when you're in a relationship, you
don't sit there and say, "Yeah, she's
good looking." Oh, yeah. Oh, she's nice.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. When you're in a
relationship, are you ugly? You only
have your eyes on one woman. So, if you
said, "Oh, is she good-looking to me?"
No, she's ugly. The only one my eyes are
on is Natalie the best looking woman in
this planet. That's it.
>> You know what I mean?
>> But when you're putting out [ __ ] Are
you people making dog accounts or weirdos, bro?
You're [ __ ] weirdos.
>> What do you mean dog accounts?
>> [ __ ] diesel accounts. They're weirdos.
>> Yeah, it don't bother me anyways. That
[ __ ] It bothers them.
Oh, that Joe's a snake. Nicolo, I've
caught him talking [ __ ] on other
channels about me, bro. I'm going to
give him I'm going to [ __ ] ruin him
when he when he comes back on here.
That's probably why he's not been on for
a few days to be fair. He's getting
ruined. He's pulling a Ricky Milling
account like what Ricky Millington done.
Yeah, he's pulling a He's pulling a Ricky Millington account, bro.
What he done?
I'd love to get one of my I'd love to
get my hands on one of these people. You
know that money?
>> Yeah. I don't see any of these like
account man then. But I don't read the
comments anyway. So
>> it's like I don't understand. It's like
that Nicolo. Yeah. Nicolo. It's like
that Ricky Millington. Yeah. Trying to
speak about women, bro. The guy's
probably never even seen a woman naked,
bro. He lives in the worst place in
England ever. Skin in his 40s. Got no
[ __ ] life trying to talk about other
people. It's the same with that Ricky Millington account.
You know what I mean, bro? It's the same
with that [ __ ] Ricky Millington
[ __ ] never seen a woman naked coming
on here trying to [ __ ] talk about
what people have, what people don't have
in some [ __ ] loser in his 40s.
I mean, stop showing stupid amounts of
money, Joe. Come on. Natalie's just
severing something later on cuz he'sing.
>> That's fine, bro. It's like, what is all
of this showing £1,500
that this Joe's doing? Why don't you
show us your [ __ ] £10,000 that we've
been waiting for? Why don't you show us
this £10,000 that you've been waiting
that we've been waiting for? Cuz you
ain't got it.
You know, cuz you ain't got it. Stop
showing some bum, 1500 lb bum chains,
bro, that everyone's [ __ ] got. Yeah.
Show us your [ __ ] £10,000.
Smokey B's done it. Why don't you do it now?
Because you ain't got it. You're [ __ ] skinned. Simple.
Yeah, he's not been on for a few days.£300
£300 in, £,500 out. Do you think anyone cares
about your shitty little 1,500 pound?
You know what I mean?
Why don't you show us [ __ ]
Why don't you show us um £10,000? Oh, [ __ ]
They're all [ __ ] snakes, bro.
Absolute snakes on there, aren't they?
I'm going to make him come in the
hangouts as well. And I'm going to talk
about his [ __ ] he's [ __ ] ugly
misses and he's [ __ ] fat. And I'm
going to talk about his kids as well.
I think he said he has kids. So, I'll
talk about his kids.
seen some of your comments I didn't even
see before. Social anxiety, bro. I never
had any kind of anxiety in my life. Not
like you people, bro. If you can't even
come on the [ __ ] hangouts, you're that scared.
You're that scared.
You know what I mean?
Oh, is that Mike snaking as well?
Oh, money Mike snaking also. Okay. Well,
he's going to be getting it as well when
he comes back on. That's already two
that's getting it. Okay. I've seen his comments.
Oh [ __ ] he's doing it as well. Okay.
Well, that's two on the list.
Yep. He's getting it as well when he
comes back on.
I don't know why these people do this
[ __ ] but they're not going to be able
to finish it. Honestly, I don't.
Yeah, I'm going to talk about
everything. His sister, their kids,
everything. Watch. Watch when he comes
back on here, bro.
Watch when they both come back on here. Watch.
[ __ ] skimp virgin channel in a
[ __ ] bed sit writing a load of [ __ ]
If you've got anything to say, come on
here and say it. Better yet, come on and Yeah.
Yeah. Stop talking about yourself.
Yeah. Oh, [ __ ] My eyelash went in my
eyebrow. Damn. Yeah. Stop talking about yourself.
All right then, PJ, put it this way. Why
do you hate Natalie then so much to for
you to call her?
>> Doesn't matter, does it?
>> But it does matter.
>> I never said I hate Natalie.
>> If you're calling her ugly, you
basically don't like her. >> Yeah.
>> So why don't you like her?
>> Cuz she's just not my type.
Oh, it's not about because he's not your type.
>> It is.
So, so, so
>> N's not your friend. Would you not as a friend? No.
It doesn't matter if she's not your type or not. It matter.
So basically, so so you so you got to
have a tie for to a woman to be a cring. Yeah.
>> How was she my friend? She never met me.
>> Uh no, meaning online like socialize
with or whatever.
That's what I'm getting at.
>> I never said that.
>> You don't No, basically you called her
ugly. So what I'm trying to say you
don't understand, do you?
>> Do you not do you not like that? No,
>> I No. So, so you don't like her one little bit?
>> Not really. No, >> I
don't know. And she And she told
everyone she was going to stab me up. So
why would I?
>> She going to stab you up.
>> Stand me up.
>> Oh, stand you up.
>> Oh, like stand up. And you're like,
"Yeah, but put it this way." What woman?
You know what I mean?
>> You know what I'm saying?
>> Yeah. But Pia, why why do you think she
would have done that?
>> That's what she told everyone.
>> Yeah, but why why do you think she would
have done that anyways?
>> I don't know.
I think she would have met you PJ to be
honest with you.
Yeah, she wanted my to
>> No, I don't I don't know PJ but no
I don't know PJ that that between you
and N I don't know what N thinking about
that cle you know why I can't speak
Fortnetly on that
>> you know what I mean
>> no PJ I don't know what you mean.
What I want to know is Natalie Natalie's
not really called you or
someone said that Natalie wanted to
groom PJ when he was just a little baby elephant.
But listen, when that money m comes back
on here, when that money mike and Joe
comes back on it, I'll be starting on
both of them as well because I've seen
their comments. So, yeah, I've seen
their comments now. So, it's all good.
>> What money makes?
>> Yeah, him as well. Yeah,
>> he's a money man.
>> When they come back, when they come back
on it, they're going to be getting
owned. So, it's all good. I'm going to
>> I will meet him. I will meet him.
>> Yeah. Go back to Birmingham. I'll tell
him about his I'll tell him about his
ugly by no self and his ugly penguin
looking sister and and their [ __ ]
ugly kids as well. >> Yeah.
>> No, leave kids out. Leave kids out of the situation.
>> You know what I'm saying, bro? >> Yeah.
>> No, I don't. But when it comes to kids
big run up into the situation,
>> you know what I'm saying, bro? So, yeah. Yeah.
>> So why would you bring your kids up or
someone's kids up about people's um
people's family and people's kids?
>> Yeah. That don't mean the right for you
to do it back. You just need them to do that now.
>> That's Terry by the way that I can. So obvious
Russell go on your your real account
Terry. It's definitely definitely you. I
can smell you on my see some of these
people Monty. Right. You can actually
smell them a mile off. I don't know if
you you noticed that.
Do you you know who it is behind the accounts? >> Yeah.
>> I can smell this [ __ ] of mile and it's Terry 100%.
>> Tell you how I know it is. But I know.
>> Is it Jerry? Yeah. Huh? Is it Cherry one?
Yeah, it's Yeah, I just call >> Yeah,
it is you. It is definitely definitely
But yeah, I'm going to start that money
working at Joe.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] I'm not like you,
Money. I I'll go to Birmingham and meet
him, Money. I'm not like you.
You know what I mean?
>> Going back and forth, back and forth.
[ __ ] this. You know,
>> I'm not getting involved in your
[ __ ] no more.
>> I don't want you to get involved. I
don't want you to get involved. It's my
[ __ ] I don't want you to get involved. Good.
>> I was involved in it when I was with
you. If there would have done something,
but I'm not getting involved in any of
this no more.
You should just saw how scared he was
when he was in London. He was so scared, bro. Like
>> [ __ ] to deal with with Money M and Timmy and that.
>> He was so scared. Don't [ __ ] listen.
Don't [ __ ] talk [ __ ] on another
channel, then come and lick my ass. I
hate that, bro. I swear to God, I hate
it. You don't understand. It annoys me,
bro. Only that annoys me. It doesn't
matter what they do or what they say.
Like on here, like they're self
projecting comments, but that's one
thing I I don't like, bro.
that and the [ __ ] um
that and um when they try to pretend
they haven't seen things, you know what
I mean? That's the only thing that
really annoys me, bro. Nothing else.
I hate that behavior, bro. I hate the
snaky behavior. I hate it, bro. It's
like that really Ricky [ __ ] Milling
Virgin. You know what? I'm going to do a
video on this, bro. I'm just going to
call them all out. I've had enough of
it, bro. I swear to God. Yeah,
I've had [ __ ] enough of it, bro.
Swear to God, I have. You know
It's like that Joe. He's just some fat
[ __ ] in real life. But you can tell he's
fat. Look at his hands, bro. You can
tell he's [ __ ] fat. He's just some
stupid fat [ __ ]
Ain't got a [ __ ] life. Showing,500.
What the [ __ ] bro? Is your life? What
the [ __ ] is your [ __ ] life? You know
what I mean?
I'm going to I'm going to start
something. Daft, Nicolola. I'm going to
start on him, bro. Yeah, I watch.
And what I mean by I don't gamble
anymore, bro. Do I have [ __ ] loan
sharks on my [ __ ] door? No. Am I in
debt like you? No.
You stupid [ __ ] [ __ ]
Am I in Am I in debt like you? No.
Did somebody put a [ __ ] petrol bomb
through my [ __ ] door? No, they never.
So, shut the [ __ ] up, you stupid [ __ ] Huh?
You know what I'm saying, bro?
No. And I'm not like, by the way, by
lone sharks, I mean [ __ ] Money Mike.
He's got he had lone sharks that he's
going at, bro.
Yeah. I'm going to do a video on them, bro. Watch.
I'm going to I'm going to say to that
Joe as well. Yeah. To to show where he is.
What's the day tomorrow? Friday. I can
go anywhere tomorrow.
I can literally go anywhere tomorrow.
You know, I'm free tomorrow. I've got
the money. I'm I'm I'm I'm free to go
anywhere I want tomorrow.
So, if he really wants to actually say
anything to anyone's face, I'll travel
wherever. I'll give him that same
treatment that I gave that Ricky Milling.
I'll give you that special offer and I
don't and I don't even have a rail card
anymore. And you know, if you're not
going to do it, then there's literally
no point in keep going on a on a
diagnosed autistic person's [ __ ] channel.
You know what I'm saying? There's no
point going on a diagnosed autistic
person's channel venting if you're not
going to say anything to anyone's face
if you're not going to do anything.
You know what I'm saying? embarrassing
yourself every day on YouTube, you know?
Well, I'm going to own all of them, bro.
And that mic,
stupid [ __ ] albino looking [ __ ] Yeah,
you're going to go on a diagnosed
autistic person channel and try and talk
[ __ ] about me when there's literally a
platform right here to do it on, you know?
But these people really got no shame,
Nicolo. You know the thing is, man,
these people really got no shame. It's
the same thing with that all night spaz.
He's still doing his [ __ ] years later.
I ran him out of Scotland two times and
he's still coming on here doing the same [ __ ]
Do you know what I'm saying? He's still
on here doing the same [ __ ] Like these
people really got no shame. Imagine
being run out of your own country two
times, bro. [ __ ] embarrassing, bro. Pathetic.
Yeah, I'm coming off this [ __ ] soon
anyways, bro. Now that Silver Surf is
not a snake. He's not a snake. He says
it on here. He says it behind people's
back. It's the snake. And I don't like,
bro. That's the [ __ ] that annoys me.
Ricky Millin, he's never even seen a
[ __ ] woman naked except his [ __ ]
mom when he come out of her trying to
[ __ ] talk [ __ ] about people. Watch,
bro. I'm gonna do a video on them, bro. Watch.
>> Monty finds this community funny in it.
I don't know how he finds this community funny, you know.
Hold on, Grezy. Was I off here for two weeks?
Was I off here for 3 weeks?
I'll just [ __ ] come off here, Nicolo,
and say, "Fuck the lot of you."
I was arguing with LT for like [ __ ] an hour.
That Jo is just some fat fat ugly old
man, bro. Can't even [ __ ] talk. You know, you know,
that's why that Joe's not been on here.
That's what it's remember that [ __ ]
There used to be an account, right,
Nicolo? If you if you're an old school
watcher, you would know it. It's called
uh what was the [ __ ] account called
now? He was some Canadian living in Birmingham.
Mr. B knows the name. What was that
[ __ ] account called now?
Oh, what was it called?
Vary. That was it. Very. And he used to
come on here and he used to lick ass and
then um I caught him talking [ __ ] one
day behind my back. He never come back
on ever again. [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
Absolute stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah,
very 08. It was
09. Yeah, you might remember that count.
He done the same thing.
These [ __ ] this fat virgins sat on
YouTube skin ain't got a life.
Imagine having to show,500 pound off.
Yeah, he goes on I saw him on Lord Jay's
the other day though.
Yeah, he was actually all right. Yeah.
Yeah. He was on Lord A the other day.
He was trying to say, "Oh, it's not
women that that are the problem because
other guys do it."
He used to be the same. Oh, well, other
people. Other people do it. Other
people. Oh, [ __ ] other people. Every [ __ ] time.
He used to be another one. Other people.
Other people. Other people.
[ __ ] idiot, bro. I remember always
having the same conversation with that um Yeah. Damn it.
Yeah. It's like that [ __ ] um LT was
trying to say that I'm an incel cuz I
said that you can see the westernity in
these women's eyes because you literally can.
Any any different opinion you have
nowadays apparently you're a [ __ ]
you're a [ __ ] incel.
You're an incel yet you've had more
women than all of these people that are
sticking up for women. But you're the
incel. Yeah. Uh-huh. Yeah. Yeah. I'm the Yeah,
I told the LT today, I'm not scared of
you, brother. I've never been scared of
you. The only reason I didn't do
anything to you, brother, is because I
had so much to lose. Money, house. Well,
the money from the house and the house,
you know, like, bro, no one's scared of
you one little bit.
You need to go back to doing this [ __ ]
to females and not me, bro. Cuz you
don't scare me one little bit.
What is it? The side men that's doing
it, Greavesy. Right.
Yeah, that's the side men doing that. No. Yep.
He sticks up for this [ __ ] USA is he
doesn't seem to know that what she done was wrong.
He seems to think it's normal.
You know what I hate, Griezy? I'll tell
you one thing I hate since we're talking
about this, right?
This whole saying, "Oh, they don't owe
you anything. They don't owe you
anything." They seem to think that
justifies shitty behavior. They seem to
think that justifies ghosting. Oh, what?
So, they don't owe you anything. So,
what? You couldn't write a message that
takes two to 5 seconds because they
don't owe you anything? Huh? Huh? Oh,
well, that explains it, doesn't it?
Yeah. You know what I'm saying? It
doesn't make no sense.
And these people use it, right?
They use it in the wrong context.
You know what I'm saying? Like they just
I just don't agree with it. I don't
agree with it, bro.
I don't know if you noticed that.
Like, yeah. Okay. Wow. They don't owe
you anything. Wow. So, what that means,
be a [ __ ] instead of just being there's
such a thing as common courtesy. You
know what I'm saying?
And they don't he doesn't seem to think
that USA is he done anything wrong. Nicolola,
she literally did.
Not that I give a [ __ ] but I don't know
how it come up in the conversation, but
yes, the [ __ ] did.
What the [ __ ] How did they not do anything wrong?
You understand what I'm saying?
Yeah. Imagine you did go around doing that.
Imagine you did go around being a [ __ ]
and say, "Don't owe you anything."
Yeah. You see what I mean? Let's put the
shoe on the other foot. You know what I'm saying?
It doesn't work like that. It's using
the wrong context.
You know what I'm saying?
They seem to go around being a [ __ ]
right? And think they get out of it by
saying they don't owe you anything.
That's just not the way it works, you know?
Yeah. There was a guy who who who tried
starting who tried starting [ __ ] on a
bus today, Nicolo,
you know, and I [ __ ] put him in his
[ __ ] place with some old [ __ ] man.
He was being a [ __ ] [ __ ] I told him
about himself. [ __ ] come didn't want
any of it, did he? Was that socially
acceptable? Was that socially
Since you want to keep saying saying
things socially acceptable, you [ __ ]
diagnosed autistic [ __ ] little
virgin. Yeah, that's what you need to
start asking people, right? Even even
these social experiments. Is that so
clown? You know what I mean? [ __ ] virgin.
You know what I'm saying? Is that
socially acceptable, mate? What about
when you get [ __ ] [ __ ] on the
road? Is that socially acceptable? [ __ ] virgin.
Could you imagine you actually do that though?
Don't know you even.
Oh, I don't know anything.
Don't know you anything. Imagine.
Yeah. Well, if you was doing Uber, you
would be dealing with them greasy. I
mean, is that socially acceptable?
You know, all of these people right that
say that is socially acceptable and try
to sort of patronize you. You should ask
them if that's socially acceptable.
But these people do it.
You should ask them, bro. You should ask
them. See what it's there.
Yeah. I put it on some guy today on the [ __ ] bus.
She shat his [ __ ] pants though,
didn't he? Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
And everyone on the bus agreed with me. Grievesy.
Um, so basically, yeah, I was basically
sat down with someone and then the guy
was like, "Oh, um, yeah, can this woman
sit down? It's the priority scene." And
I said, I was thinking, "She's not old.
She's not disabled."
Um, so why don't you mind your own
business? Um, sort of thing. And then he
was trying to like swear and I swore him
back. I said, "Why don't I don't [ __ ]
off you prick?" I said, "If you got
anything to say, let's get off the bus
now." Then he shot himself. [ __ ] went
to the back of the [ __ ] bus.
Yeah. Went to the back of the [ __ ]
bus and then um
then he just shut his mouth. And I said
to the person I was with like, "Do you
think I was in the right?" And every
single person on the bus agreed with me.
They said, "Oh yeah, we thought you was
right. Yeah, you're right."
Like everyone agreed with me.
It reminded me of the um it reminded me
of the Uber days. Entitled [ __ ]
starting [ __ ] they can't finish.
What is the point? There's just no point
in it. Why? What if you're in a bad
mood? Why piss yourself off more? Piss
someone else off more and you're not
going to finish it.
It's [ __ ] It's insane, isn't it? It's
so mad. They're so entitled, these
[ __ ] He was an old He was an older
fellow as well. He was quite old. So
it's not like it was the younger generation, you know,
and he said, "Oh, you social." I said,
"I don't need to show no [ __ ] respect
to you. Who the [ __ ] are you?" I just
just tell him about himself. He said,
"You're a prick." I said, "You're the
[ __ ] prick. Let's get off the [ __ ] bus now."
That's what I said to him. I said,
"Let's get off the bus now and see what
you're saying off the bus. Let's go.
Come on. Come on." Then he shot himself.
What the [ __ ]
Mind your own [ __ ] business. And if
you're not willing to do that and you
want to start, finish it. Don't start
[ __ ] yourself. You know what I mean?
So yeah, just so many entitled people in
this country. You should ask these
people, Greasy, if that's socially
acceptable to start getting in uh to
start um getting involved in other people's business.
You know, you know what I'm saying?
You know what I'm saying? You should ask
them if that's socially acceptable.
Maybe I'll do a video to a virgin boy
asking if asking him if all of these
things are socially acceptable.
[ __ ] try and tell me what's [ __ ]
socially acceptable or not, you [ __ ]
little virgin [ __ ]
No, I'm not going traveling again in
this country ever again.
But it weren't grievy. She wasn't
pregnant or old or disabled. That's why
I had a problem with it.
You know what I'm saying? It weren't
like they were actually they were a
priority. Then I would have understood it.
You know what I'm saying? then I
actually would have uh understood it.
I could be like, "Oh, okay. Well, you
know, if somebody was pregnant, but they
wasn't, though, that's the whole thing
is they actually wasn't."
So then I had to tell the [ __ ] [ __ ]
about himself. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
So many [ __ ] in this country, bro.
So many so many [ __ ]
You got [ __ ] 9year-old kids trying to
steal bikes and [ __ ] Oh my god.
Where's the deterrent? Eh, none.
So many [ __ ]
[ __ ] do you care what's socially
acceptable? I don't give a [ __ ]
Do you care what's socially acceptable?
Yeah. If I punched that man, he would
have probably died. If I gave him one
punch, bro, he probably would have died.
He probably would have died.
But this little autistic virgin wants to
tell you what's socially acceptable or
not. What's socially acceptable? Being
addicted to Tik Tok, looking like an NPC.
Is is that socially acceptable? Being a
robot on your phone?
Uh is that is that socially acceptable?
But why would you care about what's
socially acceptable? You don't like
people. This society's [ __ ] I
literally don't care what's socially
acceptable or not. I literally don't
care. I think most people in this
country are [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah. The bus was packed. Everyone heard
it and they all agreed with me cuz they
overheard me. I said, "Oh, do you do you
think I was right?" And they all
overheard me and said, "Yeah, I think
you was." I don't I think this country
is [ __ ] up. Full of [ __ ]
I'd love for them to think that I'm uh
that I'm not socially what I do is not socially acceptable
because I don't care about anyone in
this country. I think they're all [ __ ]
And if that man would have got a punch
there, he would have died. I'm telling
you, he would have died.
Well, then if Laney wanted a a seat,
then Laney would have asked for a seat
and not some random person getting in
other people's business like what he
done, which is typical with these
[ __ ] in this country.
So, do you know what I'm saying? And
it's not even like the woman asked. It
was some [ __ ] man that didn't even
know didn't even know her. I said it's a
bit rude, isn't it?
So, is that socially acceptable then?
Being addicted to Tik Tok and having an
attitude problem and getting involved in
people's business, is that socially acceptable?
Is that socially acceptable, Grezy? I'm
asking you a question. So, is being
addicted to Tik Tok and having an
attitude problem and being a [ __ ] that
can start [ __ ] but can't finish it, is
that socially acceptable?
Well, mate, if that's socially
acceptable, I want to go to Finland and
[ __ ] live with the penguins and never
want to be any part of this society ever again. I'm saying,
well, that's not what I think is
acceptable. So, I'm not going to be
doing them things. Well, I'm not going
to be doing them things because I don't
find them acceptable. I'd rather at this
point I [ __ ] go Finland and [ __ ]
live with the penguins.
I mean, the people in this country are complete [ __ ]
I mean, what is their what is their
version of socially acceptable? They're
absolute [ __ ] Like, do you know
how many [ __ ] I had to deal with on
a daily basis when I used to work is,
you know, absolute [ __ ] I'm saying
I'm going to do a video on this to
Virgin Boy, I think.
Yeah, I'm going to do a video to this on
uh to Virgin Boy. Maybe he could
actually uh maybe he could actually uh
answer this one, I think. Yeah.
And I'll tell him the story about today
because but it was surprising cuz the
guy was quite an old he was quite an old
elderly man. Not old. Well, he could
walk and [ __ ] It was he was he could
still [ __ ] defend himself. But you
would have thought at that age they
would have they would have seen more sense.
You got [ __ ] 10year-olds [ __ ] stealing bikes.
You got [ __ ] 10year-olds stealing
bikes now. You know
I mean is that socially acceptable? You
know what I'm saying? I mean
Yeah. Oh, also another I'm going to
bring his dad up as well. I'm going to
Don't worry, I've got a nice little
video for him.
Uh, is this stuff also Don't [ __ ] sit
there and [ __ ] tell me what's
socially acceptable or not, you [ __ ] virgin.
And everyone on the bus agreed with me,
huh? They overheard me speaking to my
mom cuz I went to see my mom today and
they all agreed with me. He didn't even
know me. Yep. He was white.
I said, "Let's get off. I'm telling you
where I'm going to get off." I said,
"Let's get off the bus. Come on." Then
he shied away. "Yeah, you're not about nothing.
[ __ ] talk to me like that, you cunt."
And I would have said it and I would
have said it in front of [ __ ] anyone.
She wasn't a priority
at all. She wasn't even that old. You
know what I'm saying? So yeah,
I'm going to do two videos. I hope you
watch them, Grezy. No, no.
Let's give it a call on that [ __ ] Yeah.
Do you think pregnant women are disgusting, Greavvesy? Yeah.
Dedicated to virgin boy. I'm going to
start it like virgin boy.
That's how I always start it. Skin
virgin in a bed. That's my uh little
nickname for him.
I want to I want you to tell me as a
diagnosed autistic person what's socially acceptable.
You know what I'm saying?
What do you think is going to happen now
for Kennedy if I go out approaching
women again on Friday?
What what do what do you think will happen? boyfriend.
It's good I won that football bet. Hey,
I would have almost been in the
doghouse, Grezy, if I tried to go out again.
Yeah, I mean, that's what happens when
you spend £400 on a Sunday, ain't it? I
could have been in some serious problems.
I could have been in some serious
bother, bro, if I tried it again two
times. Cuz it's expensive. going out
getting on the piss and stuff.
I can't I I can have a laugh with it. I
don't think any of it funny.
I generally don't think any of it funny.
I can have a laugh. I'm glad you can
have a laugh cuz I don't find any of it funny.
Dealing with stuck up women in your
country. I don't What's funny about
that? Is that supposed to be funny or
I always I actually think to myself, you
know, now like there's not even no point
ever going out ever again.
I kind of feel like I know what it is, you know?
Yeah, obviously you live life, but the
the women ruin it and it's very
expensive to go out now.
You know, next time I go out again, I'm
probably going to spend about £300
one day, two days, you know, it's
expensive and I can afford it obviously, but it's
is it really worth it anymore?
Is it really You need, you know, you
need to think long term.
you know, is it is it worth it anymore?
You know what I'm saying? You need to think realistically.
And the thing is is obviously I won that
football bet. I can go out and spend £3400
and I'll be all right. But
you need to think long term. You know,
if I didn't win that football bet, bro,
I could have been in some problems. If I
had if I tried to go out a couple of
more times, bro, I would have been in my
I would have been [ __ ] compared to my
[ __ ] My [ __ ] to other people's [ __ ]
is not the same as [ __ ] to me. I would
have been [ __ ]
you know, and I can't keep up with it anymore.
And to be honest, I shouldn't have to
be, you know, doing this anymore, you know.
It's so nice winning money, bro. It
doesn't matter. Even if it is free,
£4400, just winning any amount of money
is just [ __ ] lovely, bro.
Go away, you stupid American. You're not
coming in winning any kind of money, you know.
But yeah, I know when I go out again,
it's easy. 3 350 done. You know,
once you go to that central London,
mate, the toast.
So that's the thing. I mean,
I just don't see the point in even like
going out anymore, you know?
I just really don't see the point in it. Stuck up,
you know, shallow [ __ ] I just I just
don't see the point in it.
It's mad, isn't it, bro?
So, see how I'm different than Ant-Man
Nicolo. I won't go out every week,
you know, whether I can afford it,
whether I can't, I can afford it, bro. I
can go out every week, you know,
then it's just not worth it anymore.
See, once I do this job thing, there
won't be going out every week. It will
just be me doing it and leaving. There
won't be no going out every week. Going
out every week for what? you know, yes,
it is expensive, but at the same time, I
could I can afford it. You know, I'll
find ways to afford it. It's not about
that. It's about the whole point of like
it just doesn't seem worth it anymore.
Cuz it's always the same thing. You
know, that Finnish one stopped replying. We're talking
when I tried to get romantic interest,
they stopped replying. The others didn't
reply. Bro, I can't do this forever. You know,
it's not like you didn't go out a
million times when you [ __ ] had
thousands and thousands of thousands.
Well, it's not it's about the money in
terms of Yes. It's about the money. You
can use that money to do other things
and towards your holiday. It that's what
I mean in terms of affordability. Not
that you would go out and you'd become
skinned. It wouldn't happen. But you you
know you you it'll be true if you go out,
it's one or the other.
And even if it's not one or the other,
um and even when it's not one or the other,
obviously it's still not worth going out.
Like say you could do Uber again, right?
And you could make 200 in two days or
300 and you could literally save all of
the other money you get and spend that
going out. I still wouldn't go out.
That's what I'm trying to say. I still
wouldn't because it's not worth it.
I'd probably I'd probably rather buy
[ __ ] designer clothes even though I
don't need them with the money I make
cuz it's just not worth going out anymore.
I don't know how we used to do that every week.
And the only time I consider it now is
if I've not been out for like a month.
That's the only time I'll consider it
because I'd have to be so bored to even consider it.
cuz I just know it never changes.
And I feel like you done all of that
[ __ ] 23 to 27. You had loads and loads
of money. You lived the life. You knew
what the country was about. Just leave.
But I'm leaving, you know,
to win that football bet though, man.
It's so [ __ ] nice just getting handed
just under400 and you didn't even have
to work for it. It was nice, isn't it, bro?
I won three football bets out of five.
Oh, it was good, man.
Yeah, it was good.
What's the biggest mistake? Um
me in USA is he yeah
I'd say that
and gambling and not because what I lost
money gambling Because if if if I didn't
gamble, I wouldn't have come with this community.
I didn't screw up with the tenants. They
showed their true colors.
Except two of them. I never screwed up
with them. They showed their true colors. So,
you know, they still message me
sometimes. I just ignore them.
So, I'd say meeting USA is probably
gambling. You don't want to come on this community.
now how I still have [ __ ] money to be honest
cuz London's so expensive and I don't
get loads of I'm I'm not good for the
past few months you know with money and [ __ ] Yeah.
Know what I mean?
No. What I should have done with that
USA is I should have never left the
apartment. I should have stayed.
But now I'll never know.
Yeah. You know, with some people I would
have thought like what would have
happened if I stayed. But now I'll never know.
But he doesn't LT doesn't seem to
understand what that USA is he done was wrong.
Yes. what she ex she did what she did was wrong
cuz they've led you on they've
lovebombed you and then they've disappeared
like all of it is wrong whether they owe
you anything or not. How does he not
actually comprehend that that's wrong
and I'm the I'm the one that's supposed
to be autistic. What the [ __ ]
Like he doesn't seem to understand like
exactly what they've done.
Are you talking like I've not had one
night stands before? He doesn't seem to
think that what they done was wrong.
But the best one was, "I really want
you, but I don't think you want me.
But I don't think you want me.
Oh, that was the funniest [ __ ]
I really want you, but I don't think you
want me. This sounds made up, but it wasn't. Yeah.
Yeah. That's what her friend said.
Yeah. So why did my mama leave me then? Alpha,
is that the real Mont?
I said I do.
I really want you, but I don't think you want me.
So, where's my mama now? Alpha. Huh?
Good old days, eh?
So, yeah, you need to think about
obviously what you're doing longterm cuz
yeah, I need to go cinema tomorrow.
I just can't believe it will never
change in this country with these women.
It's [ __ ] up.
Why did my mama leave me? Um, Nicolola.
So, what would have I done?
What would have I done if that football
bet never won?
I would have been fat in it.
I would have been screwed, bro.
Like, not broke, but I would have been
No, I wouldn't have starved or anything,
but I would have been [ __ ]
Like, [ __ ] bro.
It would have been scary, bro.
It's not even funny.
It's not funny, bro. It's actually really scary,
is it, Greavves? It's really scary.
See, that's what happens. You um you go
out, right, and you and it's in the hundreds now.
Do you understand, Nicolo? It's in the hundreds now.
It's not like you can go out and spend
30, 40, 50. It's in the hundreds,
you know? It's not all you can drink or
anything. It's in the [ __ ] hundreds.
It's about £7 a pint. Yeah.
7 pound a [ __ ] pint.
What do you think about that? £7.75 a pint. Graves.
Yeah, I saw some of them I've got a
boyfriend videos again today. Nicolo,
they just wind me up just watching them.
I hate watching it, bro. I was like,
this is why I don't even go out anymore.
It's [ __ ] annoying.
Yeah, it's like um
it's about £75
a pint a beer.
The place I go to.
I might just start bringing plastic
bottles in again like I used to.
I used to bring like plastic bottles in.
It doesn't matter if they're trying to
pull or not, bro. They're still getting
rejected, even doing it for a joke. So,
no, they're [ __ ] not. No, they're
not, mate. No, they're not.
No, they're not, mate. They're not.
There were some real ones.
There were some genuine ones.
So, is it really worth going out
spending £300 just to hear boyfriend?
I could do a Thursday, Saturday or
Saturday and Sunday
just to hear.
Is it really worth spending £300 on that?
Like, is it really worth it,
Grezy? Is it worth it?
I don't think so.
That's a [ __ ]
That's a stone island jumper.
That's a Stone Island jumper. Nicolola.
I might just start working from next
week. I don't know what I'm doing yet.
Yeah, I might start working from next week.
Got the delivery bag. Greasy.
I feel like, bro, like this is really
good. You know, Ant-Man's 32, right?
He didn't leave until he was 31.
I left when I was 27 and I'm leaving
when I'm 28. I'm a lot younger.
There's nothing left to prove here.
It will never be different.
It will never ever be different.
I feel like you're best of just trying
to just work your ass off building your
money up and then just leave it. I don't
I just don't see the point in
in it anymore.
You know, I just You know what I'm
saying, Gre? I just don't see the an
actual point to it anymore.
And this is why I have to be really
bored to want to go out.
This is why I have to be really bored in
order to even consider it. You know
that's fake Monty by the way. So yeah,
what do you think? Um, Grezy.
I think it's right, is it? What I'm saying? Look,
someone will catch me.
No one's going to catch me, bro. You
people have known where I've been
several times. And all you do is get
people kicked out of pubs.
Going to catch me from this community.
No one on here is ever going to catch me.
Stop being a keyboard warrior, man.
We're past that. You know,
I done a lot of walking today, bro.
So, I'm probably going to go with that, I think.
I mean, I bought the bag.
Oh, I hate that Ed Matthews. He's a
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
If if he ever tried to get in my face, I
would smash him in, bro. I'm not even joking. Fake Monty.
Yeah, that Ed Matthews is a [ __ ]
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Just like that
guy on the bus today.
Yeah, there's a lot of [ __ ] in this
country, bro. A lot of [ __ ]
cuz there's no um disparent, you see. So
that's why people go around that tonight like [ __ ]
Yeah, I know who that Ed Matthews is.
He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. I bro, if
he come up to me, I tell him to go suck his mom. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Is he good for him, bro?
Okay, that's nice for him, bro.
Okay, that's good for him. I'm not
obsessed. I'm not obsessed with money.
I don't care about people that's got
more money than me. I'm not obsessed
with money. I don't get jealous of people.
So, good for him.
But he is a [ __ ] [ __ ] though. Oh
my god, he is such a [ __ ] So yeah,
he is a proper [ __ ] But there's a
lot of [ __ ] in this country.
There's a lot of [ __ ] in this country, mate.
wouldn't have expected it from an old man
to be honest. But
a lot of people, women do it as well.
They start [ __ ] and then when you defend
yourself, they victimize themselves. Or,
you know, you get people that start
[ __ ] they can't finish. It's just a
western thing, a westernized thing.
You know, you don't get any Asian people
do that. It's it's a West thing.
SC of [ __ ] Yeah,
that's what I'll be dealing with if I
have to go work when I do this thing
again, Grez. I'll be having to deal with [ __ ]
But they're not going to stop me making money, mate.
They're not going to stop me making money.
No, it wasn't respect. It wasn't respect
because she wasn't a priority.
Well, they're priority seats for old
people or pregnant people or disabled
people. But there was nothing wrong with
her. She was only about 50, weren't
disabled, wasn't pregnant. So yeah. Uh
yep. Just like that. USA is she coward away.
I don't know why they do it to be
honest. I don't know why these people do this.
So yeah, there was actually nothing
wrong with her, which was the whole point.
There was nothing wrong with it other
than being a bit older. Yep.
I mean, everyone on the bus agreed with
me. They overheard what I was asking my
mom. So, I mean, for them to agree with
me, I must have been right. So,
he's probably calling me a prick. I
said, "You're a [ __ ] prick, you
[ __ ] Come off the [ __ ] bus.
I said come off the bus. They sort out
outside the bus. Come on. Come on. They
just walked back. What a [ __ ] man.
What a [ __ ] [ __ ]
Peter Belly was answering back and you
could see [ __ ] little Lany's [ __ ]
head like look to the back.
looked to the [ __ ] back.
She was actually looking. It was funny
as [ __ ] No, I don't think I was going
to punch. He weren't old old. He was
old, but he could have easily defended
himself. I wouldn't have punched him.
No. If I gave him one punch, he probably
would have killed him. Probably. No.
And then when he got off the bus, he's
like, "Oh, you should show some
respect." I said, "Yeah, maybe when you
start showing some respect." You can't.
I was in my little Ammani tracksuit. My
little gray Ammani tracksuit, Nicolola. Yeah. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, man. It's a madness.
But yeah, I need to think about um what
I'm going to do, bro.
Yeah. And she There was nothing wrong
with her either. She was a [ __ ]
Did I answer back? We
did answer back. I'm cheeky, aren't I?
So, yeah. I need to think about
You're best off, right, just sending
this job thing. Yeah. every day, bro.
And then just like you can even book
another holiday for when you come back or something.
I don't know, man. I don't think I'll be
out for a long time. Um,
yeah. I need to think about what I'm
going to do, bro.
I feel like your best thing to do is go
gym. Yeah. Make some sick gains.
[ __ ] do this job thing,
make as much money as you can and just
keep [ __ ] off. That's what I think.
And then just keep [ __ ] off.
You know what I mean, Nicolo? And just
keep [ __ ] off. I don't think of
anything anything else you could actually do.
Did you see that? John Cena versus
[ __ ] Logan Paul.
Oh my god. Have you seen how old John
Cena's got? He's [ __ ] whole body is
like sagging now, bro. Bless him if he's
getting old. And Greavvesy,
bless him if he's getting old.
Have you seen a Grievy? He's getting [ __ ] old.
He's getting old, bro.
like really old man
starts. He has like loose skin and [ __ ]
It's horrible, isn't it?
Horrible, mate. Getting old. [Music]
at least this video to virgin boy.
Who's DVD is?
Yeah, John Cena is good, man. He had a
good body back in the day. He still does
now, but like [ __ ] he's got he's old
now, man. He's [ __ ] nearly 50. What the [ __ ]
So when I went to see him in WWE, he
must have been
16. He must have been 31.
It must have been when I went to see WWE
30. How old was I? 11. Say
17. Maybe 30.
Now he's [ __ ] old.
They're all old now, bro.
Yeah, they're all old now, man.
Do you remember Nexus, Nicolo? Do you remember Nexus?
In WWE 15 years ago, they were called a Nexus.
Yeah. None of you people bully no one.
You can't even come on my door, bro. You
people don't bully anyone. You just embarrass yourselves.
How? Listen, bro. How do you people
bully anyone? You just talk about
yourselves every day. You put yourselves
down. I don't want that kind of
negativity on my channel, lad. You know,
you bully yourselves. You embarrass
Like I don't want to see you putting
yourselves down, calling yourselves
skin, calling yourself a ma. You really
think I want that on my channel? You
putting yourselves down,
you know? It's not nice you putting
yourselves down, talking about
yourselves. I don't want that kind of
negativity on my channel, calling
yourselves a skin mucking horrible.
Why would I want people to talk about
themselves like that?
Get it? Cuz you're talking about yourselves.
Hey, do you know what? I might actually
do [ __ ] three videos in one day, bro.
Why were they [ __ ]
Yeah, we've all seen what happens when
you get confronted. Same old excuses.
We've heard all this before, Terry. You
live with your mom. You don't come outside.
You're boring, kid.
But on a real real, I promise you on any
anyone's life, all you do is bully
yourselves. You come on YouTube every
day in your 40s, ain't got [ __ ] all sat
there talking about people that you
don't know who you've never met. Believe
you me when I say you are the ones getting bullied.
You remember eh?
Believe you me when I say you are the
ones that are actually getting bullied
and you're all older as well. You're
[ __ ] old, bro.
Trust me, bro. You people have always been bullied.
Sat on sat on here at your age. You
should know better, man. You should
[ __ ] know better.
Do you know what I'm saying? You should
know better, man. Jesus Christ.
I don't know how you can
How do you remember all of this stuff?
That's one of the reasons I kind of
stopped going out is because of the
[ __ ] in this country. It weren't
even just like the women.
It was like it was just like different things
like today and that
you know you go out you see the same
people the same attitude the same
[ __ ] the same women you see the
same thing you know it literally never
changes. It's [ __ ] boring, bro. Just [ __ ] you know. [ __ ] everywhere.
Need to go watch the new Kjarin tomorrow. So,
feel like a 100 years old. I feel so old, bro.
It's all them Newcastle trips, isn't it, Nicolo?
It's all them [ __ ] Newcastle trips. Yep. Yeah.
[ __ ] my I'm You know what I'm saying?
Last thing I want to do is [ __ ]
is [ __ ] go and deal with these stuck
up [ __ ] You know what I mean?
I don't know if I'm the only one that
feels like it, bro, but
it just it's just tiring thinking about
it. I wonder what happened to that John.
Do you remember that John that I met up
with once and we done um approaching and
he had social anxiety? The Turkish one,
the one that used to come on here and
say approaching is in your DNA.
And I met him once and he just disappeared.
You might not. I'm sure you remember it.
You must remember it.
He was under the account John
the Turkish guy. Do you remember?
He was on like £300 a month. I remember.
I don't know what happened to him, bro.
Wonder if he still does it.
Why would I have a lot of stories to tell him?
I'd have a lot of [ __ ] stories to
tell him, mate.
If he ever came back, wait till I tell
him about USA. Is he
see what I don't understand is why
people make this dating thing seem so
easy. There's nothing easy about any of it.
Dating apps don't work.
[ __ ] you try to speak to people, they
pretend they got boyfriends.
You know, all the effort and the [ __ ]
money that goes into it. What's easy
about any of it?
What is easy about any of it, Greavvesy?
I don't see any anything easy about any of it.
I don't think any of it.
No, they like it.
No, they like it, Russell. They like it.
I was right in that situation.
I still think I was right.
[ __ ] [ __ ] met her match
just like I would meet my match if I
went around [ __ ] with people every day.
So, no, I don't agree with that, LT. No,
I don't agree with it.
And he says, "Oh, you you know, you you
shouldn't winge and that men aren't
supposed to winge." Or like, I winge if
I want to wing. I've got every right
right to winge. And I'm not actually
winging. I'm actually just doing videos
talking about this [ __ ]
I'm not [ __ ] winging.
Uh, how was I right? Uh, cuz the [ __ ]
led me on and used me and then
disappeared. What the [ __ ] No person
does that. And then starts making up
[ __ ] stories. Well, it's not even
about the stories to be honest with you.
Like, no normal person does that.
No person, unless they're an entitled
[ __ ] [ __ ] does that.
Doesn't matter if I only met her once.
Who gives a [ __ ] Yeah. So then you
write, "Listen, I'm going back home.
Catch you later, douches."
Is that not what you say? No.
Why does it matter how many times you met someone?
So you just say you're going back home, Addios. Bye.
It takes like 5 seconds, bro.
Do you know what? I've never ever had
someone else do that. You know,
I've never ever had someone else do that.
No, never. I don't think I ever have. You know, nah,
you must feel really entitled. You know,
I've never had that before, you know.
Well, if I'm sure if you wasn't
interested in somebody, you wouldn't
give them your number and sleep with
them. Huh? I Oh, it's a tricky one, isn't it?
>> I mean, yeah, but I mean, I know if I
wasn't interested in somebody, I
wouldn't give them my number and sleep with them.
I mean, so it's a tricky one, isn't it?
I'd ditch them, bro. Actually, I've
ditched someone before. But I do you
know what? Do you know the thing is,
Nicolo? Yeah. You know when I've always
done these bad things, I always just I
always ex um I always explain myself in the end.
Yeah, I didn't sleep with her. Okay,
bro. I'm not going to get I'm not going
to get into whether I've slept with
somebody or not. You know, it's boring
conversation. I know what I've done. Um
and I don't care what you think. So, you
don't know. You wasn't there. So, I
don't give a [ __ ] what you think. I
don't need to lie about sleeping with a
[ __ ] four out of 10.
I lose nothing. I lose nothing. You know
how many [ __ ] I got that that whole
year? You know how many [ __ ] I got
that April? Oh, [ __ ] the year. I don't
need to lie about sleeping with one person.
Grow up, mate. You're in your 40s. [ __ ] No.
No, I didn't say that. No, I didn't say
that. Anyways, moving on. We're not
getting into this conversation.
So yeah. Um,
so yeah, stop being obsessed as well,
bro. Why do you care if someone slept
with somebody or not? Are you Are you
Are you a virgin or something?
Pretty sure if you wasn't interested in
somebody, you wouldn't give somebody your number.
No, what it was is I tell you what it
was, Nikolai. If she wanted somebody to [ __ ]
So then when she's [ __ ] somebody and
then they've stood up for themselves,
she played victim. She played No, no.
The reason she didn't give an
explanation is cuz she she felt, "Oh, I
don't need to give an explanation. I
don't owe this [ __ ] anything." So that's
how they feel in their sick head. So
then when you stand up for yourself
So when you stand up for yourself
Yeah. I don't I don't know why people
lie cuz I'm not lying. You're the one
that's obsessed with it. You're the one
that's obsessed with it, not me. You're
the one that's obsessed with it. So,
you're the one that's going on about
sex. No one else.
And then they play the victim.
And then the thing is, right, LT was
like, "Oh, you're you this is why this
is what gives women uh gives men a bad
name is people like you.
But then I said, "Well, she gives women
a bad name and they put you off women
for two years, so isn't that isn't that
equal?" Okay, so you're saying what I
done, right, makes them scared of men,
right? Makes them scared of men, right?
So, um, isn't what she done put me off
women? So, isn't it exactly the same thing?
Yeah, exactly, bro. And then when when
when she realized he wasn't buying any
of her [ __ ] Yeah.
Um then she started playing victim
cuz she actually thinks she's
intelligent. She thinks she's smart and
she thinks that we're dumb [ __ ] Do you
know what I'm saying? And then as soon
as you match their energy, it doesn't
have to be like physically, you know, it
could just be like verbally or mentally
or whatever, they all play victim. I
don't know why they do it.
I don't talk about her. LT was the one
bringing her up.
And I bring it up because it's just
another one to add to the [ __ ] collection,
you know? It's a summary of how [ __ ]
up they actually are. Which is why I
bring it up cuz it's all [ __ ] up.
I bring a lot of ones up because it's
just a summary how [ __ ] up it is.
And that's definitely Terry. That Russell account.
That is definitely definitely Terry.
Yeah, she Yeah, because she thought she
could manipulate cuz she actually thinks
she's smart, but there's nothing smart about her.
She's just a stupid little Yankee
[ __ ] Ted the Bear Boston [ __ ]
That's all. Nothing smart about that [ __ ] you know. Yeah. So, yeah,
that's what she is. [ __ ] [ __ ]
I hate women, bro.
You know the way, you know, the more you
think about this [ __ ] with them. Yeah.
And it's not even just one person, the
more it's like, bro, like, should we be
doing this anymore? You know what I'm
saying? And the answer is [ __ ] no,
lad. The answer is [ __ ] no, bro. You know,
I I got like no energy anymore, bro. I
feel 100 years old. And you think I'm
going to waste three, four, fucking£100
to get the [ __ ] same [ __ ] you know?
[ __ ] went out Sunday
to get the same [ __ ] basically. Um,
that's why I've just got into this thing
now. I watch. You know,
I feel so old, lad.
>> Yeah. There's nothing else you can do,
but if you try, then you're just going
to be more depressed.
But it's not
I have to go out. I I'd have to not go
out for like weeks to even be tempted to
go out now.
Like it used to be every week, but now
it's like I really have to be bored to
consider wasting money in this country again.
It does drain you. It generally drains
you, bro. And obviously I tried more
than anyone in the world. You know, I've
probably drunk more than most people.
So I feel like I've done it. You know, [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying, bro? Like just
Oh, there's no coke. drunk all the coke [ __ ] sake.
You know what I'm saying?
It's [ __ ] up, man.
I feel so [ __ ] No.
Swear to God.
So yeah, I'll probably get tempted again
in like four weeks.
Yeah, I used to say to LT, we used to go
for a good oldfashioned piss up.
Yeah, but it's just the women pretending
they're having boyfriends. It just ruins it.
The women just ruin it. You know what I mean?
[ __ ] boyfriends every time. It's
annoying even hearing it when it's
happening to other people. It's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
Yeah, that Finnish one went quiet when
it was about like interest and [ __ ]
I was like, why do these women even give
you their number and even reply to you
if they're not going to be interested? I
just don't understand it.
And I don't understand why they even go
out if they're just going to tell
everyone they've got boyfriends.
It's ridiculous. Why do these women even
go out, waste money looking good?
Looking good. Let's Okay, let's just say
they go out for fun, but they they go to
that extent of trying to look that good
just to tell everyone they've got boyfriends.
What's What is even the point? It's a [ __ ] madness.
Imagine going out here and looking your
best or trying to look your best just to
not speak to anyone that you don't know.
Why do these women even go out? No, it's
not even like it's cheap, you know?
I'm [ __ ] old as [ __ ] bro. Fancy McDonald's.
Do you remember the AR? Do you remember
the black guy smiling like he already knew? Nicolo,
you remember when I was telling him
about USA and he was smiling like he
already knew it?
Oh, your imaginary girlfriend.
Your imaginary girlfriend. Yeah. Really, bro?
Yeah. He was smiling like he already knew.
N look over that. He gave me some like
dodgy smile it like you already knew.
I was like, "Ah, so you knew."
I just don't have the energy anymore, mate.
It's crazy though, is it? It is crazy. Yeah.
Nah, they don't have boyfriends.
Don't be silly, bro. I'm not going to
get into this conversation again, bro.
I'm not getting into it again.
Because no matter what somebody explains
to you, it doesn't process in your
brain. So, there's no point bringing it up.
And it's actually boyfriend. And yeah,
it is imaginary most of the time.
And I'm not going to get into it again,
bro, cuz whatever is explained to you,
uh, it doesn't process in your in your
brain. So, what's the point of even
bringing it up? If you think that they
they actually have boyfriends, that's on
you, bro. That's your problem. I know the truth.
So, you know, what's
One second, bro.
Yeah. It's crazy, isn't it? Um,
I just watching pro boyfriend. [ __ ]
Yeah. Okay, bro. You're right. You're
right. You're right. And I'm wrong, bro.
Yep. All of these women that are in
clubs slagging it off until 7:00 in the
morning, they've all got boyfriends.
Yeah, bro. You're right. And I'm wrong.
Yeah, man. 100%, bro. Yeah, I believe
you, bro. You're right. All of these
women in in clubs
Yeah. until like 7:00 in the morning.
They've all got boyfriends that are just
at home by themselves in bed having a
wank. Uh-huh. Yeah. Of course they are.
Imagine that. Your girlfriend out every
week in the club until 7:00 in the
morning while you're at home in bed
having a wank
watching Mr. Bean.
Yeah. Believable, isn't it?
Very believable, isn't it, mate?
Yeah. That's very believable, isn't it?
It's crazy, isn't it?
How all of these women that have got boyfriends
are never with their boyfriends
in their club until 7:00 in the morning.
That's mad, ain't it? Jeez.
Makes you wonder, doesn't it? >> yeah,
bro. Why are we having this conversation
when I literally am telling you that
they're full of [ __ ] They literally do
not have boyfriends.
I don't even know why we're having this conversation.
It's the most common excuse that they use.
Are you Are you a [ __ ] or you just
trolling? Like, no one can be that much
of a [ __ ]
No one can be that much of a [ __ ]
[ __ ] You got to be trolling. You
can't be that stupid, man. Come on. You know
One second. Hold.
Yeah. See? Where's the only place you're
not going to get that, do you reckon?
Can you hear me?
Where's the only place you're not going
to get that?
Nickelodeon, I have a boyfriend.
Where's the only place you're not going
to get that?
I keep seeing these videos. I have a
boyfriend. I have a Where you not going
to get that, bro? I keep seeing that everywhere.
Is there like a place you're not going
to get that or something?
Where where can you go where you're not
going to keep getting that?
[ __ ] hell, bro.
I need to do this video to Virgin Boy soon. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, I know.
Strange, isn't it? Very strange.
Yeah, that's what Ant-Man said. He said
that's the only place you're not going
to get it.
He said that's the only place you're not
going to get it.
Or like [ __ ] South American escorts.
He said that's the only place you're not
going to get that.
That sounds mad though, is it?
And I said, he said, "Oh, women are
cunts." And I said, "Why are they
cunts?" He said, "Because 90% of them
say they have boyfriends when they don't."
Yeah. He said that 90% of them say they
have boyfriends when they don't.
You said that's why they're [ __ ] Is it true, Nicolo?
Yeah, that can't Yeah.
Yeah. Cuz you don't Yeah, cuz you did
have a boyfriend.
The more this, bro, the more more
just going out just don't seem worth it,
you know? The more I think about it,
bro, like the more it just doesn't seem worth it.
The more you think about it, it
didn't have a boyfriend. He's full of
[ __ ] They don't have boyfriends.
Where is Mus?
Yeah, I put up with a lot of [ __ ] for so many years.
For so many years.
I might do a video, you know, about this
about the expenses of going out and
stuff, you know. I feel like it's interesting
and like the [ __ ] that you deal with
when you go out and
I feel like it's a good thing to, you
know, talk about
Well, that football bet that that is
quite a good return, isn't it? If you
put 120 on the football and you get 380,
ain't it, Nicolo? It's quite a good.
It's like just over the triple, isn't it?
I wish I put it on a both score, no draw
cuz it was actually a both score, no draw.
Oh, I would have been laughing, mate.
I would have been laughing even more.
Yeah, I would have been laughing even more, bro.
You can definitely get him on them
northern leagues. Definitely.
Oh, mate. But even that that was still a
good window. 120 to 380. I mean, it got
paid back money that I spent over the
[ __ ] thingy, you know.
So, I'm still able to save like 600 this
month. So, it's not bad. But [ __ ]
yeah, you can easily get a both score no
draw. Like what I was thinking of was doing like
three both score no draws in that league
and I think you got a pretty good
[ __ ] chance, bro.
because there's loads of goals in that league,
you know, but I'm not going to do I'm
not going to do any gambling now for
bit. We got somebody. So, if I need
extra money again, I will. Yeah.
You know what I want to do? I want to do
like a correct score. Imagine that,
Nicolola. Imagine guessing nil nil on
four games and putting £100 on it. Oh,
mate. You'd be [ __ ] rich. You'd be
[ __ ] rich, mate. Wouldn't you?
You'd be [ __ ] rich, Dad.
You would be Oh, mate. Imagine that.
Three correct score. Neil Nils.
Oh, you'd be laughing.
You would be [ __ ] laughing, mate.
Imagine that kind of money you get back for that.
Yeah, mate. It's happening from the
start. They just just don't score.
You're winning from the start.
You're actually winning from the start though.
You can easily get a double both score
no draw though in them leagues. Defer.
I want to get a both score no draw one
day. You know,
you can definitely get a treble. both
teams um both teams to score. If I added
that spending more, I would have had
three teams, but I think two teams is
just good. All you just put money, just
put like 150 on two teams, you still get
back like 600,
but then that that you want the National
League, that's the one you want.
So many so many goals, bro. And they
score like mad. But I literally I I
actually thought I was losing the bet.
It was 4-0 and the other was nil nil. I
was like, "Okay, I'm fucked." And as
soon as the second half But as soon as
it was the second half, they all started scoring.
All of them started scoring. I was like,
"What the fuck?" Now it's 1-1 and now
it's 4-1. Within 5 minutes, they all
started scoring. I was like, "Yeah, I
won the won the football bet.
I wish I put the extra 40 on it now
though instead of the roulette
[ __ ] sake man. Yeah boy. Virgin M.
You can never put that money on a bet.
But I would have actually been kind of
[ __ ] if I lost.
Not starving, not being able to not pay
bills, but I would have been in a lot I
would have been in the doghouse almost.
I would be kind of [ __ ]
I'm not going to lie, bro. Cuz
cuz Yeah. going out and then you know
what I'm saying? going out and that also
brought it back cuz if I didn't win then
obviously I spent all that money Sunday
and I got nothing but numbers that
aren't interested. Same old [ __ ] Same old story.
It It reminds me of the casino days
obviously on a lesser scale cuz it's
less money that I'm winning but still
money in it. So
then it would have been bad bro. It
would have been bad because like I said,
it's not cheap going out.
So, you know, it's
that's the thing you probably got.
That's you got Yeah.
It's just a waste of time, money,
everything. You know, Virgin Virgin boy
can't put 120 on a bet, can he?
But if I put an extra 40 on it instead
of the roulette, it would have been more. No,
would have been [ __ ] ace, bro. Yeah. [ __ ] So yeah.
Oh, that's the day I met my mama, Nicolola.
That's the day I met my mama. Yeah,
I said on Reddit. Yeah,
I said on Reddit,
right, um, why is it so hard to get a
girlfriend? And they said, because you
cry on Reddit instead of try trying to
talk to women.
If only they knew. Eh,
wow. If only they knew the truth. E, I'm
surprised none of these people
know the truth.
It's like the same people that reply
back as well because you cry on Reddit
instead of trying to talk to uh
to a woman. Wow. Really? Well, let me
show them some videos. Oh, wow.
I sit at home instead of trying to speak to women.
If only it was that. Okay, at least we'd
have something to blame.
Bro, I've got so many videos,
you know, so many approaching videos
that it's good enough.
I'm going to start this working thing, I
think, next week, bro. I think
Yeah, I think I'm going to do this
thing, bro. I think Yeah. Oh [ __ ] What's up
Yeah. One shot.
One sec, bro.
I'm surprised these people just don't
know the truth, Greavvesy,
about like what women are like, cuz it's
not like they don't live in America.
It's not like they don't [ __ ] live in
America. Do you know what I'm saying,
bro? So, how do they not know about this?
Cuz they live in America. [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? They live in
[ __ ] America. It's not like they
don't live in America.
They know what women are like.
So why are they acting like they're not
in a [ __ ] westernized country? It's [ __ ] up. Yeah.
I had a big Chinese today, Grezy.
A big Chinese
I know. It's crazy, isn't it? You can't
even get a conversation.
Oh, yeah. I had beef tain today and
chicken fried rice and chicken balls.
You can't even get a conversation.
And when you do, it's I have a boyfriend.
I mean, I got a conversation out of that
Finnish one and then they did reply
back. And then when it's to do with like uh
moving it further, then [ __ ]
then it's um
then it's they're not interested.
So, I mean, okay, why did they give
their number and even text you?
So, yeah, we need to think of something
else now, bro. Anyways, I don't I won't
be going out for a long time.
Just so lucky I learned at 27. At least
I wasn't Ant-Man's age in his [ __ ] 30s.
Yeah, you can't. You're damned if you
do, damned if you don't.
It's like dating is like the hardest
thing. Like even even making money, like
the thing is with making money. Yeah.
You never know when you're going to come
across money or, you know, even that's
pretty hard, but you don't really know.
But with women, it literally never
changes. It will just be the same [ __ ] for years.
you don't know how you going to get
money or you know I don't have the house
anymore. I've done pretty good somehow.
Like you don't really know what's ever
going to happen. But with women it never ever changes.
Like literally nothing. There's nothing
easy about any of it. You look smack,
you get rejected. You go casual, you get
[ __ ] around with, you know, you can't
literally nothing ever changes.
That's why I don't bother unless I'm extremely bored.
you know, you could win a football. I
didn't think I was going to win that football bet.
And the reason why
it was good I won the football bet is
cuz I went out twice and spent loads of
money. So, considering I don't have a
house anymore and I got most of money
back, I mean, yeah, it's good.
You know what I mean?
But with the women, it never changes.
That's the thing. It never ever changes.
That's the actual whole thing. It just don't change.
The same kind of people you see, you
know, [ __ ] around, it don't change.
and they live in America as well.
And America's worse than here.
I wonder why they go on like it's so easy.
They go on like it's so easy when
there's nothing easy about it.
I wish I could understand the easiness
in it, Grezy. I wish I could understand
how dating is easy.
There's nothing easy about any of it.
It's time consuming. It's expensive,
which most people don't have the money.
Yeah, like money. Like, like I said,
I've done all right now. Even though I
don't have the house anymore, I feel
like I done pretty good.
You know, I still have money and I went
out. I still spent some money. I done
some I done good on the football. So,
but you don't know when you're going to
come across money. You don't,
you know, making money is hard as well
cuz there's no opportunities. But
it's even with money, right? There's
only a few ways to make make money.
You either have to live on like £50 a
[ __ ] week or you [ __ ] gamble and
risk being [ __ ] or you
you sort of you sort of get a some sort
of [ __ ] cash inhand job.
They're really your only options, but
obviously the gambling one comes with a risk.
So, I'm going to try this thing soon
anyways. this whole um see how it goes.
But they're the only ways really.
And obviously if you lose gambling then
you're [ __ ] So yeah. Yeah. Basically,
it's not easy nowadays, bro. It's not easy.
It's not easy nowadays, is it, Grezy?
Bless you, Grezy. I've not been on a
grand a month,
even for two months, cuz I won some
money on the football, didn't I? So,
Virgin Boy is still on a grand a month.
But I'm I'm not It's not that bad, you
know? At least I've still got money, you
know? Like, [ __ ] It could have been a lot worse,
you know? But yeah,
at least I won on the football in it. So yeah,
might do another bet in a month or so. I
don't really need any new I don't need
spare money now. only done it cuz I
needed some extra money. But
yeah, if I didn't go out, if I didn't go
out, I would have been all right. But
obviously I went out Sunday and Tuesday.
If I didn't go out Sunday, Tuesday, and
I didn't go, I probably would have had a
good couple of thousand now. But
obviously I went out and I spent. So I
went out drinking and [ __ ] So
If I didn't like go out and spend that
kind of money in London, I would have
been a lot better.
But obviously, I went out drinking and [ __ ] So,
Sunday was a killer, bro.
Then I gave my mom £30 for her birthday. So
yeah, I'd be uh I'd be rich. I'd be
I'd be rich, bro.
Literally, bro. Yeah,
it's a madness, bro.
Yeah. 90k. It's not that much, is it?
It's not that much. It's good, but it's
not that much. 90k.
Yeah, it's all right. I'm up. Oh, [ __ ]
How else can you make money nowadays, Nicolo?
You could do that delivery thing. I need
to do that delivery thing. I want to see
how much money I can make with that delivery thing.
I might just do it like every day for
like a week. Oh, I'll be [ __ ]
Oh, bro. I will be so [ __ ]
It's not even a joke. I'd be [ __ ]
bro. Well, I think I could do it.
I would have to do it.
Just do it like non-stop like 10 days
and you get paid every week. It'll be
good in it. See how much money you get.
That'd be good, bro.
You might make like 60 70 pound a day. Jeez.
So it's like,
do you think you could do it every day?
I think I could.
Yeah, cuz means building money up, I
would do it. Yeah, 100%.
We couldn't do it every day. Nah.
So, how else can you make money now, Nicolo?
How else do you think you can make money now?
You can't, matey. You can't.
You can't, can you, Nico?
Yeah, I would have made a lot of money that Saturday.
I cancelled the orders and they [ __ ]
banned my [ __ ] account.
Yep. Then they banned my [ __ ]
account, the [ __ ]
So yeah, if you don't see me for 10
days, bro, I'm delivering food.
How else can you make money now, Nicolo?
You said gambling's the way.
You said gambling is the only way to
make extra money now, isn't it?
Yeah, pretty much.
I reckon if you could do that delivery
job, mate, and win a couple of bets a month,
you'll be laughing.
You'd be [ __ ] laughing, bro.
I think that's a good plan, isn't it?
Yeah, but you have to go abroad to do
that to teach English.
Three grand a month for
3 years. That's mad, isn't it? Three
grand a month for doing nothing for 3 years.
That's a madness.
It feels so weird not having that house
now, though. It feels weird. It does feel weird.
Yeah, them them roadblocks [ __ ] me,
bro. They done it more than once.
That's horrible, man.
But yeah, I'm going to do that delivery
thing for every day for like
10 days, bro. See how much I can make
from it. Should be good in it.
Oh, that Uber thing, bro. Had me [ __ ]
I come back like black as s
when I made 88 pound. Yeah, I come back
black as [ __ ] soot, bro.
But I still think I could have made 120,
you know, in a day. I think I could have
made 120 if I started a bit later.
Definitely. I reckon if I started a bit later
and I timed it right, I could have made
about 120, bro. That's sick.
What if I got used to it more? Yeah.
Yeah, bro. I was my hands were swollen
and everything. My hands were like
swollen for a week. Easy from being on
the bike, ain't it?
Yeah. From being on the [ __ ] bike.
Would you happy my football bet won? Greavvesy,
how do you know about 41 Albert Road? Nicolo.
Yeah, that's my old address.
That's where I used to live.
How do you know about that?
Imagine Greavves. You're on the little bike.
Gre in his on his little bike doing deliveries. Bless you.
Bless you. Greavves in your little bike.
on your little bicycle.
You ain't got the minerals, lad. Yep.
Good times, eh?
How do you know 41 Albert Road?
How do you know that?
Do you think you could do it 10? Do you
reckon you could do it, Grezy? 10 days
in a row.
Do you reckon you could do it 10 days in
a row, though, Greasy? That's the question. Could
you do the Uber 10 days in a row? I
could do it, mate. If I needed the
money, I would do it.
I [ __ ] done it for like 9 hours. And
the only reason it was £88 is probably
cuz I wasted a lot of energy probably
starting earlier. So, I reckon if I
started at about 12 or 1 on a Saturday,
I'm sure I could have got about 1:20.
You sure I could have if I had started a bit later
and if I kept going? Yeah, easy, bro. I
reckon I could have 120,
maybe 130 even.
But then the next hour would be [ __ ]
Then a couple more six hours is That's good, bro.
You do that every [ __ ] day, bro, for
a month, you'll be rich. You'll be [ __ ] rich.
Nope. Never got lost. You'd be rich,
bro. If you done that like
you done that for a month, matey,
build some money up, you know? Be good.
Bless you grievy.
I need to do this video to virgin boy
soon about socially acceptable
to virgin boy. So I went to Virgin Boy or
Noah, I'm just going to say
I'll say Virgin Boy, please explain this. Yeah.
Yeah. But I'm going to mention Virgin Boy.
And I say, "Can you do a video, please,
explaining what uh socially acceptable
is, please, mate?
I'm going to add some things in here.
I want you to help me. I It would be
funny for a diagnosed autistic person. Uh,
you know, just like when you said about
that Shervel Cole thing to fit in, you
wanted to look good, you know."
Yeah. [ __ ] copycat.
Who's a copycat?
Bless you, Grezy. If you're on £1,200 a
month, bless you then.
Oh, bless you.
Bless you. And if you're on If you're on
£1,200 a month, then bless Slap
this [ __ ] in. Virgin boy. [Music]
You know my little video Tim's going to
be quite vicious, don't you?
It's going to be fishes. Don't you agree Z?
You know what I mean by that? like fish.
Add a few things in there. Yeah.
Where's my little earpods gone? Oh,
I'm getting very lazy nowadays.
How do you feel about that? I'm just
becoming very very lazy.
I'm becoming very very lazy.
Is that cute?
Anyways, let me do this video. Anyways,
you're going to watch it greasy. Yeah,
I'm going to do this video now. You
better watch it.