Yeah,
let me do that video. Actually,
I already ordered to delete it. I was
actually going to do a video yet [ __ ]
20 minutes before going in the cinema, but
I can't be bothered, bro. I'm going to
waste my time on a skin virgin in a bed
suit. Got better things to be [ __ ] doing.
A waste of time.
Yeah. Complete waste of [ __ ] time. Pointless.
It's the same old argument. So, I just
thought I can't be [ __ ] bothered even
replying to it.
Same old skin self-reflectors. I mean,
they've got their own channel to do it
on, you know. So
yeah, they can do it on their channel, not mine. So yeah.
Oh my gosh.
Well, feeling that [ __ ] Money Mike
and Joe won't come back on my channel again.
If I do, Do you know what? Yeah. You're
going to laugh at this [ __ ] right?
Yesterday before I went in the cinema
before I went out I thought you know
what it's Friday today I could actually
go to Birmingham
I could actually go to [ __ ]
Birmingham and [ __ ]
call that [ __ ] out but then I realized
I've done it all before and we know what
you you people are like so
you know that's why we don't waste our
time. Same thing with the skinned virgin
in the bedset. Same thing with that [ __ ]
in Birmingham because we know what you
people are like. So we just don't waste
our time on you anymore.
Joe's not been on here.
Mike's not been on here.
And then you see these decent looking
guys with these fat ugly women.
With these fat ugly women. Wow.
With these fat ugly women. madness. I
see this guy, bro. He must have been about
[ __ ] above average looking normal
looking guy, bro. I swear to God. He the
girl the woman he was with was some fat
black woman, bro. I'm not even joking.
She was stinking.
That's That is bad, bro. That is bad.
So, it looks like in two years even the
[ __ ] won't be getting women.
just gets worse and worse and worse.
That is a madness.
I can't believe how
how low people drop their standards.
Like that's it's mad. Have you seen it?
[ __ ] me. You see some [ __ ] ugly women
with these people,
but yet they don't think there's a
problem with the dating game in this country.
Like, think about it, bro. Do you think
he wanted to choose that woman? No.
No. She was like a two out of 10, bro. I
swear to God. I was like, "What the
[ __ ] This guy should be doing better." Yep. Sure do.
I said, "Oh, yeah. Wait, uh, keep yourself busy
for a half hour."
It's a country designed to annoy you.
That's what it is, bro. It's a country
designed to annoy you. A country that
will never change. It's [ __ ] boring,
bro. Full of [ __ ] You see it
everywhere. I see some person [ __ ]
vaping in a [ __ ] cinema. What the
I'm glad to be back, bro. Glad to be back.
It'll never change. It will never Never. [Music]
Yep. It's happened to me a few times. Um,
everything's true about the video.
Well, yeah, the rain thing is um
is very true. Government, please. This
is a country designed to annoy you. This
is why people are just going [ __ ]
Thailand now. You know, we can't be
[ __ ] with it.
Going to cook myself some food later.
Got some chicken to cook. So,
could get a takeaway again, but is open.
Yeah, might do that.
Don't know why I keep getting takeway.
It's not like I'm [ __ ] rich anymore,
but we're not skin like a [ __ ] like
that [ __ ] bedsit virgin.
I ain't going back and forth with these
losers, bro. I'm not going back and
forth with them.
No, it's not that bad when they're with
an average guy. That doesn't annoy me.
It's when they're with a [ __ ] ugly
guy with no personality. That's what
annoys me. And that's what that guy was.
And before you say, how do you know him?
How do I know him, bro? I'm 20 [ __ ]
I'm almost 28. I'm a [ __ ] adult,
right? I've met these people everywhere.
You know, these [ __ ] Um, you know,
I've seen them everywhere, mate. And
that's the thing. They don't even have a
personality. So, they got to be rich or
something. If they're with an average
guy, then it's not bad. If they're if
they're just an average white person,
it's not bad.
Yeah. I saw one pregnant person.
Yeah, it was okay.
No, he [ __ ] doesn't. He's a [ __ ]
I've met so many guys like him, bro.
Listen, listen, listen. I'm 20 I'm
almost 28 years of age. Yeah. I've been
up and down the country. I know the kind
of guys in this country. He doesn't have
a heart of gold. He's a [ __ ] Just
like most of these guys that you see
with these women, they're [ __ ] And
the guys that actually have a heart of
gold that are decent looking or with
twos out of tens. I've seen it.
What does he do, bro? They because
because they're [ __ ] in this country.
You you you see them. I I see some guy
vaping in the cinema. They're just
[ __ ] That's what What do you mean?
What do they do? They've got no respect. They're [ __ ]
you know? They're [ __ ] in this
country. And then the actual guys that
have got respect, bro. I swear to God. Yeah.
I swear to God, this guy that was decent
looking was with a two out of 10 fat
black woman. I'm not even joking. And I
was like, "What the [ __ ] That is crazy,
bro. That is crazy. That is madness." It actually is.
That is crazy, bro.
I speaking to the guy in the cinema. He
works there. He's from Birmingham. I
said, "I remember you from a couple of
months ago." I said, "I was in Birmingham uh
bit over a month ago."
He was all right. But um
no, it's Porter, mate. Imagine having to
work in the cinema. Oh [ __ ] mate.
Imagine actually work there. Oh Jesus
Christ. No way.
No way, mate. No [ __ ] way.
No [ __ ] way, bro. That would be madness.
Wonder how he does it. Eh,
wonder how he does it. Wonder how that
guy does it. He's a young guy. got me
like my age. Don't know how he does it, mate.
Props to him.
Yeah, he was next to me [ __ ] vaping.
They're [ __ ] in this country, bro.
But if you see like an average looking
guy, right, and like you can tell he
goes gym and that, bro. Like, I'm happy
for anyone, you know? I mean, I'm not
jealous anyways. I'm not jealous
regardless. It's just the whole like
it's like it's trying to rub it in your
face. It's not a jealousy thing.
It's more of a like it torments you
thing cuz I'm not [ __ ] jealous of any
[ __ ] bro. What the [ __ ] But you get
what I mean. It's it's like torment
because Yeah, that's what it is. It's
like and they're [ __ ] as well.
And then the actual decent guys you see
have ugly women cuz a lot of guys are
with ugly women now.
They are mate. That [ __ ] fat black
woman was stinking, bro.
You couldn't even pay me to go to the
cinema with that. But they have to
settle now. There's there's so many
desperate guys now because of this whole
Tik Tok and this whole [ __ ] social
media [ __ ] There's so many desperate
[ __ ] guys. That's what they have.
It's that or nothing.
So that's how other guys do it by
[ __ ] lowering their [ __ ] standards
to next to [ __ ] nothing. badness, bro.
That is insane, bro. That is [ __ ] insane.
That is madness. Madness.
But when they're like decent, but then
sometimes you see like really
good-looking guys with like average
women. So, it's kind of like a mix. Um, but yeah.
Yeah. It's the pregnant women annoy me.
The the couples don't usually annoy me.
They usually would would annoy Ant-Man,
but it never used to annoy me. But that
annoyed me. That annoyed me, bro. I'm
not going to lie. That did annoy me.
Depends like, you know what I mean?
Obviously, I can't blame myself cuz
obviously I tried. So, there's nothing
more I could have done. So, I can't be
angry at myself. You can't even be angry
at yourself cuz you tried. So, it looks
like with the cinema now, I'll probably
have to start going out
probably probably Mondays.
I know most of horror films come out on
a Friday, but I have to go on Mondays.
I'm not [ __ ] looking at that [ __ ]
again. I have to go like first thing in
the morning or something.
That sounds mad. You actually have to I
feel like a famous person having to like
[ __ ] change the [ __ ] times I go
out and [ __ ]
But yeah, I'll have to go like really
early or something. That's depressing, bro.
And you'll see like people in the mall
and [ __ ] as well. Like the further out
you go, the more it annoys you.
No, I'm not feeling better at all.
No, I'm [ __ ] pissed off, bro. What the [ __ ]
So, and obviously I can't approach cuz
obviously if I approach then
the whole thing just starts again, you
know? So, like it's it's it's a country
designed to annoy you and get under your
skin. Generally is, bro. It generally is
a country. I can't wait to leave.
Honestly, I can't wait to leave, bro.
It's just full of absolute [ __ ]
It's full of them. You know, this
country is full of [ __ ]
Do you know I wish I was actually a dwarf?
Crazy. You know, I actually wish I was a
dwarf. Cuz at least if I was a dwarf,
there'd be an excuse for it.
There'd be a reason.
You know, if I was actually like a
dwarf, say I was someone like [ __ ] I
don't know, you see like famous dwarves
and [ __ ] If he was a dwolf, then
there'd actually be a reason for it.
You know, if you was like a little
person or [ __ ] I don't [ __ ] know,
bro. Some sort of disability, you know?
Then at least, you know, there'd be an
excuse for it. There's no excuse for it.
you know, you're [ __ ] young, you're
decent looking. Um,
you know, you're not skinned by Virgin
Boy. You know, there's not really no
reason for it, to be honest. It's madness.
Who would have thought, eh? Six.
I might not even eat today. Who knows? I
had like popcorn and sweets. Who knows? God knows.
I wonder how he does it. I wonder how
that guy from Birmingham does it. I was
speaking to him for a little bit
cuz I've seen him before and um I don't
know how he does it. I don't know how he
does it. I said to why did you move
here? He said, "Oh, family and
opportunities and shit." Um
I mean that would just depress the [ __ ]
out of me, but I suppose he's getting
paid for it. So,
I don't know how it doesn't bother him.
[ __ ] bothers me, mate. And it takes a
lot to [ __ ] bother me nowadays.
What am I supposed to do? Go out and
spend £300 again
or £250 again. I'm not doing it. So, [ __ ] that.
It is a country designed to annoy you.
made me think of USA a little bit today
in Listen Nico
probably does. Yeah,
unless he's in a relationship, but who knows?
I mean, I guess it would still annoy you
though, is it? But
it does annoy me, bro. This country is
designed to annoy you.
And yeah, it is the country's fault. It
is the whole country's fault. It's a [ __ ] hole.
It's just designed to [ __ ] with you. It
makes you want to do one thing that
leads to all of these other bad things.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. Stop talking about yourself, bro.
Stop self projecting.
Yeah. Yeah. Stop talking about yourself.
Everything you say is about yourself.
Back to L you go, mate. Yeah. Stop
talking about your disabled self. Your
mental health is never going to improve that way.
We all know I'm better looking than all
of you on here and I've got more money
than all of you on here, bro. It's
boring now. You know, you're a [ __ ]
old man going at somebody that you don't
even know, that you've never even met.
Get away with yourself, man. Don't try
and [ __ ] preach to others.
I'm better looking than all of you and
you're trying to call me big nose. Yeah,
I'm better looking than all of you. How
mad is that, bro? The definition of delusion.
You know what I'm saying? I'm better
looking than you. I'm better looking
than Virgin boy. And you still try to
say that I'm ugly when I'm better
looking than you. [ __ ] madness, bro.
These people, e known.
I mean, you saying about disabilities,
but you are the ones on YouTube every
day going at people that you don't even
know. How disabled do you have to be to
do that? s on YouTube in your 40s being
a [ __ ] every day of your life to
people that you don't even know that
you're never going to meet that you
never met. How ridiculous is that, bro?
That's got to be disabled, you know?
That has got to be disabled.
You know, you're another one that will
never show your face cuz you're an ugly bastard.
Why do these 40year-old ugly people try
to talk about my looks? I find it funny.
It's like, are they jealous or
something? It's crazy, isn't it? It just
makes them look so insecure.
Like I'm generally better looking than
all of them and they still try to call
me a bun. It's crazy, bro. It's [ __ ] madness.
Some these 40-year-old wrinkly ugly old
men sat on YouTube every day talking
about other people,
fat, ugly virgins. Like most of these
are virgins on here, bro. Don't watch
that [ __ ] Don't try and tell Don't let
them try to tell you otherwise. these 40
year old ugly old men that come on
YouTube every day cuz they ain't got a
life. You know, you know what I mean?
Calling people skin again. Everything
you say is about your own lives. You
people are skint. You all run away every
single time you get shown money. You run
away every time cuz you are the skint ones.
Skinn ugly old men that have got nothing
in your life. That's why you come on
here to feel better about your the fact
that you're fat, ugly, alone, wrinkly.
You can't say that [ __ ] about me, bro.
You know what I mean? Fat, spasticated,
ugly old men on YouTube every day. Who
are you to preach to anybody, bro? Come on now.
[ __ ] ugly 40-year-old virgins trying
to preach to [ __ ] others.
You know why I don't bother with them,
bro? That's why I don't bother doing a
video back to these little self-reflectors
cuz you know the thing is
you're never going to get that time
back. You argue with these people. You
know that you know when these people
self-reflect their skinnness, their
mountainness, their ugliness,
their everything is you know every time
you respond to these self- projectors
you know you just lose time your life
you show them £6,000 they call you skin
they run away. You show you better
looking than them they run away and try
to call you ugly. You try to meet these
people, they all shy away and pretend it
never happened. It's the definition of
disabled. You know what I'm saying? Like
it generally is.
These disabled, fat, ugly people on
YouTube every day trying to put other
people down. It's a madness, isn't it?
Skin fat ugly gamblers hate themselves,
so they come here every day. That's why
I don't waste my time on them. There's
something to laugh at.
It's like the skinn virgin in the
bedsit. Think about it, Nicolo. If he
really had 14 grand, why did he run away
when I showed him six? Think about it.
He's not. They've got all this money.
Why did all of them run away when I
showed them £6,000?
Why was there no Joe? There was no
Virgin boy. There was no L. It's cuz
they are skint. The evidence is that
they are skint. They ain't got nothing.
They ain't got no money. That's why they
come on here every day cuz they're
skinned ugly people waiting for their
disabled benefits and they like to
self-reflect. They like to think
everyone's life is the same as theirs.
You know what I mean? They like to think
everyone's life is the same as [ __ ]
theirs. If I didn't know any better,
bro, I would have went to Birmingham
today and call that [ __ ] mic out. If
if this was a if this was, bro, if this
was two years ago, yeah, back when me
and [ __ ] LT was going at it, I would
have went today 100%. I would have went
I would have went on a drink and
everything, but bro, they're not they're
not worth the time. They're not worth
the money. These spastics, you know, you
don't see them on here now. You don't
see Joe on here now. You don't see Mike
These fat ugly people are not on here
now. You know what I'm saying? Bro, I
would have went 100% I would have went.
But a wise person learns from their
mistakes. You know, showing these
skinned people money and then they run
away. um showing that you're better
looking than them and they can't show
their face. Trying to meet people and
they never meet you. Like a wise person
learns from their mistakes.
You know, a stable person learns from
their mistakes. You understand what I'm saying, bro?
I think that's you know, you know, you
don't make the same mistakes over and
over and over again.
If he I wish that money might done that
[ __ ] before I went to Birmingham and I
would have called him out along as along
with Timmy and along with Prime. I would
have called them out, bro. What the [ __ ]
But like, there's no point with these
people cuz they're just self-reflectors.
They ain't got no money. If they really
had no, bro, listen, listen. If these
people really had money, they would have
beat me at the money game. When I was
showing them money when I could be asked
with them, right, they literally they
literally Right. Yeah, bro. He's He's
[ __ ] disabled. He's [ __ ] he's his
[ __ ] sister's kid's [ __ ] disabled.
He's disabled. He's ugly. Sister's kids
are ugly. Like, he ain't going to he
ain't going to come for me, bro. Are you
mad? Not even one little bit.
He's ugly. His sister's ugly. Her kids
are ugly. You know, that's it. They look
like penguins, but they're the [ __ ]
Adam family, bro. [ __ ] stupid ugly
bastard with his ugly sister with her
ugly kids. And that's me saying
something about him. And he ain't going
to come for me, bro. Cuz I'll meet him
anywhere in London he wants. Yeah, you
should have saw how this guy moves.
You know what I'm saying, bro? But like
he was [ __ ] himself. You know when I
met him when he come down there, he was
[ __ ] himself, bro. I'm not even
joking. Yeah. Like, bro, serious.
They're all like that. Why do you think
Joe don't come on here, bro, anymore?
Cuz they know they're just going to get
owned. There's no point. But anyways, if
these people really weren't skin, do you
really think they would be letting me
show thousands and thousands for as long
as I did and them not show a penny? They
didn't show a penny because they don't
have money. It's because they're
skinned. Think about it, bro. Let's say
Smokey B wasn't on here. Yeah. And he
didn't see it. Let's give him the
benefit of the doubt. Okay. So, we
remove him. L Joe Virgin Boy. Think
about it, bro. If they have all of this
money, why do they all continuously run
away and not be able to show anything
but less than half what you've shown?
Because they are skint. And a normal
person that can understand things will
understand it. They do it because they
are skid. If someone has got as much
money as these people claim, well, I was
waiting [ __ ] 18 months and no one
showed me nothing. So, I was like, "Fuck
this. No one's going to show me
anything." Put the money in the bank.
Then I got some backdated money. I had
even more money by the end of it and I
was like, "You know what? [ __ ] these
people. I'm not showing them nothing
anymore." Cuz a wise person learns from
their mistakes. They're just self
projectors. That's all they are. There's
no point wasting time on them, bro.
They're just talking about theirelves.
You know, you got someone showing a
[ __ ] pension. You got someone showing
a pension that they can't even touch.
Come on, bro. I'm saying
a pension that he can't even touch.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Like,
think about it. If these pe these people
don't have no money. None of these
people have money, bro. They're sat on
YouTube every day skin. They ain't got a
life. They ain't got no [ __ ] money.
We all know what these people do.
Yeah, they were.
And you got these fat, ugly men trying
to call people that they don't know
every day. It's like [ __ ] It's like
Virgin Boy. You know why? I was going to
I was going to respond, but then I
thought there's just no point.
You know, is everyone forgetting that I
went to this c area three times and had
him crying and running to the police and
that he ran to the police of because of
YouTube? Like, bro, like there's no
point. There's no point wasting your
time with someone like that. Some little
skint self-rejecting virgin because it
doesn't matter what you show them or
what you tell these sad individual low
lives, bro, it's not going to make a
difference. It's a waste of time. You
know what I'm saying, bro?
You know what they're like, bro. Really,
I shouldn't even be on it. I know what
they're like. Cuz I I I'm just basically
just as bad as them really when I
respond to them. Because at the end of
the day, like they they do this [ __ ]
bro. Cuz they're jealous. You know,
they're fat, ugly, low lives that are
jealous or something. That's why they
try to go at people every day that
they've never met and then they don't
know. You understand, bro? Like, so when
you respond, you're basically no good as
them because they do what they do cuz
they're jealous, ugly people that ain't
got no life.
So it's not I'm not making a good
example. Do you know what I'm saying?
Can't show their face. Can't show any
money. You know what I'm saying? Like
what the [ __ ] bro? These people are weirdos. You know,
because you got anxiety, bro. Just like [ __ ] Timmy.
Like when he comes back on it, I'm going
to assault on him, bro. And and I'll say
to him, "If you want to come London,
I'll pay for everything. Your train,
your hotel, everything. Don't [ __ ]
let me catch you talking [ __ ] behind my
back, you [ __ ] ugly cunt." I don't
like that [ __ ] bro. Honestly, the only
reason I did not go today is cuz a wise
person learned from their mistakes. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying, bro? I know
what they do on here. I've been up and
down the country partly because of this
community. You understand, bro? Like, I
don't like that [ __ ] So, when he comes
back on it, I'm going to start on him,
bro, 100%. I'm going to pay for his
[ __ ] train and I'm going to pay for
his [ __ ] hotel.
Simple. I would have went today. It's
Friday. I would have just went on the
piss. I would have just went there.
What? An hour and 20 minutes? Hour and
30 minutes. But I'm not wasting my time
anymore, you know, because we all know
what happens. We all know exactly what
happens. How the cookie crumbles. They
just act like it never happened. Just
like when you show money and [ __ ] It's
why I don't waste my time, bro. It's not
like I'm contradicting anything I'm saying.
Mark Samson for example, that's the best
person to bring up. Went to his area two
times. No one ever said anything about
it. That's how you knew you were [ __ ]
from the start, bro. With these fat,
ugly, jealous people that ain't got a
life. You know, if you're you don't
understand, bro. Yeah. With with this place.
If you are not the same as them, fat,
ugly, disabled, no hopers, they don't
like anyone. They don't like people. So
whatever you do, Yeah. they're going to
deny it. Do not understand how how this [ __ ] works.
You know what I'm saying, bro? That's
how it works on here. You know,
you know what I mean, bro? So,
and that's what like even like I always
bring up that Mark Thompson thing
because I feel like that's like the best
point to bring up.
Went to that fucker's area two [ __ ]
times. You didn't come out. What the [ __ ] bro?
They're just all like, "Yeah, there's
just no point getting into it with these people." You know,
even when you show them money, they
don't show you nothing. That's why I
don't show them money no more. You don't
think I've got money? That's on you,
bro. I know my life. I know what I have.
I know what I don't have. You know what
I'm saying? Like you want to keep saying
that. You keep saying that, bro.
I weren't the one showing [ __ ]
thousands and ran away.
They're just self-reflectors. They
[ __ ] waste waste of time, bro. I mean, yeah.
That's where we're at.
The how they have so much to hate the
people that they don't even know that
they've never even met is beyond me.
Like, think about it, bro. Your life's
[ __ ] You're in your 40s, okay? you
failed in life. Don't take that on other
people. You just at home skip g all your
money, you know, and you come across
people that are better looking than you,
have a life, you know, that's the reason
why they do all of this [ __ ] You know
what I'm saying? This is the reason why
these [ __ ] fat ugly people do this
every day. You know,
it's madness. It is absolute madness.
So, I don't even feel hungry today for some reason.
You people are never going to stop.
You're never going to stop over. minute.
What's your actual like goal of this? I
don't actually understand. You know,
you're never going to meet anyone.
You're never going to say anything to
anyone's face. D. What is the whole
point of all of this?
Why are you doing this every day? you
know, calling people that you don't
know, self-reflecting your life every
day. What What are you like trying to
achieve? I don't understand. You're
never going to meet anyone. You're never
going to stop. Reaction or no reaction.
Like you you must live really sad lives, you know? Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, man.
So that's where we're at.
So, is anyone going to answer or like what?
Why are you people sit on YouTube every
day doing what you do to people that you
don't even know that you're never going
to meet? Huh?
No. Joe, no. Mike, huh? Crazy, is it,
bro? [ __ ] crazy.
They start [ __ ] they can't finish.
Typical people on YouTube, eh? Craziness. Craziness.
So, you got to like come on and explain
it or what?
Cuz if you truly wasn't jealous of
someone, you wouldn't do this every day
and not stop for years. Like, come on.
Let's let's let's really think about it,
bro. You're sat there trying to call me
all the things that you are skinn ugly.
I don't know. All the things that apply
to you, but bro, you wouldn't be doing
this if that was the case.
Self it's self-explanatory, bro. It's
It's self [ __ ] explanatory.
I don't know what I'm eating today. I've
got some chicken. I don't know whether
to cook it,
get a takeway, or I don't [ __ ] know.
I don't know. I might not even eat. I
don't [ __ ] know what I want.
Still kind of fill up on the popcorn.
But you know what I mean? Like it's fun.
Probably just cook some chicken if I am
going to eat
some chicken there.
Why you sit there and do what you do
every day? It's [ __ ] madness.
Yeah, they do hate their lives. I can go
out right now today, spend four, five,
600 if I wanted to. Have a good night
out. I'm not [ __ ] skinned. You don't
know anyone. You don't know what what
why is people skin? Because they don't
want to show you money anymore. Cuz if
every single time they do, you will run away.
And a wise person learns from their
mistakes, you know. [ __ ]
A wise person learns from their mistakes.
No. You think people can't show me
money? Of course they [ __ ] can.
And I said if I didn't win the football
bet, I would be involve if I tried to go
out a couple of times. Yes, I would. Cuz
if I went out and sp tried spending400 a
couple more times in a row, I would be
[ __ ] Just like [ __ ] most people.
So [ __ ] what, bro?
No one's going on like they're rich, but
they got [ __ ] more money than you.
You know what I'm saying? More money
than a [ __ ] skinned virgin in a [ __ ] bedit.
You know, you can sit online every day
being angry. It's a waste of time.
You're never going to need whatever to appointment.
That's where we're at, bro.
But yeah, if I didn't win that football
bet, bro, I would be
Yeah, it wouldn't be good. So, yeah,
I just start [ __ ] working [ __ ] as
well, you know. Oh yeah.
Yeah. Every time you choose to actually
go out, like it could be a Thursday, it
would start raining.
It's a country designed to annoy you and
get under your skin.
And uh it it's a country designed to
annoy you and get under your skin.
So a lot of people can uh agree with
that one as well.
I think it is. I generally think it is,
bro. People got different opinions on
it, but I think it definitely is a
country designed to annoy you
waiting around for things. Uh you have
to wait around for everything in this
country as well. [ __ ] horrible
country it is. It's [ __ ]
Just like America. [ __ ] [ __ ] Oh, [ __ ]
No, I've not had that for [ __ ] ages.
It's good. I won that football bet. Is it Nicolo? Nice 380. Yeah.
It's good, ain't it? Put my money back
for Sunday and Monday. Oh, [ __ ] Yeah, man.
I hate this country.
Nice cup of I I hate this country, bro.
You don't understand. I hate the women.
I hate the people.
That guy was right though in Birmingham, the worker.
He seemed like a nice chap, you know.
I was going to tell him about the
bounces in Birmingham. They're pricks,
but it's not really something you bring
up, you know.
How much do you reckon they get a week
them cinema workers? You know?
Yeah. God, it's like the it's like the
um when I used to go um gambling in the
casinos, but obviously on a lot lesser
scale. Like it's like a lot lesser
scale. Obviously, you're still winning
money. Money is money, but it's just on
a lesser scale. Obviously, I'm older
now. I don't go out as much now. So,
it's like it's God feeling sorry for
you, but just on a lot lesser scale.
So, I mean, obviously, but still still
money in it.
Yeah, if it didn't win, it would have
been not good, bro. Yeah.
Oh, I hate that guy. He's so fat and
ugly. Oh my god.
Yeah, he's some fat ugly bastard. Is it?
Yeah, that fat ugly bastard. Yeah.
Yeah, I know him, bro. I know who he is.
How much do you reckon they get a week
working? How much reckon you get a week
working the cinema? Like what? 450 maybe.
Would you say like 450?
It's crazy how much [ __ ] I've actually
been through in this country. I think
you underestimated, bro. I've been
through so much [ __ ] in this country.
You know what I mean?
So, how much would you guess that he
gets a week? that that guy in Birmingham,
how does he live and like go drinking
then? If he gets minimum wage, how does
he go out drinking and [ __ ]
You know, they must get over a grand a
month though. It must do.
They must do. No.
You know, the thing is most people can't
even afford to go out drinking.
That's that's the that's the problem.
That's how mad it is. It's not even
like, yeah, you can just go out and
drink now cuz you're you're [ __ ] when
as soon as you go out, you know, you're
[ __ ] cuz you're spending big money,
you know? So, I'm probably Yeah. So
200 250 maybe if you wanted to do a
Saturday and Sunday
it's expensive bro. It's not cheap. Um yeah. Yeah.
They must get a bit more than minimum wage.
They must get more than minimum wage, bro. [ __ ]
Nice when you win a bet cuz you haven't
had to work, have you? Good. Is it? Good, matey.
I'm so tired, bro. [ __ ] tired of this
[ __ ] you know? Tired of this life.
There's this sexy woman on um
WhatsApp I've got, Nicolo, and I got her
number sober and she never ever replied.
She didn't block me. She just never replied. [ __ ] man.
Never replied to [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] in it, bro.
Oh, [ __ ] man.
It's bad, isn't it?
I feel so tired.
No phone ain't [ __ ] broke. She's just a [ __ ]
Should I get a ticker curry today?
I like a lamb ticker curry. No, bro.
I know you're like I know like you're
[ __ ] you just how you know you're
like on the urge of giving up forever
when you actually want to work instead
of going out approaching that and you
don't even need to work you know
the only thing I could do is just work
and use escorts till I leave that's the
only thing I can do it's like 2 months
so that's only the only thing I can do
that's all that's left from here.
Unless you met someone online, which
ain't going to happen.
The only thing you could do is yeah, use
[ __ ] escorts and [ __ ]
uh until you leave. And yeah, it's not
the same, but it's better than nothing,
you know? So, it's better than nothing.
It's [ __ ] depressing. It is, bro.
This one going to the [ __ ] cinema, eh? [ __ ]
This one going to the [ __ ] cinema. Yeah.
What should I eat today?
I have no cash.
I don't live with Laney.
I mean, it's [ __ ] madness.
Life is [ __ ] bro. that.
Oh, definitely a sh in it. Um,
I'm going to order some food.
No, I don't go off until the 11th.
I need to be careful, bro. I can't keep
wasting [ __ ] money. Um,
can't keep wasting money, matey.
So, yeah, I think I'm going to get a
lamb chicken curry. Great. Yeah.
Right. Give me a minute. Let me do this.
How are you going to lose it? How is
Virgin M going to lose it?
What the [ __ ] M.
They make dating seem so easy. It's the
hardest thing ever.
They make it seem so easy when there's
literally nothing easy about it.
But what about the other guys?
The other guys that have to lower their
[ __ ] standards. Uhhuh.
Uh, right. We need to get some.
What? The other guys? Yeah.
The other guys that have to uh
lamb. No, I don't want lamb or chicken.
I want a chicken ticker one.
Why is there not a what? Um,
no. I want it.
I want a lamb. I want an actual lamb ticker one.
I don't want a lamb. I want a lamb tickle on.
Why isn't it come up? It's got
no one second.
Oh, for [ __ ] sake, man. What the [ __ ]
I have to go where I order before you
go like that, mate. You got laz like
Oh, here we go.
How you going lazy? How you going lazy?
Oh, I'm sorry. Chicken ticker pillow
rice. Lamb ta bindaloo curry.
Yeah. Yes, please.
If we didn't win that football bet, we
would have been [ __ ]
with a WA.
No, we would have We would have been in
serious bubber, mate.
We would have been in serious bobber.
You You believe me, right?
We would have been in some serious bother.
Some serious bother, matey.
[ __ ] And then I'd have to try and
[ __ ] I don't know what the [ __ ] I
would have done, bro.
So yeah, I'm going to get this um thing,
but then I can't have any more [ __ ]
takeaways after this, mate. We need to
[ __ ] put this money towards [ __ ]
holiday. You know what I mean, mate? So
But all you going to be all right.
No, but if this [ __ ] is serious, I'll
[ __ ] go Canada when I come back.
I don't care if I meet somebody in
another country. I'll go to another
country when I come back. I don't even [ __ ]
This is never going to change here, is it?
[ __ ] I've been dealing with for so long.
Right, let me order this food. [ __ ] me.
[ __ ] me, man.
20 quid. That's not too bad to be
honest. I got some sort of discount.
Do you think that's a good return on a
football bet? Steven Howard
120 to 380. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. It is. Yeah, man. more than
cuz I get all my money [ __ ] next
week. So obviously if they didn't win
then I would have probably had like [ __ ]
probably like [ __ ] £200.
So in my in that's me. So I would have
been [ __ ] in an account like well not
I would have still had my bills paid and [ __ ] but
you know I like to have more than that
you know so and I spent a lot of money
I actually would have been [ __ ] bro like
it's not even funny Yeah.
Yeah, he does.
He needs to get plastic surgery for his
ugly face. He might stand a chance.
I don't know what I'm going to do, bro.
Like two months.
Life is stressful, man.
When you going to lose it? How you going
Yeah. Virgin, right?
He says that I'm skim and he's got 14
grand. Uh, mate, you got 14 grand.
That's why when you got shown six grand,
you ran away. Oh, where was the 14 grand
then? Big man. Ah, you ain't got
nothing, mate. You ain't got [ __ ] all the skinting skint.
You're literally skinting flint, mate.
And it's not it's not only when you're
going to lose it, it's how you're going
to lose it. You know how you going to
lose it, Virgin boy? Wow.
Oh, you're going to lose it.
You won't, mate.
I've got a coming, mate. That you can't
uh you can't handle. Yeah.
That you can't [ __ ] handle, matey. Uh yeah.
What a life, mate. What a [ __ ] life.
What a [ __ ] life, mate. Could
be a lot. It could be a lot. It could be
a lot worse financially, bro. We could
be like [ __ ] virgin boy skin uh fing skimpling.
You know, your best bet is Yeah, you
should do this job. Yeah. Non-stop. Do
like some crackhead hours, bro. Try and
make some money on that and then do like
some big both teams to score. Like£700
on the both teams to score. You'll be
set for like maybe six months.
So you'll be right for like six months.
That's the dream, bro.
Just work every day for a month. Yeah.
Try him in like a football bet every
week. You'll be good for like 6 months,
bro. Easy. Easy. 6 months.
That's the [ __ ] dream, bro.
You know, January, February, you don't
go out in it. So, January, February, you
don't go out.
So, whatever month you choose to just
work. Yeah, it's [ __ ] But, I mean,
you'll be laughing at the end when you
by the time you've added your money up
and whatever, you won't have to work.
You won't have to um
you won't have to like work for a long
time. So, sounds like a plan. Uh it is.
do it every other day or every day
now along with the gym as well. You'd be
laughing at [ __ ] you done it every
other day for a month or a month and a
half. You be be laughing mate any kind
of job and then you try and win a
football bet as well. You're good good to go.
It's the only thing you really can do now. So yeah,
I'm not on a grand a month. I got some
money last month. I got some money this
That wasn't quite grand a month, was it? Virgin boy.
Wasn't quite grand a month, was it, Virgin Boy?
No. Virgin boy.
No, it's more like 1617, wasn't it?
Grand a month boy.
He is actually grand boy, mate.
Don't forget we won three football bets
out of five.
So all of them football bets I think we won
350 to almost £600. Yep.
Nobody was out.
So obviously just work for like a month.
You'll have enough money in you know a month.
That's the only thing I can actually
think of now going forward. lag.
You should have had my bet. I just wish
I had the whole 160 on it
to be honest with you. I just wish I had
a whole 160 on it now.
>> Would have been like [ __ ] almost 600
[ __ ] quid, man. But I just put the 40 on roulette. But yeah.
Oh [ __ ] man.
Doesn't matter, bro. Like I said, I'm
happy to have anything. So
yeah, I don't know what I would have
done. I would have been in the doghouse, mate.
I would have been in the dog house,
matey. I would have almost been in the doghouse, matey.
that Sunday, you see. So yeah,
you [ __ ] go out, you drink, the
[ __ ] money just goes.
That's another thing, you know. Virgin
boy, he doesn't have no life experience.
Never been out, never been with a normal
woman, never had designer clothes, never
been abroad until he was 31. It's just
as if everything about him just seems skint.
Do you know what I'm saying, bro?
Everything about that virgin just seems
skin. Or is it [ __ ] me, bro?
Is it me or does everything about that
virgin scream skin? Bedshit.
No designer clothes, no bed. [ __ ] me,
bro. I wouldn't like to live live that
as a as a person that's apparently got
all this money, you know.
Makes you wonder, doesn't it?
[ __ ] I've got designer clothes in
that white bag, mate. That's worth more
than his whole [ __ ] life.
You got more money than them. You're
better looking than them. And you've got
a better life than them. And it kills
And it kills them.
Yeah, his face is disgusting and he
tries to call me a monto. It's it's just
simply projection, you know.
If I'm so ugly, why have I been with all
of the women that he stalks? If I'm so ugly,
I think his disability has got himself
confused with me.
Skin m that's literally you. You should
try looking in the mirror sometimes,
man. And you actually see that that's
yourself you're talking about.
Skint M. That's literally you. You ugly bastard.
You need to stop talking about yourself.
And also skin is you as well. You are
and a fing skin flinch. Skin
Isn't that right, Zippy? Yeah, it is. Yeah.
Come on. Food you call.
One second. I'll be right back. Oh, [ __ ]
Sorry about that, bro. Almost [ __ ] fell over.
How are you going to lose it?
How you going to lose it?
How you going to lose it, boy?
How you going to lo? Oh [ __ ]
So yeah, [ __ ] Uber.
Remember the Uber thing, Steven Howard?
Uh, funny. Yeah,
you can't even get a [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's a [ __ ] madness, isn't it, bro?
You can't even get a [ __ ] [ __ ] eh?
I bet you wish. Do you know what? I wish
I had that 120 on a both score, no draw,
man. Cuz that was actually a both score, no draw.
I would have been laughing, matey.
cuz that was a both score no draw.
I'm not doing a bet Saturday. I don't
need to gamble, bro. I'll only gamble
when I need extra money.
I'll be all right now for a little while. So,
yeah, I'll be good.
For a little while. Anyways,
yeah, of course it would have
be all right for a little bit. But yeah,
it's just a going out that's [ __ ]
expensive, is it?
That's the only thing.
And then you just don't get anything
when you do go out. It's just the same [ __ ]
Same [ __ ] you put up with every time you go out. So, you know, Yeah.
Virgin boy can't afford to go out, can
he? Skint virgin boy.
[ __ ] 14 grand. The cunt's never had
14 grand in his [ __ ] life. [ __ ] skint [ __ ]
That [ __ ] virgin boy has never [ __ ] had
never had [ __ ]
He's never had [ __ ] six He's never
had [ __ ] 14 grand in his life. The [ __ ] virgin.
Is he not Is he sure he's not sucking
his dad's dick too much
and he's actually forgetting or something?
You sure he's not like sucking his
[ __ ] dad's dick too much?
Cuz uh it seems that way to me.
I think he's sucking he's had stick a
bit too much, bro.
[ __ ] Virgin boys never had 14 grand.
14 grand. But you're living in a bed suit.
No, mate. I don't think so, matey.
You're better looking than them. You've
got more money than them. And you got a
better life than them. And it kills
And it [ __ ] kills them.
That's funny, isn't it, bro? True.
It's true though, isn't it?
Better looking, more money, better life.
It's true though, ain't it? 100%. 100 million%.
That's a madness, lad.
Yeah. Nice lamb. Chick curry and uh
More teeth, more money, better looking.
But I am coming off this [ __ ] soon
though on a real bro. On a real on a
these little mongos to it, bro. At some
point though, man, on on a real real cuz
I need to like do some stuff, bro. So, I
I'm not going to have time for this [ __ ]
with these little self-p projecting
little weirdos that ain't got a life.
Sorry, bro. Like, it's called being an
adult at some point, matey. These people
can sit on here being skinn every day
talking about other people, bro. But
that ain't going to be me. That ain't
going to be my life. So,
skin like these [ __ ] people. No life, no money,
talking about themselves every day on YouTube.
But you probably won't see me for like
probably 6 weeks minimum.
Sorry about that, matey.
These people give me the EBGBs.
They're [ __ ] creepy.
Bunch of fat, ugly men jealous of people
that they don't know. [ __ ] mad. So yeah. Yeah. One second. [Music]
Should be here shortly.
[ __ ] me, man.
I'm tired, man.
So, I could go out approaching every
day, but it's pointless cuz it's just
the same old [ __ ] So,
I'm kind of done as far as this place
goes. This country, same [ __ ] you know?
It's bad, is it, bro? It's bad.
Work, make money, leave. All you can do Yeah.
Yeah. That's where we're at, bro.
No, no, no. USA
USA Izzy is a [ __ ] Oh man.
USA is the is a [ __ ]
Is a [ __ ] man.
See, Peter belly smart. He can make money, mate. Nah.
So, I need to do that. And then
don't forget I got a TV as well.
But before this whole women [ __ ] you
need to make sure you know you're financially stable.
Like don't need loads and loads of money
because you don't want to be worried about money.
It's not one thing you want to worry
about. It's [ __ ] money, bro. [ __ ] that [ __ ]
That's why I said if you done the work
thing every day for a month combined,
you probably win a couple of football
bets, you'll be set. When you get 11,200
every month, you'll be good to go.
for a little while. So, yeah.
So, imagine I put that money in Frankie. [ __ ] that.
Imagine that. Yeah. Putting that money in Frankie
980. [ __ ] that. No,
I don't 50. I want a one at 280. I'll
put 50 and Frankie.
Yeah, he's a [ __ ]
So if 120 is 380, how much would a 160
been like 530?
What would that been like? 530 in it.
[ __ ] hell, man.
Yeah, probably like 530 in it. Oh man.
Yeah, it would have been about 5:30. [ __ ] sake.
It would have been about 5:30. Yeah.
something like that.
I don't know how much I'm going to spend
when I go out drinking again.
How much do you think?
100 150 200 250 [ __ ] hell, man. Crazy expensive
just to hear
I got a boyfriend.
[ __ ] you hell, man. You know,
just to hear that [ __ ]
Yeah, that's what most people do.
Pre-drink. That's what I need to get the habit of doing.
Going through an off license and
drinking beer and getting pissed on beer.
I don't usually do that though. Need to [ __ ] Yeah. Yes.
One second, bro.
Yeah, sorry about that, man.
Just watching these um these approaches.
Nah, not since the other day, man.
I only do them when I need the extra money.
and I haven't been needing any. So,
imagine you put £500 on both teams to score.
That's [ __ ] how much? [ __ ] That's
like [ __ ] £1,900. Imagine that.
That is crazy, bro.
It's good return, isn't it?
Virgin boy could never put 120 on a football bet.
Virgin boy could never. Mr. B.
cuz his skin Mr. B.
He can't cuz he's skinnier than a
[ __ ] skink clinch.
Well, my food should be hy.
Cy's there, mate. Hey,
[ __ ] curry there, mate.
Come on up, you [ __ ] skinned bird
virgin in a bed sit with a fat ugly
girlfriend. That's my [ __ ] nickname
to the [ __ ] [ __ ]
Why? Rat face with a big fat ugly
girlfriend in the bedset. That's my
little [ __ ] uh my little nickname to you.
Nickname to virgin boy.
Look what I got.
What life is something you saw on the
phone is your [ __ ] skin
turn a skin fl.
Have you ever seen this [ __ ]
Have you seen this 14 grand virgin boy
going on about?
Have you seen this [ __ ] 14 grand
virgin boy going on about?
Well, I'm going to do a video.
I'm going to have to do a video, mate.
This is too nice. Get out.
One second, mate. I'm have to do a video
about my song. Yeah,
this is about to be a serious mood.
I thought I'd get the lamb tick up
because you can't chew it cuz you got no
teeth. You're going to sit there in your
[ __ ] bed set [ __ ] skin [ __ ]
trying to [ __ ] talk about other
people, man. You [ __ ] mud. Yeah,
they're proper jealous, bro.
You know, giving it the bigger than your
shitty little K virgin bedsuit with a
fat ugly girlfriend. One sec here, mate. What?