[ __ ] hell, man.
Uh, I can't believe that account was 18
years old. I was nine
like when I was back at the old house.
It just goes to show what I've been
saying all along about these old farts
on this community. An account [ __ ]
made 18 [ __ ] years ago. Wow.
18 years ago. That's a madness. They
really are fat old and ugly, aren't
they? 18 18 years old. That was way
before I was on Skype.
Way before I met the Virgin. [ __ ] hell.
That is insanely lame. Boring.
Yeah. So that account that's [ __ ] 18
years old. Jesus Christ. [ __ ] hell.
18 years old.
Imagine that. That's like a baby to a
[ __ ] adult. Like legally. I told you
these were old fat ugly [ __ ] I told
you, bro. Who the [ __ ] has one account
from 18 years ago,
bro? That's a madness.
These people really are fat, old, and
ugly, aren't they, bro? I knew it.
Yeah, I lost 30 pound on a boat. No draw.
Ah, so did I.
So did I, man.
So did I.
Mine was 30.
Off to the Yeah, I have an account
greasy. Yeah, I commented on my live
stream and it's 13.
Um, boring. Um, it's it was 18 years old.
18 years oldest account. [ __ ] hell.
Still going on about that Morgan thing.
Damn. You really are obsessed and
jealous. You're just something to laugh
at. You're not even anything to react
to. Well, you you're still going on
about that. Jealousy is a horrible
thing. It's been known to kill many
people. you know, jealousy. So, yeah.
Nah, man. 18 years.
18 [ __ ] years. It just goes to show
they're all old fat, ugly people that
come on this community. It's obvious.
And they're trying to talk about people
half their age that they don't even
know. Get [ __ ] real. Oh [ __ ]
That is a madness, bro. [ __ ]
Yeah, that is an actual madness.
Add a Chinese again.
Ah, that's nice.
That's nice. I run a 30 pound boat score
no draw today. I lost
I didn't mind. Really bit fun.
That's nice, man.
I'm done with I'm done with the
approaching. I'm not approaching. Uh did
you not listen to anything that I say
when I kind of tell you that I've given
up and the fact that I only go out when
I'm extremely bored, which is like every month? Uh no.
To answer your question, do you not
listen to anything I say? Have you got
um early stages of dementia?
Have you got uh have you got dementia or
something? Because somebody will tell
you something and then you'll come back
and say, "Oh, you out tonight when I've
literally told you that, no, I'm not. I
don't do it anymore unless I'm extremely
bored and got nothing else to do and I'm
dying to bottom because that's what
happens when you lose hope.
When you lose hope, that's how how it
is. You know, when when you lose hope,
that's that's the end. You know,
you don't take anything I say serious.
Really? Oh, well, you should have took
that serious cuz I was being serious
about that. I am done. You know, I was
speaking to Ant-Man yesterday.
Sorry to repeat this. Some of you
weren't on it. And he was like, "Oh,
like if he was still here, he'd go out
every week because if you ain't got
hope, then you're basically fucked." And
then I obviously explain that like I
don't have hope. Like I don't go out cuz
I have hope. I go out cuz I'm extremely
bored. And if I'm not been out for a
couple of weeks. Yeah.
But yeah, I go out when I'm like when
I'm really really really I'd have to
really be bored. This happens after like
two or three weeks. But it's like today
I could have went out easy whilst that
football was was going on. But getting
your hair done in the heat, getting the
same old [ __ ] over and over and over
again. You know, it's like it becomes a
time to like call it a day. You know
what I've done. So I've lost all hope completely.
So, but I think a lot um yeah. So, yeah. What's that? Yeah.
What is that?
Yeah. I can't be bothered with it anymore, bro.
Oh, [ __ ] My head's hurting, bro.
I was speaking to this woman in America
yesterday. I wanked so much. Yeah.
That my dick is hurting today.
Mate, I've had [ __ ] more hot food
than you'll ever have. You nasty little
virgin. Don't [ __ ] come on my channel
talking about [ __ ] curries, mate.
Where I'm [ __ ] from. They actually
make normal curries, not in your little
skint [ __ ] hole that you live in, you
skint virgin. Now, do yourself a favor
and [ __ ] off and suck your dad's dick, silly [ __ ]
skin silly [ __ ] SSC. Yeah, man.
Okay, let me let me explain this to you
one more time, right? And I want you to
open up your ears. Yeah. I have given
up. I don't give a [ __ ] about women in
this [ __ ] country.
All these women. Shut the [ __ ] up, you
old ma. Shut the [ __ ] up. I have had all
of these women, but like I said, we know
how the Subway chocolate chip cookie
crumbles with you people.
Yeah, I bet on Spenny and uh Darlington.
I only put £30 on it, so I didn't care.
It was more for like a fun thing. Um
yeah, this woman wants to meet me
tomorrow at Tinder, but on Tinder, but
she's kind of stinking. And it means
going all the way to [ __ ] where she is,
which is quite far. I mean, it's just
outskirts of London. Then I'd be [ __ ]
Like honestly, like I said, Nicolo, bro,
if I didn't know what these people are
like on here, I would have went to
Birmingham yesterday and smash that
money in. But we all know how the cookie
crumbles on this community and what
these people do.
It's worth it if she could [ __ ] suck
your [ __ ] dick.
I mean, if she gives you a [ __ ] then
it is. I mean, a [ __ ] is a [ __ ]
[ __ ] Yeah. If you're not [ __ ]
paying for it, why not? I think I could
probably get there for free, to be
honest. That's when I'd waste my time if
something was actually guaranteed.
But we all know how the Subway cookie
crumbles on this community with you
people. You take L's and act like it never happened.
Is that right, Nicolo?
Why we don't waste our time on you people anymore?
the money game, the meeting game,
you know. Yeah. Hot women everywhere
that aren't interested. Yeah.
Yeah. Hot women that aren't interested.
Yeah. I'm done with this conversation,
bro. Stop bringing it up now. I've
already told you I've given up. When I
go live again in 3 weeks out and about,
bro, you'll see when I'm out and about.
I generally have lost hope
to um Monty probably man.
Bro, I am done in this country. Do you
not understand? I don't know how many
times I have to explain this.
Do you not understand? I am done. I am
finished. [ __ ] sake. Yeah.
[ __ ] sake, bro. You don't listen, do you, man?
Why are you on Tinder then? Why am I Why
am I on Tinder?
Why am I on Tinder?
Well, the reason I'm on Tinder is to see
how [ __ ] it still is and it doesn't make
two seconds going on Tinder. It doesn't
mean me getting my haircut, wasting
loads of money,
and going out. So, yes, I've given up.
Like, I'm even doing things I never ever
used to do before. Like, I'll message
people on Instagram, message people on
dating apps. I'm I'm not putting effort
into it because that that is not even
trying. You I mean I mean you going on a
dating app is not even you trying. You
messaging someone is not even you
trying. That's not even trying, bro.
That's just doing [ __ ] you know? That's
not trying. Trying is [ __ ] getting
dressed up, getting your head on, going
out approaching people, pretending, you
know, wasting your money.
They get nothing at the end. That's
trying. Going on a dating app is hardly [ __ ] trying.
Yeah, but they're not interested there
either, are they? Suicide dark.
Yeah, could easily went out today if I
wanted to, but not worth my time.
It's literally not worth my time.
I feel I feel like I lost hope more and
more and more over the years
cuz there's a time I'd go every week.
Mate, my personal hygiene is better than
yours will ever be. You old ugly man.
You old m of a skint man. Get off of
YouTube, mate. We know some of your
accounts are [ __ ] 18 years old.
Some of your Some of these people's
accounts are 18 years old, by the way, Nicolola.
Listen to me, [ __ ] Yeah. Let me let me
start. Let me explain something to you, Joe. Yeah.
You showing your pension, right? Doesn't
mean anything. You don't have access to
your pension until you [ __ ] until
you're 70. Secondly, I beat you at the
money game. I've beat [ __ ] Yes. 18
years. I saw it today. I beat nonslegs
at the money game and I beat LJ at the
money game. Pretend it never happened
all you want. I'm not interested. And I
don't care. We all know how the Subway
cookie crumbles with you people on
there. You've been doing it for years.
And like I said, if this was 2 and 1/2
years ago, I would have been in
Birmingham yesterday smashing that mic
in. If he come out, I would I would have
called that Tim out and that mic out. I
trust me, I was so tempted yesterday,
bro. You don't know. Before I went to
the cinema, but then I was like, "Yeah,
but they're just going to take the L and
pretend it never happened. So, there's
no point." and everyone's going to lick
their ass and then then it's just going
to go around in circles again and you
know what I mean like [ __ ] look look
at look at put it this way Nicolo when I
went to see Monty right what happened
what happened bro what happened
you know he's kind of snaking me again
Timmy's coming online acting the big man
again we didn't when we called him out
we didn't call Mike out because I didn't
what Mike was doing until I come back.
You know what I'm saying?
So, and then they just come back on like
nothing's ever happened. This is like I
said, we don't waste our time on you
people. If you want to keep thinking
that you've won at the money game, um
you keep thinking that just like you
keep thinking that I never went to mock
Samson's area two times and I didn't go
to meet Bomb. Just keep thinking and
lying to yourself cuz all you're doing
is lying to yourself. You're not
bothering me. You know what I mean?
And another thing is, mate, oh that's
another thing. Thank you. Uh, listen. Right,
I've never had social anxiety in my
life, mate. Use all the people that sit
online, right? Use all the people that
sit online, right? Don't leave your
house sat online gambling all the
[ __ ] time, you know, and you're
trying to tell people about social
anxiety, mate. You're on a nons [ __ ]
channel, you know?
You Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Answer me
this question. Okay. Okay. Answer this
question, right? And don't answer it
with a question, right?
Why when I showed you thousands and
thousands of pounds,
you had none of this energy showing
money? Why didn't you beat me there and
then at the money game? Come on. Okay,
let's say it now. Let's all set up and
ask this question and let's let it get
answered. Okay, I'm skinn. I've got
nothing. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, I've got
nothing. Okay, I'm extremely skinn.
You've got all of this money. Okay. So,
when you got shown this money, where was
Nons's £14,000 that's in his head
because he's never had it. Where was all
J's money and where was your money? Just
answer the question cuz you never showed
me nothing. Right. And that's why I'm
not ever showing you money ever again.
It because of that reason, which is why
like I'm never meeting anyone ever again
because if I meet anyone again, the same
thing is going to happen.
Like I said, you know how much I'd love
to punch that [ __ ]
You know, you want me You know how much
I'd love to punch that [ __ ] money
mike in? You don't know, bro. How much?
But what's the point? You know, it's not
like you're going to get credit. I'll be
honest. I didn't have 12k cash just
kicking around it. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. You could have easily
got out the bank. You could have easy
out the bank. Stop talking [ __ ] Right.
You've you you know, you're big enough
to show two grand in cash. So, okay. So,
you didn't have 12 grand in cash. Well,
you could have easily got it out. Why do
you get out then? You knew that day
would have come, you know. Okay, you
didn't have 12 grand in cash. Okay, but
you could have easily shown um 12 grand.
You could have got it out the bank. You
must have knew that day was going to
come where somebody beat you at the
money game. So, that doesn't really that
doesn't really um that doesn't really
cut it for me because you must have knew
that day was going to come where you're
going to have to take money out the bank.
Do you want me to know? You want me to
answer you why you people didn't show
it? It's because you don't have
anything. That's that's exactly why.
Nons you, you know, and then you come
back showing less than what I've shown
and acting like you've won. Okay, bro.
You keep telling yourself that you've
won. No one cares, you know.
And yeah, how how's the gambling done?
Um, so I put 120 on three teams uh
Tuesday and it returned 380
which was a good win to me.
You know what I'm saying?
I [ __ ] out of this [ __ ] I'm just going
to go there and [ __ ] her, bro.
I could actually go for a No, cuz it's
tomorrow. She wants to meet me, so I
can't even drink. But yeah, that's
Yeah, I done a 30 pound boy score on a draw today.
It didn't [ __ ] win, but I was I
wasn't asked. It was only for fun, you
know. Yeah, Joe. So, I went to the
bookies with 160
Tuesday. Last Tuesday, it was my mom's
birthday. Lost 40 on the machine. Then I
put 120 on two teams and it returned
380. I wish I put the whole 160 on it now.
I wish I [ __ ] put the whole 160 on the [ __ ]
I wish I don't have both score no draw
on the [ __ ] It was a both score no draw
as well, but I was just happy with the
380, you know. Yeah. [ __ ]
But I lost today, but I don't mind.
So, I keep needing to work, but I've got
enough money. I've got more than enough
money, so I don't really need to work.
I'm going to have to at some point. Oh [ __ ]
And it's not because I'm skinn that I
don't go out. I can go out. I got the
money to go out.
I went out on Sunday drinking. I spent
like [ __ ] 250 for [ __ ] sake. Holy You know,
yo, I won 380 from 120 and it felt good.
You know, it might not seem a lot, you
know, 380 from 120, but to me, it's
still free money. You know, it's,
you know, most people probably don't
even earn 260 in a [ __ ] day, 270 in a
day. It was more the fact that I went
out the Sunday and got pissed and done
some approaches and I just got like more
than a money back for it. So, you know,
it is what it is.
I'm not going out tomorrow unless this
woman wants to meet.
She's [ __ ] not the best looking, but
you're not going to regret on your
deathbed, are you? How many [ __ ] you
[ __ ] got? So
that's the way I see it. You only live once.
There's nothing wrong with a quick bang,
you know? You don't need to be with them.
You know what I'm saying? There's a
difference between being with somebody
and just banging them. You know what I'm
saying? I think there's a big there's a
big difference. So,
you don't need to be with them. You
don't need to stay with them. You know,
but Joe, that that that nonsleg is a
proper proper narcissist. You know, you
want to you want to try and sit there
and say that I'm a narcissist. Yeah.
Some people tried to say I'm a
narcissist. Do you actually know what a
narcissist is? That [ __ ] is an absolute narcissist.
He is a dirty little narcissistic
horrible little virgin. That's what he is. Yeah,
mate. You do have nothing. Because if
you really had something, you wouldn't
have ran away every single time I showed
you money if you didn't have nothing. Simple.
You know what I'm saying? Nons has
nothing. You don't really have a lot. L
has nothing. You do. So,
but yeah, he's a he's a nasty little
narcissist, Joe. Nasty little
narcissist. He replied to um Timmy's comment.
Joe, how how did he come on this
community? Right. Listen, listen,
listen. You want me to tell you the
quick story? How do you think he come on this community?
How do you think this little virgin come
on this community? [ __ ]
Listen, do do you know what? He is a
nasty little [ __ ] You know, I swear to
God, you you um you um think that oh my
mouth has been disgusting in the past,
but bro, it's like I always said, I've
backed a lot of the [ __ ] I've said up.
Yeah. You know, Prime, he didn't need Do
you know the reason I called out Prime
when I was in Birmingham? Yeah. Not
because I was trying to get a W, it's
because he was keep starting on me. So,
even after he done what he done, I
thought, okay, if he wants to keep
starting and he wants it again, that's
on him. So, I called him out when I was
in Birmingham. If he didn't call me out,
if he didn't call me out, I wouldn't
have called him out as whatever because
there's no coming back from that. You
know what I'm saying? The only reason I
called him out is cuz he keeps coming on
YouTube. You know what I'm saying? But
Timmy basically said, right, that he's
obsessed that that that that Nlex is
obsessed. Yeah, that's what Timmy said
to Nlex. He was like, "Oh, you're
obsessed. You're obsessed. You're
obsessed." And then he was like, "Oh,
no, he's obsessed." you know, he's going
to um he's going um to uh he's going to
um my partner's uh
he I'm he's going to court because of
his behavior between um towards me and
my partner. Like what the [ __ ] bro? He
started everything on this [ __ ]
YouTube [ __ ] bro. He started [ __ ] as
well when I used to [ __ ] meet him. He
didn't stop meeting people because of
people's behavior, Joe. That's not why
he kept me he stopped meeting people.
You know what I'm saying? He has been
doing this [ __ ] for [ __ ] years. And
you know the reason why he plays victim
because I'm not a 15 16 year old kid.
I'm a grown man. Do you understand? You
know he has the biggest mouth right than
anyone I've ever known in my life mate.
And trust me I've known people with some
big mouths. Yeah. So he you know when I
used to meet him he didn't stop meeting
me because of my behavior. I just what
what's my behavior? saying that you're a
copycat that you saying Chev was
attractive to fit in. Yeah. You know, he
and then, you know, and then the whole
reason he come on here was because of
his dirty stinky mouth, right? And I
told him to come and meet me, say it to
my face, and I'll smash your face in.
And then he kept ignoring me. And then I
had to message all of his friends. Yeah.
So like to see like what he is about,
you know? And then when he can't stand
up to a man, he plays the victim. What
the [ __ ] It's It's a madness. And then,
mate, if that was the truth, right, if
you was if you really stopped meeting
somebody because of their behavior, you
wouldn't be on YouTube every day
obsessed with them, you know? Would you?
If you didn't want anything to do with
someone, say you stop meeting someone,
right? You wouldn't be on YouTube every
day doing this [ __ ]
If you if I was a 15, 16 year old kid,
it's because he knows, right, that he
couldn't walk all over me. That's what
it is. So then he plays the victim. He's
a loser. He's an absolute loser, mate.
You know, there's a big difference
between 17 and [ __ ] 19 and 19 and
[ __ ] 27. Do you understand?
All them days when he was projecting his
virginity onto me and [ __ ] I didn't
even know he was doing that when I was
[ __ ] 17. I thought, "What the fuck?"
I was thinking, "What the [ __ ] is wrong
with this kid?" I didn't know he was
self-projecting, you know,
trying to act a victim. What an idiot,
man. You know what I'm saying? I hate
narcissists like that. [ __ ] he's a
he's a horrible little [ __ ] He is him
and that L. You know that
nasty nasty nasty little [ __ ]
That's what he is.
Yeah, that's where we're at.
But stop doing the snaking and [ __ ] If
you want to say something, you can stay on here.
I can't stand that snaky [ __ ] bro. You
know that Mike, you do it. Ricky does
it. If you say something, you're not
going to get blocked. So, just say it on here.
You know what I'm saying?
That's where we're at, bro.
Yeah, that's the that's the when I got
380 from 120.
I would have got I would have been
[ __ ] Not [ __ ] but I would have
just been a lot lower if it wasn't for
that cuz Yeah, going out London's not [ __ ] cheap. So,
um went out to
Yeah, that number stopped replying. That finish number. Oh, boy.
And it honestly isn't about money. Why I
don't go out every week. It isn't. It's
It's money in terms of Yes. What I save
by not going out, I'm going to use
towards something else. Yeah. It's it's
that, you know, but even if it wasn't
that, I still wouldn't do it cuz I would
just spend the money on something else. So, yeah. [Music]
You know what I've been coming across? virgin women.
Um, I've come across a 22-y old virgin
yesterday who I was talking to and I've
come across a 26-y old virgin who's
never held someone's hand. Now, that
motherfucker's got to be fat and ugly
cuz how the [ __ ] can you be a woman at
26 that's never held someone's hand? I
believe it as a man.
It sounded promising, did it? They never
sound promising to me. I know what
they're about. I know what they do. They
I I always expect the same [ __ ] Did it?
I never I never um I because I've been
through so much [ __ ] Um
with them like I I I'm more surprised if
it doesn't happen.
No, it never sounds promising to me. Never.
Yeah, I know what they're like. I know
what they're about. I know more than everyone.
That's why I don't go out every week.
Yeah, you always text them for a while.
I've text loads of people for a while
only for them to say, "Oh, I'm not
looking today." Or, you know, they they
mess around. Nah, I never have high
hopes. I know what they do.
It's why I don't go out every week. I
have to really really
not forget but really really want to go
out and try again. And it's very rare I
do because it's just the same old [ __ ]
Honestly, bro, I could have went out yesterday.
Oh yeah, that Canada that Canadian one was AI. So,
and there's also the expense of going
out now as well. So,
I need to do cyber approaches. No thanks.
You can do it though, but I won't be there.
Nah, I'm good, bro.
AI means basically they pretend to be
somebody that they're not. Basically,
like a robot. So, yeah.
I'm just tired of them to be honest with
you, Nicolo. I'm sick and tired of them,
you know? I'm almost 28 years of [ __ ]
age and I'm still dealing with their
[ __ ] I'm sick of them. I'm tired of
>> I'm actually sick of them, bro. You know
what I'm saying? I am really really sick
and tired of them
cuz none of them's ever proved to be
different. Talk is [ __ ] cheap, bro.
Talk is [ __ ] cheap. So So
I just can't be bothered with it, bro. So
I don't know. Probably cuz he snaked me
again like he always does.
He sits there and says, "Oh, you've done
this to my kids. You've done this to my
girlfriend." But I'm the one that went
to Birmingham and wasted £200. Which I
didn't even need to do to be honest cuz
I was never ever going to leave London
ever again in terms of like going to
another uh another city. I was never
going to leave London again cuz I had no reason to. So,
I was I don't think I would have ever
left again. Like, um
cuz I had no reason to, bro. Like, I had
no reason to ever leave again. I had
done my traveling, bro. I'm still
[ __ ] recovering from it. I actually
feel 100 years old. You don't even
understand. I feel so old.
So I was never going to leave it ever
again, bro. But I thought, let me go see
Monty in it. Won a football bet and I
didn't want to be a let down in it. So
I wish I had someone do that for me,
mate. [ __ ] hell.
Everyone in my life has kind of snaked
me one way or another,
like the tenants and [ __ ] Pretty much
they kind of have. Most of them
in if you think about it in a way they
kind of have. We're not talking about
the ones with the LT. So mate, for him
to even get someone to even done that,
he's crazy, bro. So So
and he knows this deep down as well.
This is why he won't block me or keep me
blocked because he knows this. You know
what I'm saying? So,
and I've caught her snaking as well.
There's Oh, the only good guy on here is
that Charlie down worry clock. He's
actually a good guy, you know. I've
actually met Charlie, you know. I would
actually go back to Nottingham to see
Charlie. He's actually a cool guy.
Like, yeah, he hangs out with [ __ ]
Timmy and [ __ ] but he never gets
involved in the drama
and he doesn't [ __ ] stir. He always just
Charlie's a cool guy, you know. I don't
think he gets enough credit. Charlie's
Charlie's a good guy, man. Um,
but like all the other people, bro, like
um I've caught them being snakes like
Ricky, Joe's a snake. They're all
snakes. But you know what that Ricky
does? You You do not understand what he
does, Nicolo. What? What it is with
these people, yeah, is they're they're
old fat, ugly, angry gamblers. So when
they do their balls in, they start
talking about themselves, saying it's
about you. You're this, you're that,
you've got no this, you know, you've got
no that. Um, you know, because they've
done their balls in gambling.
Who else should get credit? Um,
I think LT should get credit.
for the amount of traveling and that
he's done like me, you know, trying to
meet people and [ __ ] because even when
we're not talking and I don't like him,
it's annoying to see how biased these
people actually are because they do it
to me as well. Like it annoys me, you
know, like he's he's traveled up to
places. I've traveled up to places.
Um, so I don't think he gets credit
either because they're all biased to
both of us. Um, and who else?
That's it. Yeah.
Can't think of anyone else
cuz they do it to me as well when I've
traveled up and down the country. They
they, you know, they don't give me credit.
They still don't give me credit for that Mark Samson.
Well, I literally beat him fair and square. Wow. Yeah,
I think all the negative experiences is
[ __ ] lacking me.
How much do you think you'll spend out
you you'd spend on a night out in
London, Timmy Eldridge?
How much do you reckon? Like 150 200
It's [ __ ] expensive, mate. Yeah.
What do you think, Nicolo? on a on a on
a night out
like 120 130.
See, it doesn't see it doesn't matter
how much money you get or you have. Your
money just goes in London. Your money in
London just goes. It doesn't really
matter how much you you [ __ ] have or
you get. The [ __ ] just seems to go, you know,
[ __ ] £7 a [ __ ] pint.
And it doesn't matter how much money you
have or how much money you get,
you know? You're just done for. As soon
as you go out, you're you're sort of
done for. That's what happens. That's
what happened to me on that Sunday.
That's why I had to kind of like win the
money back in order to save. Cuz if I
didn't, then I wouldn't have been able
to save anything, you know?
Yeah, it's a madness, bro.
It is actually a madness.
It's so expensive just to do a normal
thing. Go out and [ __ ] drink.
It is madness, bro. It is a madness.
It is really It is really mad if you
think about it.
cuz it's not like a it's just a normal
thing, you know? You go out and you
drink and you socialize, but that's like
a [ __ ] second mortgage nowadays. It's
not like a holiday or
cost a living as [ __ ] bro. Doesn't
matter how much money you get.
It don't matter how much money you have,
it will just go like
you go out, mate. That's that's you
done. If I didn't win that [ __ ] 380
on that football bet, then I would have
carried much money over to the to the next month.
I think I went out twice last month.
I think I did. Oh, [ __ ]
No, I wouldn't go to the casino.
I only done that football bet cuz I
needed the extra money. I done one today
30, but that was cuz I didn't go out
drinking and I was bored. I wanted to go
out for a walk. But yeah, I don't do the
casino [ __ ] anymore.
because of um
cuz I've done it all before going casino
and [ __ ] like and yeah. Yeah.
200 [ __ ] pound.
That's madness, bro.
I think I must have got £1,400 last
month and maybe 1,400 this month with
what two outgoings. So at the end of the
day, it doesn't matter how much you
actually get it just will just go.
So it [ __ ] seems, you know,
I don't know, but it's mad. Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I think the only thing you can win on
now on gambling is the football. Is it Nicolola?
Probably the football in it. [ __ ] hell.
Sounds about right. Even when I used to
get three grand a month, my money used
to go I used to get three grand every month
for doing nothing and it still seem to went. So,
sounds about right. And we're in London
as well, so
you need to sort of win some. I need to
try and put 500 pound on the both teams
to score, mate.
That would be lovely if that come. Oh, be lovely.
That' be bloody lovely, mate. Oh,
that would be ace. Could you imagine?
Yeah. You don't win your vets cuz
[ __ ] you you probably do too many teams.
Yeah, but then I wouldn't have lived the
life for 3 years. So
I lost a bet today. But yeah, I lost the
first season. The first game of the
season I won. Second game of the season And then
then I lost two. So, I've won I've won
three out of six.
Yeah. 108k banned.
But obviously, you're going to spend, bro. So,
you're going to [ __ ] spend, aren't you? So, [ __ ] sake. Yeah.
Yeah. I wonder how many escorts I banged
in them 3 years.
Can you imagine how many actually banged
in like 3 years. madness.
[ __ ] a lot, bro. [ __ ] a lot.
That's another thing I've done more than
anyone in the world is escorts. Yep.
anyone in the world.
Escorts. I'm sure I must have. I must have, bro.
Maybe not as many as Charlie Sheen, but
[ __ ] I I'm up there, mate. I've got
to be up there. I don't think more than
anyone in the world, but I'm sure I'm up there.
I can give up cuz I already have.
Is it? I've already given up. I didn't
know it was impossible too cuz I mean
I've already given up so
I didn't know it was impossible.
Charlie the one in two and a half men.
He got he got herpes in he HIV was
actually called [ __ ] too many.
[ __ ] knows mate. [ __ ] knows on going out
drinking gambling [ __ ] escorts.
See the thing is seaside do you know I I
was getting like three grand a month for 3 years. So
if I didn't have that and I was still
going out the way I did, I don't know
how I would have done it.
Then I would have had to deal with the
stress of money and the woman. It's bad,
bro. It's really,
you know, there's nothing easy about any
of this. It's bad. It's really, really
You know, it's so bad, bro. But people
make it seem so easy.
There's nothing easy about any of it.
I might pick two days to go out. A
Friday, a Thursday and a Friday.
Yeah, probably a Thursday and a Friday, I think.
At some point, maybe in two weeks. Pick
like two days. Thursday and Friday, in it.
But who knows? I probably won't. So
yeah, you can't get think
why do you think it's so hard in this countryside dark?
I think it's because they've just got unrealistic standards these
people on Reddit and
nothing they say rings right to real
life. You know, they say, "Oh, you got
to go on these dating apps." And when
you go to these dating apps, they're all
trolls and piss takers and half of them
are bots. Oh, go out and speak to
people. You go out and speak to people,
they just say they got boyfriends. I mean, nothing
rings right with any of the [ __ ] that they say. [ __ ] sake. No.
No. You never get a woman that acts differently.
Yeah. See, I know, bro. You know, like
even in I know that's not like you, but
[ __ ] you know, even in 200 [ __ ]
You know, even in 2009, yeah, 2010, it
was easy. House parties, no Tik Tok, no
nothing. Now it's like it's even got
harder in, you know, 2 years ago it
wasn't even this hard,
you know. It was it was easier, a lot
easier than it is now, even in two
years. So there is just no hope in this country.
There's literally no hope.
All you meet is immature [ __ ] time
wasters, women that play games. That's
all you ever That's all you ever come across.
You don't come across anything different.
You know, I used to go out every week
seaside dark. I used to go out twice a
week. So I used to go like eight times a
month. uh eight times a month
and it would just never be any
different. It was always the same [ __ ]
Yeah. I was born in 97. So What's that?
And man says they're [ __ ] I said, "Why
are they cunts?" He says, "Because they
say they've got a boyfriend." When 90%
of them don't. But 90% of the time they
This woman says that she [ __ ] but she
won't give [ __ ] Can't be with
somebody that don't give [ __ ]
They've all like the same attitude.
Have you noticed how they seem to all
have the same attitude? Um, yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm [ __ ] I don't know what I am
out of 10, but [ __ ] I scrub up well,
you know? I'd say I'm decent looking and
I can't even get a conversation out the
[ __ ] Suicide Dark.
You know what makes me laugh though?
Suicide dark is that that these people
think that one day it's just going to change
which is not realistic. That's delusional
because if it was going to change it
would have changed already in all of
these years you know
obviously right. [ __ ] Yeah.
It will never change.
It's a country designed to annoy you.
I stand by what I uh [ __ ] say.
It generally is a country designed to
annoy you and get under your skin.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
So, what I need to do is find someone in
a different country and I'll just fly
there. It's not a problem,
you know. It's not a [ __ ] um
It's not a problem, mate. Wherever the
[ __ ] they are.
Nah. Nah, it's not. Going out and trying
is more depressing because the more you
try, the more you lose hope.
Nah, nah, not at all. I think you going
out trying is even more depressing
because when you go out and you try, you
lose even more hope. See, the thing is
sees dark, if you don't go out for a
little bit, you think, "Oh, let me let
me try, you know, and then when you try,
you lose even more hope." So, every time
this stuff happens, the more hope you
lose until eventually you will just
completely lose all hope. So yeah, um so
you get me
I don't get women from time to time.
I've not been on a date for about 4 months.
I used to get women and time to time is
not good enough. We don't have money to
keep wasting in this country.
£300, £400 and no, I don't get women
from time to time.
You know, even that one of the video
took the piss.
So, no, I don't get women from time to
time. Not anymore. But yeah,
I need to get rich, matey, as well.
I need to get rich, matey.
Did you like my little 380 win, Greasy,
on that 120 bet? You must have thought I
was mad doing 120 on a bet, is it?
Nah, she wasn't that good, bro.
You weren't as good as my mama.
She was okay. But
no, I preferred my mama. My mama.
But they're all time wasters in the end. Yeah.
And you also have women that go on dates
and waste your time as well. So, yeah.
Yeah. But in the end, they're all time wasters.
They all ghost in the end anyway, so it
doesn't really matter.
[ __ ] man. Huh?
You know, it's not enough to keep trying
because I've had nothing for a very long
time. That's the whole point. No.
And also, it doesn't make up for the
amount of [ __ ] that you have to put up
with. And actually, I haven't got
anything for a very long time. So,
um, no, I haven't got anything for [ __ ] ages.
And I've had to deal with a lot of [ __ ]
as well, which wasn't worth it in the end.
See, that's why there was hope back
then, Seaside Dock, cuz although you
dealt with some [ __ ]
you know, you used to get things time to
time, now you don't get anything.
That's possibly why I could have also
lost hope as well. because of that
reason cuz obviously you know back in
the day you used to actually be able to
get stuff a day a kiss a [ __ ]
or something where you'd think oh okay
well but now you don't get nothing I got
even a kiss for I don't know how long mate so
it's impossible now
you used to actually think it was
impossible then but
Yeah. And the piss taking and the dickheadness.
But that's what they are. They're
[ __ ] in this country, you know. Oh yeah. Yeah.
Where's my mama, Nicolo? So, yeah.
It's like that Italian one that went on
a date just to waste my time holding hands, vaping, chilling,
right? And then when you tried to kiss
them, oh, they they think, "Oh, it's too much."
Which is also a form of narcissism
because we all know that, you know, if
you didn't try to kiss them, they just
wouldn't met you again. You have people
that you have kissed that don't meet you again. So, Another
thing you don't hear about on Reddit.
There's no way they would have met me
again. No way. I know people that have
wasted my time.
Well, then you're a s. Simple. Then
You're coming across like a s now.
You're a s.
No, I ain't got money to be wasting,
bro. I haven't got the money anymore to
be wasting. Oh, [ __ ]
No. Okay. Let me let me let Okay.
Seaside dark. Right. I I'll give you my
traveling history. Yeah.
Right. Cuz uh let me let I I I I'll give
you my traveling history and I'll tell
you my body count and how many dates
I've been on and stuff. And I can
actually show you my rail car to back it
up. Right. And all of the times I've
gone to these places, I've gone to
approach, drink, approach, and to use hotels.
Uh gone in hotels, approached and
[ __ ] Yeah. So,
uh I've been to where have I been to?
Birmingham five times. I've been to
Nottingham four times. I've been to
Cardiff three times. I've been to
Liverpool once. I've been to Manchester
10 times. I've been to Newcastle three
times. I've been to Scotland two times.
I've been to Sheffield three times. I've
been to Leeds. Been to Brighton four
times. Uh I've been to Bristol.
And I've gone out in London about a
million times. And all of that money and
time that's been spent. I'm sure there's
a city I'm missing. There's got to be
one. Um I've only had about four one night stands.
So I mean read and sell what you will.
And that's when it actually was
possible. So, think of how many people
I've actually approached. I've been
dealing with this [ __ ] for years with these [ __ ]
Yeah, that's what I'm doing. And
obviously, if I go Nottingham, I won't
be able to afford it
cuz I can't be going around spending
[ __ ] 300 quid, bro.
And um so I mean, you know, like you
should still have someone now, you know,
with all of that trying that you've done.
Yeah, that's what I'm doing.
That's why I'm not wasting three, four
[ __ ] on the pound going out here. Yeah. So yeah,
that's how it is.
It's bad though. It is bad.
It doesn't always work. It doesn't
It doesn't always work at all.
I don't need to win a bet. I can go now
if I wanted to. I don't need to win a
bet. But if I waste money doing that,
if I waste money doing that, it never
worked the other times I went.
I don't I think you're missing the
point. I'm trying to explain to you how
many times I've gone out and the low
success that I've had. It's very low
success for the amount I've tried.
That's what I'm trying to explain to
you. So all in all, it's just not worth
it. It's not worth doing nothing.
That's what I'm trying to say to you.
So, I don't need to win a bet. I can go literally
whenever I want, but I just won't be
able to put all of it towards Thailand.
That's what I'm saying.
You know what I mean, bro? So, yeah.
So Nottingham's not always worked. It's
only worked once. I mean, think about it
like this, right? When I went to
Manchester the first time, I got laid.
The nine times I went after that, I
never got laid.
Yeah, but if I lose the bet, then I have
even less money. So, I'll only need I'll
only do a bet when when I um I'll only
do a bet when I um
I'm in need of money. I'll just put like
160 on like two teams. But
I wish I put all of that 160 on that
football bet on [ __ ] Tuesday, man.
I'm not just 120.
Mad bastard putting 120 on a bet in it.
I'm a crazy [ __ ] [ __ ] aren't I?
I am a crazy bastard. Crazy bastard.
Yeah, mate. If I put 500 then I would
have been not good if it lost.
Yeah. And then if I lost then what? You
know, I will do it one time. Put £500 on
two teams. I will do it.
500. Yeah. It's like £1,800, didn't it? [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, it's 500. But
obviously if it loses then you're
you're in a bit of trouble, mate, aren't
you? You know. So yeah,
it's the way it is.
them fes don't pay out anymore do they?
Imagine having 500 pound on a both score no draw. Nicolola
[ __ ] hell, mate.
That's like one
It's like three and a half grand, I think.
Three and a half, four grand. I think it would be a madness.
Slow was 4-2 today.
Yeah, it's not worth it though. It's
just both score no draw. You know,
they're quite hard to come in.
So it's not worth it, mate.
Yeah, but they're not easy, mate. They
both score no draw. It's not easy,
you know. But these leagues make it
easier. But that's not I don't want to
both score no draw today. So
no, it's not impossible.
I got a both score to I got a both I've
never won the bet both score no draw but
I've had a both score no draw the first
season the first game of the season and
obviously on Tuesday they were both
score no draw
but I didn't bet on the both score no
draw but the games ended up being a both
score no draw if that makes sense.
And I [ __ ] wish I put it on that now.
But no, you can on a northern league
league. On the national northern league,
you can get them. You can
you can on them leagues because there's
loads of goals. I see, bro. I see on the
first half one of these teams scored
four goals in the first in the first half.
Yeah, I've never had a bow score on. You
know what annoys me with a both score no
draw is when you do a both score no
draw. Yeah. And it just it's just a
normal both teams to score.
Yeah. It's just a normal both teams to
score. And you think, oh, I wish I just
done it on the both scheme both teams to score. Now
that's what you'll always be thinking.
So whatever way you do it. So what what
you know whatever way you do it um
you know you'll always be thinking oh I
wish I done it this way or I wish I done
it that way.
Do you understand? But
I feel like when you do a both teams to
score and it's a both score no draw, you
still got money. So it's not as bad. But
if you done a both score no draw and it
was just a both teams to score, you
didn't get the money. So I think it
annoys you more. Does that make sense?
I think it makes sense what I'm saying. Yeah. So yeah.
So when you do both score no draw and it
and and it's a both teams to score just
that you you wish you just done the both
teams to Oh, Yeah. Yeah,
you should bet on the football greasy. I
think you'd like it, boss.
I think you'd like it.
My mommy left me.
How do you make extra money nowadays? Nicola. Nicola. Nicolola.
Yeah, quite simple. You don't
unless you win both teams to score.
But I mean, Greavvesy doesn't even leave
the house. Uh,
you don't, do you, matey? Unless you
shoplift or [ __ ] some [ __ ] Yep. Suck.
You can make loads of money. KSI makes
loads of money. Nola,
do you want to see an escort that I banged?
Oh, it doesn't let me.
I'd show you her, but it doesn't let me
show you her. basically. Yeah.
But then you're bored, so you're [ __ ]
then, is it? Yeah.
Have a gas. Do it.
Yeah, you can save money in the winter.
Yeah, it's very easy. You can save money
in the winter, but um
yeah, you can't in the summer, but we
had a good summer anyways. Other
guys do it.
Watch out for the other guys.
But I think it's so mad how many of
these guys lower their standards to next
to nothing. Like that black woman that
that guy was with
was [ __ ] stinking son. Yeah. Yeah,
it's all right for some mate.
But I reckon if I didn't do any
approaching, I think I would have just
met somebody through friends or
something. Can it? What do you think,
Grezy? If I didn't approach right, do
you reckon I would have like just found
someone through friends or a dating app or something?
I'm probably going to have to work some
crackhead hours soon. What do you mean
no? Greasy, what? How? What makes you say that?
Why? Why? What makes you say that?
People say that other guys do it.
What do you mean? I wouldn't have met
anyone through friends or dating apps. Why not?
Other people do it. So they say,
"Yeah, but you will." Yeah, but what
about dating app, Grezy?
But that guy in the cinema, his misses
were like was like a two out of 10. It
was some fat black ugly woman, bro. And
he was like a decent he was a normal looking guy.
That is mad, bro. That is mad.
There's so many desperate men, you see.
And she was bad, bro. Bad. Trust me.
No, but why when have I met anyone
through a friend? Grezy, you don't know that. [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. They always use excuses. They do
it in America as well.
They do it in America as well. Yeah. So, Grezy,
why are you saying I wouldn't have met
anyone through an app or anything? No,
to be honest with you, you would have.
Back years ago, you would have met
people through apps cuz I've met people
through uh dating apps and I had more
chances. But now, it's impossible to
even get anyone real on the dating apps.
Oh, bro. The thing is the piece I do I realized um
I had a lot of patience.
I don't know how the [ __ ] you done it,
mate. You must have been about 16 and
she must have been about 23.
Like I said, bro, I realized I had a lot of patience,
but I had to give up in the end because
if something was going to happen, it
would have happened by now.
Yeah, that's the way I see it in it.
No, I wouldn't have. I'm asking you. I'm
being I'm asking you a serious question,
Greasy. What would have if I met
somebody through a friend or something?
Because people on Reddit say you go on
dating apps, you meet through a friend.
No, I've already given I've already
given up. Is when you're dead. I've
already given up
cuz I've already found my mama. Yeah, it
is good. I give I gave up in it, Seaside.
I gave up cuz it was too depressing, you know.
But if you gave up though, seaside doc,
how would have you uh how would have you got sex?
Yeah, I know, bro. No one no one gave me credit.
But then I realized I don't get as much
money now. I'm getting older now. I need
to really start doing stuff before,
you know, I get really really old. You
know what I'm saying? And I can't keep
doing this approach and stuff. You know,
it's just because like it always goes
back to if it was going to change, it
would have changed by now. There's no
arguing that. There's no there's there's
there's nothing anyone can say, you
know? That's how it is. Yeah.
Yeah. But what would have you done if
you didn't and you gave up approaching?
How would have you got sex?
I would have just used escorts.
I just I just used escorts. Hey. Yeah.
You know, there's some things in life
that's one in a lifetime. And that USA
is one in a lifetime
where you approach somebody and they
offer you their number. That would never
happen again, bro. Never happened again. Yeah.
What What do you think would have
happened if I went approaching at today
though, Seaside Dock? If I went to like
a pub today and I done some approaches,
what do you think would have happened?
Ant-Man said uh Ant-Man said seaside
dark that they're just not interested in this country.
Is he right about that?
Seaside dark. He said they're just not
interested in this country.
He's right in it.
That's mad, bro. I laugh my ass off when
he said that. It's true, though, isn't
it? Cuz they've all got the same
attitude. They all They're all [ __ ] NPCs.
Yeah, exactly. It won't suddenly change.
Yeah, I don't think they are interested
in this country.
Yeah, I was speaking to that Finnish one
and oh, since he was going to Scotland
and we was talking, I said, "Oh, I can
come to Finland sometime. You can show
me around." Then all of a sudden, no one
replies. Whenever you show a remote bit
of interest and try to escalate things,
nothing. not a sausage. You get people
that are in nightclubs that give you
their number, that talk to you, but
they're not into dating. Yeah. They give
you their number and message you. It's
It's just so [ __ ] up. Yeah,
but the only the thing that's [ __ ] up
seaside dark is I'm not even ugly. I'm
actually decent looking.
You know, wear nice after shave. So,
it's even worse for me, you know? It's
even worse when you're not like ugly and
you still can't get anything.
That's the thing.
See, I think I got lucky with that USA
because, you know, they've just come
here. They don't really have any options.
No, never been. They don't really have any options. Um,
you know, they don't really have any
options because she's just coming. I
mean, yeah, she can go on the date and app, but
>> she probably don't want to go on a date
yet. She's only here for a couple of
days. So, I think that's how I kind of
got lucky. And so, their options never
come into it cuz obviously they're too
scared to approach a man and probably no
man was going to approach them. So, they
probably saw as, oh yeah, I'll get a
quick [ __ ] [ __ ] you know?
And it's not even about just the I've
got a boyfriend [ __ ] It's all of it.
It's all of the [ __ ] Even when you
get the number.
Even when you get the numbers, they [ __ ]
around with you and [ __ ] So
yeah, I can't get nothing now, bro. I'm
decent. [ __ ] I used to be even
better. back when I used to go gym and
you can't get nothing.
You can't get [ __ ] all.
You can't get [ __ ] all, mate.
You know nothing. You can't even get a
date. All you guys took the piss out of, you know,
they all got boyfriends.
You got a boyfriend, do you? Where is he then?
Where is he?
Nah, bro. I put 30 on a both score no
draw. I only put £30 and no never won. Nope.
But it was only a bit of fun. Easy.
I'm having anything. I've already had a Chinese.
I always [ __ ] own that [ __ ] Yeah. So
yeah, if I was a virgin like virgin boy,
I don't think I would have gave up.
I need to pop that [ __ ] V card, mate.
I need to lose that Vard. I need to pop
that V card, mate. Yeah. Yeah.
But when you finally lose it.
When you finally lose it.
I need to make my nest calls in a minute. Grieves.
Oh, cold. [ __ ] sake.
Oh, if I done if I had done if I done
Swindon and Colchester today,
that's a both that was a both teams to score.
Bastard. Different [ __ ] league. What's up?
Yeah, there we go. Two of the tons.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, man.
money. Why are you a snake?
Why are you a snake, bro?
Why you not joining as well? The link's there.
Oh, it's Saturday, isn't it? Cuz [ __ ] football, obviously.
Yeah, I'm a snake. How am I a snake? One second.
Why doesn't the thing come on?
see what my opinions be.
Why doesn't my live stream
I can't go in it to see if it's a [ __ ] [ __ ] sake. on sir.
Oh, it is Monty. Yeah.
Oh, that's not money, man. You don't you don't count Yeah. [Music]
Yeah. I got no mates.
You've got no mates.
Want a box? Yeah.
Marty, why you being a snake? Huh?
>> Monty, why are you being a snake?
>> You're the biggest snake on this community.
Why are you licking ass? I
>> don't car. You just need to lick
Natalie's ass and that's it.
>> Why do you snake people, man?
>> I don't slate nobody. You're the one who
slated Nat yesterday.
>> No, you snake me, man.
>> I haven't snitched nobody.
>> You [ __ ] have.
>> In what way have I snatched PJ? Go on.
In what way?
>> You do it all the time.
>> Go on. In what way? have a snake to you.
Go on. Go on.
>> You know what way?
>> In what way?
>> Um, you know, you have
>> in what way? That's nature. Yeah. Go on.
>> You know people going at me, you join them. >> What?
>> When people are going at me, you join them.
>> I don't anyone for going at you. I don't
even know. What?
>> How do I do that? PJ, in what way? In
what way do I do that?
>> You just do.
>> Yeah. Weird.
>> I don't do [ __ ] call PJ one. You don't
even join my panels for me to stick up
here or not to stick up for you. So
that's [ __ ] It's always me. What is
who's always joining your panel PJ? Not
the opposite way around. Edia, the one
who's too faced to [ __ ] is you when
you're sitting there slagging Nat
and doing the rest of the [ __ ] you done
to me back in the day.
>> Nah, but you you done [ __ ] on Discord as well.
>> [ __ ] on Discord. What have I done on Discord? PG,
what have I done on Discord?
Stay for that.
Go on PJ
under the bus
done by PJ
and he goes and calls Natalie yesterday.
And he says, "I'm too faced."
>> Yeah, sorry about it. I was doing something.
>> Can you hear me?
>> Yeah, I can hear you. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, you're the biggest truth on
your P. You lost your [ __ ] friends for anyway.
No. Why? Why did you send me nonslegs earlier?
>> That's who you always talk about, is it?
>> No, that cunt's got a channel on me.
He's obsessed. I don't have a channel on him.
>> That's why I sent him to you because
you're always talking about the guy.
>> No, he's always doing videos on me.
>> Exactly. That's why I sent it. Yeah, cuz
you you both keep going on about dropper
every day, so I thought I'd send it. Yeah.
You know, if I actually got you living
with me and Natalie Pi, I think you do
side dress to be honest. >> N
would you want PB living with us? No,
they wouldn't want to live with you.
I'm not sure long legs only long legs
friend PJ is
>> PJ I met I met him through you
>> didn't meet him through me at all PJ you
met through [ __ ] American
So why why did you call Natalie
yesterday, PJ? Anyway, >> um it's cuz
um it's funny.
It's funny calling them birds misses. Yeah,
>> your birds misses. >> Well,
your mates your mates misses.
>> Yeah, but you like it.
>> No, I don't like it. I do like it.
That's a bit weird. Like calling me.
>> You do like it.
>> No, I don't like it.
You must like it. No.
So, what's it like getting proies anyways? >> Huh?
>> Why is it like getting crosses? >> Um,
I don't know, man. Good.
I don't like [ __ ] someone that's got black flaps.
Natalie doesn't even
Natalie don't even have
what you said. Your words are mine.
>> He doesn't mean that she's got black fab
from me saying it.
>> That's what you said.
>> Yeah, me saying it doesn't mean that
she's got black. No,
>> you actually meant it. What?
>> You actually made it though.
EJ, do you can I go back to N if you had black? >> Yeah.
M does not have black. [Music]
The [ __ ] yellow the yellow color the
[ __ ] yellow l
with ain't a gray on it as well.
>> The blacks get taught here. Why? >> Huh?
>> I don't care about what you Why did you
Why did you call Natalie yesterday? Truth. Truth.
>> Cuz it was funny.
>> No, truth. I answer
this. Escort said that they would have a
baby with me, but in a few years.
>> They want to get their life. They want
to get their lives sorted and that, you
know, they're the only people that reply
back on these escorts, you know, that are [ __ ] Yeah.
is the only one that seem interested.
>> They're not interested in you. They
interested in your money.
>> No, not Chinese. There's the Brazilian
one. No, they're the only ones that seem [ __ ]
They're the only ones that seem like
[ __ ] willing, bro. They reply to me.
[ __ ] yeah, you give them money at the
start, but you probably won't have to
keep giving them money after.
>> Why did you call Natalie yesterday, PJ?
Come on, straight answer.
>> Because you're all [ __ ]
>> How's he aable [ __ ] In what way is she audible [ __ ]
>> You're [ __ ]
>> Because she's got in between them.
>> I never I never called her. I just said
I didn't find her attractive. I didn't call her.
>> You did? What did he say to you
yesterday? He called you a dog.
>> No, you're making stuff >> up.
You know what I'm saying?
>> Well, it's not anywhere, Pete. Yeah, go
on. What? What? What? What am I not seeing
>> on that? Why do you care what I think?
>> I don't care what what I care what I think.
>> But I want to know what you're saying about >> Hello.
>> Hi. How are things? >> Standard.
>> Ah, boys.
>> How you all enjoying our Saturday night?
It's not too bad, is it? Saturday night.
The feeling is right.
>> Yeah, it's all right. Everything's good.
How you doing?
>> Who Who's this one?
>> How you doing?
>> I'm not too bad. I'm not too [ __ ] I'm
a little bit pissed. I haven't slept
much in the last 48 hours. [ __ ]
drinking or [ __ ] It's I'm steaming.
Absolutely [ __ ] steaming right now.
>> This guy's never going to shut up.
>> Bless you.
>> Bless you if you're steaming. Well,
well, uh, are we doing any football
bits? Have you had any [ __ ] football
>> We had done one today. I lost.
>> Oh, what did you put on it?
>> Double squ.
So you So you done that. Did it come in for you?
>> N only put 30 pound on it.
>> Only 40 quid
>> and it was a loser. So you're a loser. Come on.
>> Sorry, bro.
>> I'm going
left. But I was going to kick him anyways.
>> Why? Why? He's no warm. He's no
>> Yeah, that's him. That That's That
That's what he does. He just goes on and
on and on on that same That's it.
He know he's not.
>> Yeah, that's it. It just wants to
go PJ's little wet stockings.
Are your sockings wet? Well, um here.
Why do you hang out with these [ __ ]
weirdos on this PlayStation? Bro,
>> on this PlayStation, it's YouTube PJ.
>> No, back on PlayStation.
>> I didn't really hang about with anyone
but just you really.
>> Well, they're all [ __ ] weirdos on there.
>> I don't know why you're [ __ ] off cuz
you you get game like [ __ ] twitching
sites all the time. So, I [ __ ] you off
and then you [ __ ] got me into this community.
It seems I beat you to it though, is it?
Like we just switch. I thank you. I
thank you for one one thing.
>> Yeah. For getting me with that. Well,
getting me up in that. Yeah. But getting
me on the just
trying the copy. Yeah. That's your prick.
Just get me off this community.
But in a way, thank you for one way for
getting me on here because of that.
>> Well, bless you.
>> Now, give me your number. This I don't
think that will give anyone a number online.
He wants your number now.
>> No, I give it him.
AJ, when are you going to ever settle
down with a message instead of [ __ ]
going on a bird on? >> Um,
when are you going to mind your business?
>> I think you might as well go get
yourself tested, man. Could have anything.
I've already been tested. Mhm. Yeah.
>> Oh, for your [ __ ]
>> When you get tested, PJ
only what you got
tested for is your [ __ ] disability.
>> Yeah, really.
Don't know what you got tested for.
>> You know what I don't understand,
Greavves, right? Is uh
you can't be right for doing wrong. So
what I mean Grezy like you uh you get
these messages, you text these numbers,
right? And if you don't flirt or try to
meet them, they say, "Oh, you need to be
more ins assertive." The words
assertive. And then when you're more
assertive, they say that you're you come
on too strong. So you can't win in it.
>> Okay, then what?
>> You can't win. You can't win that, can
you, Grezy? You literally can't win.
You can't [ __ ] win, bud.
Can't believe you [ __ ] introduced me
to that [ __ ] weirdo.
Can't believe you got me on to this [ __ ]
community, PJ, but I I didn't introduce
you to that weirdo. Everybody told me
what he was like, PJ. Everyone told you
he was a n, but you were like, "No, he's
not." Even though we were talking about
a kid, you were like, "No, he's not.
>> What do you want, babe?
>> I felt sorry for I felt sorry for him getting bullied."
>> Oh, you felt sorry for him? Yeah, cuz I
didn't believe all the stories.
>> You didn't believe it. >> No.
>> All right.
>> I didn't believe it, mate.
>> Multiple people told you.
>> No, they didn't.
>> I told you. Yeah. Yeah. After you
[ __ ] introduced me to the [ __ ]
>> I didn't introduce you to him, but was a very kid.
Yeah. So there you go then. So it
weren't me introduced to shark
was it? Um
who's his name now?
Let me just guess my king's name.
M was it M Taylor? >> No.
Why do you hate women so much anyway? Pier
>> because it's funny.
>> How is it funny?
>> Cuz it just is.
You know, if I get turned down by a
woman, I just say, "All right, walk up
and say, "That's fine. See you there."
>> I just think
>> I think
all women know. >> Well,
it's just it's just that most women who
you go for are rather pissed
or doing the daily shopping. So, when
they got the normal eyes on, it's like,
"Who the [ __ ] that ugly bastard?"
They'll just walk up to him.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] clearly using PJ for a
platform. I think that's true.
>> I don't think I'm using anyone for a
platform because I think I've been live
for all day and I've just come up now.
I can just go live now on my phone now.
But what what's the point of
entertaining people who don't like me or Natalie?
>> I think Monty Monty Monty. Do you know
you know how you know these people are
old people? You want me to tell you how? I know.
>> I think PJ used me for his own
entertainment on YouTube to be honest. >> What?
There was an account earlier back on
here. I clicked on it and you know how
long ago that account was made?
18 [ __ ] years ago, bro. That's how
you know that old farts on here. It's
obvious, isn't it? It's obvious
that in English, PG, I weren't listening. Sorry.
>> An account earlier that I clicked on was
made 18 years ago.
>> Yeah. Good for person. We got obsession with YouTube.
>> Yeah, cuz they're old farts. That's what
I'm saying. They're old farts. Did you
not know that?
>> There's a lot of old people in this community,
but most of them are old.
>> I'm in.
>> Yeah. But how long have you been on
YouTube for PGA?
>> Um, 6 years.
longer than six years. Come on. I've
been on here for about six or five
years. I've been on that Well, five
years. I've been on here for
>> Why did you see what I sent you to me
yesterday, didn't it?
>> Yeah, but I've been on this community
for 5 years. Yeah. So, how long have you
been on this community for?
>> A year before you.
So why did you drag me on to this shitty community ped?
>> I don't like it. Do I look like it?
>> You like Well, you know, you huh?
>> Yeah, cuz I'm only asking the question
is why why do you not like Natalie?
>> N doesn't like me either.
>> Yeah. No wonder because she obsessive with women.
This guy sucks. I agree. This guy is
such a snake, is he?
>> Plus, you got a small dick. Yeah,
>> my my dick is bigger than
your dick will ever be, mate. If I If I
met you and Natalie, she'd probably come
on to me in front of you.
>> Probably. Probably. Probably.
>> J, listen. James, stop emailing me, you
[ __ ] Cuz if you keep doing it, I'm
going to come to Wales and go in your
door. Leave me the [ __ ] alone, you
Leave me alone. Stop emailing me. [ __ ]
off. Just cuz you're a [ __ ] woman, it
doesn't mean I'm not going to come.
I just want to know why he's so
obsessive with women and hates them so much.
>> Cuz I want to.
>> Cuz you want to.
>> Mhm. It's funny.
>> So, what's the point of going out
looking for an MPG?
>> I don't
you might What's the point?
>> So, what's the point?
So, what do you do now with your life?
I'm bullying PJ.
Bullying people's not my thing.
>> [ __ ] I sent you an email once a month.
[ __ ] off, Jane.
You remember when you fancy Jane?
I've never fancied Jane.
Why don't Jane come up on the box? He
was asking for the box a minute ago.
>> Yeah, the box is there.
>> That's for you, little PJ. Not me.
>> You did. You did like Jane before.
>> I don't know who Jane is. PJ,
>> stop being silly, M.
>> I'm not being silly. I don't know who J is.
Who's being that?
>> The YouTube bike.
>> What gear? Go. What? What gear does she go into?
>> Any gear? First, fourth, fifth.
>> The link is there. You silly. Just
>> asking for a link there, PJ. One second.
The chief still need stabilizes over
being top off.
>> Don't Don't try and say that you've
backed me up before. You've never backed me up.
>> I'm backing up. Backing up. I'm backing
>> You've never backed me up, Monty.
>> My daddy taught me well. I actually
>> Okay. Well, you didn't back me up. You
didn't back me up against that red star.
>> Red star. Who's Red Star? Oh, your boyfriend.
>> No, the one that talks to me every day. Yeah.
>> My calling people are by
Are you coming up?
PJ, why don't you get rid of your head?
>> Nah, she's too ugly.
>> What? Why is it with you calling women
over the PJ?
>> Cuz I'm not a s like you.
>> I'm not a s. I don't I'm not a s
Peter is someone who can't get laid.
That's a simp.
>> No, it isn't.
>> It is.
>> I think it's someone that licks someone's asses.
>> I've got a ass too. That's the thing.
I'm telling Natalie I
a woman or what?
>> Oh, go look after a kid instead of being on YouTube. >> Yeah,
>> looks a disabled daughter instead of
looking after on YouTube.
>> Hey Natalie, I can't I can't believe you
suck money. Will he
have got a big dick in you? You've even
got a bigger dick on him.
I can't believe you done that.
>> Yeah, I should have done that with
money. So why won't you do that? Psy.
>> No, I just
>> Have you ever had a [ __ ]
>> You have you ever had a blowj job?
>> No. What is it? What's that?
Don't matter then, does it? >> No,
>> I think it's past your bedtime.
>> I don't know. I think you might be right, PJ.
>> No, I love you.
That's from um him
at the bottom.
Who is it? Even I would.
>> Even I would.
>> Who the [ __ ] Oh, >> hello.
>> Wow. Wow.
>> So, why was you and Monty having a thing
going on back in the day?
>> I've never had a thing with this woman.
>> I've never spoke to Monty.
>> Yes, you have. when you was with Mark
when you used to speak to me.
>> Why would you Why would you say that to
try and cause trouble? I have never
>> You did. I've never PG. I've never
>> I don't know Marty other than
Look what you do. Look Look because
you're so scared of what I'm going to
say. You You just tried to throw that out there. What?
>> Monty, can you ask Natalie? Will she
speak to me
>> want my opinion to be?
>> Look how scared you are, PJ.
>> James, remember how you were saying
about how you wanted to um suck my dick and stuff?
>> I No, I I if it's possible, I would like
to speak to Natalie.
You can speak to who you want. No one's
stopping you, [ __ ]
>> Okay, stop calling me a [ __ ]
>> I'll call you what I want, matey.
>> No, you're the [ __ ] not me.
>> Get in.
>> No, you are.
>> You made your bag. You lying it.
>> Welcome to the [ __ ] club. Triple H.
What's happening, lad?
>> [ __ ] all, mate. I've done a football bet
today. No, no joy.
>> No good.
No, both got I don't know. Both got no
draw though to be fair. A bit of fun.
>> Has money handed on you then?
>> He's always been too faced.
>> [ __ ] It's nothing new.
>> You know,
>> being a bit rough today, lad.
>> Why are you hung over? >> Yeah.
>> Bless you then.
>> Add a Chinese fella. Yeah, I did as well
to be fair. Be brief. Nice, isn't it?
>> Yeah, I got it then.
>> I I don't have time for the [ __ ]
takeaway [ __ ] whatever.
>> I I do. I Triple H do you remember
Jane's phone call with me? Is it? >> No.
>> Yeah, you were going to have dinner.
>> Nobody remembers it.
>> Yeah, he Hey, Triple H. He's He's
unbiased, Jen. He even remembers it. Do
you know it was actually a criminal
offense what you did against GDPR
to record someone without their
knowledge? Like you're lucky I didn't
get you look different.
>> Yeah, I know. Do you know I know you
know Do you know why Joe? Do you know
why Joe? Because I I forgive him. I
forgive Triple H.
>> So why do you want to speak Why do you
want to speak to You're the Joe? You're
the one that speaks to an aunt. Joe,
you're the one that speaks to an aunt.
I'm only here to speak tonightly.
>> So is Monty Man. So So what do you want
to say tonight? What do you want to say
>> Is Monty man and Sean friends?
>> Yeah, they're friends. They're friends.
They are friends. Yeah. >> Friends.
>> Yeah, they are friends.
>> Speak to me.
>> What do you want to talk about with
>> Oh, look. Finn finish. Izzy replied. Oh,
lovely. What? What? What do you want to
talk to N about?
>> London Taylor. >> What?
>> London. Oh, do you remember that London
Taylor trip to break?
>> What do you want to talk to Natalie about?
>> Muted, isn't he?
>> No, I don't. >> Yeah.
that you want to talk about in them for
>> I just I just wanted to know if what her
mom said was true.
>> She doesn't talk she don't know about
Natalie. She doesn't talk to her mom
>> PJ like can you like shut up
>> Jane? Do you remember that little phone
call you had with me? You said you was
going to suck my dick. >> Yeah.
He's trying to distract it cuz he
doesn't want me to say what I what I'm
going to say.
>> Say what you're going to say.
>> You wild pee.
>> That's me.
>> Monty, tell Natalie
if what Lisa said was true, then contact me.
>> About what? About what?
I I'm not I'm not gonna
>> Well, she she's here right now. She
can't answer your question.
>> PJ, not need to talk to J. Talk to PJ.
Oh, [ __ ] off. >> Okay.
>> Lisa said Lisa said Natalie told her
London Taylor back of his car. [Laughter]
>> Look at PJ's awkward laughs.
Like I I didn't want to say it like that, but
>> Well, that's no answer to saying one of
you either way. You know, that's no
>> Okay. Well, I gather silence and tell Natalie if
>> Natalie's not talking to no one. Natalie
just said, you just said that she
doesn't want to talk on YouTube. It's me
who's talking on YouTube, not her. She
She don't want to talk.
But I'm just saying if
>> I'm saying if she has something to say,
contact me private. >> Yo,
I'm Triple H. I'm going to come back to
Newcastle and rape you and you're a little [ __ ] >> Monty, I can't just ra
>> What the [ __ ] is wrong with you people on here?
I'm going to come to New I'm going to
come back to Newcastle um Triple H and
I'm going to [ __ ] you and your little
>> Why would you say that?
>> Are you coming? Are you coming?
>> Can you pass a message to me?
>> I'm coming to get you.
You know when you went to message me privately
you look didn't you know you last time
you you done all right didn't you the bad
>> yeah that was fine
>> okay thank you
>> ar these idiots with the brain cells
>> they weren't playing out
>> like literally when you've got people
refused to pay out.
>> Seriously, no. Shut up. Shut up.
>> Rage. Have they ever refused to pay you out?
>> They're not allowed. No.
>> What would you do if they did? >> Anyway,
>> you're like, sweet.
>> No. What would you do though? What would you do?
the job off it.
>> Look, look how awkward they are laughing.
>> When people are trying to be real about
something like grown [ __ ] up,
>> they refuse to pay out.
>> No, PJ like you are embarrassing
yourself at this point.
Triple H. If they refused to pay you
out, what would you do?
>> I'm missing something. >> Cry. >> Really?
>> Really? Yeah. >> Why?
>> You should You should have had a lamb
dinner after J, shouldn't you?
>> No. Jane Jane was grooming me.
>> You cheeky [ __ ] [Laughter]
She was grooming me.
>> Nobody's grooming you.
>> She did groom me. Jane used to fancy you, man.
>> Yeah, I know.
>> I'm going to be honest. Like I always
got on with you. I always thought like
you were a nice lad and I love playing out.
>> Why do you keep saying that, Peter?
>> A young family in the don't [ __ ]
Why do it
said before? L said before, right? He
said you can't get off.
>> No, he can't get off anymore.
>> No. No. I don't think any of you can get off.
>> I don't think any of you can get off.
>> I'm going to talk. I'm laughing my ass
off, bro. As funny as that.
>> I don't think any of you can get off
YouTube. None of you. You're all stuck
on YouTube. YouTube is here live. It's
what you all do.
>> Monty, why is he laughing at like some people
the same [ __ ] every day?
>> Monty, isn't it while I'm speaking to your girlfriend?
>> Well, Triple H, can I come and we're not
talking about my girlfriend or bringing
>> Can I come and live with you? I
understand that, but like what sort of stupid
>> I'm coming with
nothing more. It's just a community. Nothing more.
>> Equally Natalie's mom said something.
>> Is that Terry still being on your case?
Natalie me got nothing to do with me or Natalie.
>> Shut it down.
>> Lens and Taylor is a grapist.
And you've got [ __ ]
this prick in the background hissing
like a [ __ ] hyena thinking it's
funny. I've got Triple H.
[ __ ] rubbing his [ __ ] while he does
it. Like for [ __ ] sake.
>> I'll tell you got off here. That Craig
Goodson didn't he's not got
>> mate. Don't Don't play that because it's
it's irrelevant. Absolutely irrelevant.
>> You used to [Laughter] [ __ ] hell.
Triple H. Like you were once upon a time
like a decent fellow. Like how can you
like how can you support that?
>> Support what?
>> Like you're like cackling away with him
like as though you've both just [ __ ]
>> He's not He's not wired up right, is he?
>> Yeah, but you you're both cackling away
like you've just won. who wants to be a
[ __ ] idiot. We're talking about
somebody raping someone like
>> No, no, we're not talking about nor
raping anybody. We're not talking about
rape or we're not talking about the
subject or nothing about rape. >> No
either way. I'm not talking about that.
>> I get what you're saying, but something
was said and it should be addressed.
Like the man is a psychopathic predator and
>> he's got right touched.
>> You got this.
>> Yeah. What do you expect? Most black
people are predators. >> Pardon?
>> I said most black people are predators.
>> He's not black.
>> He is.
No, he's not.
He is. Yes, he is.
>> He's a He's a He's half and half.
>> Is he half an
>> That London Taylor is a troll?
>> I think used to be all right with you,
didn't he? At one point.
>> Why do you
go? That is [ __ ] embarrassing.
>> You and your little um you and your
little uh you accent. Bless you.
>> Isa, why you going for be? What's he doing?
>> Because I've caught him slagging me off
behind my [ __ ] back. It's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
>> It's not real life, fella.
>> Yeah, it is. It is to me, mate. Oh, I
saw something earlier which side like
you've got a Mrs. and a young family and
you know, good luck to you. Don't don't
get dragged into all this [ __ ]
>> But I've split up from her.
>> Anyways, yeah, we still former fella,
>> you know.
>> What did you say? I can't hear you. >> I
can't get away.
>> I can't hear you, bro.
What did you say?
>> It's It's like listen to the awkwardness
in the split. I split up.
>> Oh, no. No, no, no. The
>> Going home with himself and laughing at yourself.
>> Oh, the chat's not awkward.
>> Oh, Trip come to Newcastle and we can
have a good night together and we can we
can have a drink and go on a pool.
>> Is that Sean? >> Okay.
>> Yeah. Monty's bread. Just call him Monty's friend. >> PJ.
>> PJ is your friend. You [ __ ] You
call him Monty's friend.
>> PJ, while you got Triple H and [ __ ] in
the chat in the hangout, tell the truth.
Was it not a setup that you allowed him
to come into your home filming? >> No. Dad,
>> what? It's a setup that someone's coming
and smash my windows. that I'd let
somebody come and smash my windows.
>> Come on.
>> Stop talking [ __ ] Jane. Stop talking
>> Stop talking [ __ ] Stop talking [ __ ] Jane. >> No.
>> Stop talking [ __ ] Jane.
>> Stop being like your Stop being like
your partner, Mark Samson.
>> Stop being a [ __ ] like your partner,
Mark Samson. The baldy nons.
>> I'm not with Mark. I don't.
>> Yeah, he's a [ __ ] na.
>> Mark's a [ __ ] na.
>> Why are you getting
>> That's what he is. He's He's a non He's
an absolute nonst
he's a predator. He's an actual
predator. Triple H. He is he he tried within
>> What's your game lying? Would I be lying
in saying the whole Terry thing was so
what she gave me?
>> Terry, PJ, LT, the whole situation is a
fit up. Am I lying?
>> Am what you think? Yes, you are lying.
>> No, stop it. Cuz I I could put videos up
of of emails like between you all. Like, stop it.
>> No, you can't.
>> Unfortunately, your your man has got a big mouth.
>> Me and Triple H are going to go on a
night out in Newcastle. >> Okay.
>> Like me and Monty did in Birmingham.
>> Am I Am I lying?
>> Yes, you are lying.
>> I'm not. You fancy PJ? >> No.
>> Yes, she did. Did you Didn't you hear
the the phone call, Mont? She was saying
how she wanted to suck my belly in and
that. Don't you remember that?
>> I remember that. Yeah,
>> that was [Laughter]
years ago. And from that point, any
opportunity you have had to
>> You wanted me to You wanted me to put
baby Peter Belly in you. You wanted me
to put baby Peter Belly in you.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> You You turn five. Hang on. Hang on.
>> Wait. Put perspective. Monty is your
mate. His Ms. has accused London Taylor
of raping her. And yet she
>> Hang on a minute. Hang on a minute. My m
accused anyone of that. Surely you
>> It's only you who just put that on
Natalie cuz Natalie's not accused nobody of nothing.
>> It's only you who's coming here and said
that Lisa's accused not Natalie.
>> Don't get on but like
>> it's ridiculous, isn't it? Um French.
It's mental in her.
>> Let's go out together before.
>> And you notice how like they're all Oh,
that that will make the people on
YouTube jealous, would it?
>> Do you drink Guinness?
>> Yeah, I love Guinness. And I love baby Guinness, too.
>> Have you had baby got to do with you anyway? >> No.
>> But you had baby Guinness shots? >> No.
>> We can drink Guinness all day together.
>> Yeah, lad.
>> What has this got to do with you anyway?
When you come >> be
>> because psychopath.
>> Yeah. Are you going to come out?
>> Well, your [ __ ] and [ __ ] It's two two different things.
>> No, it's not.
>> Of course it is. Of course it is.
>> Then is he not about normal?
>> Your your shit's got nothing to do with
that [ __ ] Do
>> you know if if women speaking up stops
another woman on here going through the
same thing then yeah women should speak
up about it
>> well not in a relationship if you have
peace you don't want to bring any of the
past up or
>> understand that I understand that and I
get like the fact she was threatened and
things like that listen to that inel
laughing like [ __ ] some of [ __ ] telling Tubby.
>> You wasn't calling me an insert when you
wanted to suck my bell inj
>> me. And what
>> you wanted me you wanted to have a baby with me.
>> What did you do?
>> Like you know she wanted to have a baby with me.
>> Monty, what?
>> You know she wanted to have a baby with me.
>> I'm in there.
>> No. Nobody would have a baby with you.
>> You wanted to have a baby with me, Jane.
>> Nobody wanted to have a baby.
in jail and [ __ ]
the one involving you. It
>> can remember that
>> remember your mate Fraser.
>> Do you remember what you did to your mate Fraser? >> Yeah.
>> What did What happened? What did you do?
>> I I I do him patrolling me.
>> I doxed him patroling me. Yeah, you do.
No. What did you do? What did you allow
to happen to Fraser's misses?
>> I didn't allow anything, Jane. Stop
making stuff up.
>> Okay. What did you What did you enable
to happen to Fraser's misses?
>> I didn't enable anything. What the [ __ ]
>> So, Fraser and his misses were quite happy together,
and Lyndon Taylor befriended her, met
her, and raped her. And you allowed that.
women then they can't accusations
going on here.
>> PJ PJ I'll say one thing for you. You
can be a [ __ ] but you will tell the
truth. Did LP meet Fraser's misses?
>> Yes. Everyone knows that. He admits it
himself. Why? Everyone knows that. Same
situation that happened with Natalie
>> Hang on a minute. How do you know if
Natalie situation happened or not happened?
>> Natalie remember
her mom posted a video.
>> It doesn't matter if her mom put it up
there. Her mom said Natalie and her mom sped out.
>> Okay. But her mom was
>> so it doesn't matter. Her mom chat [ __ ]
Her mom's been chatting [ __ ] a long time
on YouTube. No.
>> Did you Did you go drinking on Saturday then? Um, >> no.
>> J, do you think do you think Right. Um,
what do you call London Taylor met?
>> Yeah, he did.
>> Monty, did he or did he not?
>> I would have thought Do I know? All I
know is not met. That's only what I know.
And they answered it. London Taylor has
never met Natalie. They were going to
be, but they never met. >> Rubbish.
>> They never met.
>> No, that's lies.
>> Frenzy lately, Pete.
>> Nah, bro. No. Yeah.
>> Stop it.
>> Even she just said no. She's never met himself. >> Yeah.
>> Have you?
>> There you go.
>> Don't play. Let me
cry. Her mom crying because a lot of
[ __ ] got put up there.
Stop it. Like the money.
>> I'm not stopping because everybody
already knows why these two were crying.
It's because Natalie and Lisa are fell
out. Lisa's now going to get on YouTube.
>> You remember when Timmy had the fight?
>> I know all the details of them meeting.
>> You haven't got all the details of them meeting.
>> Yes, I do. Yes, I do.
>> Because would have told me if they did
or they don't. She's not. She won't keep
it away. And I just asked her with my
night Mike nuted. Did she meet him? And
she said no.
>> Yes, she did.
>> No, she did. She come on. Natalie would
tell me nothing.
You know, if they did do that, then I'd
be comforting Natalie. So there'd be
nothing there, would they?
>> And after they met, he sent her a bank
transfer of 20 quid.
>> 20 quid would be good then, is it? That
that's mean that
>> the guy is a predator and you're all defending him.
>> I'm not offending him. Listen, listen. I
do believe you are in many ways. Plenty
of ways. But when
>> I just asked Natalie when we were m did
he meet you? Did he? And she said no.
Like yesterday when he was in here, he
even said he even said he was going to
meet up with Natalie. He didn't
>> tell everyone she had brown teeth then.
>> You had brown teeth.
>> Got brown teeth.
>> Natalie does not have brown teeth.
>> So why did he say that?
>> Well, I don't know. Well, he must have brown teeth.
>> Can I ask a question? Why does PJ keep
doing that Jimmy Savile awkward [ __ ]
laugh? If if
>> Because PJ Jimmy Sapp's son
is not well.
>> They weren't paying out. They refused to pay.
>> People in the oven.
>> Well, have you been raped by your mafia?
>> Pardon? Have you been raped by him?
>> I would never allow him anywhere near me.
>> So So why you going around then talking
about other people being rap and then
you haven't? I think you're jealous.
>> Because he posted my body all over the [ __ ]
>> Oh, I posted your body. So you got
around accusing my rap now. Yeah.
>> No, no. I'm copying what now?
>> Oh, so you're copying. Oh, okay. I see.
I'll post a video right now of Lisa saying Natalie,
>> Lisa, don't matter if you do that. It
don't matter. You can do if you want,
but it's up to you in it. >> No,
it's just a waste of time. They said
literally covering for him.
>> I'm not covering for him. Listen, why
the [ __ ] do I give a [ __ ] for someone
who I don't know on YouTube really to be
honest with you.
>> Why? Why is
>> you so be careful what you say about him?
>> She just said be careful what you're
saying about him because he could go
around and sm
listen like I just said
you doing this
with all this hair crime going on
>> someone to be messed with seriously.
Yeah, exactly. And >> that's wonder,
>> like I said to you, like I said to you,
I believe you talking allegations around and on
>> what's even true about Natalie,
>> who's not to be messed with.
>> Oh sh
>> He's wet. Come on.
>> He's not some big man. Nie, I don't know
why you go on like he's some big man. >> Natalie
>> just north. That's it.
>> Monty, tell Natalie to listen to me for a minute.
>> Thank you.
>> If you don't want to, if you don't want
to talk, that's fine. You can go ahead
and talk. I am Sophia.
>> I am Sophie. Yeah. But everybody stopped
painting him as this gangster.
>> His mother is a [ __ ] head teacher.
He's wet behind ears. He's had his like
entire life paid for. Like stop all
[ __ ] bowing down to him.
>> I think he fancy him to be honest.
>> Actually, no. He disrespected me in the
most worst possible way.
>> I know you haven't. All you've talked
about is London Tail actually, Jim.
>> Okay. Well,
>> my point people the the people in the
community will take what they want to
take from this conversation and we'll
leave it there.
>> Yeah. Change conversation ball.
>> All right. What What would you like to
talk about? Will we talk about PJ like
maybe from a comic book or
>> will he try and give Pete a lid or
>> I think I think I think me, Monty,
Triple H, and Nons should all meet up
for a beer in Newcastle. I think that's
what we should all do.
>> See, I'm sure you fancy you bring him up every day.
>> I think we and Fraser as well. We can all
>> I think I think I think he should meet
up with James. He's feeling a bit lonely. So,
>> no, I don't I don't I I don't I don't
meet I don't meet slags.
>> I don't meet a virgin.
>> And I wouldn't touch I wouldn't touch a virgin.
>> That's not what you were saying on the
phone. Love. That's not what you were
saying on the phone when you were saying
how you wanted to suck my bell end.
>> Nobody said that to you.
>> Yes, you did.
>> Even Triple H remembered it. Don't you
remember that phone call, Monty? Don't
you remember it?
Why? Why is that phone call like so
stuck in your mind? It's so irrelevant.
>> Because it's something that no one could ever
words them words were said with such
passion and love. It wasn't
it was dire like
too much to drink something they regret. Jesus.
>> Well, you had a oneonone phone call with
him, Jane, did you?
>> Pardon? You had a one-on-one phone call
with him, did you?
>> Yeah, it was set. He was having sex.
>> No, no, I I thought I was having a
private conversation and he live streamed it.
>> Did you like Did you like it more?
>> No, I couldn't think of anything worse.
>> Yeah, that's what we were saying on the phone,
>> mate. It was a long time ago and I
>> crashed on this community for that.
>> And why don't you, Natalie and Dane have a present?
>> If I ever regret having a free with me
and it's me and my fingers and that's it.
And Monty, do you know I hope you and
Natalie like [ __ ] do the whole
happily ever after and be happy and
shite like that because this community
like likes to drag people down. But go
and live your lives.
>> I am. I'm I'm putting a golden slipper
on that leave.
>> Just go and live your lives and be happy.
>> Monty man can't Monty man can't get off.
This is like [ __ ] smack to me. YouTube
is too deep in no jam.
>> There's no getting off.
>> Oh, no.
>> There's no There's no hope for him in
it. He's too deep in it. Do you want to go?
>> I've actually got a new YouTube husband. [Laughter]
I have to be your husband.
>> I have I have a new community interest.
>> Do you remember Do you remember phrase?
>> No. No. The best thing is he's been
being off YouTube. So they know
everything what's been going on and
everything else. So
>> yeah, but the thing is Monty finds YouTube funny.
>> I don't find it funny. You're [ __ ]
>> baby is like
>> it's sad what these people
>> like a [ __ ] baby
>> so triple h I'll come to Newcastle next
Saturday we'll go out yeah
>> are you coming
>> we're going to give you a foot massage pia >> never
>> so we can we can get on the guard strip
give you a foot massage
>> you know I'm going
Do you know you know we
will spend about400? Yeah.
>> Do you know who I think the most active
man on YouTube? Yeah.
>> 100 isn't it?
>> Aely averageely spend I got about 150.
>> Yeah. Normally yeah >> PJ
>> you can go out and get you can go out
and you can go out and meet some lassis now. It
>> she wants to tell you who the most
attractive man is on YouTube.
>> Do you know who I'm meeting? >> Who?
>> Oh, it's Lord J. Obviously.
>> Oh, he's [ __ ] He's [ __ ] ugly.
>> That was the ugliest thing I read. >> Yeah,
>> we're doing the Welsh Irish.
>> What? What? What was the story with what
was the story with Britney Trip launch?
Do you remember the story?
>> How exciting.
>> Basically, it was some girl he was
obsessed with on PlayStation.
>> He's taking you to CH. [Laughter]
>> No, he is free. No, he ain't [ __ ] a
PG. Why can Ro get laid, PJ? And you can
>> He can't get
Listen, you're the one. You're the one.
You're the one with Listen, you're the
one with You're the one with a fat ugly bird.
>> Oh, no. She's not.
>> It's not a fat one little also can't get
laid. How many times have we seen with a
woman on here? Yeah,
>> that's out of order. She's not at the
end of the day. At least not can get
laid and you can't PJ.
>> Well, I' I'd rather not get laid than
you. You're both ugly. I'd rather have
nothing to have any of you.
>> I don't care.
>> I think you just meant
proper jealous, bro. Proper.
>> I think that is beautiful.
>> Every single woman on this community is
ugly. Triple H. Every single woman in
this community is ugly.
>> AJ's just jealous cuz he's no one.
>> Yeah, I'm jealous. Bro, I've had more
women than you, Monty. I've ever had
>> All you had is All you've had is
Why did you want to meet her?
>> Huh? She wanted to meet me.
>> No, no, but you also wanted to meet her as well.
>> No, she wanted to meet me. Just can I
just say if me and Lord Jay have a baby,
we're going to call it um Paul Murphy PJ for short.
>> And LJ Lj can't get women. That's why LJ
That's why LJ Simps. That's why LJ Simply
so far, PJ.
>> Well, he definitely hasn't because he's
never been He's never been seen with a
woman on YouTube. I've been seen with
plenty. Oh, don't ugly as [ __ ] boys.
>> But again, you like to forget things, so
it's okay, bro. I don't blame you.
>> Beautiful girl.
>> Who else is in this chat? Me, PGA, J,
and who else?
>> Triple H.
>> Triple H. Even Triple H is better
looking than you, PG, for [ __ ] sake.
>> Yeah, but everyone's better looking than
you. You look like you got cancer. PJ
it's called being man.
>> You look like you look like you got you
look like you got leukemia
in the background. Triple H's all voice Who's like
H's little Jordy? Jordy voice in the
background. Oh, bless you. Bless you.
>> Why doesn't ever come on the hangout anymore?
>> Why with him like this?
>> You like you know that
>> you know you know you know Monty and
Timmy should be friends in it. Triple H.
They should make up
at least Timmy's got friends. You haven't.
>> Monty, you don't have no friends. You
don't have no friends at all.
>> You do is table for one for PJ.
>> I I had I had to come to [ __ ]
Birmingham and pick me.
>> I had to PJ. You wanted to come to
Birmingham. That [ __ ] different.
>> No, you said if I didn't come, you'd
never speak to me again.
>> And it doesn't matter about that rubbing
that [ __ ] in my face. She was This is
totally different. You slagged Natly
off. He called my misses ugly. So that's completely different.
>> That's rude. That's
>> you just [ __ ] up. I appreciated you
being there for me, but when you swag my
misses calling my misses, isn't it?
That's completely different.
>> Good looking guy.
>> Jeremy Peter thinks it's all a laugh.
>> It's not a laugh, Lord. When people are
actually supposed to be and he thinks
that people are going to be there when
he calls his
little accent lesson.
>> I like I like Triple H. Montre's
little voice in the background. Don't
say say stuff like that, Peter.
>> No. Fair play to you for defending us.
>> His little voice screams. Don't say
stuff like that.
>> Is that greasy on the top? You just
burned your because you feel so awkward
and and violated and do you know you
just burned your mates.
>> Listen, if you don't pack it in, Jane,
I'm going to come in your door.
>> You can't even come up a woman, you dick. >> Huh?
>> I said you can't even come up a woman. >> Oh,
>> really? Well, guess what? Rice is coming
up your baby mom every night, and you're
going to do nothing about it.
I don't want to do nothing about it.
I've got the best woman off my life and that's not
>> and you'll do absolutely nothing.
>> Yeah, I don't want to do nothing. Why do
I want to talk about
>> Yeah, that don't me one little bit. I've
got Natalie, so why the [ __ ] am I
interested in Kay's relationship or not?
I'm a [ __ ] Only what relationship I'm
interested is in my own,
>> you know.
>> Do you know Monty? Good on you. She's a
good-looking girl and good luck to you both.
>> So guys can stick keep sticking his ET
fingers in. Curly
>> TJ's crying.
>> No, never crying, mate. Yeah.
>> And I don't hear that. Why is the most
manly game that rice getting laid and you're not?
>> Well, I've already been laid many times.
More than you and him combined. No, no, no.
>> You like you like you like to forget
things and I'll answer your question.
It's because you and Rice have no
standards. You go for these ugly fat women.
>> No, no, no. You got to play the process.
That's no standard,
>> bro. I've been with other people that aren't proies.
>> Yeah, but that's when the face when
they're going home for getting really,
really, really. Okay. You know, everyone
on YouTube's had Natalie. You even said
yourself she's got black flats. Well,
okay. No, no, no. Being able to vote three people.
>> No woman has black flats. What a stupid
>> That's what Monty said.
>> No, that's what you said because Yeah.
And Monty and Monty said it in his video.
>> Bringing that up. I said that when me
and Natalie finished but no Natalie
don't have black.
>> No, no, that's what you said.
>> Everything you know this Natalie is
everyone and anyone. You know that
Natalie's anyone and everyone's. Do you get it?
>> No. Because she's
>> No, she's anyone and everyone's get it.
>> You're just jealous cuz she not do
>> Yeah, but I'm so jealous. I'm sorry,
bro. If I I could have had that woman
need a woman who just comes on and
>> Monty, listen. I could have I could have
been with that woman that you're with 5
years ago if I wanted to. >> Monty,
why would I be jealous? Why would I be
>> Why would I be jealous?
>> Yeah, you keep telling yourself.
I don't need to tell myself that.
I've had it on.
>> Yeah. Okay. Whatever.
>> Every woman in your life, including your
own mother, leaves you. >> Oh,
>> yeah. Okay. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Jane, shut the [ __ ] up. You stupid
Well, slag. You got [ __ ] disabled kids.
>> Yeah. Go look after your disabled kids.
>> No, that's a bit shable.
>> I don't have a disabled kid. Yes, you do
have the you just you do have a disabled
kid. You've got a kid with a >> disabled.
>> No, but you're disabled. You can't read.
>> I can't.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm disabled. You're not
>> disabled. No, but you you can't you can't read.
>> Well, you might disabled PJ yourself.
>> You actually had you had a video crying
over a a girl at your age. You're a [ __ ]
That just shows how much I do love that.
You're a [ __ ] simp bastard. That's why
I lost that. You know what I mean?
>> You know what I mean?
>> It's yours.
>> Yeah. How many watching? >> 17.
>> Simple YouTube crying cuz you can't get
a woman every day.
>> I've had more women than you've ever had, mate. >> Exactly.
I've been in so many relationships. It's
unreal. How many have you been in?
>> No, you haven't. No, you haven't. No,
you haven't. Go on. You got no slack.
I'm saying it's because you've got no
standards. Cuz you've you have to date
slacks. Slacks. You've got no standards.
That's what you know I mean >> PJ all crumbles. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. She has a show.
You know showed her to the hold of YouTube.
>> Me and together.
>> Yeah. She showed her family to the hold
of YouTube. No, she didn't.
>> Yes, she did. Yes, she [ __ ] did,
mate. I seen a [ __ ] There's an
account. I can't think what it's called.
Yeah, he's got lo
>> and you're trying to say she's not a slag.
>> She's not. Okay, okay, okay.
>> Only a slag would do that.
>> Think all you have to get a taste.
>> But you can't get a slack anyway. So,
>> yeah, I can't have a slack. Yeah. Jane,
remember the phone call you had with me? Anyone
>> Jane, do you remember the phone call you
had with me? >> No.
>> Yeah, I remember it. Yeah,
I remember it quite well actually.
>> Mate, it was six years ago. We've all
had too much to drink and unfortunately like
you you're just irrelevant.
Does that greasy get woman women?
>> Oh, Triple H, I love what you just did
there with the plot twist.
>> I was going to say,
>> but listen, Dane, there's no point you
coming on here, do because you always
play victim in the end.
>> You play victim and you when you blame
everything on Natalie. You're bringing that.
>> Listen, I I'm standing here. I'm
offering myself up to anyone that wants
to come at me. There's no victim. >> Yeah.
>> Should be Shouldn't you be looking after
your [ __ ] disabled kids? >> PJs, lads.
>> It's not time. Kids will be in bed at this time.
>> You know, >> you
Why do you pick up people's kids?
>> Yeah, cuz that >> sick
cuz listen to his awkward laugh. He's been
>> I love it. Yeah.
>> Just give Why don't you just give Pete
that their ride?
>> No, I don't want [ __ ] I don't want the slag.
>> I She's been with that She's been with
that ugly Mark Thson. She's been with
that baldy ugly wannabe London hard man.
Yeah, she's been with him. No one, >> mate.
>> Is he fuckard? Is that Is that overinky
man? Is he [ __ ]
>> He would batter you.
>> Me, mate. I've been to his area two.
Listen, Jane. I've been to his area two
times. He didn't come out. Everyone
remembers it. Shut the [ __ ] up.
>> Listen, listen, listen, listen, listen,
mate. You couldn't even go to Rice.
Yeah. And he's shagging your baby. He's
a stepmad. He's a step He's a stepdad to
your kids and you're allowing it. You're
allowing him to be stepdaddy to your kids.
>> You know what I mean? He is being step
to your kids and you're doing nothing.
Why are you know him?
>> He He would do you serious harm. I I
>> He will do me serious harm.
>> I promise you he would.
>> Two times then who listen? He called the
police three times when London Taylor
went on his door. That old wrinkly man
ain't going to do anything to anyone.
That I'm I promise you that he would
never. Yeah, I've been to his area two
times. He's not a hard man. He is not a
hard man. I don't know why. I don't know
what he tells you. You well slag. I
don't know what he tells you, but he
ain't about nothing. >> PJ
I've gone to his area and and he's done nothing
from your sister's boyfriend.
>> You know what I'm saying? Yeah. Listen,
man. Run up on your sister's boyfriend.
You ran off from shocked him.
>> No, I didn't run off from anyone. No.
No. You got You stupid little clown.
You can't even meet Timmy. You can't
even meet Timmy. Timmy. Timmy.
>> You can't even meet Timmy. You soft.
>> Timmy's a little soft. You can't meet
me. You haven't even met
I know you is because she was with me in
Birmingham. Yeah. Do you know what? When
are you next in Birmingham?
>> Never again.
>> Never again. Why? Why? Why?
>> Cuz I have no reason to go back there.
>> What? What? I thought you wanted me a fight.
>> Yeah, but then I said I'm just wasting
my time with you clowns.
>> Oh, no. No. No. No. I am going to slap
you, don't you?
>> Okay. Come to London tomorrow then. I'll meet you.
>> So why you said you're coming back to Birmingham?
>> No. Oh, I said I was going to >> stop
me up to London tomorrow.
You're a [ __ ] con on this community.
>> You can't take these people serious, can you? Triple,
>> you're not serious. You saw PJ. That's
the thing. Not
You're not about this life, PJ. Not
talking about it.
>> What is it? Come to London. Come to this
place. Come to this place.
>> It's not worked out for you, PJ. Is it
>> Oh dear.
>> You know, if I come to London, PJ,
you're just going to get slapped up. You
know that yourself.
>> I [ __ ]
>> Either [ __ ] way. Even [ __ ] where?
>> In case anyone's wondering, it's Tina
Turner. I don't want to fight no more.
Oh, I love this song.
>> TW, why didn't you meet up with Jane?
>> TW has got a family and he's doing the right.
>> No, he doesn't. He's single now. He's
single now. He just said he's single.
>> He's living his best life.
>> Yeah, but at least Triple H can get
laid, PG. Okay,
>> Monty, you can't listen listen. Monty,
if you could get laid, you wouldn't be
crying over some [ __ ] slag that slept
with 100 men. Listen, listen, listen,
listen, listen. You are the one doing
videos crying over some slag cuz you
can't get laid. And the reason you was
doing it, you can't get nothing. You
can't get anything. That's why you was
crying over Natalie cuz you can't get anything better.
>> I've been making it 6 months. I've been 6 months,
>> mate. Do you reckon if you could get
laid, you would be doing that? You
reckon if you could get laid, you'd be doing that?
>> You only need to get one woman. I only
need to get laid.
>> Listen, you were crying over Natalie cuz
you couldn't get anyone else.
>> [ __ ] me.
>> I'm happy with that.
>> To the music.
>> Natalie makes me happy. I make Natalie
happy and that's only what matters.
>> If you and Natalie are happy, do it.
Keep doing it. That's all that matters.
>> But yeah, I'm going to put a ring on it.
Make it official.
>> Would you would you meet Would you meet
uh would you meet Jane? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Meet up and have a bit have a have
a wine in it.
>> A lamb roast.
>> A lamb roast, bro.
>> Let's all join in on the chorus. Triple H.
>> Triple H likes this.
>> See, even even Triple H is getting laid now.
>> Yeah, you can't get laid. That's why
you're with a slag.
>> No, no, you're on about yourself, PJ.
>> That's why you're with a slag. That that that show,
she got Triple H. [Music]
>> Yeah, that's fine. I knew she's done
that. She would piss out her face.
>> Show her off. Alexa,
>> I think he's got a come to show.
>> Triple H. Are you a [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Triple H is busy with his family. He
doesn't give a [ __ ]
>> DJ, you have a [ __ ] [ __ ] You can't even
get [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> I've had more chicks than you, mate.
>> I've never had to resort to what you're
if you could get laid. If you could get
laid, you wouldn't be you would have
been crying over. You would have been
crying over Natalie if you could get
[ __ ] laid. Shut the [ __ ] up.
>> 10 out of [ __ ] 100. You being turned down.
>> But he's with He's with Natalie now. So
where where has he gone wrong?
>> Monty man has got Monty man's got a woman.
>> Monty man's got a woman. Triple H's got
a woman. PJ the only one left is yourself.
>> There you go. Triple H is with J. PJ.
Who you with now? He's meeting up with
you now. Is he?
>> This This has not worked out for you tonight, PJ.
>> Where's he gone?
>> Oh my god.
>> In it. He's got McDonald's Wi-Fi.
>> Oh my god. My neighbors are having a party.
>> He's outside McDonald's in he in the tent.
>> Oh my god. >> Yeah.
>> Isn't he back at his M?
>> Sorry, I was doing something.
Yeah. Yeah. PJ's back for himself. Yeah.
>> He just chopped his [ __ ] off.
>> Sorry, mate.
>> Does anyone vape?
>> So, why did your mom disown you, please? Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Why did your mom disown you? Talk to you.
>> Oh [ __ ] Oh god.
Oh man, I wanted to know why his mom dropped him. Do
>> you know? We don't need to dig him. We
don't need to terrorize him. He's He's
[ __ ] made his own bed tonight and
[ __ ] most definitely laiding out.
She PG your best friend.
>> No. No, no one's me friend in here.
>> No one's my friend.
>> Nobody Nobody has friends in here.
>> Yeah, definitely. It I just come on for
a laugh, mate. Like I like a laugh. for
like I was like when Timmy El used to always know