Oh yeah.
Question mark. Question mark. There you go. Yeah.
Especially when my stomach feels really Yeah.
Yeah. Well, that got heated, didn't it? [ __ ]
hell. That got [ __ ] very heated indeed.
today. Can't drink this. It's
disgusting. That's disgusting, bro.
Disgusting. Oh, that tastes vile. That was Yeah.
These people really don't like [ __ ]
live in the real world, do they, man?
They really really don't. If they
actually lived in the real world and
then they actually left the house,
they'd realize that women are such
[ __ ] But they don't know that because
they they just spend all their day on
YouTube. They spend all their day
online. So they wouldn't know how things
actually are. You know what I'm
saying? So they just defend women. Oh,
go away you little keyboardy. I remember you. [ __ ]
off. Just defend women. It's bizarre, lad. [ __ ]
bizarre man that lives in [ __ ]
Cardiff. Talking about people I've met
[ __ ] two, three years ago. Oh, you
really are sad, aren't you? You really
are a sad bastard. You need to act your
age, man. You need to grow up. Some
people in this community really need to
grow up. That's what I think. Yeah.
criticism and stuff, but it's like
things that goes beyond that cuz you've already
like you've already explained this like
over and over and over and over again.
Like, you know, it's a platform. You're
ranting. People are coming on, but these
people that are talking [ __ ] about your
looks are uglier than you. They're in a
worse position than you, but they're
trying to say, "Oh, you can't get a
woman because you're ugly, but you're
better looking than them, and that's why
they won't join the panel." Like, it's
like they've got they just don't have no
bad words to say about women. And that's
what pissed me off this morning, bro. It
wasn't a gam. I didn't care about 70,
bro. I was prepared to lose it. You
know, the only reason I got pissed off
last week is cuz I was still hung over
and then the bad experiences, bro. I was
fine losing the money yesterday. 70
[ __ ] quid. I don't give a [ __ ]
You know, it wasn't that, bro. It
[ __ ] wasn't that cuz I wasn't even pissed off
yesterday. It's the whole dating the
dating game being rigged against you is
something that I'm I'm struggling to
come to terms
with. There we go. I just ruined the
relationship with Laney. I don't care.
Do you understand? I don't care. People
need to [ __ ] know, bro. These people
have not been in your shoes. They don't
know. They don't understand. Do you
understand? They can get sex whatever
they want. They can get a relationship,
but they won't. But I I made a good
point, Samuel. Yeah, these I know you're
taking a piss, but they're saying that,
"Oh, it's you. It's you. It's you. It's
you. It's you." And I then said, "Okay,
well, if I was a woman
complaining, would anyone blaming me?"
No. So therefore, it's not you then.
Because if you was a woman, nobody would
be blaming you. That's how you know that
it is not you. For some reason, this
society just loves blaming men. They
love blaming men. I I don't know why
they love doing it. They like blaming
any man that struggles. They do. They
genuinely genuinely genuinely do because
if you was a woman complaining, nobody
would be blaming you
whatsoever. So, what is that then, bro?
Come on now. Let's be
real. They can get what they want
whenever they want. It's [ __ ]
annoying. And look at me, Samuel. I I've
got money. I've got more than enough
money, but I can go out every day if I
want to. Doesn't change anything.
Doesn't change anything. I'm that
annoyed I don't even go out anymore
because of it, you know? It's [ __ ]
annoying, bro. You know, God, it is
[ __ ] annoying thinking about that every day,
bro. I was snoring when I was sleeping.
I had nightmares
again, you know.
I had nightmares, too. You
know, I know it's a madness. I know
you're taking a piss, but it literally
is like that. And then when you complain
about it, they blame you. But when you
speak facts, they blame you. So, I don't
I don't know what they actually expect,
bro. Because when you know, then they blame you.
No, it's not women g it's not women um
it's not women dominating my life. It's
the fact that they have the dating game
easy. I don't like that. I don't like
the fact that they don't have to lift a
finger. That's the [ __ ] that annoys me.
No. No. That's the thing that's annoying
me. That's the thing that's annoying me, bro. You
know, it's annoying, bro. And they can
get sex whenever they want. they can get
relationships whenever they want. You
know, it's it's annoying, bro. Just
thinking about it, it's so annoying. Oh
my god, it's so annoying. You know,
having to wake up thinking about that,
bro. It's that's the thing that actually
annoys me. That's the thing that genuinely annoys
me. If they had to put 10% effort what
we've put into, I wouldn't care. I
mind. Like that [ __ ] one on Reddit
about I've barely traveled. I've been to
four different countries, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] Don't try and give me dating
advice when you're the one who's got a
boyfriend. Yeah. Isn't it funny, Samuel,
how all of these people, right, that
that give you advice or or the same
people that are in
relationships? Is it see money funny how
the same people that give you advice
that you're going to meet someone, you
need better pictures are all in
relationships, all of these
women. So, what's he doing? Okay, I'll
explain it again. Okay, I'll explain this
again for the millionth of time. I'll
explain this again. The women that men
go for are people that are 6'5, 10 out
of 10 men or [ __ ] with tattoos.
That's what they're doing. They Yeah,
that's what they're doing. They are
being 6'5, being white and better
looking is what they're doing because
they have got high standards. Yeah.
Won't they be the best? No. Because you
can't compare yourself to another
person. Life does not work that way. You
can't compare yourself to someone who's
low value. No. No. You
know, they go for the best of the best.
Their standards are unrealistic. And
some of them they don't even get with
men because their standards are so
unrealistic. to answer your question,
know, but they won't be the best person
to ask because you can't compare
yourself to one to another person. Life
don't work that way. I wish it did work
that way. I wish it really did work that
way, but life does not work that way
because there's not somebody for
everybody. That's the whole point of it
is that there's not someone for everyone.
There's not someone for everyone,
lad. Yeah. So, whatever what what advice
could they give you? Think about it,
bro. If you're a white guy who's seven
out of 10 and you're an Indian guy who's
7 out of 10, the white guy's got it
made. The white guy is going to get what
he gets. So, what advice could he give
an Indian person? Let's let's put it
that way. Let's put it that way. If you
really want to go technical, it doesn't
work like that because everyone's got
different looks. Everyone's different.
Everyone's in different circumstances
because you've done it. I've done it.
Doesn't work. We've all seen dating apps
when they think that you're white. You
get loads and loads and loads of
matches, but as soon as you're a bit
ethnic, you don't get nothing. What
advice is there to be had? Change your
[ __ ] skin color. You
know, they have got a materialistic
certain type that they go for. So nobody
could give you advice, you
know. So that's how it
is. Don't give me [ __ ] advice when
you're the one who's in a [ __ ]
relationship. [ __ ] off, man. Get the
[ __ ] out of
here. Then she's telling me about 20
countries. I said, "You barely [ __ ]
traveled and I get more money than you,
you silly little [ __ ] Learn your
[ __ ] place. [ __ ] off, man. Don't
[ __ ] give me advice when you're
sucking off someone else's dick. [ __ ]
off, man. I hate women. I [ __ ] hate them. They're
scumbags. Um, no. I need to go to a
shop. I can't be bothered to move out of
bed even though I was just in the
kitchen. I just made some hot chocolate.
It was [ __ ]
gross. No, guess it's better than nothing. Bye-bye.
Now, I messaged LT, by the way, about
them posters about 20 minutes ago. You
need to get them posters made, mate.
I'll put I'll put them out, lad. You
need to get them posters made. I'll put
them out. I'll put them [ __ ] out,
lad. So, yeah, a woman that can get any
man she wants. So, to answer your
question, they go for unrealistic. They
go for 6'5 white men that are eight and above lookswise.
Oh, nonslegs. Nonslegs. I messaged you
about 10 minutes ago. If you're
watching, get them posted sort Get them
posters sorted out,
bro. Get them posters sorted. I I'll
I'll dist distribute them. What you
doing, bro? I'll shut this rat face up
once and for all. Yeah. Give me a good
hundred. I'll do the other hund. And
I'll also hand post them as well. So,
yeah. You want to see about things just
being YouTube? Well, this is just
YouTube as well. when I put posters out
on you, that's going to be just YouTube
as well because it's on it's on my YouTube channel.
So, so that's the kind of people that
they go for, Joe. That's the kind of
people that they go for, lad. So, yeah,
get them posters out if you're watching
this. I've messaged I've commented on
your um I've commented on your um
channel. So, and that's that's just
YouTube. It is my YouTube channel and I
will do what I want. You know how you
say it's YouTube, you can delete what
you want and yeah, I can do what I want
as well and I'll put up posters of you
once this guy actually posted, bro. Get
get these posters posted. You say you
got a print out work, I will post them
[ __ ] everywhere, mate. Trust me. This
time I will do it
everywhere. Shut the [ __ ] up again, you
know, for another two weeks. Yeah.
So, so yeah, they're the kind of people
that they go for anyways.
So, answer your question, lad. So,
yeah. You seem to think they don't have
a specific type that they go for, lad.
Mate, it doesn't The police banging my
door down. I'm going to show them what
you've been doing every day. You little
rat face virgin. These posters are going
out, rat face. Oh yeah, that 19year-old
is better than [ __ ] disabled Sarah
who can't even talk. Mate, the police
I'll show the police what you've been
doing every day. It's fine. I want them
to bang the door down. I want them to
come. I want them to I want them to I
will show them all of your harassment. I
want them to come. You don't understand.
I want them to come. Rat face. Rat face.
I want them to come. Rodent. Rodent
face. I want them to come. I'm pulling
up posters of you. Yeah. And I'm going
to make sure you're going to get the
[ __ ] kicked out of that rat face
anywhere you think you're going again.
And you're going to do nothing about it.
And guess what? A, the police don't even
know where I live. And B, even if the
police do come, I'm going to show them
what you've been doing. Rat face. Bring
it on, rat face, with the fat, ugly
disabled girlfriend. Please. Come on.
Come on. I want to show them your
harassment rat face. Your little rat
autism coming on YouTube every [ __ ]
day. I'm going to do posters. I'm going
to shut your rat face up. You understand
[ __ ] You understand [ __ ] I'm going to
shut your rat face up again. You lanky
[ __ ] Yeah. Do you understand? Lanky rat
face or a rat face? I'm going to shut
your [ __ ] mouth up again. You hear
me? Yeah. You remember them two two
years two weeks last year. You [ __ ]
rat [ __ ] But I shut your mouth up and
you run into police. You're going to do
it again. You're going to do it again.
And I'm going to show the police all of your
harassment. Ratty rat face. Come on, rat
[ __ ] with a fat ugly girlfriend. You've
got one person ruined you. I know it's
And I'm going to ruin you. And I'm And
you know what? I'm going to make sure
you're not going to leave your house.
You're not going to You're going to get
your rat face kicked in. You're not
mate. You're still here. You ran to the
police. Literally. Okay. Okay, mate. I'm
still here as well. Yes. I'm going to
put the posters up again and you're
going to shut that rat [ __ ] face up
about me. You understand? Autism boy.
Autism boy with a rat face. I'm going to
make you shut that [ __ ] mouth up with
yours again. You and your fat ugly
girlfriend. You and your fat ugly
girlfriend. How about that one? Yeah.
Simple, mate. That's it. Yeah.
Literally, bro. I
am, bro. I'm getting LT to these posters
and it's going to cost absolutely
nothing. It's going to cost absolutely
nothing, mate. I'm going to put up
posters about you, rat face. No Indian
for you. No Chinese for you. No Barbies
for you. Woohoo. You can run to the
police again. You can run to the police
again with your fat ugly girlfriend rat
face. With your [ __ ] rat, mate. I'd
rather have a big nose and look like
you. You little rat. You ugly little rat
with a fat ugly girlfriend. At least I
don't look like a [ __ ] rat and got a
disabled girlfriend like you. I'd rather
have nothing than be a ratfaced
diagnosed autistic little virgin like
you. I'd rather be I'd rather be than an
autistic diagnosed virgin like you. I'd
rather have Pinocchio's nose than look
like an autistic little rat that can
only get disabled. I admit it. We all
admit our faults.
You know, I'd rather have Pinocchio's
nose than have a [ __ ] rat face like
you. You diagnosed autistic. Diagnosed
autistic. I would rather have Pinocchio
knows that look like a [ __ ] ugly rat
like you. That's why you could only get
disabled because you've got a rat face.
You got that rodent face. The ugly face
scares people away. Anyways, mate, I'm
putting up posters about you anyways
this week. So, I'm just going to wait
for LT to um print these posters out.
You diagnosed autistic little rat face.
I'm going to shut that [ __ ] mouth up
about me again. Yeah, I'm going to shut
him up for another two, three weeks. And
you know what? I'll probably just do him
every month to be fair. I'll probably
just after that do him every month. Alie
says he's got a free printer, don't he?
So, he can print hundreds enough.
Hundreds enough. 100 every month is
enough. That'll keep the ratfaced virgin away. Yeah.
Yeah. So, I've already commented on
these videos, so he just needs to get
back to me.
Now, I'll tell you where to post them as
well, bro. I'll tell you where to I'll
I'll tell you where to post them, too,
once you've done the posters, and I'll
just I'll just collect
them, you know?
So, it will shut the cut
up for like two
weeks. No, bro. Not even. No, not even.
I don't know why everyone thinks that
you have to lose money to get mad. No,
not even. I'm just sick of women. I'm
sick of the dating game being rigged against
men. I'm sick of the dating game being
rigged against men. It's something that
I can't sort of let go go of. You know,
I had nightmares today. I woke up
snoring. Sorry, I was snoring. Somebody
told me I was snoring. I could [ __ ]
hear you snoring. [ __ ] madness, bro.
I woke up late and um I just woke up
thinking about how the dating game is
rigged against you and a woman can get
any man she
wants only to be arrested. I'm not going
to get arrested because I'm going to
show the police what he's been doing. No
one's going to be getting arrested,
right? Because I don't live with my mom
anymore and I'm going to be showing the
police he's harassment every [ __ ] day
on YouTube. If the police even think
about coming anywhere to my door, I'm
going to show them all of his harassment
every [ __ ] day. So, at the end of the
day, no one's getting arrested by
him. You know, I'll say that this little
ratfaced virgin with his fat ugly
girlfriend, and I'll say that to him,
keeps coming on YouTube every day
harassing, harassing, harassing every
single day with his
autism. Right. And I'm going to say it.
I'm going to say it, mate. I'm not
opening the door to them if the even if
the police come. Bro, listen. I know how
it works. Yeah, I know how it works. I
will tell them they can't enter the
house without a woman. I'll say, "Do
something about this [ __ ] harassing me
every day with his fat ugly girlfriend
on YouTube, then come back to me." No.
No. This is what I'll say. Yeah. This is
what I I'll tell you exactly what I will
say. Yeah. I'm not breaking the law. I'm
not breaking the law. You're breaking
the law by harassing me every [ __ ]
day. Yeah. You can't harass someone
every day and think you can be a victim.
You can't come on here with your rat
face diagnosed autism every day and then
think you're the victim. Yeah. Yeah. And
I got you rattled. Goona. Why didn't you
come to London anyways? What? And but
guess what? He might have had me
rattled, but guess what he didn't have
me doing? He didn't own me in my own
country. He didn't have me running to
the police screaming, "I'm not a
fighter. I'm not a fighter. You're
trying to kill me. No one has ever done
that to me. Nobody has ever ever done
that to me, bro. I'm not a fighter. I'm
running to that place. That's literally
what he said when I put up posters about
him. Anyways, bro, when LT does these
posters, I'll be doing them again. So,
yeah, it's not going to work. Goona,
listen. Baldi. Baldi, mate. Baldi, why
you don't come to London, Baldi? Why
don't you come to London, Baldi? So I
can slap you around. You little monk.
Listen. Goon. Goona. Goona. Goona. Why
don't you come to London so I can slap
you around? Oh, man. What you scared of?
You're scared of finally coming off the
coming away from that keyboard? Oh,
actually, better yet, you drive, bro.
Actually, you actually you drive, don't
you, bro? [ __ ] all of this. Come to
London so I can slap you around,
bro. Um, no, bro. I wasn't even pissed
off about losing on the football, man.
To be fair.
No, didn't bother me. I I done a
football bet last night, bro. I didn't
win. Uh, didn't bother me though. Hey,
Gona. So, are you going to come to
London so I can slap you about or you
just going to keep repeating yourself?
Are you going to come to London so I can
slap you around or you going to keep
repeating yourself? Which one is it? Are
you going to just keep repeating
yourself or are you going to come to
London? Yeah. Anyways, I'm going to time
this guy out for 5 minutes because he
just keeps repeating himself and he's
not answering the question. You're not
blocked. You're timed out. Yeah,
ghosting. I I come on here today, bro,
talking about people's kids and [ __ ] cuz
I'm pissed off about women. I fell out
with my mom again, so she blocked me.
So, I don't really care, bro. I've not
seen my mom for like 3 months. So, I
don't have anything to do with any of my
family anyways. So, kind of was on his
last legs to be
fair. Yeah. I woke up today thinking
about the dating game and it was
depressing the [ __ ] out of me, bro. I
come on here, these people's winding me
up. I said, "Fuck you. I hope this
happens to your kids." Oh, she just
heard me talking about people's kids again.
And she said, "Oh, I don't um don't
contact me again." And I just said,
"Yeah, okay, fine." I blocked She
blocked me in it and I just was I was
being nasty. I told her to drop dead. I
Yeah. I told her to [ __ ] drop
dead. You know, I've heard what you've
been saying about kids again. Oh, I'm
I'm blocking you. Don't contact me
again. I told her [ __ ] off then. Drop
dead. That's what I said.
Yeah. So, what's like to have one person
care about you? You don't need um Chris
Chris, you don't need to imagine it.
It's your own
reality, you know? Uh listen, Chris, you
don't need to imagine something that's
already your own
reality. It's the life that you're
living. Do you like that one? That's
good. But um yeah, she was at the end
these women were pissing me off, bro. I
woke up today, I was just pissed off,
bro, thinking about the dating game,
Ghosted. And now like it's rigged
against men and I've got plenty of
money. I've got more money. I can do
whatever I want, bro. But I I just can't
help let it bother me that it's rigged against
men. How like they can get anything they
want whenever they want. It makes me
demotivated. It makes me just not even
want to get out of bed. It's [ __ ]
mad, bro. Like I was having nightmares
and everything. It weren't even the
gambling, but I only done £70 on two
bets, you know? It wasn't even that at
all, bro. I didn't even think about it
when I lost. I was like, "Oh, shit."
Almost. But yeah, it wasn't that, bro.
Otherwise, I would tell you it was
that. It's the whole they get everything
given to them. They get everything given
to them on a silver platter.
So, nope. It's highly against any man.
Stop being a white knight. Stop being a
white knight. It's never going to get
you laid, Buzzy. Being a s and a white
knight is never ever going to get you
laid. And no matter And you know the
madest thing about it, ghosting, is they
don't really think that I'm the problem
because if I was a woman, they would all
feel sorry for me. So at the end of the
day, they don't think you are the
problem at all. They just love defending
women for some reason. Because we all
know that if these people thought you
was a woman, they would all feel sorry
for you. Therefore, it can't be you.
Obviously, it's because you're a man.
It's a gender issue. It's not because of
you. Do you know what I'm saying, bro?
It's not because of you. So,
um, so yeah. Um, you had Christmas Day
and spend your own um, that's because I
gambled all my money, [ __ ] Yeah,
that December I gambled all my money.
Yeah, that was like four months ago. Why
are you talking about four months ago?
we're talking about now. No, it's not
even women. It's how easy they have the
dating game. It's just how easy they
have have have the dating game. It's so
unfair. It's so
So, I don't even get horny anymore to be
honest. I don't even see escorts anymore
to be honest. It's just that whole thing
is annoying when a woman is trying to
give you advice when she's the one that
can easily get a
relationship. And yeah, they can get any
man they want, but they only choose the
top 10% of men. They only choose the top
10 20% of
men. Yeah. If if listen what my whole
thing is, never judge somebody unless
you've walked a mile in their
shoes. No, I don't need to work harder.
Even if you work harder, you're still
going to get the same results. Even if
you work, and that's the thing, even if
you work on yourself, you're still going
to get nothing. Even if you work on
yourself, you're still going to get
nothing. And that's the most annoying
thing about it is that even if you work
on yourself, you're still going to get
the same, "Oh, I've got boyfriends."
You're just tormenting yourself. If you
work harder, you're just tormenting
yourself and wasting your money. So you
might as well just moan and winge
because even if you work harder, you're
it's still going to be stacked against
you. So there's there's no point but to
give up in life.
Simple. If I lived out of London and I
lived somewhere like Glasgow, then I'd be
like, okay, well, no one can compete
with me. You know what I'm saying? Then
it would be a bit different. But not like
London. That means most women would be
single. A lot of women are single. A lot
of people in their 20s are single. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no. Because a lot of
women in their in their 20s are single.
Millions of people in a happy
relationship and there's millions of
people that are single as well. There's
millions of people that have never had a
woman as well. Stop
comparing. It's not a valid argument. As
much as you want it to be an argument, it's
not the brain. Women are not the chases.
We aren't the same. Stop using the brain
dead logic of of the your standards are
so ridiculous my community stop
self-reflecting millions of mas you are
the ma stop calling yourself a
manta stop calling yourself a
m if I lived if I didn't live in London
yeah I don't think I I' I'd actually
care cuz I know that No you know what
I'm saying bro stop calling yourself a bunter
It's not good to call yourself ugly
every day, bro. It's not
nice, but there's loads of women that
are single in their 20s. There's loads
of probably mo more women are single than in
relationships would be single if they
only picked their 10. No, because a lot
of No. Well, I mean, a lot of women have
have met people before social media or
they met people through work or like
there's different reasons how people
have met, but in this day and age being
how you are in the circumstances you are
unless you're in the top 20 and even No,
the thing is even if you're good-looking
and you're a different race, you you
won't find no one, you know, even then
you won't find no one. It's it's also
your race as well.
You know, you can get somebody that
looks fully white, that's the same race
as me, same race as me, white, and he
will get very far. I will get nothing
because of my race. Even if we are well
because I look Middle Eastern. Yeah, that's another thing, bro.
That's their standards. That's literally
their standards. And they have to be
white as well. And they've got to be white, too. So,
yeah, there's nothing wrong with the way
that I look. You
know what I'm saying,
bro? So, if you look Middle Eastern as
well, that's going to hinder your
chances. They want white men. They want
white, good-looking men that are 6'
[ __ ] three, 6'5. End off. That's
their standards. That's their standards
here in London. Yeah. You
know, cuz I put somebody up as me. Same
looks, range, he was white with blue
eyes. And guess what? He got match after
match after match. Then I used a black
guy's photo. He got no matches. I I used
my my photo, right? Um, so that's it cuz
I'm I'm talking to my friend in the
army. Yeah. And I'm thinking,
what what the [ __ ] bro? How have you
got all of these matches and and he's
the same as me? Yeah. But he looks
white. I don't like He looks People
thought he was
Australian, you know? He looks
Australia. He looks
Australian. Yeah, they go for Yeah, they
go for some black guys, but not brown. I
don't I don't hate I don't hate Sean
because he's 6' three and he's not 6'3
either, mate. I'd rather be 5'10 than be
a lanky string of piss diagnosed with
autism. He's Why would I hate him when I
when I've had women that he can only
dream of getting? Hate him? What? A
lanky string of piss with no teeth? No,
thank you. Bye-bye now.
So So yeah,
bro. Yeah. And he looks like proper like white like
[ __ ] He looks proper like
um people thought he was Australian cuz
he kind of got like a tan. It's
definitely to do with your race. It
definitely is to do with your race. If
you had blue eyes, right, and then you
did have a beard like that,
bro. You would you would um you'd get
somewhere, bro. Trust me. And that's
what it is. It's your it is to do with
your race, too. It is. Cuz you can get a
guy that's the same looks looks as me.
He can look fully English, blue eyes,
and he would get further than I would ever get.
So what would that tell you then? You
know you the thing is you
people Yeah. Indian men, Chinese men,
they're [ __ ] They're [ __ ] You
know, like why do you think? Yeah.
Listen, listen. I forgot what I was
saying. Um yeah, you made me forget, but
that's what it is.
Anyways, they want to blame everything
but the woman. The thing is in in this
day and age, they want to blame anything
but the woman and they want to blame
they never want to blame something that
a man can't control. You'll notice that
in this day and age,
right? They always want to blame the man
or something that he can change rather
than what he can't change. They they
love defending women. I don't know why
they do it, but they do do it.
Yeah, I am white, but I don't look typically white.
You know, people think I'm Turkish. When
I ask them, "Where do you think I'm
from?" They say, "Fucking
Turkish." So, and then the other And
then the other races prefer white
people. So, even if they are other races. So,
yeah. Cuz you're not ugly. No. Doesn't
matter what these people in here try and
say, you're ugly. You're not ugly.
There's nothing wrong. There's nothing
wrong um with the way that you look. No
matter what these month is on here say.
So it's got to be your race. It's got to
be. How are short and not so attractive
men in relation women married? They
they're not. Um the answer is that
they're not here in London. The answer
is they're not. And if they are, that
was a time before Instagram. That was a
Facebook. Yeah, obviously I [ __ ]
do. Um so to answer your question,
they're not in London. They're not with
short unattractive men in London. You've
pulled that out of your [ __ ] ass,
mate. Not in London. It happens. No,
there is none in London. There is none
in London. And even if there was in
London, okay, let's let's just go by
your Let's just go by um let's just go
your Let's just go by your logic. So,
even if there was, even if there was,
they could have got lucky. They might
have got lucky once. They might have met
through university. Okay. And and your point
is so I don't have a bedsit. I'm not in
a bedsit like you. So, okay. So, let's
just say that was the case with some
people. I mean, most of the time when I
see a woman, she's with a man taller
than him. So, I don't know where you've
got this. Women go for shorter guys
because literally 90% of women, 95% of
women are with a guy that's taller than
them. You're talking out your ass, mate.
And you're just trying to compare again.
What is it with you comparing and
comparing and comparing and comparing
comparing? I'm 510. Bye-bye
now. You know, bye-bye now. Bye-bye
now. Oh, do you feel sorry for
Laney? How do guys have girlfriends? I
just answered your question. I just
question. Go and ask them. Don't ask me.
Go and ask them. Again, you're trying to compare, you
know. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no. They want people that are 6
foot and above. Yeah. Anyways, we're
going round and round and round around
in circles. Anyways, I'm done with this
conversation, bro. We're going round and
round and round. Listen, the only way I
can explain this to you, well, a lot of
you people a lot older than me, go out
and approach women and tell me what
happens. That's the only thing I can say
to you because we're going back and
forth and back and forth and back and
forth, you know? Go out, approach women,
and tell me what happens. That's the
only way you're ever going to know, you
know? Tell me exactly. It could be
anywhere, you know? So instead of all of
this [ __ ] stupid comparing people to
other people that's just completely
irrelevant and has nothing to do with
anything, go at yourself. Go out
approaching. Go on a dating app and tell
me how you get on.
Simple. I'm not doing good, man. I woke
up thinking of the dating game again and
how women can get whatever they want
when they want and they don't need to
lift the finger. And I fell out with my
bum as well.
So I fell out with my mom.
yeah, had better days, eh? Had better
days. Yeah, I woke up thinking about
that. Yeah, but I've been thinking about
it a lot
recently. Yeah. Well, I've got loads of
money, Joe, and I'm still
single. Oh, do you? Good for him. That's
nice for you. Good uh good for him, bro.
Good for him. I know a guy around the
corner who um cleans his garden every
day. Yeah, he cleans his garden. He
works for the council. Good. Good for
him. Do you want a
medal? But the thing is is
that these people are not you, which is
what I'm trying to explain. Some people
are made for no one.
Oh, he's always jealous, mate. Jealous
that I'm better looking than him.
Jealous that I've had more women than
him. Jealous I've got more money than
him. Well, I still ain't got this
passport yet, but
yeah, you know, and then you you give
your opinion. I don't understand. You
come online, you give your opinion, and
all these people are calling you ugly
when you're better looking than them.
So, it's like, what the [ __ ] bro? It's
weird. It's crazy as [ __ ] Yeah. But
yeah. Yeah. It pissed me off, bro, that
like the dating game is rigged against
men. Well, I've already proven this
because I I put up a dating profile as a
woman and I got 5,000 likes. I put up
Morgan's photos, all filtered. filtered
photos, right? Three filtered
photos, like selfies, and I got 5,000
likes in less than an
hour. You be any man, you ain't getting not even
0.00001% of that. But they claim that
it's not rigged against men. They claim
that it's not rigged against men when
even though you've seen it with your own
eyes, they will still bareface lie to
you and say, "Oh, it's not easy for women."
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. Yeah, of course you have it, bro.
Course you have
it. [ __ ] the football, bro. You I'm
telling you straight that I've seen it
with my own
eyes. I've also seen a woman approach a
guy with my own
eyes and they have it easier. But then
when you moan about it, ghosting, you're
told you're an incel, bro. Even if you
try to do anything about it, you're
still not going to get anywhere. That's
being real. Do you want me to lie and
[ __ ] you? Like, I don't understand,
bro. It's [ __ ] up. Yeah.
They don't have a bad word to say about
women. So you coming to London anyways,
GA? Six years. I thought it was five
years yesterday. Make up your [ __ ]
mind. So you're not coming to London then?
No. So you're not coming to London to
get your [ __ ] to to to get slapped about?
No. I mean, Ghost, what what like let's
just think about it right now. Yeah.
[ __ ] all of this moaning. [ __ ] all of
this winging. Yeah. What what's the
solution? Bye-bye. How you get another
time out? I mean, Ghost, what's what's
the actual solution now? Where where
would you go from here? Like, [ __ ] the
ranting. [ __ ] what we've
said. Where would you go from here?
Because you go out, you you just see the
same women with the same attitude
problems. So, you can't go out and you
try. So, I mean, you have to deal with
these people with attitude
problems, but that's completely fine.
Uh, but yeah.
You know, you have to deal with the same
women with the same attitude problems.
That's not an option, lad. You know,
it's like wherever you go, women have
got the same attitude. You say, you see
the same [ __ ] men, same attitude,
same MPCs. Do you know what I'm saying, bro?
Like, they don't determine my happiness,
but it's annoying how they can get sex
whenever they want. I went out and had
fun on Friday, bro. I just done some
appro approaches for the fun of it and
it was pissing me off. And it was
pissing me off, lad. It was pissing me
off. And I didn't even go out for that,
bro. I just wanted to use my passport
one last time,
lad. But I thought, "Fuck it." It lad, you
know, they have life on easy
mode. That's something that I will take
to the grave with me that they literally
have life on easy mode. They can get
whatever they want, whenever they want.
Think about that, bro. Just think about
that. And you have to
suffer. They can get sex whenever they
want. They can get sex whenever they
want. They can get relationships whenever they
want. I mean, maybe I word that wrong.
They can get sex whenever they want.
They can get relationships whenever they
want. Even though they claim that all of
the men they meet just want sex when
that doesn't ring right. There's no
way. No, no, no. My My logic is not
defeated because I've made a dating
profile as a woman and I got 5,000
likes, but women say they can't find anyone um
ghosting. Women say they can't find
anyone. They can't find anyone
apparently. I spent last Christmas
without them. No, I don't give a [ __ ]
about them. I hate them. No, bro.
No, I hate them,
bro. I spent last I spent last Christmas
by myself eating a curry, so why would I
care about this
year? See, they want to judge you for
things that you said about women and and
things that you said about kids. But
these people have not walked a mile in your
shoes. So, at the end of the
day, these people have not walked a mile
in your shoes. Because if anyone if
anyone walked a mile in your shoes, they
would have ended up killing someone by
now. They would have ended up in prison
or they would have ended up killing
someone by now. So, in a way, bro, you
I'm I'm surprised I
haven't. They didn't block me and disown
me. I disowned
them. Nah, bro. Born alone, [ __ ] die
alone. She didn't [ __ ] disown me,
bro. You know, she didn't disown me. I
used to speak to her every day apart
from today. [ __ ] her so you can [ __ ] off
and die. I don't care about her. Simple.
Yeah. I don't need support, bro. I've
been doing it by myself now for 4 months again. I'm
good. Cuz you realize the the thing is
in life, Ghost is your family, they
don't they don't really love you,
bro. You understand?
They don't like you can't trust anyone.
There's nobody in this world that loves
you unconditionally. Not even your
family, bro. Trust me. Trust me. Like
that. You know, I I They don't know.
They do not. Bro, listen. I spent
Christmas by myself with £25 to my
name. Sort it out,
bro. Sort it out, bro. £25 on Christmas
Day to my name. I had to eat a curry.
Yeah, stop talking
[ __ ] And yeah, bro. And I think that is
was like, I don't care about them, bro. [ __ ] them,
bro. I went back there twice anyways. I
don't care. [ __ ] her,
bro. I don't like none of them.
It's depressing how a woman can get
whatever she wants, whenever she wants.
It's [ __ ] mad, isn't
it? Can get sex whenever she wants, can
get dick whenever she wants. Can never
be lonely. [ __ ] hell. Imagine some of
them were incel, bro. Could you
imagine, you know? It's
crazy. Yeah. I don't care.
I don't give a
[ __ ] I don't give a
[ __ ] Now, I put enough approaching
videos on my channel, Ghost, and I'm
sure you've seen them. Oh, I've got a
boyfriend. I've got a boyfriend. I've
boyfriend. Yeah, we have to put all this
work in and get nothing. And this is
what I was saying to Ant-Man as well two
days ago. I wouldn't mind it if you
actually got something out of it. Like,
no, no, no. I wouldn't mind actually
working hard and actually having to put
the effort in if you actually was to get
something out of it. Then I'd be like,
uh, okay. Well, life's unfair, you know.
But you don't you don't literally, bro,
it is it is Wednesday today. Yeah, very
much. I could literally go out today
drinking and I would get exactly the
same [ __ ] I would get exactly the same
Boyfriends, [ __ ] that don't exist.
Um, I do have all the answers when it
comes to dating. I do have all the
answers. I do have all the
answers. There's nothing wrong or
there's nothing wrong or there's nothing
right about what I'm doing. People don't
like the approaching videos.
And that's another thing is that you
couldn't even get with a woman. [Music]
So why would you want to be alive in a
in in a day and age where it's really against
you? No, I shouldn't listen to them
because I don't compare myself to
others. I shouldn't listen to them
because just because they've got into
relationships, it doesn't mean you are
going to. It doesn't mean you are going
to. Okay, I'll give you an example,
right? Let me go up to this couple on
the street. Um, so how did you two meet?
We met on a dating app. You go on a date
and app it doesn't work for you. Nope.
Okay, bro. And and your point is it's
not brain damage. It's real life. It's
real life, mate. Just because the thing
is with with meeting people in life
ghosting, some people get lucky and some
people don't get
lucky. You know what I'm saying,
lad? Do you know what I'm saying?
So just because other people have that
the world does not work like that. The
world literally does not work like that.
You can't compare yourself to others. It
doesn't. The life the world does not
work like that. Unfortunately, I wish it
did, but it
doesn't. You know, there's not someone
for everyone. That's [ __ ]
Especially in this day and age. It's [ __ ]
Because say a couple said that they met
on a dating app like I just said and
then you go on a dating app and it
doesn't work. So what is is that you are
the problem because it never worked for
you when what can you do? Pull up
pictures, you know, it doesn't make
sense, you know, and and and there's
loads of things that go against you as
well. That's the way I see
it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No one cares.
hideous. Nobody cares. You're not going
to trigger me. So, you writing those
things. Um, no one cares. Sean's got a
girlfriend. Yes. And he sits on YouTube
all day stalking me because he doesn't
even get to [ __ ] her cuz he's still a
virgin. Nobody cares. It's not triggering
anyone. We're talking about serious
convos here. You're not going to trigger
me, so stop it. It's boring now. We've
heard it a million times. It's boring
now. You know, I just gave you an
example of how something does not work
for everyone and you're talking about
other people that no one cares about. You
know, why the [ __ ] would I
be? It's not that they don't find you
attractive. It's because of your
race. It's because of your race, you
know. Yeah. Good for you, bro. You
already said that. Yeah. Good for you.
You're not going to trigger me, so stop it. So
yeah, that's it,
lad. Yeah. Well, they didn't meet on
dating apps, mate. I'll tell you that
for nothing. They didn't meet on dating apps.
Get on data apps.
Yeah. Today and and the show I told you
so. Yeah. Good for you, bro. This is the
first time you've said this. I don't
care. Yeah. Okay. Good for you, bro. Say
it again. I'm going to block you. Stop repeating yourself.
Nobody cares. You've said this about
three times now. Stop repeating
yourself. You're not going to trigger
me. I'm not Monty Man and I'm not Timmy. Stop repeating yourself. You
know, but like how can they say that
you're not attractive, Chris, when I'm
objectively above average? I'm I'm
objectively above average looking. So,
how can it be simply that they don't
find you attractive when you're
objectively above average looking? And
I'm not going to have a conversation
about my looks, whether I'm this,
whether I'm that. I know that I'm I'm
decent looking when I'm groomed. So, the
only thing it could come down to is your
race. The only thing it could come down
to is is your
race. That's the only
thing. That is the I'm looking at myself
in the mirror now. Look at them eyes.
Look at that beard. There's nothing
wrong with the way that you look. But
look, you've got a beard. So, I mean, it
the only thing it could be is your race.
And And I was bring And I was bringing
this up before even Thingy um put it
out. Uh Mon before Thingy put it out. Um
Ben. Yeah. And I've just told you,
right? And I've just told you that I'm
objectively above average looking. And
I've just told you, right, that I can't
get any matches. And I've just told you as well.
Yeah. I've just told you as
well. Yeah. So, we've told each
other. So, yeah.
What's the time? 11.
Yeah. Nothing wrong with the way I
look. No, that means that they don't.
No, no, no, no,
no. Okay, bro. I'm ugly, Chris. I'm the
ugliest [ __ ] going. I'm the ugliest
bastard going who's unattractive. Happy.
Is that what you want to hear or? Yeah,
bro. I'm I'm the most ugliest [ __ ]
going. Is I don't know what you want me
to tell you, bro. I don't know what you
want me to tell
you. Ugliest [ __ ] going, bro. I'm super
super duper ugly. I know, man. It sucks,
isn't it? Yeah. I'm very, very, very,
ugly. I mean, I don't know what else you
want to hear, you
know? Yeah. Yeah. I'm ugly, bro. Yeah, ugly.
Very very ugly,
bro. I know. It sucks, isn't
it? Yeah, I know, man. I'm very ugly. It sucks.
I'm the ugliest [ __ ] going in the
world. Looking at myself, there's
nothing wrong with the way that you
look. Normal eyes, normal beard, hair
could do with a wash. There's literally
nothing wrong with the way that you
look. My eyes are almost black to be
fair. There's nothing wrong with the way
that you look at all at all. At all at
all. I'm looking at myself. Yeah, I'm
the ugliest kind of
going. That's super dry
t-shirt. I meet a woman and ditched me
within days. Uh, what women have I met
have ditched me within dates? Within
days? Uh, what are you talking about?
What people that went back to their
country more than three times? Yeah,
they ditched me to go back to their country.
Yeah, but I think really we need to stop
arguing about this because it's like I
know I'm right. No matter what anyone
tells me, I know how I'm right because
of my experiences with this, which is un
which is literally impossible to to get
people to understand. Like, I know that
I'm right. As delusional as that sounds,
if you know you're right, if you know
you're right, stop
arguing. Which we obviously, but that's
not the issue that that that it is. It's
the issue that women can get who they
want when they want. That's the thing that annoys
me the way that you
look. They're not very unique narrow
because you would have the same
experiences if you went out approaching.
you would have the same experiences just
like everyone else gets the same
experiences cuz I watch this guy in
London, he does approaches. I watch
people out in London and they do
approaches and they get exactly the same
thing as I get. They get exactly the
same thing as I get. They're nothing to
do with me. They still get, oh, I've got
a boyfriend. They get exactly the same
[ __ ] We can't all be wrong. There's no
way. Like these people are nothing to do
with YouTube and they get exactly the
same [ __ ] Now, if they weren't getting
exactly the same [ __ ] I'd be like,
"Hold on a minute. There's something
going on here." You know, there's
something seriously wrong here. But
every single time I watch them, they get
exactly the same [ __ ] They they have
boyfriends, all they get exactly the same [ __ ] Bye-bye.
No, Sean, but it makes you jealous that
I've been with an American that you
can't get out your head. To answer your
question, no, but it makes you jealous
the fact that I've been with an American
that you can't get out of your head.
That makes you jealous. How's that one
for you? All the time when I was your
age, I went on Hinge. Yeah, I've been on
Hinge. I didn't get any matches.
Yeah, I didn't get any
matches. How else can you get a woman? You
can't. How else can you get a woman? You
can't. There is no other
way. There is There is no other way. So
yeah, there's nothing wrong with the way
that I look. I look completely normal.
The [ __ ] bro? So you can't use that as
an excuse. It's got to be your race.
It's got to be your race. It has to be,
bro. There's nothing wrong with the way
that you look. There's nothing wrong
with the way that you
look. Pretty much.
Yeah. And it's not even that. I don't
even want a woman. It's not even about
that. It's I'm sick of them having
everything given to them on a [ __ ] silver [ __ ]
spoon. You met your wife on hinge. Oh,
did you? And how long ago was that?
Gorda. Ga, you're a bold fat ugly old
man. Don't talk about my looks. I'm
better looking than you will ever
be. You're a fat ugly old man. [ __ ] my
eyes. You're a fat ugly old man. You're
ugly from [ __ ] head to [ __ ] toe.
You fat ugly old man. I'm a million
times better looking than you will ever
be. I'm a million times better looking
than you will ever be, lad. Never mind
my [ __ ] eyes, son. I'm not seeing
you, bro. You've said it yourself.
You're fat and bold. It's come out your
own mouth. It's come out your own mouth
that you're fat and
bold. It's come out your own mouth.
Yeah. The facts is that I'm better
looking than you will ever be. Yeah. But
the fact is I'm better looking than you.
That's a fact. And you even admitted
that you're [ __ ] fat and bald. You've admitted it
yourself. You [ __ ] idiot.
You've admitted it
yourself. Yeah. Good. Yeah. Nice try,
Gona. Gona, is that supposed to make me
insecure about my
looks? Is that supposed to make me
insecure about my looks, bro? Cuz you're
doing a very bad job about it. You're
doing a very You're doing a very You're
very You're very
um You're doing a very bad job of it,
lad. Is this supposed to make me be
insecure or something? Cuz you're not
doing a very good job. See, the thing
is, Gona, I can show my face, you know?
I can show my face. You can't show your
face. That's the difference. So, who's
the ugly one?
Bro, you're doing a very bad job. Elaine
destroyed me. Oh, really? Yeah. Okay,
bro. Do you do anything by
repeating? I just [ __ ] I just hate
him. I just hate them. I hate them. I
hate women. I hate how they have
everything given to them as well. I [ __ ] hate
them. I [ __ ] hate them.
Yeah. Anyways, I'm good. I'll be back later.