Sorry about that. I had to reply to this
[ __ ] stupid Timmy Eldridge. Any
self-reflecting followers? [ __ ] hell.
Stat on YouTube self-projecting because
their lives are [ __ ] It's [ __ ] It's
actually madness, isn't it?
Self-reflecting 40, 50y olds because
their lives are [ __ ] in the pits and
they try to tell you that you're these
things that they are themselves skint
fat ugly bastard virgins. [ __ ] hell,
bro. You just know that these people
just do their bollocks in like all the [ __ ] time.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] trying to call me
out. What the [ __ ] bro?
Listen, listen, listen, listen. I'm
doing a reply to this [ __ ] Yeah.
Firstly, Yeah. Timmy, you're not going
to end up anywhere. I've I've been to
your city last month and you didn't come
out. You know this. This is exactly what
I mean with this disabled community.
Yeah. Come on my street with money,
Mike. I will pay I will literally pay
for your train fair. I will literally
pay for your train fair. Yeah. Yeah.
Please do. Yeah. Please do.
Please do, man. Yeah. Come.
Yeah. Yeah, bro. Yeah. It doesn't
matter. Same with him. You, Ricky
Milling, all of you people, you can come
to London. I'll pay all of your train
fairs. All of you fat, ugly, 40-year-old
virgins that ain't got a life. I got
some fat 40-year-old virgin Nicolo
trying to tell me, "Oh, I'm the skid one
that's got no job and I've got no
girlfriend. Already had a girlfriend.
Already had more women than you. The
same women that you've wanked over." I
swear they're the same self-reflecting
fat, ugly 50year-olds that ain't got a
life. I swear it's the same for our people.
I swear it's the same 40-year-old angry
skint gamblers that ain't got a life
doing this. I I Bro, I swear it is. It's
the same four people in it. It's got to
be sat at home lonely, never seen a
woman naked, ain't got no money, sat
there skinn as [ __ ] waiting for
their£300 a month. Bro, I swear to God,
they they've got a they've got a degree
in talking about themselves. Like, they
actually have a degree in it. So, do you
know what? Yeah. To be honest with you,
they're not even that [ __ ] stupid.
They're [ __ ] fat, ugly, 50-year-old
skint little losers, bully victims
trying to talk about someone half their
[ __ ] age. These old wrinkly fat skintos
trying to speak about somebody half
their [ __ ] age. What the actual [ __ ]
And then you got some [ __ ] fat
[ __ ] in [ __ ] Birmingham, right?
trying to [ __ ] say, "Oh, oh, you you
you can come to Birmingham. I already
went to Birmingham last month and you
didn't come out, you [ __ ] when you
was on the chat. We don't waste our time
on you people anymore. If you want to
come to London, you can come to London
today. I'll meet you anywhere."
You know, you can even go on that same
street if you want and I'll smash you
both up. Simple. Stop being a keyboard
warrior. This is exactly what I mean,
Grezy. Yeah. Even when you go to these
people's cities, right, and they don't
show up, they just come and pretend
they've won. This is this is exactly why
I don't waste my time on them anymore.
This is why I let them self-reflect
their skiddness. I let them keep talking
about themselves every day, cuz it makes
themselves feel better, you know? I
don't This is why I don't waste my time
on them. these little 40-year-old
[ __ ] low lives trying to tell me I'm
approaching [ __ ] 30 when they're in
their 50s all alone sat on YouTube ain't
got a job never had a [ __ ] job sat
there skin obsessed with other people
that they don't even know
what the [ __ ] they're trying to talk
about me are you [ __ ] mad like I said it's jealousy
just like what Ronald Pump said it's
jealousy you're better looking than them
you got a better life than them and it
kills them they'll never leave you alone
jealousy so Right.
Jealous [ __ ] Mate, you don't have all
of these [ __ ] people obsessed with
you every day because you're ugly and
you're skint. Come on. Let's Let's be
real about this now, bro. Let's be so so
real about this. You do not have fat,
ugly old men, right, obsessing over you
every second of every day cuz you're the
ugly skinned one. Do you understand, bro?
You That's not how it is. That's not how
it makes sense. Do you understand? It's
it's the reverse. Do you understand,
bro? It's the reverse.
Yeah. You are my nons. Bye-bye. Now,
I'm going to go on his live stream. One second.
One second. I'm going to go on that live
stream. Hold on. [Laughter]
See what I mean, bro?
See what I [ __ ] mean?
He would never beat anyone. He's a
keyboard warrior. There you go. I've
just spoke about his sister and her
kids. You know,
come to London Fair. It's only an hour
and 20 minutes.
It's only an hour and 20 minutes. Simple.
It's only an hour and 20 minutes. What
you waiting for? Oh, [ __ ]
I'm not even friends with money, but
[ __ ] hell. I was in Birmingham last
month. We called you out. You didn't
come out. Shut the [ __ ] up, you stupid
idiot. You know, you
2 years old, mate. Listen one sec. Let
me come back.
[ __ ] absolute calam reflectors.
for 30 and never had a girlfriend. I've
had a girlfriend, mate. You people in
your [ __ ] 40s and you've never even
seen a woman naked?
Fun fact. Hyperlinks, right? Fun fact.
Hyperlinks, right? Never been in a
relationship, bro. What do you actually
think that's a skit? if I actually had
never been in a relationship. These
people in their 40s, they they've never
even seen a woman naked for [ __ ] sake.
They've never had a job in their life.
They're sat on [ __ ] YouTube fat, ugly
old farts, calling people what they are
every day, skin. You know what I'm
saying? Like, what the [ __ ] man? What
in the actual [ __ ]
[ __ ] a madness, bro.
Yeah, man. One second. Let me [ __ ]