Yep.
I can't be bothered, bro. [ __ ]
Oh, Jesus Christ. [ __ ] me. Yeah,
I did say that was the end of that
tonight. So, I did see your reply, but
I'm wasting my time with you.
Yeah, I'm not responding anymore. So,
Someone's message me. Speaking of friends, [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I I did see your response though,
but I'm not replying to you anymore.
It's clear that you've got some sort of fetish um
for a young man to keep replying to you
or some weirdness because you generally
can't be that stupid.
cuz you Yeah. I'm not I'm not even
replying anymore. I'm not answering any
of your questions anymore. I mean,
you've literally just said it yourself.
I didn't have 12 grand. Exactly. So, you
lost. But that's the end of that. You
lost the money game. And that's that.
I can't be bothered anymore.
Yeah, one second.
Yeah, I'm not arguing with you, Monty.
Anyways, I'll let you up, but I'm not
arguing with you.
One second. I can't be asked for this [ __ ] anymore.
I can't be bothered with this [ __ ]
anymore on this, bro. Community
It's just weird.
>> But you get like you get addicted to
their stupidity at the end of the day.
These people [ __ ] idiot.
Absolute idiots. That's what you all are, idiots.
>> What you crying about?
>> No, I'm just talking about these little mongos.
>> What? What you about? How they just like
have no life? Like just self projecting
every day. It's sad.
>> Yeah, they do like 47 every single day.
>> Yeah, but I don't know why they do it.
What they actually get out of doing it.
They get out of watching you and make a
tit of yourself.
>> They've been making a tit of themselves
their whole life.
>> Yeah. But they also But also,
>> you know what I'm saying?
>> So, you know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Do you remember Jane yesterday?
What? Have you been texting her? Have you?
>> No, she emailed me and I just [ __ ]
ignored it. She's a game player.
>> You fancy?
>> Nah, she fancies me.
>> Why don't you get rid of it then?
>> Nah. Why? Did you see what I sent you?
And now and you're going to tell me I'm
the obsessed one. >> Yeah.
>> No. What did he send me? Virgin boy. You
saw it, didn't you? Huh?
I'm going to make myself a big nose.
You have got a big nose.
>> No, just seen it in chain. I got a big nose.
>> Yeah. 17 minutes.
>> You see what I mean? That's They're
obsessed with me. I don't think you get
it. They're obsessed with me.
>> Yeah, I know. I catch a bit. Yeah. >> Yeah.
What's this guy saying? [ __ ] shocking. [Laughter]
Okay, let's see if this curry place is
open. I'm starving, man.
This person wants to go for a beer with me.
[ __ ] starving, man.
Going out and about making friends and [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm going to get a courier. I'm
going to get a curry. He thinks. Yo,
>> why do you always talk about the [ __ ]
longlegged Peter piss anyway?
>> I know, bro. He's the one that
every single day by saying, "Oh, Mong is
his friend." And that's basically
talking about him. That's basically
bringing him up every time.
>> Yeah, look at his channel on me.
>> Yeah, but don't you think he's pretty
pathetic? You're crying at him doing
videos of you. You're basically making
response videos back of him. He's going
back and forth. One of you are going to
have to give. Are you going to give or
is he going to give? Meaning, who's
going to stop talking about him? Are you
going to stop talking about him bringing him?
>> Yeah, I I am. But he's not going to stop either way.
>> Do it then and then to look like the
offess is freaky is. But you doing it
included is making you look like more of a freak.
>> It's not just him that does it, Marty.
It's a few of these people that do this.
>> Yeah, even they're just freaks. They
want you to rage. They want you to
shout. They want you to say all the [ __ ]
you say on here. That's what they want
you to do. What do you think? They want
you for content to go up on their
channels to make a chat off yourself.
What do you think they want you for?
You're the content PJ.
>> They're just weirdos.
>> That's all they want they want you for.
That's why they bring all this [ __ ] up.
They won't put up what they saying to
you to get you like that.
>> They just put you up there like that.
>> But stop bringing long legs up like it's your boyfriend.
>> Yeah. Okay. Literally stop saying this
one my mate and all that. Stop saying I
introduce you to him because I didn't
introducing you to someone saying hey PJ
this is the pedophile call [ __ ] long
legs. Yeah there you go. Yeah I didn't
do any of that
>> madness isn't it?
>> At the end of the day if he got caught
the dad's going prison anyways.
>> Yeah. What you had to do is bring up all
the underra kids just being with [ __ ]
nons. [ __ ] off.
>> No, don't let him up. He kicks everyone.
>> He kicks everybody.
>> If these people have got anything to
say. Hey, Monty. Yeah, Triple H can come
in. He's cool.
>> But yeah,
>> you all right?
>> I know.
What are you up to?
>> [ __ ] all, bro. I'm going to go Chinese
in a bit.
>> I'm going to have an Indian, I think.
>> What you getting?
>> Lamb ta curry.
>> You had Chinese yesterday, didn't you? >> Yeah.
>> See, Monty, it's okay, you know, letting
people up that can actually have a
conversation. But [ __ ]
>> when you go on about [ __ ] pedo long
legs over and over again, he he's going
this nothing giving. What's actually
giving is you and him going back and
forth at each other. That's it.
>> What's going on with you? What you get?
What are you getting for the
>> Sh making videos of PG and PG because PJ
keeps talking about Sh and bringing them
up on every [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but um the trips. What are you
getting from the Chinese?
>> Salt and pepper chicken. Um
salt and pepper chips and probably
>> See, look at these pedophiles, man. Oh
my god. I'm not even going to tell you what account
>> you know what this account's called. See
the pedos on here, man. >> [ __ ] It
>> doesn't matter what they do. You're
reacting to them. Just leave them.
>> Yeah, but Yeah, but they're bringing up
your kid saying about >> rap.
Yeah, leave them to it. Leave them to
it. Let them talk about that [ __ ] Don't
bring Don't react to it. You don't do
Like just leave them to it. You react to
that. That That's what they want you to
do. They want you to react to just kick them, man.
>> Yeah, I have kicked them. I've not let
them up. I have kicked them. They're
trying to come in the hangouts.
>> I'm not reacting to it anymore because
you react to it. They're just going to
put you up on something like what you
thought they done would be a pot must
bust. What I call kids
do though, man. They've got no life, have they?
>> No, they are. They
>> You react to him, PJ all. You want Yeah, you can.
>> I'm not reacting to these people
anymore. I'm not arguing these people no
>> [ __ ] them.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Keep coming. Keep coming.
Keep coming on here with your P
accounts. No one cares.
Um, nothing, man. Just been chilling,
bro. I went for a walk and then Yeah.
>> I've got two fake, mate. >> Really?
>> [ __ ] kill an eye.
>> Take some cocoon more.
>> I've took an approxin. I've took you
offenders, but he hasn't done that.
>> Yeah, I think you're right. Ignore these
people in it. Oh, don't kick them. Let
people [ __ ] keep them up just to show
how embarrassing they are. Don't kick the comments.
>> Don't get the comments. See if the
comments up and let them embarrass
yourself with the comment.
>> What? You don't like Indian, do you?
>> I'm not a big lover. No. No. >> Really?
>> No, I'm not about Indian.
>> Well, you don't like
No, not really. No, no, I like Chinese me, man.
>> Yeah, I I like the chicken balls from
the Chinese. They're so nice, man.
>> Yeah, I sometimes get chicken bottles.
Yeah, but I had
>> They're so yummy, isn't it? They're
filling as well.
>> Yeah, they are. Yeah, they hardly.
>> When I come to Newcastle next week, we
can we can go Nando trips before getting
on the Guinness.
>> You've got chicken balls, don't you, Pet? >> What?
>> You've got chicken balls, don't you? We
could do a little bet on the football
>> and get on the gin eye.
>> Yeah. And the baby. I can't believe
you've never had a baby Guinness. What
the [ __ ] You don't know what you're missing.
>> No. What I thought a baby Guinness was
literally Guinness put in the shot glass.
>> It is. It's a baby. Yeah, but it doesn't
taste the same as Guinness. It tastes
like It's nice, bro.
>> It's It's a shot of Guinness. What?
Monty had it. It was nice, isn't it?
>> Yeah. It tastes like piss water.
>> No, it doesn't.
>> Horrible. No, it [ __ ] does. No, it doesn't.
>> And it tastes like coffee.
>> It tastes like chocolate. Yeah, like a
bit like coffee. It's nice. You'll like
it. I think you'll like it.
>> It's like a coffee chocolatey thing. Like
>> like a beer less.
Yeah. The cream is creamy, but it's kind
of a coffee kind of scent to it.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> What's the What's What's the biggest
you've won on a football bet? [ __ ]
Not [ __ ] not loads. Like I think 40
co the most I've ever won. I think um
about 500 normal 500 quid the more I
think. No about Yeah, just just shy of
500 quid. I've never like
>> Yeah. What was it from? Was it from like a five?
>> No, like 20 I normally do that. I put
the 20 20 quid on um four teams normally
and I put like both teams score like
six, seven teams on. Yeah, that that's
hard to that's hard to cut. Yeah, but
>> Yeah, you're the most hard one. PGM
footballish [ __ ] all.
>> Yeah, you used to be bad. You used to be
bad on that roulette though, didn't you? Triple.
>> Yeah, I used to be wild. I used to put I
used to get paid for I put on me wages, didn't me?
>> Funny, isn't it?
>> Apologized to that anyway. PJ, >> huh?
>> Apologize to Natalie.
>> She should apologize to me. No, no. She
had done nothing to you that day. She
would just done nothing except you being
quiet and you just called you rugged on
your channel. You weren't even up on
your channel. She said nothing to her or nothing.
>> You find it funny, is it, Triple?
>> The full community is just [ __ ]
stupid, isn't it? Really? Just when you
>> are you are you back with your parents
now, Triple? I >> really
>> for the time being I
>> Why did Yeah, but why did you break up
though? That's mad, isn't it?
>> I couldn't be I couldn't be asking it no more, fella.
>> What? Like you just wanted to meet
someone else or you just wanted to be single?
>> Trying to be single. You enjoy the pub
life a lot, mate.
>> The what? The pub life. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. We should I'm going I'm going to
come next Saturday. You better meet me.
>> I will. But it'll be next Saturday. Like
I think I've got um got out on this.
is up on the bum. PG
>> if you come it'll have to be the end of
the month. Really? Like
>> on a Saturday? Yeah.
>> All right.
>> Who's coming up then?
>> I should do the Friday and Saturday to
be fair. I'll try and do the Friday and the Saturday. >> Yeah.
>> Probably be better, would it?
>> Yeah. My woman, you you done all right,
didn't you, when you last came?
>> Yeah, they're too stuck up in London,
man. It seems easier in Newcastle, huh?
I thought you would have been coming up PJ me.
>> Why Triple H? Why do you think they're
less stuck up in Newcastle? Isn't weird, isn't it?
>> Haven't you noticed that?
>> Full of slags in there.
>> Yeah, London. They're too stuck up, man.
>> Why don't you go Plymouth, P? Yeah,
Plymouth is full of slags.
>> No, it's too far. Plymouth.
>> Plymouth's [ __ ] ages away from me. Like Plymouth.
>> Yeah, it's way far from you. It's like hours.
>> It's far away from me as well. So, it's
even about 3 hours from us, isn't it? >> London 2 hours.
>> Yeah, but the train is like 3 hours and 20.
>> What? Back to London.
>> You ain't You ain't You ain't been You
still ain't been Scotland yet. Triple H.
>> No, Scotland.
>> It's only an hour and like 20 for you.
You should You should go out there for a
night out. You like it?
>> Have you been Birmingham?
>> No. No.
>> I think like I've been liber's
all right. It's not bad. Go out at night
out clubbing and that. It's not that bad.
>> You should go for a pint. Jamie, you
should go for a pint with Timmy.
>> [ __ ] off. I'm battering myself.
>> Have you ever seen Timmy like in
Birmingham or not?
>> No. Yeah, I've met a man for a fight
before even remember.
>> Yeah, remember that. I'm just saying
like have you just do you like do you
not see him like like around?
>> No, I'm scared of Timmy in it. I'm scared.
>> Remember the fight in the bus station?
>> I think I think them two are a pair of
[ __ ] if you ask me.
>> Yeah, me and Timmy are best friends. Steve D.
>> you you give me a nod legs.
>> Well, see what I mean again.
Why do you do that Pia? Why do you bring
Sean up like he's some kind of you fork
every conversation up with that guy?
>> When you bring him up, do you know I'm
most like you give me the shivers with
his name. Just his name.
>> I just get shivers with his name. He's a
[ __ ] weird one.
And it makes me shiver knowing you've met him.
>> I met him through you.
>> You did meet him through me. Like I said,
>> is that Triple H? Is that your favorite
wrestler or something?
>> What? No. I don't know why you made that
name or I just made up.
>> That's funny, isn't it?
>> Hey, you should [ __ ] that J. >> Huh?
>> Bang that J. Nah, she's a game player.
>> Yeah. Do you know what? [ __ ] PJ.
Everyone wants actually try and meet PJ
or try getting with PJ again.
So why don't you just meet her?
>> Yeah. Why don't YouTube? >> Huh?
>> Go for it. Go for it. Get a number. Go
for it. You order this once. Look at me.
I'm I'm at my
I'm happily happily married mate now to that >> what
>> I'm happily married
>> I'm a [ __ ] mar that man I want to be
able to run off one day
>> trip why do you find this community funny
>> that is the one to marry I am of course
I'm going to marry that
Why do you find this community funny?
>> Full of [ __ ] idiots in it, right?
They're just full of just just
full of mongos. PJ
just sad people have gotten out in it.
That's like that's what they're doing.
[ __ ] come on. I come on for a laugh,
mate. Like I think it's all a laugh,
>> I I don't think it's a laugh. Do you on here?
Get I need that Tim Eldridge.
>> I need that Tim Elder John.
>> So, Triple Triple H, do you like miss
like not getting sex anymore or uh
>> I'm not asking, mate.
>> Yeah, you probably have a wanker every
morning. Is it?
>> Nah. No, I uh I don't um I don't really
miss it to be honest. just I've never
had an IC [ __ ] never bothe
his mom comes upstairs and start
shouting his mom mom still wanking
>> well you've never what you've never
really been asked about sex
>> I'm not really bothered with it
>> that's good it
>> no PJ them people who's had sex on
people who get sex they're not really
bothered about sex them people who don't
really get Sex like yourself
self-reflected on that.
>> No, I've had sex multiple times. I've
proved I've had sex.
>> I don't care when you I think it's as
you get older as well. Is it Triple? You
was a holy beast when you was younger. Is it?
>> I don't know because I think it gets
worse when you get older. I think you
almost started getting worse when you're
a man to be honest.
>> I don't care as much anymore.
>> [ __ ] off. >> What
>> did you say? Is he?
>> Maybe, maybe not.
>> Which one? There's two, isn't he? This
American is here. He's the British, is he?
>> That's That's funny, isn't it? Yeah. You
always had your eye on Izzy, in it, Triple H.
>> Izzy, mom.
>> Somebody said to me, somebody Hey, hey,
Monty, I can make you laugh. Yeah. One
of these accounts said to me, "Did you
touch Isabelly's boobies?"
No touch them right now.
I was speaking to this woman on Tinder.
Triple H. Yeah. She said she'd [ __ ] me,
but she doesn't give a [ __ ] I said,
"Fuck that." What's that? What's sex
without a [ __ ] Is it?
>> I got I got a thing for [ __ ] Me,
Triple H, didn't it?
>> I like I like my [ __ ] To be honest with you,
>> you can't [ __ ] without a You know what
I'm saying? It's just weird to me. What
do you think?
>> No. No, you can [ __ ] without a [ __ ]
Just stick the [ __ ] in, is it?
Yeah, but like it's not as
it's not as good.
>> So, remember the last time you had a bit them, PJ?
>> A little while ago.
>> I don't even remember. I last had it.
>> You want me?
>> I don't even remember when I last had it.
>> Oh, doesn't don't you get much off that? No.
>> No, no, no. They don't give it me.
You you won the marching powder.
>> You packed that in, didn't you? >> Yeah.
>> Bless you then.
>> Remember when you'll be on it?
>> Yeah. No, but when did you last do it?
>> A while ago. >> Really?
>> Yeah. It's good. Is it?
>> You'd be You'd be in the [ __ ] doghouse, mate.
>> You don't know what that means, do you?
>> Yeah. It means you're [ __ ] You get in the neck.
>> You know what?
>> You know what? You know, she struggles
so much with women. Why don't you try
try it with cosmic courtesy where that gets you?
>> Yeah. I've had more women than you though.
>> I don't think so.
>> I think so. No, I don't think so. PJ,
>> I think so. You have no standards.
>> I'm got standards.
>> Occupies prostitutes. [Laughter] >> Yeah. >> Pro times. Yeah.
>> Yeah. But you've done you've done it. Triple H. >> No.
>> You've never done it?
>> No. Not with Fuzzy. No.
>> Would you? No.
>> Well, if someone paid for you to do it, you would.
>> That's bottom of the barrel that lad.
>> No, but you you would do it though. Is it?
>> Yeah. But sniping me sister Nick
Snickers don't count. Yeah.
>> Yeah. But it's so Yeah, but it's so
Yeah, but it's so easy to do though. Is
it like Triple H say you win money? You
just Hey, bang an escal. It's so easy.
You can see why people do it, isn't it?
>> It is easy. Well, it's [ __ ]
>> No, but I didn't [ __ ] I don't [ __ ] them
most of the time. I just get a [ __ ]
from them. I don't even [ __ ] them.
>> Yeah. Was that story true? What Sean
said when he said [ __ ] you had that
prozy and you had elder rostage to get
you 150 back?
>> Yeah, everyone knew that.
>> Did you get it back? >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] hell. That's awful at that. What
was [ __ ] that?
>> Well, why did we No, but most when he
was saying stuff about my dad hitting my
mom and sisters, that's [ __ ] That's
made up. He couldn't even he couldn't
even he couldn't even keep a straight
face when he was saying it. That's
[ __ ] made up. My dad was never even
My dad was never even in my life, Monty.
I never lived with my [ __ ] dad ever.
>> Yeah, cuz when you were born, your dad
thought, "Fuck these bastards. I battle his life."
>> You know?
>> Yeah. What?
>> No, but you see what I mean though. But
you see what I mean? Like my dad never me.
>> So why did you want the 150 back off the brass?
>> Uh cuz I lasted 10 seconds.
>> Did you like >> Yeah.
>> You like it though, is it? Where you going?
>> No. Don't.
>> When you next come back,
>> what did you say?
>> When you next drinking?
>> Probably on Friday.
>> I didn't get a pizza shop. Actually, you
know, I had Chinese last night, didn't I?
>> Yeah, you did, didn't you?
>> Bless you. Do you like [ __ ]
You should get um a pizza with jalapenos.
>> No, lad. Huh? I like a don to me. >> Yeah.
>> Can you get that?
>> I've never had one. >> Why?
>> I'm spending time with N.
>> You don't want to spend time with me.
>> No, you too. I
>> love you too, Monty.
>> See you later, too.
Yeah, I'm going to go out on a drink on
uh Friday, I think.
>> Friday, right?
>> Yeah, man. Um
you know, you know the best kebab is
this um chicken ticker kebab, but they
don't have it in London. They It's
chicken tickon, but they have it in
Wales, but they don't have it in um
>> I get I But I got a picture. I get um I
get chicken ticker donor, Mick. Chicken
tick. What's called t? It's called
chicken taker, man. Chicken ta >> t.
>> That's ta.
>> No, it's ticker.
>> Chicken ta. Right with Donna me. Right.
So, it's like a mix but without the
chicken. Lovely line.
>> Yeah. Nice.
>> Do you get Do you get a pter bread on? Na bread.
>> Um, what with what? >> Kebab.
>> Uh, p bread or sometimes have it with
chips, but yeah, p bread. Yeah,
>> I like a shish kebab, but they're expensive, man.
>> What a shish kebab is a [ __ ]
>> It's like um you know, don kebab is like
processed with grease. Shish kebab is
like where they grill it. It's like
chunks of meat. >> Yeah.
>> But they're expensive. But you know, the
best thing Yeah. You know, after a drink
is a pizza cuz you don't get a hangover.
If you have like a nice pizza, you don't
really get a hangover the next day.
>> Ah, I seen your video. You had a pizza,
didn't you? When you were last out on
the drink. I seen that. Yeah. M
>> come on now.
>> Is that okay with you, [ __ ] [Laughter] >> Hi.
>> So, you're you're you're on the pool
again this week, aren't you?
>> No, I'm not doing that this week. I've
got the off demand the B this week.
>> You got you've got what?
>> I've demand the B this weekend. So, I
won't be drinking this week anyway.
Well, the weekend coming now.
>> You drink like twice a month, is it?
>> Yeah, something like that.
>> Yeah. It's expensive though, ain't it?
>> So, you have night or you have an Indian?
>> Yeah, I've just ordered it, man. I'm starving, bro. >> Yeah.
>> When are you ordering yours?
>> About six. [Laughter] >> Really? >> Why? >> Huh?
>> Pick up.
>> Is it near your house?
>> It's about 10 minutes away. Yeah.
>> Well, bless you then if you live in the northeast.
Yeah, any them?
>> Nah, man. Not really.
>> I will be out on Friday, but I just go
right now cuz I want a drink, you know.
But [ __ ] Yeah.
>> What do you think just Guinness like?
>> Yeah, I try to stick to just Guinness
because you know when you stick to just
Guinness Yeah. you get like you don't
get hangover in it, but sometimes I
drink the white rum. [ __ ] strong though. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Have you had it? White rum.
>> Yes. I've had it go.
>> It's [ __ ] The hangovers the next day
are horrible. Is it
>> any drink man hangovers don't I like um
I like lag me but I like Guinness as
well. I mix it up with me.
>> Yeah. Guinness is more like the win like
a winter drink. Yeah.
>> It's nice Guinness. Like Yeah.
>> I love Guinness, man.
>> A lot of people don't like Guinness.
>> A lot of people don't. But it's so nice.
There's I like it. So,
you know where how much is a pint of
Guinness? How much is a pint of Guinness
where you are here? It's like It's like almost £85.
>> Yeah, it's like £8 here. >> Like,
>> yeah. Go on, Monty. What?
>> Why don't you have standards?
>> You don't have standards.
>> I [ __ ] got standards. Me if you want
my If you want my opinion, Monty, I
thought that Katie was a [ __ ] pig.
Yeah. Yeah, you're right about Kayie.
Yeah, 100% on Kayie.
>> She was a pig, isn't it?
>> 100% she was a pig. 100% on Natalie's not.
>> Can I have Natalie?
>> Can you [ __ ] Natalie?
>> Oh man. Me, me, you, and Trip H need to
get on a drink, lad.
>> No, not until you apologize to that.
I don't apologize, Monty. You know me.
>> Yeah, but I think you should apologize to
>> How do you know about the American
Monty? Did you fancy her?
>> No, she fancied me. Peer.
>> I thought was I thought was it the you [ __ ]
I thought it was the other is you
fancied Monty or Monty fed there, didn't he?
>> Yeah. No, I've always had a I've always
had a thing for Natalie me.
>> I've always had a thing for that. Always
had a thing.
>> What you going to do, Trip H? Eat and
then just watch some telly and go to sleep.
>> I'm going to eat and just just be on your YouTube.
>> Oh, bless you then.
>> I don't mind that Tik Tok is on me. >> Huh?
>> That Tik Tok. I don't mind that Tik Tok, mate.
>> No, it's addicting, is it? [ __ ] in there.
>> What month? Uh what month are you going
called approaching net speed? Yeah.
>> Uh your mom.
>> Well, I'll probably take it to be honest. >> Yeah.
>> You got me.
>> I I Hey, do you remember when they used
to go on about your bed sheets triple?
They went on about that for years.
>> Ah on the burger
half a burger.
>> Yeah, but they don't they don't do they
still do it. Uh, do they still do it triple? >> Yeah,
>> triple beats don't come up on your panel
much. So, probably not as much as they
do it with me and you. No,
>> that's forgotten. That's that that's
begotten. There's no videos up there.
All is our [ __ ] burger. That's it.
>> I've seen what you I've seen what you
look like. Triple H. Isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> You haven't. You've never seen me
actually. Now, you've
>> Yes, I have. You put your seen PJ you
put your you put your what you put your
WhatsApp picture as you. Don't you
remember a few years ago?
>> I've seen him. I've seen him. He's
better looking than you PJ.
>> No, you remember Triple? >> Close.
>> Yeah. It's all [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Are you Triple?
bedroom was has a was >> I
remember when Freddy got nicked there
and he got his vi devices um and he went
back on YouTube the next day.
>> I know I know he done that and know yeah
he was on that match last night that
after he got Yeah. He got back out the
fell and he was back on.
>> Yeah. Monty just couldn't get off of
YouTube, could he?
>> No. Monty Monty's deep now.
>> Yeah. There's no hope for money anymore.
>> Yeah. There's never hope for me. Even
[ __ ] There's never been hope for me
since the day.
>> How did my mom's ass me?
>> How did Jamie even get on here?
>> EJ, do you know what? No,
I watched Tim El's gambling videos me
and then [ __ ] that was it.
>> One second. I'll be right back. Yeah,
hold on. I just need to go toilet. One second.
>> Yeah, make sure you fall down at you bastard.
>> Get lost.
>> Ever been mates with him at any time?
>> No. No. Is PJ's fault to be honest with you.
>> Not forgetting you're on here.
>> No. [ __ ] through lockdown PJ ends up
getting Timmy Eldridge on a WhatsApp
call with me and me and to to call him.
So I started calling Timmy El on a
[ __ ] WhatsApp call that come on to YouTube.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Then [ __ ] PJ said, "Oh, do you want
to come on YouTube? He's he's good or
he's banter or that little come on." I
said, "All right then." That's when I'm
getting dark [ __ ] Yeah, don't worry about it. >> Yeah.
I wish you never come on here now, but
in that I off because of Natalie.
>> Yeah, you making that money, mate.
>> Sorry about that.
>> Won't make me the same as Timmy. They
both make up excuses.
>> I live in Birmingham. We live in their own city.
He said they were going to come to me
and his money m found out. Well, if it
was excuses or I got a problem with him, it's me.
>> See what I mean?
>> Oh, yeah. >> Yeah.
>> No, P. Yeah, we don't see what you mean.
You can't get laid.
>> I've been laid more times than you.
>> How many times have you laid the table to
>> And I've had I've had better looking
women than you have as well.
>> How many times have you laid Why not?
Not this best looking one in the world.
Better than what woman you've ever been with.
>> Hey, Triple H. Would you ever get with
an American bird?
>> No. Would you? Why would you?
Why wouldn't you? Why wouldn't you?
>> Would you get with Natalie's mom?
>> Don't be silly. >> No.
>> Would you?
>> No. I wouldn't. >> Why?
>> Wouldn't fella. >> Yeah.
you. I don't really I don't know. I
don't know really. Well, I don't know.
>> But no,
>> I thought she could have been for you. >> Yeah.
>> Don't like his granny's
>> H has been to America, you know.
>> That's why you won't go out with that J
girl. Give that J girl the chance.
>> I think you fancy J.
You keep going on about her. Do you fancy her?
>> I'm just saying. Why don't you give her
a chance, PJ?
>> Cuz she's an old woman.
>> But how how old are you, PJ? 27? Yeah.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Yeah. Well, there you go then. She's not
too old for you then. Do you see?
>> How How old are you now? Now, triple.
>> 29, lad.
>> Is your birthday October like mine? >> No. >> January?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Why don't you go and shed
something like your mom peeve? Yeah.
Might throw hands.
>> So yeah. So your Yeah. January. Yeah.
>> What's happening with this then? Is he
he's taking it to court in he
>> see he's bringing up now. Monty see
>> he's bringing he's bringing the virgin up now.
>> He's taking you to CO is he?
>> No. of YouTube.
>> Yeah. He's allowed to talk about 13 boy.
He's different. He doesn't go on about
him all day long. You do PJ,
>> you know?
Do you fancy your PJ?
>> Yeah, I got a whole channel on him and I
go on about him every day.
>> Yeah. How do you
>> I don't know. It's just how you talk about him.
It's like how you both have got these
like little odd little videos going on
between you both. >> No,
>> it's like wants to stick his dick up
your ass or you want to stick your dick
up his ass. It's one of them.
>> Back Sean in it.
>> I think it is Sean who wants to stick
his dick up PJ's ass. I think it is.
>> Nature girls posted where's all black flaps. Sean AJ. >> No.
>> Why? You need a good looking mad. You know, >> no.
>> I'm really hungry. Chip rate. I've just ordered food.
>> I'm going to get started in a bit. Like,
>> are you starving? Is it
just got a bigger dick in your P? Yeah.
>> Your mom?
>> My mom? Yeah, man.
>> Mad. Right here. I'm going to shoot off
if you're back on a bit. jump back on.
>> Okay, catch you later.
>> Ra loves my little voice.
>> I think he knows your little dick. >> Yeah.
>> Why don't me Why don't we go Newcastle?
Me and Monty. We can go meet Trip Rage.
>> No, that stick with my Mes. I don't need
to go out. I've got a Mes to attend to.
>> Yeah, we can still go out with the lads.
I'll have a go out with Slug.
Yeah, that's your boyfriend, isn't it?
>> I blog over to be honest with you.
>> No, seriously.
>> Yeah, seriously.
>> You horrible old [ __ ]
Are you a horrible old [ __ ]
>> Yeah. How do you make a woman orgasm? >> Um,
you tell me.
>> Not with your [ __ ] anyways.
You You love my [ __ ] right right up your mouth.
>> It's a blaze of you, PG. It's too small.
And if you ever say, "Have you ever seen
it?" Yeah. Yeah.
>> I'm going to Finland next month to meet
a woman. Monty.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yeah, I met her last Sunday.
>> So, why do you have to go out your own
city? Just to find a woman. I can get a
woman in my own town. In my own city.
>> Cuz I want to go uh Finland.
Mongo's favorite je
I'm not jealous.
I've had more funny PJ. Not paid for,
>> bro. I've had better looking women than you.
>> Natalie is better looking woman than all
the woman you've been with. >> Nah. >> Yeah.
>> Well, you used to stalk women in it. No,
not you. PJ,
you remember when you was crying loudly?
It was funny, is it? >> Yeah.
Like that crying over a woman.
>> Yeah, cuz I'm laughing. I want to cry over it.
>> Oh my god. Yeah, I'm going
>> I'm going to see finish Izzy next month.
His helper Natalie is ugly. What?
Oh, like his car. >> Yeah.
Would you your mom's carer? >> No.
>> Yeah. And somehow your Yeah. Pier. >> No.
>> Yeah. Won't you your mom's car? Yeah. >> No.
>> And your sister career for you or
something? Or you were car or your mom
was a carer for you. >> No,
>> something like that. Something that
dodgy were going on there.
>> No. Yeah, yeah, Monty's always been a
snake. That's just the way he is, man.
>> I'm not a snake. I told you all I'm PJ's
[ __ ] Look, people use all these snakes on here.
All you are the biggest snakes on here.
Talking about snaking.
EJ is the biggest snake here for one >> m
call his mates girlfriends
and this guy can't even get a bird.
[ __ ] can't even pull a yacht dog.
>> I've already pulled multiple women. You've seen
>> what? Multiple men. Yeah, I know. You pulled
>> pulled a woman in Manchester. Pulled a
woman in Nottingham. pulled a woman in
London multiple times.
>> Yeah, you have to go out your local town
just to try and pull. Sometimes that
don't even work.
>> Yeah. Well, at least I didn't end up
with a slag like you.
>> I was not a slag. She's with one man. She's loyal.
>> She's been with the whole of YouTube, mate.
>> No, she hasn't been with the
>> I just ordered some Indian Grezy. Some lovely Indian.
>> No, she haven't been with the full of
YouTube. started being with three people on YouTube.
>> How How does it feel that How does it
feel getting money m sloppy seconds?
>> Money M's got a lot of dicks or not?
>> I got a cheese. I got a cheese.
>> I got a cheese ny. It come to 28 pound.
You can't afford a takeaway, can you?
>> Of course, I can afford a takeaway.
>> You sure?
>> Yeah, I'm sure. P. Yeah.
>> You are skint now.
>> We're skint. >> No. >> Okay.
>> If I didn't win the football bet on
Tuesday, Greavvesy, what would have
happened, do you think?
>> Why do you have friends on YouTube, not
in the real world?
>> What do you think would have happened?
Uh, cuz it's funny.
What have I been friends?
>> Yeah, but what have I been able to go
out drinking? Greasy.
>> I I've got more friends than you.
>> Now, why you always on the table for
one? Have you got more friends than me?
>> Why was you crying over some woman that
you was only with for a couple of months?
>> Because I've known Natalie longer than a
couple of months.
>> You reckon I can afford to go out
drinking now, Grezy? Yeah, cuz it's
terrible for one, is it?
>> Uh, do you think so, Grezy? Oh, really?
>> Yeah. Yeah, cuz you're not paying for
anyone else, just your own. So, yeah,
you got the money to go out.
>> Been listening for a few minutes.
Natalie is a sketch. She gets her
clothes off to random men on YouTube. Ride,
>> hang on a minute. Hang on a minute. He's
the one who's got to get a woman piss
out of her face to do that [ __ ]
Natalie won't have done that at all by
now. Like you all old know that.
And Natalie didn't even know nothing
about that until a couple of days after
until she seen a picture of herself. [Laughter]
But Natalie didn't even know she done that.
>> Is a M. Yeah, you are M. Stop talking about yourself.
>> At least I've got what you ain't got.
And at least I've got more than what PJ has got.
>> You don't have more than what I've got. Of
>> course I've got more than what you've got.
>> Monty, I have pulled more times than you ever have. >> PJ,
>> I'm in a relationship.
>> I've been in I've been in a relationship.
>> You been turned down more times than a
[ __ ] hot dog ass by a [ __ ] homeless guy.
>> Listen listen. You was crying over
Natalie because that's all you can get.
>> Natalie is a woman that
>> if he if he listen if this guy could get
>> How many people find Natalie in this community?
>> He wouldn't be quiet. How many people
he didn't get rejected? He wouldn't be cried overnight.
>> He was wanting to meet Natalie.
>> [ __ ] crazy, man. What the [ __ ]
>> You wanted to meet Natalie? What the [ __ ]
>> You wanted to meet her
>> until you found out it was He was crying
over that. No, I didn't want to meet
her. If I wanted to meet her, I would
have met her.
But the [ __ ] you wanted to meet her
because she she you know, it was fake.
>> No, listen. If you didn't get rejected
and you can get women, you wouldn't be
crying over a slag. You got a video.
>> Does that sound like women?
>> Does that sound like somebody that can
get women? It was all them women that
were talking to on meet on meet and all
the fake video.
>> You didn't meet any of them.
>> It didn't matter didn't matter. I could
have met but obviously didn't but you didn't still
got still got the number
>> but you didn't
>> still got the number. Still got them
pulled there. They still see what I look like.
>> Yeah. Okay. Whatever.
>> Yeah. So I can pull more than you
without [ __ ] woman saying no more ped.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Of course you can. Yeah.
Yeah. Oops. Of course I can't that. You
keep saying yourself.
>> Remember the woman in the [ __ ] pub
who didn't even want to talk to you. You
smile on to me.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You keep saying
but you was crying over a slag. So shut up.
>> Was it crying over what slag? Who's a >> Pia's a slag.
>> Pia. All the girls he been with were all slags.
>> Okay then. Yeah. Yeah.
>> All about my slags down and out. That's
why we go downtown every weekend to try
and get a C. Yeah.
>> If you could get if you could get women,
if you could get women, you would be
crying over Natalie. You wouldn't have
cried over Natalie if you could get women.
>> Look, it's called love, PG. Yeah. You've
never been in love.
>> Yeah. It's called love. Yeah. Okay. At first,
you're too love PG. All you love is your mom
at 34 years of age. [ __ ] hell.
>> 34 of age. PJ, don't matter if you're 30
or 40 or 50 or 60.
>> You've already had a girlfriend,
Natalie. Go self-reflect somewhere else. Try again.
>> No one cares what you self-reflect say,
man. You just No one cares.
>> Self reflect.
You're the biggest one. Yeah. You're
calling Natalie. You're calling me. You
call whatever. But look at you.
>> Yeah. It's a woman.
>> Yeah. Okay. I can't get a woman. Yeah.
Yeah. You keep saying whatever.
You really can't.
>> So why do I need to go out and go cold
approaching women pier when I'm wiping
with one woman?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Come on.
>> I'm not arguing with you. I can't be bothered.
>> I'm not arguing. I'm just saying the
truth. Why the [ __ ] do I want to go
corner person when I'm happy with what?
>> If you could do better, you wouldn't be
with a slag. If you could get women, you
wouldn't be with a slag. End the story.
>> One. One. I've done better. Two.
>> Well, you haven't done better because
you would be
>> done better. Natalie. Natalie is 10
times better than what I was with. >> Okay.
>> 10 times better. >> Okay.
>> Natalie was pissed when she did all
that. That's I'm not blaming Natalie for
that. You can cuz that's the kind of man
you are. Natalie was pissed when she
done all that. He didn't know what she was doing.
Well, you did.
>> It's not an excuse, though, is it?
>> No, no, no, no. It's no excuse. No, it
isn't. It's no excuse for these getting
a woman pissed. Knowing a woman will do
that pissed. They don't really matter.
>> Even this ghosting guy, Even the
ghosting guy says you're a muppet, Jamie. >> What?
>> Even this Even this ghosting guy says
that you're a muppet.
>> Ghost is a muppet.
is the same as you self-reflected sat in
his mom's basement.
>> Sat in my mom's basement. Oh, that's
news to me. Yeah, I'm sat in my mom's basement. Okay.
>> Obviously, my mom's left obviously. Not you.
>> You learn You learn You learn something
new every day, man. You learn something
new every day.
>> You s your mom's empty house.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> That's it. You literally you literally
had to buy nine burgers because you were
so skinn you couldn't even [ __ ] eat.
Oh my god.
>> Actually, actually actually it was 40
burgers peas. Yeah, I had to talk about me.
>> You want to talk about me?
>> Listen, listen. Let me tell you
something about you. If it wasn't for
you, I wouldn't have met that [ __ ]
nons. I wouldn't have met [ __ ] Jack
the Ripper if it wasn't cuz of [ __ ]
you. You all know you listen. >> Yeah.
>> Listen, you're the one who entertain
yourself with them.
>> You're the one who put yourself with
them. Yeah, I did. Cuz you're the one
who put yourself with them people.
>> You're the one who met them people.
Yeah, I know. You met them.
>> I met them through. Yeah. Through you.
I've met them through you.
>> No. No. There's nothing. No. Everyone
told you what you both were like and you met them.
>> You're a freak. Cuz like
>> you and Nlex was fighting over Britney.
Man, how long how long have we been How
long have we been friends for? How long
have you been You two was fighting over.
>> PJ PJ, you can make up any excuse you want.
>> How do you think they know each other?
He was fighting over an underage girl.
>> PJ, you can make up any excuse you want. >> I'm
You can make up any excuse you want.
>> That's why you hate each other. That's
why you hate each other. Sean is because
he's a nun. You like Sean. You were
talking to Why was you talking to him
all the way through?
>> You both cuz you both wanted.
>> This is the thing. And who got you
talking to Sha L the American?
>> You introduced him to him.
>> He's up on your channel where you met
American who introduced you to to Shakes.
>> You did.
>> Yeah. Your community.
>> You're a bit of a weird pedia. No wonder
why mommy [ __ ] you up.
>> You went to your mom over YouTube. You at least.
>> Oh my god.
>> Your mom Your mom hanged the phone up on
you. She doesn't listen.
>> No ass with it. Your mom's [ __ ] want
to from you.
>> Yeah. Okay. Okay.
>> Run from you.
>> Okay. Okay. and his sister want to be with you.
>> So why was you and Sean fighting over Britney?
>> You don't even know what you want about Lia
PlayStation. So I don't know what you
want about Lopeia.
>> He was fighting over an underage girl.
>> Are you sure about that? >> Yeah.
>> Oh Pia P. Yeah. Just listen to what he's saying.
>> Yeah, I know what I'm saying.
>> Yeah. So, a man used to who used to sit
on a panel with Sean 24/7. PG.
>> Yeah. I didn't know what he was like.
>> Never was on my friend list. Never. I
met him through Dean. Yeah. Bought him
up when I found out he was a nons and PJ
was was still talking to him when were
going on about Britain.
>> You know what I mean? [ __ ] hell.
>> And then and PJ meets up with him
knowing that that N.
>> I didn't know it was a N. I don't know.
>> You did. You met all knowing they
knowing well facts and what he were.
>> Even these people say
>> even these people say that you
introduced me to nonsex.
>> Oh, these people will say it.
I've never introduced you to nobody.
Nons is your own [ __ ] fault. Pediats
ain't got nothing to do with me. community.
>> He is a stalker freak. Yeah, he is.
>> He's a lot of weirdos in like Pedia.
>> Yeah, he run. Yeah, you were. Yeah, if
it wasn't for you, I wouldn't have met
that weirdo and he would be stalking. If
>> it weren't for me, PJ, you're the one
who [ __ ] added him as a friend, not me,
>> you know.
>> So, where was I? So, so what did I said
to you then? Maybe introduced you to him,
>> you know.
>> Well, it's No, no. So if I te your legs,
what did I say to you?
>> What do you mean? You said he was a good guy.
>> Did I [ __ ] say he's a good guy? No. No.
No. You are full of [ __ ]
>> No, you really are full of [ __ ] PJ.
>> You know, you know you said he was a good guy.
>> I would never ever ever say that about
Sean long legs.
>> Never. Never.
You telling me that his mom telling me
that you telling me that his mom stole
your pe. You know what? I find it funny
that like he actually goes for you to be
honest with you.
>> You know what I mean? Oh
>> yeah, he can go for
he would ever meet me in real life. So
that's all that's all good.
>> Who want
>> [ __ ] nodd legs?
>> Yeah. It's a soft ass.
a bit like you.
>> I would be ashamed if he was my daughter.
>> I'd be ashamed if PJ was my son.
>> Where is Lisa nowadays? Anyways,
>> anyway, I'm going to jump off thinking
that I'm not going to give PJ my time
all day anymore to be honest with you.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Listen. Okay. >> Self can't get.
>> He's got to pay frosty cuz you can't get
I'd rather pay apostle than to be with
that slag that you're with. Bye-bye now.
Hey, listen. Natalie, you are lonely.
Story of your life behind that account.
You are lonely. Lonely 40-year-old
virgin on YouTube. Ah, that's you. I
love it. I love the fact that you're a
lonely 40-year-old skinned bastard on
YouTube. I love it. I love it as well.
Righty O this account just like you.
Lonely middle-aged man on YouTube ain't
got a life. I love it. I love the fact
that I'm in my 20s showing more money
than you, better looking than you. I
love that you're the 40-year-old loner
coming online every day hating on people
that you don't even know. Isn't that
right, Ghoston? You people are the
definition the definition of Mr. Lonely
on YouTube. Mr. Lonely on YouTube.
Loners that can't get off of YouTube in
their 40s. That is you, bro.
Lonely, fat, fat, ugly people that can't
get off of YouTube. Mr. Lonely. When
you're [ __ ] telling people that
they've got no money and you're telling
people that they got no women. All of
the things that you wish you had that
you never have. You're just trying to
self-reflect your skin ugly old man life
onto me. You know what I mean?
I let But bro, I don't, like I said, I'm
not wasting my time with these people anymore ghosting.
They're little self-reflecting comments.
Your skin, you're you got no friends.
Funny enough, my friend messaged me just
now saying, "Do you want to go for a
beer?" I don't waste my time with these self-reflectors. These self-reflecting disabled people.
I'm [ __ ] starving, bro. This food
needs to come.
self-reflecting people. Come on. I'm
[ __ ] starving, man. I said to the
guy, "You still in Stratford?"
I'll be off here soon anyways. Um, ghosting, lad.
Yeah, I'll be off here soon.
Yeah, they're self-reflectctors.
They're all middle-aged fat, ugly,
lonely people that ain't got a life.
Angry gamblers. I like to call them
angry gamblers. Just like Ricky Milling
and just like [ __ ] these stupid
people. These [ __ ] sad, ugly people.
They ain't got a life. Yeah, they're
just something to laugh at, bro.
Self-reflecting little bastards.
Calling people they don't know for a living. Um, nah.
Yeah. Another takeaway, bro. Cost me £28. Starving, lad.
You know what I find so mad? that I've
shown these people £6,000, they've all
run away. I've shown these people all
these women, they've run away. That's
why it's just a waste of everyone's time.
It's a waste of everyone's time, these
people, you know.
It's just a waste. Just a waste.
Know what I mean?
Like I said, if you're not fat and ugly
like these people, they're biased.
It's like that Joe. I'm sure he's
addicted to like younger men's attention.
Yeah, man. But I want some money on the
football and [ __ ] in it. So, I'm all good, man.
I'm all good.
Don't worry, bro. I'm all good, lad.
I won't be starving, man. Yep.
No, I won on Tuesday. I won last
Tuesday. I put 120 on the football. I
got it to 380. So, a decent profit in
it. And I won some football bets a few
weeks before that. So, I'm kind of all
right with money. I'm all good. What's that? Yeah. What's up?
I am [ __ ] starving, bro.
>> Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
>> I'm going let this video on.
>> Yep. Story of your life, little self
projector. You're lonely every day of
your life. You middle-aged ugly bastard.
Not just Christmas. You're lonely every
day, Mr. Lona.
Yeah, you're lonely. But you're Mr.
Lonely every day.
You're Mr. Lonely all the time. Still
your life. That's what I used to say to these people.
Oh, is that actually the real Natalie?
Natalie, listen. Listen, listen. I would
never have to resort to someone as ugly
as you. And you're a [ __ ] slag as
well. You showed your [ __ ] Fanny to
the whole of YouTube. Not even normal
[ __ ] slags do that, you know?
Yeah, you're [ __ ] stinking, son.
You know you love me. Really?
What was you saying about £15? Yeah,
she is stinking
proper. She is [ __ ] stinking, son. Yeah.
Yeah, I will in a bit, man. I will in a
bit. I'm the first person that he had a cross on.
It's because they're too ugly to get anything themselves.
It's the same with that Ricky Milling.
He's never seen a woman naked and he
tries to sit there and say that I can't
get a woman and I'm going to end up
hurting a woman. It's because they're
they're too ugly to go and get anything themselves.
I'll be out on Friday.
Maybe. Maybe I'll be out. Maybe, who knows?
I don't have the energy for it anymore, mate.
I'm starving, man. I am actually [ __ ] starving, bro. Are you
[ __ ] it. Now I'm [ __ ] starving, bro.
Come to me. Come to me,
Birdie. Come to Peter Belly.
Come to me.
I'm starving, lad. Not even a joke.
I need to start the gym soon. Me, man.
I need to start the [ __ ] gymnas.
I'm looking at myself in the mirror,
man. Look how good looking I am. Jesus Christ.
Better looking than virgin boy.
You think this is where the jealousy
comes into it? Bongo bast it. My little
cute eyes. My little cute face. My
little cute eyes.
Yeah, pure fat.
Tim has better looks.
N still fancies me. Yeah.
Yeah. N loves me.
He loves me.
They're not even ordering. They're not
even Come on, man.
I'm [ __ ] starving.
I'm so much better looking than Virgin boy.
It kills him. It kills Virgin boy.
Where are you? Virgin boy.
How long is it going to be, mate?
I kind of want some ice cream now.
Right. I'll be back soon. Gonna eat this food.