Yo, a leopard never changes its stripes
with that magnetic roulette.
[ __ ] waiting five [ __ ] minutes.
What the [ __ ] bro? Still rigged as
anything. Damn. I thought it would have literally
it would have stopped the [ __ ] now, you know.
Uh because of your rigged roulette. It's
always exactly the same reason like
every three or four months, isn't it?
Because of your rigged roulette. That's
literally the only reason why somebody
would want to close something down
because of your rigged magnetic
roulette. [ __ ] hell,
bro. What What else would somebody Why
would somebody close their account? Cuz
of your fixed games consistently
going on losing numbers. [ __ ] three
months ago, this first time in three
months, I thought, "Fuck it. Let me try
£100. And it's still rigged. It's still
as rigged as a [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's still rigged. Even after three
months, it's still seeking that loser.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Dirty, dirty, stinky [ __ ] pedo.
[ __ ] dirty [ __ ] pedophile number.
That's what it is. It's a dirty [ __ ]
pedo. Shitty [ __ ]
Yeah. [ __ ] hell. What the [ __ ] was I
thinking after [ __ ] three months?
Jesus [ __ ] Christ. It's the same
[ __ ] [ __ ] with it.
There's nothing luck about it. Suck my
dick. [ __ ] off.
Suck my [ __ ] dick. It's [ __ ] luck.
Shut the [ __ ] up about it luck. It's
nothing luck about it. You know, you
control the outcome. Just get the
account gone. [ __ ] same conversation every time.
Same conversation every time.
There's nothing luck about it. Look
right there is right I'm explaining this
to you again. There is 20 there is
[ __ ] 36 numbers. 37 numbers on a
wheel. You're covering 20 numbers.
You're not missing that many times. It's
common sense. Even with £100, it ain't
no house edge. Get [ __ ] get [ __ ] and
[ __ ] off. Stop using it as a [ __ ]
excuse. There's nothing luck about it.
You control everything.
Uh, yes you do. Yes, you do. And I'm not
arguing about it. I want to close it
down. [ __ ] annoying as [ __ ]
You control [ __ ] everything. Isn't it
funny how, look at before you
participate in the game, it's always
random. And as soon as you put money on
like 20, 30, 40 pound spins, same rig
[ __ ] You control [ __ ] everything.
You literally control [ __ ]
everything. You know, I barely even This
is the first roulette session I've had
in months. I don't [ __ ] [ __ ] with
this [ __ ] anymore. Same old story. Same
old sad song. You would have You would
have thought in in a few times of
someone doing it, they would have won something.
Stop talking out your ass. Stop talking
[ __ ] You control [ __ ]
everything. Thanks for the fucking£3
pound [ __ ] fee by fee by the way. You
[ __ ] idiots. [ __ ] £3 [ __ ] fees.
Oh my [ __ ] god.
Stop talking out your [ __ ] stupid
wanking ass. You control everything.
[ __ ] off. Always the same left side of
[ __ ] zero. Same old stad song that it
continuously seeks out. [ __ ] off and
suck my dick, you [ __ ] annoying [ __ ]
This is what these people must [ __ ]
do, you know.
This is what these people must do. Do
their [ __ ] bollocks in and then
[ __ ] go mad on YouTube. But I haven't
done my bollocks yet.
Yes. And you're cheaters now. Close the account down.
I'm asking them nicely as well, you
know. Please can you just close my
account down? I want you to close it
down. I don't want to see your rigged
[ __ ] on my screen like you always
[ __ ] do. Making it [ __ ] go on zero
section every [ __ ] time. How many
zero sections I've seen in my [ __ ]
life. You see any person that part that
that that that participates, they don't
get this rigged [ __ ] with it. You know
what I mean?
[ __ ] off, stupid [ __ ] Rig bastard.
You know, this is exactly why I didn't
want to do it, bro. But I thought, let
me just try 100 pound. This is exactly
what I mean with it. It's the same [ __ ]
with this [ __ ] rigged roulette. It
ain't got [ __ ] all to do with House
Edge. And if that scoop account come on
right now, I tell him the same thing.
It's not no house edge. Cuz I remember
this two three months ago as well when I
when I last played. It was the same
thing. Net zero section. Zero sections.
The same kitty fiddler area every single
time. [ __ ] off. You know
[ __ ] annoying it is. Yeah.
[ __ ] go [ __ ] your kids. Yeah. You
closed my account now. I'm good. Now go
[ __ ] your kids. It's [ __ ] annoying.
It doesn't matter how. Even if it's [ __ ]
Yeah. Close your account, man. You
stupid little [ __ ] [ __ ] Stop [ __ ]
trying to wind people up.
[ __ ] annoying [ __ ] Good. Close the
[ __ ] account, man.
Hey, bro. I just lost 100 pound, man.
[ __ ] on this [ __ ] rigged ass
roulette. keeps loving, loving it,
loving it, loving it. It's loving that
zero section. Same old sad song, boring.
This happened three months ago as well.
I thought, let me just try with £100 and
see if nah, nothing. Same story as
always with this [ __ ] you know.
Nah, it's nothing to do with the house.
They use magnets. It's nothing to do
with the house edge. Yep. Nothing to do
with the house edge. They use magnets.
It's nothing to do with the house edge.
They're cheating little bastards.
No, they're cheating little bastards.
It's nothing to do with House Edge. It's
cheat. They're cheating little [ __ ]
Nothing to do with House Edge.
Funny enough, the House Edge is only
little as well.
It's a little baby. Nothing Nothing to
do with the House Edge. They're just
cheating little [ __ ] That's what they are.
Yep. Cheating little [ __ ]
Same old story with it. I ain't played
[ __ ] roulette in months, bro. I can't
remember the last time. Same old sad
song story with it. Yeah, same old story
with the rig [ __ ]
Oh, just 100, bro. Just 100. It's just
so fixed. It is honestly so fixed.
You know, it's been the same sad song
when I played like months ago. It's the
same sad funeral song. You know, left
side of zero, left side of zero, 22
every [ __ ] time. You know, you cover 1920
numbers and it continuously continuously misses.
No, I just played it online and then I
started talking about their kids on the
live stream. I started talking about
their [ __ ] kids. It's [ __ ]
annoying, bro. It's [ __ ] annoying.
This is what I'm saying. It's not even
about £100 or whatever. It's annoying as [ __ ]
But I thought, oh, let me try and win
some money. Yeah, that was fat chance of that happening.
[ __ ] depressing. It makes you want to
kill yourself. It's [ __ ] horrible. I
hate it, bro. This is why I don't do this [ __ ]
This is why I don't do this [ __ ] bro.
I hate I was trying to win some extra
money, but No, that ain't happening.
That ain't happening for [ __ ] toffee, mate. Yeah,
they put I actually lost £103 because
fucking£3 pound fee in it.
You can't even win money. I started
talking about their kids and everything.
It's [ __ ] annoying, bro. Started
talking about their [ __ ] stinky [ __ ] kids.
cuz it's [ __ ] annoying. It's so
fixed. Honestly, it's so fixed. It's
unbelievable how fixed something can be.
It's so fixed. You know, even if it is
£100, it is so fixed after them four
time. I played four times, bro, in like
maybe four or five months, maybe three
times, I think. Same old rig sad song with it.
Why do they cheat? They they've got the
house edge anyway. So why do they cheat?
I don't understand why they cheat why
they would cheat somebody out of £100.
I just don't understand it to be honest.
What what's the point of cheating?
Honestly don't understand what's the
point of cheating. You know why cheat? Yeah.
So, I probably won't go out this month
to be honest. I probably won't even be
able to afford it if I'm still if I'm
saving for something else.
What a depressing life, eh? Jesus
Christ. I thought it was actually going
to be back. Well, I'm leaving. So, I
need to put that money towards that.
What a [ __ ] depressing life, eh? And
I actually thought I had it and I
thought I actually had it worse before.
What a [ __ ] depressing [ __ ] life, you know.
Really, really bad.
Yeah. So, it is it is fixed. [ __ ]
100% it's fixed.
It's so fixed, bro. I swear to God. I
was talking about their kids and everything.
I was talking about their [ __ ] kids.
And then they terminated a [ __ ] chat.
It's [ __ ] annoying as [ __ ] That was
the first time in like two and a half
months, bro. I don't I just thought,
"Oh, let me just put £100 in it cuz I
found this [ __ ] site. I just started
talking about their [ __ ] kids. I
don't give a [ __ ] mate."
You know what I mean? It's [ __ ]
annoying, bro. It is annoying as [ __ ]
Now I probably won't even go out now, be
able to go out comfortably now because
of that [ __ ]
This life is depressing, bro. The only
thing you can pray is that you go to
sleep and not wake up, you know? This is
boring, bro. You don't want to be
worrying about [ __ ] money, bro. [ __ ]
that. That's a dead life, bro. That is a
dead dead life. You know,
that is a dead life. Well, here in
London anyways, cuz everything's
expensive. That's a dead life, bro. I
swear to God, it's a dead life. You
can't even [ __ ] win any [ __ ] money
on these [ __ ] rigged pieces of [ __ ]
I just closed the [ __ ] account now.
What a dead life, bro. What a dead dead life. [ __ ] me.
It's bad. Bad that. Same shitty numbers
every [ __ ] time. It's not even a
[ __ ] It's not even like another tier number.
[ __ ] start talking about their
[ __ ] kids, bro. You know,
they want to get under your skin. I'll
[ __ ] get under their [ __ ] skin.
And that's money we can afford to lose.
If you want to be technical about it,
that is money we can afford to lose. And
what what's your point? And And what's
your [ __ ] point?
You get it?
It's bad, bro. Really bad.
Really bad, man.
You can't even win money. You can't
[ __ ] do anything. This country is
[ __ ] a [ __ ] bro.
Sooner I [ __ ] drop dead the [ __ ]
better. It's [ __ ] depressing, bro. Honestly,
I'm going to have to have this
conversation with my mom, I think, over
the phone about this [ __ ]
saying that basically I'm telling you
the situations though like if you
you know come across me dead then you
know not don't say I didn't warn you
cuz yeah I know like most people have to
stress about these things but I'm not
I'm not I'm not wanting to you know so I
don't I don't have to if I don't want to
I don't want to if I don't have to
you know so you So, it's your choice to
do whatever you want to do, bro. It's a
dead life, you know? A dead dead [ __ ] life.
Like, it really is. It's not even a
joke. It is generally a dead life. A
dead ass life.
You know, I [ __ ] hate gambling as
well. I only done it to try and win some [ __ ]
uh to try and win loads of money.
Actually, not some money. the [ __ ] else
option do you [ __ ] have, you know?
[ __ ] hell, man.
Whating [ __ ] hell,
I'm not struggling. Like, I'm not going
to starve or [ __ ] like I've got all
my [ __ ] paid. I'm not low or anything,
but the point still stands. I like to
have a lot of money when I [ __ ] go
out, you know?
You know, I don't need to get down to my
gamblers anonymous cuz I don't have a
gambling problem. I haven't gambled for
like 3 months on [ __ ] roulette and
[ __ ] I don't need to go to gamblers
anonymous cuz I don't have a gambling
problem. I only lost £100.
I just closed my account down. [ __ ]
this. I won't chase losses.
So, yeah, it is a pretty uh pretty dead
life to be honest.
Dead depressing life.
Yeah, it's a life not worth living to be
honest. to be honest.
Don't want to be stressing about money,
bro. That's one thing you don't want to
be doing in your life, matey. You know,
this is why you should have a really
luxur luxurious life. Because if you've
got a lux if you've had a luxurious
life, you're going to find it very very
hard to adjust
to a normal person's life. You know what I'm saying?
This is what happens, J. when you have a
life that I've had for like 3 three and
a half years and then you can no longer
live that life then
you know it's um
it's not a life you yeah it's just
depressing is it
the normal person's life you Yeah.
Yeah. It's really bad. It is really,
It's really, really bad, bro.
I've still got money. I've still got all
my [ __ ] paid and that. But it's not the
point, you know? It's not the [ __ ]
point. It's [ __ ] depressing, bro.
Now you got to worry about the women
[ __ ] and you got to worry about money.
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro. I want to
I want to like
I would happily die, bro, at this age.
Honestly, bro, I would happily die at this age.
You know, I wouldn't give a [ __ ] bro.
Fine at this age. I've done what I'm
about to do. I've got enough pictures.
Why am I going to live a [ __ ] life?
It doesn't It doesn't make any sense.
Why am I going to live a [ __ ] life? It's
a normal It's normal to a lot of you
people, but it's not normal to me, you know?
So, why am I going to live a [ __ ] life
and be frustrated every day? That's
[ __ ] ridiculous, bro. You know,
especially when there's nothing you can
do to change it. It's [ __ ] shite.
You know what I'm saying, bro? No one
gives a [ __ ] about that.
You know, I won't even I probably won't
even feel comfortable going out even
drinking to be honest.
Honestly, don't even think I will, bro.
Not either, man.
And now I have to live a a [ __ ]
boring normal life. Who wants to live a
boring normal life after 3 years?
You know what I'm saying? Like, it's
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. You know what I mean? So,
it's a dead life or a [ __ ] dead life.
But at least we know roulette never changes.
At least we know that thick [ __ ] never changes.
I didn't want to lose 150. I thought 100
pound was like just right. Even though
it is still a lot to lose and stuff.
Yeah. [ __ ] bro.
Well, I don't need to go on GameStop.
I'm not addicted to gambling.
It's not about [ __ ] gambling.
No, I don't get money from my house. It
seems so long to to get money. It is a
dead life, bro. It actually is a dead
life. It generally generally is a dead
[ __ ] life. Boring [ __ ] life. Now you got
multiple stresses now. You don't just
have the women stress. You've got multiple stresses. You know,
[ __ ] that. I'm not living that life,
bro. That's dead. That is [ __ ]
absolutely dead. That is absolutely
Yeah, this life is really really dead,
bro. It really really is.
It really really really is dead. Yeah.
Goes very slowly now.
It goes very slow,
you know. Very slowly,
Nah, bro. I'm not doing that.
No, I'm just going to eventually just
end my life, bro.
Because it's not a stressed that
somebody wants in their life, you know?
You people don't want to worry about
money. It's not something that you want
them to be worrying about. And yeah, I
know most people do. And yeah, I might
have more money than a lot of people,
but at the end of the day, bro, it's
like it's not really life you want to be living. So,
I don't know, bro.
It's dead. It's very, very dead.
And where you spend every single month,
it seems the money goes down and down
and down and down and down and down and down.
You know what I'm saying?
And down and down and down and down and
down. So, because when you don't have it
coming in, it just goes down and down.
It's dead, bro. It's it's a dead life,
you know? A very dead life.
It will go down. If I didn't win that
football bet, I would have been in some problems, bro.
So, it will go down. It would always go
down and down and down. Once you go out
in London, you're you're knackered. One
night, one night out in London, you're knackered.
So, I've got £1,100 in one account,
right? You get your haircut, you go in
London, you're knackered. You try and do
it again, you're [ __ ] It's [ __ ]
depressing, bro. [ __ ] this [ __ ] Life.
And I feel like I've actually had a good
life at 27 as well. So, I honestly
wouldn't wouldn't even care, bro. Like, about like, you know,
it does go down no matter what you do.
Well, unless you don't go out and you
stay bored, then yeah, you'd save. But I
mean, if you actually want to go out and stuff.
Yeah, it's depressing. It's a dead life.
It is a dead dead life.
Yeah. But it's not enough money. Yeah,
it's not enough money for somebody with my lifestyle.
Yeah, it's not it's not enough money for
me. It is for It's nowhere near as bad
as these people say, but I'm saying for me. Yeah,
that's probably why your bones and [ __ ]
ache. That's probably why your bones
ache. It's not easy to get a job and I
wouldn't be better off at all getting a
job either. It's probably why my bones
and [ __ ] ache, bro. It's probably from
the depressing, from all that income
loss. Come to think of it,
if you actually think of it. Yeah.
So, yeah, I'm probably just going to end
my life eventually at some point to be
fair. Oh, [ __ ]
Cuz it is dead. It is. It is dead.
It is a dead life, bro. So yeah,
it's not even funny either. It's [ __ ] madness.
But at least we know roulette never changes.
At least we know roulette never changes.
Cuz look, for example, went out that Sunday.
Now, you won't be better off. I'm just
going to kill myself eventually, I think,
because it's not a kind of stress that I
want in my life. So,
yeah, I probably will just kill myself soon
cuz what what did you think was actually
going to really happen eventually to be
honest? People don't feel the sting
straight away. You know, it could take a
month, two months, three months. It
depends. You know, I went out Sunday, I
spent hundreds. If I didn't win that
football bet, I would have been [ __ ]
So, yeah, it's not a kind of life you
want to be living to be honest with you
cuz I' I've lived both lives. I've lived
this life and I've lived having a load
of money life. It's not having loads of
money. It's getting a monthly income.
Yeah. But this life is dead, bro.
This life is generally generally
generally dead. Yeah, tomorrow can be
another day all at once. I'm I'm killing
myself soon. And I'm going to let my mom
know as well. So, don't say I didn't warn you.
which is inevitable really. You know, if
you've lost that kind of income a month,
you're not there's not there's no way
you can recover from it. Simple. That is
a dead life. Horrible. You don't want to
be worrying about money. It's one thing
you don't want to be worried about,
which was the whole point of why I done
the football bet, you know.
Yeah, I think eventually I am going to
do it, bro. I'm not even joking.
Nah, no link. So, yeah.
It's bad, isn't it? It is bad.
It is very bad, bro. It is very bad.
Very, very bad.
I don't like these people on here. I
hate these people on here. I just come
on here to like vent
like, you know, LJ and all of them. I
hate them, bro. I'd love I love them in
front of me. You really don't understand
how much I hate these narcissistic self
projectors on here. But I thought, let
me go live and see any decent people
wanted to join, you know. So
think is coming to the end very soon.
Yeah. You don't want to be worrying
about money, mate. It's one thing you
don't want to be worrying about, matey.
Matey, go out. You're [ __ ] knackered.
You know, that's what happens. [ __ ] that. So, yeah,
I'm not going to chase the loss. Like
I've said a million times, I don't have
a gambling problem.
I've said that a million times.
So yeah, if I go out again,
it's like, yeah, you can have 11,200
pound in your account. Yeah, you could
do. Yeah, but as soon as you go out
once, you're spending god knows how
much. So it doesn't really [ __ ]
matter, you know?
I close the account down. I'm not going
to chase the loss. Um
Yeah. I wonder how my
[ __ ] um how my friend from Scotland's doing.
Yeah. It's never going to change either.
Yeah. It's brutal and it's never going
to change either. Fun fact.
It's never going to change either. I
want out of this life, bro.
It's depressing. I think that's why I
didn't do anything for all them years
cuz I had that house and I was getting
money from the house. So I mean like
yeah you can complain but you're a lot
better off than a lot of people. Um
yeah. So I think that's what always like
kept the spirits up. But yeah when you
get stung like that there's there's no
going back really. But you know and I've
still got money as well.
I've still got money as well. Like it's
not even like you're going to starve or
anything, but you you you tried to go
out [ __ ] once. So yeah,
it's [ __ ] depressing. It is depressing, bro.
I think if you was used to it then it's
more than enough probably for most
single people you know if you used to it but
you know or you may be lost like maybe a
little bit but you know
it'll catch up with you in the end.
Trust me will catch up with you in the end.
Yeah it's depressing bro. Nothing's ever
going to change in a [ __ ] life anyways. So yeah,
it's bad, isn't it? Really bad.
Don't know what to do now. It's bad.
Catching up with you eventually, bro. It
could maybe take like three or four
months to be honest with you of an
income loss. It will catch up with you eventually. So yeah,
it will catch up with you eventually. Definitely. Yeah.
Bad. Bad bad.
I'm not used to all this, you know.
I'm not used to normal life,
you know. I'm not skin like Virgin boy.
Nothing like that skin [ __ ] in a bed
sit. That's the whole reason why Virgin
Boy don't go out. See, with them people,
they're used to that life. You know what
I'm saying? Like Virgin Boy, Lord J cuz
they're [ __ ] skimp. That's why they
never go out. You know, they're used to
that life. I'm not used to that life.
And to be honest with you, I don't think
I will ever be used to that life. So So yeah.
really really really bad. Yeah,
he doesn't go to bars. He goes to
special needs clubs. Yeah. And he
doesn't spend nowhere near as much. And
we're not getting into this conversation
anyways, bro. You know, so yeah,
he's [ __ ] he's [ __ ] skin.
He goes to special needs clubs that are
cheap as [ __ ]
But I thought I just come on here to
vent about this [ __ ] loss. Well,
£100, but you know, still still either
way, ain't it? So, yeah. Yeah.
It's bad, is it, bro?
Bad loss of uh income in it.
I don't think anyone really cared cuz it
doesn't affect them. So, you know,
you should have died in that house to be
honest. You know, when they took the
house, you should have died in the house.
You should have died in the house, bro. Like, [ __ ]
You know, think about it, bro. You live
probably a better life than most people.
So, what you going to do now? Just live
a a [ __ ] normal life.
Like, it's there's no way around it.
There's no plan. I'm probably just going
to eventually kill myself,
you know, at the end of the day. That's
there is no other option to be honest. Cuz
it's no life, you know. It's no life.
All of this [ __ ] you know. It's no life. Yeah.
No, I'm not staying strong. I'm killing
myself soon. [ __ ] that.
And I mean it, bro. I [ __ ] mean it.
You know, before when I when I said
about like the women [ __ ] I was like,
"Oh, whatever and that." But no, [ __ ]
I don't want to be worried about money.
And like I said, to be honest with you, um,
that to the wrong [ __ ] person now.
Um, you know, I know, like I said, most
people do worry about money and people
have a lot less than me, but I don't
want to worry about it. So, if I don't
want to worry about it, then at the end
of the day, that's it.
You really should have died with the
house, bro. I'm not even joking. So yeah,
who knows where we would have been
without the house to be honest. We might
have already killed oursel
probably. Probably would have already killed oursel.
I won't feel different tomorrow.
I won't because the whole money thing is depressing.
That's what it is. It's just depressing, you know.
Obviously, I've got more money than
Virgin Boy and whatever, but they don't
they have [ __ ] lives. They're happy to
live their life skin, you know, [ __ ]
not being able to do anything. You know
what I'm saying? That's not me, bro. It
would have been me if I didn't have the
house because then what else would have I known.
So I feel like
that's a big um
problem, you know.
I work through different tomorrow.
I wouldn't be able to probably go for a
drink now and still save for the money
for Thailand. So, uh, it's depressing.
Very, very depressing.
just about money. It is about money when
you have to worry about money.
So when you have to worry about money,
yeah, it kind of is about money.
It's not about money to an extent like
if you for example don't have to worry
about money then yeah it's not about
money like being a millionaire. Yeah.
You don't need to be a millionaire. You
don't even need to be rich as long as you're stable.
You know what I'm saying? As long as you're stable.
So I'll go out once and I'm basically [ __ ] basically.
I still have money in that, but then
I'll have to make it stretch for a
month. It's dead. So, it's about money when it's
when you know you're not financially stable.
That's that's when it is about money.
That's when life is about money, you know. So,
Yeah, it's [ __ ] It is [ __ ] And I'm
up for I'm up this month gambling as
well. Would you believe it? So Yeah,
but these people seem to do it. Virgin
boy and [ __ ] Kieran, you know,
they seem to do it.
But I never ever like doubted [ __ ] bro.
Like I I knew I was lucky to have the
house, you know? I never ever said like
I was about you and I never have to
worry about money t
that's the only good thing you know it's
what Sig said like oh like you got the
house and whatever now you don't have
the house you don't make money on the
house what really are you living for you
know the situation is not going to get
better so it's like it's obvious now
just like nothing ever gets better you
know what I'm saying it's just
depressing you didn't want to worry
about money that's the problem that's
something you didn't want to
You know what I mean?
It's [ __ ] annoying, you know. So, so yeah,
probably three grand what I was getting before.
Nah, probably about two grand. Maybe
maybe two grand. 1,800.
Yeah, probably about that.
When you're getting three grand a month
and you're not working, mate, you you
realize the sting. You actually
understand the sting, you know. Yeah.
But that's where we're at anyway. So
I'm not explaining it, bro. If you can't
figure it out, then you can't figure it out. So,
yeah, it seems that suicide would only
be the would be the way out.
I said to my mom as well, like when I
was on the phone, like, this is very
serious. I've lost like most of my
income here and she didn't really seem
to care. Um,
and you know, you don't adjust, you
know, not from that much of no, it's got
nothing to do with trolls or anything to
do with these people on YouTube, just
like they've never ever affected my life
ever in any way,
you know. And I was telling her like,
you know, eventually it's going to catch
up on me. You know, you might have lost
some of yours. I've lost most of mine.
and she's like, "Oh, no, they're all
right." But it isn't because at the end
of the day, look, I'm still sort of up
from gambling, you know? We've sort of
still budgeted and we're still going to
struggle if we go out again. I'm not
worried about money, you know, and I
like to go out. So, at the end of the
day, [ __ ] that. Simple.
And it's got nothing to do with these
trolls. These trolls have never affected
my life ever.
But yeah, I'll probably save my life
soon. So, cuz yeah, [ __ ] that. It's a
dead life. Absolute dead life. You know,
if any of these people ended my income,
I would have killed one of these people,
bro. If any of these people was behind,
um, you know, I would have physically
got my hands on one of them and I would
have killed them. You know, I'm not even
joking. Like, it wouldn't even be here.
I anyone that's [ __ ] with me, even if
I couldn't find even if I couldn't find
any of these people that are behind the
accounts, I'll just call out someone
that's been [ __ ] with me
and have it just as good as them. You
know, that would be just as good. You
know what I'm saying? Like, bro, of
course it wasn't these [ __ ] people.
But yeah, I'm ending my life soon. This
is dead. I ain't worried about money,
bro. Other people can do it if they want
to do it, but I won't be doing it. Simple. Yep.
So, that's where we're at.
Nothing's going to change now. See, if I
never had the house and I weren't
getting that income, this is a normal
life for a lot of people, if not better
than most people, you know? But you can't [ __ ]
get that sort of money a month, right?
And then lose that kind of money and
somehow seem to adjust to it.
Unless you have like [ __ ] [ __ ] tons
of savings, and I mean [ __ ] tons, or you
leave like 20 or you lose like 20% of your income.
You know what I'm saying? So,
I probably will just end up killing
myself soon to be honest with you if I
can't figure something out. Well, obviously
And then the [ __ ] cancel took the
[ __ ] house back,
which I should have just killed myself
in the actual house because you've lost
tenants, you've lost food, you've lost
the house, and you've lost money, bro.
You're as good as toast. You might as
well just killed yourself there and
then, you know. But like I said, people
like Laney and other people, it doesn't
affect them. So, they seem to think it's
okay. And it doesn't affect you straight away because
you know it's not um
it takes a while to catch up on you
catch up take 2 months 3 months 4 months
depends how long you will feel you'll
feel it eventually living month to month
with shitty money you know
but they seem to think it's all right so you
cuz it doesn't affect them.
Because it doesn't affect them. You see,
that's probably why you're depressed to be honest.
Yeah. So now obviously I don't have
that. So what is actually the point of
living to worry about money?
Do you know what I'm saying? Like what
to worry about money? I'm living to
what? Worry about [ __ ] money. I'm not
[ __ ] living to worry about money.
[ __ ] that. Oh, [ __ ]
So, yeah. And there's no other way to
make money now as well, which is the
problem we we knew was going to happen, you know.
So, there's no new ways to make money.
It's not as easy as that.
Obviously, it's not as easy as that.
Otherwise, we wouldn't be having the
conversation and we wouldn't feel the
need to actually want to gamble. So, yeah.
So yeah, that's why I'm basically [ __ ] now. So Royally [ __ ] Absolutely roy, you know.
Yeah, but I can't do that.
That's what I'm saying. I I I don't go
out much. I went out on Sunday and it
cost a lot of money.
I don't need to go food bank. I've got
money to eat and stuff. I've got money
to more more than enough money to
survive. But if I go out again
now, when I went out on Sunday, I spent
a I spent a [ __ ] ton of money,
you know, I spent a [ __ ] ton of money. Um,
like couple hundred pound just [ __ ]
drinking. So obviously I won the
football bet and then Yeah. So yeah,
this is a big problem now, you know. So yeah, about Andy.
So, I'm sure most people would have
already killed themselves by now, to be honest.
I'm sure most people would have just killed themselves.
I'm sure they would have.
That's bad bad news.
Yeah, but it's not lucky though. It's not lucky.
It's not lucky because your lifestyle is is being
what's the word? Your lifestyle is being
kindered by it now. Do you understand?
See these people at Red Star and Virgin
Boy, you know, they're they're happy to
to have no life and sit online and be
[ __ ] skint and whatever cuz that's
their life being skint. But it ain't me,
bro. I like actually going out and
having a drink.
Do you know what I'm saying?
No, I'm not thankful. I'm not thankful at all. you know,
not thankful at all, mate.
And obviously, I won't be able to date
anymore cuz I won't be able to afford
it. So, there'll be no going out and
dates and [ __ ] like that because you
just won't be able to afford it.
So, that's uh that's the problem.
But then the way I kind of see it is
you've had that life, you know, you've
done it for 3 years. You was lucky to
have it for three years. You know, it's like
it was going to end one day, wasn't it?
You know, if you think about it, you've
been there, you done it, you worn the t-shirt.
All you do, all you really need to be
doing now is just leaving, which you
wouldn't even be going out anyways. So,
I mean, if you put it that way, I mean,
that's the only positive thing you can
say about it.
Is that like you had it, you've been
there, done it, worn a t-shirt, and that's it?
I three years. I don't know what I would
have done in them three years without
without that house cuz I was like in my
prime and [ __ ] wasn't I?
I was in my prime. So,
God knows I might have ended up I don't
know what the [ __ ] I would have done, bro.
Maybe skin every month.
I don't know. I dread to think, mate. I
dread to think. I actually dread to
think. where I'd be.
I don't know what I would do.
Be [ __ ] Probably. No. Maybe.
I don't know.
I don't know, bro.
So, even if I won like 78 on the pound
today, it would have been good. Would
have been well good for the month.
Still good for the month. I can still
eat. I'm [ __ ] You know what I'm
saying? I just won't be able to go out
and get [ __ ] So, that's the thing. But still,
no. In a couple of days and I think I'll have like
I don't know, man.
No, I've already got it. What am I
talking about? I've already got it. I got like 1150.
So 11 fucking50 and 80 a week, which is like 1,4500
by the end of the month. So, I mean, yeah,
but you know, it's the problem with it
is is that, you know,
it's bad. It's bad. It's bad. It's bad,
bro. It's bad.
I've got all my bills paid and [ __ ]
I've got all my bills paid and whatever, but
the only thing I can think of doing is
starting this delivery job and just
killing these hours. Killing the hours.
Killing the hours. Trying to win a
football bet and sort of build myself up.
I really need to focus on like building myself up
before like going out and drinking and
you know whatever like you I really need
to think about building myself up
and then obviously if you build yourself
up then you know you're fine it is what
it is but
it's going to have to be something like that
if they can't even [ __ ] if they can't
even [ __ ] pays cuz that's what I was
doing with these football bets. I was
building myself up, you see. Um yeah. So,
who knows, man. Who knows? God knows.
And I just thought I was going to put
£100 in because what have I got to lose
if I lose £100?
I might win a couple of thousand. That
was in my [ __ ] mind. You know what
I'm saying? So why not? Why not give it a try?
it ain't good, bro. It ain't good. Well, nope.
I got it to n it went down. Then I got
it to 90 and then
yeah, just miss miss. Same [ __ ] with it.
see if there's no frequent income coming
in, it's a worry, you see,
cuz when you get paid rent, you get paid
on this date, that date, this, so you
know you've always got it coming. you know,
you can't do that with um with this. I mean,
cuz of um Yeah.
So you kind of have to make you kind of
have to make [ __ ] 1,200 lb stretch.
That's so crazy to say that because like
most people don't even have like [ __ ]
300 lb. But still, you know, it's still
you still have to make it stretch for
like a whole month.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
But it is what it is, eh?
is what it is. All right.
What do you think of the situation, Alan?
[ __ ] up in it.
It's [ __ ] up, bro. It
We are [ __ ] aren't we?
But I tried to say to the tenants that
I'm not [ __ ] You're actually [ __ ]
You know, cuz they are actually [ __ ]
Now, you see when I say I'm [ __ ]
right? I'm [ __ ] compared to the life I
was living [ __ ] Like, I'm not going
to starve. I'm not going to go homeless.
I'm not going to, you understand what I
mean? I'm not going to, but I said to
them, "No, you are the ones that
actually [ __ ] because you work every
month and you got nothing at the end of
the month." I can never end up like
that. You know, technically, I can never
end up like that. So at the end of the
[ __ ] day, you know, you are the ones
that are actually fully [ __ ]
cuz I'm wearing clean clothes. I can
eat. I can still, you know, I still have
some money. You know what I'm saying?
Like they are actually [ __ ] [ __ ]
Know what I'm saying? Their whole life
has been [ __ ] since coming to this
country. You know?
Yeah. Yeah. And then if you can't get
money off that, then you're basically [ __ ]
That's what I'm trying to say. If you
Well, then then I am [ __ ] in terms of
[ __ ] like you can't do anything, but
you're not going to
then the only thing would be trying to
win money gambling. And then if you lose
gambling, you're [ __ ] So yeah.
And yeah, if you lose money gambling,
then you're screwed.
So, it's all just you're just [ __ ]
basically, but not the way that they're [ __ ]
You know what I mean? You just won't
ever be able to go on holidays and [ __ ]
which is pretty depressing really. Your
life is limited. So, yeah.
But that's the thing. There's nothing
you can do.
Maybe win the lottery.
Win the lottery. Imagine that.
We're getting a McDonald's craving RN, bro.
I'm getting a McDonald's craving RN.
No, no, it could be worse, bro. How
could my situation be any worse?
After this Thailand thing, I'll never be
able to afford the things I want to do,
you know? So, um,
and even with this delivery thing, I
need to buy a phone cuz this phone's
blocked. So, I'm going to be like [ __ ]
I'd have to The first week is probably
going to be trying to basically make the
money back from what I've spent.
But I mean these things happen, you know, so
I'm not sure.
It's not if I actually go to Thailand. I
am going to Thailand.
So say you wanted to go back to America
or go to Canada. How would you afford
it? You just would never be able to
afford it, would you? No. Never.
I don't think you would. Would you? No. Sh.
You would be fat.
You are [ __ ] We are [ __ ]
All of us are [ __ ]
I've already been to America. So,
I mean, the first time I didn't go, but
I've already been. Yeah,
that's one of them. [ __ ]
I'm going to have to do this thing, I
think, bro. This week I'm going to have to, man.
Yeah, I did go to Jamaica just the first
time I booked it.
Yeah, I'm going to have to do this. Um,
get this out the way. See if it's an
option or not.
And you can't win big. You can't even
win gam you can't even win money gambling nowadays.
You can't even win money gambling. Oh [ __ ]
nowadays. Well, I mean
Well, I mean, you can win on a football. So,
I am suicidal now, but I'm just trying
to distract myself from the fact I'm completely [ __ ] So yeah. Oh,
what a madness.
If I wanted to win big on a football
bet, I'd have to put big on a football bet.
I'd have to put a lot on a [ __ ] football bet.
We have to start the show.
I don't even have a working phone. I
don't even have a proper working phone.
Yeah, I don't even have a [ __ ] proper working phone,
which is madness. Yeah.
Uh, it's probably easier, man.
It's probably easier just to give up in
with life, bro. To be honest with you,
I think it's just easier to give up with life, man.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, but it's not going to win.
Well, it's not going to win. That's the thing.
[ __ ] sake, man.
I'll be skitting like that virgin one
day, ain't it? I'll be skinn like the
Orington virgin one day.
Could you imagine? Eh,
you imagine one day
being skinned by that virgin. Imagine. No
be skinned like that bastard.
Like that [ __ ] virgin. Ain't it?
I didn't be in skin like that. Virgin Aaron.
[ __ ] that, bro.
I think I would just probably just kill
myself, man. I'm not going to lie to you, bro.
It's [ __ ] depressing as [ __ ]
It's too depressing, lad. Honestly,
it's too [ __ ] depressing, you know.
Let me get Yeah,
I pretty much think anyone in my
situation would actually just kill themselves.
I generally feel like they would.
Germany feel like they would, bro. Anyways,
I want to make myself a tea and um go to Yeah. No. Madness, bro.
Well, I'm out of