Yeah, I'm not your friend, bro. I don't
want nothing to do with you anymore.
Yeah. One second.
Hey, listen Liam, bro. I went on L J's.
I actually lost brain cells. Does anyone
else ever feel like that? When you go on
L J's, right, you actually lose brain cells.
Nah, bro. I calm down and realize that
if I went there, he weren't going to
show up. I learned from my mistakes. A a
wise man learns from his mistakes.
And I know exactly what happens. Just
like if I show these people money, I
know exactly what they're going to do.
They're going to run away like they
always do. A wise man learns
from his mistakes.
I think that's fair.
You know what I'm saying? A wise man
learns from his mistakes.
I shot it from Terry. Yeah, I shot it
from Terry. Yeah. Uh, funny no one said
that when I went to Terry's area and he
didn't show up.
Huh? The biasness is real.
The amount of [ __ ] self-reflecting
people right on L J's is insane. You
know what I think these people do, bro?
Do you want my honest opinion? What I
think these people do? I reckon,
listen, hear me out. Yeah. I reckon most
of these people are on benefits
and they um
uh what about when I went to Terry's
area last time and you and he didn't
show up. Suppose you forgot about that
one. Um I think what a lot of these
people do is they gamble all their
benefit money to try and win more and
that's why they never have any money.
And I think a lot of these people um
um a lot of these people um I think a
lot of what these people do they uh Yeah.
Um a lot of these people um I think some
of them work and then they lose all
their money. Stop living in the past.
Oh, stop living in the past.
Huh? Stop stop living in the past.
One second. One second. One second. Hold
on. Hold on. Stop. Stop living in the
past. Greavves. Is that what this guy
just said? Stop living in the past. Or
am I reading things?
Uh, so stop living in the past. Okay
then. Well, stop talking about Prime.
Stop talking about [ __ ] LJ coming on
my [ __ ] door. Stop talking about all
of these [ __ ] women. Yeah, that's
some of them [ __ ] me over if you don't
want to live in the past. So what? You
don't want to live in the past when you
take L's. This is what I mean with this
community, bro. This is exactly what I
mean with these people. These people
constantly live in the past. It's like
they're in a time machine, bro. Going
back. This is what I mean with these
people. This is exactly why I don't
waste my time, bro. This is exactly why
I don't waste my time. You understand
now, Grezy? This is why I don't waste my
time with these people.
This is why I don't waste my time. I had
some salmon for lunch. Greavves. I had
some lovely salmon.
But yeah, this is why I don't waste my time, bro.
It wasn't two days. It was yesterday.
Yeah. You remember all my hours, don't you?
You're not talking about these things,
but you people do talk about these
things. Isn't it funny? Every single
time these people take an L. Oh, don't
live in the past. Don't live in the
past. Don't live in the past. It's like,
bro, it's like earlier when I was on
Large Asia, they were trying to make the
excuse for not showing money because
they didn't have 12 grand. Okay,
you didn't have 12. You know, they
they're full of, you know, with these
people, bro, they're not even worth entertaining.
You know what? Then they're not even
they're not even worth it, bro. I swear
to God, these people are not even worth it.
No. So therefore, it's not two days.
This is what I mean with these people, bro.
Um, is it an L? No, I just couldn't be
bothered to waste my time. It's
something that I didn't do.
What is that?
No, you can't see one P. I have no
money, bro. I'm skin.
>> Yeah, I had some lovely salmon grievy.
Have you ever had salmon or
Yeah, that's the Monty snake that we know. Yep.
Yep. You remember I don't you
>> snake? You PG. I'm not your friend no
more. You're a big snake.
>> You are a snake.
>> You are a snake on here.
>> You see that I'm You see I'm arguing
with somebody and you're getting
involved. What the [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I'm sticking up for the guy who
you're arguing with.
>> Yeah, that's good for you.
>> but you know what's going to happen
again? You know, just people are just
going to turn on you again. So, why even
do this? Why bother?
I'm not I'm only coming at you. I'm not
coming at you because of these people.
If that's what you think.
>> I'm only coming at you again
>> because you called Natalie. I don't care
about these people. Only what I care
about is you calling Natalie and that's it.
>> Okay. Well, let me Okay. I just don't
find that attractive. End of.
>> Yeah. Natalie don't find you attractive either.
>> Okay then. Well, that's that then, is
it? We don't need to argue.
>> That's fine. Is it? But she Yeah, but
the thing is though, she does find me
attractive though. That's the thing.
>> But that's the thing. She don't find you attractive, PJ.
>> Oh, so she never used to come on saying
that. Oh, let's meet. You're cute. No,
no, no. Okay.
>> Okay then. That's in my head.
>> That's in your head.
>> Yeah, that's in my I think everybody remembers.
>> Does anyone remember that? Yeah.
>> So you can read then.
>> What? What? What do you mean?
>> And you're not and you're not my mate
any anyways cuz you never even defend
me. So why would I even be your mate
anymore? You don't even defend me.
>> I'm not always committed to offend you.
You're a [ __ ] man. You call these people
back how you do. Yeah. And you expect me
to stick up for you when you're giving
it on back?
>> So what? They So but they don't start
they don't start me as well.
>> I'm not going to show you. You
do it yourself. You sit on YouTube.
Yeah. You call the [ __ ] out of these
people. So when these people give it,
you expect you get back and then you
expect me to jump on these people with you. That's what
PJ I don't care if the queen started on your PJ [ __ ]
>> Jen likes you. Why don't you go out with Jen?
>> Nah, [ __ ] her, bro.
>> Why not? She wanted to meet you and all
that, didn't she, please? Yeah.
>> I don't like Jamie.
Do you like JD?
>> I don't know. J
off YouTube and last night
you have a lot of skin.
>> EJ, this is what I'd like to say to you.
That would appreciate it. Didn't even
ask you to come down for a night out.
>> You know, I'm sure you're not going to
come to London if Yeah, you did. You
said that if I didn't meet you, you were
going to be done with me. What are you talking about?
>> Yeah, you did. If you don't come down to
London, I mean, if you don't meet me,
then I'm done. Not me. So,
>> so if I end up So what if I end up
skinting? So what if I end up skinting
two months? Are you going to come to
London and help me?
>> AJ, you come down to [ __ ] [ __ ] the big come.
>> Do you know what I'm saying?
>> Not to help me out.
>> I was asking.
>> Yeah, I think that's true. You can tell
[ __ ] is strugg struggling with not going live.
>> I don't want to go live. If I if I want
to go live, I can go and get a new card.
>> These people are actual pedos in this
community in it. What the [ __ ] bro? Why
are you writing [ __ ] like that? I'm not
repeating it again. I'm not repeating
it. What they're saying?
>> Yeah, I've been wearing a bit. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Go on
the free pedo guys.
What do you think of that? The free pedos.
Yeah. What if I end up skinning in like
two three two three uh months?
I'll be [ __ ] won't I? Bonnie's not
going to help me, is he?
No, I won't.
He's not going to [ __ ] help me, is he?
Smells a [ __ ]
It smells a [ __ ] in here.
That's not the real Jane either.
It's Virgin boy in the bed seat. Virgin moment.
I agree with you. I'm going to kick my
mom out the house, bro.
I'm going to I'm going to kick my
[ __ ] [ __ ] house. Some the whole house, man.
Because the government trying to kill
me. You see,
you know how expensive living is. I
actually won a couple of football bets
as well. I actually won a couple of
football bets as well. So, they weren't
even that bad [ __ ] wage for the
[ __ ] month. It's actually mad.
Nothing, bro. I'm just going to kick her
out. Stop. Let the rooms.
They're trying to kill us, isn't it?
This Greavesy. I won some football bets.
I actually This is how [ __ ] up this
is. Yeah. If I was working right and I
was paying rent, I would be [ __ ] I'd
have less than I actually do now, which
I don't even have less money, but you
know what I'm saying? I would because I
actually won a football bet.
You didn't get You didn't get my sublet
money stopped. You didn't get my sublet
money stopped. Keep thinking that. No,
you didn't, mate. I was subleting that
house for 4 years. You didn't get my
sublet money stopped.
I swear to God on my dead dad, none of
these people got my sublet money
stopped. They tried to get my benefit money stopped.
You didn't get my sublet money stopped.
You didn't get it stopped. And bro, I
don't give a [ __ ] I had that money for
4 years. I've got designer clothes that
you can't afford. I banged them in
escorts. I went traveling. I don't give
a [ __ ] I don't really care, bro. Good
for you. And you didn't get my money
shots. You didn't get my money stopped,
bro. You none of these people got my
money stopped. And yeah, go self-reflect
on another. I'm just I'm just saying
that. I'm just I'm not reacting to these
people, but I'm just saying these people
never got my money stopped.
They tried to get my benefit money
stopped two times. Yes.
Like two times they tried to get my
benefit money stopped and they called me
up, but they never got any of my sublet
money stopped. Of course they're
jealous. I'm better looking than them. I
got more money than them. That's why
they go for me every day. So what, bro?
It's fine. I had I had a better life in
four years than you would ever have. I
don't give a [ __ ] I don't give a flying [ __ ] bro.
Yeah. No one cares about you jealous
people. You didn't get my sublet money stopped.
And I've still got more money than them.
No, they're not even married, bro.
They're [ __ ] ugly. skin. Bro, do you
know these people, Jay? They ain't even
got 20 quid to their name. They don't
even have 20 pound to their [ __ ]
name. They ain't got nothing. They're
sat sad, ugly skin [ __ ] that ain't got
nothing in life.
They ain't got nothing in life.
You know what I mean? They ain't got
nothing in life, bro.
Yes, I was moaning because I wasn't
going to get really big fast money
anymore, but I got money. More money
than them. I still got more money than them, bro.
And they never got my sublet money stopped either.
And let's just say that they did, even
though they never, bro, I've been living
a better life than they will ever leave
live. More escorts, more women,
drinking, designer clothes. I've still
got designer clothes. You know what I'm
saying? Like, bro, like they didn't get
anyone's money stopped.
Believe you me, I would be in jail now
if they if they got my money stopped. I
would be in jail, mate.
I'd be in prison. I would. Trust me, bro.
Believe me, man. That's serious [ __ ]
You know, when people try to people when
people try to get people's income stopped, bro,
I would be in prison.
Yeah, they're very jealous of me, Jane.
They they don't I mean, [ __ ] sake,
man. Like, how long are they going to do
this for? And Jane, do you know the
reason why I didn't go to Terry today,
even though I said I was going to go
last night? Because we know what happens,
you know? We know what happens on here. You know,
we all know what happens on here, lad.
You know, you meet you go to meet these
people, they don't show up. Like, how
many times have I beat them at the money
game and they run away?
Like, bro, they're idiots. They're
[ __ ] s They're sad, ugly, hopeless
old people that ain't got a life. They
ain't got a life. They got nothing.
Literally, [ __ ] all. They're talking
about a grand a month. They don't even
have 20 quid to their name. They got nothing.
They're ugly, angry, sorry ass, hopeless
gamblers. That's all they are, bro.
They're nothing. They're literally nothing, man.
Mate, when I was on £700 a month, I had
a better life than these people.
When I had £700, I had a better life
than these people.
Yeah, I shut it, bro. Yeah, you keep
telling yourself that. Yeah, I shut it. Yeah.
Yeah. Why did I? Cuz I was [ __ ] angry, obviously.
Because I was [ __ ] angry.
That's why I said it.
Scared the Terry, mate. He didn't beat
me the first time I met him and the
second time he didn't even show up.
Like, it's like LJ when he was trying to
do this thing today. Yeah. £40. Yeah.
Um, double it, bro. You really think I
don't have 80, 90, 100, three, four, 500
pound? What the [ __ ] man? Come on now. Yeah, exactly.
Yeah. Better looking than them, better
clothes than them. Yeah, that's why they
do this every day, man. It's Look at
that [ __ ] Red Star. How long he's
been doing this for,
you know? And it's the extent they go
down. I mean, if somebody comes on
typing [ __ ] then okay, maybe they just
want a reaction. You know, it takes 2
seconds. But the what the these people do? Yeah.
They ain't got nothing.
I'm going to get a tattoo next month. Anyways,
I don't have loads and loads of money
anymore, but I've got way more than
these people. put it that way. But I'm
going to get a I'm going to get a tattoo
um soon, next month. You've got a better
life than them. You got more money than
them and you're better looking than
them. And it kills them with Ronald Pump signature.
My first tattoo. I've never had a tattoo before.
I was thinking of maybe getting it on my arm.
Like when I was supposed to go to Boston
the first time, I was going to get um
I was going to get a uh
a tattoo of Ted.
Ted with a love heart to remind me of my mama we
bro. Look, let me show you this right here, bro.
Oh, I shouldn't even be showing you this.
Uh, where is it?
You want me to show you this [ __ ] that's
been just just there for ages, bro?
Where is it? That way there. Oh, god.
Clothes. Someone been robbing my clothes, matey.
I'll show you, bro. Haven't been done it
for a long time.
>> One second.
>> Bastard. Why do you think so much being here?
>> Cuz it's funny.
>> I said supposed to go to Boston the
third time if you listen properly. >> Yeah.
>> So why do you snare people?
>> Why do you snare people? Cuz I like snakes. >> Really?
>> Yeah. Do you not like snakes? I like snakes,
>> mate. Listen, Rory. One second here. One second.
One second, bro.
Where's this bag?
Where is this bag of clothes?
Where is it? Where the [ __ ] are them
bags of clothes gone? I'm gonna show you
uh a year's worth of Rory's money right
now. One second. Right now and actually
find these clothes.
Hello then. Are they here? I'm going to
show you. I'm going to show you a year
of your money.
A year's worth of your money here.
Oh, let's have a little look.
Right. Let me show you a year's of your money.
We're going to show you about literally
two bags here right now. They've been
collecting dust. They need to be dry cleananed.
So, we got the sties, Rory, that you don't have
that you can't afford.
Now, to be fair, a lot of these are
collecting dust. Rory, look at all the
things money you can buy that you don't have.
Oh, look at that. You can't afford that.
Woo! Look at that.
I got more money than you. Look at my
clothes. Woo! Another one. It's got to
be like two grand here. These are all
Stone Island jumpers. But Rory,
I've got more money than you. So, you
need to do an extra room.
I've got more money than you. It's not
extra money. I've got more than you.
Hey, that's two grand, bro. Rory, how
does it make you feel that I've got more
money than you and more clothes than you
and you can't show a tenner?
How does it make you feel that you can
never afford them clothes cuz you're on benefits?
You need to give a bigger. Come on.
These are like two grand right here.
This is two grand.
Not to mention the other things. Robbie
can't afford that because he's on benefits. [Music]
Love it. Woohoo. But he can't he don't
have that because he's on benefits.
Okay, Rory, do you want to play the money game?
Hey, Rory, do you want to play the money game?
Hey, are you going to play the money
game or you just going to keep calling yourself skin?
You can't afford damn clothes because
your benefits extra money or no extra money.
[ __ ] hell. So, you're not going to
you're not going to show any money, huh?
Oh, [ __ ] me, bro.
So, you took an L again.
>> You got owned again. You just keep
repeating yourself. I was just showing
them two grand worth of clothes, lad.
Just showing two grams worth of clothes
that need to be dry cleaned.
Rory, I want to
benefit boy that can't show nothing.
Woohoo. That's you.
Extra money. I got extra money this
month and last month.
They're self reflectors.
They're literally self-reflectors.
I've got I've still got more money than
them. These people ain't even got 20
quid to their [ __ ] name, lad. They
ain't even got 20 quid to their name.
They ain't even got 20 to their name, lad.
Bro, listen. I've got more. Bro, I put
the link out. You're just
self-reflecting your life onto me again.
You ain't got nothing. You can't even
play the money game with me. You don't
know how much money I have.
You know, you're on benefits and you
ain't got nothing. So, I don't know why
you keep telling people about extra
money. I've already got extra money this
month and last month.
But guess what? You ain't got no money
cuz you're skint. Woo. That's a proper
woo. That's a Ric Flair woo. You can't
show money cuz you ain't got no money.
So, yeah. Self-reflecting
selfreflecting skinta who's got no hair.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Do you
know what? Yeah. Even if I was on 600
700 pound above, I'd still have a better
life than them. Think about it. I'm
better looking than them. I got better
clothes than them. Think about it, bro.
Even with even with adjustment changes,
I'd still have a better life than them.
Even if I got £700 a month, say you got
700 [ __ ] pound a month, bro. I would
still have a better life than all of
them. They ain't even got 20 quid.
That's why I woke up today and I didn't
even think much of it because these
people ain't even got [ __ ] 2030 pound
in their account. They're all skin.
That's why they sit online
self-reflecting every day because they
they are the ones that have got no
money. They're the ones that have got no life.
Um the jumpers, the Stone Island jumpers.
Stone Island jumpers. Yeah.
Yeah. So, you just going to keep Are you
just going to keep talking [ __ ] in your
skin bedset? Are you actually going to
come on show money?
Are you actually going to Bro, it makes
you warm inside, bro. It makes me warm
inside that I've got more money than you
and I've got better clothes than you.
That makes me warm inside. It makes me
warm that you're old, ugly, and you got
no life and you got no money. That's even worse.
Can I see them? Yeah, you can see them
if you want. Why would it make you warm
and gooey? You're an old man that ain't got nothing.
That makes me sleep. The fact that
you're old and you want benefits and you
ain't got even 20 cookie. That makes me
gooey inside. And it makes me gooey and
lovely that in 3 years. Yeah. Listen.
And in 3 years I've lived that life that
you will never live. It was there to
live that you never had and I've still
got more money than you. That makes me feel lush.
3 four years more money than these
people and I've still got more money
than I've still got more money than
these people. I will sleep well tonight
knowing that I'm not in my 40s and I
ain't and I've got more than 20 in my
account unlike these people. It makes me
feel so lush that they get. And another
thing is right, you know, even when
you've shown these people 6700 pound
before, they've run away. Even then, it
makes me so glad that I'm not ugly skin
and old like these people. I could be
old, ugly, and skinn. Think about it,
Jane. People get losses in life and
stuff, but could you imagine being these people? Old
what the [ __ ] old.
Could you imagine being these people?
Old and ugly.
Okay. So, you want to see uh Yeah.
Anyways, bro, you want to see the You
want to see the You want to see the
clothes? Hey, bomb. You shouldn't talk
like that. At least I'm not skin on
benefits like you.
That makes me lovely, not old, not ugly.
And I'm going to go out Friday and I'm
going to get some [ __ ] something you
can't do cuz you ain't got the money and
you ain't got the looks. So stay tuned on Friday,
you know, it's going to make you even
more gooey that I'm going to do
something that you can't do. So yeah, lush,
right? So you want to see these stone islands? Yep.
It makes me so lush knowing that I'm not
skinn and old. I'll sleep well tonight
knowing that I have that little bit of
hope in life unlike these people like
large age followers and all of these
people. They all sat on YouTube skin. I
ain't got nothing.
Anyways, I'll show you this if you want, lad.
You think I give a [ __ ] about a few bit
of extra money, bro? I've still got more
money than you people. I've still got a
better life than you people. Uh, anyways,
I'll show you if you want. Where's the badges?
>> Oh, they're all here.
>> Oh, you run away again, huh?
shown you money and it made you run
away. We're not going through this
again. You've already been shown money
multiple times. I'm not playing your
silly games again. But I thought I'll
just show this guy cuz he wants to see globes.
Uh, this is this is the one I I had when
I met Izzy. USA Izzy.
No, it's just like this.
I met you, Izzy. The first time I bought this.
Um, I I met her. Yeah. Yeah, man.
It was good, man.
Also, you know, if I make
Yeah, that was the first day I bought
that Stony and then I uh Yeah, my my
bro, your bank balance is zero.
Your bank my your bank balance is zero,
Dad. You ain't even got 20 quid. Uh
yeah, my bank balance will never be the
same again, bro. I've got more money
than you still. So what's your excuse
now? So what's your excuse now?
Um what's the score, Joe? Um that I've
already shown you money before and I
made you run away again. It doesn't work
like that. The game doesn't work like
that, Joe. We're not going round and
round in circles. But guess what? I've
still got more money than you and a
better life than you.
better looking, better clothes, more
money. I actually do as well. I actually
do have more money than them. I swear to
God, bro. Yeah, they they're talking
about money, but they don't know how
much savings I've got. They don't know
anything. They don't even know what's in
my bank account. That's why I said if
you really want to play the money game,
we can play it. You start.
It doesn't matter how much money I've
got. Listen, Joe, let me let me explain
this one more time to all of these
people that are listening, right?
I'm not playing the money game with
these people because every single time
you play the money game with these
people, they don't show you anything, you know?
So why why am I going to play the money
game with you? You haven't beat the you
haven't beat me at the money game
either, Joe. You haven't shown 12 grand,
you know. You show me 12 grand and come
back to me.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm so skinned. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. Yes, you can, Joe. Yes, you can.
Uh, no, I never said I had to £300. I I
use £300 as an example. Anyways, um,
see, I know this sounds mad to you,
Ghosting, but what these people do is
they want you to show them money, right?
And every single time you show them
money, they don't show you nothing. And
then as soon as you put the money back
in the account, they'll start their [ __ ]
up again. Ask here. And this is what
they do. This is why I said I'm not
showing no money. You're not getting any
money out of me because this is just a
way of them self projecting.
I am never showing no money. No Fiverr,
no£10, no nothing. Unless that guy wants
to come in and show it. Yep. You can
call me broke all you want. Yep. You can
keep calling me that. I don't mind.
That's fine. I'm not showing you no money. Simple, you know.
So, bro, listen. Listen.
I'm not playing your games. Sort off.
Sod off. You're not going to get what
you want. You want me to show you,
buddy? So, you could you could all run off again,
bro. I've shown these people ghosting.
Listen. Listen, bro. I have shown them
I'll tell you how much money I've shown
them. I've shown them 6,000. I've shown
them 1,000. I've shown them 2,000.
Um, Red Serious shown uh Yeah. And I've
shown And I've shown 6,000. Good for
him. I've shown a,000, 2,000, 3,000, 6,000, 700,
1,000, 1100. I've shown all different
amounts and every single time they've
all run away. That's why I don't show
them anything anymore because they're self projectors.
That's what they are. They're
self-reflectors. It's a form. It's a
form of a reaction, lad.
Joe doesn't have all this money, bro. If
any of these people had all this money,
do you think they would continuously let
me keep winning at the money game?
You know what I'm saying? Uh,
anyways, you're boring now, you fat ugly bastard. Yeah. What? No.
No. I'm not. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
No. No. No. No. No. I'm not showing you
nothing. I ain't showing you nothing.
And I've just explained why I'm not
showing you nothing. You show me 12
grand and come back to me. You show me
12 grand cash and come back to me. End
the story. I'm having this conversation
again. You show me 12 grand and then
come back to me.
[ __ ] these people are idiots, man. I
swear to God.
They just want you to show money so they
can run away again. Doing they do this
all the time, bro. Like all the [ __ ]
time they do this. Show money. Show
money. Show money. And then when you
show them money, they all run a [ __ ]
way. You know what I'm saying?
[ __ ] off. Stop repeating.
Didn't Prime show me seven grand? Uh, no he didn't.
Uh, no, he didn't show me seven grand. So, yeah.
I don't know what it is with these people, you know?
I don't know what they're trying to get
at. Like, are they trying to say that
I'm skin? Okay, I'm skin. I've got no
money. Keep telling yourself that. Okay,
if you think I'm skin, then keep that's
okay. That's fine.
I'm skin. I'm going to starve,
bro. These people are the ones that keep
bringing it up. I don't give a [ __ ]
about money. They're the ones that keep
bringing money up cuz they ain't got no
money. You know, I'm trying to change
the record and they keep bringing it up.
Okay, I'm skinned. I'm going to starve.
I don't have 10 pounds in my name. I'm
not showing you nothing. If that's what
you want to hear, you've heard it.
I'm not bringing it up, lad.
You know what I'm saying? I'm not doing
this again. I'm not playing these silly
games. [ __ ] sake, man.
Okay. Okay. Well, I'm I'm changing the
subject now. Okay. I'm changing the
You know, this is why you shouldn't just
w you shouldn't waste your time with any
of these people on here.
You know, I don't care either, Ghosting.
They're the ones that keep bringing that
up. You go on LJ's channel, bro. Skin.
Your skin. Your skin. Your skin. I I ask
you, why do you keep doing this every
day? You're skint, you're this, you're
that, you're this, you're that. But all
I'm going to say, I'm not going to keep
going over this, bro. But if these
people weren't skin, they wouldn't be
sat on YouTube every day calling people
that they don't know. So, I'm just
leaving it at that, bro. I'm not going
around in circles. People are bored of it now.
You try to have a conversation, you hear
you're this, you're that. And I told him
like, "Stop looking at your bank balance, lad."
You know what I'm saying? I called
everyone out. I called everybody out
[ __ ] a year ago to show money and and
none of you did.
I don't know why people even go on low
days to be honest. It's just it's a
bunch of 40year-olds that self-reflect every day. Self-reflecting 40year-olds.
Surprised people go on there to be
honest. It's just a bunch of
self-reflectors that never made it.
I don't even I went on there earlier cuz
they kept [ __ ] talking about me, bro.
Someone told me.
Yeah, they they go on about skin. It's
because they're skin themselves. They're
the ones that are truly skin. They ain't
got a pot to piss in, you know. That's
why they talk about other people every day. Yeah.
You know, even if you go on there, the
first word you see is your skin.
Your skin. Your skin. Your skin. Your
skin. Your skin. Your skin. Your skin.
That's what they say. Your skin.
These people are skin.
I don't know why they do this, bro. Cuz
you know when I was on £700 a month, I
used to still live life. I don't know
what what they're obsessing or what
their obsession is with money.
Well, obviously we know what the
obsession is. They don't have money,
obviously. But yeah, just like Joe has
no money. What these people do, I tell
you what these people do. Yeah.
I would say most of these people are on benefits, right?
Um, I'd say most of them are on
benefits, right? And what they do is
every time they get their benefits, they
gamble it away to try to win more money.
And then obviously that's why they call
people skint because they end up
skinting themselves. And I think like
maybe very very few of them work and
then they just gamble what they work for
and then they just call you skin.
That's that's what they do, bro. That's
what they do on it. I'm telling you
that's exactly what they do. You know,
I don't know why they do this, bro.
I don't know why they do this. I I
seriously don't know why they do this, lad.
It's strange. Very strange
at their age.
How can I say your skin?
Um, well, I done a I Well, I done 12
pound on two teams.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Uh, no. I'm speaking about you people
that's been shown money. Listen, bro,
but you people don't even have 20 quid
to your name. So, no, I'm talking about
you people. Yeah, I'm talking about you
people. And I actually went out [ __ ]
twice as well, bro. Yeah, I wanted to
win a football bet because life's
expensive, but you people don't even
have 20, 30 quid. So, no, I'm talking
about you people.
Yeah, like I said, Joe, you was nowhere
to be seen.
Oh my god. You're a [ __ ] idiot, man.
I'm telling you, you people are skinned
because every time I've shown you money,
you've ran away. End of story. If you
weren't skin, you would have shown me
money, but you all ran off. Whatever you
want to say, whatever you want to say,
oh, it's the past. No, no, no, no, no,
no. You've been shown money and I've
made you all run off. Evidence is there.
You're skin. End the conversation.
There's no back and forth, but I'm not
going back and forth and back and forth.
I've shown you all money. You've all ran
away. You can call people what you want.
I don't give a flying [ __ ] I don't
care. My evidence proves that you are the skintans.
You know, we know what you people do.
You run away. And I'm not playing that
game no more where you all run away. You
can go self-reflect on [ __ ] Ly's
channel. You don't do it on my channel, you know.
I'm not playing these silly games anymore.
Most of the people do. Yeah. Not not everyone. Ghosting doesn't.
And another thing is s I'm not your uh
I'm not your mate.
I mean, yeah,
I can go bro even on benefits. I can go
out every week. I just I didn't need to
win more money. I just wanted to win
more money for a buzz. Yeah, virgin
forever and skin. Yeah, you're talking about yourself.
Yep. You're talking about yourselves daily.
Oh, [ __ ] At least the time. Yep. You're
talking about yourselves.
You're talking about yourselves daily.
Virgin skin. That's all you people.
That's why you're sat on YouTube every
day hating cuz you are the virgins and
you asking. That's why you're sat on
YouTube going after people half your age
that you don't know. Yeah. Talking about
yourselves, but you're too disabled that
you don't even realize you're talking about yourselves.
You are the virgins. You let Okay, let's
Should we go by the evidence on here?
Right. Should we go by the evidence?
I've shown the most women on here. I've
shown the most money on here. I've shown
that I'm the best looking on here.
Isn't that a madness? You know,
bro, I don't really care what you say
about yourself or what you don't say
about yourself. All I want to know is
why these people sit on YouTube all day
calling other people skin and then when
they get shown money, they run away.
But still, no one's answered it.
Um, you know, because you got to
understand that everything that these
people do is just self- projecting.
Every single thing they do is self-reflecting.
Self-reflecting their own lives onto
other people every day.
I'm telling you, bro, everything is about themselves.
Skin virgins. Bro, don't tell me about
me being live. You people can't even
take a day off of YouTube.
At the end of the day, you people can't
even take a day off of YouTube.
Yep. Lonely skin and a virgin. Yep.
Story of your life. How I used to
respond to these people, right? It's the
story of their life. Lonely skin and a
virgin. That is definitely your life,
buddy. So, you can keep putting yourself
down. I'm not even going to block you.
Okay? I'm not even going to block you.
You can keep talking about yourself.
Yeah, you it's not funny. I think it's
quite sad you keep talking about
yourself like that.
You know, I don't know why you just keep
I don't know why you keep talking about yourselves.
Lonely skin and a virgin. You're making
me feel bad for you talking about
yourselves, putting yourselves down.
You know what I'm saying? Strange. Hello. >> Hello.
>> Welcome. What's happening?
>> You all right?
What's going on? [ __ ]
>> all, bro. Just chilling.
Just chilling, man. Yeah,
>> keep talking about Why is everyone
talking about money?
>> I don't know why they do it, bro.
They're weirdos, man.
>> You know, I don't know how long you've
been on here, bro, but you know, I've
shown these people serious money on it before.
>> I don't know. I've not been on here
long, you know, about a year.
>> That's what I'm saying, bro. That's
That's what I'm saying, man.
Man, you know what? I need to go back to
Liverpool, bro. Every time I I hear you
talk, it reminds me I need to go back, bro.
>> Yeah, I come here, lad.
>> Yeah. Go for some Guinnesses and [ __ ] in it.
>> The lobster pot, bro.
>> Yeah, I went there before, bro, but it
made me feel a bit ill, you know. Man,
>> it's stinking, lad.
>> Bro, I went I was staying at the Travel
Lodge by the water. Yeah, you know the
water that crosses over to the rule. You
know that Travel Lodge? There's a Travel Lodge there.
>> Yeah, man. by the sea and then I had
like the lobster pot and I brought it to
the hotel but it was nasty man. [ __ ] disgusting man.
>> Yeah. Then where did you stay?
>> The travel. >> Like
>> Yeah. Yeah. And then opposite is like a
it's like the river that goes to the rural.
>> I'm sure it's the R. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> But I've only been Liverpool once
though. I've been like I've only been
once. But yeah.
>> Get any bees?
Uh, I think I got like a few numbers and
that, bro, but I went on a Monday in it.
I went to go see someone, but yeah, I
need to come back on a Saturday. I've
always been wanting to do it, but just
ain't got round to doing it, man.
Expensive, isn't it?
>> I don't know. Ming it.
>> Yeah, man. You want to drink?
>> Don't know. Don't know what I'm doing.
Should come here on the weekend, lad.
>> Will you meet me? I was, >> huh?
>> You met um Harry?
>> No, bro. You know when I Listen, here's
another thing. Yeah. You know when I
went to Liverpool? Yeah. You know, all
of these people you know that McFry cooks at all,
>> bro. When I when I went to Liverpool, I
swear to God, bro, none of these people
were saying anything like at all. Like,
they all went off. Yeah. And then when I
come back to London, they just started
their [ __ ] again. It was a madness. I
swear to God. Mhm.
That's what they do on here, is it?
>> I haven't seen for ages.
No, bro. He's under He's under. >> Huh?
>> Had he brought me on here?
>> Well, you know him in real life.
>> Yeah, man. He was trolling that slug.
So, [ __ ] I just got involved in it.
>> [ __ ] hell, man.
>> Oh, no.
>> Yeah. I'll come back to Liverpool and we
can meet up.
>> Yeah. Daddy showed me um that video was
slug on the bus giving drinks to him and
them kids and I just [ __ ] I don't
like nons I hate nons's lab.
>> Yeah, money's a n as well is it?
>> He's a [ __ ] weirdo and he
>> but I mean he's a [ __ ] wrong you know. Yeah, man.
>> Saying you met him,
>> bro. You know when I was in Bro, you
know when I was in Birmingham last
month, I called him out. You know, he
didn't come out.
>> He still comes on in the big [ __ ]
>> It's a little funny, bro. >> 100%.
>> Heavily disabled and he
>> So, do you work?
>> No, I don't. Just do do a do a few things.
A few drug dealing things in it.
>> Other ways to get money in there. >> Yeah. >> Uh
>> what do you do for work?
>> I don't.
>> Yeah. [ __ ] work, man.
>> There's [ __ ] in it. It's pointless.
But um yeah, don't know. Just come over
here in it. Call out. Yeah, but you
should never meet me if I come in it.
How are you doing, Kieran? Man, you're right.
>> Yeah, but you're not going to meet me though.
>> That's all.
>> You don't.
>> I'm from Hayen. Do you know Hayen? >> No.
So, it's quite rough around here, you know.
It's always like shootings.
One second, bro. Yeah, bro. One second.
What's the [ __ ] bomb?
>> Oh my god. Bro, no one cares about that
money, bro. You've been showing the same
buddy for ages. No one cares. Bomb. And
guess what? That ain't 12 grand. No one
gives a [ __ ] man.
>> Let's have a look. It's not.
>> Yeah. I just don't want him to put nudes up.
>> Yeah, that's good, bro. That ain't 12
grand. Good for you. How much is that?
It's about 10k in it.
>> Not even, bro. And it's not 12 grand either.
>> No one cares. Bomb.
>> Do you know what I would You know what? Yeah. >> Huh? >> Bomb.
>> Bomb. Look at your hands. You're getting
fatter, mate. Well, he says it's him,
but yeah. You're getting fatter.
>> Definitely without getting fatter.
>> Huh? It's definitely not Simmy with that money. >> No.
>> See like Simmy can only show.
>> I think it is. I think it is. Bomb.
>> Get him to talk.
>> But nothing. It doesn't matter. It
doesn't matter though because you've
been shown more money than that bomb. So
you've lost. No one cares. Nobody cares, bro.
>> Nobody cares. >> Huh?
>> You seen Bomb's face?
>> Yeah. He's a [ __ ] ugly bastard, bro.
He's an ugly bastard.
>> He used to be the wor He used to be the
[ __ ] worst self-reflector on here, bro.
>> I don't know him. I don't know anything about him. >> Yeah,
>> bro. No one cares about that. You've
been shown more money than that several
times. Nobody cares. Doesn't bother me.
So, I don't know why you keep flashing
it. And guess what? Let me tell you
something, Bob. You could have all the
money in the world and it won't change
your ugly face and the fact that you're
old. Nothing's going to change that,
bro. No money in the world's going to
change that. And I love it.
I don't know, bro.
Kieran gets £1,100 a month. Bro, the
thing is, right, let me tell you
something, bomb. Yeah,
that doesn't bother me one little bit
here because you've been shown more
money than that. You've been shown more
money than that and you've also Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah. Simple as that.
It's not 10 grand. It's not 10 grand.
It's not 10 grand at all. But here's the
thing, Greavesy. You know, it doesn't
even matter any of this [ __ ] Like, you
know, once you get to a certain amount
of money, bro. Yeah. It doesn't matter.
You know, you do you do realize like
once you're at the stage where you're
financially stable, it doesn't even
matter. You know what I'm saying, bro?
It doesn't kill me. I know I'm better
looking than these people. I've got a
better life than them. I'm not ugly like
them. Do you think I give a [ __ ] what
somebody shows from one month to the
other? Bro, I'm not asked.
Like, I'm not asked in the slightest.
Not even in the stat itis, bro.
What the [ __ ]
Oh my god.
So, at the end of the day, bro, once
you're financially stable, money doesn't
even matter, you know? at the end. I've I've come
I can do it now if I wanted to.
Oh my god.
Once you've got a couple of grand in
your account and you've got a decent Oh, [ __ ]
you got some sort of decent income. You
know what I'm saying, bro? It's that's
it's only if you're skinn like these
people. That's when money matters.
You know, that's it, bro. I could put
£800 on roulette right now if I wanted to,
which I'm not going to obviously, but
you get it. You know what I mean?
You know in them three years right I
done more than bomb will ever have ever
done ever have. You know what I'm saying bro?
Bro listen I'm not going to talk to you
people bro about money this money that
money this money that. Get a [ __ ] grip.
For [ __ ] sake. Where was all of this
money when I was showing you money? For [ __ ] sake.
It's the same thing with these people on
it every single [ __ ] day. Change the
subject. Oh my [ __ ] god.
It's so boring now. You know what I
mean? Yes, you people have got all of
this money. We're skint. Okay, whatever.
You are the ones on YouTube all day
calling people half your age that you
don't know cuz you're rich and we're all
skint. Like, I don't know what these
people want, bro.
You know what I'm saying? [ __ ] I
swear they fry your brain.
It's [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Don't worry
about what other people have.
Yeah. You I was just saying yesterday,
Kieran. Yeah. That like it's [ __ ] that I
used to get three grand a month, now I
get like£1,200 a month. Yeah, it is a bit [ __ ]
But you know, it is what it is, eh? But
then when I look at these people, it
makes me feel better because they ain't
even got anything.
You know what I'm saying? So like, so yeah,
they don't have anything. Then they go
on about other people, but they don't
know what what's in people's [ __ ]
bank accounts. You know what I mean?
Madness, lad. Madness,
bro. You don't get over,200 a month. So,
what are you talking about?
Same thing again. Same conversation
again. This is why you don't see me on
here for like two weeks, Ken. Sometimes, bro.
They these people fry your brain.
Why do they care what other people have?
They've got all of this money. They've
got all of this money, bro.
They've got all of this money,
apparently. So, they should be happy
then, shouldn't they?
It's madness, bro. [ __ ] madness.
They're absolute idiots. Why are they
even comparing people?
Yeah. And And you know what? I'm not
even going to explain that again because
I've already explained it to you, bro.
how somebody would live off 111,200
pound a month. I've already explained it
a million times. This is what I'm
saying. Just worry about your own life.
It's the same argument, Kieran. Every
single time. The same argument every
The whole point is don't even worry
about that, bro. You know what I'm saying?
You go on large A's, they call you SK.
Like just, bro, they're just a bunch of
self-reflecting nobodyies. That's
literally all they are, bro. It is the
same argument every time.
That's why I didn't go on on [ __ ]
That's why I didn't go to [ __ ] meet
that Terry today, cuz it's a waste of time, you know?
Yep. Whatever you say, buddy. You've got
all of this money and no one else has
got anything. Yep. Congratulations.
We're all skin. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
They sit on here with no money trying to
talk about other people's lives. This is
what I don't understand with this place.
They've all got no money. That they sat
on YouTube talking about what other
people have and what they don't have.
And they're like older than us. They're
[ __ ] weird, bro.
sat there with no money talking about
other people. What the [ __ ] bro? You
know what I mean?
Same thing with bomb showing these city
tank throwing shitty money that I've
already shown more than. What the [ __ ]
bro? It's not going to change the fact
that you're old and you're ugly. No
money can change that money. Have you
ever heard of something that money can't
buy? No one gives a [ __ ]
No, I'm not, Aaron, bro.
No, I'm not.
No, not even that, bro. Not even that.
You know what I'm saying, bro? [ __ ]
madness and to think you've never met these people.
I'm not answering your questions. Worry
about your own life. This is what a lot
of these people don't do, bro. Worry
about your own life.
Well, I think Kieran gets the same like
1,200 a month
and the whole place is you're not going
to and and it's like these people need
to worry about their own life.
You know what I mean?
You know, your rent gets paid for.
Once you get £200 extra a week here and
you'll be sorted, bro. If you got
something that pays you £200 extra a
week, that's more than enough with no
rent cuz obviously we don't pay rent.
So, I mean, you're laughing, but if I if
I if I get £200 a week, right, from
something else, then I'm back to exactly
how much I was getting before.
Now, I'm going to wear my blazer. I
think I'm going to wear my blazer
on my thing. Something like that. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm not living with my mom. You
don't know where I live. So yeah,
Kieran, if you got something that paid
like £200 extra
a week, then you're basically
back to the same um same money.
So I don't understand what Bomb's
talking about. He ain't got no money.
The only time he shows money, mate, is
when he's won like a [ __ ] football
bet. He gamble. This is what he does. He
gamles all his money every month, right?
And he tries to win. And then when he
when he wins, he shows how much he's
won. It's [ __ ] pathetic.
[ __ ] [ __ ] pound.
Yes. Out of her house.
Yeah, bro. You need to worry about your
own lives, bro. All of you people have
got all of this money.
You've got all of this money. Your
life's better than everyone else's. Yet
you spend all your life on YouTube, you know.
It's mad how these people have got all
of this money, Kevin, but they sit all
day on YouTube hating on people they
don't know. Wowza,
it's crazy that isn't it?
Oh my god. It's crazy that isn't it? But
they've got all this money.
It's saying madness.
But they sit on YouTube stalking people
they don't know. Wowza. But they got all
this money. It's mad, isn't it?
Hey bomb, you should come in and have a conversation.
You should come in and have a conversation, man.
No, these people are not in the same
boat, Kieran. They don't have anything. You understand?
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that.
Basically, this is a place where the 40
year olds that never made it, they ain't
got no life, they ain't got no money.
They come on here to feel special. Do
you not understand, Kieran? These people
that are sat on here every day, they got
no money, they ain't got no hope, their
lives are over. Why do you think all of
these people that talk to each other are
all all the same? All old, all fat, all
ugly. You know what I'm saying? Why do
you think they do this, bro?
You know what I mean?
And you got bomb showing a shitty 10
grand that's not going to rest them show
that's not going to [ __ ] um do him
the rest of his life thinking that he's
got money and he's got nothing. Just
like most of these people, they've got
nothing. It's madness. And the bomb he's got nothing
cuz what's that? Two months money. Come
on now, bro. You're a bit too late.
A little bit too late, man.
Of course, they have no hope. I was
saying this to L. I said, if me and you
was in the same boat, I've got hope. You don't,
bro. That's like
two months, three months money, bro.
I used to [ __ ] go through loads and
loads of money. It doesn't matter what I
have. You don't believe what people
have. So, it doesn't matter, does it,
what people tell you. You're not going
to believe it.
I've seen this account.
So, yeah. They ain't got no hope.
They ain't got no hope. They ain't got uh madness.
Oh, I'm not going to get into this
again, bro. Listen, worry about your own
life. You're all rich. You've got all
this money. So, good on you. You don't
need to call anyone else skin. You don't
need to call other people.
You've got all of this money. You're all
rich. yet you spend all your life on
YouTube. It's funny that. But anyways,
just move on from it now, bro. We're
having the same argument over and over
and over again.
We're having the same argument over and
over and over again.
There we go.
>> Yeah, bro. No one cares about your
shitty little money that your three
months worth of money. No one cares.
Nobody cares. Stubby hands. That's why I
let you in, lad. Nobody cares.
>> Do you know why nobody cares? Bomb.
Because even if you had a million pounds,
right? You can't get laid. You're old.
You got no money. You got no life.
You're showing money there, bro. But
that's not going to last 3 months. Come
on now, bro. Nobody cares. I've shown
more than that. Nobody cares.
So yeah. No, it is him. It is him.
No, bro. It's not that serious. It's
about 10 grand maximum.
What the [ __ ] And it's not 12 grand.
Nobody cares. It's not going to change
the fact that you're fat and ugly.
Nobody cares. I've shown more than that.
[ __ ] eight and nine. Nobody gives a
[ __ ] That's exactly why I let you in.
Yeah, it's madness. So, yeah,
bro, it's not that much [ __ ] money.
They're in 20s and tens. I've never had
10 grand. No, it's not 30 grand. No, the
[ __ ] it ain't. That's 30 grand. No, it
ain't. No, it ain't.
No, it [ __ ] ain't because he's come
on the account. PJ loses. It is him.
That is nowhere near 30 grand. No, it's
not 45 grand.
What? In 20s? Get the [ __ ] out of here,
bro. No, it ain't. Try again.
Isn't it so mad? If I was showing that
amount of money, they'd say, you know
what I'm saying?
Wow. Isn't that a madness? Isn't it mad?
This is how you know you're wasting your
time with these people. If you showed
exactly the same amount of money, they'd
pretend they never saw it.
You know what I'm saying, bro? It's mad.
It's a madness, lad.
That's actually a madness, to be honest with you.
All right, Kieran, do you remember when
I was showing money? Yeah. And no one
ever said anything about it. Maybe that
one person. This is how you know you're
wasting your time with these people.
You know what I'm saying? This is how
you know that you're seriously seriously
seriously wasting your time with these people.
Yeah. You're seriously wasting your time
with And by you, I mean [ __ ] me, bro.
Of course. You know what I'm saying?
You're wasting your time with these
people. You know what I mean? I I mean
arguing and stuff, bro. Like, we can
come in and have a conversation,
you know what I mean?
They weren't 50s.
They weren't 50s. And I don't even give
a [ __ ] anyways, bro. You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, man. See you, bro.
You know, it's just pointless getting
into any arguments with these people, lad. Madness,
bro, it doesn't matter. I've still got
more money than them.
It doesn't matter, bro. I've still got
Yeah, bro. Listen, I've still got more
money than them, so I don't give a [ __ ]
I'm not asked.
You know, I'm not skint like them.
They've got no money, so I don't give a
[ __ ] what they say about me, bro.
These people ain't even got 20 quid. So,
do you think I give a [ __ ] what they try
and say about me, bro? Come on.
Yep. Think so. >> Yeah.
Kwin, you still got your £400.
You still got your £400, bro?
Madness, isn't it? Madness deleted.
What are you going to do, bro?
I ain't nowhere near loaded, mate. I
[ __ ] wish I [ __ ] was. But I'm not
skin like these people.
>> I just can't. So you're not going to talk?
>> You going to talk or what?
>> So you're not going to So you're not
going to talk?
>> You going to talk?
>> Okay. Are you going to talk?
Not one50 to be seen.
Not one. Look at them10. Look at all
the£10. That's what Virgin Boy does.
Look at all them£10 notes. [ __ ] hell,
mate. That's hilarious, bro. You really are funny.
>> Clap. Clap. Yeah. Good, man. There's
literally not one I didn't even notice,
bro. There's not even one 50 note there.
>> Bro, that's 100% bomb. Look at his bedset. [Music]
>> What the [ __ ] lad? [Music]
>> That's definitely the fat bomb.
>> So, you don't want to talk? No.
You see this bomb? Yeah. You know, he
actually could have won, you know,
>> you know, you know, you know this bomb
could have actually won, but he [ __ ] himself up
>> really badly.
You still pretending that you've
traveled to places.
>> Doesn't even talk.
That cunt's never left these [ __ ]
beds. Sit, matey.
>> And let me tell you something, right?
There's actually quite a few ways to uh
get money. What the bum's showing? Yeah,
there's actually Do you know what he's
probably done, bro? 100. It's It's quite
easy to be honest with you.
>> Anyone could actually work it out.
Nice10 notes, by the way.
>> Nice 10 pound notes, matey.
>> 45 grand. 45 grand. My [ __ ] ass. [Music]
Bro, why are you getting happy showing
the same amount of money? No one cares
about that. And there's not even one 50
note there. Look,
>> Bob ain't got 50s. You ain't got 50s,
have you, Bob? Like Peter Belly have
has. You ain't got 50s, do you, mate?
You ain't got no 50s. [Music]
>> You ain't You ain't You ain't got 50s,
do you, lad? Nah, you ain't got 50s.
>> You ain't got 50s.
>> You ain't got no 50s, do you?
>> You ain't got no 50s, do you, mom?
Yeah, it's about It's about five grand
cuz I remember when I had it all in
notes, tens, 20s. You ain't got [ __ ] all, mate.
You ain't got nothing.
So, you going to talk or what?
>> Are you going to talk or what? [Music] >> Nope.
I'm not going to let him in if he's not
going to talk, bro. He just keeps
showing the same couple of thousand. Oh
my [ __ ] god.
Uh, he's not talking, bro. It's annoying as [ __ ]
No, it's nowhere near It's nowhere near 30 grand. It's about
probably about four grand, five grand
cuz I had a w like that before when I
kept everything in cash.
It's nowhere near 30k.
Nowhere near 30k. Oh [ __ ]
plenty of behavior.
>> Yeah, man.
So, what are you going to do when you
get paid again, Kier? And you're going
to lose it all. [Music]
You're going to lose it all, lad. Having. Yeah, man.
That's nowhere near over 20 grand. Yeah,
you need to pack that gambling in, Kieran.
You need to pack it in, laddy.
Nah, bro. I'm good. Thank you very much.
No, I'm all right.
I'm all right, mate.
I'm all right, matey.
One of five player. Yeah.
This is what I mean. How biased they
are, Kieran. You see what I mean with
these people? This is why I don't waste
my time. This is why I don't waste my
time arguing with these people, bro.
Usually, but today was an exception.
But you see what I'm saying, bro? This
is what I mean by they're biased on here.
That's why there's just no point with
them, you know.
No point, lad.
Literally no point with these people. No point.
They're all They're always going to be like this.
Isn't it mad how Terry hasn't come on?
Uh, madness, isn't it? Yep.
Bomb's never been to America in his life.
Bomb said a lot of things. Bomb also
said that he's got children. Bomb says a
lot of things.
Bomb says a lot of things, matey.
Yeah, he says a lot of things, don't he? Well, yeah. Yep. What?
Bomb's never been Thailand. Never. And
he's never been to America either.
Never been to America. I never been anywhere.
[ __ ] hell, man.
Yeah. No more Monty, man. By the way,
he's a snake.
No, I had salmon.
No, I had salmon, mate.
Virgin boy ain't got no money.
He ain't got no money. Virgin boy got no
Where's your money, Virgin boy?
Where's your money, Virgin, boy? Get
your money out for the lads.
Get your money out for the lads.
Get your money out for the lads. You
ain't got no money.
Virgin boy ain't got no money.
Virgin boy. Virgin boy. Virgin boy.
Where's your money?
Where's your money? Virgin boy.
Where's your money, Virgin boy?
Where your money, virgin boy?
>> So, you going to talk or not?
>> You going to talk or not?
>> Is this supposed to be affecting me or
something? Is he just trying to like I
don't get it. Uh, nobody cares.
You know what your little bedset looks
like? It looks like one of them brothel
bedsits. You know when you go and you
[ __ ] the escorts and the brothel?
I swear that's I swear that's what it
looks like, bro. Like, you ever been to a brothel?
Looks like a brothel, bro. Virgin B. Virgin boy.
All right. Bomb. Do you want to play the
better looking game?
See who's better looking. Do you want to
play the better looking game boy?
No, I want virgin boy on there. Virgin boy.
I mean, yeah, man. Might as well. It
Let's do two of them. [Music]
What the [ __ ]
>> Mom, are you still trying to call people
ma when we've seen your face already?
Oh, the definition of disabled.
>> What the actual [ __ ] bro?
He tried He tried to call me a M when
we've actually seen his face.
Go away, bomb. We want Virgin boy.
We want the rat face [ __ ] in the bedsit.
We want the rat face [ __ ] in the [ __ ] bedsit.
We don't We don't want you, mate. We
don't want you.
We want the skint [ __ ] in the bedsit.
The virgin boy.
Right, mate. All right. We want Virgin
boy. We don't want you la
cuz you don't talk.
I don't know why people on here have to
pretend like they've got loads of money
like you know L J. And
why do they pretend that they have money
when they have [ __ ] all?
It's crazy, bro. Yeah. Yeah, bro. What's doing?
If he tries to join a virgin boy, boy, I
can come up
the skin [ __ ] in the bedit.
The skint virgin in the [ __ ] bed, mate. Yeah. Virgin boy
Get bing boy.
Why don't virgin boy come up?
>> I saw you and I thought you was kind of cute.
>> Oh, you're sad, aren't you?
>> He's married. Oh, so what you do?
>> Yeah, man.
There you go.
That's two I've done. I don't know if
you know the first one, but I've done two.
>> Bye-bye now, weirdo.
I love how you're watch. Oh, that's
another thing, bomb. You can never cold
approach. That's another thing you'll
never be able to do is cold approach.
Yeah. Another thing that kills you. You
can't cold approach.
could you imagine bomb cold approaching, bro?
Could you actually imagine, bro? [ __ ] hell.
That's a madness, man.
right? What does the ver what did virgin
boy say? Hold on, let me just read this.
Clothing is an asset. Unless you have
something like a jacket that belong to a historical
figure and it's worth thous you'd be
lucky to hear a secondhand store50 eBay.
That's for now 12 grand. That's
realistic. Normal people that aren't
drug leaders do not have 12 grand. I've
already explained this a million times.
I've already um explained this a million
times. If you don't have 12 grand, you
can get it out of the bank. They're
making this [ __ ] seem impossible because
they don't have it, right? And then he
then contradicts himself as the mon
have in the house in their bank account.
Sure. A bank isn't even going to let you
withdraw that much money. Yes, it would.
Of course, a bank is going to let you
withdraw that amount of money. It's your
money. They're going to ask you a
fuckload of questions. See, this is what
I mean with these people. It's just
excuses every time.
Um, a bank isn't going to let you
withdraw that money. You'd be asked a
lot of questions and red flags would be
raised. A big nose [ __ ] You are. You
are a [ __ ] You ugly ratfaced.
Live in a bro. Mom's spare room. Bro,
you live in a bedsit.
You live in a [ __ ] shitty council bed
[ __ ] with no bed in it. What the [ __ ]
And you know, and you've never shown 14
grand. You're not rich in your little
bedsit. And then you're saying 14 grand
and some chains once. It was my money
put with some of my It was my money put
with some of my dads. I showed it all in
cash in old notes. I know many of you
remember. No need to keep going on about
it. No normal person has thousands lying
about their name Skid Morren. Listen,
bro. You've never shown £14,000 in your
life. You skint [ __ ] in a bedsit, right?
Listen, you skint [ __ ] in a bedsit,
right? You've been shown multiple money
different times, right? In your shitty
skint bedsit. Shut. Right. Let me do a
video to this [ __ ] One second, bro. Let
me reply back. You know,
right? Listen, for [ __ ] sake, I'm
going to do a video to this this [ __ ]
skin [ __ ] in his virgin bedset. Knock
some [ __ ] sense into him,
right? [ __ ] hell, bro. I can't
believe it with these people. Listen,
and another thing, you've never shown
£14,000. Cuz if you was going to show £14,000,
[ __ ] boy, you wouldn't have ran off
when you got shown six grand. And we're
not just talking about six grand. You
[ __ ] ratfaced toothless [ __ ] in a
shitty bedsit. There's no point trying
to throw out insults when you know
you're not gonna win with me, but you
[ __ ] trampy shitty clothes in a
shitty skin bedsit with no money in it.
Don't [ __ ] even try to [ __ ] talk
about [ __ ] You know what I'm saying?
How do you think people buy a [ __ ]
car, you [ __ ] [ __ ] if you can't
[ __ ] withdraw 12 grand, you [ __ ]
skin bastard. How the [ __ ] do you think
people buy cars with places that only
accept cash? You [ __ ] Of course, if
you wanted to withdraw your own money,
you skinned bastard. They would let you.
What the [ __ ]
is this guy for real?
They'll ask you a lot of questions. Yes,
I want to buy a car would be one of
them. You know, it's not going to they
won't they wouldn't let you. You [ __ ]
in c in a shitty bed sit with shitty
clothes, right? People buy cars in cash.
Yeah. They'd ask you questions. Yeah.
And it might take a week to get your
money. Yeah. You You won't get the money
straight away, but they will give you
your money. It might take a week. It
might take a couple of days. I don't
know. But I'm sure if you wanted your
own money, you can. Stop making excuses,
you stupid little skinned [ __ ] in a
shitty little skit bed with no bed in it.
[ __ ] skin [ __ ] bastard. You know
what I'm saying? Stop [ __ ] talking
You know, you [ __ ] skin [ __ ] with no
bed in it. Go get yourself a [ __ ] bed
before calling people skin. You [ __ ]
little [ __ ] If you put your money and
your disabled fat, ugly girlfriend's
money together, I'd still have more than
you. Get yourself a [ __ ] bed before people.
What the [ __ ]
You're going to sit there and you're [ __ ] shitty.
Little What do you mean? Why would
people do it just for YouTube? Because
you're asking people to show you money.
We're having the same argument over and
over and over and over and over again.
Virgin, stop it. Listen, the reason you
would do it is because you are starting
on us. You are asking us to show you
money. We are showing you money. We're
asking you to show us money. Are you a [ __ ]
I mean, I swear these people have got
down syndrome. I'm I swear these people
have got down syndrome, bro. Honestly,
they don't understand.
>> [ __ ] hell. I swear arguing with
retards, it really fries your brain. I
actually think these people have got
down syndrome. I genally [ __ ] do.
Yeah, if he wants to come back, he can
come back, bro.
[ __ ] madness. I I swear to God, I
think these people are actually disabled on here.
What do you mean? Why would you do that
all just for YouTube? Because you're
asking us to show you money. Why should
we have to show you money then?
>> Why do you keep asking us to show you money?
>> Mhm. Let me do a video to this skint
[ __ ] with the ugly rat face. [ __ ]
this [ __ ] in these shitty little [ __ ]
gay beds trying to call me skin. In his
shitty little bedsit with no money in it
trying to [ __ ] call me skin.
this little fat [ __ ] with a this little
stupid [ __ ] with a fat ugly girlfriend.
You're going to sit there in your no bed
little shitty little council bedsit with
no bed in it when you don't even see
your mom and try and tell me who I live
with in your shitty little skin bedset.
Your virgin bedsit. [ __ ] [ __ ]
dographs on me. You silly little rat
face [ __ ] You've got all of this money,
mate. You got no [ __ ] teeth in your
[ __ ] head. You wearing charity shop
clothes. You ain't got a bed. How the
[ __ ] can you talk about anyone?
You [ __ ] skin [ __ ] on £1,000 a
month. Who the [ __ ] are you talking
about, bro? And yes, I can say that cuz
I didn't get £1,000 last month and I
didn't get £1,000 this month.
So yeah, I can actually safely [ __ ]
say that, bro. And guess what? I
probably won't next month fever, you know?
So, I can actually [ __ ] say you
actually [ __ ] say that to be honest with you.
You know, you've never shown 14 grand,
you silly little bastard.
You know what I'm saying?
What? Because [ __ ] What? Because I
can't resell Stony Jumpers. I'm not
selling re I'm not reselling Stony Jumpers.
What the [ __ ] We're not selling the
jumpers. We're showing what you people
can't afford. What the [ __ ]
No, it's more than £200.
You absolute skin little virgin. You've
never shown [ __ ] 14 grand, mate.
You've never shown nothing, virgin boy.
£14,000. You've never had £14,000 in
your skin life. Stop [ __ ] making up
stories, you virgin.
I'm going to do a video back to that as
well. You're [ __ ] going to sit in
that cancel [ __ ] bedsit with no bed in
it. Bro, listen. I would happily rather
live with a parent. I would listen, I'm
going to I'm going to try and get this
through to this content. I would rather
live with a parent in a bed than live in
a cancelled bedit that ain't even got a
bed in it. I would rather live with a
dad. I would rather live with a mother
than live in a [ __ ] council shitty
bedsit outside of London. I would rather
live with a parent, one individual
parent. Yes. To live in your virgin
[ __ ] [ __ ] council [ __ ] bedsit.
We're not reselling the stonies. We're
showing what you people can't afford.
We're going by each other's lives.
Do you understand?
At the end of the day, you got no
[ __ ] bed. You wear shitty clothes.
You didn't go on holiday till you was
30. Who are you to talk about anyone being skinn?
You silly little lanky [ __ ] Who the
[ __ ] are you to [ __ ] start coming on
here talking about people [ __ ] being
skinned in your [ __ ] [ __ ] bedsit when
every single time you've ran away when
you've been shown money? Get the [ __ ]
out of here, bro.
We're not reselling our stuff.
We are not reselling our stuff.
We're not reselling our stuff. You skint
in a bedit. Right. And I'm going to and
I'm going to clear this once and for all, lad. Yeah,
we're not reselling our jumpers. We're
showing what you skint people can't
afford. One of two of them jumpers would
have actually got you a bed.
And yes, a bank is going to let you
withdraw that much money, but you'll
just have to wait probably about 3 4
days. Oh, but why should you have to do
that for YouTube? Or why should we have
to keep showing you people money then?
You know what I'm saying? You [ __ ]
ratfaced toothless [ __ ] ugly [ __ ]
Watch what watch this video I'm going to
do on you, bro. Watch this video I'm
going to [ __ ] do on you. And then you
contradict yourself by then showing that
you got 14 grand. So if you show 14
grand, why did you have 14 grand then?
That doesn't make any sense. You're such
a low IQ [ __ ] thick. You're thick as
[ __ ] You're you're thick as pig [ __ ]
Fatter than your [ __ ] girlfriend in
the [ __ ] mind. Do you know that, lad?
You know that
you need [ __ ] hell, bro. You're
thicker than your fat ugly girlfriends
as [ __ ] You're a [ __ ] idiot. You're
an absolute [ __ ] [ __ ]
You [ __ ] ugly rat face with no teeth.
You ugly rat face with no teeth with
your greasy shitty hair and your fat
ugly girlfriend going to sit on here and
try and tell people that you're [ __ ]
Do you know what I'm saying, bro? Yeah.
Come on. come on the panel. You're
[ __ ] skinned little [ __ ] with a
fat ugly girlfriend. We've got We've got
[ __ ] We've literally got Yeah.
nicknames for each other. He's my He's
to me is big nose. Mine to him is the
rat face, skin ugly [ __ ] with a fat ugly
girlfriend in the bedset. That's our
little That's our little nickname for
each other. The ugly [ __ ] with a rat
face with no teeth in the bedset. That's
that's that's that's my that's me to him.
That's me and him, lad.
The skin ugly with a fat ugly
girlfriend. Now, I know I might get a
bit personal here, son, but um yeah,
New York [ __ ] Listen,
about 12 grand is not even re is not
even realistic. He's going on like it's
a million pound. What the [ __ ] Casinos
pay people 12 grand, 15 grand, 16 grand.
And I think they pay maybe up to 20 grand. [ __ ] madness.
Don't sit there in your council bedsit
trying to tell people who they live with
when you're the one in your council
[ __ ] I would rather live with my mom
than live living in your live live how
you're living in a shitty bedsit with a
[ __ ] disabled [ __ ] I'd rather live
with my mom. Well, I don't even live
with my mom anyways, but I'd rather live
with my mom than live in a council
bedsit. Who are you to talk about
somebody living in a spare room
when you live in a [ __ ] bedsit that
you wouldn't even take anybody to? What the [ __ ]
And I never once said clothing I never
said clothes is a [ __ ] asset.
I never said clothes is an asset. What the [ __ ]
You've literally never ever ever shown
14 grand. You skinned little bastard.
You skinted little bastard. You have
never shown 14 grand in your [ __ ]
whole skint life. In your whole lanky
virgin life. You have never shown
£14,000. Why do you keep lying?
We have literally
seen everything that you've done. You
have never shown 14 grand.
You never shown 14K ever in your life. I
know all the people on here that show money, right?
Like years and years ago. Mr. Bomb. Um,
uh, who was the other one?
There was another [ __ ] that did
it as well.
And I think Daz, I think they're the
only ones that have shown money. You've
never shown, you have never ever shown
money in your virgin life, in your skin
virgin life. And you've been shown and
you've been shown different amounts of
money multiple times. You ratfaced ugly
[ __ ] in a shitty bed sit with no bed in
it. [ __ ] going to try and tell me who
I [ __ ] live with, you silly little
You've never shown £14,000 ever.
Stop contradicting yourself as well cuz
firstly he says, "Oh, no one has 14
grand. No one has 12 grand." Then
apparently he said that he shown 14
grand. So make it make sense. You've
just said the average person doesn't
have 12 grand. And you go on to make up
the story that you've shown 12 grand.
You've never shown You've never shown 14
grand. I remember every single person on
here that's shown money.
Literally every single person on here
that has shown money. You've never shown
You've never had bar grand in your life.
Skin boy, listen. Are you Are you
forgetting right that it took you till
30 years of age to go abroad because
that was the age you was when you could
finally afford it?
You [ __ ] skint bastard living in a bedsit
>> trying to talk about people's living
conditions when he's living in a bedsit
with no money and you're and you're
trying to talk about other people. What
the actual [ __ ] Why don't you actually
move into a house and and move out of
your bedsit before talking about other people?
You stupid lanky [ __ ] You lanky skinned virgin.
ain't got a life.
He's so full of [ __ ]
The only person that is skinn is yourself.
You live in a bedsit. I don't understand
how you can sit there
and literally go on about where people
live when you live in a bedsit. I I
think that seems to like go over your
head. You literally live in a bedsit.
You literally live in a bedsit. You've
got a girlfriend that is disabled and
you're trying to talk about other people.
You're 30 and you're with a disabled
girl and you've had to stalk all of my
sloppy. Bro, where are we actually going
with this back and forth thing? Because
no one's ever really going to meet each
other. It just seems all redundant to
me. You've never shown 14 grand in your
life, Virgin Boy. And I'm going to do a
video on this as well. Um there's I
don't understand the whole back and
forth. We I'm a bit lost here now, bro.
Like I don't understand. Yeah. The point
of just going back and forth and back
and forth and back and forth. We're
going round and round in circles. No
one's ever going to meet anyone. So, I
think it's best we should just meet each
other or just stop going at each other,
you know? Hey, what about you, Barry?
You need to get a job. Hey, what about
you, [ __ ] You also need to get a job.
Like, we need to we need to like stop
going back and forth because it's
ridiculous here because you're saying
something, I'm saying something. You're
never going to meet anyone. So, don't
you think you should just leave it now?
I'm 30 and I've literally been with more
women than you have ever had hot dinners
and I have had a girlfriend. What the
[ __ ] are you talking about? How many
times have I actually met someone,
mate? You have to go for disabled girls.
I don't know how the [ __ ] you why you
keep coming on here trying to preach
about other people, bro. You're living
your worst life. Like, at the end of the
day, yeah, people can come on here and
try and [ __ ] judge about me, you know?
And then he's saying, "I've never shown
14 grand in my life." Mad thing is, it
mostly wasn't even my own money. It was my dad's.
Exactly. Because your skin. And you've
never shown 14 grand, even if it was
your dad's. Because everybody remembers.
I don't understand the whole point of
this. You What? What is the point of
doing this every single day?
You know what I'm saying?
I'm 30. I'm almost 30. And I've had the
women that you wish you could have that
you [ __ ] probably wank over every
single [ __ ] day. You silly little
[ __ ] You're with a disabled girl
and I've also had chances to be in
relationships and I've actually already
been in a relationship again. You like
to forget things. What the [ __ ] You're
the one that tried getting with all of
my sloppy [ __ ] seconds [ __ ]
stalking them and [ __ ] [ __ ] What the
Hey Barry, you're involved as well.
You're you're involved as well. You're also autistic.
There'll be three of us.
Then you're saying that you're showing
your dad's money. But you just said that
no normal person has 14 grand. So make
it make sense, Virgin boy. Is it? It's
one or the other. What the [ __ ]
Madness, isn't it? Absolute madness.
Yeah, there is autism in you, buddy. Of
course there is.
I've [ __ ] been with women that you
wish you could get with. Everyone's seen
you [ __ ] messaging people and [ __ ]
I've been reading your comments
and I actually have had a girlfriend and
I've met women several times as well.
And even if I didn't have a [ __ ]
girlfriend, bro, you're you're with a
disabled [ __ ] girl.
What the [ __ ]
What the actual [ __ ] What are you on about, bro?
One second, bro. I'm going to do a video
to this little [ __ ] Holes everywhere and [ __ ]