[ __ ] hell, man.
[ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] spastics
keep defending women. That's all they [ __ ] do,
bro. It's all they [ __ ] ever do.
It weren't going to be long until that
word was said, incel. They've got
nothing to call you. They've got nothing
else to call you because they got no bad
words to say about women. All they do is
stick up for him. Now, what I'm going to
do now is I'm going to post as a [ __ ]
woman moaning about men. And let's see
if people keep blaming me when they
think I'm a [ __ ] woman. Let's see if
when I'm a [ __ ] woman, these people
are going to start think they're going
to start blaming me.
Yeah. Let's see if these [ __ ] going to
start [ __ ] blaming me.
All they do is [ __ ] defend women. I'm
I'm going to post I'm going to post as a
woman complaining now in about 10
minutes. I'm going to post as a woman
complaining on this Reddit and we'll see
if people start blaming me when they
think I'm a woman. Let's see if when
they think I'm a woman is people going
to start blaming me. [ __ ] off, man. Get [ __ ] you
know. [ __ ] off, man. [ __ ] right off.
Yeah, you're blaming all women, but yet
they're blaming you. They sit there
blaming you for being a man. Just like
if any other man was to come on the
internet and complain, they would get
blamed for being a [ __ ]
man. You know, all they're interested in
is blaming you. Not helping you, blaming
you. And this is what all of these
videos are about. The dating app videos,
the approaching videos, there's nothing
wrong with them. There's nothing wrong.
But they love blaming the man. They get
a kick out of it. This is what I'm
saying, bro. If you was a woman
complaining, they would all feel sorry
for you. They're sexist. They're
everything that they call incelss. They
are literally everything that they call incels. They're
hypocritical, you know.
Yeah. There we go, bro.
Where you got that?
Yeah, same with me as well, bro. They have
no [ __ ] annoying man. All they do is
defend women. That's all they [ __ ]
do. Literally, bro. It's all they [ __ ]
do about this as
well. He said he had the [ __ ] same
problems as well.
Here we go,
bro. It's all to do with them
[ __ ] [ __ ] hate them. I [ __ ] hate them, bro.
I swear to God I [ __ ] hate
them. Yeah, [ __ ] Reddit. They're
blaming me again. Ghosting. All they do
is blame the man that struggles. That's
all they love to do is blame men. Blame
the man that struggles. Blame the man
that struggles. That's all they love
doing. That's all they love doing on
Reddit is making excuses for them. Man,
I know I'm right, bro. I know I'm right
when it comes to these [ __ ] in this
country. These [ __ ] women. I know I am
[ __ ] right, bro. Like, I would bet my
whole life on it, you know? Listen, I
bet my You laugh at yourself. [ __ ] off,
you little virgin. But, bro, I know I'm right. You
know, well, that's it,
bro. I'll probably just end up doing
myself, bro. I think this is this is
enough to drive anyone to do themsel in.
It is enough to drive anybody to do
themsel in, bro. Like, no [ __ ] bro. I'm
not even joking. Like, it's depressing
enough like every single day thinking
about it. Like, I swear to God, bro.
It's enough to drive anyone to death.
I'm not even joking. I swear to [ __ ]
God. I've already fell out with my mom
because of it now for probably more
months. Is that not enough? Because of
these [ __ ] And when you have people
keep defending them, defending them,
defending them, comparing and comparing
and comparing, you
know, [ __ ] off, you know? [ __ ] right
off. I [ __ ] hate them. Do you not
understand, bro? You seriously seriously
not [ __ ] understand? I hate them. I
hope they all get raped. Them and their
kids, cuz I was talking about [ __ ]
people's [ __ ] kids on [ __ ] YouTube, bro.
You know, I was talking about people's
kids and she said, "Oh, don't contact me
again. I don't like what you're saying."
Yeah. This is because of women. Yeah.
[ __ ] scumbag. They all need [ __ ]
raping. It needs to be legal, mate. Them
to be raped. They're [ __ ] evil, bro.
Yeah. And what they do is [ __ ] mad.
Yeah. And what they do is mad. And what
they do is also [ __ ] mad. But again,
no one's got an opinion on it cuz they
all defend them. That's what I'm saying.
because they all [ __ ] defend them.
They all [ __ ] defend women. It
doesn't matter what [ __ ] platform you
go on. All they do is lick their ass.
There's no way of you changing their
[ __ ] minds, bro.
[ __ ] mad it is, bro. I swear to God,
it's driving me mad, you
know. Yes, they are all [ __ ] bad. All
women are [ __ ] bad. All women are
scum. Read my lips. All women. All women
are scum. All of them, bro. Yeah. Do you not understand
me? All of them. All of them. They are
all like that. Do you
understand? Yeah. And I've dealt with
more of them than anyone,
bro. Yeah. And they are all like that.
They're all [ __ ] scum of the earth.
All a L. Yeah. [ __ ] me, bro.
The [ __ ] madness it
is. No, it does [ __ ] wind me up, bro.
It does [ __ ] wind me up, bro. It does
wind me up. And it winds me up that they
can get whatever they want when they
[ __ ] want. That's what [ __ ] winds
me up, bro. That's what [ __ ] winds me
up. Yeah. [ __ ] off with your stupid
little comments, you little [ __ ]
Yeah. Go and f You're a gay one, man.
You [ __ ] off with your stupid little
comments, you little [ __ ] You are
gay, you [ __ ] Yeah, how about that
one? You are You are the gay [ __ ]
already. How about that one? You're
already gay, you little [ __ ] [ __ ]
defending women about not all women. It
is all [ __ ] women. [ __ ] them. Hope
all their kids get raped. Them and their
kids. I hope they all get raped and
miscarriages. All that great stuff. All
that lovely stuff. I hope they all get
miscarriages and get the baby kicked out
of them. [ __ ] get raped all of them.
Every single last one of them. You know
what I'm saying?
Like, yeah. Yeah. Maybe, maybe, maybe,
maybe, maybe. But I can't How can I be
spoiled because I've never been spoiled.
So, I mean, how how could I technically be spoiled? Huh? Go
on. No, no, no. I'm sick of how women
have has this [ __ ] how they how easy
they have the dating game. That's what
pisses me off, bro. That's what pisses
me off. Yeah, that's what pisses me off,
lad. They always defend them. People on
Reddit, people on YouTube, they all
defend them. They all defend these
[ __ ] They all defend these [ __ ]
No, it's not why I don't get what I
want. No, no, no. It's not about getting
what I want. I don't want anything. I'm
pissed off that they can get whatever
they want whenever they
want. You know, that's what pisses me
off. I [ __ ] hate them. I hope them
and their kids get raped. Literally, I
hope them and their kids get raped. And
I said it to Elaine as well. I don't
care. I hope their dad rams their dick
down their child's throat. I hate him. I
hate him. You don't understand. I hope
they all get raped. All of them. I
swear. Yeah. Good. I don't care, bro.
Good. I don't give a [ __ ] I don't care.
Yeah, simple. I don't give a [ __ ] if
it's morally wrong. I don't give a [ __ ]
what women do is morally wrong. Yeah,
what women do is morally wrong as well,
but no one has an opinion on that. But
what women what women do is morally
[ __ ] wrong. I'd abuse that [ __ ]
[ __ ] in America if I could. I I messaged
my mom saying, "You're a stupid
asthmatic little bitch." That's what I
said to her as well. I said to her I
said to her, "Yeah, that you're a stupid
asthmatic little [ __ ] [ __ ] off." Yeah.
So, God knows what I'd say to that
[ __ ] American, bro, if I had [ __ ]
half the chance if the [ __ ] didn't
[ __ ] change her [ __ ] number. You
watch, bro. I'm on one today, bro. I
woke up in a foul [ __ ] mood, mate.
Even before I [ __ ] woke up. Yeah, I
called Elaine an asthmatic stupid little
[ __ ] with arthritis cuz that is what
she is. An arthritis asthmatic little
[ __ ] That's what she will always be.
[ __ ] you know. Yeah, I'm on one today,
bro. I don't give a [ __ ] And I don't
give a [ __ ] what's morally wrong. They
seem to get away with doing all of these
things that are morally wrong, you know,
but people keep defending them. People
keep defending them. People keep
defending them. Just like, you know what
I'm saying, bro? It's [ __ ] up. It's [ __ ] up,
bro. Yeah, she did deserve that. She did
that. She did defend that. [ __ ] her,
bro. [ __ ] her. about you don't want to
contact me again because you just heard
me talk about kids. [ __ ] off then. [ __ ]
off. Remove yourself from my WhatsApp list. [ __ ]
off. You know, don't judge a man unless
you walked to mine in his shoes. That's
the saying, bro.
You know what I'm
saying? Yep. They do. They do. They do.
Little fright. They do. And it And it's
sad. And it is sad. But they do do
that, you know. No, I'm not I'm not
saying she would. I don't give a [ __ ]
bro. Remove yourself. I don't give a
[ __ ] Maybe. Right. Maybe she should
give you a little bit of leeway because
she knows what you've dealt with with
these [ __ ] women. And everything I
have said is justifiable. As [ __ ] up
as it sounds, mate, you're lucky I've
not gone out and killed someone. You're
lucky that I'm not in [ __ ] prison
because any other person but me would
have been by now. Any other person would
have been. Everything I say is
justifiable. Even if it is about kids.
Yes, the [ __ ] it is, bro. Have you dealt
with the [ __ ] that I have dealt with
with these [ __ ] No, you have not, bro.
So don't [ __ ] talk unless you have.
This is my whole thing, bro. You know, [ __ ]
off. They always defend
him. Anyone that was me would have ended
up killing someone by now. I would have
went in prison. I'm telling you, bro.
They would have. I'm telling you they
Yeah. No, it doesn't matter if I'm Yeah.
And why am I talking about raping kids?
Because of these women and their [ __ ]
attitude. And I'm [ __ ] sick of them.
Do you know what? Bro, I still can't get
over that thing that they ghosting.
Yeah. How a woman can just get sex and
get a relationship whenever she wants.
That is the thing that pisses me off. I
don't even care about them. I don't even
want them. But doesn't Wouldn't that
make you mad? Think about that. Would
that not make you [ __ ] mad? Yeah. how
how they will sit there, listen, listen,
listen, and try to give you advice, but
they can get anyone they want and they
don't have no struggles. Don't don't
listen to them saying, "Oh, they get
sexually harassed. Oh, everyone wants
them for sex." Don't listen to what
they're saying. They're gaslighting,
bro. They're gaslighting. They can get
whatever they want, whenever they want.
Yeah, I rephrase that. Do not let them
tell you otherwise. Oh, we deal with dick pitches.
Like, don't let them don't let them
[ __ ] tell you that it ain't [ __ ]
no easier for them, bro. Don't sit there
and tell me how it ain't no easier for
them. You know what I'm
saying? Don't tell me how it's not no
bit easier for them. You have these
people on Reddit, they try to tell you,
they need to straight, they try to tell
you that it's not any easier for them.
Yes, it is, bro. Yes. The [ __ ] it is. Yeah.
I know what I do. Yeah. So that's it.
But the thing
is, but the only thing is is that even
if you work on yourself, it's not going
to change anything. It's not going to
make anything better. Even if you worked on
yourself, you know, they literally even
if you worked on yourself, it's not
going to get any better. That's the
whole thing about it. I could go out
today approaching today. What's today?
Wednesday. I would do nothing but deal with
[ __ ] So why don't people just let
you rot and [ __ ] suffer instead of
saying, "Oh, you need to uh you need to
uh work on yourself. If you need to try
some more, bro, this is exactly what I'm
saying. Even if you do all of that
stuff, you're still going to be in the
same position and you're still going to be
frustrated. So, you're better off just
[ __ ] sitting there moaning and
[ __ ] winging, you know? At least you
save money and you save time, too. You
know, [ __ ] work on yourself. You
never get a woman told to work on
herself, though, do you? Yeah, that you
never get a woman told that gets told to
work on herself. You never get a woman
that gets told a man don't owe her
nothing. It seems that they really don't
think that you're the problem because if
they genuinely thought if they genuinely
genuinely thought that you was the
problem, right? Why is it as soon as
they think you're a woman, they defend
you? Think of it. Think of it. So
they're trying to say right that it's
you. But then when they think you're a
woman, they somehow no longer think it's
you. So I mean they don't think it's
you. They're blaming you because you are
a man. Just like if any other man complained. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying? Like I would
actually understand it. Yeah. If is if
is if trying actually made it better.
I'd understand it. I'd understand their
point. I would fully fully understand it
if you went out and you stopped
complaining and you done this and it
actually got better. But it doesn't get
better. That's my whole point that it
doesn't get better. We could go out
today and it would be the same [ __ ]
People go out today, Wednesday. We'll
use Wednesday as an example. It's going
to be the same [ __ ] How many times do I
have to keep recording and showing you
this until it drills into your thick
mind? You know,
Like I wasting my own money doing this
well. See, I would say if you give me
£50, I will go out today and prove it. I
will go out today and I'll prove it. But
I would never accept money from anyone.
I don't need your money. But I'm at the
same time, I'm not wasting my money. You
see, if I was someone like L J, stop
calling yourself a M. It's not nice.
It's not good for your mental health.
Stop calling yourself a ma. But anyways,
bro, I would, but I would never accept
money from anyone. But like, you know
what I'm saying? I would fully go out
and show you what happens when you go
out and you try. Yeah. Simple. People in
love with themselves. Same attitude,
same women, same people, you know.
So yeah, but do you know but guess do
you know the funny thing is though,
Terry, is that these people are not in
your shoes. So they can't really judge
you unless they walked a mile in your
shoes. And like I said, if somebody
walked a mile in my shoes, they would
have ended up killing
someone or they would have ended up in
prison. So I mean,
yeah. Yeah. So
yeah, probably, bro. Yeah.
They're [ __ ] evil,
bro. They can sit there and get
everything given to them. But then they
say that we're entitled. Then they say
we don't they don't owe us nothing. But
yet they have literally been given
everything to them on a silver
spoon. On a [ __ ] silver spoon.
Imagine that, bro.
But they don't think that you're
uh stop repeating yourself and stop
calling yourself a ma as well. It's not
good for your mental health. I've said
this a million
times. You've never with the mental
health problems because you've never had
people try to get women in this day and
age and have to keep dealing with their
[ __ ] It's not even just that. No. No.
Do you know what? Yeah. It's not even
just that. It's the fact that they, like
I keep saying, they've got life on easy
mode. They can get sex whenever they
want. They can get [ __ ] relationships
whenever they want. That's the [ __ ] that
annoys me. That's the [ __ ] that [ __ ]
annoys me. That's the [ __ ] that annoys
me, bro. Nothing Nothing really else to
be fair. And how we should just accept
it. How we should just keep working on
ourselves when we know that none of that
stuff makes a [ __ ] different. [ __ ] off,
man. [ __ ] off. So
yeah, the island
Don't give up. Giving up. So, okay.
Okay. So, what do you expect, Ghosting?
Keep going out and keep tormenting
yourself. Keep tormenting
yourself. Is that Is that what you want,
Ghosting? Okay, that's that's a good
opinion. So, what do you want me to do?
keep trying and keep getting negative
results even though the dating the
dating game is always going to be rigged
against me. Does that sound like a
better idea to
you? Does that sound like a better idea to
you? So, you want me to put myself out
there, keep dealing with these women
with attitude problems, right? With
attitude problems. Keep trying. Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay. So if keep trying
worked, I would have found someone by
now. Why should I keep trying when women
don't have to try nothing? Why should I
have to keep trying and dealing with
[ __ ] Okay, [ __ ] this. [ __ ] whether
you get something or not. Answer me this
question. Why should I have to go out
there, keep dealing with these [ __ ]
women when they don't have to deal with
when they don't have to have the same
experience? Why should I have to deal
with these [ __ ] with attitude
problems that think they're better than
you? Tell me why I should. Why should I?
Whether I get something or not, why
should I have to deal with these [ __ ]
women, you know? No, no one should have
to do that. They don't have to [ __ ]
do it with men. So why the [ __ ] should I
have to do
it? We've basically given up.
Yeah, they're not better than me, Beex.
And you're not better than me. You're
single and you've got two kids. There's
no woman in this world that's better than me. You
know, listen, Beex, you've got two kids
that you probably touch up, you dirty
wrong. Don't [ __ ] tell me about
people being better than me and not
being bad. Okay, Beex, let's compare our
lives, right? You got two kids, you got
no money. You probably touch up your
kids cuz you're wronging. I get more
money than you. You're a single mom and
you don't even have a [ __ ] father to
your kids. Let's talk about me and you.
Yeah. Let's talk about me and you. Let's
talk about me and you. Yeah. [ __ ] other
men. [ __ ] ever other women. I'm better
than you. I've got more money than you.
I get more money than you. You. I'm not
a single mom like you. Yeah. Do you
understand? That's the difference. Oh,
Ronny's been trolling me.
How about you come off of YouTube and
deal with your stinking kids? You
know, you know what I'm saying? I'm
better than you. I'm better than you.
But you know the funny thing is is you
know the funny thing is uh Beex is I
probably had more women than you've had
men in about a decade. That's probably
facts. And you're older than me because
nobody likes you. You're a single mom.
Why Why are you on YouTube? Why are you
on YouTube seeking attention?
Why? No, they're not single parents. No,
they're not. No, they're not. My
sister's um baby dads are with them. No,
they're not. None of my family are
single parents. No, they're [ __ ] well
not, mate. Both my sister's dads are
with their kids. Try again. Try again, Vex. Try
again. Yeah, that's [ __ ] You know,
that's [ __ ] Vex. You're the one
that comes on YouTube crying, "Oh,
Ronny's been trolling me."
Oh, what have you been trolling me? You
have to come on YouTube to get
attention. That's funny. Goona, guess
what though? Goona. Goona. Goona. Beex
didn't come to my country and owe me
though. Beex didn't come to my country
and owe me though. Beex didn't come to
my country and owe me though. How about
that one? I came to your country and
owned you three times, you little [ __ ]
Yeah, whilst I was still there. Beex
didn't come to my country and owe me. I
went to your country and owned you,
slaphead. How's about that one? How was
about that one? Where's your Where's
your baby? Listen, your Where is your
baby, Dad? Where is your baby's dad's?
Go on, tell us.
Yeah. Yeah. You are a mental. Yeah. Oh,
is that the other excuse? Where's
Morgan? I don't know, man. I had her
body and made her split up with her
boyfriend. I wouldn't know, lad. I
wouldn't know where she is. I don't care
about her. I met her once. Where's your baby, Dad?
[ __ ] off. [ __ ] off with another woman.
Huh? Yeah. [ __ ] Bro, listen. Goona.
Goona. Goona. Stop deflecting. I've gone
to your country and I owned you. Stop
deflecting on other women that I've met.
You seem to be obsessed with other women
that I've met. Considering you're
married, considering you're so married.
You're married. You're married, but
you're obsessed with other women that
I've met. [ __ ] other women. Worry about
me and your country and your [ __ ] ass
not coming out. You [ __ ] Welsh Mong.
Yeah. Yeah. Keep repeating yourself. You
[ __ ] bald prick. You [ __ ] bold prick,
mate. Yeah. It doesn't [ __ ] matter,
bro. I don't care.
Yeah. And I And I And I harassed Listen,
bro. Oh, I made her change her number. I
made her split up with her family. I
harassed her boyfriend. Sorry. I made
her [ __ ] I harassed her whole family,
bro. to the point where they had to call
the police from me five times. I don't care,
bro. Don't care, mate. Do you think I
give a [ __ ] who block my number? I had a
[ __ ] run to the police on me. I made
her split her boyfriend split up with
her, mate. Do you want me to put the
Instagram messages up? I'm in a bedit.
I'm in and I'm skinn. Oh, Beex, I'm
skinn. Really? Really? If only you knew
how much money I had, Beex. If only you
knew how much money I had. You really
You really think I'm skin, mate? I sold
over £1,000 on Friday. You don't even
get that a month for
benefits. Yeah, I No, I done more than
touch her tits. I had her body. Guna,
why are you so obsessed anyways, bro?
Are you a married man? You're not
married. You're a loner. That's why
you're on YouTube every day. Cuz you're
a loner. You're a [ __ ] loner. You're
a loner. You're a baldy prick trying to
deflect from the fact that I came to
your country. I wished rape on your
daughter and you didn't do anything about
it. I went to your country. I I wished
rape on your daughter and you did not do
anything about it. Never mind any other
situations, lad. Yeah, Terry. You're not
going to You making things up. You're
not going to trigger me, bro. You're not
going to trigger me. Yeah. I wish rape
on your daughter, Gona. I hope she gets
raped. I hope your daughter gets raped
and she gets a miscarriage. I'm talking
about your daughter. I'm talking about
your daughter, lad. Yeah. I'm talking
about your daughter now, Gula. Are you
going to come to London and sort me out?
I wish rape on your
daughter. I wish rape on your daughter.
So, are you going to come and do anything about it?
Huh? Yeah. Do you know what I love? that
you're a fat ugly old man and no woman
wants you. You're a Welsh monk and I'm
I'm wishing rape on your daughter. You
know, I wish rape on your daughter. Are
you going to come and do something about
it? Because I remember you said to Timmy
about how nobody wishes you rape. I'm
wishing rape on your daughter and I'm
telling you to come and meet
me. I'm wishing your daughter to get a
miscarriage. Are you going to come and
do something about it? No. because
you're just a little keyboard warrior.
How long have you been doing this now,
Gona? Six, seven years. Six, seven
years. Yeah, people will believe her
because they're Yeah, Terry. People will
defend People will defend them. People
will defend her because she's a woman
and they're all simps and they're all
jealous. So, of course, people are going
to defend her because they're all simps.
They've got no bad words to say about
women, which has already been proven a million
times. Yeah. That's nice. But I'm
laughing at what I've said about your
daughter and you're not going to do
nothing about it. And you're not going
to do nothing about what I've said about
your daughter. You're You are not going
to do anything about what I've said
about your daughter. Yeah. And that's
it, lad. But guess what, Gona? I make
more money than you and I don't have to
work. My life's better than yours. I'm
not some fat ugly man on YouTube like
you. Scared to come to London, [ __ ]
boy. I'm not like you hiding behind a
keyboard. Luna, why don't you come on
right now and show us your face? My life
is so bad, bro. Okay. Why don't you come
in the hangouts and show us your f Why
don't you come in the hangouts? You
know, you've been on YouTube all day for
somebody that works, right? Come
on. Come on. Come on. Come on. And I'll
play the money game with you if you
want. Come on. Let's talk about each
other's lives while we show our face.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on, bro.
Join the hangouts. Come on. Don't be
scared, Ga. Come on. Come on. Yeah,
Beex, I'm a virgin. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm a virgin. Yeah. Yeah. I'm a virgin.
Beex, listen. You've got no baby dad.
Your baby dad [ __ ] off. Your your
children are growing up without a kid. Yeah.
Yeah. And that's funny, mate. And I love it. It's
lush. I love it. It's [ __ ]
lush. Yeah. That's what I find lush. I'm
a virgin. Beex, have you had a word with
yourself, mate? There's a video of me
getting a [ __ ]
[ __ ] I slept with both Izzy and
Morgan. And why do you keep bringing
them up as well? You jealous? That does
I know what I've done with them. So,
whatever you say, it doesn't it's not
going to trigger me. But calling me a
virgin. Really? Come on, bro. Come on,
Please. Yeah. Yeah. Rejected constantly.
Well, at least I'm not rejected as much
as you and your ugly kids. Ugly kids.
Ugly kids. Mate, I've slept with both
Izzy and Morgan. Doesn't matter what
they say. Prove it. Prove it. Anyways,
GA, why are you so obsessed with my love
life? Is it because you're a fat ugly
old man that can't get an erection? Is
it because you're a fat ugly old man
that can't get an erection that lets
people talk wish on these kids? Yeah,
I'm better looking than you, but guess
what, Bottle? I'm better looking than
you, you [ __ ] ugly [ __ ] I'm better
looking than you and I've had more women
than you. Go on my YouTube channel. If
you go on my YouTube channel, you will
see it. I can't be as stinking as you.
You fat ugly m. At least I'm not as
stinking as you mutters. You've never
even been seen with any women. You
little pathetic skinties have never even
been seen with any women. That's what I
love about you is that you mutters, you
fat, ugly mies, have never had a woman.
You've never even been seen with one.
So, what does that say about me being a
bunter? What does that say about me
being a ma when a manta has had more
women than you and fat ugly manta boy
ain't been seen nothing? You are the
manta. You are the fat ugly monties of
YouTube. This is why you come on here
every day doing what you do cuz you are
the alltime monties. We've seen what you
look like. Do we need to put somebody Do
we need to put Right. You are stinking.
You are skin. You are a manta. You are a
virgin. Everything you say is about your
own lives. Everything you say is about
your own m lives on benefits. Everything
you say is about your own lives. You're
all skin. You're all fat. You're all
ugly. You're all [ __ ] loners, which
is why you're on here every day. Seven
years, right? As soon as I started
watching Timmy, right, about a year
after I started watching these property
videos, I swear down I have seen these
same ugly fat projecting loners,
singing, right, that has never even been
inside a woman come on here project
their life onto people every day. These
same special needs, skint little single
people that's never been seen with a
woman. Everything is about your own
stinking fat ugly lives. This is why you
don't come on here and join the
link. Yeah, that's it, bro. You are all
the fat, ugly, stinky little m little
virgins. Listen, put your money where
your mouth is. Why don't you start
showing stuff? Why don't you start
showing stuff? Just like when I showed
money the other day and no one can show
me nothing. Just like you can't show
women because you're all single. Goona
with his erectile
dysfunction. Erectile dysfunction. Goon
the little slap head. Dennis because I
slept with Morgan. Dennis cuz I slept
with Izzy the little Welsh mom. Cuz he
can't get his little dick up and he has
to try and rape his daughter but they
don't go up. How mad is that? How mad is
that, bro? Just cuz you tried to rape
your daughter and because and your dick
don't [ __ ] go up. You [ __ ] stinky
[ __ ] Yeah, you stinky little
[ __ ] who's never been who has never. But
I've listen I am I'm calling you
singleton fat ugly munters and I'm
calling you you are fat ugly monters.
This is why you come on YouTube every
day calling people mters. You are single
skin ugly monties. It's all about your own
lives. Yeah the [ __ ] out of me. That's
not going to trigger me. Yeah. I love
that I had her body and you obsessed. I
[ __ ] love that I had her tits and I
[ __ ] her. I [ __ ] love that I made
her change her number. I [ __ ] love
that I made her boyfriend split up with
her. I [ __ ] love that I made her go
to the police on me five times. I
[ __ ] love it. I [ __ ] love how I
harassed her whole family and I got away
with it scotfree. I [ __ ] love it. I
like doing the I like doing a belly
dance. I harassed her family. I made up
I made her boyfriend split up with her.
I made her cry to the police about me. I
made her beg to LT. Oh. Oh, he's coming.
He's coming. He's coming. I'm scared. I
made her run to the police, screaming
like a little [ __ ] Oh, I'm scared.
What if he actually comes? What if he
actually comes? What if he actually
comes? Bro, what if he actually comes? I
made her change her number. I made her
go to the police for me. I bullied her
and her family for 2
years. I got away with it, mate. I made
her split up with her boyfriend.
I made her split up with her boyfriend
and I harassed her whole family. What
are you talking about getting away with
it? I harassed her whole family. I
bullied her into fear. I made her so
scared she had to go to the police about
me. I've never done that about anyone
before. I did do something. I made her
split up with her boyfriend and made her
run to the police about me, which made
her a victim. Yes, I bullied her so much
she had to change her number. She had to
number. She had to change her number. I
bullied her and her family. Yes. Owned
by the foreigner. Yeah. Okay. You keep
telling yourself that, Sean. Yeah. Ma
owned by the foreigner. Even though I
made her go to the police on me and
split up with her boyfriend. I [ __ ]
her relationship up. I [ __ ] her
relationship up with her boyfriend. I
[ __ ] her relationship up. Do you think
I'd give a [ __ ] about her talking [ __ ]
about me after I've had her skanky body?
After I've had her skanky body? I'm glad
I made her I made her split up with her
boyfriend. I made her go to the peace
for me. I harassed her whole family. I
put up posters about her. I don't care,
bro, about the skanky little rape victim
with the STD that slept with 24 people
before me. I don't care about the Syrian
rape victim [ __ ] who I made her split up
with her boyfriend.
Yeah, I [ __ ] made that Syrian skank
[ __ ] go to the police on me and [ __ ]
split up with her [ __ ] boyfriend. I'm
living that life, bro. Living that
life. You know what I'm saying? [ __ ] off,
man. Listen, listen, listen. She didn't
reject me. I had her body. I had the
[ __ ] I had her body. Anyways, I'm not
going to explain this anymore with you
little rejects. You little rejects on
here. Anyways, yeah, I don't give a
[ __ ] bro. Guess what though, Guna? I
made her split up with her boyfriend and
that made me happy. I I [ __ ] her
relationship up. I [ __ ] You are the M.
Beex. Listen, Beex. Have we seen your
Listen, have you seen your face, Beex?
You are the M. You and your stinky
little kids. You and your [ __ ] ugly
mixed race kids. Have you seen you and
your manta ugly mixed race kids that
don't even look human? [ __ ] off, mate.
Get the [ __ ] out of here. You and you
and your [ __ ] M stinky kids are going
to come on here and try and tell me what
I am. You and your little mixed race
kids. [ __ ] off, mate. You and your downy
looking [ __ ] ugly special needs kids.
[ __ ] off, mate. Yeah, she didn't kick me
out. She did. And I'm not going to keep
going over I'm not going to go over this
over and over and over again. I'm not
going to go over this, Terry. You're
just jealous. I'm not explaining this
Morgan thing to you again. You're
jealous. That's why you keep going on
about it. That's why you keep going on
about it over and over and over again.
Juna, stop trying to rape your daughter.
She doesn't want you, mate. Your
daughter don't want you. Stop trying to
[ __ ] rape your daughter, you silly
scumbag. Yeah. You're fast enough. You
are the mex. You are a single mom. Your
kids are monties. You and your [ __ ]
kids. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Um, I didn't lie
about anything. Listen, Beex, you and
your ugly half cast kids. Yeah. The
Monte kids. You are the Montes. Yeah.
Stop [ __ ] coming on here talking
about me. The only Monties is you and
your [ __ ] ugly kids. You understand?
You and your downy kids. They're the only ones,
bro. So listen to me, you ma. Where's
your [ __ ] half cast kids [ __ ] dad?
Come on. Come on. Come on. Where are
they? Where are them [ __ ] little
shits, Dad? Before asking someone, bro.
Yeah. Go on. Go on. [ __ ] [ __ ]
man. Trying to [ __ ] talk about anyone
else. [ __ ] right
off. Yeah. Why? Because she's racist her
[ __ ] self. Yeah. Cuz she's racist her
[ __ ] self. [ __ ] her. Yeah. [ __ ] you. Simple.
And that's it. [ __ ] off, man.
Yeah. Yeah. That [ __ ] that foreigner
ow me, mate. When I was in her country,
she shut her [ __ ] mouth. She shut her
[ __ ] mouth. She shut her [ __ ]
mouth. Okay. You Do you want me to prove
to you? Do you want me to prove to you
this stinky little Syrian foreign for
foreigner? This little broke [ __ ]
doesn't owe me. Why don't want to use
get her back on YouTube and as soon as I
get my passport back from the renewal
offer, I'll go back there. That's how
much money I've got. I'll go back there.
Let me see if this dirty stinking fat
[ __ ] foreigner Yeah. really does owe me.
Go on. Go on. Go on. Go on then. You
really want it, bro? You really want to
go there? You really want to go there
with me, bro? You really, really want to
go there with me. Listen, Beck, stop
calling yourself a manta. The only m is
you and your half cast kids. They're the
only people that are a manta. The only
people that are misers is you and your
half cast m kids. That's the only people
that are montis. Yeah. Let's go there
then. Go on. Listen, GA. Listen. Just
because some [ __ ] lied about me.
Doesn't mean it never happened. You're a
silly old man that can't get an
erection. You try to rape your daughter
every day. Yeah. But you can't get your
dick up. But you can't get your [ __ ]
dick. You can't get your dick up. You're
the one that has to sit there and try
and rape your daughter. And because she
doesn't want you, you keep talking about
Morgan cuz you're jealous. Because your
daughter won't let you rape her. You
sick [ __ ] Yeah. You sick [ __ ] [ __ ]
Because what? Because your daughter
doesn't let you rape her. That doesn't
mean I've not set with Morgan. You silly
[ __ ] Yeah. [ __ ] off, man. [ __ ]
off. Yeah. It's the truth.
And you know how we all know you're a
[ __ ] goona because look how big you are
to go for Timmy. Why don't you come to
London? I gave you this time and time
again. Come to London. Come to London.
Come to London and you won't come. Why
won't you come for me big man? Why won't
you come for me big man? You said that
you will do anything and stop people who
talks about kids. I'm speaking about
your daughter. Come to London. I'm
speaking about your [ __ ] [ __ ]
daughter. But we're not seeing you in London.
You've all got anxiety, mate. You've all
got anxiety. No, Terry. She didn't say
anything because nobody on YouTube has
spoke to her. You [ __ ] Not one person
on YouTube has even spoke to the real
her. So, go figure, bro. Go figure. Cuz
if that was the case, you would be on
here now. You're obsessed with my sloppy
seconds. You are
obsessed. Yeah. [ __ ] off, man. You're [ __ ] obsessed.
You're obsessed, bro. Why do you care
about this ma anyways? You keep going on
about this Morgan Ma. No one's even
spoken to her. The real her. You're
obsessed. You got nothing on me, mate.
As you say that, I've had no
relationship. Yeah. Yeah. Yes, they
know. Yes, they have. No. How would they
know where she was staying? They didn't
know where she was staying. They didn't
know where she was staying. No one knows
where she was staying. So, stop talking
[ __ ] [ __ ] No one knows where she was
staying. Yeah. You're obsessed, bro. What the [ __ ] You're
obsessed. Nah, definitely not me, mate.
me. So, that's it. You
know, you you're calling me a virgin,
Beex. You're being silly now, Beex.
You're being very silly now. You're
being very silly now. Yeah, she did it.
Terry, Terry, Terry, Terry. Listen, let
let you really think. How could she
physically boot me out of anywhere when
I am physically stronger? How could she
boot me out of anywhere when I'm the one
that's stronger than her? Mate, I would
smack her in her mouth. You know how I
feel about women. That can't even make
sense cuz she couldn't boot me out,
mate, because I would slap her across
her face or anyone. So, how would that
even happen? How could that even happen?
Yeah. And that never happened. That
never happened. You're obsessed. She
didn't tell me to leave. She got her
tits out and I started sucking them and
kissing her and I [ __ ]
her. Yeah. Doesn't make sense. You're an
idiot, mate. No one takes somebody to
their p to their B&B to then kick them
out. Doesn't make sense. I'm not going
to Wales. I'm not wasting my money on
this country. He can come to London.
I've already been to Wales three times.
Yeah, I' I've already I've already been
to Wales three
times. If he wants me, he can come and get
me. Simple. I told you I'm in London.
I'll meet you in
London. That's it.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Well, get the [ __ ]
on here now then and I'll go as soon as
I get my passport. And I'll go as soon
as I get my passport. Come on. Come on.
on. Come on. Come on then. Simple, mate.
The [ __ ] can't even say nothing cuz she's [ __ ]
shook. Yeah. Yeah. Goona. Goona, you're
not going to trigger me. You're not
going to trigger me. You're the little
loner with the erectile dysfunction,
mate. Aren't you supposed to be a
married man? Aren't you supposed to be a
married man? You're jealous. Just
because you can't get your little dick
up anything doesn't mean you need to
make up stories.
Yeah, it's not going to trigger me, bro.
It's not going to trigger me. Get your
ass to London instead of making up
stories about something that you don't
know anything about. Why don't you come to
London? Oh my god, bro. You're boring
now. You're a keyboard warrior. Stop
being a keyboard warrior, GA. Stop being
a keyboard warrior. Stop being a
keyboard warrior. You're not going to
get me justifying myself. You can make
up little things to try to trigger
people. Are you coming or are you
not? You're a keyboard
warrior. You You're a keyboard warrior. Goa, stop
it. Okay. And another thing, Goa, is you
don't know what happened. You can only
It doesn't matter what she said. It
doesn't matter what she said. It doesn't
matter what she said. Anyone can say
anything. You know, when you've got
actual evidence, then come back to me,
lad. When you've got actual evidence,
come come back to me.
Yeah, come back to me. Come back to me.
You You mate, no one cares what she
says. [ __ ] lie all the time. Let's
see some actual evidence of what I've
done, but you can't. [ __ ] off, man.
You're a keyboard lawyer. Goona, listen,
mate. You are a
keyboard. Oh, yeah. You've been doing
this for years. [ __ ] off. Yeah,
[ __ ] off, bro. You're fine. Want to talk
about owning people in their country,
mate. Listen, can I ask you a question,
GA? I'll ask you this question. What did
you want me to do, bro? When somebody is
acting like a little [ __ ] in my country
and they sleep with me and then they
start all of their madness when they
when they go back home. What did you
expect me to do, bro? They never had
this energy when they were here. What
did you want me to do? I harassed her
family. I made her boyfriend split up
with her. I made her change her number.
I made her go to the police on me. When
I went to America, she didn't come out.
What did you want me to do when they
were going the next day? If someone's
not having this energy to my face, was I
just supposed to assume they were like
that? I've even said if they if I ever
find out they are in England again, I'm
going to end them and they're not going
back. Yeah, April time's coming up soon,
so they should they should be here soon.
They are not coming to know England.
again. Am I a [ __ ] mind reader or
something, you know?
But it's a man is Yeah, I know. But bro,
that that's all they can do. But but
listen listen, that's all they can do,
bro. It's easy to do that stuff from
across the pond. It's easy to do that
stuff from across the pond. All they got
to do is tell me when they're back in
England and I'm there. Simple. If
somebody wants to be a keyboard warrior
having having group chats about people,
that's fine, bro. But I made their
number. I made them change their number.
I made them go to the police on me. I
went to America. and they ain't come
out. What more could have I
done? I couldn't have done any any
[ __ ] more, bro. You know, like tell
them to come back here and start their [ __ ]
Happen. It will never ever happen. So,
uh, Goona, stop changing the subject and
get your ass to London. Get your ass to
London. Shut up, bro. I don't need to show you
nothing. There we
go. Mate, she's not with Charles. No,
she's not. Charles has got a new
girlfriend and I know that cuz I've got
him on Instagram. Try again, Beex. Try
again, Beex. Try again. I can actually
show you Charles's new girlfriend if you
want. There's actually a picture of them together. So, yeah. Yeah.
Sorry about that, man. I had to
um Sorry, you you need to stop calling
yourself a ma. You need to stop calling
yourself a mex. It's no good for the
mental health, man. It's no good for the
mental health. I'm telling you, it's no
good keep calling yourself a bun.
Really? It ain't nice, mate. It's not
nice. And why do you bring up this
Morgan? You seem obsessed with Peter
Bell sloppy seconds from two and a half
years ago. You seem very, very obsessed.
Are you okay or something?
But bro, that [ __ ] will never ever own
me. Never. She done her [ __ ] when she
was back in America cuz she knew nobody
could get to her. Oh, they're still
Okay. Okay. They're still together, are
they? Okay. One
second. This is Charles's new girlfriend. I'll show
you. This is Charles's new girlfriend.
Yeah, you can see her a little
bit. There you go. That's Charles's new
girlfriend. Stop calling yourself a bun.
You need to stop calling yourself a bun,
bro. It's not good for you. It's looking
good for the membrane. Stop calling yourself a
bun. Yeah, that is Charles's new
girlfriend right there. That's his
Instagram. What are you talking about,
Max? You're a [ __ ] idiot.
Ah, come on
now. Try again.
Bro, he literally says it's his
girlfriend. You [ __ ] [ __ ] They've
got pictures together.
Yeah, they are a couple. You [ __ ]
[ __ ] Go on his [ __ ] Instagram.
Yeah, they are a couple. Go on his
Instagram, bro. Man made them come split up.
No, I know how relationships work. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah. Okay. Whatever, man. You people
need to look at your own lives before
judging other people. You are the M as
well. I've noticed that every single
person that calls me a M is uglier than
me on this community. Isn't that mad?
They come on here, they try calling me a
M, but they're uglier than me. It's mad.
Selfreflection, mate. Most of you people
in this community, yeah, you're fat,
ugly losers. You ain't got nothing going for
yourself, you know. But laugh at me.
Okay. Okay. Well, let Well, tell them to
let me know when they're back in
England, you know.
Yeah. Yeah. But they can only do it a
thousand but they can only do it
thousands of miles away. Come tell them
to come and do it to my face. Terry,
tell them to come and do it to myself to
my face then. Tell them to come and do
it to my face. Bro, was they laughing
when they went to the police for me? Was
they laughing when they when I made them
change their number? Was they laughing
when I made her boyfriend split up with
her? Bro, anyone can make a group chat
about anyone. I can make a group chat
about you right [ __ ]
now. You know, at the end of the day,
you change your number. You didn't come
out when I was in your
country. Or, you know what I'm saying?
So, at the end of the day, you're you're
an idiot. You're stupid, bro. Because
it's like, if I go there right now, none
of them would come out. And I don't even
know how I would contact them because
they changed their number. Yeah.
You know what I'm
saying? Oh, I'm quite loud, aren't I,
lad? Doesn't matter if I've been in a
relationship. I'm not a single I'm not a
single mom with
kids. I didn't fake a holiday. I didn't
fake a holiday. I didn't fake a holiday.
Okay. Okay. But let's just say I faked a
holiday. And I never I never faked a
holiday. So, I made you go to the police
on me. I've made you change your number.
I've made your boyfriend split up with
you, but yet you win if I fake to
holiday. Yeah, bro. You really won. Do
you want a Do you want a Do you want a
gold medal or do you want a silver
medal? It doesn't even make [ __ ]
sense. Yeah, you win nothing, mate. You win [ __ ]
nothing. You win nothing. Goona, stop.
Stop deflecting, bro. Stop deflecting.
You got a car. There's no reason you
can't come to London. I'll meet you in
Paddington Station. End of
story. Yeah. Don't stop
deflecting. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay. Okay. Okay. So, if I faked it,
fake. Okay. Goa. So, if I faked it, if I
faked it, right, Gona, if I faked it,
right? Listen. So, if I faked it, right,
how how was I supposed to get her to
come out so I could smash her face in
there? How how do you want Okay. All
right. So, you're telling me that I
faked holiday? Okay. Okay. Then, so say
I go there next week or two weeks, I'll
never get my passport for argument sake.
Well, if I go there, they're going to
ignore me, right? So, you know that
they're a little [ __ ] that will never
say anything to anyone's face. So, you
know that. I would smack her up in front
of any man, bro. Oh my god. She's so
lucky she didn't come out the the
[ __ ] first time. You
know, and that's it, bro. Like, go on.
Yeah. Her dad laughed at me, bro. Bro,
her dad got mad at first. No. No. Her
dad got mad at first, bro. Her dad got
mad at first. They pretended to laugh.
Yeah. She's a little scumbag, man. So,
you know that if if she ever comes back
or I go there, that she's going to
ignore me. There you go. Cuz you know
cuz I'll smash your [ __ ] face and you
know that as
well. Yeah, I stalked you for over two
years. I'll keep [ __ ] stalking you,
you little [ __ ] You got a taste of your
own [ __ ] medicine. You got a taste of
your own [ __ ]
medicine. But nothing happened. He told
mate, he told me that he was going to handcuff
me. No, he actually said he was going to
handcuff me. Yeah. Yeah, I know. They
laughed at me. That's why they went to
the police five times and I made her
change her number. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay, good. That's why they changed
their number and went to the police on
me five times. I know, bro. It's one of
them things, isn't it? Yeah. And I made
her go mad saying, "Oh, you're stalking
me. You're stalking me. You're stalking
me, mate. I can keep harassing her
family if you want. I can keep harassing
her family if you want. I don't
mind. I can keep harassing her family
and stalking her if you want, mate. I
can send [ __ ] to her dad's if if you
want. I've got her dad's
address. I mean, you know, I can do that
if you want, mate. I've got her dad's
address. I don't have her her address,
but I have her dad's address. I'd get
the whole house swatted. If you want,
lad. I moved through fear. No, never
move through fear. Anyways, [ __ ] all
this. Come to London. Come to London,
man, and stop being a pathetic repeater.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, yeah. Yeah. I just
wanted I just wanted like to leave her
with a bit of something to not be a [ __ ]
in the future. Yeah. Yeah, bro. I just
wanted to be I just wanted to like leave
her with something to never be a [ __ ]
again ever in your life, you stupid fat
Syrian [ __ ] You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. I just wanted to leave her with a little um
souvenir, you know? Like a little
souvenir, you know, bro. Yeah.
little souvenir, you
know. Take it. You're not coming to
Glasgow. Um, you're not coming to
Glasgow Friday then, Gona. I take it.
[ __ ] You're a [ __ ] [ __ ] man.
God [ __ ] you are
man. Literally you are
lad. Yeah. You're talking about
yourself. Yeah. You're talking about yourself,
lad. You're talking about yourself. It's
not nice to talk about yourself like that.
It's not nice to talk about yourself like that, Dad. So, yeah.
Uh because I'm going to um I'm going to
Glasgow to find this guy that I met once
last year. He lives in Glasgow and I
can't find him. So, I'm going to have to
try and knock on as many doors as
possible to find him.
Why wouldn't you go to
Glasgow? Tram will meet me. Yeah. Okay,
buddy. Yeah, he doesn't even live in Glasgow. Okay.
Yeah. No, Tram doesn't even live in
Glasgow. I'm there to find
someone. Terry, I'm there to find
someone. Terry. Terry. I'm there to find
Yeah, I'm there to find someone,
Terry. How's that sound, Terry? I'm
there to find someone,
boss. No, but I'm going to go like all around Glasgow.
Huh? Peter Belly's parents flew away and
left him with these nesticles.
Yeah, I said to Ela, "You're an
asthmatic, pathetic little
cunt." Oh, I'm quite I can be quite
nasty. E, it's mad how women can turn
you like this. It's so mad how women can
turn a normal, stable person into into a
mad person. I think everyone's got it in
them. They just need a trigger. They
just need a trigger. I think everyone's
got it in them. Everyone's got
Everyone's got it in them.
Everyone's got it in there, Terry. I
reckon I think everyone's got it. Got
Yeah. Got it in them.
Yeah. Yeah. I can be nasty to both. I
can be nasty to both,
Terry. I can be nasty to both if you want.
Yeah. Yeah. I [ __ ] my pants. Yeah. Well,
I stood up to that guy last week in the
bookies. I stood up to that guy in the
bookies. I told him to come and then hit
me with your [ __ ] pole then. You bad
man. Come on. Yeah. Yeah. That's the
excuse. I only go for women. Oh yeah.
[ __ ] I'll go for men and [ __ ]
women. [ __ ] asmatic little [ __ ]
That's why I called my mom asmatic little
[ __ ] Yeah, asthmatic little
[ __ ] This is all because the dating
game is rigged against you. [ __ ]
hell, bro. It's mad, isn't
it? And you got people telling you you
need to you need to keep
trying. It's [ __ ] madness. Madness. madness,
bro. But let me know in that Syrian
cunt's ever back in England anyways,
Terry. And we'll see a proper oage. We
will see a proper proper wool oage,
bro. I can't even stalk them to find out
when they're coming back because all
their shit's on private now.
All their shit's on private
now. [ __ ] I I said to I hope you get raped.
No. [ __ ] knows what I do.
Yeah. [ __ ] lady. There will never be
lane. There will never be king again.
Greavvesy. They'll never be They'll
king. They will never be king. There
again. [ __ ] it.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm always afraid of other
men. Yeah. Is that the excuse? So what?
So because I tell women the truth about
themselves, that means I'm scared of
other men. Okay. Oh, okay. So what what
what what do you what do you define as
an incel? Somebody that doesn't lick
women's asses. What's what's your what's
your um opinion? Um what do you define as an
incel? Yeah, I'm afraid of other men.
Yeah. Yeah. Am I?
Uh I might just put this video up where
I was owning a man actually a couple of
years ago, but it probably wouldn't suit
you. I just hate women. Doesn't mean I
don't go for men. I hate women. I hate
the double standard. I hate how rigged
dating rigged against you. That doesn't
mean I don't go for men. What type of foolishness is that? You know, [ __ ]
me. What type of foolishness is actually
that, bro? Come on.
What actual foolishness is that
bro? The whole family know about
me. That's a madness that is, bro.
Imagine that T whole family knowing about you.
Eh, imagine that,
bro. You don't know where I am. You
don't know where I am, bro. You don't
am. Stop talking about
yourself. You people are such hateful.
Terry, Terry, Terry, Terry, you don't
know where I am. If you know where I am,
why don't you come round? It doesn't
make any sense. You claim No, you you
say that I'm in Albert Square. I'm not
in Albert Square. And even if I was in
Albert Square, which I'm not, so why
haven't you done a video knocking on the door then?
Doesn't make any sense, bro. If you
listen listen, bro, if you claim that
you know where I am, why don't you come around
then? Why don't you come around then,
bro? It doesn't make any sense. See,
you're call The thing is, bro, you say
that I'm a [ __ ] You say that I can't
give it to a man. You don't know where I
live. Yeah, even when you think you know
where I live, well, why don't you come
knock on the door and then you'll see
then, you know, don't prove. Just do
what you got to do, bro. You You'll find out, won't
you? You really are a weirdo, aren't
you, Terry? You really are a [ __ ] weirdo,
man. No, no, that's that's okay. Okay,
bro. That's a very common kitchen
counter. That's a very very common
kitchen counter. And that's not even the
same kitchen counter as the old house.
So try again,
Terry. And this [ __ ] Morgan is [ __ ] stinking,
lad. This Morgan is absolutely [ __ ] stinking,
son. He's [ __ ] stinking,
son. She is stinking,
mate. He's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
Um, but I've had women But I've had
many, many, many, many, many women. I've
had more, Do you know what? I've had
more women. I've had more
women than um than actual white
knights. I've never had a woman. I've
never had a woman. Okay, that's news to
me. News to me.
Oh, okay. So, dates, having sex, having
[ __ ] that doesn't count now. Okay. Okay.
Right. He is [ __ ] stinking, son. I'm
on Morgan's thing right now. She is [ __ ]
stinking. She is [ __ ] stinking, son.
I'm looking at all the pictures.
Do you think I'm funny, Grezy? I think
I'm very funny. Do you think I'm funny? Where's my
daddy? No, I'm not still at 96. You're
wrong, mate. You're so [ __ ] wrong.
You don't know where I am. You don't
Yeah. Right. So, where's my daddy then?
Greasy. Can I your
mama? Yeah. So, where's my daddy, mate?
It's a common [ __ ] kitchen [ __ ]
tabletop, you [ __ ] idiot. Yeah.
Crazy. So, where's my dada then? So, dada?
H where's my daddy then?
No, my daddy's a Celtic fan.
Bezy, you said Peter belly in his little
nest whilst his parents flew
away in the nest by himself.
Hey, I was really nasty to Elaine. Have
the baiffs come? The baiffs are never
coming because that wasn't me on Reddit.
It was me today on Reddit talking about
women. Yeah, but that baiff thing
nothing to do with
me. And stop calling yourself a
m stop calling yourself a m. It's not
good for your mental
health. Keeping me power, mate. You will
never make me paranoid. Not one of you
people would ever make me paranoid. You
will never give me an ounce of anxiety.
Making me paranoid. Never
paranoid. [ __ ] never
paranoid. Especially not of any of you.
Yeah. Yeah. I was mean to Elaine today.
greasy. Yeah, I like it here. I can
shout as much as I want. I can do whatever I
want. No one says nothing. No one can
say nothing. No neighbors, no nothing.
It's lovely, bro. It's actually lush. Yeah.
Yeah. I was snoring as
well. That's how you know you're
depressed when you're having nightmares
and you're [ __ ] snoring. [ __ ] hell, lad.
Uh, no. Cuz no one I've ever approached
has said that to me. Her friend said
that to me cuz she was jealous because I
didn't approach her. So, no, she
never. But no. Do you remember how your
kids have got no dad? How your kids
grows up with no
daddy? That's [ __ ] lush, mate. That's [ __ ] lush.
Yeah, women are evil, man. But
yeah, want me to go on Reddit now
complaining about men as a woman?
Greasy. We'll see if I get the blame
when people think I'm a woman. And I
that is the telltale sign as how you
know you're not the problem. They're
blaming you cuz they think that you're a
man. That's the only reason that they're blaming
you. Because why? As soon as they think
you're a woman, they no longer blame
you. Cuz it's because you're a man, they
like blaming men. They get off on it.
See, they're no different than incels.
See, they're very they're very
hypocritical. They saying that they say
that incelss blame people for their
problems and te but they're the ones
that blame men for any man that
struggles they blame they'll do anything
but but blame the woman. This is what
I'm saying. So they actually contradict themselves
really. But yeah, you go on Reddit as a
woman complaining, you never get anyone
blame you. That's how you know it's not
actually you. It's because you are a you
are a man. That's how you know. That's
exactly how you know what it is. Cuz if
you was a woman and they were still
blaming you, I'd be like, "Okay, maybe."
But they they don't they defend you when
they think you're a woman. Same person, different
gender. So, I mean, I think that says everything,
man. I don't care about her kids, bro.
That's her That's her life.
Yeah, but if you really was the problem,
they wouldn't be defending you when they
think that you're a
woman. All of this working on yourself
and you shouldn't have to do it. You
should have everything given to you just
the way women do. Women get everything
given to to them. They're entitled. They
get everything given to them. So So
should men. Men should get everything
given to them the way women do. The way
women get everything given to them. You
know, very funny. So, GA, I've got a
question. So, if I go on Reddit right
now, moaning as a woman, complaining as
a woman, will everyone start feeling
sorry for me? Oh no. Will people be
giving me the same
excuse? I don't have hygiene, mate. I
bath every single day. Try
again. Try again, mate. I wash my
clothes every day. I bath every day, but
I don't have hygiene. Bro, get real with
yourself. So, anyways,
so if I go and I complain as a woman
that all men are [ __ ] all men are the
same, am I going to get the same
responses or not? No, you're not going
to get the same responses, which also
means it's not you that's the problem.
Because if it really was you that's the
problem, they would think that you're
the problem when you're a woman as well.
So, I mean, that tells you that it isn't
you. And it's a problem with this
society. No, I No, I don't do it to make
myself feel better. I I I do it I done
it as an experiment, Duna. Actually,
initially I actually done it as an
experiment because when you moan as a
man, you're told that, you know, um the
world don't owe you nothing. You're an
incel. You need to work on yourself. You
need to do this. You need to do that.
You need to do this. You need to do
that. But then when you're woman mode
and everyone feels sorry for you. So I
mean it was a it was a very fun
experiment, you know. It was very eye
opening. Very very eye opening. That
along with the dating app ones as well.
I is it normal for a man to never had a
relationship in their mid20s? No. Yes,
it is. Uh, yes it is. I met some guy
yesterday, especially in this day and
age with Instagram and dating apps,
which inflates women's egos. Yes, it is.
There's people in their 20s that have
never even had sex. There's There's
people in their that's never even had
sex. A B I met some guy the other day
and he's only this is his first
relationship and he's 29. He's 29. Yes,
it is actually very very normal. It is
very very normal, mate. There's people
out there that haven't even kissed
anyone. Where do you see where do you
get where do you get these statistics
from, bro? So, and you and Well, mate,
if I'm the problem, then why are people
defending me when they think I'm a woman
then? And no, it being easier for women.
It being easier for women,
right? Uh is an understatement. It's way
easier for women. No. No, no, no, no,
no. It's It's way easier for women. That's an
understatement. My chat is awful. I have
immature no sense to admission. Oh, I'd
like to see you do an approach. I'd like
to see you do an approach. Oh, okay.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Isn't it
mad how I'm the M, but I'm better
looking than all of you on here. Is it?
It's mad how you call me a ma, but I'm
better looking than all of you. And
don't say that you've got a wife and
that you've got a kid. And you are
coming on here calling me a ma, but I'm
better looking than every single one of
you that are calling me a m. Do you not
know how stupid that makes you look?
Like you are way uglier than me and
you're coming on here calling me a m
despite what you claim you have. It
doesn't make sense, Terry. It doesn't
make sense. The only manta is yourself.
Listen, mate. Okay. Okay. If I put a
link up right now, are you going to show
people on YouTube what you look like?
Are you going to show people on YouTube
what you look like? I'm a ma. Okay, bro.
Should we both show our faces? Come on,
man. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on,
bro. You know, if not, then you're just
making yourself look silly, you know?
Yeah. Well, I [ __ ] do. Well, you say
no. No normal no normal person
approaches on the street, but it's
worked for me in the past. Yeah. Never
had girlfriend. Terry, you're in your
40s and you've never had sex. Never mind
a 27 year old. Look at your own life,
mate. You're about 4'2. Two. Yeah. And
you've never had sex and you're uglier
than me. Look at your own life. [ __ ] a
27y old. [ __ ] a 27y old. You're older
than me and you've never had a woman and
you're a m. [ __ ] me, bro. Like the thing
is with you people on here. Yeah. Well,
most you people is you like to talk
about other people's lives. Uh no, I a
football bet yesterday. You like to
judge other people, but your lives are
way worse than the person that you're
talking about. Like this is what I
always say. Yeah. These people, right,
they they'll be like, "Oh, 27 and never
been in a relationship." These people
are 47. They've never had they've never
even been with a woman. When the sooner
you realize on this community, it's a
self-reflection of their own misery.
What people do on here is they're fat,
ugly losers. They've got nothing going
for themselves. And then they see
somebody with a better life than them,
more money, better looking, cuz I am,
and they hate. They That's all they do
is come on YouTube every day and hate
and hate. But these people are 47 and
never had sex. That's that's my whole
sort of thing. Like, you know what I'm
saying? And it's like the only thing
they have is you're 27. You've never
been in a relationship. Mate, you've had
more sex. You got more money than these
people. Like why do they care if you've
been in a relationship or not? What? How
do I know what people look like on here?
Because I've seen these people. I've
seen when these people put their camera
on and they're all fat and ugly. This is
why they say that you're 27 and you've
never been in a relationship cuz you got
a better life than them and it kills
them. So the only thing that they can
say is you're 27 and you've never had a
relationship. Meanwhile, these people
are 47 and never even been with a woman.
So, which one's worse? This is exactly what I'm saying. You
know, I lost 70 yesterday and it never
bothered me, mate. Losing the 70
yesterday did not even bother me. I woke
up in a foul mood today because of
[ __ ] women. That's why I woke up in a
f file mood because of
women. I've seen a handful of people,
mate. And and and what do they all look
like? Fact. Well, then show your faces
then. Okay. Okay. Cool. I I admit when
I'm wrong. Yeah, I could be wrong.
There's a chance that I'm wrong. Okay.
Show your face then. That's my whole
argument. Okay. Okay. Right. I'm wrong.
I admit being wrong. Show your face.
Exactly. So, you just make yourself look
You just You just make yourself look
stupid, you know.
when you do this this stuff, you
know. Oh, we're just ranting about
women. For what reason? People need to
show themselves. Um, because you're
coming on YouTube every day judging
someone else. That's why you need to
show yourself. Because you're coming on
YouTube every day judging other people.
So, that's why you need to show
yourself, you know?
That's why you need to show
yourself. And GA didn't even ask my
answer my question, lad. If I go on
Reddit and I moan about men being a
woman, is anyone going to tell me that I
need to work on myself and that the
world don't owe me nothing? No. So, that
answers your question. It's the women's fault. You
know why? Just sick of women. Just sick
of women and the dating game and how
it's rigged against you. Just just woke
up thinking about it, man. Just Yeah.
Just pissed me off, man. Nothing to do
with money. I've got plenty of money.
I've got plenty of money. I got more
coming as well. Nothing to do with
money. Nothing to do with nothing. Just
women. Women and how the dating game is
is rigged against you. It's rigged
against you. I woke up thinking about
it, bro. It's [ __ ] awful, man.
Snowing and everything.
Yeah. And they have it easy as well.
Slug on a run. They can get sex whenever
they want. They can get in a
relationship whenever they want. They
never have to work for nothing. It's
crazy, bro. Isn't it? It's [ __ ]
crazy. It's actually crazy. Slug on a
like they have life on easy mode. They
get anything they want whenever they
want. It's a madness, isn't
it? It's crazy, bro. Ain't it? Think
about like that. They don't have to work
on themselves. They don't have to do
nothing yet. They get everything handed
to them on a silver spoon. [ __ ] hell,
bro. And that's what made me like think
like what's the point of being in a
world where the dating game is rigged
against you. Think about it, bro. Like
we have to go out every week dealing
with people that pretend they got
boyfriends and getting ghosted or being
led on or all of these negative things
that come with it. Yet they can go on a
dating app and get anyone they want
without even stepping foot out that
door. Think about how mad that
is. How mad that is. But not only how
mad that is, there's no way to make it
better. Like there's literally no way to
make it better. Like I just gave an
example today, bro. I was like I was
like I could go out today, bro. I could
I could go out today and I would get
exactly the same
experiences. No. If you was trying to
find a partner, you would have to go out
every week. Yes, you would. If you was
trying to find a partner, you would have
to go out every week, you
know. Um, Debt, have you seen their
attitude? Have you seen And this is what
I'm saying, bro. They just defend women.
They just defend women. Like, it's it's
like they're allowed to be [ __ ]
They're allowed to have an attitude
problem, but as soon as you say one bad
thing, your attitude against women. This
is exactly what I'm talking about. Like,
you go anywhere in London and they and
they stink of attitude problems. They
literally, bro, you go around London and
you talk to women, they stink of
attitude problems. We never hear about
women with bad attitudes. You get my
point, bro? Do you get my point? They
never talk about women's stinking
attitude. They never tell women that
they're not owed nothing from a man.
They never told a woman to go work on
herself, but they claim that they're
equal. It doesn't make sense, bro. I
promise you, go out in London and they
have got the most stinking attitude,
bro. Like, I I will go out and prove it
again one day when I can be [ __ ] When
I go out again, they have got a stinking
dirty attitude, bro. No, UPN North is no different. They're
westernized. Don't know. I I I I told
her she's a pathetic asthmatic little
[ __ ] That's what I call her, Joe. A
pathetic asthmatic little [ __ ] Up north
is no different. They're all [ __ ] up
there as well. Like Manchester I've been
to. They're all [ __ ]
man. Yeah, people might be friendly up
there, but not the women. All the women
are the same. People might be friendly.
Women are not friendly. They're
[ __ ] Even there as well. Anywhere
you go, they're the same. I told her
that she's an asmatic stupid little [ __ ] and [ __ ]
off. It's these westernized countries.
It doesn't matter where you are,
[ __ ] Unless you go to South
America or you go to [ __ ] Asia,
you're going to have this
problem. There's not one city where all
of a sudden they're going to be
different. Yeah, they might have been
they might be nicer, but probably that
they might be nicer to you and nicer to your face.
But in terms of
like sort of getting with you and stuff,
no. No. It won't be the same in
Thailand. It wouldn't even be the same
in Japan. It wouldn't even be the same
in [ __ ] anywhere in
Asia. Yes. Yes. Ghost.
Thailand is full of British, American,
and Australian men that are there to get
[ __ ] women. Yes, it's full of
Westernized men that's gone to [ __ ]
Asia in a to get [ __ ] women. That's
why it's full of British Americans and
[ __ ] Australians [ __ ] because men
are going there to get women that they
can't get in their own country. I know
Thailand's been there. Antman's been
there. He's been there. He's there
now. You know he's there now, bro. He
gets laid every day. Every day he gets
laid. Yeah. It doesn't matter if you've been Thailand, bro. So
what you feel for me, bro? Thank you,
man. No one else understands. They just
blame you for being a man.
Doesn't matter, mate. Anywhere's got to
be better than here. Anywhere's got to
here. Anywhere is getting better than
here. Anywhere's better than here,
lad. Yes. Obviously, I know it's the
same if you weren't going to go for Asian
women, but snug. Okay. What? Okay. Okay.
Let's have a prediction. If I go out on
Saturday, [ __ ] today. Scrap today. and I
go out approaching women in bars and
clubs, what do you think is going to
happen? Let's have a prediction. Let's
predict. I predict what will happen is
they're going to say that they've got
boyfriends, that I'm too old for them,
that I'm too young for them, that
they're going to give their number and
don't reply or reply, stop replying,
arrange to meet, and then don't meet.
That's my predictions. What's your predictions?
If only there was a [ __ ] bet market
on this, mate. [ __ ] hell, I'd be a
millionaire. If there was a bet market
on what happens when you go and you
speak to a woman, I'd be a millionaire
cuz I know all the words. I know all the
sayings. It will be the same story.
They'll say that they've got a boyfriend.
Um, you might get a kiss, maybe you get
a number, and it never goes anywhere.
That's what will happen.
But the thing is in this day and age
slugging on they want to blame men. They
want to blame men but they don't realize
that the real problem is not men that
struggle if any other men struggles.
It's these women and their unrealistic
standards and their inflated egos.
That's where that's what it comes down
to. But no one wants to admit that. They
want to tell you that you need to work
on yourself, that you need to do this,
that you need to do that.
You know it's but we all know I know
from experience that it is it is them
you know even if like maybe I sound
delusional but it is bro you know
so I wasn't asking personal questions. I
was trying to get to know her. I was
trying to get to know them. And I've
also done it in a bar in a club as well.
So, but yes, log on to a run. It's mad
how the dating game is rigged against
you and there's nothing you actually can
do about it. It's mad, is it? Now, I was
talking to this woman for a month and
within that month, she got in a
relationship. She's got sex life and
everything. I'm still here with nothing.
Yet, she's trying to give me
advice. That's why I hate him,
bro. Millions of men entering to have it
up. Here we go. Comparing comparing
comparing comparing to compare me to
others again millions of men enter into
happy relationship every year. If all
women are monsters, oh this would not be
true. You need to look at yourself just
like all of us do. Millions of men don't
enter into happy relationships every
year. Stop comparing. They don't. Most
men nowadays struggle. Yeah. Most men
nowadays struggle. They don't go in and
out of relationships, mate. I've I've
met people and it took them until 27 28
until they finally got into a
relationship. Stop talking [ __ ] Most
women are single. Yeah. You go to any
bro listen listen. You go to as long as
women you go to any bar, you go to any
club and you will find that most women
are single. So can't be true. So what
you're saying cannot be true. I would
tell you right now, bro, word 75% of
women are single and they're single for
different reasons. A, they don't want to
they don't want anything less than
perfect. Some of them are feminist
feminists and some of them just give up
with men and some of them just give up
with men. So there's a few different
reasons. No, there's not millions of
people. There's not many There's women
that have actually given up on men. So
no one's enter and and and at the end of
the day these people that are in
relationships bro there's different
reasons for them being in relationship
they might have met through work they
might have met at school they might have
met different ways but that doesn't mean
you are going to that doesn't mean you
will the only way to make this
um comparable comparable right is if
somebody was in your exact same position
and they were able to get out of it, but
they're not. See, all of these people
that tell you that these people in
relationships, they're in different um
circumstances, you know, like there, you
know what I'm saying? Everyone's in
different circumstances. That's what
you've got that's what you got to think of,
bro. I've not dated people, but I've
been in I've had dates with people
yet. This is what I'm saying to you. How
like it's not even just about people
being single, people not being single.
It's also how
like when dating apps work. Dating apps
have never worked for me. Approaching
work for me, but people tell me to go on
dating apps. So, it's like what is right
and what is wrong? Cuz if you didn't
approach, you'd be a virgin. You'd never
had a date. So, it's like what's right
and what's wrong, bro? Who knows? You
know what I'm
saying? Yeah, I know. John West, I'm
I've had more women than a lot of these
people and they still defend them. They
still [ __ ] defend them. Lads, your
life begins in your 30s. It is not
uncommon not to get married to your
ladies. You need you. It is.
Yeah. So, yeah.
Like, so that's what will happen, bro.
They'll just say that they've got
boyfriends and then the only way these
people will know, lad, is if they go out
and they do it
themselves. Mate, I've already gave up
gambling, mate. I've
You don't need to tell me to get a job.
I I'm Listen, GA. I make over three grand a
month. I don't even gamble much anyways.
So, yeah. Try again, buddy. I don't even
gamble much anyways. So, try again,
buddy. I done I done 70 pound on a football yesterday.
Yeah. Yeah. And there's nothing you can do about
it. I don't make anything
good. I get over three grand a month.
You believe it or you don't believe it,
bro. That's entirely up to you. I'm
telling you how [ __ ] well, dude.
Yeah, I can get out money right now if I wanted
to. So, mate, you don't know you don't
know a thing, lad. you don't know a
thing. So yeah, but that's how it goes
with the women. And it's annoying that
they can get sex whenever they want.
Even though I don't really care about
sex, slug, but it just annoys me know
that they've never had to work for
anything. And it also annoys me that you
know when these women ghost you and [ __ ]
um or or they do something shitty, you do realize
that you do realize that it's probably
cuz they found someone
better. So you can't stop that. So why
would you put yourself in a game that's
rigged against you? It's stupid as [ __ ]
bro. I don't know how much it is, bro.
But I'm telling you, I get three grand a
month. Over three grand a month. Believe
it. Don't believe it. That's on you,
bro. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. You keep telling
yourself that. These people, the only
way these people are going to understand
SL on a run is if they actually go out and approach
themselves. That's the only way they're
going to actually understand how [ __ ]
women are. Unless they do that, they're
never going to understand, bro. They're
never ever ever going to
understand, you know? Like, you go in
circles all day with these people. You
go around in circles all day with these people, bro.
But you're wasting your time, lad.
Because they don't know what life is
like. Yep. Well, Peter Belly's got his
way, bro. You think that's that's not
even too much
3K? That's not even That's not even too
too much, bro. I think out of that now I
probably got about 1,600
left. I probably got about 1,600 left out of
that. Think so. Yeah, something like
that. I had to get my passport and I
went drinking and [ __ ]
madnesses. But better than
nothing. Think I've got about 16. Yeah.
What about carrying over? Hey, buddy. Yeah.
Yeah. How about this, Joe? If you donate
me £50, I'll go out approaching today in the
nightclubs and show you and tell you how it
is. It's just like this Morgan [ __ ] in
America. this evil bastard who I've got
to fight off. You know, she went back to
her [ __ ] man in America. I probably found someone
better. And that's where the entitlement
comes from. They just ghost people
because they don't think they owe you an
explanation. They think that they can be
shitty to people just because they can
find someone else. It's all [ __ ] up,
bro. Even when you get past the
approaching thing, it's all [ __ ] up, you know?
That's why I don't believe in the saying
work on yourself and and and and and
[ __ ] Cuz think of it, bro. Someone
who's three, four out of 10. And here's
another thing. Slug on the run, right?
Though I I put I put up a dating
profile, right? I put up a dating
profile. I I put up a dating profile of
me and my pictures, right? People's
like, "Oh, you need better pictures. you
with friends, you with
hobbies. But yeah, a woman can put two
selfie pictures up and get 5,000 likes. 5,000
likes. How mad is that, bro? But we're
told we need to change our pictures and
[ __ ] Better pictures traveling the
world and [ __ ] Hey, see what I
mean? They get And that's what made me
fall out with my
mom. This [ __ ] women [ __ ]
It's bad, ain't it, bro? It is
bad. But what can you do, slug? You go
out. They say they got
boyfriends. How are you supposed to get
sex? So, how how are you supposed to get
sex then anyway? Sex, [ __ ] How are
you supposed to get any of that stuff on the
run? This bartender's gone
quiet. Same old [ __ ] She's gone quiet.
E, good old gone quiet.
E, isn't it lush when they go
quiet? Oh, she's gone
quiet. She's gone quietly, lad. Don't know,
mate. So, you have to pay in order to
get s sex. Like, you know what I'm
saying, slug? You need to pay in order
to get sex when a woman can get anything
she wants. Imagine
that. Imagine that. A woman can get any
she can get sex whenever she wants. She
can get dates whenever she wants. She
can get into a relationship whenever she
wants. And you have to sit there and suffer.
I think London's the worst place.
Me, London's the worst place,
bro. London's the worst place.
So, what's your advice, Slug? Sad, isn't
it? It is sad, bro. You
know. No, they're not, mate. I've been
to Wales three times.
I've been to Wales three times and it
was pretty pretty
similar. Well, the first time I went, I
killed it and then the other two times I
went, I got nothing. I got it the first
time, but not the other two times. Nah,
they're westernized. They're westernized,
bro. I'm not believing you. I don't
trust you. I think you're a
liar, bro. It's not It's not a city.
Yeah. Well, no. Who says I've got no
job, no ambition, no prospects? You're
talking about yourself, Gula. You're
making stuff up. I get more money than
you. I don't need a job. I get more
money than you. I make money. You're
just making excuses for [ __ ] women.
They've always got excuses for women.
Have you noticed that slog on the run?
Yeah. Do you remember before when it was
I live with my mom? Do you remember
before, right, that it was because I
live with my mom? I couldn't get a woman
because I live with my
mom. You know, do you remember that? And
then when I'm they say, "Oh, you who
would want somebody that lives with
their mom?" Yeah. Do you remember that?
And then I moved out and then I'm still
having the same
problems. So it's what it is. These are
just excuses that people make for women.
You understand? Think of it. A woman a
guy would date a woman working a
McDonald's. A woman would date a man
working at McDonald's. You
understand? It's just another excuse.
Like I used to when I used to live with
my mom and that people used to say, "Oh,
you live with your mommy. What woman
would want somebody that lives with
their mommy?" It's just another
excuse. I don't even take it personal
anymore, bro. It's just another excuse, lad. You know.
Yeah. I have disabilities. What
disabilities do I have?
Uh, underage sex, bro. Yeah. So, it
doesn't matter if you go to I've been to
Scotland slug on a run. I've been to
Edinburgh and it was similar there. They
were just stuck up. They didn't say they
had boyfriends, but they had It's the
same, bro. The West is the West. It
doesn't matter where you are. You
understand me, bro? I don't have any disabilities.
Guna. I don't have any disabilities, buddy.
Yeah, I would date a woman on benefits.
Most men would date a woman on benefits.
I'm sure most women would date a Most
men would date a woman on benefits.
I just think women are
evil. I just think women are evil. Me
and no one and nothing is ever going to
change my mind unless I'm shown
different. Yes, they would, Gona. Yes, they [ __ ]
would. Yes, they
would. And bro, of course. No, I know
that I'm wrong. I know that I'm wrong,
bro. I'm the big bad wolf. I know that
I'm wrong. Yeah. Yeah, bro. I'm wrong.
I'm wrong. I accept that I'm wrong. I'm
the big bad wolf that chases Goldilocks
down three flights flights of stairs. I
know that I'm wrong. Of course I'm
[ __ ] wrong, bro. I'm a male. Of
course I'm [ __ ] wrong. It's always
the man. It's never the woman. Of course
I'm [ __ ] wrong, bro. I think we've
already established that as a man, you
are always in the wrong. Doesn't matter
if you're right or wrong.
But yes, they would. Goona, I met a
woman and she works um in the shopping
center. She ain't got a very good job. I
would get with her. I would date
her. I would date her. Why not? Why not,
bro? But the thing is, would a woman
date a man working in McDonald's? Nah.
So, that's the difference. Yeah, I know.
I'm I'm disabled. I know, bro. I'm so so
disabled. Well, answer me this question,
Slug on a run. How how comes when I moan about
women, when I moan about when I moan
about men, when I pretend I'm a woman,
why does nobody tell me that I'm wrong
then? Cuz surely if it's your
personality, right? Think about it,
right? These people are saying that it's
your personality, it's you t. So why is
it when people think you're a woman,
nobody blames you. Therefore, it can't
be you then because as soon as they
think that you're a [ __ ] woman, as
soon as they think you're a you're a
woman, they all defend you. So, how does
it even make sense? You get me, bro? It doesn't make sense. You
know, I'm living these experiences,
slug. I get told about an attitude. It's
not an attitude. It's reality.
It's not an it's not an attitude. It's
reality, bro. I could go out Saturday
and it would be the same
old. Yeah. But do you know what the the
the men that simp had less than you, you
know? No, no, no,
no. Listen, listen, listen, listen,
listen. It doesn't matter how many women
get raped, mate. Shut the [ __ ] up. Yeah.
Stop trying to use that as a [ __ ]
excuse, you know. Yeah, but the thing is
that women go for these men. Yes, Goona,
but women go for these men. Women choose
these men. Women choose these men that
abuse them. They go for these men. Think
about it, bro. Any nice guy that comes
their way, slug, right? They will reject
them. Any guy that's not a woman beer,
any guy that's not the same men that
women go for, they will reject them.
They will reject them and go for these women
beaters. They literally go for these
men. They don't want decent people. Go
all around England, bro. They go for the
same guys. White tattooed woman beater
or a drug dealer. That's the only people
that they go for. Same people, same
attitude, bro. They get [ __ ] abused
because they're the men that they go
for, you know?
Yeah. Yeah. But guess what? But the
thing is, but women can get sex whenever
they want. They can get into a
relationship whenever they
want. They can get a job
easier. And what what? Yeah, they might
not get paid the same. They might not
get paid the same, but [ __ ] What's that
about? B by about a couple of pounds.
Oh, whipy [ __ ] woo, bro. Whipy in
they have the dating game on easy mode.
I know that for a fact. They have got
the dating game on e not
facts. Ask yourself that question mark
Taylor because you are alone you fat
m how it feels good but you are alone
you fat m. Bye-bye now. So
yeah. So yeah, let me ask you this
question. How long do you reckon it
would take a woman to get into a
relationship? Slug on a run. If I was a
woman, how long do you reckon it would
take for me to get into a
relationship? I don't care, bro. I don't
care about my
life. I don't give a [ __ ] if I'm wasting
my younger days, bro. I've done
everything I wanted to do. Morgan
rejected me. Yeah. Good for you,
bro. Yeah. That's nice for you, man.
Yeah, they can get a they can get one
instantly. How unfair is that? Yeah.
But I don't know like
Yeah, I choose not to look after my personal hygiene. Really,
bro? Really? I will tell you why. cuz
she's the same as you and hates people.
Hatred is killing you. Who? Who's that?
Uh, my family. I don't give a [ __ ] about
my family, mate. I don't care about them.
Yeah. Now, all women are the [ __ ]
same. Well, let me let me tell you
something, slug. Let me tell you
something, bro. I have met probably more
women than most of probably most of the
people on this community. And let me
tell you something, they're all the
same. They are literally all the same.
The only one that's was kind of
different is someone from like New
Zealand like a few years ago, like by my
birthday. But but honestly, no, no, no.
They're all the same. They're all
devious. They're like NPCs. They're
literally like the same. They're
literally all the same. They all say
they got boyfriends. They all can't meet
you because they're always working.
Like, they are literally all the same.
Like, even the excuses that they use are
all the same as each others. Like, I
was, bro, I was going on my um pictures
um I think it was last week when I used
to travel around to places, right? And I
was looking at the conversations and
it's literally the same [ __ ] Like even
from three years ago, I'm reading some
of these convos cuz I was trying to look
for something and I was like, "Oh my
god, this is exactly the same [ __ ] I'm
working too much. I'll let you know."
We're hearing exactly the same
stuff. We're hearing exactly the same
stuff as we're hearing 3 years ago.
They're all the [ __ ] same
Yeah. I don't know how to act around
women. No, I don't. No. No. Yep. I'm
boring. Yeah. Could be that. Could be
that. Could be that, Joe. Yeah. I could
just be boring, bro. I could be. I could
just be. Yeah. Even though they're the
ones that show no interest. You know,
the the the thing you got to understand,
Slug on the Run, is that it's not this.
It's not that. It's not this. It's not
that. They are just not interested in
this country. There's no Jedi mind
tricks. There's no, "Oh, you need to say
this, Different. Oh, you need to do that
different or, oh, you need to put your
hair this way. You No, these people are
addicted to their smartphones, bro.
These are the same people that are
addicted to Instagram, that are addicted
to Tik Tok. They are just not interested
in this country. You don't need to waste
your time another 10 years before you
figure this [ __ ] out, you know? Believe
you me, bro. What I'm saying is I is
right for the same people in my position, you know. So,
yeah. I mean, we know what the problem
is, but people won't admit what the problem
is. They're just [ __ ] They're just
[ __ ] Like, I I don't know what else
there is to
say, but that was annoying me,
bro. Yeah, you should believe me, bro. I
I didn't I don't go out every
week to tell you that I told you so,
bro. I don't go out every week or
whenever I do go out to tell you, I told
you so. I told you so. I told you so.
I'm right and you're wrong. N like, bro,
I'm not a psychopath. I don't sit on
that barber chair for over an hour to
tell you that I told you so, bro. You
know, it's long for me, too. It's
expensive for me, too. Um,
so, you know, people don't do that to
say that they told you so. Believe it or
not, I don't. You
know, just to say that I told you
so. And I don't use escorts anymore.
So, you seem to have this thing in your head
where you think women are these things
that they're really not. Like, they go
for personality and and they don't. They're just
[ __ ] Like I wonder how when was the
last time you people actually spoke to
women. Like slug, I went out on Friday
uh just before I renew my passport. I
spent hundreds, bro, drinking. I got
nothing. I got some
numbers and he and they just [ __ ] and
they just say
like and they just didn't get anywhere,
bro. They just replied and then stopped.
But you need to ask yourself a question.
When was the last time these people,
right, actually spoke to a woman that's around my
age? That's what they're not doing,
bro. But yeah, they're just not
interested in this country. There's no
over analyzing it. There's no Jedi mind
tricks. That's what people need to to to
to say, but they will never say that. But
yeah, I know what they're like, bro.
I've gone I I'll show you an approach
right now if you want. Let me I'll show
you an approach. I'll show you an
approach, slug that no one's ever show
that and I've never showed before. This
was in Wales. Yeah.
Okay. This one was in
Wales. Um Okay, Joe. Do you want me to
show these conversations again?
Oh, okay. I'm Okay. Okay. All right. Do
you want me to show you the
conversations again and then you can
tell me why they've stopped replying?
They reply to you to take the piss out
of you, to give you false hope. That's
what it is. Anyways, I'm going to show
you an approach. One second. In Wales. I
think not many people seen this
before. Actually, I've won in Wales actually.
Yeah. There's no working it out. They're
just not interested in this country.
There's nothing you're going to work
out, lad. Anyways, one
sec. Where's that one in Wales? Where
the [ __ ] is it? Hold on.
Oh, here it
is. They don't even give you a chance.
chance. There you go, bro. That's one in
Wales. No, I'll let you know, bro.
That's one. This is
two. There you
go. Go watch them.
No, I'm not. No, I'm not. There you go.
There's two approaches for you, man.
There you go. I think I've got some more
ones as well.
One of these are my favorite ones. Hold
on. This is my fave. This was my fave
one. I remember this one. This was like
when it started getting hot.
That's my fave.
There you go,
bro. There there's three videos for you.
I thought that even though they're from
quite long time ago, I
mean, what what, bro? What what do you
want me to do? Do you want me to put a
gun to someone's head or something? And
this is what creates the mindset. These
experiences is what creates the mindset.
Even when I see other people
approaching, it's like I'm seeing myself, bro.
So yeah. Do you like it? I think they
were good approaches, right? Did you
like them? I think they were good
approaches. I think they were good. Even
though they were from a long time ago. I
mean, I tried, but yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I haven't done an approach
sober for ages,
lad. But I don't know. I don't know what
the problem is, Slug, because I look
normal. My face looks
normal. You know, I've got
hair, but men are told they have to keep
trying. I think it's cuz of my race,
lad. Yeah. D yourself confidence. And
that's what I'm saying, bro. And what I
mean is like if people tried as long as
I have, they would have ended up killing
someone or ended up in jail. Like I
wasn't joking when I when I was saying it,
bro. So yeah.
Yeah, exactly. That's why I'm so angry, bro. Yeah,
man. I don't know what what why this is
why are they doing why why is this
happening? Slug on a run. Why is it
happening? Like why is this [ __ ] happening, bro?
Huh? Why is this happening, bro?
No, you've seen me with women as
well. So what? You don't think it's the
way that I look? Slug on the
run. So you don't think it's the way that I
look? This was actually
me. Uh, no, [ __ ] You've seen
me? You've seen me with women as well. No.
Yeah, it makes me feel suicidal
sometimes. Slug on the
run. It does make me feel suicidal,
bro. What's the point in living if
you're never going to if you're going to
if you're if the dating game is rigged against you?
Sometimes I feel like killing myself,
bro, cuz nothing's ever going to
change. No, I I can't be happy knowing
that they get what they want whenever
they want. That's what I can't be happy
with. That they can get a relationship
whenever they want. They can get sex
want. Who is
this? You can't be happy alone cuz why
can't why are women never
alone? Why can't women be alone? Why are
they never alone? They can get anyone
they want. So why shouldn't
we? So why shouldn't we? They can get
anyone they want. They can get sex
whenever they want. They can get dick
whenever they want. And we have to
suffer. Why should we, you
Yeah. Hey, notorious. I went out last Friday.
Yep. They all have boyfriends.
Notorious. How are you, man? You uh you
off the detox? I know moaning about it
isn't helping it, but neither will doing
anything else help it. So, I figured
like moaning is like the cheapest thing
because if you go out and do anything,
that's not going to help either. So,
wouldn't you rather sit there and moan
about it and save money? Think about it,
bro. If we go out again and we approach,
we're going to get the same old. So,
wouldn't you rather just moan about it?
Cuz at least that way it saves money and it kills
time cuz there's nothing else to do but
to moan about it. Because try don't
work. Putting effort into your life don't work.
So you have there's nothing else but
Timone. Yeah, they've all got
boyfriends. Notorious. I got a
bartender's number as well. She went quiet
though. They will never
understand. They've all got
boyfriends. [ __ ] hell. They've all got boyfriends.
You know the thing that annoyed me slug
on a run and notorious last week I was
speaking to this woman who I spoke to
about a month little over a month ago
and even though she's in New Zealand
she's in a relationship now and it just
wow me up. So I was like hold on this
person was giving me advice and now all
of a sudden they're in a relationship
they're getting sex and you're sat there
with nothing and it was probably not
even a month. Like it's it's bad, bro.
And you have to suffer and get nothing,
know. It's really, really bad, isn't
it? You have to stay there sexy, frustrated,
nothing or sec or single if you want a
relationship, whatever you want. And
there's nothing you can do about it.
There's nothing you can do to make it
better. That just makes me want to die,
bro. like that. Just thinking about that
every day just makes me want to die.
Like I wouldn't mind struggling if they
struggled as well. Then I'd be like,
"Okay, well, we're all struggling in
this or we're struggling to some extent, you
know, cuz men, other men, they don't
bother me because I know that it's hard
for them, too.
So, but the fact that they just can get
it easy, it just it just annoys
me. It just annoys me, bro. How they can
they're probably sucking a dick right
now and you're sat there sexy, frustrated. It's
horrible. It is [ __ ] horrible,
bro. And there's nothing you can do in
the world to change your situation.
There's nothing you can do to make it
better. Imagine that.
Yeah, it's a madness,
lad. Approach here for you, Notorious.
You You've never seen this one before.
Notorious. This is an old school
one. Yeah. I wish I was around before
social media. Just where women never had it
easier. That's what annoys me. How they
just have it
easier. Stop talking about
yourself. Stop self-reflecting. A
yeah, having eight today. I'm probably
going to wait for the Chinese to
open. Go and watch that. Go watch that
approach video. Notorious
It sucks it,
bro. The [ __ ] name again. I
agree. Seems like suicide is the only
way out, bro. I'm not going to lie to you.
Seems like it's the only way
out, which is sad,
right? Women are the devil. Women are
evil. They really are.
No, it's not even dependent on women or
gambling. Not at all. It's the fact that
women have the dating game easy. That's
the [ __ ] that's annoying me. It's not
even dependency. That's the [ __ ] that
annoys me that they they can get anyone
whenever they want. They can get sex
whenever they want. They can get dates
whenever they want. It's disgusting. It's [ __ ]
Really? I hate me. I hate them. They're
evil. They're [ __ ] evil,
lad. Yeah. They've all got
boyfriends. And then when you show your
experiences on Reddit, they block
you. Funny how none of them are with
their boyfriends, though, isn't it?
That's what I find. Out of all of the
ones that claim they've got
boyfriends, they're never with them. You
know, I thought that was a point of
actually being in a
relationship. I hate him. I do, mate. I
[ __ ] hate him. worse than Ant-Man. Trust
me, it's like they're born just to be [ __ ]
Yeah. So, what if I go out on Saturday and
approach? What if I go out on Saturday
and I approach?
Notorious. Maybe you might pull
it. Who knows? Hey,
Saturday. Maybe I might pull it.
I [ __ ] hate
them. That's why I've gave up, bro. Like
the tourist, the only reason I went out
um last Friday is because I had to renew
my passport. So I had to take some pictures.
Um so I had to take some
pictures. Um so I thought, "Fuck it. I
got my hair done and that I thought [ __ ]
it just send it in it. One last last
world for the month. And yeah, it is the
same old and it will always be the same
old. It'll always be the same
old. I remember I said to Adman, "How's
the approaching going, man? How's it
going?" He's like, "Ah, they've all got
boyfriends. That's how it's going." I'll
never forget that. I'll never forget
that. Ah, they've all got boyfriends.
Huh? They all got
boyfriends. Oh, that's funny as
[ __ ] All got imaginary boyfriends.
You won't hear that in
Thailand. A notorious. You won't hear that in
Thailand. I'm an eight. Oh, that's nice
of you to think I'm an eight, bro. Thank you.
Yeah. Also depends on your race as well.
Oh, that's nice of you to think I'm an eight boss.
Everyone gets it
easy. Cuz the thing is, look at that.
Look at that USA Izzy, right? She's like
a four. Yeah, she's legit. That's her in
the picture. She's like a four and she
can get any man probably she wants.
Whereas me, I can't get nothing as an
example. So they can [ __ ] with people,
lead them on, move on to the next, and
then you can't get nothing. That's the
way the dating game
is. Yeah. You gave up though, didn't
you, Dtorius? To be fair, you did give
up, didn't you? Yeah.
What if you went to Scotland, Notorious?
Would they say they got boyfriends there, too?
Yep. Oh, I love you,
bro. That's why I gave up. I need to
eat. I haven't ate today. Some Chinese
Yeah, you have to give up,
lad. Yeah, I I fell out with my mom
today. I told her to drop dead cuz the
women [ __ ] was pissing me off,
bro. [ __ ] hate them, aren't
you? I've already been to Wales three
times and yes, they've got boyfriends
there as well.
I've already been to Wales, bro, three
times. And I've been to Scotland as
well. They all have boyfriends there, too. I
think. No, I can't remember what
happened there, bro. But I never got
anywhere. So, yeah. I've been to Wales,
bro. Do not follow the [ __ ] channel.
I've been everywhere in
England. Why should I give up those
slug? People say that I need to keep
trying and I need to work on
myself. I need to work on
myself. They say that I need to work on
myself. That's what people on Reddit
say. You need to work on yourself.
Yeah. That's why I'm not trying. That's
why I'm not trying,
bro. That That was it for me Friday.
That Friday was it for me, lad.
And yet a woman can get whenever she
wants. She can suck dick whenever she
wants. It's horrible thinking about it,
isn't it? Just thinking about it is mad,
it? It is mad ass.
Yeah. Yeah. I just woke up today pissed off,
lad. I thought some cunt's going to get
it, mate. Yeah.
What about getting a fat woman? They've
all got high standards,
too. They've all got high standards,
Yeah, they've got high standards, too.
Notorious. They've all got
boyfriend. They've all got
boyfriends. Nah, it's not London. It's everywhere in
England. It's everywhere in England. They're all
[ __ ] They're all [ __ ] there. It's
like everywhere in England, mate. I had
it in Leeds. I remember I went to Leeds
once. I remember I went to Leeds
once. I went to leads only went to leads
once and it was pretty much similar there as
well. I don't think the dating game is
for [ __ ] 85% of men to be honest. you
know, and I don't know anything about
gambling. I don't even gamble that much
anymore. What? Small amounts. [ __ ]
hell, I've still got plenty of money,
you know? It's nothing to do with that all. So, the time Yeah. Yeah, pretty
much. Why they are Why is it when you
message somebody on Reddit, you you show
them your experiences, they then block
you? Well, obviously not.
Yeah, but the reason I said other people
is because you was trying to make it
seem like it was only me that experiences
it. So, yeah, that Friday was it for me,
bro. So, the only hope we have is this
bartender meeting us next
week. This bartender, but I don't think
it's going to
happen, but we'll see anyways.
Yeah. And then they blocked me cuz she
was like, "Oh, work on yourself." I
said, "I have worked on myself. I've
gone here. Look, I showed her my
stuff. You need to work on yourself. You
need to work on yourself. You need to
work on yourself." That's that's that's
the famous line, bro. That's the famous
line. Just around the area. I said, "Oh,
I'll give you £500." She suddenly
started replying saying, "Oh, yeah. I'll meet you."
But she's gone quiet. So, like they
always do. So, we'll see if she comes out next week. But
yeah, tempted to go out this week, but
obviously I'm not going to cuz the situation. So,
yeah. So, yay. I fell out with Laney
today. Uh my situation's still the same. Yay. [Music]
Yeah. She blocked me because I was
talking about [ __ ] kids.
Yeah, I was [ __ ] pissed off. I had to
wake up thinking about it, bro. It was [ __ ]
annoying. These [ __ ] women are
[ __ ] annoying how they can
just treat you like [ __ ] ghost you, and
then just get with someone else or just
get with someone else. It's [ __ ]
disgusting. It is actually so disgusting, bro.
It is bad. It's really bad.
I don't even know why she's watching me
on YouTube, the [ __ ]
freak. You know why are you even [ __ ]
watching me, you
freak, you know?
Yeah. Anyways, I'm gone.