Yo,
you know what? Yeah, I'm just going to
stop with these people now.
You know, I was thinking about this last night.
It's actually three
You know what? Yeah, bro. I'm going to
stop arguing with these people now and
I'm just going to let them look stupid.
That's what I'm going to do now.
I don't have no plan for today, bro.
my always saying doing nothing.
But I'm going to stop arguing with these
little skit self-reflectors now that
clearly just want attention.
So yeah, I'm going to let them keep
calling people for what they are and let
them embarrass themselves.
That's what I'm going to do now. Clearly, bro,
just going to let them keep calling
themselves. Let them keep calling
themselves a M. I'm just going to let
them keep self projecting self
protecting their life away, you know?
How would I make them look stupid? Just
let them keep talking about themselves.
You know, when they keep coming on here
saying that people are skinned and
stuff, they're just talking about
themselves. I'm just going to let them
keep talking about themselves now. These
people are here.
Yeah, that's what I'm going to do. I'm
just going to let them keep self projecting.
No, never self projected in my life.
Going back and forth with people that
you never know that's never going to
meet you. That's never going to stop.
Yep. You're not going to get a reaction.
You've been saying that for years. Yep.
You're not going to get a reaction.
Bye-bye. Now, you know, all of these
skinned people, they just want a reaction.
So, they're not getting it anymore.
these little sad little people with no
money, no life. I'm not going to be I'm
not reacting to them anymore. So, yeah.
So, yeah. What What the [ __ ] is there to
There's nothing to argue about.
There's literally nothing to sit there
and argue about. These people have shown
themselves up with a money game. They
have no money to show and stuff. There's
this pointless arguing with these people.
Listen, the more they bring stuff up,
the more stupid they look. The more they
come on here and trying to call other
people's skin, the more it just proves
their skin. It just takes one to no one.
So, just let them keep showing
themselves up. That's what I'm doing. Yeah, man.
let them self-reflect their life away.
Anyways, I'm not replying to that.
You're not getting a reaction. Anyways,
people, uh, what we up to today?
We're playing some GTA. To be honest
with you, I might actually, um, might
actually go for a walk to be honest with you.
Yeah, might do a food shop. Moving on
now. Franklin doesn't come on come out
for a couple of weeks.
We're not reacting to these people
anymore. We're not giving them what they
want. So yeah,
remember the main thing is people,
if you're not fat and ugly like these
people, they're never going to like you.
They're never going to agree with you.
Don't waste your time. Just don't waste
your time with these people. That's what
I'm not doing anymore.
I've done it before, lad. I've shown
these people money. I've had them
running away and then they act like
they've won. Waste of my time. But we
all make mistakes, right? So,
these sad people want a reaction.
These sad skinned people want a
reaction. Anyways, I'm not replying to
your comments now. I'm going to let you
keep wasting your time typing. So, yeah.
Greaves is going to come on in a bit.
Yes, you are on YouTube again.
Oh, yeah. You're not going to get
reaction. I saw that.
Right. Anyways, so Franklin's in the big red car driving around.
Greavves is a bit late today.
Must be having McDonald's.
Where are you greasy? [Music]
See, this is what you need to do. You
need to do content. You need to do
content live streams, not going back and
forth with people that self project.
That's [ __ ] That's a waste of
everyone's time. It's not going to get
you the [ __ ] views in.
It's not going to get you views, man.
You might as well just let these people
just keep embarrassing themselves every day.
Let them embarrass themselves for what
they are and show and show everyone what
they are really.
Matter of fact, I'm going to actually
delete that video actually.
But like, you know, you say you don't
really know about people in here and
stuff, but the more they do this, I said
in the video yesterday, the more Virgin
Boy does this, the more it goes to show
the skint one with no life. The more
they do this
every single day, the more they show themselves up.
because they're not idols that people
look up to. If they had all this money,
all this life, they wouldn't be on there
doing this every day.
I mean, people can go on YouTube with
[ __ ] money, obviously. But they
wouldn't be sat on YouTube doing this every day.
Oh, another self-reflector. I'm not even
going to block the comments. I'm just
going to let them keep showing
themselves up for what they are.
You know what I'm saying?
Just going to let them like show
themselves up. It's funny to be honest.
Uh, he's a sad bastard. That's what he
is. He's a sad bastard. I'm saying guys Boston
and these people in here, you know, like
what they do, they're very, very narcissistic.
very very narcissistic horrible people.
Like at the end of the day, I've had it
in my face, man. Before I'd love to
squeeze one of these [ __ ] skin ugly
people, but I mean, come on, man. It's
not realistic. None of these people ever
going to meet.
They're actual they're very, very narcissistic.
You know, even what they were doing
yesterday, very, very narcissistic,
horrible people. That's why I'll just
leave them to show themselves up now for
what they are.
Cuz we're one here now. We're not going
to talk about money. We're not going to
talk about anything.
And we'll see what happens. We'll see
how the chat goes.
But there's a lot of narcissism on this
um community. I'm not saying every
single person is a narcissist, but
there's a lot of narcissists.
Like when they're talking about how
they've stopped my money when they
literally haven't stopped my money and
they don't know how much money I've got.
But just how them saying it, they're
narcissistic. They're old people that
have nothing. That's why I would leave
them to it now. Just leave them to
self-reflect their life away
just like somebody that gamles their life away.
Yeah, Liam, I'm just going to let these people
argue with themselves now and call
themselves for what they are now. I'm
not arguing with them anymore.
When you start when you start creating
content on your channel, right, and you
stop doing this every day, then I'll
maybe think, h well, maybe these people
aren't the ones that are this and maybe
they aren't the ones that are that. But
so long as they keep doing this, the
more they just show themselves up. So
let them let them call themselves skin.
Let themsel reflect every single day, you know,
on YouTube every day going back and
forth for absolutely no reason.
Yeah. They don't argue with themselves.
I don't even know what what the [ __ ] I'd
even be arguing about. They've been
shown money. They've run away. What's
there to argue about now? It never
happened. Get a [ __ ] grip.
Hey, bro. You're right. I'm not I'm not
um going back and forth with these
self-reflectives anymore, bro.
you know, when they want to try and call
people's skin and all of this. I'm just
going to let them talk about themselves
now, Cory. I'm not going to go back and
forth with these little bongos anymore.
So, I'm just going to let them show people
show people what they are themselves.
That's what I'm going to do now, bro.
Because the more, like I said, the more
they do this, the more they show that
they're the ones that have got no money,
that they ain't got no life. So if you
let if you if you stop replying to these
people when it comes to that, they just
embarrass themselves. Just let them keep embarrassing themselves,
you know? That's what you need to do, bro.
I don't mind other arguments, bro.
Someone wants to join in hangouts and
funny as [ __ ] but
that [ __ ] skin thing is boring now,
bro. Very, very, very boring.
It's really, really boring.
And the more they go, "Yeah, show me a
quid." Yep. We're not entertaining that.
That's self- projecting. That's self-reflecting.
So, uh, we're not entertaining them kind
of comments. But if you want to um,
come and say something else, bro, you
can. Yeah. So, what's the point of And
then the thing is, you're going back and
forth, bro, and no one's going to meet
anyone and no one's going to stop. So,
if they're prepared to keep doing it,
then they're the good ones. You
understand? If they're prepared to keep
doing this, it goes to show that they're
the ones that ain't got nothing. But we
can just laugh at them. You know,
we can just laugh at them, lads.
But yeah, bro,
just do other content and other drama,
bro. That's what you should do.
Like I said, Corin, you're not fat and
ugly and you're better looking than
these people. You've already lost from
the start before you even said anything
because they're never going to agree no
matter what you say.
They're never going to agree with um
what you say. So
that's why it's pointless, bro, with
them. You know what I mean?
Cuz look, they're they're they're double
my age, bro. And they want to go back
and forth on this
as much as they want to go back and
forth on this as much as I keep going
back and forth with them. Like they're
as long as I keep doing it, they're
never going to stop. So make it, bro.
Keep it real, bro. They if they had all
of this money and they had this life,
they wouldn't be on here doing this. You
understand? They wouldn't be on here
doing this, bro. All day, every day with
no end goal. Just let them So just let
them keep talking about themselves. It's funny, bro.
You got [ __ ] people in bed sits
trying to tell you you live with your
mom and you don't even live with your
mom. And even if you [ __ ] did live
with your mom, it's nowhere [ __ ] near
as you're making it out to be. I think
that was a [ __ ] good point.
And don't go on L's channel either. It's
just full of self-reflectors.
Don't go on that channel. Don't go on
the the [ __ ] channel for the self-reflectors
cuz every time you go on
cuz every time you go on there, they're
just going to keep calling you what they are themselves.
They're going to keep looking in their
bank account, seeing no money, and then
calling you skin. That's all that's
going to happen.
Pointless. Pointless argument over and over again.
No, I'm not.
No, he's a snake. So, yeah.
Think of it, bro. If these people had
all of this money, do you think they
would be on here doing this every day?
Do you think that they would be on here
every day if they had all of this money
and they had a life and they weren't sad
individuals? Do you think they'd be
prepared to go back and forth every day
with somebody half their age?
No, they wouldn't. It's because they have nothing.
Do they come on here to feel special? You know,
we got some [ __ ] idiot trying to say
they've stopped my sublet money when
they literally haven't and I've got
savings and I've done more in four years
than they've done in their whole life
with that money that they they never
had. And then I said, "Okay, well then
come and hang out just pay the money
again." They don't. So, so it's just
pointless. It's just pointless arguing
with them, you know.
I'm just chilling, bro. I got no plans
to be honest.
And I also think a lot of them are
actually gay as well because they they
desperately want um a reaction from
somebody half their age.
Like desperately want a reaction from
someone half their age. I think some of
them are actually bisexual or gay to be honest.
That's another gym.
>> Just the same old projecting people that
ain't got a life then.
Same as usual.
That's it really. Yeah.
It's the same people, same people, same argument, same self-reflectors.
Monty snakes me again. Yeah,
he's just a snake. I went to Birmingham
to see him. I don't know if he scored
that because he was crying over Natalie.
He's with Natalie and um yeah, he's just a fake.
He was just a snake.
You remember Cory? The three great pedos.
The three pedos. Not the three great
guys. The free pedos.
Yeah, I went to Birmingham to see Monty and Yeah,
that's a thing.
You know what I find so funny on here,
Ben, is that you got these old people
that call you every day and they don't
even know you and they're never going to
meet you. They're never going to stop.
You know, you're basically [ __ ] from
the start. You didn't realize that. You
know, when you're better looking than
these people and you're younger than
these people, you know, you're you've
just lost anyway, isn't it? You know,
you've just lost everything. you you
every every time you try to argue with
them, they're just going to be biased
and say you didn't show money and say
you didn't show women. That's why they
that's why they all get on on here
because they're all fat and ugly and
old. They're all the same. So anyone
that's younger and better looking than
them, they just go for
they're just angry gamblers that ain't
got no money and ain't got no life.
That's why they come on here every day
trying to tell other people that they
ain't got a job or they ain't got a car
or they they're just talking about their own lives.
And what I was saying as well, Ben, is
that you know the only thing that these
people are guaranteed that they don't
have, they don't have hope cuz they're
too old. So even if all the things that
they try to project onto you is true,
which it isn't, guess what? You have
hope and they don't cuz they're old and
there's nothing that they can say to
that. I think it's just I think it's
just a weird community, bro. To be honest,
40y old nerds talking about people that
they don't even know.
Madness. Mad. Madness.
So, I'll just let them carry on now, you know. strange.
They do it because, you know, it's the
same as what nonslegs is. You know,
they're doing it because they're skin.
They ain't got no life. And that's why
they and that's why they like to try to
talk about other people.
That's what they do. But they don't
bring anyone down. They just embarrass
themselves. I showed my face [ __ ] all
day yesterday. None of these people can
show their face.
So yeah, and they're narcissistic as
well. Very narcissistic.
You got Bob trying to say that he's he
stopped my sublet letter money when he
literally never and I've already got
savings anyways and I don't even go out
much drinking anymore anyways because
I'm [ __ ] because I'm [ __ ] I'm 27.
I'm almost 28.
[ __ ] I had the house for 4 years.
I've got savings. I've got designer
clothes. So what, bro? I'm not I'm not
even going out much anymore now cuz I'm
I've outgrown it.
They're such narcissists to even say
stuff like that. They're just horrible
narcissistic little keyboard warrior
little virgins. That's what they are now.
They ain't got a pot to [ __ ] piss in.
They ain't got no life. Sat on YouTube
calling people they don't know every
day. You know,
and this need and this living with your
mom thing needs to stop. Ben, I was
explaining this. Yeah. They don't even
know who I live. I don't even live with
my mom, firstly. And second of all,
loads of people in London live with
their parents. Literally, loads of
people in London live with their
parents. They either live with their
parents or they live in a box room
unless they had a [ __ ] That's how
people live in London because of the
prices. That's literally how people
live. I don't know. I'm sure you're
aware of this, but they live with either
both their parents or they, you know,
they live with their parent or they live
in a [ __ ] box room, lad.
That's how people live in London.
That's literally how people live. That's
how people live. So, even if you lived
with one parent, bro, it's it's not
ideal, but it's [ __ ] nowhere near as
bad as these people are making it out.
It's nowhere near as bad as these people
are making it out. PE the people that
work in London don't even live by
themselves most of them unless they've
got a kid and they and a person's got a
cancel house by the kid with a kid
literally bro like it's nowhere near as
bad as people make it out to be what
these people need to do is worry about
their own lives and worry about their own finances.
Don't forget Ben. I've lived with
tenants. I've lived by myself. I've
lived in that house by myself.
I've lived with my mom, you know, I've
lived with loads of I've loads um I've
lived in different circumstances, bro.
I've slept on the [ __ ] stairs.
And trust me, it's nowhere near as bad
as these people are making it out to be,
you know? It's nowhere near as bad as
these people are making out to me.
Especially if you're single.
I mean, I people do it even if they can
afford it. I guess they do it to save money.
A lot of people do it.
So when people work, what they normally
do is they rent a room. They don't rent
a house. So you'd actually be uh it's
not even bad even if you live with your
dad or you live with your mom. There's
nothing wrong with it. There loads of
people in London do.
The reason Virgin Boy has got a problem
with it is because he didn't have a
relationship with his mom and his mom
hates him. That's why anybody that has a
relationship with their mother, he
doesn't like it.
But yeah, man. I was subleting that
house for ages, but I was getting like
three grand a month.
No, I lost the house now cuz the baiff
eventually took it back. That had
nothing to do with these people on
YouTube. So, but I was thinking about
this last night. Yeah. Really hard.
And to be honest with you, uh, nods
legs, at the end of it, bro,
yeah, at the end of it, bro,
um, you know, I'm like 28 next month,
and I'm getting old now, and I'm done
with the going out now, and No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. So I feel
like bro it kind of evened itself out
you know even though it is even though
it is like a lot obviously is a big loss
of course but you know when you're like
23 24 25 you know you're in your prime
and going out and I don't really I'm not
going out anymore.
So, not old. I'm not getting old, but
you know what I mean? Like, I'm going
obviously I'm not old in that way, but
like I'm going out like the whole going
out and trying to pull and [ __ ] Like,
you know what I'm saying? And I looked
this up yesterday how how old people was
when they stopped going out. And a lot
of people were my age.
Don't get me wrong. You go out like
twice a month, Ben. Like, you're still
going to go out and drink with money or
without money. But um
it's kind of mad how like
yeah like a lot of people said that they
they they they don't do it as much as as
27 28 but it's not old like you're an
old man but it's just older than like
23. So, think about it, bro. 23 to 24,
Ben. 23 to 27, I never had to work. I
was getting three grand a month.
Imagine that, bro. No working. Still got
designer clothes. All them [ __ ] It's madness, bro.
I won a couple of football bets this
month and last month as well, so
obviously it sucks a bit, but you know,
it is what it is, bro. it.
But think about it now at this time,
bro. Yeah. They never like, bro, you
know, even with people's YouTube. Yeah.
There's people that's made 40 grand on
YouTube, bro. And they've lost it. They
don't get nowhere near as much as they
used to anymore. And the thing is, the
thing is as well,
the thing is as well is that the only
thing that you need to do now is leave.
So even if it takes you twice as long,
slower money is better than no money if
you think about it, bro. Because you're
going to be leaving now, you know?
You're going to be leaving, right? And
when you leave, here's the thing. So
when you leave, bro, like, yeah, even if
if it took you [ __ ] four to 6 months
to save up for holiday, bro, you're
leaving rather than not leaving. So, you
know what I'm saying? Um, but yeah,
I still got some designer clothes and
[ __ ] so it's all good, bro. Like, it's
is a bit [ __ ] but you know, is what it is, man.
Even if you got, you know, you win a
football bet every month, bro. Even if
you got 1,500 a month, that's way more
than enough for a single person. That
doesn't work. That has no rent.
then it would definitely even itself out. So, you know,
it's mad how I had that house for so
long, is it? No one on YouTube made me
lose the house either. I don't know why
they keep saying that. They lit They
really really never cuz think about it,
bro. They I had that house for 4 years.
If anybody on YouTube was going to get a
house, they have no power over getting
someone's the bay lifts coming on
people's door. [ __ ] landlords need to
need to start [ __ ] landlords need to
court proceedings which have nothing to
do with people on YouTube.
They [ __ ] never they try to get my
benefit money stopped
and that's why they go for you. They go
for you because they're jealous. It's
not because of things you've said about
kids or things you've said about women.
Because the thing is Ben, let me tell
you something. They, you know, they like
this reaction. You know, you know when
you give them these mad reactions, oh,
your kids are this, your kids are that,
they like it. Like, deep down, they like
this reaction. Like, don't get don't get
it twisted, bro. They like it. They
actually like it when you react like
that cuz they're sick and twisted.
That's what I'm saying. They're narcissists.
Just like that. Bob, he's another
narcissist. Narcissistic little [ __ ]
That's why they all get That's why they
all get on, Ben. Yeah. Um,
yeah. But yeah, we hate to have my
mothers and sisters. Yeah, bro. Cuz like
I said, it's nowhere near as bad as um
as he's making it out to be. So, you
know, you live with one parent who's a
[ __ ] old woman. You know how big that
house is? Okay. And what
I remember when this [ __ ] used to say
the same [ __ ] when I was 19. If he
didn't get that cancelled bedset, he
would be on the street. If he if he
lived in London, right, if he if if if
that virgin, right, didn't get that cancelled bedset
and he had to work and live in London,
bro, he would be living with his mother
or his dad. He would be living with his
mommy even even at a younger age.
So, um, [ __ ] hell. I don't know how
how people like that can talk about
people's living circumstance, um, living
circumstances. It's [ __ ] beyond me.
Virgins be virgins. You know, what can
we do? Like,
where's Greasy today? H
nothing wrong even with your mother.
Nothing wrong at all. Some self
projection going on there.
Like when you were subleting a house.
Why do you think I lived with mommy?
Mommy fight to save money.
Kieran, let me tell you something, bro.
Yeah. I don't I don't know how I don't
know if you want to agree with this or
not, but bro, there's nothing wrong with
living with your parents. Yeah,
especially if you live in London.
Yeah, there's nothing wrong with living
with your your mom. Most people in
London live with their parents or they
live in a box room. So, they work these
mad hours and then they and they have to
rent a room. They don't even live by
themselves. They live with [ __ ]
tenants. What the [ __ ] bro? Why does
this virgin go on like it's it's the
worst thing living with a parent?
Like it's literally nowhere near as bad
as these people make out. You know, it's
not like you can [ __ ] buy a house
with [ __ ] one or two pound. Do you
know what I'm saying, bro? What the
[ __ ] It's a madness, bro.
They go on about
It's mad, Kieran. Bro, it actually is a
madness. What the [ __ ]
You know, even when I was in the house,
I was paid. Did you know how much I was
paying my mom? £200 a month,
having a nice room, nice bed, and I was
paying my mom £200 a month. Why the [ __ ]
wouldn't you live with your [ __ ] mom?
Why wouldn't you live with your mom?
You know, it would help your [ __ ] mom
out. You [ __ ] save money. Why
wouldn't you? You're single now. You're
[ __ ] single now. So what? What?
When I had that house, I used to go to
my mom's at the weekends to get a proper sleep.
You know what I mean, Kieran?
Yeah. I used to do it to get a proper sleep, lad.
When I had that foot injury, bro,
sometimes I couldn't sleep because of
the noise they were making. So, I went
to my mom's.
Nowhere near as bad as that punt's
making out. If it was somewhere like
Liverpool, right, and you could buy a
house like really really cheap, then
okay, yeah, I understand it. You know,
you're being a burden, you know, you
might be a burden with at your mom, you
know, and it's really cheap, like super
cheap, then okay, yeah, fair enough. But
at the end of the day, lad, like
Kieran, people in London, they live with
their parents. Most people that you will
you you you will find actually live with their parents.
They live with their mom and dad.
Obviously, my dad's dead. You know what
I'm saying? But you know what I'm
saying? They they live with their mom
and they live with their mom and they
live with their dad or they live in a
box room. That's what that's how people
live in London, bro. Why do you think so
many people move out of London? Because
it's so expensive.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah, man.
I'm getting old, Kevin, bro. I feel 100
years old. I actually do, bro.
I actually feel 100 years old.
I fully do, bro.
100 good [ __ ] years old, lad.
You know, I was thinking about this in
bed. I was just telling uh Ben, you
know, you know how like I'm not even
going to be going out much anymore drinking because
you just outgrow it.
I'm [ __ ] 28 next [ __ ] month. And I
looked on Reddit, a lot of people said
that they were the same age.
They said that they were the [ __ ]
same age when they stopped the whole
clubbing and that
they stopped the the whole going out
clubbing and that you know. So yeah, you
might have lost the house but bro you
lost the [ __ ] part for [ __ ] going
out as well. So even itself out really
if you think about it.
I don't know what I would have done in
them years K without that help.
you know, trying to go out three times a
week. I don't know what I would have
done, bro. Honestly, I don't know what I
would have done.
Reminds you I need to get these Stone
Island jumpers dry cleaned. Honestly, I
don't know what I would have done, bro.
I think about what what would have
happened in that situation.
Honestly, just trying to think. Um,
[ __ ] knows, bro. [ __ ] knows.
I might have not even been able to get
got laid, Karen.
Who [ __ ] knows, lad?
What would have I done for them years?
Yeah, I could do I could rent a room,
but then I wouldn't have much money at
the end of the month,
so I wouldn't do that.
>> Yeah, I mean, I could, but I wouldn't do that.
I'm trying to justify it. I can go out
whenever I want. I can go out every week
if I want to.
Stop self- projecting. I can go out
whenever I want to.
I can afford more than you'll ever be
able to afford.
I can go out whenever I want. I can go
out today I want to do. So again, you
don't know what people have. You don't
know what people don't have.
So stop self projecting. Oh, we said
we're not entertaining you little self
projectors anymore, bro. So, stop coming
on our channel.
Cuz by the looks of it, bro, it looks
like you people can't afford nothing.
You're the ones that are sat on YouTube
every day arguing with people, arguing
with people that you don't know.
You are the ones sat on YouTube arguing
with people every day that you don't
know. So, I mean, and that's the thing
here. And you should just let these people, right?
Right. you just let these people keep
talking about skin and whatever because
they're just talking about themselves.
Like there's just no point in
entertaining them. And bro, how many you
know, Kieran, even when I had that
house, there's there'd be times I didn't
even go out for 6 weeks. There'd be
times, bro. Do you know when I had that
house like a few months ago, I wasn't
going out every week. I wasn't going out
like every two weeks.
I swear to God, bro, I was going out
every two weeks. I swear to God, bro, I
was going out every two weeks.
Every three weeks sometimes.
I think it was like every two, three
weeks, bro, when I was living in that
house. But I didn't bother with it. I
didn't bother with it anymore, bro.
Really? I just used to chill and play [ __ ] GTA, bro.
Yeah, bro. Like it always come. Yeah, it
is the same. It's just the same thing,
bro. It's just the same thing.
They're always going to sit there and
call you skint, lad. Kieran, they're
always going to call you skin.
You get three grand a month, they call
you skin. You show them six grand, they
call you skin. You get a grand a month,
they call you skin. Just let them just
keep self projecting, bro.
Just leave them to it. Let them look stupid.
Yeah, bro. Like, yeah.
And I never went out every week. For the
past 6 months, I didn't go out every
week. I might not even go out this week.
Does that mean I can't afford to go out this week?
I can go out this week if I wanted to, Kieran.
But I don't even know if I bother.
Don't know if I [ __ ]
don't know if I'd even bother to be honest.
Maybe I will, maybe I won't. Depends how I feel.
>> Oh, here we go with the snake.
>> Oh. Oh, here we go. So, why you why you
say you're done with me? Yeah, but then
you sending me um Screamyards links to my Facebook.
>> I want to know why you I want to know
why you snake,
>> PJ. Only the one who snakes is you.
You're not a rat. >> Okay.
F is you. The only one who talks about
being skint every day is you.
>> No, that's them. No.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. They
have been coming on here for years
projecting their skintess onto me. When
I show them money, they will run away.
Get get your facts right first.
>> When you don't get laid, you protect
women when you don't get laid. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay,
Snake. Okay, Snake. >> EJ,
>> just because Just because I beat Just
because I beat everyone at the money
game. You don't have to cry.
>> EJ, you know if you want the money game. Really?
>> Wait one second. One second. Hold on.
Hold on. I just seen this comment.
>> So, it's dumb and dumber and the
dumbest. So, you need to come on now.
You're saying it's dumber and dumber,
but the dumbest is not here, which is
you. You need to come on dumbest.
>> EJ, you're the dumbest by reacting to these clowns.
>> No dumbest
>> 300 p.m. Mongol, you two chicken. Oh, to
me when you come to me when you man like you said
the police you grasp
called you kids
in Birmingham and we'll go
off you in lad
to come to park mongol why are you scared
>> I'm not going to go in that natalie's
not going to hold your hand and I punch
you to the floor.
>> Jimmy, have you got what? Have you had your cheeks? Are
>> you a man child? Mongol. Are you
>> a man
by 300 p.m. Are you a chicken? Why don't
we come back? That's easy.
>> N the [ __ ] up, you [ __ ]
>> Then you could No, you need to grow the
call. You keep calling me out. I keep
>> You're calling me out. Also, I told you
where to go. I'm not running to no location more.
I'm not going to go to a location where
you're not going to be
>> where you going to be. I'm not going to
go to more locations where you're not
going to be >> mrified
to come to [ __ ]
DJ's more sensible than you. Why don't
you [ __ ] stop phoning the
>> He's more sensible than you, you [ __ ]
meet me at Mr. Tumble. Mr. Tumble
yourself, Mr. Tumble.
>> Don't want to get Shrek Shrek. Who's Shrek? [ __ ] man.
Step up, man up, and come and meet me on your own.
>> All right. Okay. So, no. Then what did
he just say about there by 3 p.m.
Mongol? Are you going to let me down?
>> No. I want to know who SK is.
>> Okay, [ __ ] You go live when you're
there and I'll be straight down.
>> Go live. Why the [ __ ] I don't even I
can't even go from Canon Park.
>> I can't go live. I don't have a live channel anymore.
>> So, I can't go live.
>> You're the one who wants to
go to city center and just go live.
>> Get her
on YouTube. End of story. End of story.
Why don't you Why don't Why don't you
just do that? See how much of a grownup man you
>> I'm fighting while the cameras pee you.
>> Well, go can't you go to like a park or something?
>> This guy's not going to meet you. This
guy's not going to meet you anywhere you
>> Yeah. But so what's the point of the
argument then? It's pointless. is
[ __ ] down here special.
He's a funny bro. is Mike
>> and I don't self these people on me
every day open your eyes
again for John >> Eldidge money yeah
show us your money are you going to show
us your museum money as you never go out
>> and another thing I'm not I'm not
reacting to these clowns anymore
>> you do react
they They can call people skin all they
want. I'm not reacting to them anymore.
>> PJ just like
>> Yeah, good for you. I'm not I'm not I'm
not I'm not going to react to these
self-reflecting skin comments anymore.
So, you can keep calling me what you
are. I don't care. >> PJ
you call people skin cuz you're skin. It
takes one to no one.
>> But there's no 200 quid. Come on, PJ.
I'll show 200 quid if you show. not
playing these games.
Not playing these games.
This is what they want. They want a
museum piece like that.
>> Show money away. We played this game
before. We played this game before.
>> That's can't use a bank account cuz he's
a [ __ ] DWP.
>> And another thing, Timmy,
see what I mean? Show me some money, PJ.
>> Yes, I've shown you money. I've shown
you I've shown you six grand. There's a
lot more I can show than that. I love
PJ. I'll go to the bank PJ and show the [ __ ] grand
money and I'll go to the show.
>> Not not not the museum piece. He's got
no bird, no family, no hope.
>> Imagine Imagine being 30 [ __ ]
collecting fuckingimmy. Timmy, how much
is that to go out? Jimmy Mashing 40 and
looking like how much is that [ __ ]
going out first be a loser like you
>> [ __ ] virgin
you are a virgin Mongol anyway Mongol
are we meeting at 3's
these two both are little [ __ ]
They've been arguing.
>> These people they've been arguing for
[ __ ] months. No one's trying to meet
anyone. It's [ __ ] pathetic. You're
not about a lot of you.
You're on YouTube.
No one's going to meet anyone.
>> [ __ ] hell, man.
>> There you go. I just told you to meet
him at the park wings.
The same [ __ ] argument. It's not the
same. If one of you wanted to meet, you
would go live somewhere. Any of you, you
would go live somewhere. One of you, you
don't want to meet. You don't want to
>> You don't want to [ __ ] meet. If
somebody wanted to meet, they would have
[ __ ] went live.
>> He can't phone the [ __ ] police in the
park. He's a [ __ ]
>> It's [ __ ]
[ __ ] if you're not there, you a [ __ ] for life.
>> I'm a [ __ ] for life. I'm not going to
be late to me. I just told you I'm not
going to be lur.
>> You two are little soft asses. Oh my god.
>> PJ, I'm not meeting this basty crew who
I've already battered.
>> You're absolute soft asses.
>> AJ, you're the softest in this
community. I'm sorry. Why are you
arguing if you're not going to meet him?
>> Ask him. Why is he arguing? I got better
things to meet you. So, just leave it in
now in it. I got better things to do
instead of meeting a down in it.
>> Do you know what I mean? I got better
things to do.
Okay, now I could be having a wank for
[ __ ] sake, man. A wank's not important
meeting for [ __ ] sake.
>> You know what I'm saying?
>> Is that what you pig do is mate a lot?
>> [ __ ] rings please and mommy because
he's so scared of YouTube.
>> I'm not scared of YouTube. One little bit.
So, what's PJ doing then when he say
apologizing to people when he got hold of him?
>> Yeah, I got caught off guard.
>> Got caught on guard.
>> You got beat by Timmy Aldridge.
>> I've never been beaten by Timmy Aldridge's
>> in the station.
>> Oh my day. >> What?
>> You shag. You shag Timmy. Timmy owns you.
Tiby's got Timmy got more money than you money.
>> You've been to Timmy's house. What was it like?
>> More money than you. It
>> got more money than me. He spends his
money straight away as soon as he gets
it. Like now going on a cheap bus with
with Tiger and Money Mike.
>> You know
>> that's what he does in you had nine
burgers to last you two weeks.
>> BJ, them burgers were nice. So don't
choose them burgers. Well, what do you
got to even afford?
>> I couldn't afford. I spent [ __ ] £200
when I was with you, you [ __ ]
>> Did you? [ __ ] What you saying [ __ ] for?
>> Yes, I did.
>> Well, that's what you do, PJ.
>> No, I don't [ __ ]
>> And that's what you call a snake.
>> No. No.
>> Anyways, why did you get me into this [ __ ] community?
>> EJ, you're the one who got me into this
[ __ ] community. No one else but you got
me into the [ __ ] mongos. Yeah, you're
the one who you're the one who was in
this community before me. So you're
calling yourself a [ __ ] right there, PJ.
>> Well, it is a it is a [ __ ] community.
I'm not lying.
>> Oh, is that why you got me on? Cuz I'm a [ __ ] Yeah,
>> you're not coming in, LJ. Go and get
attention somewhere else. Go
self-reflect somewhere else. Bye-bye. You're back.
>> You're scared, L.
>> Yeah, I'm terrified, bro. Yeah, I know.
>> Yeah, you were. I love to meet Lil J.
>> Why do you never Why do you never go on
these panels then?
Why do I never go into his panels? >> Yeah.
>> Why are you going to go on to someone
who selfrelexes on everybody and does
the same [ __ ] [ __ ] every day? It's
got the same shitty pictures.
>> There you go then. That's why I don't
let him on.
>> Yeah, they'll let you go then cuz he's
just a repeating who sit there talks
about everybody else but himself.
>> What? And you and you read the chat as
well is it?
>> I don't read the chat cuz I can't read
chats. Yeah, but you know what they're
doing, is it?
>> Yeah, I know what they're doing. Yeah.
>> Let's be friends again.
>> I'm not being your friend. >> Why?
>> You couldn't even apologize to Natalie.
>> I didn't even do anything.
>> You didn't even call do anything. You
called her a slag. You called her a [ __ ]
You said she's ugly. Not bothered about
the googly thing, but obviously you
wanted to meet her yourself. Peas. Yeah,
>> she wanted to meet me.
>> No, you wanted to meet her as well.
>> No, she wanted to meet me.
>> Yeah, but you wanted to meet her. Yeah.
>> No, but that was that was funny. The
video you done crying of her though. It
was funny, isn't it?
>> I'm going to ask if I was crying in
that. I bet you just bruising my mind.
At least I cry over a woman. I've never
>> You're taking a piss in it. Why? Why
would I take the piss?
>> I don't know. I just feel like you are.
>> Why would I take the piss, PJ?
>> I don't know.
>> Well, I've never cried over a woman.
Never. Not even cried over fat Kay.
>> Never cried over that whale. Not once.
Not a That's the first time I cried over a woman.
>> Oh, bless you then.
>> First time and [ __ ] last time.
Bless you then.
>> But that's cute though if you c over a
woman. Bless you. Is it?
>> Yeah, but you can't get laid though.
>> I know, man. I'm a virgin.
>> So what?
>> Are you sure?
>> Yeah, I'm a virgin. So what? Yeah.
>> What's wrong with being a virgin?
>> Nothing. Prostitute don't count by the
way either by losing your peculiar.
>> I know I'm a virgin.
>> Yeah, I know. I know. He was mates with
N legs back in the day. Monty, reason
you met. Yeah, I know. Everyone knows
that though. Everyone know that. So what?
>> I was never m with N legs. Say that was
Mitch with shy long legs.
>> You [ __ ] introduced me to that horrible virgin.
>> No. No.
>> That [ __ ] skinned version. You [ __ ] did.
>> We can do it.
>> I didn't.
I was going to give you some basketball shorts.
>> Don't want it. Keep it.
>> You know what I find so mad? How these
people try to call people every day that
they don't even know? I find that funny. Me, Karen.
calling people skin because they are skin.
>> What? What? What do you mean kissing? Do
you mean kissing Mitchell with the
banana? Not Emma. You're on about there.
>> Monty, do you remember he's asking is it?
>> Yeah, but PJ as well.
Why are you Why you not cold approaching
now? Why you not out?
>> At least I can get a woman to [ __ ]
herself with a banana, guys.
>> DJ can't even do that. But
when's the last time you give someone [ __ ]
>> Never. Remember when PJ booties? Oh,
that's repeating. Stop repeating. Why?
>> Why did Why did you ask me if you could
give me a [ __ ] when you was at my gap? Uh
>> cuz it was funny.
>> What? You ask me to give you ask me if
you could give me head. >> Yeah.
You sick [ __ ]
>> Listen, um, Monty. Yeah. You know that
account saying, "I pooed my pants." Do
you know they've been saying the same
comment for like six years?
>> Got to believe it though, PG.
>> Yeah. So, why do they keep repeating it?
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah, you did, didn't you? You shot yourself.
>> So, why do these people repeating it then?
>> I remember your dirty boxes.
>> Yeah. Oh, that was that's our little secret.
I'm joining Discord.
>> Are you?
>> Yeah. With the three great guys.
>> What? The three great pedos. Yes.
>> The three great guys.
>> The great pedos. PJ.
>> That's another thing. Oh, that's another
thing. Greavvesy. Do you know what Monty
did when when I went back to Hes and
this is actually a true story. He wanted
he wanted to [ __ ] escort.
Did I fall? I swear to God on my [ __ ]
dead mom's life. He said get an around
here and I said it's a bit too late and I didn't
do that anymore.
>> I swear to God my mom's life he did.
That's the truth. I swear to God cameras,
>> you know. I swear to God. I swear to
>> I swear on my mom's life. I swear to God.
>> I swear to I swear to God I'm not even
joking, bro. We got places full of
>> my mom's life. On my mom's life. He
wanted me to get an escort.
>> Why didn't you get one, PJ?
>> Because I didn't have the money on me.
>> Don't you remember? Don't you remember?
I left my bank card at home and had to
get my my sister to send me money.
>> PJ, we was in a lie that all of this is [ __ ] >> Huh?
>> I did not want to escort.
>> Yes, you [ __ ] did. And I I can I can
swear on anyone's life. I can
but I would never ever go near the
escort. Even if
>> when we got back to your apartment, you
wanted an escort.
>> Did I?
>> Yeah. Probably cuz you was hoing from
the drink like I was and I said, "Oh, I
don't get into my alcohol. It's plenty
hard for me to get into a nonp I wish I
recorded it. I swear to God, I wish I
recorded it. to recording it.
>> You did want an escort. Why are you
lying for? You did. Stop lying.
>> Yeah. Even if I did not, I would piss
that place for the cameras anyways.
>> Well, there you go.
Asking for a escort.
>> No, I can't recall ask asking for a yes.
>> Well, you [ __ ] did.
>> Well, if I did, I did, but I don't recall that.
>> Exactly. If if you know you didn't, you
would know you didn't. So that just goes
to show you did.
>> I don't recall. I don't recall asking
for esco. I was pissed. So if I did, I
don't if you know you never done it, you
would be certain you did. You did do it.
You did ask for it.
>> I am certain that I didn't do it.
>> You did. You [ __ ] did.
>> I am certain that I did not do it with as you
>> did. You actually gay as [ __ ]
>> That's as [ __ ] bendable gear. That is
>> You wanted an escort,
>> EJ. You wanted the escort,
>> but you couldn't get one because you
were skinn like your boyfriend. Nons
legs both skinn
I might be yours, mate. Actually, this
could piss you off now.
>> You You You're already his mate.
>> I've never heard.
>> You're already his mate, is it?
>> Easiest one of excuses. No, but you're
already his mate in it.
>> PJ, you you talk about Sean every day.
Like you want to bend him over or something.
>> It's funny because he's obsessed. It's
funny to talk about him.
Make a tit of himself every day on YouTube.
>> But you're making this yourself. No,
>> you know what I'm saying?
>> Calling everybody skin calling people
skin. They're calling me skin
>> because PJ
I am skin. Um I I never showed money and
and made these people run away. I know.
I'm so skinned. I know, bro. Thank you.
>> Yeah. He's going to run away from you.
>> Well, ask these people.
>> [ __ ] only person who would actually
run away from you. That's Casper the
[ __ ] friend to go. So he don't really
run away from anybody.
>> You know
will probably run away from you. It's Casper.
>> He's was 14 when he met Monty. He was
20. Then Monty met PJ when he was 15.
Yeah. Monty. Yeah. Yeah, money met me
when I was 15. Just about to be
>> Yeah, wrong with that either way.
>> with that either way. You make you do
people fighting over Britney? >> Brittney.
>> Oh, PG. It's like yourself. I don't love you.
>> Fighting over Britney. Is it
>> PJ? I've never fought over Britney in my
life. Once she's too young, obviously
not much. She's in her 20s obviously
now. But [ __ ] still still know
you you know the truth PJ know the truth. Yeah.
>> You met through the community while I
was in Yeah. >> Mhm.
>> Yeah. So I got you into that community
but I w you met SH.
>> Yeah. I wish you never [ __ ] got me
into that [ __ ] pedo community.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I went mates with him. So
you met him through someone else through that.
>> But I'm just saying I wish you never got
me in just it through me. You met him
through someone else.
>> Why did you introduce me to that community? >> Why?
>> Well, what why was you talking to a gay
[ __ ] old kido?
>> You was
that Kron? What do you think of the
three the the the free pedos? The three great pedos.
>> Yeah, cuz I met you in that old old
man's chat room and then I got you into
the community what I was in
>> and then you met John
through someone in that community. So,
not through me.
>> The three great pedos.
This is the thing, PJ. Why do you meet
[ __ ] weirdos? Like what? Jack the Ripper
>> because I didn't know what he was like.
>> Didn't know what he were like. Just let
me explain to the community what Jack
the Ripper is like. And you went and
meet And you went and met him. Jack the
Ripper is a kind of a man who will jump
on a bed completely butt naked bouncing
around with his stick dangling out to his legs.
Yeah. And that's a chat room with full
of people in it. He's not [ __ ]
scared. There' be a couple of times he
come in the chat room and he' be a
stuffed teddy and he's and he shagged
the teddy bear and he [ __ ] his dick
move on the [ __ ] floor. And these are the people.
>> What's your plan? Are you staying on this community?
>> No, I'm just jumping plat platform to
platform like everybody else does. I'm
not going live no more.
>> You like this community though, is it?
>> No, I just want to destroy the great
[ __ ] pedos. The great three pedos.
>> No, you're one of them. So, it's the
great four pedos now. >> Nah.
You're [ __ ] aren't you?
>> I'm not [ __ ] I'm [ __ ] I've got a
woman who knows about the community,
>> who knows everything what they do either way.
>> So, I'm I'm right.
>> Would this Would this community ever change?
>> Why the [ __ ] would I want to get with a
woman off YouTube? Yeah. Knowing that, you know,
>> would this community ever change?
>> EJ, you will never change. Yeah. But
will the community change?
>> It doesn't matter about the community.
It matters about what you do, done it,
and you can't change.
>> Yeah. But will they stop repeating?
>> It's not repeating, is it? When you do it back.
>> Okay, then. Why won't them?
>> So why do you repeat back and call these people skint?
>> Because they go for me first.
>> Yeah. So that means you repeat. So if I
So then if I don't repeat and I ignore
them, then they're talking about
themselves. Is it?
>> Nice girl. Bringing up something different. >> Huh?
>> Bringing up something different in it.
>> So So if they if they What I'm saying is
if they keep calling me skin and I
ignore them, then they're skin isn't it?
>> That's what I mean. They're skin.
They're skin. That's up to them. If they
want to be skin,
>> that's up to me if I want to be skin or
not. That's up to them.
I don't know why they do this though. Huh?
>> Why do you do it? Why do you do it back?
>> Because they do it to me.
You say that these people are old farts, Monty.
>> A lot of them are old farts. But you're
going to be one of these old farts soon. Juan,
you're going to be one of these old
farts on YouTube. He deceives these most
of these old parts. Yeah.
>> Bongastic beast needs a kicking.
>> You can't even kick a football straight. Shut up.
>> It's the same people in it.
>> You have to push your sections to
[ __ ] kick them all. You bastards.
>> It's the same people in it.
>> Most of these suit you
>> disabled pervert.
Most of these actually suit you.
>> They call you a disabled pervert.
>> How can I be a pervert when I'm in a
relationship and these are not? These
are all perverted by getting women
pissed and then sending them money for getting naked.
That's what what you call pered.
>> The bombs.
>> Yeah. Ugly bomb.
It is like a bomb. Huh?
>> Yeah, he look like you bomb, don't he? >> No,
>> he does. >> How?
>> He look like you. I'm sure that bomb's
your lost brother.
>> No, mate.
>> I think he is.
>> No way.
>> Cuz she makes your mommy run away. >> Really?
>> Where? Where did your mom go anyways?
>> I don't know. You tell me.
>> Where your mom gone? It's not that song
in it. Where's your mommy gone?
>> It's funny, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Like like your mom's had enough of
you being on YouTube and she's had
enough of your behavior. You [ __ ] up.
>> Yeah, man. YouTube.
>> I know you do. PG. Mom might come back
if you get off YouTube.
>> You need You need to get off YouTube.
>> You got YouTube first. You got off
YouTube first and I get off YouTube after you.
>> No, you first.
>> I'm already off YouTube. You [ __ ]
>> But Monty, why do these people keep
calling me skint? I'm not skin.
>> You see what I mean? Because you are skint. Yeah,
>> you skin virgin boy by table for one.
>> Yeah. And you cry over a [ __ ] slag
who's [ __ ] [ __ ] every man in Birmingham.
>> Yeah, but this is where you're going
wrong. You're repeating.
>> Yeah, you're repeating as well.
>> Yeah, terrible for one, is it?
>> Well, you got you got See, the thing is
most people in here are on my side and not yours.
>> Yeah. And I don't know why. Cuz the way
you treat women.
>> I can. Yeah. What? Because I don't cry
over women like you.
>> Well, at least I got a woman on my car. Fil.
>> Did [ __ ] just say he is off YouTube
yet? Here he is. What a spaz. >> Yeah, >> exactly.
>> Yeah. Like I just said I'm a go on other
people's panel, not me.
>> Yeah, he's still on YouTube.
>> Yeah, I'm still on YouTube.
These people on my side owner
had to get his mom to pay for his clothes dicks. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. So why was you claiming benefits
of for your mom?
>> One guy has been off YouTube for months.
He wasn't on when he went to Blackpool, too.
So why why why do you [ __ ] get car
allowance for your mom and all that PG? Yeah,
>> I don't know what you're talking about.
>> Well, what? You don't know what I'm talking about? >> No,
>> you're going about people being skin,
but you got all for your mother. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I don't know what you're talking about.
>> You really don't know what I'm talking about.
>> I'm not even arguing with this [ __ ]
[ __ ] I've already said everything
I've had to say. It's just repeating
now, you know.
>> I know, babe. So why is there send me a
link on Facebook to join your [ __ ] Discord?
>> Cuz I wanted to ask you why you snake,
>> PJ. The only one who snakes is you. And
that's basically repeated.
>> You know, they they're asking me to own
you. They said own this freak. See
>> own then PJ. That's own.
>> Okay. How do you spell your name?
>> That's just repeating is it really? So that really
that's just repeating.
>> How do How do you spell your name?
>> Repeat. Yeah, that's just repeated.
>> How do you spell it though?
>> I'm not spelling [ __ ] for you. PJ really
owning anybody, is it? That's like something.
Oh [ __ ] PJ, you need to grow up big
time. No wonder your mom [ __ ] you up.
>> So how she didn't [ __ ] me up. I see my
mother would [ __ ] you up. Your mom
[ __ ] you up. Yeah, because you're a
loner. You ain't got no It's a table for
[ __ ] one all the time.
>> How do you spell your name?
You destroyed your sister's life. You
destroyed your [ __ ]
>> You destroyed You destroyed your life.
>> You destroyed my kids my that would care
that you done now.
>> You destroyed kids life, mate.
>> That's what it comes to. Kids with you
PJ. You're not allowed nowhere near your
niece or nephew.
>> Okay. You keep telling yourself that.
>> I don't really keep telling myself that.
How do you
call your sister, aren't they?
>> How do you spell How do you spell Natalie?
>> Your niece and nephew are in care now, aren't they?
>> How do you spell Natalie?
>> Yeah, but aren't your sister's kids in care?
>> Aren't your sister's kids in care?
>> How do you spell Natalie?
>> I spell it when you answer that
question. Aren't your sister's kids in care?
>> No. And they're not my kids. They're my
sister's kids. We're talking
>> We're talking about your kids. Yeah, my
kids are not in care. They're with my mom care.
>> No, they're not. They're with my mom.
That's different is the new stepdad.
>> Why isn't low name my kids? PJ.
>> How How do you spell How do you spell PJ?
>> PJ Easy, is it? PJ PJ.
>> What's 4 + 4?
>> 4 + 4. That's eight in it.
>> What's 8 plus 8?
AJ, we're not doing this [ __ ]
It's just repeating in it.
>> Yeah, but you like to repeat. So
repeat. So I repeat.
>> You say table for one skin. That's
that's that's repeating. So I'll repeat then.
>> EJ your skin.
>> What's What's one What's one?
>> You can't get laid. No woman wants one
in Birmingham or out of Birmingham.
>> What's one time one? Even your Even a
woman in your life doesn't want you
one times one.
>> EJ, stop repeating though. Yeah.
>> So you you can't even spell your own
name. How can you talk about anyone?
>> I can't spell my own name. I'm not saying
and this te dating app or something.
Yeah. At least we'll bring up the
repeating [ __ ] I'm not repeating.
>> I don't have to sit with you. I I don't
have to sit here and bring all this
[ __ ] up like I already have about 5,000 times.
>> I don't have to sit here and explain
that anymore. Do you either way or PJ?
>> But why would you shag an 18year-old at
being at um 27?
>> Uh cuz it's legal.
>> Doesn't matter if it's legal. She's
still a teenager.
>> You went after [ __ ] 14y old at 25. So
I don't know. I've never been out with
that any of that.
>> You was after Britney.
>> I wasn't after Britney at all. So why
would you [ __ ] Why do you stalk women anyway?
>> I would get with an 18 cuz it's legal.
>> Yeah. No, no. I just said like if they
Birmingham that we was talking to I
would I would have [ __ ] her. She I
don't give a [ __ ]
>> That's the thing. You're a weirdo. Yeah.
>> Why? Because I don't go for 14y olds like you.
>> Well, no. But the thing is is you only
go off with one finger, one thing finger
on and that's just to try and get funny.
>> And every time nine out of one none field,
>> you stalk a lot of women. The one who the woman
>> Okay. The one who didn't want to give
you a [ __ ] didn't want to sleep with
you when you paid for a beer and all
that but wine.
>> Yeah. You know what that one is? You
were going off your red at her cuz she
paid for a beer. Why you you don't know that?
>> Because she started on me. So I started
on her and I messed with her family. She
wanted to be a [ __ ] So I was a comeback to her.
>> Oh. Oh. So So she's a cult for not
giving you edge. Yeah. She's a cult. I [ __ ] her.
>> If you poke [ __ ] her.
>> And another thing is And another thing
is she started it. She started it. So
what did she start? Why did she start
saying she feel uncomfortable around you?
>> No. making up stories and being a little snake.
>> No, no.
Being a little snaky littlebody
and they actually Monty, they started it
and couldn't finish it. So what? Okay. What?
>> They didn't like it.
>> Who else? Who else?
>> Who else? Who else? This launch PG.
>> There is no loads. There is no load. The
[ __ ] started it. The [ __ ] started it
wanted to be a [ __ ] They're a bit
What about the ones who said they got
boyfriends and all that?
>> And also when I messaged their also when
I messaged their family, you was
laughing about it.
>> Well, exactly. A stalker, a rat.
>> Yeah, but you were laughing about it.
>> I miss it. I weren't laughing at it. I
told you you're in a rank.
>> You know that USA is Yeah, she deserved
it. She's a little [ __ ] I don't give a
>> You don't You see what I mean? What? Do
you know what I'm saying, Cory? Yeah.
>> You abuser to women. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. You know what? Yeah.
>> Stupid little [ __ ] walk all over me like you.
>> What? What? Because now they didn't want
to meet you. You call the over there in
a slag and all that. She didn't want to meet you.
>> That's not what you didn't want to though.
>> Oh, she didn't want to.
>> But she did.
>> You didn't want to? PJ. No. No. Why? Why
am I not allowed? So why why was I not
allowed to defend myself against that
USA? Is he
>> Why you have found me involved in it
threatening behavior and [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I asked them to apologize numerous
times. I said, "Can you just apologize, please?"
>> threatening. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I said, "No, I said, can you just
please apologize?" I said it multiple
times and they wanted to keep being a
[ __ ] So they got they got it back
because to [ __ ] do [ __ ]
>> You know what I'm [ __ ] saying. Yo,
they [ __ ] going to end up killing women
one of these days out on the street.
>> Yeah. Really? Really?
>> So So it's okay for them to be a little [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> What? What? It's all right for them
getting turned down. Do
>> you know what I mean?
>> It's all right to get turned down, PGA. Yeah, it's
>> I just don't like little [ __ ]
>> I wish you a [ __ ] to you explain PGA.
>> I've explained it a million times.
Everyone knows the story.
>> Well, I don't person knows the story.
Don't. Don't you, Kieran? Even Kieran
knows the story.
>> How does she sn
I've explained it a million times.
>> Come on. How does she snake you? In what
way did did she a million times?
>> What? What? Because she didn't sleep
with you. Yes.
>> Yeah. Cuz Yeah. Cuz she didn't sleep
with me. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
>> [ __ ] Kira knows the story, man. >> Yay.
He He can't. He doesn't know the full
story. How it all happened. You
>> Yes, he does. Because I've told >> him.
>> I've told him.
>> Yeah, but the full story. The full
>> The full story.
>> Well, there's two sides of the story. P. Yeah.
>> Do you know what I'm saying? Do you know
what I mean, bro?
>> I know what you can get like P. Yeah.
When you get turned down a woman, you
start chucking your dirty out your mouth.
>> You wanted to be a nasty little
narcissistic [ __ ] making up story. So I
gave her what for?
>> Well, saying she didn't sleep with you.
Obviously, she did.
>> No, it wasn't. No, it's not about saying
she didn't sleep with It's not that she
didn't say she slept with people, right?
It's the fact that she was making up
[ __ ] stories and then when I asked for apologizing,
>> being a little [ __ ]
>> But what do you see with me nurse?
>> She is a [ __ ]
>> No, I'm asking you what do you see with
me nurse and she started trying to get
rude. See the thing is Monty with people
like you right and with these women
they're big until they meet their match.
>> It's same with these women. They want to
be go around being a [ __ ] to people and
then as soon as
they're a [ __ ] woman. Stop your [ __ ] then. Simple.
>> When you when a woman turns you down,
you don't like it.
You don't like it. When she's got a
boyfriend, you don't like it.
>> It's not the same excuse. It's the truth.
is your rare [ __ ]
>> No, I just don't like little [ __ ] with
attitude like her. Little entitled [ __ ]
that think they're better than people.
>> Even if she is,
>> she was being a [ __ ] Like, bro, she
legit was being a [ __ ] You
>> Kieran. Kieran Kieran. She legit was
being a [ __ ] Like, who does she think
she is? Like, agree with me, bro. That's
fine if they don't want to agree with
me. That's They don't have to. Like, I
know what happened. I know what they're like. So,
>> hang on. She lives in one of the best
countries in the world. PGA America. So, why?
Bro, most people in America are on
anti-depressants. Most people there are
killing themselves now.
>> Depressants in the UK. There's people
killing a [ __ ]
>> Yeah, England's a [ __ ] hole. But it's our country.
>> It's still our country. And this is
what's going on now. You'd rather sit
here and argue with [ __ ] when
there's more [ __ ] to
>> the fact that she was a [ __ ] Karen. But
Monty's so much of a s he doesn't you know
>> you are a simp you say you were sing off
of women you can't get
>> okay you I'm the one sing over women you
was the one crying on video over [ __ ] woman
>> that's PG I was with that woman I'm
still with that woman for [ __ ] three months
>> you simp women what you even been with
>> okay really like you
>> yeah really
like you I kiss it. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. The one who shagged the man behind
[ __ ] a man home. Shing and you had
his sloppy seconds. That is it.
>> What? The one that come on to me. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. But still took all my other
man that man.
>> You know what I'm saying Kieran?
>> You're desperate PJ for love in it. You
haven't had that.
>> I'm the one crying over a woman. Yeah.
>> Off a woman.
>> Yeah. I'm the one crying over Yeah.
Yeah. How do you know man? Oh,
>> you haven't had attention of a woman.
Not even your own moms give you attention.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> I can't believe you defend that America.
You really are a simp.
>> I'm not offending no one who I don't
know. I don't know this woman. But the
way you treat women is
>> you're an absolute s. You actually are.
>> What? What? Sticking up for a woman who
I don't know. I'm not sticking up for >> Yeah.
>> I'm just calling you a way though.
Starting on women who you don't know.
>> What are you on about? I I don't know. Huh?
>> Well, you don't know about going over to
random ass women when they said they in
a relationship or they got a boyfriend.
You flip out, you start crying about it.
>> That's because you ain't got the Just
cuz you ain't got the balls to approach.
>> Yeah, I have got the balls to approach.
I don't need to approach. I'm happy.
I need to approach any women. Huh?
>> Why the [ __ ] do I need to approach any
women? I have got to approach women.
You know what I mean? All of you, the
only reason you people go on about women
on here is because none of you get
women. That's why you defend about
women. That's why these people sit there
and say you're going to you're going to
attack women because these people can't
get a woman.
>> So they make you believe that you're
ugly like them. You know what I mean,
bro? You're going to end up hurting a
woman. These are the same people that's
never seen a woman naked. So I I let them
off without paying without
>> you know these people in this community.
Do you know these people in this
community? Yeah. They the only people
that they've seen probably naked is
their mom and the only [ __ ] they've seen
is their moms when they come out of it.
>> So what you see when you peeping on your
mom and your sister in the room virgins
I've ever seen. These are all virgins.
>> So why did you used to peep on your
sister in the shower room and that? I
>> I didn't. I was too busy peeping on yours.
No, you you used to [ __ ] poop on your
mom and your sister in the shower room.
This is why you're so
>> and so obsessed with women.
>> You used to peep on your sister all the
time. Peeping on her.
>> Dirty washy basket.
>> What is it with you and Virgin boy
making up stories?
>> I'm not making up stories. This is
>> I like looking at my sister. What is it
with these six? It just goes to show you
a pedo making up these stories.
>> Your sister's ordering.
>> What the [ __ ] are these stories about?
>> Your sister's ordering you PJ. So how
does that make and you're saying that
I've peeped on my sister? How would you know that?
>> You're the one who told us back on PS3
back in the day.
>> I told everybody on PlayStation I peep
on my sister.
>> Me and you. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I did.
>> This is how you know this guy is a pedo. >> Oh.
on your sister. I want your sister.
>> How's your sister?
>> I want your sister, PJ.
>> This is how you know he's a pedo.
>> PJ, your sister's ordering you. You clown.
>> That's how you know this guy is a pedo.
>> What? What? Because you used to per on your sister.
>> So why did you Why did you try on with
Beth 20 on PlayStation?
>> Oh my days, PJ. What is it with you and
[ __ ] your excuses? What do you mean?
>> You [ __ ] on here. But you have
actually sniff your mom knickers on your
>> This is all projection by the way. This >> It's
no protection PG. And you know it's not
>> this is self projection everyone.
>> 100% not PJ.
>> You're just like nonsense.
>> You're like nonsense best mate. PJ, you
sit there every day on the panel with
him back on PlayStation 3 talking to him every day.
>> That's your mate.
>> Every day when when they were telling
you that he's a nons cuz I'm getting
bullied off everybody. No, he's not.
Leave him alone. Leave me alone. He's not
>> your mate.
>> No, it's your mate. You met the guy.
That's your mate.
>> EJ Shy Long Legs is your best friend.
And at the moment, you and Shy Long Legs
have got a lovehate relationship going on. No, >> you
I met him because of you.
>> Yeah. No, you met him through the
community through someone else.
>> Because of you.
>> Okay. You met him because of me, PJ, but
you're the one who
have a beer with him.
>> PJ, you've already had a drink with Sean.
>> He's going to take you to his shitty
little virgin bedsit. And you're going
to have a drink together.
>> You probably already been to his bedit.
You've already been there, done that
with his own leg. So why do I have to
>> skin bedsit with no bed? give in to give up. >> Yeah.
>> Well, well, you know that's a lie, PJ.
You know that's a lovely excuse for
>> But the excuse is is why did you
actually meet him? Why did you >> What?
>> Why do you date slags?
>> Why do I date slags?
>> I said why do you date slags?
>> Who's a slag? >> Natalie.
>> Natalie's a slag. Yeah. Bongo has to see
his kid supervised.
>> I don't have to see my kid supervised. [Laughter] >> What?
>> That's funny as [ __ ]
>> There you go. Natalie just called you a monster.
>> Natalie, you love me really.
>> Why is it a [ __ ] cook?
>> You love me really, Natalie.
>> I don't think so at all.
Yes, you do. You used to love me a lot.
>> No, you don't.
>> You wanted to meet me.
>> Oh, whatever.
>> You did though.
We used to talk all the time.
>> I bet your girlfriend to cook dinner.
Oh, you ain't got one. Sorry.
>> You can't even cook, you silly [ __ ]
Oh, better cook than you, PJ.
>> White women can't cook. It's a known fact.
>> Okay. Is it a known fact? Is it? >> Yeah.
One might say,
>> you know, if I if I came to Birmingham,
Natalie would choose me over you, Monty. It's obvious.
>> Okay. Okay. Why don't you come to Birmingham?
>> Obvious, isn't it? It's so obvious.
>> So, why don't you come Birmingham then
and put that to the test PJ? >> Nah. >> Yeah.
>> I don't want you I don't want you to do
another video crying again.
>> No, no, no. I won't do another video
crying. It goes to goes to you. So why
don't you come and see kids using an intercom?
>> Yeah, it just shows how much they know,
don't it? Ain't it
>> you like? Yeah, but you like these people.
>> No, it's people writing the comments.
>> I think Natalie would give me a [ __ ]
in front of you, Monty.
>> Yeah, your dick's too small. She can't
find it. You know what I'm saying? >> Yeah.
>> Even if Natalie wore glasses, she still
won't find your dick.
>> You You should You should You should
show Natalie the video of me getting a
[ __ ] She'd probably finger herself to it.
>> Easy. Or do Or do you finger herself off
like your own mother?
>> No, you you you liked it. You had a wank over it.
>> Easy. I've never had a wank off your
small dick. You I couldn't even see nothing.
>> Yeah, cuz half of it was in someone's
mouth. I don't [ __ ] know PJ. She even
>> Natalie, have you ever seen my Pekka?
he said, "Have you ever seen this Pekka?"
I give you when he pulled it out that
day online and
>> it's a little pecker. Another one.
A little [ __ ] little mini me.
>> Yeah. What do you like it? Is it?
No cracking one off to PJ getting a
sucky. Yeah, I know. It's weird, isn't it?
>> One call for you, PJ.
>> No, me getting a [ __ ] though.
>> No, not not even you getting a [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but so you you must have watched
the video to know it was me.
>> You can hear yourself talking and it
said, "Oh, that's nice." Like, "Oh,
yeah. Okay." Yeah.
>> Yeah. You like it, is it? AJ, your dig
small. If your digital
>> Natalie, you know Monty circumcised.
>> You say that again to Natalie, please. Yeah,
>> you know Monty, man. He's circumcised.
>> No, he's not at all.
>> Yeah, he is. You can tell that he loves me.
>> She loves me more than you. Def.
>> Yeah, she wants Pekka. But why is Ning
not with you then?
>> Because I didn't come to Birmingham and
meet her. So you were second best.
>> I was second best at all.
>> Yeah, you were. Yeah, you were.
>> Natalie was sending me [ __ ]
Valentine's gifts when I was when we
were going out with Kayie.
>> She bloody never.
>> Yes, she did.
>> Natalie wanted me to put a baby peter
belly inside her. Natalie was sending me
Valentine's presents and all that like
when I was going out with Kayie asking
>> you want me to put a baby Peter belly
inside you wouldn't it Natalie
>> yeah didn't you Natalie
send me [ __ ] Valentine gifts and that
when I was going out with >> Kay see
I think Natalie likes me better me and
Natalie well Natalie was sending me Valentine
when I was at my old house in Plymouth.
>> Think of it. But Monty's got no Monty's
got no hair.
>> Yeah. Natalie loves it when I ain't got no
>> Yeah. Yeah. See
>> likes my bald head. >> Baldy. That's Yeah.
>> Yeah. These Natalie loves my boulders.
You're you're bald. So
>> So me being me being bald like I pull
more women than you and I'm bald.
>> You can't. That's why you was crying over Natalie.
>> Yeah. In the pub. The girl next to him
was stroking that man's head. They were
bald in his house.
>> Yeah. But that wasn't you. But that
>> Daddy stroking my head.
>> Yeah. But it wasn't you.
>> Yeah. She stroke my head with that other
guy's bald head. And then you were
saying why you're not stalking my head.
>> Baldi. That's funny. Is it baldy?
>> I'm glad to be bald. PJ,
>> you're a bold [ __ ]
>> You're bit you're bit you're admitting
you're a bold [ __ ]
>> PJ, I'm happy to be bald. These my not yours.
>> DJ, they will be on your side. They will
be. But if I [ __ ] off, don't come back
on here and then they be starting on
you. Just think about it. >> Nah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You be this virgin. You be
>> Yeah. You are skin.
>> Yeah. Virgin.
>> You know how you know that you're a non
share is because you were speaking to
that 18year-old with me. The other 18.
>> I was I was behind all the time. You was
having fun playing with her and tried to
chase her for your rat and [ __ ]
>> Yeah, you Yeah. And you was you was n
the other one.
>> I went nons
another one. I was basically on my own
basically when you were talking to him.
>> I was talking You got a thing for the
youngs, don't you?
>> No, definitely not you PG. You got for
19y olds and 18y olds and
>> you got your eye on the young and
>> Natalie, do you want to meet Natalie? Do
you want to meet up for some goodness?
>> Actually, Natalie's too old for you. PJ, >> huh?
>> Natalie's too old for you.
>> Why? You already said that um anyone um
ordering you is too old for you.
You've already said that. Anyone older
and [ __ ] Natalie's age or mom's age
is older too old for you? >> No. >> Yeah.
Natalie's what? 36. I'm 35. They might
too old for you, PJ.
>> You're a pair of old [ __ ]
>> There you go. So, so you like your
younger ones then, PJ, don't you?
>> You You fancy that one in America, is
it? That I I got with
>> No. No, I thought start changing the subject now.
>> You know what I'm saying? You fancied her.
>> We never fancied no American woman.
>> Yes, you did.
>> So, go on, PJ. Why won't you go out with
anyone older than you?
>> Um, I have been out with people older
than me. USA Izzy was older than me. She
was uh she was 27 and I was 25. Yeah.
Basically in a 20 age your age group. Yeah.
>> Yeah. She was born in April 96. I
remember my mommy's date of birth. Older
mean older than that. That's what I mean.
>> You do realize it's normal to be born on April.
>> Yeah. April's full days for you. Is it?
>> That's good. Is it cuz you always get
April fool by every woman.
>> Yeah. I was born in on April.
I was born on April the 1st.
What do you think of that, Monty?
>> What do you think of that?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> No, think about the [ __ ] you talk about. Yeah.
>> I'm born on April 1st.
Yeah. Pools rules for you then, is it?
>> When's Natalie's birthday?
>> That's none of your business.
>> We're going to get our birthday cards.
>> Oh, Franklin.
>> So, what's our address then? Pedia.
>> I don't know your address.
>> I don't want to know your address.
>> I don't think any of these people know
my address in this.
>> Yeah, but you know when when they find
it, you're in a doghouse.
>> You're not going to find it because my
camera's always going to be turned off.
You love YouTube, is it?
>> I don't like Timmy been doing videos. What? What?
>> I'm off anyways. I got things to do. Got
people to meet. I got mates to meet.
People who you ain't got.
>> Yeah, you can take yourself that. Bye-bye now.
So, why don't you have mates, PJ?
>> I don't like mates. They're [ __ ]
>> So, basically, you're calling um
your [ __ ] then. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> You're supposed to be meeting him. >> Yeah.
>> You love me. Really, Monty?
>> Triple H. I couldn't. Yeah,
>> you need to join the three great pillos.
>> Nah, I'm all No, I'm all right. Me, PJ, >> why?
>> Yeah, being with the great free Pos.
>> No, seriously.
>> Well, so when are you next in Birmingham then, PJ?
>> Maybe next week.
>> Are you?
>> Yeah. Is that all right?
>> Yeah, that's fine for you to get a slap.
>> you can't slap me. Find out what next
land you said you come in Bingham next
week. So you find out next week.
>> Yeah, we will.
>> Your fingers by squeegee.
>> You're just jealous. I got that woman
from America. You never
>> E. I'm not asked about a woman who
you're never going to be with either
way. Even if you got with her or not.
>> I already got with her. Never going to
you're never going to see you again.
What? Every two week
>> I already got with her.
>> What? A two week holiday then back home
again and then that's it.
>> No, I already got with her.
>> Yeah, that's good for you. You already
got with her. Slept with her. But you
didn't [ __ ] get with her by being
with her. You cried when she put back
your own country and she [ __ ] you over. She
>> She had nice boobies. Bonnie, you'd get really jealous.
PJ, I've got a woman with nice boobs.
I'm not eating with one pair of boobs.
The boobs I've got are nice enough
I've got is tasty enough. Right.
I've got a tasty vagina. So why am I asked?
You're mad. So why does no one like you
on here then?
cuz you got me onto this community, PJ.
So, so what? >> So,
>> why did you get me on this community?
You always ask me that, is it?
>> Yeah. So, why did you get me onto this community?
>> Cuz it's funny.
>> Cuz it's funny for me to fight your
battles for you. Yeah.
>> You don't fight. I fight my own I fought
my own battles.
>> You cry when I don't help you out. You know
>> this all these like little skin virgins
in the background texting away >> what
>> I said like all these skint little
virgins who were texting away in the background.
>> Yeah, but you like them.
>> You you obsessed about him. PGA.
>> You like them? They're your mates.
>> You like them? You sit there talking to
them every day.
>> Yeah, cuz I like Griezy. He's a cool guy.
You like more people? Well, there's
people who want one person.
>> You know,
>> one person. Yeah. PJ,
>> do you know how I know you're a
narcissist? Because you never laugh at anything.
>> Well, because I never laugh at anything. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Like, this community is funny. I
don't know how you don't laugh at it.
>> What do you mean?
>> This community is funny, isn't it?
>> No, not really. It's pathetic.
Yeah, but like what they do is funny
sometimes, is it?
>> No, not really. Some shit's funny. >> Huh?
>> Some of the shit's funny, but not all.
>> You say that. You say, "Oh, why am I on
YouTube?" But every time I go on
YouTube, they're on YouTube as well. So,
>> yeah. Your mom don't love you, PJ, does you? >> Nah.
>> So, why did mommy run off then, PJ?
>> I don't know, man. She got bored.
>> Yeah, she got bored of your [ __ ]
Even Mr. B owns you.
>> Mr. B got can't even on himself. He's
got a perfect voice on like all the rest
of him. That's Charlie's.
>> That's his real voice.
>> No, it's not his real voice.
>> Of course it is.
>> No, it's not.
>> I like this community, buddy.
>> Well, you sticking it.
>> It suits you as well.
>> It don't suit me. [ __ ] weirdos. AJ,
>> it's funny, isn't it?
>> No, it's not funny.
>> Anyways, I'm off. I'll be back later.