Right. Sorry. I think I thought I'm
going to respond to uh the little
virgin. Um because if I don't, people
are going to think I'm running away so
we get more people to join.
That is literally not six grand and it's
not 12 grand. Again, I'll explain the
money game again when people join
because I feel like a lot of people
forgot the game that they invented, you
know. And I'll get uh and I'll say a few
things right here now.
Yeah, firstly that's not six grand and
it's certainly not 12 grand. So I don't
know why you're on here again showing
your little shitty housing benefit off
again thinking that you've got money and
more people join when people join again.
I'll explain that's not 12 grand. That's
not six grand and it's not four grand.
So I don't know why you're putting them
20 notes to pounds together acting like
you've won at the money game. There's
nothing madness about it. That is
nothing. You're You're showing a few 20
notes stuffed in plastic, which is not
12 grand. Same thing as same thing as
bomb. That is not 12 grand.
Bro, that is nothing. The money that he
is showing is literally nothing. He's
he's literally stuffing stuff stuffing
20 pound notes in saying that it's six
grand. It's not six grand and it's not
13 grand either. He's actually admitted
that it's not 13 grand. So, stop trying
to [ __ ] stir. And that's not six grand
either. What you said it was, that's
literally nothing. That's your housing
benefit. And what have I told you a
million times about put if that's if
that's six grand, count it all out.
Count it. But no, it doesn't matter if
it is six grand or not because that's
not the game actually. So I don't know
why I'm saying that. It's not six grand.
It's a couple of 20 notes.
Nope, it's not. I've shown six grand.
I'm the winner. A few 20 notes has not
beat me. Nope. I've shown six grand.
I've got no business with these people.
I have literally got no business with
people. I've shown six grand. I'm the
winner when it comes to cash. I win.
Ding, ding, ding. I've shown six grand
in 50s, 20s. Him showing two grand
maximum is not beating someone. I know
you like to be biased and I know you
like to be, you know, whatever. That is
not six grand and it's not my 12 grand.
You haven't won. Again, you're going to
come on here and act like you've and
you're going to act like you've um think
that you've won, you know, but you
haven't. That is nowhere near £6,000
because I've had £6,000 in [ __ ] 50
notes and it was thicker than that. It
is not six grand. It is nothing. And
another thing is how you know it's not
six grand either and it's not 12 is it?
Okay. Is it is it 12 grand? Okay. [ __ ]
the six grand anyways. Is it 12 grand?
Is the money 12 grand?
Is the money £12,000?
[ __ ] the six grand. That's That's what
we want to know. Hold on. [ __ ] all this
arguing. Is the money six uh £12,000?
And if it is, count it out. Cuz from
what I'm seeing, I don't think it is. Is
it Is it £12,000?
Is Is it 12? Cuz if it's not, I've got
no business with you. The whole game is
showing £12,000, not showing your
housing benefit off. And another thing
is people that go on holiday, even even rich people,
um, even rich people,
bro, I've shown £6,000. I've shown more
money than him. But again, you seem to
forget that. This is why I'm wasting my
time with these people because I have
shown more money, way more money than
that bum change that he's showing. And
you're saying that he's beat me. This is
what I'm saying. You're never going to
win with these people. This is exactly
what I was saying earlier. I have beat
them at the money game and they still
act like they've won. There's no point.
It's it's a waste of time. This is what
I'm saying. It's going back and forth.
And this is why I'm coming off of this
[ __ ] because it's just back and forth,
back and forth childish [ __ ] every
single time. You have been shown 6,000.
That is not 6,000. That is not £6,000 in
bundles. That is not £6,000. That is
nothing. And nobody.
No, he hasn't won because I have shown
£6,000 in cash, mate. I'll have you
know, mate, that I have shown £6,000 in
cash, mate. I have shown £6,000 in cash.
That is not £6,000 in cash. Yeah. No,
it's Virgin Boy.
Yeah, I've shown 6,000. That is his
housing benefit. That is nothing. It's
bum chains. That is nothing. They're 20
notes. A [ __ ] bundle of it looks like
a [ __ ] not even a,000. Listen, mate.
I've shown £6,000 and that is not
£6,000. And it's not £12,000 either. So
come back when you've got £12,000.
You know what I'm saying? Thinking that
he's got money, showed a few 20 notes.
That's literally nothing. That's
literally [ __ ] nothing. I've shown
£6,00050s. I've still got the picture.
I've literally still got the picture
before I banked it.
Yeah, it's not 13 bundles and it's
not,000 bundles either. Like I said,
you're going to pretend that you've won
either way. You're all biased. We all
know who's won the money game and it's
me. Yes, you're always going to pretend
like you've won. I'm wasting my time,
bro. Just don't waste your time with these people.
You know, you're going to act like
you've won regardless. I'm not wasting
my time. I'm not wasting my time.
Simple. I am not wasting my time.
Anyways, I'm not wasting my time.
I'm literally I've literally lost before
I even open my mouth to be honest with
you. You get show money.
It's not £13,000. It's nowhere near
It's nowhere near £13,000.
Stop showing your housing benefit
thinking that you got money. No one
literally would go on holiday and with
char and with and change 15 grand to
euros. Yeah. And he's not doing better
than me, mate. I'm better looking. I've
got more money. I've had more women than
him. I've been on more holidays than
him. I'm better than him in every way. I
am better in every way possible. Better
looking. I've got teeth. I've never
resorted to a disabled girl. Yeah, I
know there's always somebody doing
better. I'm doing better than him. I'm
not disabled. I'm not ugly. I'm not
skint like him. As much as he tries to
show you his benefit and says it's
[ __ ] six grand. I know, bro. I'm
better than him in every way. I've got a
bed, don't live in a bedsit, not ugly,
never resorted to disabled, been to more
places than him, younger, better
looking. I've beating him by a [ __ ]
milestone at the end of the day, bro.
I know there's always someone doing
better. Me doing better than him. I've
actually got teeth in my mouth and I've
never had to resort to disabled. And I'm
not skin like him either.
And I'm not a skin bastard like him
showing his thousand benefit.
So yeah, I'm doing way better. Way better.
I I've never shown you anything ever
again because every single time I beat
you at the money game, you run away.
I've already beat all of you at the
money game. I'm not playing it again.
And yes, I'm doing way better. Better
looking, more money, more teeth, more
women. [ __ ] more women, more friends.
I'm doing way better than that virgin.
You know, all of the stuff that he's
doing now, I done it when I was 23
because I'm not skinned like him. He can
show you his little housing benefit,
acting like he's got money, but bro, we
all know the real him.
We all know the real him. He ain't got
no money. Virgin boy ain't got no money,
mate. People that have got money does
not take them 31 to go a [ __ ] road.
I'm doing way better than that skin
virgin. Don't even try to compare me to
that skin virgin. It's not £13,000.
They're trying to say that Virgin Boy is
showing 13 grand. That is not 13 grand.
That is nowhere near 13 grand.
Even if it was in 50 notes. That is not
13 grand. You don't understand what
Listen. Listen to me, [ __ ] Right.
I've had wallets at 50 notes. Yeah. And
it was thicker than that. That is not 13
grand. It would not even look like that.
Yeah. Yeah. He doesn't have 13 grand. I
know it goes on and he doesn't have 13
grand. Life does go on. Yeah. And he
don't have 13 grand either. I know it
goes on. I'm not the one bringing it up.
I'm better looking. I've got more money
than him. Yeah. I'm better looking. More
money. Better looks. And he doesn't have
13 grand. And I've got more money than
him. And that's not 13 grand. So try
again. And it ain't 13 grand, mate.
Trust me. I buy wallets of 50s that were
thicker than that. If they were if they
were wallets, mate, they would be
thicker than that. That is not 13 grand.
That is nothing. Nowhere near 13 grand. So yeah,
put your housing benefit back in. So yeah.
Yeah, that is not 13 grand. Nowhere near
13 grand. Nice try though. Good try.
Trust me, my 50 wallets were thicker
than that and they were 50s and they
were actually 50s.
Stop thinking that you got money. You
ain't got none. You're skinting a bedit.
You might fool these people your little
housing benefit. But you don't fool me.
You don't fool me, matey. Put that Put
your housing benefit back in the bank,
mate. They're going to start charging
you soon. You know, if you keep taking
your little shitty housing benefit out
that ain't nowhere near 13 grand,
they're going to start charging you, lad.
Yeah. He won't go he won't be off to
Vegas. He can't afford it. That's why he
only went abroad when he was 30 because
he can't afford it.
High roller. High roller. Showing his
little housing benefit with his disabled
girlfriend. I wouldn't call that a high
roller. He's got nothing. High roller.
What? With his one grand a month skin in
the bedset. I wouldn't exactly call that
a high roller now, would you?
And another thing is, yeah, you did list
how much your holiday costs. £1,200 for
two people. Yes, that is cheap. And you are skint.
Yes, you are skint. He's balling pretty
hard. No, he's [ __ ] not.
No, this is exactly why you don't waste
your time with these people because
they're all biased. This is what I'm
saying. Even when they've won, even when
they've won, even when you've won, they
still pretend they've won. This is
exactly what I'm saying. There's no
point with these people. If you're not
fat and ugly and you're better looking
than them, they're always going to take
sides. This is what I'm saying. There's
no point. Because I'm better looking and
I've got more money, they're always
going to go for me. This is what I'm saying.
You know, this is what I'm saying, bro.
He showed about a couple of grand and
they're trying to say it's 13 grand.
It's nowhere near 13 grand. No, it's not
13 grand. No, it's not 13 grand.
No, it is not 13 grand. Go on the video.
know it is not nowhere near 13 grand.
But listen, nature girl, it's funny how
you never said anything when I was
showing six grand. You're all biased.
This is what I mean. It's a waste of
time with these people. This is exactly
why I said I was coming off this [ __ ]
but then this little [ __ ] drags me back
in with his housing benefit, thinking
that he's got money, thinking that it's
13 grand when it ain't 13 grand. He
ain't got nowhere near 13 grand. This is
exactly what I'm saying. They're always
going to be biased. If you're not fat,
ugly, and you're better looking than
them, they're going to do this forever.
This is why I knew like I was just
wasting my time with these people.
They've got less money than me, less
looks, [ __ ] nothing, and they still
go for you. You're wasting your time
with these jealous people. Once you get
it in your head, you will come off this
[ __ ] which is what I was doing. And you
dragged me back in. They will always act
like they've won because they're jealous
of you. Once you've get that, when you
get that in your head, Yeah. Uh, yes, I
have shown six grand and you've seen it.
And you've already seen my six grand.
Yeah. And you've already seen my six
grand. I'm not doing it. I will never
show you people anything again. No £10,
no 20, no £30. Because I know what you
people do. You will buy cuz when these
when someone's jealous of you, listen,
you don't understand, right? I'm saying
this to myself. Sit down. Sit down on
the bed and talk to yourself. You're
better looking than them. You've got
more money than them. They're jealous of
you. This is why they do this every
single day. Your mom's told them that
they're jealous of you. Other people
have told them that they're jealous of
you. How many times are you going to
keep wasting your time on these skinned
low lives that have got nothing? How
many years you going to waste your time
on skinned people like nonsexs? Skinn
people, they're jealous of you. It's
jealousy, bro. As long as you stay on
here and you keep arguing with these
people that want to be you, you're going
to waste your life away. Do you want to
be like them in a bedsit, can't show
money, accept £2,000, ugly fat
girlfriend, no teeth? Do you want to be
like these people?
I don't want to be skin pretending I've
got 13 grand when I [ __ ] don't
showing a couple of£100, couple of
thousand pounds and pretending it's 13 grand.
I can because it's not 13 grand. And and
and this is what I'm saying. You're
asking me to show six grand. You've
already seen six grand, but you pretend
you never saw it because you're all
biased. When you're not ugly and you're
not fat like these people, they get
jealous of you. This is the main thing.
and everything that you do, whether it's
meet people, show money, they're always
they're jealous of you. That's why you
need to get off of YouTube. Jealous of
you. It's like what this guy said to me
before. You got more money, you're
better looking, and you got a better
life than them. Leave YouTube. And it's so true.
And it's not 13 grand. And it's not 13
grand. Yeah. It's not 13 grand. It is
not £13,000. No, it is not. Yeah. Money
talks and he ain't got no money. He's
got his housing benefit.
Uh-huh. Exactly, bro. Yeah,
but he talks and he ain't got none.
Yeah. And he ain't got no money.
Exactly. Anyways, we're moving on from
this now because no matter what I say
and no matter what I do, you're always
going to take the people's side because
you're all jealous of me. I know this.
This is why these people sit on here
every day doing this.
Yeah. He doesn't have anything. Anyways,
I'm changing the subject now anyways
because I've shown six grand. That's not
13 grand. I've won and no one can show
me 13 grand. So, anyways, I'm I'm
changing the subject now. I'm changing
the subject now because we've gone on
about this a million times. Moving on
now. Anyways, changing the subject now.
Anyways, I'm changing the subject now
because I don't waste my time on bias
people. Anyways, moving on now. No
accounts are going to get blocked. They
can keep writing stuff and whatever. I'm
literally not talking about it no more.
All I know is it's like what I was
saying to Thingy before I was beefing
with him. There's lit. He hasn't beat to
me. He hasn't beat to me. He's literally
not shown 13 grand. Bro, I'm better
looking than him. I've had more women
than him. I'm not disabled like him.
I've got teeth like him. Even if he had
more money than me, which you don't. I'm
living a better life than him. been on
holiday more times, better looking, no,
I've got teeth. Even if he had more
money than me, which he never, I'm
living the life that he wish he had.
That's why he goes for me every day cuz
he's jealous. And him pretending that
he's got 13 grand when he don't ain't
going to change that.
You know, he done some talking. That
ain't 13 grand. That is not £13,000.
That is not £13,000, son. And you can
keep pretending it is, but it isn't.
It's not £13,000.
Listen, do you really think someone's
going to go on holiday with £13,000
and change it up to euros? Okay. Okay.
Let's let's Okay. Let's let's let's
let's go by your logic, right? You think
somebody's going to cross the ocean with
£13,000 in cash and change it up? No.
Never in a billion years because it
ain't £13,000. That's the whole point.
That's the whole point. Yes. And it's
not 13 grand because there's no way
someone's going on holiday changing up
13 grand. Yes, I played it and it's not
13 grand. Yes, I have. And it's not 13,000.
Yes, I have. And it's not £13,000.
I don't need to play it again.
I have. And it's a few 20 notes. And
it's nowhere near 13,000. And it's
nowhere near. It's nowhere [ __ ] near.
Anyways, we're moving on now. Anyways,
because we're going round and round and
round around in circles with you little
low lives, which was part of the reason
why I said I was leaving because of you
biased, jealous people. And that ain't
nowhere near 13 grand. So, as much as
you're going to try and say it is,
human. Ah, bro. Fuming of you. You fat
ugly bun. You little skin bastard.
Someone that's never left [ __ ] where
you live. You [ __ ] ugly baldy skin
bastard. And And that's six grand that
you showed as well, mate. That's three
months money. You ain't got nothing. Bum
the bum. You got bullied off of YouTube.
And that's not 13 grand either. You got
bullied off of YouTube with your little
boyfriend. Got no money. Got no 30 grand
cuz that ain't 13 grand. And that little
[ __ ] buddy that you're showing because
you won a football bet. Listen, bomb.
That money that you're showing, that
money that you're showing last about 3
months. No one cares. You're skintit.
You're lonely. You got no women. You got
no kids. You're an ugly bastard. You get
bullied every day. But if you got
bullied off of YouTube for your
ugliness, your fat ugly head, no amount
of money is going to change the fact
that you're all ugly and you're all
alone. I would rather sit here, bro,
with 20 quid to my name than be you in a
bed sit with your fat ugly hands, your
fat ugly self, your no money. Six grand
ain't going to last three [ __ ]
months, laddy. Six grand ain't going to
last three months. You ugly bastard in a
bed sit. All this money, but you got no
kids, no women, no life. Thinking that
you got money, bro. It's free. It's
literally, bro. It's literally Mr. B.
What that [ __ ] is showing is not [ __ ] 13 grand.
Bomb. I would rather have no money than
be like you. Ugly in a bedsit.
Ugly in a bedit with no misses and no
kids and no money. Mate, you show money
every time you win a football bet. Yeah.
You gamble your benefits every month and
then when you win, you show it. You are
the forever skin in a bed sit ugly man
pretending that he's been to America.
You've never been to America. You've
never been anywhere. Ugly man. Ugly bomb
with his shitty little money that's not
going to last more than 3 months. No one
cares about your ugly self. Listen, you
can have all the money in the world, but
you're still going to be ugly. You're
still going to be alone. You're still
going to have nobody. Think about it,
bro. Let's Let's be real. So real about
this, Dad. You've You claim that you've
got all this money. Look at you. You're
in a bed suit. Yeah, that's you, bro.
100%. No friends, no women. That's you.
You should, bro. Surely to God you've
been watching this um bomb for the past
2 years when you left. I've shown
friends women that you can't get because
you're too ugly. No money. Bro, listen. That's it.
Uh that is not £13,000.
That is not £13,000.
Nope. It's nowhere near £13,000. So yes.
No, there's no point. He doesn't talk.
Listen, Bomb, you've never had a woman.
You're still a virgin. You're one to
talk about people not having a woman.
You're a [ __ ] virgin. You could have
all the money in the world, bro, and
you're still going to be ugly and alone.
Ugly alone in a bedsit with nothing. It
doesn't matter what you say you got.
You're always going to be ugly and alone
with no woman. I've had more women than
you. You [ __ ] virgin. You silly
little [ __ ] Barely traveled. Let me ask
you this question, Bob. Have you ever
been to Thailand?
Yeah. He's not a high roller. That's not 13 grand.
Yes. That's not a high roller. That's
not 13 grand. He's not a high roller.
That's not 13 grand.
That is not 13 grand. That is not 13
grand. I I can't show£10. Bomb. Stop
being silly now. Stop hijing about
people can't show£10. I'm not angry. I'm
angry at you people pretending that he's
got 13 grand when he doesn't. When he
literally does not have 13 grand. That
is not 13 grand. You can even ask Bomb.
Not ask Bomb. You can ask Mr. be, bro.
That is not 13 grand.
That is literally not nowhere near 13
grand. That is not no 13 grand, bro.
Bro, I've flown unlike you. You [ __ ]
anxiety [ __ ] in a bed in a bedsit. You
want to talk about anxiety, bro? You
left YouTube cuz you got bullied for
your ugliness. And no amount of money is
going to change your ugly face. And no
amount of money is going to change the
fact that you're a virgin. You got
bullied off of YouTube due to anxiety.
You ugly bastard. You ugly man. No
matter how much money you've got, ugly
man, you're always going to be alone
because money can't change ugliness.
And you will find that out on Saturday,
bro. When I go out on the pool, I'm
going to do something on Saturday that
the virgin bomb can't do. And no amount
of three months £6,000.
Go. It's not 13,000, Mr. B. It's not
nowhere near 13,000.
It's nowhere near 13,000, bro.
Yeah, you're on here after Yeah, you're
on here after two years, you [ __ ]
little victim. Yeah, you're on here
after two, bro. You bully me in your
little bedsit with your free monthly
money in your little shitty little
bedsit. Have a word with yourself,
Virgin. You know, when you was off of
YouTube for two years, right? I was
getting more women than you. We were
laughing how bullied you were. You
couldn't even come back cuz you got so
bullied. You got bullied off of YouTube
for two years. You got bullied off of
YouTube for two years. That's how
bullied you are. You can You dare come
back, bro. You dare come back. I can
show you money anytime I want, but I'm
not going to show you money because
you've not beat me at the money game. I
will never show you money though because
I I don't need to show you money. I've
already beat you at the money game. I've
already beat you at the money game and
you keep saying I'm skin is not going to
work, mate. Everyone knows exactly what
I've got. Thousands. I've already told L
my savings and I'm not showing you
little skid people anything. And guess
what, Mom? Let me ask you this question.
Yeah. Let me ask you this question, Bob.
You know this money you're showing now,
show it in 3 months time. Listen,
everyone listen to this. Yeah. Cuz this
is a major thing when it's people's
income. Show that money in 3 months time.
Exactly. Show that money in 3 months
time because, bro, do you not
understand? Yeah. Think of it. Someone
that gets £300 a month. Yeah. Can show
any amount of money. But come back in 3
months and show it. Now, you don't have
to show it every day for 3 months. I'm
not saying show it every day. Come back
in 3 months and show that money, bro.
Bomb, you've won on the football. Yes,
you're talking about yourself. No woman,
no life, no football. That's you. Yeah,
that's your life. That's why you in your
40s in a bedsit. That's your life, Ma.
That is your life, Ma in a bedsit. That
is you. Yeah. 40, no woman, no money.
That's you. The 40-year-old in the
bedsit. That's you. The manta with no
woman. Well, you're sat there saying,
"I've got no woman." But you're sat in a
bed sit alone in your 40s. What kind of
life is that? And another thing is
right. Let me tell you something, bomb.
Yeah. Let me let me tell you another
thing, bomb, as well. Yeah. Do you
remember that time that you claimed that
you showed 10 grand? Right, bro? I'm not
crying. I'm laughing at you. Bullying
you. Life has already bullied you. No
money, no woman, no life, ugly looks,
sat in a bed sit in his 40s, never been
Thailand, never been America. Bro, I'm
laughing at you. I'm laughing at the
full e with nothing, no money. And do
you remember that time before, bomb?
Yeah. When you claimed that you showed
10 grand and then two months later you
showed£600. You are skint. The only
reason that you've shown money, lad, the
only reason that you've shown money is
cuz you've won a football bet. You are
skint. That's another reason why you did
not come on here for 2 years. Because in
them two years, you was constantly
wasting your [ __ ] benefit money. You
are absolutely skint. Like I said, come
back with that money in 3 months. Yeah.
Don't show it again. Come back in 3
months and say how you've got all of
this money in your bedset when you keep
doing your bollocksing. Especially
women, bro. I've had more women than
you. I've had more sex than you. You're
still a virgin. Like I said to you, come
back and show that money in 3 months
when you've lost all your benefits.
You've got nothing, mate. It took you 2
years to show a [ __ ] proxy six grand.
That's the definition of poverty, bro.
You left YouTube for two years and you
come back with six grand. Poverty to the
maximum, lad. Yeah.
No, I haven't took no L's. That's not £13,000.
Listen, Bomb, do you want to come in the
hangouts? Do you want to come in the
Do you want to come in? Do you want to
come in the hangouts? Listbe with your
free monthly money with your free
monthly money? Do you do you want to
come back in the hangouts? You ugly
bedshit. No money. No woman, bro. I've
had more women than you, bro. You
[ __ ] little virgin. You little skint
[ __ ] in the bedsit. Life has bullied you
since birth. You can't even leave your
bedsit due to anxiety cuz you're too fat
and ugly. And six grand ain't going to
change that. Your little bum chain six
grand that's not going to last for three
months ain't going to change that, lad.
I've already shown you money. I'm not
showing you money ever again. Until
somebody beats me at the money game, I'm
not playing it. I'm not showing you
nothing. Lj exactly knows exactly what
I've got in savings. I am never showing
you money. You can say that I've not
got5 pound, that I've not got 10 pound.
I don't care. I'm showing you nothing.
Never again. Never again. And everybody
know that I won them football bets as
well. I am showing you nothing until you
show me my 12 grand, then come back to
me. Yeah, you show me my 12 grand and
beat me, then come back to me. I am
showing you nothing. Not even a penny.
Not even£1. I'm showing you nothing. But
I am going to tell you exactly what I'm
going to do. I'm going to go out on
Saturday and I'm going to get pissed to
prove that I'm not showing you nish. No
money, nothing. You can call me skin all
you want. You can self-reflect all you
want. Right? You can self-reflect all
you want. I'm literally not ask Uhhuh.
I'm showing you nothing. I'm not showing
you not even a Fiverr. So, mate, you're
wasting your time asking me to show you money. Simple.
You are wasting your time.
[ __ ] I've had more women than you've
had dinners, mate. Bomb. I've been with
more women than you will ever get sat in
your little virgin bets it.
So you don't No, I'm going to No. Shows
more money, mate. He's got a disabled
girlfriend, mate. He's got a disabled
girlfriend and he's still on my sloppy
seconds. I'm better looking and I've had
better women, mate. Even if he had more
women funny money than me, I'm better
looking and I've never had to be with a
disabled girl. He's the one still
obsessed with my sloppy seconds, mate.
If he had a girlfriend that he actually
loved, right? If you had if he had a
girlfriend he actually loved, he
wouldn't be on my sloppy seconds. I'm
better looking. I've got the more money
and I've never had to resort to a
disabled girl like you were saying Izzy
that he wish he could have got with, but
he can't get with because he's got ugly
looks. So, mate, he could have all the
money in the world. It don't change ugly
looks. It don't change the fact that he
can only get disabled girls. And [ __ ]
Ronald Pump, Ronald McDonald's lad is
going to agree with me. I'm better
looking. I've never been with a disabled
woman because I'm not an incel. I'm not
an so much of an incel that I have to be
with a disabled bird cuz I'm not an
incel that can only target disabled
girls. I can get actual women. Yeah.
actual women that people are obsessed
with, not disabled girls. And I've got
more money than him. And you know what?
Right. Let me tell you something right
here and right now.
Yeah. That's it, lad. That's it. His
bird is disabled. Yes, his bird is
disabled. Everybody knows his bird is
You know what I'm saying, bro? Yeah. I'm
better looking. I've got more money. And
I've had better women. I've got teeth in
my mouth. He's an ugly [ __ ] [ __ ] that
can only get disabled girls. No money in
the world can change that. Literally,
there's no people like Virgin Boy and
Bomb. They can have all the money in the
world, but they're still going to be
ugly and no one wants them. Old, ugly,
no one wants them. Listen, bro. I've had
girlfriends. I've shown you with men
multiple multiple multiple times. And
now this is exactly why I'm not showing
you money. I'm I'm explaining to you why
I'm not showing you money. Yeah. Because
of what you do, you have seen me with
women. You have seen him stalk the women
that I have been with. Yeah. You have
seen the women that he has stalked. I'm
better looking. I've got more money. And
I've never had to resort to a disabled
girl. And listen, I have I've got more
experience in my life than him. And yes,
I have had a girlfriend. And we're not
getting into this anymore. Anyways, I'm
changing the subject anyways.
I'm changing the subject now. Anyways,
so change the subject. We're not getting
into this again. And this is exactly
Yep. I've got nothing, bro. You can keep
saying that I've got nothing. You're not
going to bait me. I'm not showing you
nothing. Yes, I've got nothing. Okay.
I'm not showing you even £5. I'm not
showing you money. So, you can keep
saying what you want to say. I'm not
giving you little skint self-reflectors
what you want. So, you can call me all
the names under the sun. I am not
showing you nothing. I'm not showing
people that have got no money nothing
anymore. You can go self-reflect your
skess on another [ __ ] channel, lad.
Yeah, I'm not doing it, bro. Simple.
You can say that I'm skinn. It's not
going to bait me, mate. You've all been
shown £6,000 and you've all ran away.
The evidence is there. Anyways, changing
subject now. I'm changing the subject.
Yep. Yep. Yes, I am skin. We're changing
the subject now. Until somebody shows me
my 13 grand, I'm I'm changing the
subject. Simple. Yep. I am skint. This
skint person has shown you six grand and
made you all run away. Has made you all
[ __ ] run away. That's how skint I am.
This skint [ __ ] showed you six grand and
made you run away.
Yeah. This skint [ __ ] has shown you six
grand and made you all run away. That's
what this skint [ __ ] done multiple times.
Yep. So you can keep talking about
yourselves having no money and listen
bro. Yeah. Even if that is 13 grand,
right? Even if that is 13 grand, which
it's not 13 grand. It took you two years
to beat me. Enough said how skint you
are. I know I didn't lose it gambling.
And it doesn't matter if it was ages
ago. And listen, bro, even if that is 13
grand, bro, it took him two years to
save that. That is the definition of
skint that it took you two years to show
[ __ ] 13 grand. That just goes to show
how skint you are on benefits. And in
them [ __ ] years, you've had
absolutely no life experience. It took
you two years to show 13 grand. That's
the definition of skint. And there's 24
months in [ __ ] two years. If that
doesn't say that you're skint, I don't
know what [ __ ] will. So yeah, simple.
>> Hello PJ. You seem very worked up today, lad.
>> No, I'm good, man.
>> Mate, what what what are you bothered
about? Someone's got loads of money. You
are the ones that go on about money all the time.
>> I haven't gone on about money. PJ, can
you put my camera on? PJ, that's
interesting to show.
>> Mate, he is skint. Okay. Okay. Okay. Let
me ask you this question. One second.
>> If he's not skin, right, and you're
saying it's 13 grand. Why did it take
two years to show 13 grand? Because you
had to save so hard cuz you're that
skint. You never had it. That just goes
to show that you're skinn. I'm better
looking, had more women than him, been a
broad model, bro. I've got a better life
than him. Do you think I give a [ __ ]
about his three grand that he's showing?
Do you think I give a [ __ ]
about your little three grand pretending
that it's 13 grand? And the fact that it
took you two years, it goes to show how
skint you really, really, really, really
are. It's the same as somebody It's the
same as somebody putting 150, right?
It's the same thing as putting one. He
says you're better looking. I'm better
looking than that [ __ ] [ __ ] And
you're not coming in, LJ. You can go
self-reflect your [ __ ] skickness onto
someone else. Bye-bye now. You're not
coming on. Bye-bye.
Oh, I'll let him on.
>> Hello, PJ. How much is that?
>> £400. I can count it out. Why don't you just show
Why don't you show £400?
>> I am never showing money ever again.
Bye-bye now. I'm not showing you
nothing. You're not going to bait me. We
all know how the cookie crumbles when
you've been shown money. I am not
showing no money. There's no point. You
keep asking me to show money.
I'm not I'm not doing it. You can ask me
a million times. I will not show you
even £20. No way. I'm not showing you
nothing. I am literally showing you
nothing. I'm showing you no money.
Nothing at all. Not even £5. £10. Nope. Who was