[ __ ] stupid idiot trying to spoil all the fun.
[ __ ] noobs, man. What the [ __ ] bro?
Why would you even do that?
400 [ __ ] pound.
[ __ ] 400 [ __ ] pound. What the
[ __ ] The [ __ ] thing went in, man.
>> Why would you even do that? Like
literally lowering, bro. What the [ __ ]
And then he shows me [ __ ] bro. I'm
literally not showing you no money.
I'm literally not showing you no money.
I'm showing you no money. What the hell?
Want to put it in with it?
I'm not I'm literally showing you no
money. You can say I've got none. You
can show me £20. You can show me £400.
You can show me three grand like Virgin
Boy pretending that it's uh 30 grand.
Um but I'm not showing you no money. I'm
not showing them no money, Daz.
>> No money at all, bro.
>> How much money I've spent on takeaways
this week? I'm not showing nothing,
Daz. I'm literally showing no money. I
refused to show any money. Just like the
bookies refused to to uh
they refused to pay out and [ __ ] lad.
Yeah. Yeah. I got no money. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yep. Oh, you keep telling yourself
that. Yeah. I got no money. Just like
you people had no money when I ran you
off of YouTube and I showed you six
grand. Stop self-reflecting. I'm not
showing you nothing.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You
keep telling yourself that, buddy. You
keep telling yourself that. But do you
know what kills you, bomb? That I'm
better looking than you and I'm not a
40-year-old virgin like you. And money
is not going to change that. Money is
not going to change that. You are ugly.
You are 40. You are a virgin. You have
nothing. And that six grand ain't going
to last you more than 3 months. Show
that money in 3 months. Exactly. You
have absolutely nothing. Yeah. I didn't
lose the money game. I didn't lose the
money game. I didn't lose the money
game. That's not 13 grand. So, I didn't
lose the money game. You must be talking
about someone else. I couldn't imagine
it cuz it's never happened to me.
Imagine taking two years to to then
pretend that you showed two years. Two
years. Oh my god. Two years. Bro, I've
had a relationship. You're the one that
pretends that you got kids. You little
bully victim. You're the one that
pretends you've got kids in your little
lonely bedset showing your [ __ ]
£6,000 figuring that you got money.
You're a couple of,000 bum change that
ain't going to last 3 months. Get out of
here, bomb. You're a ugly bastard. Ugly
skinned bastard. We've never seen you
with a woman. We've never seen you with
a woman. We've never seen you with a
woman because you're too much of an ugly
[ __ ] That's why you had to pretend you
got kids. You literally Yeah.
It doesn't wind me up because No. No. Do
you know what winds me up? Do Do you
want Do you want me to answer that?
Okay. I don't Do you want me to answer
that question? Okay, I'll answer you.
Yes. Why not?
I'll answer your question now.
It doesn't wind me up. What winds me up
is how biased you literally people you
people literally are.
You literally are biased. You ask people
to show you money, they beat you at the
[ __ ] money game, and then you pretend
that you've won. You know, bro, you
people have never had a relationship.
You're all single. You're all ugly and
you're all single.
You know what I'm saying?
You're all ugly and you're all single
that you self-reflect every [ __ ] day.
You know what I'm saying? So, what I'm
saying is, bro, what annoys me is how
biased you are. You get beat at the
money game and then someone shows three
grand and pretends it's 13 grand and
then you act like you've won. That's
what annoys me.
I didn't block you. I don't I don't need
to block you. Ugly Bob. Ugly virgin Bob.
Oh [ __ ] Yep. I'm ugly and single. Yep.
You're talking about yourself. Listen,
you people have never been so
You people have never been seen with a
bird. You're all ugly. You're all
virgins. You're sat at home every day
wanking your little dicks off.
You are single. You are ugly. That's why
you're on YouTube every day. You're all
ugly. That's why you come on YouTube
every day calling people skin because
you are really ugly. Really ugly 14y olds. Yeah,
that's what you are, bro.
And that's not £13,000.
That's not £13,000.
Oh my god. Why is that so loud?
That's horrible, bro. You know what I'm saying?
Listen, you people are the single ones.
You're in your 40s every day with no
money coming on YouTube. Listen, bro.
And that's what I'm saying. I never said
I had £300, mate. You don't know how
much money I have. And I'm not showing
you nothing. I have literally Listen,
listen. Let me let me let me stop.
Literally, let me just let me just tell
you something. Right. Yeah. I am never
showing you money again. No amount of
money. £10, 20,30.
I am showing you nothing. Get it in your
head. I'm not showing you money. Yeah,
you are single and skinny. Yeah, you're
talking about yourself. I'm the ones on
here that's been seen with women. Unlike
you little 40y olds, you little
40-year-old virgins. You people are the
ones that are single and skinned. That's
your lives. Stop looking in the mirror.
Yeah. Stop looking in the mirror. That
is your life. Skin and lonely. Why do
you think you come on here every day
hating on people half your age? Cuz you
are single and you are skinn. That's why
you're on YouTube every day hating. Cuz
you ain't got no money.
Take a picture. Take a picture.