I just want to get a drink.
There we go.
Hey, I'd rather get that to to be
fair. So, is that the only downside to
dating as a woman is that you get to
send dick [ __ ] and someone says to
you how much [ __ ] would you would
cost? I'll take that. Yeah, I'll take
that, mate. Everyone's got to deal with
some [ __ ] annoyance. Try going out
and hearing about make believe. Try
having to deal with the ghosting. That's
[ __ ] I'll take that any [ __ ] day, bro. [ __ ]
hell. [ __ ] off, man. Don't try and sit
there and try and tell me how dating is
hard for women. [ __ ] right off,
man. [ __ ] right off. I'm
so the [ __ ] right off, man.
So, is that all you get is a couple of dick pictures
sent? Oh, I just pissed off with these
women, bro. I just woke up and I was
like, [ __ ] Like, it's so mad how dating
is rigged against men and there's
nothing you can do to change your
situation and all of these women that
have been [ __ ] to you can get sex
whenever they want, can get
relationships whenever they want.
It's annoying, bro. Even when you don't
want it, it's annoying just thinking
about it, bro. It's not the gambling,
bro. I got [ __ ] I lost 70 pound
yesterday. I didn't care about it. Yeah.
H mate, if it was as easy to go, why
would I go
gay? Stop being stupid.
I'd rather have dick pictures and
[ __ ] people ask me how much to [ __ ]
rather than dealing with make believe
boyfriends and [ __ ] all the other
madness that comes with it. They're
really trying to say that dating is not
easy for women. They are [ __ ] stupid,
bro. Yeah, I hate him. I actually
generally hate him, bro. I hate how they
sit there trying to give you advice when
they're the one that's in a relationship
or like they're the ones that wouldn't
get with you. It's hypocritical. I hate
them. I actually generally hate them. I
fell out with my mom today as well. They
weren't even over gambling. It's got
nothing to do with gambling, bro. I
still got over 1,500 pound left. I'm
good. I'm good,
bro. I don't try to be in a relationship
with them. I generally hate him. I hate
him. The last time I went out was
Friday and that was cuz I had to get my
hair done anyways, get my passport
renewed. I [ __ ] hate them, bro. If I
could murder one of them and get away
with it, I would do
it. Like, if I could actually murder one
and get away with it, I would do it. If
there was a way, I'm not even joking.
Emily would do it, bro. I'm not even
joking. I [ __ ]
would. Just like that [ __ ] in
America, you know, just like a lot of them,
bro. Yeah. A lot of the things they do
is wrong as well, though. Acting [ __ ]
having an attitude problem. taking the
piss out of people. That's all wrong,
but no one has an opinion on that. No that. You
know, no one seems to have an opinion on
that though what they [Music]
do, which is quite strange. They're
allowed to be [ __ ] They're allowed
[ __ ] It doesn't matter, mate. It
doesn't matter. Actions speak louder
than words. It doesn't matter.
Actions speak louder than words. I hate
them. I [ __ ] hate them [ __ ] bro. I
only went out Friday cuz I had to renew
my passport and do my hair. Anyways, I
won't be going out this week. I won't be
going out next
week. Trust me, it wasn't over the
gambling. I lost that football bet
yesterday. I didn't even care. I didn't
even care, bro. I didn't care about
losing 70 pound. Believe you me, I
didn't care. Honestly, I didn't care.
For real, man.
I actually hate them, bro. I actually do
them. I don't understand how other
people don't. They're [ __ ]
evil. Did I get my eyebrows waxed? No, I
just got him down at the barbers.
Yeah, I just got him down at the
barbers. That's when I went out last Friday.
Yeah, they're really evil, but no one seems to
care. No one seems to care,
bro. It's mad, isn't it? So,
yeah, it's a sad life, isn't it?
No, I need to go get some food in a bit.
Then I'll be back to bed. I need to get
some uh tea bags as well. I run out of
tea. Oh, [ __ ] I forgot the tea bags. I
just went to the shop. I forgot the tea
bags. But yeah, then I'll probably just
stay in bed.
Yeah. Uh hopefully die in my sleep. I'm
getting close to it to be honest, man. I
mean, I'm snoring. I'm [ __ ] having
nightmares and [ __ ] So
yeah, I think that's how you know you're
depressed. I'm waking up like 9:50,
which is quite late for me. Which is
quite late for me to be
fair. But yeah.
Yeah, it's quite late for me,
Dad. Yeah, life
sucks. What they want, whenever they
want. It's sad, isn't it, bro? It's a
sad life, eh? There's nothing you can do to change
it. Nothing you can do to change it. [Music]
And I fell out with my mom today.
So trying to give you advice when
they're the one that's in a relationship
that has just got into a relationship. [ __ ] off.
It's sad, isn't
it? It is sad.
Yep. A lot.
Oh, I just came on here, started talking
about kids, and then she just said, "Oh,
don't contact me again." Because I was
talking about kids, and I told her to
drop dead. I told her to drop dead.
She's an asthmatic little
[ __ ] But yeah, this is what women in
this country get you like. But people
still defend them. To the heels and
back. It's mad, isn't
it? [ __ ] hate him, I
do. So she said, "Yeah, don't contact
her again." I just told her, "Fuck off and drop
dead." Yeah, we used to speak every day
that ain't it, but I don't give a [ __ ]
I saw she's an asthmatic [ __ ] [ __ ] off. You know,
simple. That's it, bro.
Yeah, it sucks,
bro. Nope, not today.
Saturday. Yeah, I'll probably get some
food soon and then
just sleep and hope I don't wake up.
It's a bad life, isn't it?
It's a bad life, bro. It sucks to suck at
it. Nothing you can do to change the
situation. Yeah, women can get sex
whenever she wants. And this woman on
Reddit tried having the cheat to tell me
that, "Oh, you've barely traveled."
Barely traveled. I've been to three
different countries out of the UK. Yeah.
in terms of out of the UK and there's
people that's not even been out of
[ __ ] England about barely travel just
because you're a spoiled little brat
that's probably been around the [ __ ]
world that's not barely traveling mate
at [ __ ] not even 30 years of
age you know I [ __ ] hate it
mate yeah but it's not barely traveled
traveled yeah it's not much but it's not barely
traveled and I'm not your [ __ ] mate
either. So don't call me mate cuz I'm
not your [ __ ]
mate. Yeah, but it's not barely
traveled and she's trying to give me
advice when she's the one that's in a
relationship. [ __ ] off, man. [ __ ] right
off. What the [ __ ] would you know? You
know who the [ __ ] are these women to try
to give you
advice? Who are they to try to give you
advice when they're sucking someone's
dick every day? Ask me this question,
Ghost. Who the [ __ ] are they to be
giving you advice when they're sucking
someone's dick every day and they're
having sex? Who are they to be giving you advice? You
know, I [ __ ] hate them, bro. I really
do hate them. Like you don't understand,
bro. I absolutely do. You
know, I really hate
him. Well, I answered you. Sorry. You
was pissing me
off. So, who are they to give you advice? Yeah.
feel to give you advice,
lad. So now I don't speak to any of my
family now. I spoke to my sister
occasionally, but I spoke to mom every
day. So now I don't speak to any of
them. The dating game [ __ ] Nothing's
going to change. Is there really a point
in life at this stage? Is there really a
point in living at this stage? I don't
think there is, bro.
I don't think there is at this point,
bro. At this
stage, no family, bro. But I don't care.
That's the difference. I don't give a
[ __ ] Uh, just woke up the press, man. I
was talking about kids because this guy
on YouTube was pissing me off and then
my mom was like, "Oh, don't contact me
again." Cuz she heard what I was saying
about kids cuz she's got no life and she
stalks my YouTube.
I I told I told her to drop dead. I told
her to drop dead and get raped. That's
what I said to my mom. Asthmatic piece of [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ] I woke up in a
foul mood today, bro. A foul, dirty,
stinking mood. I did cuz these [ __ ]
women. Oh, man. I woke up in a bad mood, bro.
bad bad mood. Bad bad bad mood. And
rightfully so, after all the bad
experiences you've had, you should feel
this way. You should be like this. You
know, you're in your right to feel this
way after all of these experiences that
you've you've displayed on your channel
as well. You
know, I hate them, bro. They're [ __ ]
They don't get the hate they deserve.
Men do, though, you know.
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ]
bro. But you know what? I've got a good
mind to go back to that [ __ ] American
going that dad's door. I've got a good
mind, bro, when I get this passport to
come and go in that [ __ ] store and put a
brick through his [ __ ]
window. I feel like someone needs to pay
for all of these bad experiences. I feel
like someone needs to pay. And what's
this, bro? They're having group chats
about you laughing at you, bro. Just do
you want I feel like we should just go
to his door on it. I feel like we should
just go to America and go in the [ __ ]
store. [ __ ] it. We know where he lives.
We know where he lives. Do you know what
I'm saying? [ __ ] Scott the dad. I'll
show you little group chats, mate. I'll
get the whole YouTube [ __ ] laughing
about you and your slaggy Syrian family
by the time I'm done with you.
Yeah. You want war, brother? You got it.
Watch when I got this Watch when I get
this passport back as well. Bro, there's
things that are happening. Watch when I
get this passport back for like someone
has to pay, bro. Someone's got to pay,
bro. You know what I'm saying? Someone has to, lad.
Yeah. Nah, not really, bro. She's just a
scumbag. Nah, not even, bro. I don't
even care about the bits anymore.
Nah. Oh, yay. We've received your old
passport. Okay. So, yeah, should be a
should be here in a couple of
days. Should be here in a couple of
days. I just got a notification. Yeah.
Nah, it's not even that. I just don't
like her. She's a [ __ ] I hate her. I
hate westernized [ __ ] Nah, not even
a job with me, lad. No, I don't talk
about her every day. No, I [ __ ]
don't. Like, just go to just rock up to
the dads and just slap him up, bro.
Like, he's a [ __ ] old man, bro. Like
what could he
do? Just rock up through his gap and
slap the [ __ ] out of him, bro. Since we
don't know where she lives. Yeah.
Yeah. Just just
like I'd pay good money, bro. Like [ __ ]
the 70 pound, bro. Like I'd rather be
skinn. Yeah. If I could have that Yank
[ __ ] in front of me, I'd rather be
skinned for a whole month, bro. I would
rather be skinful for if I could have
five minutes with that [ __ ]
Oh, bro. I call Sean obsessed. Yeah,
because he's got a channel on me and he
makes community post on me every day. He
is obsessed. Have you gone on his
channel? Yeah, Sean is literally
obsessed. He's an obsessed weirdo. Have
you gone on his channel? Where he
doesn't stop making community posts on
me? He literally is obsessed with me.
His whole life is about me. He literally
stalks me all day, every day. Yes, he is
obsessed. He really is. Dolly's channel.
Yeah. Yeah. You couldn't find Tam
though. Yeah. I'm receding. Yeah. Stop talking about
yourself. Yeah. Stop talking about
yourself. You are single and you are you
you are a manta. Can't even show 20
quid. I showed you [ __ ] over a grand
on Friday. Go self-reflect on another
channel. Go self-reflect on another
channel. Not this channel, man. This is
not the This is not the channel for self-reflecting
spastics. That's how you know these
people are so skinned, lad. Look, bro.
This is how you know these people are so
skinn because they're coming on here
asking you to show 20 pound. That's how
you know they're skinn. these people,
bro. This is how you know these people
are skin. But I don't make videos on
her. But I don't make videos on her. And
that's how you know these people on here
are skin. Because why are they asking
you to show them 20 when you show them
£1,100 on Friday and you've just [ __ ]
gambled 70 quid. That's how you know
these people are skin. They got they got
nothing in their life, bro. They want
£300 a month. I swear to God, these
people on here Yeah. They are skin. They
are the skinnest flints going skin
benefit little fat lossers that have got
nothing going for themselves. That's
what these people are, bro. These people
are skin. They're losers. They're fat
sos. They ain't got nothing going for
themselves. So they come on here and
project their misery every single day
and their [ __ ] lives and they've been
doing it for [ __ ] years now.
Pathetic, man. Pathetic. They are
pathetic, bro. And to think these people
are older than
me. Yeah, I don't make videos on that
[ __ ] I just said I'd want five minutes
with them. I would smash them up, bro. I
wish I could have woke up next to her
today. Oh, I would have smashed her. I
would have chucked her out the window. I
would have threw the [ __ ] out the [ __ ] window,
bro. You know, I want to take out on
someone, bro. Like I really want to take
out one of these
women. Maybe she's she'll be back here next
April. Maybe she'll be back here next
Eh. Yeah. Bye-bye now.
Bye-bye. These people are fat loss.
They've got nothing going for
themselves. This is why they do what
they do every day on YouTube. You
know, brav brav brav. How am I
westernized? How do you explain I'm
westernized when I'm when I'm from East
London? How's how am I westernized?
What? But yeah, I wish I could have five
minutes with that [ __ ] American deck.
I would slap the [ __ ] out of her,
bro. Oh my god. I would slap the [ __ ]
out of her. Smash her teeth down her
throat. Look, I'll put a video,
bro. Uh, sorry, a picture
up. I would smash this [ __ ] up so badly,
bro. I would smash this [ __ ] up so bad,
I swear to God,
man. Yeah, I'm I'm obsessed with wanting
to smash the [ __ ] [ __ ] out of her.
Yeah, I want to smash the [ __ ] out of
her, bro. Cuz I haven't got to do it yet
because the [ __ ] don't come out. Yeah.
got all your little
pictures. What has she done to annoy me?
Um, just that she's a [ __ ] I just don't
like her because she's a [ __ ] and she
thinks she can lead people on and play
with them and then just get on with her
life being a [ __ ] Not really much. Just
she's a [ __ ] and I don't like [ __ ] So,
anything recent? No, I just don't like
her. She's a
[ __ ] She likes to be this evil person,
Steven Howard. But when she meets her
match, she wants to play victim. This is
what a lot of these people like to do,
bro. They like to play a [ __ ] right?
And be a [ __ ] to people, but then
when they meet their match, they go a
running, playing the victim. Oh, you
know what I'm saying, bro? It's crazy.
Just nothing. I just don't like the [ __ ]
You know, you know when you just don't like
someone like someone, bro, it's hard
it's hard to explain, you
know? Like, who the [ __ ] does she think
she is, bro? Like, who does she actually think she is, you
know? That's all. Nothing
recent. Maybe she is really nice. Uh,
no, she's not really nice. She's a
scumbag. She's a [ __ ]
scumbag. So, about Oh, I'm not
interested. I'm sorry. As soon as she as
soon as she wrote that line, yeah, after
I told her what she done to me, I was
like, "Okay, let me try and play the
nice person and get an apology out of
this person." And then when they didn't
want to give me an apology, I thought,
"Fuck it. I'll just ruin their life."
Message their family. I gave them
chances. I did give them chances time
and time again. Please can you just
apologize? Like you're pissing me off.
And they thought they could just ignore
me everywhere. So I just started
messaging their family, you know? Who do
they think they are, man? Like have a
bit of [ __ ] sympathy for someone, you
know, and then making stuff up about
people. [ __ ] that. I'm messing your
family. Simple. She deserved everything
she got. She deserved everything she got, bro.
everything she got. She's a [ __ ] I hate
her. She was prepared to leave somebody
depressed because of what she done.
Think about that, Steven Howard. She was
prepared to not give a [ __ ] how she made
anyone feel. Does that sound like a nice
person to you? Does that sound like a
nice person? Like they they pretty much
essentially [ __ ] with you on purpose.
Yeah. They done it on
purpose, you know, and then they think
they can just get back with their life.
Like, nah, bro. That's not the way.
That's not the way that's going to
work. Just talking about just how much I hate
women. Just hate women, mate. We're just
going on about women and how they're evil.
She thought she could be a [ __ ] to me
because she probably saw you as
vulnerable. Vulnerable and a [ __ ]
And she thought, "Oh, let me [ __ ] with
this [ __ ] Let me [ __ ] with their head."
They're not They don't have a different
side to them. Because that's how they
think. You see, these women are sick in
the head. They're
evil. So, obviously, because you know,
you spent money and stuff and the way I
was dressed, you wouldn't think that
I've got a crazy [ __ ] side to me. [ __ ]
that, bro. I'm not going to let this
little [ __ ] walk all over me. You know what I
mean? I might go to her dad's house,
bro. I might actually go to her dad's
house cuz where I've gave up with this
dating [ __ ] now and these women, I feel
like someone's got to really pay, bro. I
feel like someone's really really got to
pay and it's me or them, bro. You know
what I'm saying? Like, I actually think
cuz I've got the dad's
address. Like, I have his address, you
know? They've received my passport as
well. So, I should get
that hopefully. I was saying by Friday,
Friday, Saturday, hopefully I get this pass ball
back. Just women. I hate women. They're
evil. I hate how women have the dating
game easy. Smokey. Like, they don't even
have to lift a finger and they can get
sex and they can get relationships and
they can be [ __ ] to people. I hate
them. I [ __ ] hate women. I genuinely
[ __ ] do, bro. I really hate them. They're evil
[ __ ] Some might post posters out, bro.
Not nice. What do you
mean? I just hate women. I hate them,
bro. All right. Who do you actually
think is right, me or this USA? Izzy? I
think I'm right. I think I'm definitely
definitely definitely right. Who do you
think you are? You [ __ ] Yeah. And then
you think you're going to try and start
playing a victim and then you think
you're going to [ __ ] ignore. Yeah.
You think Yeah. And then you think
you're going to [ __ ] ignore,
right? People everywhere and people not
going to message your family. Who do you
think you [ __ ] are? You [ __ ] Huh?
But it's many different experiences,
bro. We're not talking about one or two.
We're talking like these [ __ ] you
know. Who the [ __ ] do they think they are,
bro? Always, bro. Always.
I [ __ ] hate women,
bro. And she's [ __ ] stinking as well.
She's actually stinking. Like, she's
actually ugly, bro. Like, if you
actually look at her.
Yeah. She's actually [ __ ] ugly,
bro. And she thinks she can act like
that towards people. She's actually [ __ ] ugly,
bro. And she's even worse now. She's
older. You know what I'm
saying? No, I can't remember, bro.
She looks okayish in this
one. Bye-bye. Bye-bye, Peter
Griffin. She looks okay in this one, but
this was old.
Maybe a six or
something. Yep, pretty
much. Yeah. You don't look like that
anymore, though, do you? You
can't. You're [ __ ] stinking.
stinking. You know what I
mean? You don't look like that anymore,
mate. All in all, she's actually stinking,
bro. Except that photo, but she's stinking, bro.
[ __ ] My stand is in the dirt,
bro. You know, if you look at this
picture, she's stinking,
bro. That picture is all right, but
no. See on the right there. She's stinking, bro.
I know. She was pissing me off,
bro. [ __ ] pissing me off, bro. Yeah,
she's mid, but she looks worse
now. She looks worse now. These are like
from like a year and a half ago. So
now, so imagine having someone like that
thinking they're better than you. Imagine
like having someone like
that thinking that they're better than
you, bro. Imagine
like Yeah, she's mid now. She She's even
worse now, bro, cuz she's a like two
years. But she looks Imagine having
someone like that thinking that they're
better than you. Eh, who the [ __ ] do
they think they are, man? Huh? [ __ ]
Bye-bye. Bye-bye, Peter
Griffin. The only picture you kind of look good
in. That's like the only picture you
look good in, bro. Imagine
that. You got some fat hands there.
AP. Now she's proper bad, bro. [ __ ]
fat and everything. Yeah, I never been
me been fat me
lad like these fat
cons cuz he's a
[ __ ] now got no figure. She's got
nothing but no figure.
Nothing Mark Taylor. Let me see.
Yeah, he is a stalker, bro. He stalks
me. He is [ __ ] man.
This guy is such a sad eye, man. I swear
down. Yeah, she's gone really fat, man.
Why has she got really fat? There's a
meal actually got really
fat. She's got really fat in
it. She's got really fat in it. Steven
Howard, you got fat man.
I'm going to go to America and go on her
dad's door. Uh, Groomer Chan, as uh
Timmy would call you. Yeah, I'm going to
start laughing at them in real life. I
got the passport off it. Just just said
we received your old passport. So, uh,
yeah, I should get it in a couple of
days. Yep. Going to be another 10 years,
mate. Another 10 years. I'm going to
call some chaos. Steven Howard. I'm
going to cause some chaos with this [ __ ] basketball, mate. Groomer Chan.
Groomachan. Yeah, they got a group that
laughing at me. I will laugh at them,
bro. I'll let the neighbors know what they're about.
Yeah. Yeah. This is the only picture you
don't look like a complete mining.
You fat [ __ ] And that was like two
years ago. Now you look
[ __ ] Now you look Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Goona, listen. Whatever you
say, you're not going to you're not
going to trigger me.
No matter what you say, bro, you're not
going to trigger
me. Yeah. I can't afford to go America. Yeah, bro. Okay. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, look at the
doggy. No one cares about Morgan the
manta. You've aged a lot. A
Zippy, you've you've aged a lot. You have a
Zippy. She's scared of me, bro. And she
will always be scared of me.
Yeah. And she will always be scared of me, buff.
You I don't, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] I
[ __ ] Who's her ex? Hold on. Who's her
ex? Her ex? What? What ex? What are you
talking about, bro? Bye-bye Peter
Griffin. You know Mahuza
X. Yeah, don't worry, bro. I'm going to
go on the door. But bro, but they're
laughing behind the keyboard across the
sea. That's not an achievement, bro. That's cowardly.
Yes, but the thing is, bro, that's
cowardly because that's doing stuff
behind a keyboard across the pond. That's
cowardly, you know? It's like me going
to Belgium. It's like me going to the
Netherlands, right? [ __ ] with
somebody and coming back and starting
all my [ __ ] when I come back. It's
cowardly. That's what cowards do. So, it
seems like the coward, the cowards
running the family. They run in the
I didn't lie about going to Boston.
There we go. Look at that face. Yeah.
Okay. Yes, I did. And I'm going to go
back there as
well. Charles has got a new boyfriend
now. Uh, sorry, a new girlfriend now.
Where is this [ __ ] Charles has
got a new girlfriend. He moved
on. Yeah. Well, there were never lies to begin
with, you know. There we
go. That's Charles's new girlfriend. I'm
so happy, bro. I'm happy for him, to be
fair. You got away from that [ __ ] You
got away from that [ __ ] in
America. Okay, she wins. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Okay. She wins. She changed her
number. Okay. Okay. Listen,
bro. Gona, you're trying to say you're
trying to say that I lied about going to
America. Bro, she changed her number.
So, how would have I contacted her if I
apparently wasn't even there? She's a
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
I'm on Reddit asking for
advice. Nope. I never said I didn't
sleep with Izzy. And why are we I'm not
going on about who I've slept with and
who I've not slept with. Mate, you're
obsessed. Every time you keep bringing
it up, you're
obsessed. Nope. You're obsessed, bro. You are obsessed. Yeah. There we
go. I don't give too much information
right away. No, I [ __ ] don't.
Ah, okay. Goa. So, if I go there
tomorrow, is the little [ __ ] going to come
out? If I went there tomorrow,
hypothetically, let's speak
hypothetically cuz I don't even have my
passport back yet. Is the little [ __ ]
going to come
out? Come on. Come on. Is the [ __ ]
going to come out or
not? No. Exactly. So, [ __ ] off.
I would love to throw acid all over her
face. I would love to,
bro. I would love to throw acid all over her [ __ ]
face. Just throw acid all over her, bro.
You know what I mean? Blow that
acid. You know what I mean?
Yeah, I'm [ __ ] mad. I'm a mad
bastard, bro. And I can't
lie. I can't
lie. See that? I can't lie.
lie. I can't lie. But it [ __ ] woke me
up. It woke me up, mate.
I would love to just get acid and just
throw it all over her
face. I would love to just get a load of
acid and just throw it in her
face. You know what I
mean? Have you ever watched Chucky? They
done that in
Chucky. And just throw it all over her face.
I don't care if it will get clipped. I
don't give a
[ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] mate. I don't
give a [ __ ] if it will get clipped. I
don't give a [ __ ] mate.
I don't care. They can clip it all they
want. I don't give a
[ __ ] All right. So, if I went there
tomorrow, hypothetically, would the
[ __ ] come out or not? Would the [ __ ]
come out or not? You know what you
should do, Guda? I'll give you her
Instagram and you can find out when
she's coming back to the UK or anywhere
in Europe and we'll see who will be
laughing and we will see who will be
laughing. I think that's a good I think
that's a fair deal cuz I think they
pretty much come to Europe every year.
You message them and you let them know
you tell them to let you know whenever
they're anywhere, Amsterdam, England,
Germany, wherever it is. You you find
that out and you come back to
me. Yeah. Because I think they come
every April the
12th. They've been doing that for a
couple of years now, not England. And we
will see who will be laughing. A time
and a place, a location, and we'll see
who will be laughing then. Yeah, I'll
have my passport by then. That sounds
like a really good deal. And she can
bring whoever she wants, wherever she
wants. How's that?
Go on, Guna. Go on. Go on. Find out.
Morgan Jobert, you know the cunt's name. So go
on. Yeah. And meet Terry. I went to
Terry's area and he didn't come out. out you little
[ __ ] Mate, listen
listen. You're saying about how I'd meet
Tram. Yeah, I want to meet her and slap
her in her face. Bro, listen, listen,
listen. Her dad was getting scared. You
know what her dad said to me? Her dad
said that he was going to handcuff me.
Her dad said that he was going to
[ __ ] handcuff me. Yeah, I went to
Terry's area and he didn't come out. You stupid little
[ __ ] Yeah, I went to Terry's area.
When was it? No, it weren't last year.
Not last year. The year before that. And
he didn't come out. Yeah, just like that
time. And the [ __ ] didn't come out and
he said he was on probation. Yeah. Get your facts right.
So the dad wouldn't meet me.
Yeah. The dad wouldn't meet me.
Yeah. My ass fell out, mate. They They
went to the police on me. No one's ass
fell out. They went to the police on me.
Yeah. Look what I was texting to the dad.
Yeah. I'd love to throw acid on her face
all over it.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, go and find out when
she's coming anyways. Guda, find out
when she's coming. Come on.
Yeah. Living her best life, mate. I get
more money than her. She's not living
her best life. She's got given an STD.
She's passed her sale by date. She's not
living her best life. She's a skank with
like two pairs of clothing. Yeah, she's
not living her best life. She's a slag.
She got given an STD. Her [ __ ] ain't
even that good. She's not living her
best life, bro. I'm the one who's living
the best life. I'm getting over three
grand a month and I don't even need to
work. That's what you call semi living
your best life is. She's not living no
good life. She's a slag.
She has to work for her money and she
gets less than me. She ain't living no
best life. Believe that. She didn't go
abroad until she was 20 [ __ ] seven.
She ain't living no best life, bro. I'm
telling you, it's seeming less and less
like it, you know. Do I still gamble
occasionally? No, good. I slept with
her. Yeah. You don't know what's
happened. Was you there? Was you there?
You wasn't there. So stop talking like
you know anything. And Gona, listen, let
me tell you something as well. A woman
is not going to say, "Oh yeah, I [ __ ]
him." No woman's going to do that. And
you know that. Even if I listen listen.
Okay. Okay. If I met a woman tomorrow,
right? If I met a woman tomorrow and you
messaged her, she's not going to tell
you that she slept with me, dummy.
They're never going to tell you the
truth. Some some random person is
messaging them. asking personal
questions is never going to tell you the
truth. You idiot. And you know this. You
know that they were never going to tell
you the truth. And they were also
cheating. So why are they going to tell
you the truth? What did you expect them
to say when they were cheating on their
partner and some random person messaged
them? You don't know. You wasn't there.
Why do you keep talking as if you was there? You
know, you know what I'm saying?
No, no, no, no, no, no. Difference is
Morgan was cheating. No. Morgan was
cheating on her partner. There's a big
difference. Yeah. Who then soon broke up
with her. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
No. No. No. No. Okay. Okay. Let me Okay.
Let me ask you. Okay. I Right. Let me
Okay. I'll ask you a question. Okay.
I'll ask you a question. Right. So, Okay.
Why would I don't even know why I'm
repeating myself. Why was you in her
apartment in the first place? Okay.
Okay. Okay. Right. So, why was I in her
apartment in the first
place? Why did she take me back to her
apartment in the first place? Answer.
Answer. No, no, no. Let's Let's go by
what your Let's Let's go by the logic.
Okay. [ __ ] what one of us said. Why am I
in that hotel room? Because mate, when a
gay guy was trying to follow me to a
hotel room, I told him to [ __ ] off. I
didn't keep him around. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no. Answer me this
question. Why is it after dinner they
took you round to their hotel
room? Answer me this question.
Why were they asking me if I had
condoms? Answer me this
question, you know? So, it doesn't make
sense even with what they
say. So, no. Everyone who goes into a
person's house [ __ ] pretty much. Yeah.
Pretty much when someone's only visiting
the country. Yeah. When you've met
somebody once and they've took you
straight back to their hotel room. Yeah.
They normally do [ __ ] yeah, bro. When
you've met someone once. Yeah. It
usually happens when you meet somebody
the first time. Every single time I have
met somebody once and I've gone back to
the house hotel room, we [ __ ] Yes.
Yes. Especially if it's the first time
you've met them. Yes. That means it's
[ __ ] time, buddy. But you would know
this because lack of life experience. Yeah. Done.
Um, I have never ever been with a been
to a hotel room and um room with someone
and not [ __ ] them except that person in
Nottingham cuz she was on her period but
she gave me a
[ __ ] again. Someone else I met once.
See, doesn't make sense,
lad. It doesn't make sense. It literally
does not make sense. She took me back.
You [ __ ] me just like she [ __ ] me.
Which is why she was the first one that
come on to me. And there's no point me
going back and forth with you, Gona. There's no
point. Do you
know? Cuz you're an idiot. You don't
know nothing, bro.
And you really are a s bastard,
lad. Okay, bro. Yeah. So, she took me on
to Right. So, she took me to her
apartment and she came on kissing me and
then she threw me out. Okay, bro. That
makes so much sense. Yeah. That's what
happened. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That
makes so much sense. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay, bro. You got it, bro. You got it.
You got it, bro. Yeah. Coming on,
kissing me. letting me suck her tits,
but then she kicked me out. Yeah, bro.
You're right. I got kicked out. Totally. Oh, bad.
Yeah, but that's a big notorious because
the problem with these westernized women
is they think that they're better than
everyone. Even when you we know that they're not.
Bye-bye. Yeah, he must have blocked you.
Yeah. He blocks everyone, I
think. And no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no. Listen, listen. Also, Sig
did make up stuff. Also, uh, Sig
actually did make up
stuff. Not to that extent, but actually
Sig did make up stuff. They all make up
stuff. They're all liars all in
different ways. They never with a woman.
They will never tell you the truth.
Notorious. They will never ever ever
tell you the truth. Do you remember that
time before, Notorious? Yeah. Well, you
might actually you might not have
actually remembered it cuz you weren't
on it. There was a woman before from
about four years ago when I had my iPad.
Yeah. She was like, "Oh, he was sending
me dick pictures. He was sending me dick
pictures." I said, "Oh, you were sending
me pictures as well." And she would deny
it. And she come on the community,
right? And she kept denying it and
denying it and denying it. Bro, I had to
update my iCloud and show everybody. And
then eventually she just she just come
off because they're liars. Women are all
liars. They are known to be liars. Their
word doesn't mean
nothing. You will never get the truth
from a woman ever. Especially somebody
that you've just met once. And you know
this as well, Gona. You know this
yourself. She didn't say that we did
stuff. She didn't say that we did stuff.
We She didn't say that we did stuff
because no one on here has ever spoke to
her. So, she didn't say
that. Nah, women are
scumbags. Women are [ __ ] scumbags.
That's what they are. They're [ __ ]
scumbags. Women are [ __ ] scumbags. I
hope they all get [ __ ]
raped. Stig is um somebody from New
Zealand who I had a one night stand with
two years ago. You might have missed it.
Me, I think they're I think they should
all get raped and
die. Yeah. And how Okay. So, how would
have I got weird then? Okay, bro.
Whatever you say. Okay. Well, she's
lying. Well, what she's saying is she's
lying. And the the thing is, GA, you
shouldn't even care whether I'm lying or
whether she's lying. Why why are you so
interested in this when I've been with
other women after her? Why are you so
interested in in this as well? Can I ask
that? One second. Why are you so
interested whether I've had sex? Wait
one second. One second. You claim that
you're a married man, right? I'm telling
you I have [ __ ] this person. You're
telling me I'm not. Why do you
care? Because I've had other people
since before and after them. even that
same April. So why why do you keep going
on about it,
bro? Why would I lie about [ __ ] her scan [ __ ]
bro? Nah, women are not amazing. I hope
they all die and get raped. Me, I hate
him. I [ __ ] hating me, lad.
Yeah. No, she she said to me, "Do you
have any condoms?" I said, "No, I don't
condoms." That's what that Morgan said.
She's like, "Do you have any condoms?" I
said, "No, I
don't. I don't use condoms anyways.
She's like, I prefer to [ __ ] without
um Yeah, they didn't reject me. They
me, mate. You keep telling yourself
that, bro. You keep telling yourself
that. You keep telling yourself that,
lad. She didn't reject me. I had the bitch's body.
But they both know they didn't make me
lose. She's a fool. Yep.
basically. Uh yeah, because the [ __ ]
led me on so I wondered why they
disappeared. Okay. Yeah. Did you see
what they were saying to me as well?
Yeah. Yeah. I was going along with what
they were saying.
I was going to [ __ ] saying look at
what they were [ __ ] saying to me. You
[ __ ] idiot. They were telling me to
go get tattoos with them. You [ __ ]
idiot. You [ __ ] idiot. You [ __ ]
idiot. No, but how? But she didn't
reject me cuz I got her body. So I got
what I wanted. I got what I wanted. When
somebody rejects you, you don't even get
a kiss out of
them. I got what I wanted.
So, no, cuz I got exactly what I wanted
when I wanted it. So,
yeah. Yeah. So what, bro? I got her body. So
what? And I thought because she was a
[ __ ] No, no, no. It wasn't that. If she
You know what? Yeah. The thing is,
Stephen Howard, let me let me tell you
what it is. Yeah. Ignore this Goona
Chan. If they turned around and said,
"Yeah, that um that they didn't want to
take it further because like you live
for or they got a man or like some sort
of I wouldn't have cared honestly. I
wouldn't give a [ __ ] bro, cuz I already
got what I wanted." But it's the way
they went about it and it was my whole
thing is thinking like who the [ __ ] do
they think they are? And because they
have an ego problem, I thought, "Okay,
let me try and lower that ego down." You
know, that's what it was. They played
games. They got the game played back
with them. They played the victim.
Simple. You know, they played games on
purpose. You fought back. They played
the victim. Story of your life, eh?
Yeah. So, if they said something like
that, then I would have cared to be
fair. And I didn't even message them for
like days after. So,
yeah. It was their ego that annoyed me.
Like who the [ __ ] do they think they
are, bro? You know. Yeah, she owed me.
Good. Yeah, just like when just like
when I went to Wales, I owned
you. Of course. What do you mean? Um, if
I got what I want, I I wouldn't I
wouldn't be obsessed. What makes you say
that? So, what is everything about sex
then? Okay, so going by your logic,
everything's about sex then.
Yeah. Ah, that doesn't make sense
then. And I didn't fake holiday.
So yeah, nice try,
Guna. So you think that you meet
somebody once and if you [ __ ] them, you
can't be obsessed with them, bro. Come
on, have a word with yourself, you [ __ ]
idiot. It doesn't even make any sense. God, you're
stupid. You're [ __ ] stupid, man.
God, you're a [ __ ] idiot. You
are. That is what you said. Yeah. But yeah, anyways, moving
forward. What I mean by I got what I
wanted. I got sex. That's what I meant.
That's what I meant by I got what I
wanted. You're obsessed, Gona, man.
You're [ __ ] obsessed, bro.
think you're you're you're
uh I'm starting to think, lad, that
you're um that you're not married, bro.
I'm starting to be less of a less less
and less of a believer in you, bro. Cuz
you've been going on about this Morgan
all day. You've been going on about this
Morgan all day. Why the [ __ ] would a
married man with kids care? It just
doesn't add up, bro. It really doesn't add up. us.
Yeah. You're obsessed, bro. All you go
on about is this [ __ ] American.
You're the You're the one that brought
it up today. I've got nothing to offer,
woman. Yep. Stop
self-projecting. You don't know what I
have. You don't know nothing about me. Stop
self-reflecting. And even if I had
nothing to offer a woman, good for me.
They reject you before they even get to
know what you have to offer. Stop
self-projecting, you little white
knight. You've been going about Morgan
for years. Why would someone who who can
get women uh Okay, GA. Um I showed many
many women after her. I showed many
her. Huh? Bro, listen. You know how many
women I had in that April alone? Then it
kind of died down until the summer and
then I met that New Zealand. But bro, I
had [ __ ] like three one night stands that year
after. I had like three one night stands
after that. That year round that October
time. Yes, I did. Do you think that
matters? I don't I just didn't like her,
bro. I wanted to [ __ ] with her cuz who
the [ __ ] does she think she [ __ ] is?
Do you not understand the
principle? Clearly, you
don't. Just because someone can get It's
like, bro, you you really think I can't
go out and and and probably get a woman
in like 2 3 weeks, but I don't want to
try because they're [ __ ] they're
[ __ ] I don't want to deal with their
attitude. I don't want to deal with
makebelieve boyfriends. I think you're
missing the point. The whole thing that
pisses me off is that a woman can get
any man she wants, can get sex anytime
she wants, and you have to put all this
effort in, deal with these [ __ ]
just to get someone in the end. No thank
you. I think that's the point you're
missing. I think that's generally the
point that you are actually
missing. Yeah. No, it doesn't [ __ ] with
me though because you don't know what
happened. So, it doesn't [ __ ] with me.
So, no, it doesn't [ __ ] with me. But
that's what I'm trying to say. It's
like I just find the whole dating game
unfair and people shouldn't have to put
up with it. People shouldn't have to
deal with it. It's wrong. It's not
right. It's not
normal dealing with these westernized [ __ ] women. You
know, I [ __ ] hate them. Every last
one of them, lad. Every last one of
them. And if these people actually went
out and dealt with women, they would see
what women are like. They're all
[ __ ] They would see what women are
like. [ __ ] absolute [ __ ]
[ __ ] They would see what they're
like. So that's what makes me think that
they don't have much life experience,
these people on this
YouTube, you know? They don't have much
life experience. I I I don't think they
do, bro. I don't think I generally don't think they
do. Never mind what I can offer a woman.
That's none of your business. That's not
what we're talking about. We're talking
about how disgusting it is how a woman
can get sex whenever she wants. How a
woman can get um dates whenever she
wants and a man has to go through
madness to be in with a chance. That's
what we're talking about. And how
disgusting it is, you
know? They're they're [ __ ] vile, man.
They're scum of the
earth. Well, it's not what I'm talking
about. Well, it's not what I'm talking
about. So, you're talking to your [ __ ] self,
lad. That's what makes me That's what I
woke up thinking about, bro. It's like
if they struggle the same, I wouldn't
have cared. I don't really give a [ __ ]
about struggling. It's the fact that
they can get whatever they want,
whenever they want. And people go on
Reddit saying, "Oh, yeah, but they've
got to deal with dick pictures, so
they've got to deal with people asking
them, "Oh, how much would you [ __ ] me
for?" So, we've got to deal with
[ __ ] women. We've got to deal with
makebelie boyfriends. We've got to deal
with getting [ __ ] nothing our whole
lives. So, what what's a few dick
pictures? Really? Is that what That's
nothing. That's nothing. I think I've
been sent [ __ ] dick pictures before.
They have got the upper hand with dating
whether they like it or not.
Simple. What the [ __ ] is that? Just see some
chat. Doesn't matter what I can offer.
Never you mind what I can
offer. Yeah. So why would you why would
you play a game that's rigged against
you? It doesn't make any sense. They can
get whatever they want when and the
thing is even if you put effort into it,
you still won't get nothing.
Even if you work on
yourself, you still won't get nothing.
You will still get the makebelieve
boyfriends. Like, okay, fair enough,
right? You might get big pictures. You
might get weirdos messaging you on
dating apps. I'm not just Okay, yeah,
you might get that, but we've got to go
out and approach and deal with your
[ __ ] attitude. You know how Do you
know how much worse that is? We've got
to go out and deal with you pretending
you've got boyfriends, you being [ __ ]
[ __ ] Which one's worse? Which
one's worse? I know which one's
worse. You know, like what? People send
you dick pictures. You've seen dicks
millions of times. You've sucked enough
drug dealers [ __ ] dicks. So
what? I [ __ ] hate him, my bro.
I [ __ ] hate him, my dear. [ __ ]
hate him. How people defend him is
beyond me. Must be a different day and age,
J. I [ __ ] hate him. I do, bro. I swear to
them. So, yeah.
Why would you play a game that's rigged against
you? You know, evil women. Like, why why
would you play a game that's [ __ ] rigged against
you, you know? They can get every
anything they want whenever they want
and you have to sit there and suffer and
deal with their attitude. What do you
expect someone to say, bro? I don't understand. You
know [ __ ] annoying it is.
Yeah. You in your [ __ ] fat [ __ ] face. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, I generally don't think anyone
hates women more than me. I generally
don't think there is one person in this
world. There's no Ant-Man. There's no no
one. I hate him cuz I know what they're
like. And I take I take offense to it
when people come on here and try to say,
"Oh, it's not like that. They're not
like that." I [ __ ] hate them. I can't
get with an old woman. It's a
madness. There's a reason I can't get
with an old woman,
bro. You know, I can't get with an older
woman, bro. I would do, but I
can't. Because when you try to get with
an older woman, their excuse is, "If
only you was
older." You know, "If only you was
older." That's what they say, bro. These
That's what these older women
say. Yep, they do. They're [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] The games never stop.
Even when they're 40, when they're in
their 40s, when they're in their 50s,
whatever, they're get it never ever
stops. Yeah. They'll say if you're
older. Yeah. They won't they will use my
age as an excuse even though I'm 27.
So now he's
married. She's married. She
is. Yeah, she's married,
bro. That's suck though.
It I'm not even living, bro. I'm I'm
actually just existing. And it's not
even gambling, Stephen Howard. I've got
like 1,600 pound. I still got some money
left over and [ __ ] Uh, you know what I mean, bro?
like good amount in it, but I'm still
waking up every day fed up, you know?
Every [ __ ] day fed up, fed up, fed
up, fed up, fed up, fed up, fed
up, you know? It's bad, bro. You
know, [ __ ] fed up every [ __ ]
day. Should you be waking up every day
fed up, lad?
You know, waking up every day fed
up. You really think that's a lie for anyone,
bro? Waking up every day [ __ ] fed
up. This [ __ ] it's a [ __ ] life, bro.
No, I don't need some direction. I need
to give up. That's what I need to do. I
should have gave up a long [ __ ] time
ago. That's what I need to do. I need to
give up just like I should have a long time
ago. That's what I need to
do. I need to give up.
Like I should have a long ass time
ago. No, I've got like 1,600 pound. I'm
still not better. I've got some money
coming in a couple of days. Nah, I still
wake up every day fed up. Fed the [ __ ]
up every day. Thinking about my bad
experiences, thinking how the dating
game's rigged against you sucks dick. It
does. It's like torment. Every day being
awake is literally torment. I'm not even joking, bro.
I won't feel better cuz I got money now.
I've got like
1,500,600. You know what I'm saying? Nothing
changes. Nothing changes,
lad. And that's what happens when you go
and that's why you gamble, you see. And
that's when it becomes dangerous. We
like, oh, just go
gamble, you know? And then that's what
happens. Oh, we'll just gamble. And then
when you gamble, that's how you lose.
It's just a [ __ ] life. I just want to die, you
know? I'm not going to be speaking to my
mom anymore now anyways.
So, I don't really have anything to live
for. All thanks to women. Eh,
mad. Really, really bad guy.
Yeah. Wish I was [Music] dead. Dead,
lad. Nah. And no good women
exist. Yeah. If you kill yourself, they win.
Yeah. Yeah. Everyone's in the same boat.
Yeah. There's no good women that exist.
They're all the same. Sadly, all the
ones I've ever
met, they're all the [ __ ]
same. They're all the same, sadly, mate.
I've gave them chance upon chance upon
chance upon chance to prove me wrong.
But every time I get proven right,
they're all the same scum. Every single
one of them I've met.