Timmy's projecting again. He's
projecting his skimpness and he's
virginity again. What have I told you,
Timmy? He's not even letting me on the
[ __ ] panel cuz he knows I'm right
about him and Virgin Boy. He knows I'm
right about the two virgins. That's why
he won't let me back up cuz he knows I'm
right. He knows I'm right. They are
skint. And yes, 13 grand in in two years
makes you [ __ ] skint. Cuz it's not
even a life-changing amount of money.
And if you'd stopped kicking me, right,
then I would have said that Timmy, you are skints.
That's why every single time you get
show money, you run away cuz you are
skint. That's why you're so obsessed
with the word skint. Cuz it's what you
and nonslegs is. Skint. Yes. That's what
it That's why you keep going on about
skin people cuz you are [ __ ] skin.
What the [ __ ] bro? Four months ago
asking where the [ __ ] money was.
Doesn't matter where the money was. You
got shown money and you ran away. Cuz
you are [ __ ] skint. You are skint.
That's why you won't let anyone on the
[ __ ] panel. You're [ __ ] idiot, man.
What an idiot. Not even letting me
[ __ ] on the panel.
Timmy, I'm not showing you money ever
again. You can keep projecting your
skittness. Like I said, it's about time
you and your followers started shutting
me up. It's about time you and your
followers started shutting me up once
and for all. You little self-reflector.
pretending that you got [ __ ] four
grand. You ain't got [ __ ] nothing.
Just like non legs. 13 grand is not a
life-changing amount of money. It
wouldn't even see you through [ __ ] 6
months. Yeah. So, before I [ __ ]
comment on here talking about [ __ ] that
you don't know anything about, you
[ __ ] fat virgin. Remember remember
the word what I said about be biased.
Yeah. You've seen me with women. You've
seen me with money. You're a
self-reflector with brain damage. Just
like most of these people on here.
You're self-reflecting [ __ ] fat, ugly
disabled people. Timmy, you're still a
virgin. Just like [ __ ] launch legs.
That's why you defend the [ __ ] so much.
You know what I'm saying? That's why you
defend the [ __ ] so much cuz you're both
virgins. Skid virgins. And yes, 13 grand
in two years. That's skint.
It's not a life-changing amount of
money. And if you actually let somebody
[ __ ] joined, you know what I mean?
like all of this. Why the [ __ ] should I
have to go out and show this skin [ __ ]
money again? Every time I show them
money, they run away. Same as nonslegs.
Then they're going to come back in two
years with a small amount, 13 grand. And
yes, it is a small amount, 13 grand. It
ain't no life-changing amounts of money,
even though people are going to [ __ ]
pretend that it [ __ ] well is.
You know, it's it's a madness.
Is he going to let me join
like the Let me try join again. Right. Yeah.
in. Yep. He's not letting me in. What is
the [ __ ] point, bro? If they're not
even going to let anyone in. Pointless. [ __ ] pointless.
So every single time these people have
done their bollocks and everyone's skin
to them, every single time these angry
gamblers have done their bollocks and
everyone else is skint
they talk about skin every day because
they are skinned. That's why they're sat
there on YouTube every [ __ ] day cuz
they are skinned. Skint than anything.
Same as nodd legs. 13 grand skint 31
that is skint. Yes. No one's ever going
to say that because they're all biased
on it. Listen to me. Why should people
have to show you money again for what?
The millionth [ __ ] time for you to
run away again, huh?
For you to run away a [ __ ] again? Oh
my [ __ ] god, bro.
Same self-reflecting with these clowns.
I swear to God, Reddit [ __ ] got me
back on this [ __ ] bro. I'm not even joking.
Madness. Absolute madness.
Proper proper madness, lad.
£250 a week. You don't know what people
get to meet. You don't know people's
lives. Stop acting like you do cuz you don't
selfrelecting every time to these people here.
You're trying to call Greavves a fat
loader, Jimmy. You are a fat loaner. Sat
on YouTube every day. No life, no money
in your 40s. You are a fat loaner. But
guess what? At least Greavves got hope.
Let me let me let me back Greavves up a
sec with this one. Yeah. At least
Greavves got [ __ ] hope. Yeah, you're
a 40-year-old fat loaner on YouTube
every day. What are you doing now? Who
you with right now? Who are you with
right now? No one. You little keyboard
warrior. And you are the ma. The
40-year-old ma. The ma ugly man. At
least Greavvesy has got some [ __ ]
hope. You [ __ ] loser in your 40s
coming on here trying to talk about
other people, lad. Trying to talk about
other people. When you're in your 40s,
still a virgin and you ain't got no
money and you want to talk about other
people. What is it with these disabled
people on here getting themselves
confused with other people?
Like even though they're talking about
greasy and they're not talking about me,
it's like, bro, you ain't even got hope.
Like there's not even there's no denying
that. Like you these people have not
even got a hope in the world. Sat on
[ __ ] YouTube every [ __ ] day
talking about people that they don't
[ __ ] know. Greg is 28. Is he not?
You're in your [ __ ] 14y old fart.
Your old [ __ ] fart. You would have
thought it'd be the [ __ ] other way around. So
this is I swear to God, bro. This gives
you great damage.
Yeah. I can't show anything because I've
I'm skinn. I've shown you money and
every time I've shown you money, you
can't show nothing cuz you are skinned.
Again, other way around again. Every
time you get shown money, you run away
cuz you are skinned. Again, your
disabilities has got you confused with
other people. Again, every time you get
shown stuff, you can't show nothing cuz
you are skinned. That's the reality of
it. You are the ones that are skinned.
That's why none of you have ever shown
nothing because you are skinned. You
ain't got nothing but YouTube and being
a keyboard warrior every day because you
are skint. Skin is your middle name.
That's why you come on YouTube every day
calling other people skin because skin
is your middle name. Let's talk about
what you people do on here every [ __ ]
day sat on YouTube. No lie, no misses,
no money, nothing but a [ __ ]
keyboard. Am I lying? No. No, I'm not
lying. It's the truth, bro. Yeah.
can't win with these mongos. I swear to
God, you can't win with these mongos,
lad. Yeah, he is live. I swear to God,
bro. You know what? Yeah. Every single
time you argue with them, I swear you
get brain damage. I swear you actually
get [ __ ] brain damage, bro. I swear
you get like short-term brain damage.
They're absolute [ __ ] mongos. PJ will
never have over a grand. They don't even
know what I have. This is all
self-reflecting. This is why I stay away
from I try to stay away from these
channels, bro. Because it's just
40-year-old skinned people that talk
about themselves. 40y old people that
ain't got nothing self-projecting on
YouTube every day. It's pointless. Yeah.
This is why I don't go on Law J's, but
[ __ ] Timmy always dragged me into it.
Listen. Right. I'm going to end it like
this. These people, uh, I'll link you
his channel. These people have been
showing money a million times and they
all run away. They're always going to
say that you're skinn cuz they're
talking about themselves. They are the
skinn ones sat on YouTube every day. You
know, [ __ ] how many times you have to
keep showing these people money for them
to keep running away. Yeah. What it is
with these angry skinned gamblers is
they got nothing in their life. This is
why they're trying to drag down other
people with them. They're sat on
YouTube. They ain't got no money at all.
that they're trying to talk about other
[ __ ] people every [ __ ] day. It's a
waste of time, bro. You go back on this
channel and you're getting a hard on
over 13,000. It ain't even that much.
Okay, bro. If you you know what I'm
saying? It's not even it's not even a
lot of money. But I would actually go as
far as actually saying that. But it's
just it's just a waste of time on this.
I'm coming off this community, bro.
There's no point with these people.
They're actually giving me brain damage.
They're so disabled. They're actually I
swear to God, bro. They're giving me
brain damage. I swear to God, bro.
They're not even bothering me. They're
actually making me feel [ __ ]
It's actually I swear to God, bro. It's weird. Weirdos.
£13,000 is not a million. He's not rich.
He ain't got no money. Why would I want
to be jealous of somebody that don't
even have a bed? Somebody that can only
get disabled girls? Somebody that ain't
got no teeth? What? Because they've
shown what? 3, four months money in
London. Wow, bro. Who's the one that
keeps bringing it up? Not me. I'm not
jealous of of a tiny £13,000. That would
buy you what? Just about a secondhand
car. That is no big money. Let's
actually, bro, do you know people that
are actually to be jealous of?
Millionaires. Actual millionaire. Not a
small tiny £13,000.
That ain't really any money at all. Like
actual millionaires, bro. Yeah. Let him
come, bro. Let him come with Mike and
I'll smash them both up.
Like Cory, like, bro, listen. Why would
I be jealous of somebody in a bedsit
with no teeth that can only get a
disabled girl? What? Because they've
shown £13,000, bro. That's not a lot of
money. Everyone knows that, bro.
And no matter what you say or what you
do, you're just wasting your time
explaining it to these people, bro. They
clearly ain't got nothing in their
[ __ ] life every day on there doing
this [ __ ] Just leave them to it, bro. I
can't be bothered.
>> And but you know what is entertaining is
they talk like they know people, bro.
They don't know nothing.
These ugly 40year-old mongos don't know
nothing. These their skin on YouTube
every day. I'll never have over a grand
again. Bro, I've got well over a grand
and I'm not showing you nothing. So you
can keep saying that people are skin cuz
you're skin. You can keep looking in
your bank account and seeing nothing and
calling other people what you are.
That's what they do. They look in their
bank account, see they've got no money,
and then take out on other people. Bro,
how many years have they been doing this
now, bro? Come on.
They're sat on YouTube, ain't got no
money, trying to talk about other
people. And yes, they've got no [ __ ]
money cuz they don't look they ain't got
no [ __ ] money, you know?
They want people to show them money.
Yeah. For them to run away again and the
self projection continues again. Same
thing with this L J. They ain't got no
money. They're sat on YouTube. They are
skint. I don't know how many times you
have to say it to these people, bro.
They call you skin cuz skin is their
middle name. Their life is being skinned
every single day of every month.
You know what I'm saying, bro? They call
people skin because they're skint sat
there with nothing. They've got nothing,
bro. Not a pot to piss in. You understand, lad? Yeah.
Shout on YouTube every day. But they've
got all this money and everyone else's
skin. I didn't come on here until late today, bro.
I was watching [ __ ] money. I didn't
come on here till late, lad.
Yeah, LJ, you are skin. That's why you
can't show no money. Cuz you are skin.
Skin is you. That's why you and your
little disabled followers call people
skint every day. Because you are the
ones that are skinned. And every time
you look in your bank account, you see
zero. Because you are skint. It took you
12 [ __ ] years to afford Vegas.
There's nothing not skin about you,
mate. You might be able to pull the wool
over other people's eyes. Yeah, but you
ain't got no money. Just because you buy
a [ __ ] shitty pair of trainers, you
ain't got no money. So, I don't know why
you keep talking about other people when
you're sat there with nothing, begging
on YouTube. Ain't got no money to show
anyone. Listen. Listen, Cory. When was
the last time this LJ showed money? When
was the last time this Timmy showed
money? When was the last time all of
these people have shown money for how
long? What? Go on. Answer the question.
Exactly. Because they ain't got no
money. They ain't got nothing. They're
sat on YouTube skin 40. No hope, no
life. Takes out on everyone else that
they've got no money. They take out on
everyone else, bro, because they're all
skint. And bro, £13,000 in 2 years is
skint at 30 years of age. Yes, it is. If
you look at the average person, lad.
Yeah. £13,000 is not a life-changing
amount of money. How much is a life
change a life um
changing amount of money to you?
250 200 £13,000 is laughable, bro. It's
nothing. You wouldn't even plan to even
rob that amount of money, bro. If you
see someone on the floor, bro, you're
going to take that money. It's literally
no money at all what these people are
showing. I don't understand the whole
point of it.
You know what I'm saying? They literally
have nothing and and they're talking
about other people. It's a madness, bro.
They're showing, bro. They're There's
actual millionaires out there, lad.
They're actual millionaires. This little
bum change that bomb is showing that
won't even last 3 months. And this silly
[ __ ] Mickey Mouse £13,000. And bro,
do you know how I know this stuff, um,
Cory? Because I've had this sort of
money. And bro, it does not last long in London.
You know, anyone would think these
people are [ __ ] millionaire and it's
literally no money at all.
You know, can they show Can they show
the same amount of money in two months? No.
I'm coming off this disabled community
anyways, Cory. Bro, they it does my
brain in. They're so [ __ ] disabled.
It's unbelievable, bro. I swear down,
bro. They they they make you develop brain damage.
What? Bro, does anyone even put gambling
videos up anymore?
The £13,000 is making me go insane. No,
it ain't because it's no money at all.
It's nothing. It's funny. It's funny how
you keep going on like it's a big amount
of money. It's literally nothing.
It is literally [ __ ] all in the scheme
of things. It is literally [ __ ] all.
You'd barely even be able to start a
business with that amount of money. Why
would some little skint [ __ ] in a virgin
bed suit with no bed that ain't had no
life experience? And think about this,
Cory. Yeah, think about what Timmy was
saying. Yeah, think about what Timmy was
saying, bro. Sat indoors saving for two,
three years. Yeah, some people do save
for two, three years. What was I doing
in them two, three years? Getting women
wish you could designer clothes, more
life experiences, not stuck in a bedsit
with only £13,000 to my name. Do you
understand, bro? But again, they're
biased. So they're going to act like
it's a million pounds. They're going to
act like it's a million pounds when we
all know it's literally nothing. It's
actually about three months people. It's
actually some free mocks people's wages,
lad. It's literally know some people
London. It's about three months wages.
Yep. About It's not a lifechanging
amount of money, but I'm coming off this
[ __ ] anyway soon, Cory bro. Cuz these
people make me develop [ __ ] brain
damage, lad. They're so disabled. I
swear arguing with them, bro, it make I
swear to God it makes you lose brain
cells. They're so disabled. I swear to
God, bro, they actually are.
Why do you think I never go on large J?
Cuz it's just the same 40year-olds that
ain't got a life. That's why I don't go
on it, bro.
None of these people have got nothing.
They're all [ __ ] 40-year-old munters
that ain't got no life, ain't got no
money. That's why they come here and
call other people that they don't know.
Think about it, Cory. Yeah. If these
people had [ __ ] money and they
weren't muners, do you think they'd come
online calling people every day that
they don't know? Think about, bro, think
about for a second what these people do.
They like to try to talk about other
people's lives that's got a better life
than them. Yeah. They're the ones that
are sat on the internet talking about
people that they don't [ __ ] know.
Yeah. Yeah, bro. Cuz they make you lose
brain cells. They're [ __ ] so
disabled, bro. They literally argue with
these people make you [ __ ] Bro,
they're not even winding me up. They're
so disabled that bro, they give you
brain damage. I swear to God, bro,
they're so [ __ ] disabled. Arguing
with these people where it makes you
lose brain cells. I swear to God.
Just repeating yourself cuz it's a disabled community.
You know how many times I have shown you
people money. Every time you get show
money, you all run away because you are
the ones with no money. I don't know how
many times you have to explain to these
disabled people that.
No, it's just this [ __ ] stupid
[ __ ] Timmy. Why don't you stop? Why
don't all of you shut us up? Listen, do
you like what I said in the video? Why
don't you people shut me up and show us
your money and show us your misses? Huh?
You always want people to show you money
so you can keep running away, Timmy. Why
don't you people start shutting us up
like Jimmy Jazz and all of these people
that are scared to join the panel? Why
don't you start shutting us up at the
money game? Why don't you start showing
your women? Why don't you start [ __ ]
showing your [ __ ] women, bro? No one
cares about 13 bags. It's nothing. It's
literally no money at all in the scheme
of things. For [ __ ] sake, it's madness.
But again, you're biased, so I don't
even know why I'm even wasting my time
explaining anything cuz you're all
biased. So, I don't even know why I'm
even wasting my time. But I'll put the
link up, you know?
Like, you got to understand these people
are jealous of me. This is why they go
for me every single day cuz they hate
the fact that I'm better looking. I've
got, you know, it's not even really
about [ __ ] money. So, they're always
going to do this. This is never ever
going to stop, lads. They can keep
pretending £13,000 is a million pounds
and keep pretending that I've not showed
anything. Bro, they're never going to
stop doing that. Why should I have to
show these skinned people money again,
bro? Why do I have to show these skinned
people money again and again and again
and again and again and again and again?
Every time they get show money, they run
away. Like, does anyone not have a brain
and understand that? You know, they're
skin. So they self- project their
skintess onto you just like [ __ ]
Timmy Eldridge, just like Nons. And yes,
13 grand is skint considering you've got
no life experience in 3 4 years. Yes,
that is skint.
Yes, it's about 3 months people's wages.
They're [ __ ] all idiots suicide. I'm
coming off this [ __ ] soon, bro. They're
actually making me develop brain damage.
[ __ ] I'm actually coming off this [ __ ]
lad. I swear to God I am, bro. I'm just
going to stick to Reddit. I think at
least you could actually get more sense
out of people.
Do you know what I'm saying, bro? He's
This guy is a [ __ ] [ __ ] It's
Timmy. Every time this guy gets show
money, he runs away.
Yeah, I don't have 1K. You don't know
how much I have. So, keep guessing.
Keep guessing. You don't know what I
have. And this is exactly why I'm coming
off of this community because of what
it's weird what you people do every day,
bro. They're [ __ ] Mongols.
I'm not fighting any of you people. I'm
not wasting my time on any of you
[ __ ] people. You're clearly disabled.
The fact that you can come on here every
[ __ ] day and create the same. You're
just 40y old losers that ain't got
nothing going for yourselves. That's all
it is. This is why you do this every day,
you know? Like it's it's [ __ ] a
madness, bro. No, no, no, no, no. It
doesn't wind me up. Do you know what
what what winds me up, Sean? Is arguing
with disabled people is disabled people
that are jealous every single day.
Jealousy every single day of me every
single [ __ ] day. You know what I'm
saying? They do all of this stuff cuz
they're [ __ ] jealous, bro. They could
have all the money in the world, but
they're fat and ugly and their life's
losers. They're sat on YouTube every day
calling people that they don't [ __ ] know.
[ __ ] bomb. He ain't got nothing. And
then few thousand pounds is nothing. At
your age, you should be retired, bro. In
the 100,000s. This money that they're
showing is peanuts.
It literally is, bro.
Know what I mean, lad? It's a madness.
But yeah, I'm coming off this [ __ ] bro. 100.
You can get more sense out of stubbling
in [ __ ] Finland than these people.
You know what I'm saying? Seaside dark, bro.
Bro, I got more going on than you 40
year olds calling people on YouTube that
you don't know every day. Yet everyone
else is the skinned ones. Look at your
own lives, bro. You're sat on YouTube
calling people that you don't [ __ ]
know every [ __ ] day cuz you ain't got
no life and you ain't got no money.
That's why you start on people younger
than you because you want to take it out
that take it out on people that you are
the ones with no money and you are the
ones with no life. Angry gamblers. You
know what I'm saying? You want to take
it out on people that your skin and your
life sucks. That's why you do all of
this [ __ ] every day. Like nons showing [ __ ] £13,000.
It's no money. It's not in the millions.
Do you have to understand? You're
talking to someone like me. Yeah. And at
the end of the day, bro, 3 years, you
should have more than epoxy 13 grand.
You know, obviously I know that
obviously people got staying and saying,
"Why do you think he's still a virgin
that's never had his leg over?" Because
he's not had the money to go out
and that's why he's still a virgin like
Virgin Timmy. They're both They're both
virgins. They got on.
13 grand is not nice. It's not even
life-changing money. And mate, if I did
not go out for three years, I'd want
more than 13 [ __ ] grand. You know,
I'd want more than 13 grand. It's no
money at all.
It's no money at all. You're not a
millionaire. You know, at the end of the
day, you need to look at people's
lifestyle. Who's got the designer
clothes? Who's gone out drinking? I've
been not sat in a bed sit with only 13
grand to my name. That is, bro, I save I
could save honestly about three grand in
a month if I wanted to.
That is no money, bro, for wasting your life away.
No, it's not more than You don't know
what I have. You don't know what I have.
You don't know nothing about me. You
don't know what I have. I've got more
than you people will ever have. Youth,
better looking, more women. Something
that you little clowns don't have. Sat
on YouTube with no money, crying over 13
grand when it is literally nothing.
You know, I've got a date Saturday if I
even want to go on it to be honest, bro.
I can go on this date with this woman on
Saturday. Do you know that one I met a
few weeks ago? I can't be bothered, bro.
Cuz I can't be [ __ ] you know?
You know what's even more [ __ ] Being in
a shitty little bed sit with no bed with
no teeth with a disabled girlfriend
shoving £13,000 off like you're a
millionaire. Like you're you're talking
to someone like me, bro. I know what
money comes in and what money goes.
Yeah. And £13,000 does not make you even
the slightest bits better off than
anyone. It's nothing literally. But like
I said, we are we all know why you go on
like it is. It's because the person
who's showing it. It's obvious. Yeah,
obviously it makes sense because obviously it's
it's the person who's showing it.
Obviously, it's not the 13 grand.
Um, I can beat that 13 grand, but I'm
not going to waste my time with you
people anymore. And the fact that it
took two years to show it screams skin.
The fact that it took two years to show
epoxy 13 grand and you act like you're a
millionaire, it just screams skin. Cuz I
literally I literally, bro, yeah, for
you to have wasted your life for 3 years
and you've only got 13 grand. 13 grand is nothing.
That literally, bro, she's like, "Bro,
listen. Listen. You got to understand.
Yeah, I think you're unbiased at Yep.
You can keep calling yourself skin. No
one cares. You are skin. That's why you
bring up money every single day.
Yeah. You You talk about skin every
single day because you are skin. That's
why you know it takes one to no one.
Because you are skin. You call people
skin cuz you're the skin 40year-olds
with no life. Think of it seaside dark.
Yeah. Is that amount of money worth 3
years of having no life? Seaside dark.
Ask yourself this question, bro. Is that
worth it for having 3 years of no life?
No, no women, only disabled birds, no
bed, no nice restaurants, no designer
clothes, sat in a in a bedsit with only
30 grand to your name. Do you really
think that's worth three years of your life?
You know what I'm saying?
You don't know how much I get skin bomb
with your little couple of thousand
pounds thinking that you got I want to
actually see big money, bro. I want to
actually see big money. And no, this is
not big money. See dog, what these
people are showing.
None of this is big money. None of this
is big money at all.
It's literally nothing. But they think
they're millionaires. It's literally nothing.
I'm not asked about money. These people
are the ones that keep bringing it up.
Sad, I don't know how long you've been
following me. Yeah. But have you not
seen what I have done in 3 years?
Have you literally not seen what I've
done in three years?
Have you not seen what I've done in
three years, bro? I haven't been sat in
a bed sit with a [ __ ] disabled girl.
You know, all of these cities, you can
cross them that I've already been to,
lad. You understand? Even though I know
it's not a real seat, do you know what I mean?
They go on like they're millionaires
when in reality they've got [ __ ] all.
I think they've got this I think they've
got this um this disability that gets
them confused with other people.
I think it is, bro. It's like they they
have this disability that gets them
confused with other people.
Their skin every day on YouTube trying
to call other people that they don't
know. Go and live your life. You've got
all of this money. See, do you really
think if these people had money, they
would be on here every day doing what
they do? You know, I'm planning to get
off this [ __ ] soon, bro. I need to go to
do this [ __ ] in Finland.
I might go out meet this. You really
think if they had all this money in all
this life, they'd be sat on YouTube
calling people they don't know every
day? Calling people that they don't know
every day? That's That's something what
a skinned person would do. That is
something what a skinned person would do.
And that's why my video got three thumbs
up, lads. I've gone out. I've enjoyed
money. I've lived life. You know what
I'm saying? 3 years of doing nothing is
not worth £13,000.
Traveled up and down the country. I've
been abroad. Bro, listen. Let me ask you
something. Let me tell you something.
Listen up. If somebody truly had money
like him, do you think they would be sat
in a bed sit with no bed, no designer
clothes, no holiday, no nothing? Do you
really think somebody with money lives
like that? Let me let me ask you the
question. You know, obviously there is
Well, no. Like the thing is, lad, like
not everyone likes designer clothes.
Okay. Yeah. Not everyone likes designer
clothes, but then some people like
traveling or some people like this or
some people want assets. Do you really
think somebody that's got all of this
money would sit on YouTube, right, all
day in a bedsit, no life? it. People
with money would do that, bro.
Like, he ain't got money. I don't know
why he goes on like he's got money. He
ain't got some money. Cuz why have I
lived a better life? Why have I Why have
I lived a better life in 3 years if I
would have gone that skin? And the only
reason I don't go out much anymore, see,
is cuz I can't be bothered. It's cuz I
genuinely can't be [ __ ]
I'm [ __ ] 28 next month. Like been
there, done it, worn the [ __ ] t-shirt,
you know, I'm not s there all day every
day. And yeah, Red's okay. But the
difference is I'm not like you little 40 year olds,
you know? I'm not like you little
40year-olds sat on YouTube hating your
life away because you are the ones that
asking. That's why you do this every day
because you are the angry 40year-old
with no money and you take out on other
people that you ain't got to [ __ ] all.
That's why you go on about the word.
That's why you go on about skin so much
cuz it's what you see in your bank
account. A big zero. That's why you talk
about everyone else. Well, you try to
talk about everyone else because you
ain't got nothing.
What the [ __ ] have you been doing in
[ __ ] What have you been doing in
three, four years? What have you been
doing in three, four [ __ ] years?
Oh, the link. Yeah. Sorry, bro. What
have you been doing in three, four years?
[ __ ] sat on YouTube. No life. [ __ ]
calling other people that you don't know
skin. You can't even come on here and be
normal. You know what I'm saying?
We get it, bro. You We understand, Dad.
Yeah. He said he's left YouTube. Like,
you can't even come here and be normal.
Can't even be [ __ ] normal, bro.
Put nude up or something.
How you doing, matey?
>> Good. You
>> I'm good, thanks.
You miss you.
>> How long is it before you kick me? >> Huh?
>> I don't know who you are.
>> Are you sure?
>> Definitely. Yeah.
>> I bet I can make you remember. >> No.
Don't you remember saying sorry to me?
>> Oh, you still being a keyboard warrior.
I was going to say, Prime, hey, Prime,
listen. I was in Birmingham last month
and you was nowhere to be seen. You
can't even use it anymore.
>> You're going to kick me now, aren't you?
>> No, no, I'm not going to kick you at
all. I'm just saying that I was in your
I was in Birmingham last month and you
was nowhere to be seen. And I And if you
remember, I specifically said I'm in
your city and you're not going to move
me. And what did you do? You shut it.
So, mate, I'll give up now.
>> No, no, no. I didn't.
>> Yes. Yes. Yes. I was with Monty. Don't
you remember? I was with Monty and you
was nowhere to be seen. Just like Timmy
was nowhere to be seen and he was
actually on the chat. Isn't that funny?
>> Yeah. Listen, I don't care. You can do
what you want when you want. Just like I can do.
>> So, why didn't you come out then?
>> Why didn't I come out? I wasn't in the area, mate.
>> Oh, you wasn't in the area. Really?
Where was you?
>> I can't even remember the day, mate. You know.
>> Oh, cool. Shard.
>> Of course. Like, listen.
>> You're full of [ __ ] Is that why it took
you over a month to come back on YouTube?
>> It took me over No. What do you mean?
>> It took you over a month to come back on YouTube.
>> I'm I'm on and off here. Like, you know,
I'm off for a week, 3 weeks. Depends how
busy I am.
>> Okay. So, what do you want to What do
you want to talk about? You going to
come to London so I can smash you in or
>> smash me in? Okay. >> Yeah.
Do you reckon you stand a chance?
>> 100%. I will meet you anywhere in London
if you want to come back
>> by myself. So it's fair. Yeah.
>> You you seriously reckon you stand a chance? >> 100%.
>> So if you stood a chance, why didn't you
do it last time?
>> Why did I do it last time? I was in
Birmingham last time. You didn't come out.
>> No, I'm not. Okay.
>> Again, we're not living in the past,
remember? Of course. Well, sorry. We're
not living in the past. So I shouldn't
bring out Birmingham and you should
bring Remember the past doesn't count on
here, does it? So sorry about that. But
forget the Birmingham thing and forget
the the other thing because that's the
past, isn't it?
>> Who says the past doesn't count? Like I'm
>> Well, you all say the past doesn't count
when you've been open the money game. So
the past don't count, does it?
>> You all like I'm not you all. I'm me.
>> Wait, so wait, so the past does count then?
>> Everybody has their own opinions and
they're entitled to their own opinions.
>> So So the past does count then? >> Yeah.
>> Okay. So when it So So it counts when it suits yourelves.
>> Okay. When it suits yourselves. So when
it suits yourselves,
>> it counts.
>> What you on about? So what you getting
at? I don't understand. Like when I've
shown six grand and I made you all run away.
>> Who run away?
>> You run away and everyone on here run away.
>> I've shown you more than six grand, mate.
>> No, you have not. You [ __ ] have not.
>> How much,
>> bro? You have not. You have not showed
me more than that.
>> So, the video that Lord J put up some
time ago with PJ Skint in 50 notes with
>> It wasn't 50 pound notes, it was 20
pound notes. So, that was
>> not with 50 pound in the background. It
was that was not more than six grand.
>> That was That That was seven grand, mate.
>> That was not more than six grand, mate.
>> That was That was seven grand.
>> Yeah, of course it was. Yeah, of course
>> It was. I know it was.
>> I know.
>> So, they want to meet in London.
>> Listen, I'm not going to London for a bit, mate. >> Why?
>> Because it's a long way.
>> You're in Birmingham. It's only [ __ ]
an hour and a half.
>> It's not far. Oh, I went there last
month. You didn't show up. Yeah, but
when you got a busy schedule like me.
>> Nah, you don't have a busy I'm sure you
can fit time in.
>> Yeah, but look, it's pointless telling
you what to do and stuff cuz you just won't
>> Listen, I How about this? Right. I'll
give you my number and when you're back
in London, you can contact me. How about that?
>> Listen, when I
>> I'll [ __ ] you up, huh?
>> Yeah. Listen, when I want to see you
again, I will see you again.
>> Keyboard warrior.
>> Keyboard warrior. I'm trying to arrange
something and you're not having it.
>> Why am I a keyboard warrior? Can you explain?
>> Because you will you know you're not
going to see me when you see me. How is
that doesn't even make any sense?
>> Why aren't I?
>> Because you don't know where I am. You
don't know where I live. You don't know
where I go. You silly goose.
>> Well, you don't know where I live and
you don't know where I go.
>> Yeah, that's why I'm trying to arrange
to meet you. >> Listen,
>> you [ __ ] spazz.
>> Did we have Have we met before?
>> Have we met before? Yeah, but you're not
going to I'm you're not going to make me
meet you again, you idiot.
>> Trust me.
>> Trust me, you won't.
>> Trust me. Like, listen. >> Okay.
>> I will be where I will be. You will be
where you will be.
>> So, you're just being a keyboard warrior.
>> How am I being a keyboard warrior?
>> Because I'm trying to meet you and
you're talking nonsense.
>> Listen, I'm a busy man and the day I
want to meet you again, I will meet you again. >> Okay.
>> And and then you can do what you say
you're going to do.
Yeah, I will do. Yeah.
>> [ __ ] virgin boy. You need to get laid, man.
>> How am I a virgin?
>> I'm not talking about you. I'm not >> Okay.
>> But anyways, I want to meet you anyways.
>> Yeah, of course. It will happen.
>> Come to London.
>> Why have I got to come to London? Come to Birmingham.
>> Because I went to Birmingham. You didn't come out.
>> I wasn't there, mate. I was I wasn't
>> mate. You was there. Stop talking. Okay.
So, where exactly were you then?
>> I could have been anywhere. I'll get around, mate.
>> Well, where Well, where was you then?
>> I could have been anywhere. I don't know.
>> Exactly. Cuz you're [ __ ] a [ __ ]
house. So, shut up then. You're a [ __ ] house, bro. >> How?
>> Cuz I was in your city. I wanted part
two, bro. I was in your city and I
wanted you to move me.
>> You was in my face and you didn't move.
>> I was in your city. No, no, but this
time I was in your actual city.
>> Yeah, but you was in my
>> And you done nothing. This weren't
reading. I was in your city, bro. And do
you know the only reason I called you
out? Do you know why I called you out?
Not the fact that you live there, right?
Or the fact that you had to meet me.
It's the fact that you kept coming on
and talking [ __ ] and talking [ __ ] So,
it's like you wanted part two. So, I
thought I'll give you part two and you
didn't and you didn't want it. >> Listen,
>> cuz you know, if you never done this, I
wouldn't have called you out. I would
have been, "Oh, you left YouTube. It's
whatever. There's no there's nothing
now." But you you [ __ ] yourself up
because you come here acted like a big
man. Then when someone was in your city,
you was nowhere to be seen. I gave
ridiculous opportunity to be someone on
this community. You could have smashed
my face in a big man. You could when the
time the time I grabbed you, you could
have turned around, smashed me
>> and beat me up, laid me on the floor.
You could have bought my face all over the internet.
>> You could have embarrassed me and you
could have actually got some credit on here.
Yeah, but you Yeah, but you Yeah, but
the thing is you know you've done
nothing which is why you keep coming on
talking about meeting again because you
know you've done nothing.
>> Okay. I did what I wanted to do
>> because you would just leave and just
stop coming back.
>> Do you want the truth? Do you want the
>> It's funny. Yeah.
>> Do you know what stopped me from
smashing your face in that day? The honest truth
>> is because you're proper disabled.
>> Oh, really? Have you? Oh, really?
>> I did not want to smash you because you
were proper disabled.
>> You didn't smash me because you shot
yourself. That's why you shot yourself,
didn't it? Listen, and I even said to
other people, I says, "Look, I couldn't
smash him." Like,
>> if I was disabled, if that was if that
was the real reason, you wouldn't even
met me and grabbed me.
>> Bigger than what you are. I have one hand.
>> Yeah. And I will meet you now. And I
>> And I'm bigger than And I'm bigger than
you now. So,
>> you think you are?
>> I know I am. I know I am.
>> The simple fact is, yeah, I couldn't hit
you that day because you look you you're
you're so disabled. You honestly are.
>> Have you Have you seen Have you seen your face?
>> Listen, don't I don't care about my face.
>> You know, listen listen. If I was
disabled, you would I don't care about
my face. I have a happy life and I'm happy.
>> Okay. I don't care about my face. If my
face is the meaniest face in the world,
I really couldn't give a toss. Yeah. >> Okay.
>> I really couldn't give a toss. As long
as my wife is happy and my kids are
happy, that's all that matters to me.
Yeah. So, it doesn't really care what
other people think and I don't care what
other people think. So, do do you want round two?
>> Listen, if I want round two, we will
have round two. Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, you don't actually want to
meet, you just want to be a keyboard or
>> listen, I might just meet you again just
to see if you're going to try and smash
my face in this time because
>> I will smash your face.
>> If you did try and swing at me, you'd be
on the floor.
>> Yeah, we'll see about that. Won't you big man?
>> There's a reason why
>> put your money where your mouth is and
come to London today.
>> Listen, there's a reason why I couldn't
do it last time, and that's because
you're proper disabled.
>> Yeah, I'm proper disabled. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'm proper disabled, bro.
>> But you know you are. You got a disability.
>> So then if I'm disabled, if I'm
disabled, why do you keep coming on
here? Do you want to meet again or
>> I'll just come here just cuz I like the entertainment, mate.
>> Okay, mate. So listen, do you want to do
you want to meet on Saturday?
>> No, I'm busy on Saturday, mate.
>> Do you want to meet on Friday?
>> Uh, no. I've got work.
>> See? Excuses. Excuse excuses. Excuses.
Listen, listen. How much do you get
paid? How much do you get paid a day for work? Roughly
>> a day? >> Yeah,
>> it depends where I'm working.
>> Like roughly? Can you give like an estimate?
>> Because uh it probably ranges from the
low end I would say 180 a day, but it
could go up to like 280 depending on the location.
>> Okay, how about this? Right, you you
come here and I will give you I will
give you the £500, right? That will see
you that will see you through and I'll
smash your face in. How about that one?
So, what am I meant to do with all the
jobs that I've got lined up, mate?
>> Yeah, you just go to It's only one day.
You just skip one and then I'll give you
the £500, right? Yeah.
>> For that for that day and then you can carry on.
>> Yeah. But it doesn't work like that.
>> If I work, I'll lose reputation. I'll
lose business. I'll lose customers.
Like, it doesn't work like that.
>> Listen. Okay. What What time do you
start your job?
>> Again, it depends where I'm working.
>> Okay. So, on Saturday.
>> On Saturday. Um, oh no, I never said I
was working on Saturday. I said I was
busy on Saturday.
>> So, what are you busy doing?
>> Things, mate. Family things, you know.
>> You know, so you never actually want to
meet anyone. You're just full of it. I I
just told you I'll give you £500. That
was that that's that's more than [ __ ]
enough, you know.
>> I tell you what, now you come.
>> I'll pay for your petrol. I'll pay more
than your work. I'm prepared to give you the money.
>> Okay. What area are you in in London?
>> What do you mean what? No, just come to
London and I'll meet you.
>> Do you want Okay,
>> I'll tell you what then. I might have a
proposition. So, okay. What What's your
plan on uh say Monday?
>> Monday I'm free.
>> Okay. All right then.
>> I I I might pop into London on Monday cuz
>> Pop London. I'll meet you anywhere you
want me to meet you.
>> I'm actually working quite close in
London on Monday. >> Reen?
>> No. Closer.
>> Middlesbrough. No, closer >> Scotland.
>> No, closer to London.
>> Uh, slow
>> to London. No, >> slow. >> No, >> Essex.
>> Crystal Palace area.
>> Okay. Yeah, that's good enough. That's
near where the Virgin lives. So, you
want me to meet you there? I can meet
you there. That's not a problem.
>> We'll sort something out. Don't worry. I'll
>> Yeah, 100%. 100%. Yeah,
>> I'll be I'll be back in touch.
>> And I'll come and smash your [ __ ]
face in you, you little [ __ ] And I'm
going to rub you as well. And I'm gonna
rob you as well. And I'm gonna rob you
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> You're lucky you didn't come out that
day in Birmingham. You know that. You're
so lucky. You would have got [ __ ] up.
Oh my god. You would have got [ __ ] up.
>> And no one believes that you wasn't
there either. You was there.
>> You You will not smash my face in.
>> We'll see you on Monday then, won't we?
Listen, listen, listen. I will beat you
no matter what it takes. Believe that. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Of course.
>> Yeah. 100%. Well, no matter what it
takes, I will beat you.
>> Yeah. Of course. Of course you will.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> I'm going to take your [ __ ] phone as
well, you silly. I'm going to degrade
you so badly. It's going to be on the internet forever.
>> Oh, can't wait.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Good.
>> So, Monday? Yeah.
>> Yeah. We'll sort something out.
>> I'll be live on Monday anyways. So, you
can join anytime you want.
>> Yeah, that's not a problem. I will join
and we can uh we can arrange something.
Not a problem at all.
>> It's true though, isn't it? >> What?
>> What's true? you know, I'm going to see
you and put your face in.
>> If you want to think that, then think
>> you know,
>> it's it's completely up to you. You can
think what you want to think. But the
true fact of what will happen, we'll
find out on the day, won't we? >> Yeah.
>> That's fine.
>> You don't get bored of working. >> No. >> Why?
>> Why? Why would I get bored of working?
>> You know, getting up from your comfy bed every morning. >> No. What up?
>> Because it's the satisfaction of
providing for my family and my kids, you
know, and I enjoy what I do, so you get
the satisfaction out of it.
>> Yeah, but you have to drive quite far
away, don't you?
>> Yeah. What difference does that make? I
get paid mileage as well, so what
difference does it make? The further the better.
>> Well, you can you can literally go
everywhere. You like you can be called out anywhere.
>> Yeah. The further the better.
>> Yeah. Obvious. Well, yeah, obviously.
But I can't wait to see you Monday.
>> That's fine then. It's not a problem.
>> Have you ever Have you ever done a job in Middlesbrough? >> No.
>> I've been to Middlesbrough a few times, though.
>> Yeah. I thought you belong
Middlesbrough. Is it?
>> Why? Why do I belong in Middlesbrough?
>> Cuz it's a [ __ ] aren't it?
>> Listen, there's plenty of places around
this country. When I meet and when I
meet you when I meet you on Monday, I'm
going to say I take the apology back and
I'm and I'm going to say sorry to no
one. I'm going to say the only thing I'm
sorry for is kicking your ass.
>> You reckon?
>> Yeah, 100%.
>> one punch will be on the floor.
>> You reckon?
>> You got to understand you're an old man, you know.
>> I'm an old man. Okay. Of course. Of
course I'm an old man. >> Yeah.
>> So if if I was an old man, why don't you
do something about it before? Why? Well,
you didn't even do any I tried to do
something about it on Birm in Birmingham.
>> But why didn't you do something about it
when you was in my face?
>> Well, why didn't you do anything?
>> Because I told that Huh?
>> I felt bad for you.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. Excuse it.
>> Well, how's it excuses?
>> What's his excuses? It
>> It's true.
>> So, you What would have you What would
What was your plan to do then?
>> Well, originally my plan was to kick the
[ __ ] out of you.
I was I I was going to grab you. I was gonna
>> I was going to grab you and then push
you up there and then beat you up.
>> What? For how long?
>> Till I felt happy.
>> Oh, really? Well, you can do that on
Monday. Is it?
>> But then I realized how bad you was h
wobbling down the street to me and
having no idea who I was. Yeah,
>> it was Wasn't it funny how you asked me
where the pub was as well that we was
meant to be meeting? Wasn't it funny how it all
>> it all just happened and it just all
came together and
>> Yeah, it was funny, isn't it?
>> Yeah, it was.
>> You love me, don't you?
>> PJ, don't start.
>> You do, don't you?
>> I don't.
>> Listen, listen. I mean,
you'll be on the floor if you meet me on Monday.
>> Well, we'll see about that, won't we? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, we'll see about that.
>> The simple fact is that you could have
done something when you was in my face.
When you was in my
>> You were too busy shaking and sh and saying,
>> Yeah, but and so could have you. You
could have done something as well, but
you never. So, the same thing goes to I
didn't want to because I realized how
disabled you actually was.
>> Okay. Okay. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Fair. Of course. But do you think that
excuse would wash with anyone else? It wouldn't.
>> Well, anybody else would have been
swinging at me, mate.
>> You know what I'm saying? Like, no. But
you saying that you never hit me cuz I'm
disabled. That would never wash with
anyone else. You know, it doesn't wash.
>> Well, anybody else would have been swinging,
>> you know?
>> Who who who wouldn't be swinging at that
scenario when you get grabbed? You tell
>> you tell me who wouldn't swing.
What didn't? Well, I know I'm saying you
struck. You didn't swing.
>> Yeah, but I grabbed you, the person.
>> Yeah, it Yeah. So, so you had a chance
to hit me
>> cuz that was your plan. So, you can't
say, "Oh, because you were disabled, I
didn't." That doesn't wash.
>> Why, doesn't it?
>> Because it just doesn't. >> Well,
why didn't you swing? >> Huh?
>> Why didn't you swing to me?
>> Because I didn't.
>> I'm not the one making excuses.
>> You caught me off guard. I mean, you
caught me off guard. I mean, that's that.
>> I haven't heard that.
>> You caught me off guard.
>> Yeah. So, why didn't you swing? So, if
anybody grabs you, what you going to do?
You're just going to Oh, so you caught
me off guard.
>> No, obviously not. But you did catch me off guard.
>> So, what happens when I grab you Monday?
>> You're not going to grab me Monday.
>> What do you mean?
>> You're not going to grab me. You're not
even going to put your hands on me.
>> How do you know?
>> You're not even going to get You know
what I mean? I might I might send you to
a location and then before you know it,
grab you before you get to the
>> No, because I'm very I'm very alert, you know.
>> Oh, you're very alert because it's happening before.
>> All right. Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, how do you know it's not going
to happen again? Someone's going to
>> Because it's not going to happen again.
>> How do you know?
>> Because I know.
>> What makes you feel?
>> Because we cuz we'll see on Monday, won't we?
>> Well, all right.
>> Yeah. Good. >> Okay.
Well, you you had your opportunity last
time, didn't you? And you didn't.
>> Well, so did you. And I had my
opportunity in Birmingham as well, and
you didn't come out. Well,
>> you was in my face
>> and I was in your face and you couldn't
even hit me. So, at the end of the day,
>> big big nose to normal nose and you did.
>> Sorry, I don't mean to interrupt, but
let's be honest, PJ, he did hit you cuz
I can replay both of you know what funny
both of you are here because you none of
you two come out last month. Is that
man? None of them come out last month.
>> You can rave and [ __ ] scream the internet.
>> They didn't come out last month in
Birmingham, did they?
>> PJ None of them come out today. Last
month, did he hit you, PJ?
>> Prime and Timmy never come out.
>> He did hit you. He did hit you. Yeah.
All right. Prime. He did hit you, PJ.
>> No, he didn't hit me.
>> Yes, he did.
>> Timmy, you didn't even come out last
month. You didn't even come out last
>> PJ, we're not [ __ ] stupid.
>> Okay, let me ask you this then. Why do
you ask people to come to Birmingham
when you don't show up? Answer it. Why
don't you answer my question?
>> No, no, no. Why didn't you show up last month?
>> No, no, no, no. Why don't you be man
enough and meet in a park and we'll business?
>> Why didn't you show up last month?
>> No, no, no. [ __ ] your excuses, PJ. Meet
us in a park and we'll mean business.
>> Jimmy, why didn't you meet me last month?
>> No, no, PJ. Canill park or a park in
London. I will meet you if I'm in the
March Saturday. You didn't come out when
I was in Birmingham.
>> I don't live on [ __ ] planet [ __ ]
world. finally be sparking.
>> I tell you what, why don't you go and
meet Timmy on Saturday and then meet?
>> Yeah, go and meet.
Listen, listen, Timmy. Okay, I will meet
you on Saturday. I will meet you on
Saturday. Why didn't you come out last
month yet, PJ? I've got to sort out.
>> Why didn't you come out last month?
>> PJ, I didn't come out last month because
one, I live [ __ ] in the suburbs of Birmingham. Like,
>> no. Excuses. Excuses. Excuses again. If
I would knock your nose off, your mom
would go, "Oh my god, her excuses. with
you, Peter. For me, it's in the park. PJes
me. No, no excuses. This guy is full of
>> No, no, no, no. Me in a part. No, no,
no. Your excuses, PJ,
>> but you both have excuses because I was
in Birmingham last month. You didn't
>> ignore it. It's obviously Middlesbrough situ.
>> See what I mean with these people?
They're [ __ ] idiots.
>> Like you in Manchester four months ago
as well. You didn't.
>> Right. Anyway, I'm going to let primone
you. But anyway, I'm It's going to be
doom day for you Monday, PJ, cuz you're
going to be drinking.
>> Oh, you've been saying Yeah, that's and
and and Saturday before Monday, you're
you're supposed to be coming to London, aren't you?
>> You've been saying you're coming to
London for [ __ ] years. This guy is a
[ __ ] [ __ ] isn't it?
>> I was in Manchester 4 months ago, mate.
Why didn't you turn up?
>> Why didn't I turn up? Uh because I don't
live in Manchester and you live in
Birmingham. I went to you live in
Birmingham. Why you turn up? I went to
Saturday. Um, December. Won't you turn up? Wemm.
>> You was where?
>> Uh, in Wembley. >> When?
>> December. Won't you turn up?
>> Did you let me know you was there?
>> When you turn up?
>> Because you didn't let me know you was
there. I let you know I was in
Birmingham. Like Timmy.
>> Did you do realize Wembley is nowhere
near me as well? You know that?
>> I was in Stratford the other day as
well. Weren't you?
>> Really? Was you? In your dreams. You
wouldn't last a minute in Strapford,
mate. You'd probably get you'd probably
get beat up. You'd get beat up by a
bunch of kids.
>> Remember Do you remember when Lord Jay
put a video up in Stratford?
>> You what? 8 what? 8:00 in the morning. Yeah.
>> No, it it was probably around 12:00 on a Friday. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, that was my video.
>> Okay. Did he say it was you? >> No.
>> I didn't tell him to.
>> I didn't.
>> So, so what was you doing in Stratford?
>> What's got to do with you,
>> mate? You're a keyboard warrior, mate.
You for more time you think.
>> If you was in Stratford, if if you was
in Stratford, you would have knew where
I live then, wouldn't you?
>> What you on about? I've been I've been
in Stratford this week as well. I'm in
Stratford quite a lot.
>> Oh, really? Are you? Okay. Okay. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Of course you are.
>> Listen, Brian, this whole [ __ ] is
not scaring me. You don't scare me one
little bit. I'm prepared to meet you anywhere.
>> All right. Well, I told you.
>> So, I'll see you Monday. So, I'll see
you Monday. Simple.
>> Yeah. I'm
>> Have you ever heard of round two?
>> Listen, I've I've seen round one.
>> Yeah. So, now we're going to have round two. >> Listen,
I've seen round one. That's all I can say. Like,
>> yeah. And you're going to see round two
as well. So,
>> and how long how long ago was how long
ago was round one?
>> Don't know. Don't care.
>> No, but how long was it?
>> I haven't got a clue, mate. I really don't care.
>> It could have been yesterday. It could
have been two years ago. It could have
been five years ago. I don't really care.
>> There you go. There you go then.
>> It makes no difference of when it was. >> Okay. Okay then. Yeah.
I'll see you Monday then. Is it? >> Yeah.
Simple. Should I tell you what I'm doing now? What?
>> I'm going for a drive.
>> Good for you.
in my nice little car, matey.
>> That's nice, man. Well, I'll see you Monday.
>> Yes, mate. I'm just going to go and
drive and cruise and enjoy the speed of life.
>> Yeah, man. Make make the most of it
because you'll be getting smashed in Monday. >> Yeah.
>> You hear the horsepowers, mate.
>> Yeah. Well, and and I'm going to take
your car with you as well.
>> Yeah, of course you are.
>> Yeah. You going to have your car with
you as well?
>> Um, no.
>> Well, I'll take I'll I'll nick the fan. So,
>> I'll nick the van.
>> No, I won't have my van with me either.
>> So, what are you going to have?
>> What do you mean, who am I going to have?
>> I said, what are you going to have?
>> What do you mean? My two legs.
>> Okay. Well, I'll see you then. Yeah, Monday.
>> Yeah, that's not a problem. As I say,
Crystal Palace, I'm sure you said you'll
be live all Monday anyway.
>> Yeah, I will.
>> I don't know what time it will be
because we've got we got a lot of work
to get done.
>> I'll be live all be live all day for you.
>> That's fine. So, I'm not going to have
no excuses. It's too late to come
somewhere cuz it might be like, you
know, 9:00ish or something.
>> Yeah, that's fine. Cuz by the time I finished,
checked into my hotel,
had food, couple of beers with my mates from work.
>> What kind of beer do you What kind of
beer do you drink?
>> I drink anything, mate. Anything I want
on the day. >> Guinness.
>> Guinness is all right, but you know.
>> Well, after I smash your head and we can
go for a beer. Uh,
>> okay. Firstly,
I won't go for a beer with you. Secondly,
>> there we go.
>> You're not going to smash my face in.
>> Okay, we'll see, won't we?
>> Yeah, we will. We will.
>> We'll see, old man.
>> Are we going to like
what what goes goes what happens happens like >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, that's fair enough. That's fine by me.
>> And you can bring whoever you want. I
love you all.
>> Yeah. Okay. Okay.
>> I love the [ __ ] all of you.
>> Yeah, that's fine. Yeah.
>> Well, I will have I will have some other
lads with me, but then they won't get
involved unless other people get
involved. So, it's not not
>> Well, there's not going to be other
people. It's just going to be me, isn't it?
>> That's fine. But, as I say, they won't
get involved anyway.
>> Yeah, that's good.
>> That's fine. Right. I'm going. I need to
go and feel some speed.
>> All right. See you Monday. Yeah.
>> See you later.
>> This guy is not about it, bro. He's just
a keyboard warrior. He knows now that
I'd smash his [ __ ] face. And yeah,
that [ __ ] happened two two and a half
years ago. No, no, no. But bro, he knows
now he'll get [ __ ] up. Him and Timmy,
I was in Birmingham. Yeah. And he
literally they were nowhere to be seen.
Nowhere to be [ __ ] seen.
You know, same [ __ ]
>> Are you going to enjoy hospital food?
>> Yeah. [ __ ] all food. You and him is
never going to beat me. BJ, least look
on the bright side. You're that skin. At
least you're gonna get free grub for a week.
>> Yeah, I'm skin. Yeah. Wait, how how much
did you say I have again? Uh uh uh Timmy,
>> three p.
>> You wish. You don't know what I have and
I love it.
>> I love you. Keep calling me skin. I love
it. Keep calling me skin. I love it.
>> Okay. You keep telling yourself that.
>> DJ, I tell you why I know your skin.
Because why you doing the old Timmy
Aldridge, which is me yourself.
>> DJ, you are skin.
>> Yeah. You've sat there all day on here
all day calling me skin. That must mean your skin.
>> That must mean your skin.
>> All you got to do is show me 20 quid and you're not
>> mate. I've shown you 1300. You run away.
I'm not playing your games anymore.
>> I don't care. I don't give a [ __ ] how
long it was. You run away. I don't want
you running away again.
>> You've lost it all on number.
>> He doesn't. Yep. You keep Do you know
what Timmy's doing? He's projecting
right now. He knows that he's the one
>> PJ PJ. What? Let's have a serious talk.
Right. Let's talk. Let's take the
internet out. Not showing you [ __ ] nothing.
>> PJ, PJ, I'm not on about showing to you.
Let's take the internet out of consideration.
>> I'm not showing you nothing.
>> PJ, I know you're [ __ ] 5 years old
and you're heavily autistic. Calm down.
>> I'm not showing you nothing, mate.
>> You haven't got anything.
>> Okay, got it. Listen, any of you people
on here yet, you can add me on SL on
Snapchat and I will show you money right
now with me talking.
>> In case you want to believe it, I just
don't want to show anything to these
little mongos anymore.
PJ PJ, do you know why I know your skin?
And I'm going to be honest. I'm trying
to talk to this one. You head up like
[ __ ] Two. You
>> my head up because I'm arguing with a
[ __ ] like you.
>> No. No. No. No. PJ, you are.
>> Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. I've argued
with a [ __ ] like you.
>> You're triggered now. You're [ __ ]
raising your voice, lads.
>> Raising my voice. Really?
>> I'm I mean to have a normal conversation
and you're triggered.
>> Okay. Let me ask you this. When I showed
you 1300, why didn't you show anything?
>> I showed a grand PJ. No, you didn't show
a grand. No, you did not show a [ __ ]
grand. No, you did not. No, you did not.
Everyone remembers it. It was four
months ago in the park.
>> Oh, for God's sake.
>> You ain't got nothing, mate. You're self
reflector. You're just like non legs.
Ain't got nothing. 13 grand to his name
in three years of doing nothing. That is skint.
>> Yeah, but at least at least he can go
out and get a bird and go on holiday again.
>> Mate, I've already had birds. More birds
than he would ever get. And you will
ever get PJ.
>> Yes, you have again. This is the
biasness kicking in again, people. This
is the biasness kicking in again. Okay, PJ,
>> this is the biasness. We've all seen me
with more money than non legs. More
women than nonjaire.
You're a millionaire.
>> You're a millionaire, PJ. Okay, you're happy now.
>> I'm not a [ __ ] I [ __ ] wish I was a millionaire,
>> PJ. There's no arguing with you because
you've done your balls and you're
triggered and selfing again.
>> Yes, I'm self projecting, PJ.
>> Self projecting again. You don't know
what I have.
>> You don't know what I have.
>> Do you know what self projecting means, Pete?
>> Yeah, it's what you and your little
followers do every day. No, it's not, Peter. Except
>> it's what you and your followers do every day.
>> Self projecting is something what you're
doing. Lying to yourself, kidding
yourself, and [ __ ] and and making
yourself believe in something you
haven't got, PJ.
>> Okay. Yeah. You keep telling yourself
that, Timmy. Like I said,
>> whenever you get show money, you run
away. That's why I'm not wasting my
time. Yep. I'm skinn. Yeah. I've got
nothing. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
>> I think I think Mongol's got more money
than you at the moment.
>> I've got more money than [ __ ] both of
you. No, you haven't. PJ.
>> Okay. No, mate. You ran away when you
got shown 1300 pounds. PJ PJ,
>> you ran away. Let's listen. Listen. But
you like to forget the past. See, with
you biased people, you like to remember
matters, PJ. The past is going to fix
everything, isn't it, PJ?
>> Yeah. Well, you people live in the past.
All you do is go on about the past. So,
I'm going on about the past. I'm not
living. I've shown you six grand. You've
run away. I've shown you,00 you and legs
run away cuz you didn't have nothing.
>> PJ mate, get the [ __ ] out of here, man.
PJ, you're the one who's living in the
past, not us. You're the one who's
living in the past.
>> Same as why don't you show me £500.
>> Same as [ __ ] I can show you£500 right
now. PJ, I've already shown 250 today.
>> PJ, it's 250 more than what you've got
in your pocket.
>> Yeah. You don't know what I've got. You
don't Hey, listen. Yeah. If you want to
add me on Snapchat, if you want to add
>> if you want to add me on Snapchat, I'll
show you what money I have. I'm just not
showing these little skin projectors anything.
>> Yeah, because you won't show him
anything. It's [ __ ] You're doing
what I do.
>> I won't show him because I don't want
you to run away again.
>> Yeah, because it' be a screenshot from
>> Because you're going to run away again.
No, I'm going to show him the cash. I'll
>> Yeah, the one from 3 months ago.
>> Yeah. No, a video of me talking right
now with the cash.
>> Yeah, but PJ, you could have done a
video of talking with the cash three
months ago. PJ, we're not
>> Oh, for [ __ ] sake. This guy is a
[ __ ] You don't want
>> No, PJ, you can't handle the truth. PJ Le,
>> you are making me You're making me
develop brain damage.
>> You've already had brain damage. PJ,
>> you're making me develop brain damage.
>> I don't mean to make you have brain
damage. You already have got brain
>> This guy's giving me brain damage.
>> But PJ, serious question, right? This
>> You are literally making me have brain damage.
>> I'm not making you got brain damage. You
were spazzing anybody.
>> You making me have [ __ ] brain damage.
>> You've already got brain damage. You
have brain damage.
>> Why don't you come to London? and I'll
knock your block off.
>> Well, you just called Prime out and
Prime's going to push, mate. You do you
know what, mate? If I If I took on Prime
and I own it, I wouldn't brag about it.
It'd be a [ __ ] match. You live in a
fantasy world like Liam and PJ and you
you're a [ __ ] [ __ ] like
>> Yeah, you keep telling yourself that.
>> It's I don't have to tell myself it, PJ.
If I There was no police, no law, you
would be six foot under now.
>> Yeah, you keep telling yourself that.
>> I don't need to tell myself that, PJ. I
know. Yeah, you keep telling yourself that.
>> PJ, you live in a [ __ ] [ __ ] world. Do
you know what world you live in?
>> You know what? Because Timmy is skinned,
he's calling me skin. He's self
projecting just like his followers.
>> PJ, I've already ordered a statement.
>> Just like his old man followers does.
Just like the old man followers.
>> He has brain damage. PJ. Oh my god. Can
Can I actually like Can you calm down
for your anxiety for once in a while?
>> And you've never shown 12 grand,
>> PJ. I have.
>> No, you haven't.
>> Yes, I have. PJ.
>> Yes, PJ. Seven years ago.
>> Okay. So, how did you win it then?
>> On the roulette, PJ with Toasty. Me and
Toasty had a massive winning streak,
>> right? And did they pay it out straight away?
>> Yes, PJ, they did.
>> Yeah. What? 50 pound notes.
>> PJ, we had more 50 notes than you've had
hot dinners, lad.
>> Yeah. You keep telling yourself that.
>> We don't need to tell ourselves that.
One, we 20 years older than you. And
two, we know him.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Of course you do. PJ, you're
still a manchild. That's how it is.
>> You keep telling yourself that.
>> I don't need to tell myself. PJ, the
whole planet knows. >> Yeah.
>> PJ, you're the one who's hurting
yourself. You're the one denial and
you're the one who's angry on YouTube.
Few woman, no life.
>> You're talking about yourself again.
Self projecting again. That's all you,
>> PJ. All you're going to do is say that
people talk about themselves.
>> Jimmy, I've had more women than you've
had hot dinners. You're still
>> PJ. Okay. There's literally been there's
videos of me [ __ ] [ __ ] people and
kitting people. But again, you remember
what you want to remember.
>> PJ, I don't give a [ __ ] if you [ __ ] the
queen or not. PJ, you're still a virgin.
>> You are a virgin. Yes, you and Nonss are
a virgin. That's why you get on so well
because you're the Virgin Mary.
>> PJ, you know what? I've been triggered
in 12 years. And I've said
>> him and him and Nonss are the biggest
virgins going. That's why they get on.
>> That's why they get on so well cuz
they're the biggest virgins going. I'
I've said some foolish things in my
time, but you are the biggest fool I've
come across on the
>> And you you and Nlex is are the biggest
virgins. You're a big virgin, you know.
>> Okay. I've had a girlfriend for 20 years.
>> You're a big virgin.
>> And so is nonslegs. He's a virgin and he
can only get disabled girls cuz that's
all that will go out with him cuz he's kid.
>> But PJ, ain't you disabled?
>> Um am I disabled? Um
>> yes, you are PJ. >> No.
>> Yes, you are.
>> Um no. Yes, you are. So, why are you
going on about disabled girls when
you're disabled yourself?
>> Um, no. Jimmy,
>> PJ, I will ring up the DWP and I will record.
>> I've got a date this Saturday.
>> Okay, PJ, answer the question. Say
>> I've got a date this Saturday. Do you
want to see it?
>> PJ, you got no dates.
>> You want to see me? Do you want to see
me on Saturday, Virgin?
>> Well, what with 13y old girls? No thanks, PJ.
>> No, you're the one that offers kids alcohol.
>> No, you're the one who goes with kids.
>> That's why you and that's why you and Nons get
>> PJ. This is why you and nons get on so well.
>> PJ, I've got the pictures of you showing
birds from [ __ ] wedding at old. So,
how can you go on about
>> See what I mean? This guy's a proper pedophile.
>> I'm not. Yeah, you a pedophile, PJ.
You're the one who 14y old girls. PJ,
they tell you they're 18 and they're 14
and you fall for the base every [ __ ] time.
>> This guy is a pedo.
>> No, you're the pedophile, PJ. You're the
one who speaks to 14y old girls on reading.
>> This guy,
>> you know what a pedophile is, Peter? Do
you know what a That's why he likes not
cuz they're both skin. They're both pedos.
>> PJ, I haven't even offered at any kids
alcohol. You and Baz want to go on about
it. You'll get [ __ ]
>> They're [ __ ] They're both
>> You're going to come to this meeting.
You're going to come to this L EDL
meeting Saturday, PJ, and get owned for
being a pedophile.
>> Listen, you and nonsense.
You're not the one who puts 14year-old
girls on [ __ ] pixies on your own.
>> You're the skin pedo.
>> No, no, no. You're the skinn one, PJ.
You can't even show a Fiverr because
you're in a Fiverr and Liam and Liam is
such a [ __ ] [ __ ] I can't show a
Fiverr. He's going to see a video from
three months ago because you're that delusional.
>> Okay. Yeah.
>> Okay. PJ [ __ ]
>> This is why he likes nons so much. No,
the only nons is you only 14y old. It's
>> because they're both skin.
>> You got one who's got 13year-old teenage
dating apps and chatting up Emma Metro
at 13. We've got you chatting 14y old
girls from America. So, who's the nice
PJ? Not us.
>> They're both skin pedos. >> PJ.
>> Oh, I'm dead.
>> PJ, I've spoken to the women you spoke
to and they have gone to the police on
you cuz you have done underage stuff.
>> This guy PJ PJ, the only Pedo is you.
Why were you talking to that 14y old
girl then, PJ from America? Why you away
to rap for 15y old PJ? And it's all
>> See, he's making stuff up now. See,
>> I'm not making stuff up on the [ __ ]
internet you idiot.
>> He makes up stuff. See what I mean?
>> Okay, answer my question. Why did
somebody try to climb through your
bedroom wall for chatting up a 14-y old
girl? And I've got the evidence on that.
PJ, see what I mean?
>> Before you call someone to this, see,
>> no, no, no. PJ PJ is the brother of a
daughter tried to climb through your
window. I've got the evidence, PJ. So if
you want to call people pedophiles mate prop
so why did somebody try to climb through
your window PJ
>> they never
>> they did PJ got the evidence PJ don't make
PJ don't let me make a fool of you
>> I can't take this gun serious bro why
you talking about
>> your silence for 3 seconds gave it away then so
why did somebody try to climb through
your bedroom wall for T up a 14y old.
>> Always about kids. It's always about the
evidence of this as well. Oh,
absolutely. Sky pork you. Oh, here we go. Mother,
you little bacon.
>> Yeah, you're the bacon, mate.
You're like PJ. He's going to get beat
up by you up when I get your address. >> Norton.
>> I will do something. You'll be surprised.
>> Stop talking about kids.
>> I will do something bad when your
address is out there. I will do
something. What are you going on about kids?
>> He's a [ __ ] bacon.
>> Oh god, we got three bacon. No one's
talking about why do you keep bringing
kids [ __ ] bacons at 13?
>> Talking about kids
went with Emma Mitchell at 13. You support that?
>> Jesus Christ.
>> What about you?
>> No, you're the n mate. You look the
biggest on here. Bones
do think about you fell. You are
completely wrong on your bollocks in
lad. This is my bollocky mate. I got a
lot more money than you little spazzy.
So why don't you give me your address
mate and then we'll see you if I don't
do nothing about it. Go on. You tell me
where you live. Tell me where you live
and let's see what you about lad. You
about it. Let's go mate. Let's go. Come
on. Give me smash your head. You're
going to smash no one's heading, mate.
You're a little mommy's boy with 10 grand petrol.
scared to get burgled. You [ __ ]
troll. You nons you [ __ ]
like man who went with Emma Mitchell.
Who went with Emma [Applause]
Mitchell? For [ __ ] sake. I've never been
with Emma Mitchell. Go forage.
>> Everybody hates you, Baz. Everybody
wants you dead.
The gift that keeps on giving. No one
likes you, Daz. We're going to find out
your wheel nons going to get you and
you're going to get like what York he's
got, mate. And there's nothing you're
going to do about it.
>> [ __ ] beacon.
>> Yeah, you can call me what you like,
mate. At least my windows ain't going to
go through and your address is out there, lads.
>> Anybody coming to the Saturday?
>> I am coming.
>> Are you going to come to the march
Saturday, Baz? Are you going to support
>> You'll never go on the EDL you lad.
>> No, no, no.
[ __ ] support bacons like you mate and
then got the sheets to call other people
invited don't you
never be a Pakistanis don't you
can smash your face I need to
go live and hide in your little
>> Jimmy We got a free bus. Yeah. So you
can get the bus for free. Yeah.
>> It's got an IVA
and absolutely owned.
>> He's left.
>> No, he's still here. Timmy.
Hi, Monty. Why did you block me on Facebook?
>> Cuz you're cuz you're [ __ ]
>> Oh, really? Thank you. I love you, too.
>> I don't love you, PJ. Well, you must be
a [ __ ] stain on this community.
>> You been in this [ __ ] community
longer than me.
>> You know,
>> I'm only in this community because Okay,
now tells me to go live. >> Why?
>> Oh, he's left now.
>> Now they don't tell me to go live.
>> You're addicted to YouTube, isn't it?
You're addicted to YouTube.
>> So are you.
>> Why can't you get off YouTube?
>> I'm coming off this [ __ ] soon anyway. So
I'll leave you to it. I'm going to leave
you to it soon.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You can
>> cuz I can't be bothered anymore. But
lad, you can you can do what you want. I don't care.
>> Yeah. Well, I might as well go live
then. Knowing it subs it.
>> Yeah. You can you can entertain spastics
all your life. I don't care. It's your
life in it.
Oh, thanks BJ. Thank you.
>> It's true, though. It
>> No, no, you're well kind. You're proper
>> Yeah, they're going to say skin and all
of this same old [ __ ] It
>> Yeah, they know that [ __ ] don't bother
me like it bothers you anyways.
>> No, it's just it's just boring repeaters.
>> Doesn't bother me. It's just repeating, is it?
That's their life, don't it? So,
>> yeah, but it's class for your life.
Yeah. No, it's not. Matey,
>> hey, money, I've got a question.
>> Go on then.
>> Do Do you think £13,000 is a lot of
money? Yes or no? Just answer it.
>> Yeah, money doesn't make you happy now, does it?
>> No, no, I know. I'm just asking you.
>> Well, that's one of the Ask one of Lead
who gives a [ __ ] about money, Pet No,
but they just give biased answers. So,
I'm just asking you.
Well, I see. So, we'll answer that
question. What is a lot of money, PJ? >> Yeah.
>> I just want to ask you it.
>> 30 grand's a lot of money, PJ.
>> No. 13. >> 13. >> Yeah.
13 or 14 is doesn't matter. Money is
money, Pia. Why Why are you bothered
about money? How much? They're the ones
that bring it up every day. And then you
and you say that I'm the one that brings
it up, but they're the ones that bring it up.
>> Yeah, but you're the one who sits in
flirt of it, repeats after brings it up yourself,
>> you know.
>> Okay. No, man.
>> Timmy is funny though. You know, Timmy
is funny. He's coming back. >> Funny.
>> I'm not funny. I just tell you two
clowns how it is. You can call us nons,
but we're not the ones who want to
approach 13y old kids like Emma Mitchell
and want to do sexual
>> never happen. Can you get the prom
the evidence? Get the evidence in there.
Can you actually ask him
instead of listening or [ __ ] shy long
13y old mate? You a dirt [ __ ] nons means you
[ __ ] to me. Why? Why do you Why are
you talking about young girls?
Explain that. Explain that. Mongol never happened.
>> No, no, no. Explain it, Mongol. Yes, it did. Mongol
the fact that you come onto a 13y old
talking to two underage underage kids on the bus
and you can
hate for me on yourself.
He can control as much as he [ __ ]
wants, but the geese has finished. And
when I get my >> answer
is funny, isn't it?
>> PJ that you've got not one person with one account.
>> Listen to me,
PJ. And they're all nons.
>> Do you know what? Yeah, Monty, listen
listen one second, Monty. Yeah, I said
it. Cuz Timmy's Timmy's been on about
money all day.
>> Tell me more money.
>> Show me 20 quid, lad. Show me >> nothing.
>> Money. I'm not showing him nothing.
>> PJ. PJ, you're broke. You've been going
on about for three weeks. PJ, when
Universal Credit comes in a week, you
won't be on YouTube.
>> Okay. Okay. Timmy,
>> it's not okay. It's true. >> Listen,
>> when you lost your Universal Credit,
you're going to die. All Timmy goes on
about is money.
>> Why do you keep going on about money to me?
>> PJ, right? Let's have a serious chat. I
can understand why you don't want to
show troll stuff. But the fact that
you've been bragging and going on about
it, you can't get out of this, PJ. If
you don't show money now, you are broke.
>> I'm not showing him money. Modly.
>> You are broke, PJ. I'm not showing them money.
>> You're broke, PJ. You're broke.
>> It doesn't mean you're broke. PJ,
I'm not showing them money.
to show money first go to the whole
every single time I've shown him money
he's run away that's why I don't run
away you're saying this cuz you're scared now tell PJ everybody
will show your money excuses cuz you're
a skint [ __ ] bot you show the money
first and then PJ will show
>> like Mongol Mongol can't show 20 quid
Jimmy, I don't want to show you unless
someone to Buffy Island.
>> I don't know. You need to pay nothing.
>> Well, you can't even speak clearly
because you smoke too much weed.
>> Well, at least I can afford.
>> At least I can afford it, Jimmy.
>> Mate, I can afford to smoke weed. I
smoke a lot more than you. You skink.
You're broke. You're bastard. You got
50 quid, Mongol. Why don't you show me some?
>> Oh, why don't you show me 200 quid first
island? You [ __ ]
>> If you want to see it, Timmy, if you
want to see it, you on here. Nobody on
here. If you want to see 50 quid, yeah,
you got to show me first. >> See,
>> can you do that, Jimmy?
>> You coming [ __ ] you coming to the
march on Saturday or you going to be too
[ __ ] scared? Timmy, Timmy, you know,
you know I'm going to be up [ __ ] you know,
you're going to be up there from
you. You're all going to be up.
>> You can't afford to get a train to
London. You're asking
a to get a train ticket to London.
>> Mongol, show us 50 quid and I'll show
you a tenner first. Yeah.
>> Don't go to the bank. Mongol, show me50.
Give me show me a tener first.
>> [ __ ] hell. You know I'm going to call you.
>> I'm not showing money again because
whenever you show them money got any
[ __ ] can show your money first. Tim
keeps going on about money. So ask
Listen Monty. All that's going to happen
is you show them money and they run
away. That's what they do. That's what
they do. Excuses. Excuse
>> is a clown on PJ.
Enjoy your first evenings.
>> Yeah, we're scared. Okay,
>> now Natalie, I'm going to pick up in 15
minutes and I'm taking her to Buffet Island.
>> Jimmy, I'm sorry, but you got no chance
or likes Mr. Timble.
>> Yeah, he's left anyways. I'm not playing
these stupid games. You can play if you
I'm not playing these games. End of
>> Why would you you suck to me PJ?
>> You've already g to me a [ __ ]
>> Out with him.
>> Yeah, exactly. You went out with him.
>> No, you made out with him.
No, you did. You met him and everything.
You went to his scalp and everything.
What happened there? >> Number job.
>> Are you making up weird gay stories?
>> Why did it take off another transat
question if it weren't true?
>> Because it's not true. You're talking
stupid. Why did you ask me for Why did
you ask me?
>> You're talking stupidness.
>> I'm not. You're not.
>> You're talking absolute stupidness.
That's why it's ridiculous.
>> Why would I want some baldy? Why do I
want some baldy [ __ ] giving me a
>> Cuz you want me to cut my baldy head
while my dick, you g bastard. >> No. Yeah. Yeah. You sp
Why did you ask me to give you Why did
you want to give me anywhere, PJ? What
was that about?
>> Stop making up. Swear on your kid's
life. That happened.
>> No, no, no, no, no. If you, if that
happened, you you'd swear in your kids'
life. Go on. Cuz I can swear in my mom's
life, no crossing included. That never happened.
>> Well, I swear in my mom's life, it happened.
>> No, I swear in your swear in your kids's
life, no crossing included.
>> I swear my mom's life it happened.
>> Exactly. Cuz I'm talking [ __ ] and you
know you are. You can't even swear in
your kids life cuz you know Yeah. Cuz
you know you're full of [ __ ] And that
never happened. Stop talking [ __ ]
>> You know what happened.
>> Stop talking [ __ ] Stop lying. You
know what happened.
>> Stop lying.
>> You don't need to lie, PJ. It's okay to be gay.
>> It's okay to be gay. Yeah. Yeah, you are
>> You know, PJ, it's okay to be gay.
>> Yeah, I know you are gay.
>> So, I like to call the classic now and again. PJ,
>> you are gay. >> Babes, I got
>> Why do people go on about money every
day on you anyways?
>> Skin like you, please. Yeah. >> Yeah.
You look who's back, [ __ ] man. the guy
who's left YouTube and here he is now
and makes a new channel.
>> Yeah, I'm back for good now. Get rid of
the mango, man. [Laughter]
>> Oh, I'm dead.
You can't live without YouTube, is it?
>> DJ YouTube's
like smack to you.
>> Yeah. Is it really? Well, I'm getting
off um from I'm getting off tomorrow until Monday.
>> Yeah, Monday. Why not now? Why Why give you
>> I'm coming back I'm coming back. No, I'm
coming back up. I'm leaving um today and
I'm coming back Monday.
>> What? So, you're coming back on your period? Yeah.
>> No, cuz I need to meet Prime on Monday.
>> Prime m.
>> Look, this is Prime.
>> How you doing, Monty?
>> See what I mean?
>> No, I I I do actually like Monty. I
think he's got some good banter about him.
>> Yeah, that's good for you, man. You
didn't You should have met me at Monty
in Birmingham when I was calling you out then.
>> Listen, listen. I just got one simple question.
>> Who would win? I've got I've got my
opinion on this, okay? And everybody's
entitled to their own opinion. Like, you
can have your opinion. Monty,
>> we'll see. We'll see you on Monday, won't we?
>> I'm I'm just asking you now. Who would
win in a fight between you two? My
opinion, Monty obviously wins.
>> But we're not talking about us. I'm
talking about me meeting you on Monday.
>> No, I know. I'm just asking the question.
>> But we're not going to be fighting
though. So why are you asking that?
>> Well, no. I'm I'm just hypothetically
like who would
>> Yeah, but why would you come in and ask that?
>> Well, why not?
>> All you need to worry about is when I
kick your ass on Monday if you come to London.
>> What he thinks?
>> No one cares. We're talking about me
coming and whooping your ass on Monday
in Crystal Palace.
>> I think a bit of a [ __ ] bag, PJ.
>> Thank you, man. You're right.
>> Yeah. Do you know this is the guy that I
called out when I was with you in um
Birmingham, by the way, along with Timmy?
>> Is it?
This is prime. This is prime. Yeah.
>> Who do you reckon would win? Monty,
>> why are you? >> Huh? Who?
Me? Me and PJ.
me. I'll see you on
>> Well, PJ is a little soft ass, so I
don't know to be honest cuz PJ is he is
a soft ass.
>> Yeah, you're a soft ass as well. You can even be
>> met me once. He's already
>> Monty. He's Monty. He's already met me
once and I made him say sorry. So he could
>> You done nothing to me. You caught me
off guard. You caught me off guard and
you was bigger than me two years ago.
I'll see you on Monday like you said.
Yeah. Do you not think he could have
done something then? Monty,
>> listen. All of this Yeah. All of what
you're doing, it just goes to show
you're never going to meet again, are
you? Like you never met in Birmingham.
Cuz you're a [ __ ]
>> You're a [ __ ] Is it? >> Listen.
>> So why don't you go back to Birmingham
then if he's a [ __ ] Pedia?
>> Why am I not going to go back to Cuz I
was in Birmingham last month.
>> Hang on a minute. You come back to
Birmingham a couple of days ago.
>> No, I recording that.
>> No, I wasn't.
>> Yeah, you were. I've literally said I'm
never ever meeting any you again unless
you come here. I
>> don't need to come back and shout them
all out because she was with me.
>> Monty, a quick one. If Monty, if someone
grabbed you. Yeah. >> Listen,
>> out of the blue, someone grabbed you.
What would you do? >> Exactly.
>> You didn't Yeah, but listen,
but Prime, you done nothing. You got a
panic attack midway through and you done
nothing. And then you're trying to say
you didn't hit me because I'm disabled,
bro. Come on now. Monty, does he look a
bit disabled when he's walking? Be honest.
>> Listen, I will see you on Monday.
>> I will see you on Monday then, won't I?
>> Proven point.
>> Well, I'll see you on Monday, won't I? Then
>> I've just proven the point. That's why I
didn't hit you.
>> Okay, whatever. I will see you on Monday
and and by the time I'm done with you,
you'll be in a wheelchair. How's that one? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah, it will be.
>> Why don't go then PJ and sort it out?
>> Cuz I've already explained it, you
[ __ ] I don't know how many times I
have to explain it. I was already in there.
>> Are you Have you got brain damage? Have
you got brain damage like these people?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I've already explained it a million times.
>> I swear this community is disabled. I
swear this community is domesticated.
>> He's not coming back cuz he knows I'm
going to slap him up. That's why he's
not coming back.
>> Listen, if he was going to slap me up,
you would have done something. You would
have done something about it. Listen,
>> what what you said about my kids
yesterday? Well, I said to you, I said,
"Oh, by the way, by the way, oh, another
thing, Monty, I didn't wish rape on your
kids. I said rice was nonsing them up. I
didn't wish your kids to be raped.
That's another thing I forgot to mention."
>> Oh, so that's basically rice is nons
basically saying you want rice to basically.
There you go. So, they were lying.
>> You talk about nonsified.
>> You're listen. Why don't you come to Why
don't you come to London on Monday?
>> Why don't you come to London on Monday?
AJ, you won't show up.
>> Exactly. No, I I won't show up. I went to Birmingham.
>> Exactly what you just said. Exactly. You
won't show up.
>> I I went to Birming Oh my god. It's the
same argument. You people are
spasticated, bro. I give up. I I give up
with these mongos, bro. Swear down.
>> Listen, why keep disrespecting Monty for?
>> I give up. I'm not saying anything anymore.
>> Disrespectful all the time.
>> I can't be bothered, man.
I'll just see you on Monday. Prime.
Yeah. Why have you got to keep disrespecting just
>> Timmy? Why is a [ __ ]
>> Well, you're a [ __ ] mate.
>> Anyway, PJ, let's get to the point. You
did get wed by It wasn't a hard rack,
but I'm going to put the video back up
in a minute. PJ,
>> hey, listen. Timmy, are you are you in Birmingham now?
>> No, PJ. I'm in Australia. M
>> Why don't you and Monty meet now?
>> I'm in Australia. PJ
Monty. Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold
on. Why don't you and Monty meet now?
>> I'm in Australia, PJ. What? How many times?
>> He's thinking he's in Australia.
>> Why don't Why don't you two meet now?
You've been arguing for months. Why
don't you two meet now?
>> The fact it's a grass. You're going to
the police and I'm not getting a grass.
>> You are a grass. Why don't you meet me now, Jimmy?
>> Okay. Okay. I'll upload the videos where
you rang the police on belly. Go on then.
>> Oh, I will.
>> So, you've just admitted it then. So,
why did you go?
>> No, no, no, no, no, no. I haven't you
just said you're going to upload a video
of me. So, I said go on then.
>> You've just said go and upload the
video. So, that's a cut. So, to me, you've always
>> No, no, because you haven't got to
Mongol. Why did you grasp? You're never
going to meet me, are you? You're never
going to meet me again. Stop talking to
me, Bongo. You're never going to meet me
again. Can't handle it, can it?
>> Your conscious can't handle
>> like this [ __ ] [ __ ] on the chat.
What's it bal who's the biggest number
who supports PJ Mongol actually
contacting him the biggest community
needs a slap because he ain't got a clue
what a bacon is. He needs to getacons
on your chat right now PJ are actually bacons.
>> They support you. They support you two
contacting miners on PlayStation and [ __ ]
>> That was your white.
That was your That was your friend.
>> That was Skid Nex. That was Skid N.
>> Okay. Okay. And I'll tell you why you've
got the [ __ ] nons on here cuz Pora
[ __ ] went to toppings kids on Discord
and put a penis in them and he's got the
cheeks called the Sons. You are going to
[ __ ] hell and you're going to burn in agony. Listen,
>> I'm going to [ __ ] love it.
>> Timmy, the only the only the only nons
is you and NGS.
>> Well, no, no, no. Well, nonslegs doesn't
chat 13y old, PJ. Yes, he does. Show me
the evidence, PJ. Show me the evidence.
>> Do you not know him?
Listen, listen. Him and [ __ ]
>> All right. Listen, listen, Timmy. Timmy,
Timmy, Timmy. Nons. Monty was fighting
over a kid. So they both died.
>> So they basically come off. This is
about the Emma Mitchell. Film me in more.
>> They were fighting over a girl called
Britney. Not Emma Mitchell.
>> Yeah. And [ __ ] hell. You bacon. You absolute bacon.
>> It's not even true.
>> Yes, it is true. Yes, it is true.
>> I swear down on my kids life.
>> Oh, so you swear down on your life. You
won't swear on your kids life when you
see this. How you know he's a
bullshitter? He's a bullshitter. Do you
know what I mean?
>> What? Well, because he said
you are finished.
>> Great dreams, Dazzy boy. I'm coming.
>> You three are the great the three great pedos.
>> PJ, so why do you sit down here talking
about king that you talking about my
kids about rice and that's a bit weird,
don't you think?
>> I said you and was fighting over
Britney. You was fighting over.
>> Definitely didn't happen. Definitely did
>> It did.
>> You're [ __ ] weirdo, PJ.
This is why I'm not your mate.
>> This is why I [ __ ] you off because all
you talk about is an actual [ __ ] pedophile
and then you put me on level.
>> You know what? I should have sparked you
out in that club in front of all them
girls and embarrassed the [ __ ] out of
you to be honest with you.
>> The three great pedos, isn't it?
>> You know what? I might actually go to
London actually now >> literally.
>> Yeah. But the three great pedo isn't it?
>> You are the [ __ ] pedo man sitting on
PlayStation 3 with actual nons talking
to him day in and day out and actually
meeting him knowing what he was. You're a freak.
That's the truth. Is it PJ?
PJ meets nons.
>> You are a nons.
>> You met the [ __ ] worst person or
[ __ ] PlayStation chat the ripper in
person. Everyone wonder about him. You still bet.
>> Who was you talking to? Who was you
talking to before you even met you? A
you wrinkling man.
Fulk knows what you used to were talking
to talking about for your back.
>> You know,
>> you're a freak. I mean, you put music on
your long legs. [ __ ] Come on, man. Net
ads are biggest nuts on PlayStation 3.
>> I'm going to do damage to PJ. [ __ ] it, man.
>> PJ's phone under the bus and said that
So, so why did you watch this Emma
Mitchell? Why got through
Mitchell's never happened?
Cuz that's [ __ ] all even the [ __ ] That's [ __ ]
>> Why did you a 13y old girl? Why did you
write to a 13y old girl?
>> It's not Oh my god, Mongol. The evidence
is Oh my god. Because nothing
I'm not listening to a clown like actually knows
>> Jimmy you know nothing you know nothing at all
>> wants bacons man I hope the black gets killer [Laughter]
>> what would that say
>> what would that say about natty G's a
[ __ ] bacon lover
>> bacon lover Okay.
>> You get life can get by for what can you get?
>> What can you get, Jimmy?
You know why I'm not getting angry? Do
you know why I'm actually not getting
angry? Cuz it's old people. The evidence
is there. We must not be in prison,
mate. You're lucky that you're not in
Listen. Listen. Why don't you contact
Mitch and find out if it's happened?
Yeah. Why don't you contact her?
Right. She's on Facebook. Her name's
called Emma Mitch. Give her a text and
ask yourself, you [ __ ] idiot.
>> Hold on. Mongol. What possess you?
>> Go and ask yourself, you [ __ ] get out
of this, Mongol. It's all over the
>> I can't get out of it because it never happened.
>> You've done it.
>> Oh my god. So, oh my god, [ __ ] you're
on the outside
police. You'd have [ __ ] good me. So,
if you're not scared of me then, so why
won't you meet me now?
>> [ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] how spazz no
you're not scared of me. Why won't you
meet me now? Why you got excuses or
return to me?
You are mong
and find out for yourself to me if you
got the fact that what's possessed you
to do that you are [ __ ] wrong lad
Jimmy you are a wrong gun saying I'm a
boss talking to two actual kids mine's
false nothing's happened with me
yours is actually real you are the nons
you are the bacon
I'm Sorry. I'm sorry. I'm the boss, man.
You're You're a weird one. You only get
tired on social media cuz it's a
platform and you're behind the camera.
That's only what's detecting you.
Whenever you're out for fighting me, you
a [ __ ] [ __ ] >> [ __ ]
I've called you out for the last 6 months.
Let me get this offion
with [ __ ] have never met
once. Not once.
Do you want me to push?
>> You are a scared bacon. You are a scared
defensive push. Is that what you want me to do?
>> Going to defend you soon. Mongol. You don't
enjoy jail. Why do you want to Why do
you want to go back park? to me.
AJ, you're a freak. You put in Sean with
long legs on me. You're a freak, lad.
>> Yeah, but you like him.
>> No, I don't like him. That's the thing.
So, so, so what did I know on PJ? GoP.
So what what what what PlayStation
account did I know him on?
>> You already know.
>> Yeah. No, no. You you put this remark
on. So what PlayStation account was he
on when I was talking to Sean? When I met him,
go on PJ
on putting his remark on me about Sean,
but he doesn't even know what account I
was on when I met Sean. Yeah, I do. So
what account was it then?
>> Don't worry about that.
>> No, of course he does. But what was it then? PJ,
>> don't worry about that.
>> You don't know [ __ ] PJ
to get everything off you and that's it.
>> Well, you're the biggest [ __ ] [ __ ] in this community. >> Nah.
>> Yeah. when you can't get there
self-reflecting all the time more times
than you have. Yeah.
>> Legs. You're so obsessed with that lad. It's unfucking.
>> I know that's why he's got a channel on
me. But yeah. Okay.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You and him got this
relationship thing going on. I met him
through him through you.
>> Well, through me, PJ, I can swear down
my kids. You never met him through me.
You met him through some American like
you were saying on your channel.
No, you didn't mean through me at all.
PJ, I introduce you to the community.
I've never had Sean on my friend list.
Never. Ever. When you was on my list.
>> So, you can sit there and make up
excuses, but everyone were telling you
what your voice was, but you were sat
there talking to the weird one and then
decided to go on these little dates with
him to kind of town and stuff like that.
All right, Baz. Last one before I go.
Stop crying like a big girl's blouse on
the comments, right? I'm not interested
in words. No one gives a [ __ ] about you.
You're going to
and I'll show you what I'm about. Enjoy
your night crying on
why you don't bo on time.
>> You on your bollocks in
>> Jimmy. PJ, you can't even get your
bollocks. Ain't it?
>> I've already been laid more times than you.
>> What? What makes you think you've been
laid more times than me?
>> Because I have. EJ, I'm happy getting
laid by one woman and I've been made
more times than you woman. >> Yeah,
>> listen. Look what you look what you order. Escort.
>> You wanted an escort. Yeah, but you
>> Why the [ __ ] would I want to sleep with
when I went when I went back to you
wanted an escort?
>> He's holy [ __ ]
>> I swear on my [ __ ] mom's life. No.
That's where I'm living my kids. Nice.
Why the [ __ ] would I want to sit with a escort?
>> You did ask for an escort.
>> Oh god, did I? I must have been pissed then.
>> And that's the thing, guys. Escorts.
Escorts can't go back to that place
anyways cuz PJ forgetting. Yeah.
>> So yeah, you didn't want escorts.
>> Yeah, but I I would have been able to
get escort in PJ. That That's the funny
thing. when they when there was a camera.
>> Your skin.
>> Don't forget Don't forget you actually
climb off a fence just to come through
the front door.
>> You're skil
the best you got. PJ,
>> you're a bit skin is it?
>> PJ, listen. This is the best you got.
This is how much you've been calling
people skin for now. No starting it on me.
>> That's all you have. I'm leaving this
community soon anyway, so I'll leave you to it.
>> No, that's fine. That's good. That's
good. I'll leave you to I'll leave you
to the repeating bastards. Yeah.
>> Or maybe deleted you off Facebook or
yourself like calling my message.
>> I'll leave I'll leave you to the repeaters. Yeah.
>> PJ when you go probably won't repeat.
>> Really? Go live now then.
>> What? Go live now.
>> Yeah. No one really talks on my channel.
No one comes on. No one really knows my YouTube account. Really?
>> Really? Yeah. They have about four or
five people watching me these days.
That's good. Is it? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. And I definitely don't get the same repeaters.
>> You do.
>> EJ, you thrive off this [ __ ] on this
community, don't you?
>> No. You like it.
>> PJ's been leaving YouTube for the last 3
years. How would you know on YouTube?
How would you know that if you weren't
on YouTube? So you must be on YouTube
then as well.
>> Yeah, that's pretty. You're the one who
dragged every [ __ ] on here.
>> You created this community. It's from
you dragging everybody on here. >> Really? >> Yeah. >> No.
>> Yeah. You You dragged everybody on this
community. You dragged Natalie on it.
You dragged me on it.
>> You [ __ ] I dragged Natalie on it. Are
you stupid before me? You mong.
>> Yeah, she was on it before me, you idiot.
>> No, I didn't think you tried his long
legs on it.
>> Yeah, I dragged you and him on it, but
Natalie was on it before.
>> No, no. Yeah, not you dragged her on it.
You dragged me. You dragged
>> I dragged Natalie. Natalie was already on it.
>> Yeah. Was she? No, you you dragged her
on. And TX man, why do you keep um
self-reflecting your skintess onto me
every day as well?
>> Since you're typing,
the more you do this, right, the more
you embarrass yourselves on YouTube, the
more it proves that you are the skint
ones. So, I'm just going to leave.
>> You're skint?
>> Yeah, I'm skint. Yeah.
>> Oh, PJ, do you not remember back on
PlayStation? Yeah. When me and you used
to always talk a tree trophy. Yeah. And
they ask you, "What you doing today?"
Yeah. And you say, "I'm going out with
my mates." And that and then you go out
and then you send me these pictures of
you when you run start on the step.
Where's your mates?
>> No. Never happened.
>> Never never happened.
>> So you going live?
>> When we going to go live for you, PJ?
You never join my hangouts,
>> you know. So why you on mine then? Why
you on my live? Cuz I thought I'd give
you a bit of attention, PJ. Cuz that's
what you want in it. A bit of attention.
Mommy don't give you no attention no
more. So I thought I give you a little attention. >> Nah.
>> Oh, do you get enough attention off
these do? You that repeating more, don't you, Pia?
>> Yeah, totally.
>> You love it.
When was the last time you got married? Yeah.
>> The last time I got laid. >> Yeah.
>> Never. I'm a virgin. Why? >> Yeah.
>> Do you know how do you know how immature
you you you sound when you say about
getting laid? You're 35 and you're
talking about getting laid.
>> Yeah. 35. You know what?
>> You're old and you're talking about
getting laid and you're with a slag.
>> Old might actually.
>> You're actually old.
I'd rather I'd rather have nothing than
be with Natalie G. I'd rather have nothing.
>> You was You were crying to meet Natalie G. >> No. >> Yeah.
>> Definitely definitely definitely not dead. PJ, >> huh?
>> Swear down on your mom's life.
>> Swear down on my mom's life.
>> Jack [ __ ] You were crying to me.
>> Yeah, I was crying to me. Okay.
>> Everybody knows you're crying to meet N.
>> Yeah. You keep telling yourself that.
>> You keep telling yourself that. You know
you wanted to meet Natalie. Natalie
knows she wanted to meet her.
>> Yeah. Okay.
So, you didn't want to meet Natalie. Who
was it then? Who did you want to meet? I
just wait to tell me to get off.
>> No one. >> Yeah.
>> So, what are you looking in life then, PJ? >> Huh?
>> What are you looking for in life?
>> Never your mind.
>> I know. HV is Yeah.
>> No, you're looking for kids.
>> EJ, that's what I mean. You're supposed
to wear this [ __ ] Timmy bringing kids up.
You're looking [ __ ] in the playground.
>> PJ, you have a weird one.
>> It's funny, isn't it?
>> Yeah, but this is why I thought too, PG.
Have you not thought about that?
>> You know what? I don't even know why PJ
contacted me back [ __ ] through
this [ __ ] To be honest with you,
>> he was part of a P. I think weird though
that that you had to run back to me
because you had nobody to run to in this
community and you already had to run back.
>> Yeah, we were
>> DJ not ruined my life. No, I still got
my kids in my life.
No, not not because I still got my kids
in my life. I still see my kids.
>> Oh no, not like someone said why even
talk to the snake. Yeah, he is a snake.
>> He is a snake.
>> He snakes on people all the time.
>> I know myself. Yeah, better than PJ.
Yeah, pick all your views. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> What would you tell them my YouTube channel? Yeah,
>> they know your YouTube channel.
>> No, they don't.
>> They do. No.
>> All right, Mongol. Just to let you know
that Natalie G is going to get picked up
in two minutes outside a limo with
luxury bubbles champagne and got the
money going to get down on one knee and
give her £1,000 and apologize and
they're going to make it up.
>> Money m
you mong you haven't got £1,000,000
that last two seconds. The limo's
coming. The limo is coming.
>> Compete against that Mongol. You say you
love Natalie. I'm all out of love. Jimmy
compete against it against this Mongol.
It's one minute to go. He's coming.
>> Yeah. So, what's the address then, Jimmy?
>> Oh, I know Nataly G's address. It's out
there. We don't need your address,
Mongol. We're just picking up Nat G.
>> Yeah, but I live with Nat G though,
Jimmy. That's the key. Bongol. No, you don't. And
>> do not look to me.
>> Yeah, look.
>> You have just fell into my trap. DJ, this [ __ ]
>> I knew this was going to work. And
>> BJ, this [ __ ] Aedo that had a team
dating app on his phone.
>> The same address, [ __ ] That's all I
needed to know. Chicken Tica coming on strong.
>> BJ, this Mongo's Aedo that had a team
dating app on his phone. Yeah, we know that.
>> You don't have to repeat yourself. We
only had you once.
>> Yeah, because it's true, though, is it?
No, but no, but we hear this [ __ ] every
single day though.
>> Yeah, it is true. We had one on my
phone, but I didn't know what it were.
Who? That's why I put up on YouTube.
They all know about it cuz I put it up
on YouTube. If I knew what it would and
it would have been up on YouTube, so
that [ __ ] wouldn't bother me anyway.
None of this [ __ ] bothers me what you
say on here. Not really. [Music]
just got me to ride a matter of fact is
that use a real nonsense.
That's it. Does that appear a bit like a freak? >> No,
it's true though.
Yeah. PJ legend [ __ ] [ __ ] get in.
It's funny, isn't it?
We've got you now, Mongol. We've got
you. But before we do, let's play a
game, Mongol, because I love gameplay
for you. It's going to eventually happen.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Timmy. So,
>> what part of suburb of Birmingham do I live?
>> Me? I don't not Timmy. Where is it?
>> Timmy, why do I need to tell you what
part of Birmingham?
>> No, no, no. I know you're from
Ernington. I can even say your door
number where you are right now, Dad.
This is the beauty of Wolf Creek.
>> So, I've got you, Mass Miller. And I
pretty much got Banger, which I'm not
going to do Spangers. Banganger's not
that bad to be fair. No, no, no, no, no,
no. Mongol. What part of suburb do I live in?
>> Very close the other day. Very close.
>> You live in Kidding, Minister. No, I'm
not from there, but I'm close. But come
on, Mongol. Let's play a game.
>> You know, you're playing these games on your
>> No, no, no, [ __ ] I can even name the
streets of Erdington. You are your Sky
or I'm not. So, let's play.
>> Okay, let's play a game, man. So, what's
my street name, Timmy? So, what's my
street name? I'm not >> send address. So anyway,
>> send me a take away now to me.
>> I already have.
>> Well, have you then be on here? Send me
>> £300 worth of kebab, mate.
>> Oh, that's fine. That's fine, Timmy.
>> And they're going to make you pay for it
cuz it's a loan shop.
No tonight, Mongol. You'll be on a skewer.
>> Timmy 7.
>> Anyway, Mongol, let's No, Timmy. Timmy,
what part of Birmingham do I live in?
Let's play the game. >> Timmy,
you don't even know Birmingham that
well, do you? Should I give you a bong?
Should I give you a little hint what
part of Birmingham I live in?
>> Okay, then. Blurers Heath, Northfield,
Kings, Norton, Red Hill, um, Sio. Um,
um, I know what it's called. Um,
uh, not Hansworth. Oh god, I know where
it is cuz I live around there. Harbborne,
Erdington, not Erdington, sorry. Edgebaston.
What part is it, Mongol?
>> What part is it?
Timmy. Timmy. But why you my I'm not a [ __ ]
>> Wrong goal. Wrong goal. We kill.
>> You know where I know where you are, but
you don't know where I am.
>> Why do you think I call you out to
Cannon Hill Park, Mongol? I've already
given you a very close clue of my location.
Come on, Mongol.
PJ's the closest. So far, >> Wolverampton. >> Nope.
>> What's beginning with?
>> Well, I'm not telling you PJ. This is
this is the idea of a game. >> Solo.
>> No, PJ. Very close for PJ. Solo's no
nowhere near Kiddaminster.
>> Kitty Minister's Yam isn't it?
>> No, it's Worersha. It's not far from
Stalbridge. Yum. Yum. You are white. >> Warsaw. >> No.
>> But you were born in Warsaw.
>> No. PJ.
>> He wasn't it.
>> If I say yes, PJ, your rocket get hard.
>> But you was born. You was born in Warsaw.
>> You PJ, you were very close.
>> Yeah, but you was born in War.
>> PJ, you're the closest in 16 months so
far. What? Said it.
>> But you was born in War.
>> No, no, no. I wasn't PJ. PJ, you
actually are the winner. Out of everyone
who's been doing guest games in the past
17 months, you are the closest. >> Uh,
>> Lemonton Spa.
>> Oh, getting warmer.
>> Ah, see, I'm good at geography, aren't I?
>> Getting warmer. Getting warmer. >> Uh,
that place called uh
Den. Oh, what's it called? Forget. I'll
give you a clue, PJ. Right.
>> You are not far far wrong from
Kiddaminster. It's between Bradford and
Haven and Kiddaminster. That's all you
need to know.
>> So it's not Birmingham.
>> Bradford, sorry. Bidford and Haven. It's
between Bidford and Haven and Kudley.
>> Dudley's nowhere near Bidford, you [ __ ] clown.
>> Yeah, you know Kitty Minister's near
London, isn't it?
What the [ __ ] am I hearing here? But
it's near London, is it?
>> [ __ ] Blanca.
>> It's near London, isn't it?
>> No, it's nowhere near London. It's near
the Y plunka.
>> No, but yeah, but what I'm saying is
Dudley um the minister is near London.
>> Right. This is all you need to know
because Mongol is dying to find me. If
you want to find me, Mongol, this is the
clue of the widow. I am between
Kiddaminster and bid for the Naven.
You just all you got to do is look on
your map, Mongol.
>> That's if you can That's if you can read a map.
>> It's funny, isn't it?
>> It's funny that Mongol is fuming that I
can knock his door any minute and I live
miles away from him.
>> When When are you going on a piss again?
>> I probably might be doing it now. PJ,
>> can we meet up on tomorrow?
>> PJ, I said to you on my live, if you're
willing to apologize for the mistakes
you've done, cuz I know you're autistic
and I know you lie about it, PJ, I am
willing to help you. But if you are not
going to apologize for the mistakes
you've done and that, I can't help you,
PJ. You've done a lot of [ __ ] up
things on here.
>> Yeah, but can we meet up? PJ, do you
think I'm going to meet up with you and
I'll get the whole country on my back?
>> That's funny, isn't it? It's
>> not funny. PJ, no. There's about 65
million people who want you on a skewer. [Laughter]
>> No, seriously,
>> PJ. If long as you're willing to change
and you apologize to everyone, Tram, I
know Tram's trolled you, but you have
said some bad things about Be the Be the
bigger man, PJ. Apologize to bomb trap
staring everyone and Shauny and I will
>> they can all suck they can all suck my
dick them skin flints
>> but PJ they're winning and I'll explain
you know you know a bigger man walks
away and apologizes
>> you know n see so you're the bigger so
you're the bigger man or not serious question
>> a bigger man gets a life and gets off YouTube something
>> no a bigger man PJ just admits defeat
>> something that Red Star can't do
>> PJ He'll leave you alone if you get on
your knees and say I'm sorry.
>> No, he leave me alone. He can do what he
wants. I'm not asked.
>> You do know
you do know I know who Red Star is.
>> He's a sad [ __ ] isn't it?
>> Yeah. And he owns you.
>> Yeah, he owns me.
>> You do. You do know. You do. You do know
Red Star is my real friend in the real
world. You do know that, don't you?
>> You wish he owned me. You wish PJ
And it's not Pat Mustard and it's not Bob. So
>> you wish, mate. You wish.
>> It's not. I know who Red Star is. I keep
in touch with them on the phone and I
get on with them very extremely well.
And if you knew who it was, PJ, you
would [ __ ] your pants.
>> But I actually
>> I'm saying cuz it could be the C. Oh, really?
>> Might be doubt it.
How do you know PJ about it?
>> Okay, PJ, I've just had a text from Red
Star. He says he's going to confess who
he is. Do you really want to know who he
is? Seriously, I'm talking on a serious
note now. Do you want to know who Red Star is?
>> Whoever it is is a [ __ ] coward.
>> It's Mike Cariegi.
>> Yeah, of course.
>> Honest honestly, it is Cariegi.
So Cariggi has been trolling you for
years. So you're going to you're going
to meet up with not you're going to meet
up with Cariegi and have a fight?
>> Yeah, one of you need you need to grow up.
>> PJ, I'm being serious. Red start is Carnegie.
>> No, I'm being serious. You need to grow up.
>> PJ, I'm being serious. What can I do? Do
you want me to show the evidence? Do you
want me to show you the evidence that it's Carnegie?
>> You need to grow up.
>> No, no, no. You need to grow up because
you can't handle that red star. It's
Cariegi. He needs to This Timmy's a
[ __ ] [ __ ] and he
>> now honestly PJ who do you think Red
Star is? Real talk.
>> I don't [ __ ] care.
>> You do PJ cuz they trigger the [ __ ] out of me.
>> Whoever it is, it's a [ __ ] coward.
Like I said,
>> it's CargI. There we go.
>> Yeah, of course
>> it is CargI. I'm being honest.
>> Yeah, of course it is.
>> PJ, do you want me to humiliate you again?
>> You've never humiliated me.
>> I do, PJ. The whole internet humiliates you.
>> Yeah, of course.
>> So, how do you feel that Cariggi has
been trolling you under the Red Star
account for years?
>> Feels fine.
>> He shown you three grand and owned you.
>> I showed him six and owned him.
>> So, you're going to fight Cariegi on
Saturday or you a [ __ ]
>> I owned I showed him six.
>> Are you going to meet Cariegi on
Saturday or are you a [ __ ]
>> Um, yeah. I'm a [ __ ] Yeah. Are you
going to meet him? He's been trolling
you for three years in the Red Star
account. I wouldn't have I would I would
have this PJ.
>> Timmy, you need to get laid.
>> I've been laid yesterday, PJ. And the
day before and the day before,
>> you've been you've been laid yesterday,
>> PJ. I've got a misses now. I get laid regularly.
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah. It's lush, isn't it?
>> Do you really?
>> And she's blonde as well, PJ. >> Really? >> Yeah.
Timmy, you're still a virgin. You're
like nons 54. PJ,
>> you're you're a virgin like nonslegs.
You're never going to lose it.
>> PJ, you only n is you cuz you're the
only one who chats up at 14y old girls.
I chat. You and you and nonslegs never
going to lose.
>> PJ, you're the only n on here. No one
chats [ __ ] Emma Mitchell up like you and Mongol.
>> You You and You and Nons are never going
to You're never going to lose it.
>> PJ, you will never get a 54 year old girl.
>> You and Nons are never going to lose it.
I PJ I've lost it four times this week
with my 50y old [ __ ]
>> You've got to laugh at this [ __ ] clown.
>> No, we got to laugh at you that car
owned you for free. You're solid.
>> So why are you subleting to me?
>> So no, no, no, no. So why are you taking
on Prime and [ __ ] saying you're going
to beat Primer, but Car Why do you sublet?
>> No, no, no, no, no. Cariegi's been
owning your ass, but you won't fight CargI.
>> Why do you sub it? Why do you [ __ ]
let Cargi troll you?
>> Why do you sublet
>> Why do you let Cariegi troll you?
>> I don't.
>> You do. Red Star owns you. And that's Cariegi.
>> Oh, okay. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah, it is. Yeah.
>> So why do you sublet?
>> So why do So why do you let Carnegie own your ass?
>> Why do you sublet?
>> No, no, no. I don't I've never subleted
in my life, PJ, because I'm not like
you. I'm not Get yours in prison. So
anyway, anyway, you've never sub any
anyway PJ, why have you let Cariegi own
your ass for three years?
>> He hasn't.
>> He has. He's [ __ ] owned you clearly
on Red Star cuz you get triggered every 5 minutes.
>> He's the one on YouTube triggered every day.
>> You PJ,
>> for you for you to sit there on YouTube
spastics on your chat, you think they
>> For you to sit here and do for you to
sit here every day. Okay. Car. You are
triggered. You like Carnegie's text me.
He said, "You're gonna meet him on
Saturday or you gonna be a pussy?"
>> You are triggered.
>> No, no, no, no. Are you going to meet
Cariggi on Saturday or are you running away?
>> Um, I'll meet him.
>> Okay. He said 3:00 outside Big Ben.
>> Right. Be there, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> All right.
>> You're going to get I don't think
Prime's going to get the chance to beat
you up because Carig is going to put you in hospital.
How do you I mean, look on the bright
side, PJ. You've got no money. At least
you get free grub. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. And you little [ __ ] [ __ ]
trolls are going to do nothing about it. PJ,
>> no ones you talk to are [ __ ] [ __ ]
hoes like you.
>> Cari is going to put you in the
ambulance. D lad.
You're looking forward to hospital. Oh
god, my mother [ __ ] nons. Are you
going to meet me on Saturday? So I'm
going to put you in hospital like Carie
is going to put PJ in hospital and I'm
going to put you in hospital.
>> You can carry on chatting as much as you
want, lad. You're going to do nothing.
You're scared to lose your 10,
bro. Bro, go on. Get triggered, bro. Go
and get the wool out of you. Come on.
Get that wool out of you.
>> Get some blood, lad.
About time you grew up.
>> Come on. Get that [ __ ] angry wool
accent out of you, >> lad.
You got to laugh in there.
>> That wall is too scared to come to the
meeting on Saturday cuz he's going to
get a [ __ ] hospital job like you, PJ.
And you both can eat hospital chicken.
>> Proper boss nons.
>> Anyway, bro, the only nons is you.
Because if you're that bothered about
it, and I was really that, even though
I'm not, you come and meet me, you
[ __ ] clown. You are a [ __ ] Even a
nons would beat you up. That's the
embarrassment of the UK and the police
force of this country because you would
let a nons hurt a hurt a kid because you
are a [ __ ] Daz.
>> No, no, no. You're not a [ __ ] Why
don't you come and meet me? I came to
Welsh pool and you were using [ __ ]
excuses. Now everybody on the internet
knows a nons would own your ass. And
that's [ __ ] tragic.
>> You give alcohol to kids, lad. like you
get owned by all the wrongs cuz you're
full of [ __ ]
>> You're the biggest wrong in here.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You're like you're full of
[ __ ] mate. See you on Saturday. I'm
ignoring you now, Bacon. I'm ignoring
you and I'm talking to PJ. See you soon.
>> Anyway, PJ. Yeah, PJ. Anyway, PJ, are
you going to meet CargI on Saturday or not?
>> Put your camera on. Are you going to
meet Cariegi on Saturday or is Carnegie?
>> Put your camera on.
>> Bro, look at the state of PJ, man. Have
you had a shave?
>> No, don't shave, lad.
>> Why don't you shave, bro? That looks
like Bin Laden. [Laughter]
>> This guy's a [ __ ] isn't it?
>> This guy's [ __ ] owning you, lads. >> No.
>> Anyway, Bong. Anyway, PJ, so it's not
going to look good for you. Got Cariggi
wants to kick your ass and now you've
got [ __ ] points.
>> What I mean? This guy's a [ __ ] man.
>> You're the [ __ ] mate. Carig [ __ ]
trolling you. Cariggi is going to get
>> Yeah, you're [ __ ] Timmy.
Timmy can't put his camera on like me.
Red Star can't put his camera on like me.
I'm meeting that woman on Saturday, Steven.
You know that one you saw me with in the video?
Yeah, she wants to meet on Saturday. So,
[ __ ] it. I'll meet the [ __ ] in it [Music]
cuz I might go out Saturday, but yeah, I
was going to go out tomorrow, but I
think I'll go out.
Maybe I'll go out tomorrow
and still meet the [ __ ] on [Music]
Saturday. But I'll still I think I might
just go out tomorrow, bro.
>> [ __ ] it. In it. You can't exactly meet
someone and then know what I mean again. So,
I got some nice clothes to wear, lad.
Nice blazer, nice turtleneck.
But I don't know if I can even be
bothered to go out, bro. Don't know. Maybe not. experiences
are too demotivating.
Like the bad experiences with women and
[ __ ] is so demotivating, lad.
I can't be I don't know if I can be
[ __ ] you know.
Yeah. One sec.
You know what I'm saying?
I hate life game. Life sucks. I want to
die in here. I hate life.
I don't even want to go out. I've got
the money to [ __ ] go out. I don't
even know why I need to say that [ __ ]
Everyone knows I got [ __ ] money to go
out, but don't [ __ ] be bothered, man.
I'm saying I don't know if I can
actually be asked sucks.
I hate going out seeing couples, seeing
people. I grew to hate people as I got
older. As I got older, I really grew to
hate people, you know.
Yeah, it's even a joke. I actually did. Nah.
So what I'm saying, Jane,
you kind of go to hate people, hate
women and [ __ ] You actually do. As you
get older, you do.
Where's the family at? Three weeks ago.
Three weeks. Three weeks.
I I don't know if I can be bothered to go out
to be honest with you.
It's too depressing, bro.
You know, I have no hope anyway, so
there's no point even going out.
You get to that stage in life where you
just give up. You know,
that's what I'm like. can just give up life
like I don't know what other people see
like what what annoys you people what you see
it annoys me seeing like pregnant women
couples and stuff it triggers me it's
It's a trigger.
That's why I don't really go out much anymore.
Didn't leave the house today, did I?
It's a trigger trigger point.
I don't know if I can be bothered, bro. You know. Yeah.
It's one of them in it.
Yeah, it's a trigger for me. Yeah. And
that's all and that's enough.
Get his get his money stopped.
Oh, I could do. You know what I find so
funny? How they go on like £13,000 is
life is a life-changing amount of money
when in reality it's not even that much.
People go on 13 grand for it's not even
that. It's not even a life-changing
amount of money.
But yeah, they will call him up and that
is it. So yeah, I could do actually. I
could actually do that. Yeah, cuz then
he'll get grief in it like they done to me. Yeah.
Yeah, I could do that actually. I know
his date of birth and everything.
Yeah, I might report him actually. Yeah.
Yeah. You tell me. Yeah. Go on then,
Jane. Try and tell me. >> Yeah.
But yeah, I could do because they done
it to me, didn't they? Where the benefit
people's calling me up. Yeah, I might I
could I might report him, you know. Yeah.
Send them screenshots and [ __ ] Yeah. Do
what they've done for you. Yeah, I might do actually.
Even though it's not even a big amount
of money, but still. Yeah, they'll be on
his case. Yeah, I might do that actually. Yeah,
they want to try and grasp on me a
million times. But do you know the bias
now, Stephen Hour? Do you know what's
going to happen now if you do that? All
of these people are going to call you a
grass. This is why I don't like this
narcissistic place, this narcissistic evil place.
That's why I really hope that, you know,
Prime does actually meet me on Monday,
cuz I'm going to [ __ ] whoop his ass,
bro. I really hope he does meet me on
Monday. I'm going to whoop his ass.
I'm going to give him a good
oldfashioned ass whooping, lad.
I'm my own worst enemy. Yeah, you keep
telling yourself that.
Yeah, he I know he's a grass, but no one
Well, like I was saying, bro, these
people here are biased.
So, we know he's a grass, but no one on
here is going to say anything
cuz, you know,
Yeah, they're biased. So, Mhm.
That's what they do on here.
But yeah, I don't know if I can be
bothered going out. I feel like I've had
enough bad experiences to last me a lifetime.
So, I don't know. It probably work to be honest.
I can't remember the last time I brushed my teeth.
There's just no point.
There's no point doing [ __ ] all.
That's what they That's what they're
like on here, lad.
All right, Stephen Howard, you report
him as well. I'm going to report him,
but you should report him as well. I'm
going to get my mom to report him as
well and get everyone to report him.
Just so like the benefit people give him
[ __ ] like they gave me [ __ ] Yeah, [ __ ]
it. Damn right, bro.
Damn [ __ ] right, bro. Might as well it. Yeah,
that's what they done to me, bro.
[ __ ] like two times.
[ __ ] mad inconvenience.
21st of February 1995. Nons.
And also show them where he's leaving
the company. Um, show him where show
them where he's um
where he's uh leaving the country as well.
Show them where he's leaving the country.
Make sure you report the [ __ ] though.
Yeah, cuz I'm going to report him. Not
cuz I'm Dallas. I don't care about 13
grand. I just want him to get his [ __ ]
cuz he's a nasty little grass.
Oh, but it's okay for people to grasp on
me. You see what I'm saying? This is
exactly what I'm saying. This is the
narcissist coming out. You know how when
these people grasp on me, right, they
have no opinion. They don't care. And as
soon as you, this is what I'm saying
with the narcissism. Remember what I was
saying earlier with the biasless with
these people. It's okay for them to do
this is what I'm saying. This is exactly
what I'm talking about. It's okay for
these people to grass. No questions. And
as soon as you say it, you're a grass.
Yo, they're narcissists. This is what
I'm saying with this community. This is
exactly what I'm saying about this
horrible narcissist community. I hope
this prime comes on Monday so I can
really whoop his ass. I really hope this
guy meets me on Monday. I'm going to be
live all day. Yeah, but why don't you
call them a grass for grass on me? What
about when they grasp on me, Mike? Huh?
You never had any problems them and they
were grassing on me, you narcissist.
There's a lot of narcissists on here,
bro. Yeah, there's a lot of narcissists
on here, bro. It's unbelievable. Yeah,
just say that you are a grass. Just say
that you're doing what they do. Just say
that you're doing what they do. Yeah,
you're you're not a grass. You're doing
exactly what they do. [ __ ] with him,
bro. And show them where he's like
leaving the country. Try and get the
cunt's money stopped. The nasty little ratfaced virgin.
Show them. Show them that bum change. £13,000
and um tried to get his money stopped.
Show them the bum change. £13,000. Could
bum change. It's nowhere near as m as as
much as these people are making out to be [ __ ]
[ __ ] hell, bro. Yeah,
right. I need to make a cup of [ __ ]
Right. So, I'll be right back. Yeah. 26. >> Yeah.
What is wrong with this Reddit?
Yeah, it's too depressing, bro.
I think I've had my time and money
wasted enough by these [ __ ] I don't
even think I'd even go out, bro. [Music] Oh, [ __ ] Yeah. Madness ladder.
I'm not going to go out. I've decided.
Yeah, I'm going to stick to my guns
cuz it's the same [ __ ] with these women
and I think we've wasted enough money
and we've wasted um
enough time on it. I think we're Yeah, man.
I think we're where we need to be now. Yeah, therefore,
they're just all [ __ ] All of them are
[ __ ] I don't want nothing to do with
any of them. They're all the same.
They're all [ __ ] stuck up [ __ ]
[ __ ] and I'm done with them.
Maybe go see King or something. Yeah.
Just the same [ __ ] behavior.
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] behavior. Yeah.
Yeah. I was going to put some clothes in
a wash for like Saturday or tomorrow,
but nah, I'm all good, bro. I'm sound.
I'm all right. I do need to do some watching, though.
Yeah, it sucks when you've truly given
up with life.
Does generally suck, isn't it? Mhm.
Yep. 21st of Feb.
And his middle name is David, by the
way. His middle name is David.
Yeah. His middle name is David.
Uh, no. I'm not doctoring that. I I'll
continue what I want to do. Um, so
I can't believe I'll be the one like
actually flaking this time cuz usually
it's us that flake,
but there usually it's us that flake.
usually extend that plate, but now it's us.
Yeah. Stop giving [ __ ] attitude then.
She's like, "Oh, stop calling me a
cunt." Well, stop giving [ __ ] attitude.
Stop giving punty attitude. No saying
Women are [ __ ] Jane. They really,
really are [ __ ] I [ __ ] hate him. Yeah.
Yeah. These women are all the same.
They're all the damn same, bro. Yeah.
There you go.
Yeah, I'm not going on dates anymore.
Been there, done it, worn the t-shirt. Yeah. Heat.
It is Thursday, ain't it?
I've not had a drink for like weeks,
Jane. I think I've given up the
drinking, you know.
And like I said, I was looking this up
and it seems a lot of people have um
given up going out and drinking at 28, 27.
I've given up with it. Me
giving up with women. Giving up with
drinking. Giving up with going out.
I don't like to be around people.
Feels like Friday, doesn't it? I don't
even like being around people. I hate
I might do a video later,
you know. I might do a video later.
I'm going to do I might do a little presentation, Jane.
A little uh presentation.
You like my little presentations, is it?
I don't like seeing couples and pregnant
people and [ __ ] It's torment. Who's that? Listen.
I'm not acting like an adult.
What the [ __ ]
These people don't know what it's like
to be in your shoes, Jane.
By you, I mean me. So,
so yeah, I'll just chill, I think. Yeah,
just chilling, man.
Yeah, I might go for a walk tomorrow, but that's it.
You know, I sleep in Yeah, I sleep until
like [ __ ] 1:00, you know.
I sleep until like 1:00
cuz I never used to sleep until 1:00,
but I sleep until 1, you know. Yeah.
Yeah. I won't be going out tomorrow or Saturday
even though this person wants to meet.
I'm wasting my time. Don't waste my money. you know.
Yeah, it's a [ __ ] life, man.
It's a [ __ ] life. Yeah,
women are the same. All the same.
I think it's funny.
I get some money tomorrow as well and
the next day.
I've still got money now, but I just
can't be bothered wasting it, you know? Yes, sir. Yeah,
if they if they called you a misogynist,
then fair point.
>> But you've got every right to be a
misogynist after your bad experiences.
You have every right to hate women. You
know, everything that you've been
through with them and [ __ ]
You have every right to hate them.
How much do you spend on a night out
drinking, Sun-Kissed? I spend about 100 120.
>> Yeah, I won't be doing that tomorrow. Yeah.
Tomorrow I might be going for
Yeah. a walk.
Yeah. Like son, I've got money. I can go out
if I wanted to, but I just don't want to
waste my time anymore. All women are the same.
Feel like I'm I can't be bothered with
it anymore, bro.
Yeah. In London you spend about 70 80 I reckon.
I hate even reading up stories where
people have had children and [ __ ] cuz a
lot of the people on uh Reddit said they
stopped drinking because they had kids. So
I don't like reading up that kind of
stuff, bro. But yeah, I'm addicted to
Reddit at the same time.
just [ __ ] behavior.
Once you've met one, you've met them all.
They're all [ __ ] All of them are
I remember, right? I uh
I tell you a date I went on before,
right? And I knew, see, this is how I
know all this [ __ ] that I knew they were
going to be a [ __ ]
Do you know why um Sun-kissed? Cuz this
is going to be very hard to explain to
someone that doesn't know this, but when
I even little things like this, I said,
"Oh, oh, it's fine. I'll buy you a
wine." They said, "Oh, you don't need
to. It's not necessary." That in itself,
for somebody to say that, you knew they
were just going to be a [ __ ]
Um, sounds ridiculous but true. You
know, you know, little things that they
say, their little matterisms, how you
just know they're a [ __ ] and that is it
gives off the vibe that
um it's hard to explain it. Like
it's kind of like a stuck up vibe.
It's hard to explain. Um, but even
little things like that, you know,
they're all just you know what they're
going to be like. So,
just time wasters.
I mean, yeah, they're all the same.
I've heard that one before. I'm not
interested. I'm sorry. I've heard that one before.
I said to this person, "Oh, let me show
you my experiences. I'm not interested.
I'm sorry. I heard that one before. I'm
guessing you're American, right?"
Let me ask them.
Uh, they're all the same. This is why I
don't even waste my [ __ ] time on them
anymore, bro. And I'm not even going to
meet this one because they're all the [ __ ] same.
Women are all the same. Literally,
women are all the [ __ ] same. Yeah.
Women are all the same.
Wadley, women are all the [ __ ] same.
I know you got hating on Timmy, but still. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, I won't be going out
tomorrow or Saturday.
Next I'll be out is Monday to kick the
[ __ ] out of that prime.
I go to sleep very late now. Like 6:00
in the morning.
Yeah, I go to sleep about 6:00 in the morning now.
Um or 7, maybe even seven. I go sleep
about 7, you know. Yeah.
I don't like being around them. I already ate.
I already ate, bro.
Yeah, I don't like being around them.
I don't even like being around them.
these women. So,
looks like the next three days
depressing in bed, isn't it? Mad life in
it, bro. I can't wait for it to end.
They're just all [ __ ]
I had some chicken and rice.
Get some chicken nuggets. Maybe I can
get some nuggets from McDonald's. But
no, I can't be asked. I'm all right. I ate. So,
I woke up at like 2:00 today, man. Did I
go to bed at like 7?
I watch these like incel videos and then
just go to sleep.
Sad life. Sad life.
Sad depressing life. E.
Can't wait for it to end. Bro,
this life sucks.
women are all the same.
I remember when I used to meet non legs
and he says, "You don't know all women."
I said, "I don't care. They're all the
same." But you know, I used to say the
same [ __ ] when I used to meet him.
Three years and no life experience. just
for 13 grand ain't worth it, bro. You
can't put a price on life experiences.
Yeah, you can't you can't put a price on
life experiences, lad. I mean,
how come people live like that though?
bored and not go out and [ __ ] during
your prime years. I don't know how
people can live like that though.
I don't know how people can actually
live like that. Do you? No.
Yeah, Liam, I won't be going out
tomorrow and I won't be going out the next day. Pointless.
I'm just ready to give up my life now. I think
if anyone wants this date, they can have
it. I already know the result. Why do
you even go on a date when you already
know the result?
There's literally no point in even going
out drinking anymore, is there?
I don't even like being around people,
you know, especially women. I don't like
being around people.
Yeah, I could do that. Yeah.
I can't believe people are going on like
£13,000 a lot of money. It's madness, isn't it?
But obviously they will cuz it's it's
them who's showing it. It's not you
that's showing it. So obviously that's why
I can't believe all these women are the
same. Liam West
can't believe all women are the same.
It's madness. All of them are the same. [ __ ]
Absolute [ __ ] [ __ ]
They don't want nothing to do with any
of them. They're all [ __ ] They've
been the same [ __ ] for years.
But I'm glad they call me a misogynist.
Even though it's completely my misogyny
is completely justified.
Yeah, but the re No, no, but what I'm
trying to say, Liam, is that is they're
making it out to be a lot because it's
somebody else showing it.
They don't spoke about on here because it's biased.
because they're biased on it. They will
say that it's a lot and no no no cuz they're biased.
So they obviously will always it doesn't
they could show £10 and they still act
like they've won. That's what they're
like on here. They're bongos. This is
why I shouldn't even really be on here
entertaining them to be honest.
Look at these people bro in their 40s
every day on YouTube calling people skin
that they don't know.
Quite pathetic if you think about it, is it?
Yeah, I'm reporting him anyways
cuz they reported me for a few things
and they called the police. So, I'm I'm
reporting the [ __ ] anyways.
And I told Steven Hour to do the same
thing as well. I'm reporting the [ __ ]
definitely. And I'll say on here, I'm
reporting. And I'm doing what they've
done. I'm doing exactly what they've
done to me. It's not even grassing. It's
what they've done to me. They've called
it benefits on me two times. Grasp me
the [ __ ] up. But where they're so
narcissistic, what I mean now, Liam, is
uh they will they will call you a grass.
This is the narcissism. Narcissism in
them. They'll call you a grass. Um you know,
why do they do this every day? Are they
like jealous or something?
What What do they get out of doing this
all day every day? Are they like jealous or something?
Like genuine question. Are they like
jealous of me or some [ __ ] Uh
I I'll tell I'll give you his uh
details. One sec.
Yeah. Report him, bro. You're not grassing.
Do what you do it, bro. Uh,
I'm doing it as well cuz he's a dirty,
stinky little grass. So, I'll do the
same thing as well. Uh,
give me the date of birth as well.
I know everyone's date of birth.
There you go.
You got that? Yeah.
Screenshot it. You got it. Yeah.
There you go. Did you get it? Yeah.
Report that [ __ ] endlessly, bro, because
they've reported me to the police.
They've reported me to the benefits.
Report the [ __ ] out of them.
Make sure you get every bit of that last
penny of that cunt's money stopped.
And I'm not jealous at all, mate. I
don't need to be jealous of a small 13
grand. I've got money. People don't know
what I've got. But it would just be lush
to see someone's money get stopped. You
know what I'm saying? since they're
never going to see the thing is these
cowboys are never going to beat you,
Liam. So, you have to do second best.
You have to do second. You have to do second best.
Yeah, you have to do what's second best.
They're never going to beat you. They're
always going to be online being a little
keyboard warrior. So,
they're always going to be a little keyboard warrior.
So, [ __ ] it.
Yeah, tell them to, bro. 100%. Yeah,
they're never going to meet you. They're
always going to be a little keyboard
warrior. So, you know, why not cross
them? Why not do what they've been doing
to you? me, you know.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
Yeah, Liam. But yeah, I don't know why
they do this every day, Liam. Don't know
why they do this weird [ __ ] every day.
Yeah, Liam. Do you know how I knew this
date I went on was a [ __ ] before? before
I'd even met her.
You want to know?
So, basically, this is going to sound
weird to you. I was explaining to this
to the other this other dude that's no
longer on here. But, so when I said to
her, "Oh, like, let me buy you a wine."
She's like, "Oh, that's not necessary."
That's how you know from the getgo
they're a [ __ ] because somebody to
somebody that talks like that is a [ __ ]
Like no person that's not full of
themselves says that. They say, "Oh, um,
no, it's all right. You know, I'll buy
my own one or you don't have to, you
know, but saying this, yeah, that just
proves that they're a cunt." For
somebody to say that, I just said, I was
like, "Oh, no. It's going to be a waste
of time." Just like all of these dates
are a waste of time.
Even that word, it's not necessary.
Like, who the [ __ ] do they think they are?
That's why I don't bother with them
anymore. They're just [ __ ]
I've got one that wants to meet me on
Saturday, but I'm not even meeting them.
They're just all [ __ ]
They're all [ __ ]
What's the point of me going on a date?
What? To hold hands with somebody that's
not even going to kiss and waste my time
and waste my money? Come on, man. Why am
I going to do that?
I hate women, man. I hate women.
You don't understand me. I actually hate them. Yeah,
I really really hate them, man.
They're [ __ ] evil.
Evil little [ __ ]
Yeah, it's all right when someone calls
me a misogynist.
Yeah, I mean I'm I've got no energy
anymore, bro, for it.
It's all right if they call me
misogynist, but I'm not an incel. Yeah,
you can call me a misogynist, but my
misogyny is justified.
No, they [ __ ] don't, mate. In their
30s. No, they don't. Even in their 40s,
they don't drop their standards. No,
they [ __ ] don't, mate.
Even [ __ ] ugly ones are [ __ ] Even
they are [ __ ] I was speaking to one um from Australia
and she was 30 something. I think she
was 32, 33.
And um she said, "Oh, she doesn't give
[ __ ] It's not her thing." So I
[ __ ] her off.
Well, I'm Well, I'm 30 in a couple of years, so
it is. It is.
It is lad.
It will never change.
It will never change. Lad,
what annoys you? But I hate seeing like
couples and pregnant people and [ __ ]
That's why I don't like going out.
Yeah. I mean, I'm glad I had that house
for 3, four years to pay for all of the
nights out I went on. Liam,
the only re the only thing that kept me
going for them years is obviously I had
that house. So, I was making money on
the house for like three, four years.
all the times I was actually going out.
So, I mean that kind of like stopped me
doing anything cuz obviously I had a
responsibility. I was better off than most people.
You know, it's you can't really complain
when you're, you know, doing nothing and
you're getting that kind of money every
month. But obviously, you know what I'm
saying? So, it's just a waste. It would
be stupid to waste your life like that.
Do you know what I'm saying? So, that's
why I just made the most of it whilst I
could. I'm 28 next month. [ __ ]
But I'm depressed. And it's not even
about money. It's just depressing.
Yeah. I'm happy I had a house for 4 years, bro. You know,
that stopped me doing Yeah.
Look, I don't want to go out drinking
ever again, bro. I hate women. I swear down. Yep.
Yeah. I was reading up like where people
um stopped drinking and a lot of people
stopped drinking at 27 28 Liam
um and uh
and um people saying how they stopped
when they got like pregnant and had a
kid and that and it was just depressing.
It was just depressing, bro. So
depressing just reading it. Yep.
Everyone's on their phones. Clean up.
Depressing life in it, lad. Mhm.
Remember that time I went to Liverpool?
It was funny, is it?
It was funny, eh?
>> Yeah, it was funny, bro.
People don't join, bro. Yep.
Just lying depressed in bed.
Same as tomorrow, same as Saturday. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] sake. A pro.
Just women and life. It's horrible. Oh, [ __ ] Yeah.
They're all the same.
Is that not working? Hold on.
What the [ __ ]
Yeah, it's [ __ ] depressing, bro.
Come up. What the [ __ ] lad?
Yeah, they're all the same women are
hating me. We all hate them.
That's what happens. It becomes [ __ ] laggy.
I'm just staying live now, bro. I'm just
staying live now.
Well, that's not going to work, is it? some reason.
Don't know why Reddit banned people.
Don't know why this Reddit banned people, lad.
say they can't get relationships and
then when somebody messages them they
don't reply. You get these women that
moan and winge. They can't get a relationship,
but then when people message them,
they're such hypocrites.
Of course, you can get a relationship.
These trolls haven't made me down.
These trolls haven't made me down at
all, bro. What the [ __ ] These people do
not bother me. That's why I come on
YouTube every day. These people, they're
not even trolls, lad. They're spastics.
They don't make me down. These little
skint middle-aged [ __ ] mongos on here
making me down. Are you mad, bro?
These people have never made me down.
These women have never uh these people
on YouTube have never made me down. Bro,
you must be [ __ ] capping, bro.
I hate them. I actually hate these [ __ ]
One sec. I need to go and do something. Hold on.
They're just repeating bastards. >> Yeah.
So, yeah, they've never made me feel um
made me down these little losers on
here. All they do is talk about
themselves. They put themselves down.
You know what I mean, lad?
Yeah. I don't even bother going out for
a drink anymore cuz of it.
Cuz what's the [ __ ] point?
So why are they sat there saying they
can't find a relationship? Then when
somebody messages them,
dating, no luck. And then when someone messages them,
nah, there's nothing to enjoy. Been
there, done it, won the t-shirt. There's
nothing to enjoy. Been there, done it,
worn the t-shirt.
I should have gave up with life a long time ago.
Should have gave up a long time ago with life.
There's nothing to enjoy. It's the same
old [ __ ] with women. I don't even
like being around people.
It [ __ ] infuriates me. Nah, I'm all
right, bro. I'm good, man. We all die in
the end anyways. So,
nothing to enjoy.
been there wonder t-shirt.
I know what's around the corner. I know
exactly what's around the corner.
Chicken shop, Chinese shop,
uh, and a grilled chicken shop.
I know exactly what's around the corner.
Nothing will ever change, lad. Nothing
will ever change. So yeah,
nothing will ever ever ever change with these women.
I hate seeing couples. I hate seeing pregnant people.
I just hate even being out in public now
because of it, you know. So yeah.
Yeah, I think if I don't go out this
week, it'll be three weeks since I've
not been out drinking. Obviously, I've
been out the house just not drinking.
So that's what it is, isn't it?
This life is dead, bro. Very dead. It's
a dead life.
I've done so much in three, four, five
years, you know,
because of my experiences with them. the
piss taken, the them pretending that
they've got a boyfriends,
uh the leading on
um the stuck upness. You every reason to
hate women. You have every reason to hate them,
you know? I don't like seeing pregnant
people. I don't like seeing couples. I
don't like even being out in public.
Like, it's that bad. I'm going to have
to change the time I go to the cinema.
Probably go on Mondays. I probably go
cinema on Mondays now when there
something comes out like maybe the
earliest so you avoid seeing it. So it's
that bad. I'll probably have to change
the times I go cinema. It's depressing
you know and obviously I've tried more
than anyone in the world as well. So how
you're feeling is completely justified.
You don't need professional help. It's justified.
You shouldn't even be in the position
that you're in.
you're in the position you're in because
of them. At the end of the day, you it's
justified and you don't need
professional help. You need better
experiences and you've had years to have
them and you haven't had them. So, at
the end of the day, it's Yeah.
So, that's it basically. That's where
we're at, lad.
No, all women are exactly the same.
Listen, listen. You won't find the one.
They're all the same, mate. I Let me Let
me tell you something, right? I don't
know how long you've been on this channel, right?
I was subleting a house for 4 years. I
was out two, three times a week going
out, approaching. I probably met about
6,000 women. Yes, women are all exactly
the same. I swear to you, God, now on my
life, that I have met more women than
anybody in the world. And they are all
the same. I'm not even joking. What do
you think someone gets up to in three years, bro?
What do you think someone gets up to in
three, four years? They get up to a lot
of [ __ ] They get up to a lot of [ __ ]
So, I mean, believe it, don't believe
it, but they are literally all exactly
the same. They do the same stuff. They
say the same stuff. If you was going to
meet someone, you would have met someone
in them four years. Considering most
people work and don't even have the time
or money to even go out.
So you would have you would have found
someone. You would have 100% found
someone in them years. It's it's
guaranteed the crazy [ __ ] I used to do.
So there's not even no hope.
You can, but I'm not going to take it
because I've tried everything. But you
can do Yeah, no problem.
You need to understand if nothing's
changed in all of these years, it's not
going to change now. Things don't
suddenly change cuz they told you that
four years ago.
So, I'm nowhere near 30.
I'm nowhere near 30. But yeah, I'm
Like, if I die, I'm happy to die now,
bro. I've been to a lot of places. I've
traveled to a lot of places in my own
little way. I don't I wouldn't give a
[ __ ] if I died, bro.
So you you would have met someone in
them four or five years.
You would have met someone in them
years. If you was going to meet
somebody, you would have found someone
by now. In all them years, considering
you tried more than anyone in the world,
there's no dismissing that. So that's it.
There was We didn't know what was around
the corner 4 years ago, lad.
like we didn't know what was around the
corner four or five years ago. But we're
in the same boat.
So you would have generally found
someone. If there was someone for you,
you would have found someone. I'm
nowhere near 30. You've been saying I'm
nearly 30 for about 4 years. So yeah,
but if it makes you feel better about
the fact that you're in your 40s, then
keep saying it, bro. Yeah, I'm almost
I'm almost 30. If that makes you feel
better about the fact that you are in
your 40s, then yeah, I'm close to 30,
lad. Yeah. Have I tried dating sites? I sure have.
Yep, I sure have, Captain. So,
yeah, I've tried ding apps. No good.
Now they're all fake profiles.
Try dating us, tried approaching.
It's completely justified
cuz it doesn't matter what people say.
It doesn't matter what people say. Talk
is talk is cheap. You know, if you if
women were really all different, you
would have found someone by now. You
would have been proved wrong a long ass
time ago. And it's not to say that
you're right or you're wrong, cuz that's
not the whole point of this. But if they
truly was if truly what was if truly
what you were saying was true, you would
have been proven wrong a long ass time
ago. You know, you put yourself in every
single position to be put to be proven
wrong. Like you put yourself in mad
positions to be proven wrong and no one
did. So, I mean, for [ __ ] sake, bro. Like,
it doesn't matter how I approach women.
If you ain't seen the videos, then, you
know, that's on you, lad.
All I know is it's the same [ __ ] and
I've lost complete and utter hope. So,
that's all that's all that counts, I guess.
But yeah, you've put yourself in um
you've all uh I put myself in positions
to have been proven wrong a million times.
But all that happens is when you
approach someone is I have a boyfriend,
I'm not interested.
Um they give their number, they play
games. Literally, it's it's always the
same. It generally is always the same [ __ ]
It never changes.
Or like if you're really lucky, you'll
get a date that just wastes your time.
And you don't need them digging
experiences. You don't need to be digged
and digged and digged even more. You
know what it's like. You know what this
what it's like, you know? So yeah,
there's legit like no hope. Like
literally none at all.
And that's sad, you know, when there's
like no hope whatsoever. That's crazy.
There's literally no hope whatsoever.
Cuz if there was, you would have found someone.
That's the truth of it.
It's not just all of a sudden going to
change. How's it going to all of a sudden change?
>> So, unless they ban social media. So, yeah.
Yeah, that's what happens when you had
so many bad experiences. Oh, [ __ ]
That's what happens when you've had so
many bad experiences with women. You do become depressing.
They're depressing. Hearing about their
makebelie boyfriends, dealing with their
[ __ ] that's depressing.
Dealing with their [ __ ] is depressing.
Trying to speak to somebody in here and
I'm not interested straight away, that's [ __ ] depressing. So yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Good for you.
What I find funny is all of the dates I
used to go on that just wasted my time. Cheers. Yeah.
Madness by madness.
So, you're saying that you're struggling
with dating and you can't find anyone?
I've messaged them to see what they'd
say and no reply.
But you said that you're um
But you said that you're dating and no
luck. Yeah, I have messaged this person.
That's crazy, isn't it? No job, no
friends, no boyfriend. Feeling like life
isn't worth it. Yet you've got people messaging you.
So then you're just moaning and you're
just complaining for the sake of complaining. Yeah.
So, you moan about not being able to
find someone and when somebody messages
you, you don't even have the decency to
apply. Well, maybe that's why you can't find anyone.
Who the [ __ ] eh?
Who the f the f?
You've been on them dating apps and you
can't find someone. Is that what you're
trying to tell me?
So, you never had a boyfriend at 20. Try
try never having a prop relationship at
28. And you actually have you actually
have options. You know, these women make
me sick. You know that these women
generally make me sick.
It actually feels like they're actually
trying to mock men that struggle
because there is no way you have not
found a guy that don't just want sex.
There is no way. I'm not buying that at
all at all. So, it's like they're
actually mocking men that actually do
struggle because that you are not
struggling. You know, you've got people
on here writing and don't just sit there
and say that they only want that, you
know, sex and stuff.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I'm
sure there is somebody that wants a
relationship, even if it's one out of
30, 40 [ __ ] people, mate.
See, that's just like a That's like a
parody. That's like somebody actually mocking someone
because there's no way in a million
years you can't find someone.
There is no way in a million years
unless you're like two out of 10. It's
like they're actually mocking the average man.
[ __ ] there's good looking men that
can't [ __ ] find anyone and you're
probably there [ __ ] going through all
of these guys.
[ __ ] get the [ __ ] out of here. So yeah. Yeah.
>> No, I'm not the problem all along. Women
are the problem all along.
That's what my approaching videos are for.
the women all 100% the same.
We'll keep going.
women are all the same.
Yeah, I was going to go on this date um
Mike P on Saturday,
but I'll save myself the tournament.
I'll never stop hating women and you
will never ever ever ever
and you will never ever ever ever ever
stop defending women. So
yeah, they are narcissists.
They are narcissists, bro.
And the fact that they think £13,000 is
life changing money, it just goes to
show how biased they are. They are narcissistic, bro.
All of them.
That's why I really want this prime to
show up on Monday so I can kick his ass.
I hope he does show up so I can kick his ass.
They are narcissistic.
They really are not sister.
They're in their 40s, right? With no
money, trying to talk about me.
Trying to sit there sit down and talk
about me, but having no money.
So, when they don't even know what I have,
just self projecting, bro. Just self
They're just self-reflecting little
virgins. That's what they are. They're boring, bro.
low life little virgins.
And it's like that what nonsle was
showing. Yeah. Even if it is 13 grand,
what have you done in 3 years? I can
tell you what I've done in 3 years. So,
do you think 3 years of doing nothing is worth £13,000?
Do you think 3 years of nothing is worth
£13,000? Bro, come on now. £13,000 on
life experiences. Which would you pick?
So that's what he was doing all of them
years sat in his little bed stick. Oh, interesting.
I couldn't be like that for 3 years in
my prime, bro. I couldn't have been like
that for three, four years in my prime.
I literally couldn't, bro.
I was up and down the [ __ ] country. I
was abroad by the time I was 23.
I couldn't do that, bro. What the [ __ ]
It takes some It takes some uh
discipline. I'll give you that.
All for 13 grand.
Come on, man. It's like four What is it?
Four grand a year. and a half four and a
half grand a year. Come on, man. What the [ __ ]
I couldn't live like that.
Yeah, that's why he stalks all of my
women that I've been with. But I hate women.
But I will never go on a date with one
again. I don't want to speak to one
again because I know what women are like.
That's [ __ ] bad, though.
You know, all of these abroad things
that he's done, Mike, I done that when I
was 23, you know.
Yeah, bro. I done that when I was 23.
Literally, when I was 23, bro.
She ain't going to join, man. She ain't
going to join. Yeah. I went abroad when
I was 23.
That was the first time I went.
And you know what else I've done that he
hasn't done? Gone on a plane.
If I if I saved up all that money that I
got, I'd have like over 100 grand. But
but the problem with it is that I'd have
no life experience. And you can't put a
price on life experience.
You understand? uh m you can't put a
life on you can't put a price on you
know life experiences
for four or five years. So
when did I go to Liverpool? I went
Liverpool. I think my mom was Yeah.
Women are evil, lad.
Yeah, this woman wants to meet me on
Saturday. You know the one I done a
video with. But I'm going to save myself the torment.
I'm going to go get my haircut and dress
up only for her to say, "Oh, you're not
my type." or I'm not interested in
dating or no. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that, bro.
Absolutely [ __ ] that. They're all [ __ ]
I remember one I went on a date with
before I offered her a drink. She said,
"Oh, that's not really necessary." What
a [ __ ] And I knew from then her just
saying that she was going to be a [ __ ]
And I was right.
I knew then I was I was right about that [ __ ]
and she turned out to be a [ __ ] They're
all [ __ ] That's why I don't bother
with them no more. >> Yeah.
It's a game to them until you play the
game back and then they play the victim, right?
>> Um Yeah. and then they start playing
victim like what these people do. I
watch a guy called Oreo man and he's 36
and he, you know, he might not be
healthy to watch but I like watching him
until like 6:00 in the morning.
That's a channel you go on when you've
given up hope.
But to be honest, he kind of brought a
lot of it on himself cuz he could have
got escorts. He could have tried a bit
more. You know, I'm I've tried
everything. You know what I'm saying?
So, I mean, and I'm 10 years younger than him.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
But some people like that never really
helped themsel whereas me obviously I
tried everything. So, I mean, people
can't say that about me, you know. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Yeah, there'll be no going out drinking
this week either. [Music]
I just had a block of cheese. Yeah, bro.
I'll be in bed all day tomorrow and the
next day and the next day
and the next day and the next day and
the next day and the next day. Yeah.
Yeah. I got some food cooked for me today. So,
I just want this life to end. It's [ __ ]
Honestly, I just want a [ __ ] life to end.
Don't know about you.
Yep. I've got some videos of my memories
and stuff from
what I've done and [ __ ] That's what I'm
saying. Nonss don't have no memories.
It was just some skin skinned little virgin
in a [ __ ] bed suit for 3 years.
That is ridiculous, bro. What the [ __ ] man? Like,
that is insane.
You think I give a [ __ ] Like, think
about it, bro. You can't take money with
you when you die, right? So, would have
you rather have done them experiences?
You never know. You could drop there
tomorrow and then sit around saving
money for for nothing cuz like
think about it, bro. Yeah.
No life experience
at [ __ ] 30.
Look at me. I've had better women,
better food, better travel, better life, better clothes.
Wouldn't you rather that than sit and be
bored just to show somebody?
See, I had the money and the life. You
don't You have a [ __ ] life.
You understand? You need a good life
to make anyone jealous. You need a good
life. You don't have a good life. You
have a [ __ ] life.
You have a kind of uh virgin life. so to speak.
Did you a [ __ ] virgin?
>> Yeah. Oh, I know, mate. Do you remember
when he was contacting USA? Is he
Never to blame, are they?
Women are never to blame, apparently.
Yeah, women are never to blame, apparently.
But they are to blame. Why wouldn't I
blame women, Mike? I've tried. I've
literally tried. I put approaches up
there. I put conversations up there. It
is women's fault. Like I know a lot of
these, you know, incels and [ __ ] they
don't try to sit there and blame women,
but don't you think what I'm saying is
justified after my considering I've met
more women than anyone in the world.
So, don't you think it's I don't don't
you think it's um warranted?
Don't you think it's justified? I think
it is. I've met a lot of women and
they're all the same. They're all [ __ ]
I mean, what the [ __ ] Yeah.
Know what I mean?
You know what I mean? Bro,
do you not think what I'm saying is right, Mike?
I think what I'm saying is right about
women being out to get me and [ __ ] I
believe it. Otherwise, I wouldn't say
something I don't believe.
If I didn't believe it, I wouldn't say
it. You know what I'm saying?
I think what I'm saying about women is right.
that they are all evil and [ __ ] I
generally generally do believe it.
Otherwise, I wouldn't say I wouldn't say
something I don't believe,
you know. I wouldn't say I do think they're evil.
Women, I generally believe it, you know.
I generally generally believe it.
They should all get [ __ ] raped. All of them.
I don't feel sorry for any of them. I
don't give a [ __ ]
They should all get raped. It's all they
actually write out.
I don't give a [ __ ]
I hate him. I don't give a [ __ ]
But yeah, they're all [ __ ] I hope
they all get raped. All women. [ __ ]
Where's that channel gone?
Hopefully he does.
What would you What would you do if you
was me, Mike, about the women thing?
You'd blame them, is it? Damn right
you'd [ __ ] blame them. often the
experiences I've had. You would blame them.
You would blame them in it.
Why are these women such [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah, mom. Native.
I just told this woman, "Fuck off."
No, I probably won't even do the
football. I'll just be staying in bed.
No, I'll just be staying in bed.
I won't be doing [ __ ] all. Maybe go for
a walk if I can be bothered.
Something like that.
I won't be doing no football bets, no
nothing. I'll just be chilling in bed.
I know. What a madness, eh?
Uh, I had his number, but I lost it and
he didn't text me anymore. Yeah. Heat.
Yeah. I won't be I don't really gamble
that much, bro.
I don't really gamble that much. So, yeah.
Yeah, I don't really gamble that much,
lads. So, yeah.
A lot too many.
The last football bet I done was £120 on
two teams and returned 380.
So it was a nice win from 120 in it. 120 to 380. Yeah.
Wish I had all my money on it.
I wish I had all my money on it, mate. that day. You know,
yeah, but they're easier to come in.
But they're easy to come in.
I've won three I've won three football
bets out of six in two months.
I done 80 return 280. Done 80 return 230.
Then I done 120 returned 380.
I think I lost 100 pound one and I've
lost a 80 one. I've won three out of
three. Three out of six.
No, she's not joining. I don't want
anything to do with this [ __ ] [ __ ]
She's a troll. Yeah.
[ __ ] life sucks, isn't it? Sun-kissed.
Life [ __ ] suck.
Why does life suck so much? Yeah.
Look at me, bro. Jeez.
Look at that beard.
That beard is mad.
should get a haircut. Really, I can't be asked.
I trying to grow a mullet as well.
Trying to grow a mullet. Don't know.
Jeez. What is long, man?
But I can't be bothered going barbers. No thanks.
I look like Bin Laden, didn't he? Yeah,
a young Afghani.
I need to brush my teeth. My teeth are
hurting, bro. I remember the last time I
brushed my teeth.
Yep, I do remember him.
He's an ugly bastard.
These people in here are weird.
You remember that account that said I'm
a jammy get? Do you remember that
account? Mike Hunt, you jammy get.
They're [ __ ] weird, isn't it, bro?
Yeah, they're weird on it, is it, bro?
You jammy get.
They're [ __ ] It is weird, bro. They're
[ __ ] weirdos on it here. Is it [Laughter]
these people in it?
I I got Monty on here and it ruined his
life. That's mad, isn't it?
Monty come on here and it ruined his life.
No. Why don't I hear anything from that slag?
What the [ __ ] Why don't I hear anything
from that slaggy bastard? Yeah,
she was a [ __ ]
Why are you speaking about her anyways?
Why are you bringing USA up? Huh?
Why are you bringing that slag up anyways?
Why are you bringing that slag up? I
hope she gets raped.
I hope she gets [ __ ] raped by her dad.
I hope she gets raped by her [ __ ] dad.
I hope her dad rapes her in a little [ __ ]
Yeah. I hope her dad rapes her in a little [ __ ]
Gets her pregnant. Yeah. I hope
I hope her dad I hope her dad rapes her
and gets her pregnant. Yeah.
[ __ ] slag, bro.
Yeah. No, I'll talk what I want.
I'll talk what I want. Actions speak
louder than words.
No. Actions speak louder than words.
Yeah. Actions speak louder than words.
I'll talk about what I want.
Oh, I've already [ __ ] her. So yeah,
women are [ __ ] scumbags, bro.
No, I don't like the [ __ ]
No, I don't like the [ __ ] And I hate
women. So, and like I said, actions
speak louder than words.
They've done actions. I've only said words.
Yeah, I'll go down what road I want to go down.
I don't give a [ __ ]
She's lucky I didn't go the first time I
was supposed to go cuz that 19year-old,
you know, I would have [ __ ] her [ __ ]
up, bro. I would have [ __ ] her [ __ ] up.
You don't even understand, bro. I would
have [ __ ] her [ __ ] right up, bro.
I hate women, you know. You don't
understand, Candy. I actually [ __ ] hate women.
They're all [ __ ]
The more I think about it, the more it
actually annoys me.
I hate him. You don't understand. And I
generally hate them, bro. Really, really do.
Women are horrible. Horrible.
Why are women so evil anyways?
What is it? Yeah. Heat. Sorry, All right.
I'll be back in like an hour. Yeah,
I'm just talking to someone. I'll be
back in like an hour.