Franklin. Oh man.
Yeah. Can't believe the simps yesterday.
She started it. Oh man,
she [ __ ] started it the batch. Yeah,
I know. I was looking forward to that
[ __ ] steak, you know. I was really
looking forward to it.
I know. At least I gave the cut the runaround.
Calmly [ __ ] virgin boy though.
[ __ ] defending them. Virgin.
Jesus Christ. I don't know how many
times I've had to say. I'm not trying to
convince people anything. I'm telling
you that you're a [ __ ] virgin. I
don't care about anyone else. I'm saying
that you are the biggest one going. I
don't give a [ __ ] about other people.
I'm not trying to convince anyone
anything. I'm tell I'm telling you
telling you what you are. [ __ ] virgin Yeah.
Yeah, bro. That's That was even ownage.
You don't even know what I was going to
do. And to be honest, she was being a
[ __ ] She started it. She started it,
bro. Trying to give people a lecture
about their appearance and trying to
make people feel insecure, lad. Yeah, man.
She started it.
She started it, lad.
She's very lucky, bro. She didn't come
out and have a steak. I would have
rinsed her. She did start it, though.
She actually did start it. She was being
a [ __ ] They weren't just some random
person that I picked up [ __ ] from the street, lad. Yeah,
she was avoided buying any drinks as well. Yeah,
look at all of these simps, bro. It's a
madness, isn't it? Look at all of them simps
defending her and they do it to men all the time.
Jesus Christ. So, I was looking forward
to that steak, bro.
Obviously, I'm not going to pay out of
my own pocket, am I? You know what I
mean? [ __ ] that. I could buy a million
steaks if I wanted to, but it tastes
better when it's free, you know? Yeah.
Yeah. She's lucky she just got a bit of
her time wasted. A little [ __ ]
She wasn't She was nasty, bro. She was
She weren't nice. I don't know why you
got people defending her. It wasn't just
a random person I picked up. I picked
up. I thought, "Oh, let me [ __ ] with
them." She was being a [ __ ]
So, just like they are all [ __ ]
Oh, I've got everything. I've got
everything, mate. I've got a whole um
I've got a whole folder. I've got 161
things. It's called harassment folder.
I've got everything, mate. Literally,
I've got everything.
Everything, buddy. 100%. I've got
everything of what this little virgin
has been doing for years and I already
sent it to my solicitor. I've got
everything. I've got the lot
and I already sent it to the solicitor as well.
No, I didn't do a bit yesterday. I wish
I did to be honest. There was a lot of
goals, wasn't there?
Yeah. He can't treat his message to a
state cuz he can't afford it. No, I was
looking right at my life experiences
again yesterday and what I done in them
four years I have in the house. Mate, I
would not trade that for 14 I would not
trade that for 13 grand. I would not
trade that for 13 grand,
bro. I would not trade it. I would not
trade that for £13,000, lad. No way. Um,
where's this folder again, bro? One sec.
Yeah, harassment folder. 161 things.
Yeah, I've got everything he's done,
bro. Don't you worry about that. Peter
Bell is on top. I've got everything this
little skinned virgin has done.
And I was looking at like the stakes,
the traveling and [ __ ] like
and the the actual thing is right
the actual thing is right is that um I
wouldn't trade I wouldn't trade that for
14 grand, lad.
Yeah, he won't have he won't have a leg
to stand on. He's [ __ ] He is
completely [ __ ] I've got everything.
Yeah. Grand a month. I've got more than
a [ __ ] grand in my [ __ ] account.
Grind a [ __ ] month. You know what I'm saying? Um,
so yeah, like
Yeah. So I was looking at things I've
done in three, four years, bro.
And I would not trade that for £13,000.
Bro, you you take memories to the grave
with you. You can't take money to the
grave with you. Simple, in it. So that's
the way I see it. Ain't it?
No, I was just tired. I was just I just
couldn't be [ __ ]
I know. I was looking forward to it, mate.
traveling, hotels, restaurants, dates I
went on, food, everything, bro. I've got
everything on my folder, bro.
You know what I'm saying?
Why did I? Cuz it's just something to do.
No, she blocked me.
She blocked me. Bro,
I'm a bully cuz I told her to gain
weight and get a boob job. But it's okay
for her to talk about my appearance,
trying to make me insecure when there's
nothing wrong with me. Okay.
Yeah, she was being a [ __ ] She was
trying to give me electric. She was
trying to tell me I need to start a
weight training program and I need to
change my hair, but there was nothing
wrong with it. What the [ __ ]
You want to [ __ ] take my money, I'll
[ __ ] take yours.
You want to take my [ __ ] money, I'll
Because it shows that she's blocked me.
Even though I blocked her cuz her picture disappeared.
She wasn't But she weren't trying to get
them drinks, was she? She wasn't trying
to get them drinks.
No, she weren't trying to get them drinks, matey.
You know what I mean? But yeah, I've got
some good memories on my phone, bro. So,
I wouldn't change it for the world. So,
I'll take the L, bro, and move on.
Simple. At least I still got money. Yes.
So, you know, the way I see it,
she was being a [ __ ] bro. She was
actually being a [ __ ] She was being a [ __ ] lad.
I've got where I took us. I've got loads
of steak restaurants, salmon
restaurants. So, I just keep them on my
phone, you know. So much approaching.
I've got everything. And it's like
you're reliving it, bro. You're reliving
it, you know? It's mad. Madness the
amount I used to do, bro. Oh my god.
Makes me feel tired now.
Makes me feel tired thinking about it.
And I I was watching that when I was in
Manchester for like two days
when I met that German guy. We got on it
together, bro. Madness.
I think I don't know. I just done it.
I don't usually do it. I think I just
done it cuz she was the only one there.
She was the only one in the bar. It was
a Sunday, so I thought, why not?
I'm so mad to think that I've been to
all of these places and then you got
Rocky Road who's never even been up
north. Not judging, doesn't make me
better. I'm not better than anyone, you know?
Yeah. You know what's so weird about
losing this house? It's not even just
the money. I've got money, you know, I
kept some money away, you know, from the
football and that. It's not even Do you
know what's so weird about it? It's just
not having it a part of your life anymore.
That's the weird thing cuz when I used
to travel, obviously I had like people
[ __ ] pay me in that. And it's not
even just that. It's like it's been a
part of your life for so many years. And
it's not it's not even just about the
money, you know? I have money. Well, I'm
not going out much now anyways cuz I
can't be bothered. But it's mad to think
that like you know you it's been such a
big part of your life for so many years.
You know when you know when people ask
you like what do you do right and you
just say I'm a landlord and you're not
even joking when you're saying you're a
landlord. It's just so mad cuz it's like
well what would you say in the future if
you do come across someone and they ask
you what you do? What are you going to
say now? It's weird.
It's mad like how it's just not a part
of your life. And it's not even it's not
just the money bro. I've got some money
away you know. It's not It's not about
that. No, I'm older now. It's just It's
just the whole thing. It's just mad this, bro. So,
it's It could be a lot worse, bro. But
I'm just happy I'm leaving now. You know,
I'm leaving in November. You know, it's
been a long time coming cuz think about
it. You know, these people on Reddit,
right? They were saying about how they
got sick of drinking at 2728. A lot of
the most common ages are 2728.
and they're saying 27 28 and they've
probably not even been out as much as
you and then you got a lot of people
saying oh I can't afford it I can't
afford it I can't afford it most people
now just can't afford it so you got
these people that stopped at 2728 even
when they could afford it you know then
they and they actually could afford it
right think about it and they actually
can afford it and they stopped at 2728
and they probably not been out nowhere
near as much as you have they probably
would have stopped at like 24 25. Wow.
It's madness, isn't it, bro? Madness.
That is mad, bro. It's so mad to think
that you was like one in a million, you
know? You didn't have to work for four
years. Don't have to work now. No, it's
just it's a good thing to look back on.
It's just mad to think that you got all
them people working. Yeah. Can't do [ __ ]
all. And then you're just chilling, bro.
Doing whatever you want to do.
You know, it's mad.
It's madness to think about it, bro.
Like, oh, I used to do it. I don't know
how I used to do it, bro.
It's crazy, isn't it? It's crazy how
it's such a one ina million thing, you know.
All right, Kevin, I was watching Oreo
Man again yesterday. He said uh he said
um he said, "Oh yeah, if Valentine's is
just a day to poke fun out of the men
that ain't wanted by nobody." What a way
to poke fun out of the men that ain't
wanted by no one.
That ain't wanted by nobody.
Yeah. What a way to make fun out of the
room that ain't wanted by nobody. I was
dead. I couldn't stop watching it, bro. Yeah.
Say I'm a delivery driver. Could you
imagine, bro? Yeah.
But no, like
Yeah, it's madness.
It's madness, bro. Is it?
It is madness.
Nope. I wouldn't trade 13 grand for
three years of experiences, matey.
I would not I would not
change it, bro. I would not change it
for [ __ ] 13 grand. No way.
Wouldn't even change it for
probably even a 100,000
cuz you can't. And And I was watching
where my little legs used to take me places.
My little legs would take me wherever, you know.
Madness, bro. It is madness, you know.
I'm I'm surprised how I put up with it
for so long, you know.
I'm surprised I put up with their [ __ ]
for so long, bro. Madness.
Madness. [ __ ] madness, man.
So yeah, when I look back on my videos,
I I regret nothing, you know?
At least you had the life to live, you know?
Like that's it. That's the way I see it.
And I still got money out of it as well.
See, when I won that football bet, I put
some money aside. So in case I want to
go out, but I probably won't go out now for
a very long time. So,
I can't be asked with it anymore, bro.
I really can't be [ __ ]
I think it started hitting me at like 26.
Yep, they would. Maybe 26.
You'd have to tell people you're a
[ __ ] delivery driver now.
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Virgin boy. Skin in the bed.
Skin in the bed seat.
Yeah, bro. I was going to I was thinking
of going out yesterday, but I was like,
nah, can't be asked. Pointless.
No point, lad.
And I realize when I'm and I realize at 27/28.
So, I kind of got But at the end of the
day, I don't regret it, though, because,
you know, I had a good life. You know,
when Antman was my age, he was eating cold beans.
He was eating cold beans. So, you know,
you need to see it like that. And got
designer clothes. I still got money and
[ __ ] So, don't mind, bro. Isn't what it
is, is it?
I realized I've realized.
But the thing is, you know, when you
when you live in London and you have
money, you know, and you you have that
money, you're not working. Who wants to
really leave the country? You
understand? Who wants to leave the
country? Think about it, bro. You're 24, 25, 26.
you know, you have this money coming in,
you're winning money all the time. Who
really wants to leave the country when
you live in somewhere like London?
That's why I didn't travel as much as I
could have. I did travel just in
smaller ways, you know, you you'd
understand what I mean.
And I still went abroad a few times as
well, but you you get what I mean, is it?
It was just fun getting a train there,
getting a train there, getting money. It
was just so, you know, you wouldn't be,
you wouldn't think about leaving the
country, bro. That would be the last
thing on your mind.
And I think because I used to get like
little successes here and there. Um,
that's probably why I thought it was
going to happen again. But
yeah, but I wish I got that steak out
yesterday. LT would have loved it. LT
and his little mates would have loved it.
LT and his little mates would have loved it.
Isn't that right?
They would have [ __ ] loved it.
I had it better than most 20 [ __ ]
three 24 year olds, mate. Trust me. And
I was watching where I used to wear my
little Air Jordan coat. My little nice
My little beige Air Jordan coat with my
little trainers. Remember the little
glittery Air Maxes?
Yeah. Madness, bro. Madness.
I live that life, bro. Trust me. Believe
you me. I used to bring a [ __ ] escort
back to that house multiple times a week, bro.
It weren't even a joke. So, yeah.
Yeah, I had to throw it out cuz of um it
got [ __ ] up in a washing machine. But
think about that. I was going gym,
getting money, doing what I wanted to
[ __ ] do. It's a good life, bro. a
very good life.
Then you feel like you really have
nothing to complain about. You know, the
more you watch these videos,
you know, you realize that, okay, well,
you learned at 28
and [ __ ] you've been doing madnesses
for years, bro. Like, what the [ __ ] Now
you can leave. Simple.
I want to start up the gym again, bro.
I want to start the gym again.
That's what I want to do. Start up the
gym again. But yeah, I do remember the
little Air Maxes I had. The little
sprinkly the sprinkly Air Maxes.
They were nice, bro.
Yeah, they were nice, lad.
That's what I'm doing, bro. I want to
build up that I want to build up that
body for it, lad.
I need to go [ __ ] gym
cuz that's the plan now. Leaving this
country, that is literally the plan. And
it's not about affordability where I can
go out when I want to go out, but I'd
rather put that money towards something
better now. You know,
I'd rather put that money towards something better.
Did you say I've gone out drinking more
than everyone in the world? Um, no.
But I'll say I've traveled the country
more than anybody my age. Max.
And then you got look and you got little
Rocky Road. He's not been passed the M25.
Who's not been passed the M25? Bless him.
Bless him then.
He's not been passed the M25. Bless him.
That's so cute. Ain't it? Bless him in life then.
Bless him. Bless him in life. Bless.
It does seem weird though. It does seem
weird. That does seem weird.
Harry's never been up north or anything.
Like, it does seem strange. Look, what
the [ __ ] was he doing for all of these years?
What actually was he doing for all of
these years? I get the going abroad
thing. Once you've done it, you've
you've you've done it. You know, all of
that [ __ ] Virgin Boy is doing. I done
that [ __ ] when I was [ __ ] 23.
But obviously his finances a his
finances aren't as good as mine. So
that's why it took him a little longer.
What the [ __ ] was he doing all of them years? Jesus.
Makes you wonder, is it?
Yeah. What about virgin boy?
I think you got a phobia. Virgin boy.
see it. You don't really have anything
to actually uh repeating.
I've already explained that. I'm not
explaining it again. Stop repeating.
How do you explain that?
a woman in Finland. So that's not even
that expensive as well.
Yeah, you saved 13 grand instead of
living your life. [ __ ] virgin.
And it's not even a life-changing amount of money.
That's the funniest thing about it.
Why do I give a [ __ ] about 13 [ __ ]
grand, bro? What the [ __ ]
I'd rather look back and say I've done
this and say I've done that and say I've
done this and say I've done that. I'd
rather look back and say I've done this
and that. Bro, what the [ __ ] You know,
life is meant to be lived,
you know. And obviously there's people
out there that are better than me, but
it's not it's not a competition.
Do you know what I'm saying? It's not a
competition, but you know,
he actually is skin. Like he didn't go
abroad until he was 30. Like he actually is skimped. Um, so
I mean I'm not a landlord anymore, but
you get what I mean.
They don't understand, bro, the money
that I used to go through. Gambling, drinking, [ __ ]
Oh my god, bro. It's insane. It's
actually insane, man.
Uh, and I don't even I haven't even have
I don't even have everything saved. So,
I don't care, bro. I can take the L.
You know, I got I got bored of the
gambling, you know, where I done it so
much. Even when I had the house, I got
bored of it. I think I'd play roulette
like every 3 months.
I where I done it so much, I got bored
of everything. It wasn't even a trigger anymore.
So yeah, I need to go gym, bro. And I
need to like go to some destinations.
That's what I need to do. That's the
only thing I care about now, bro.
And just call it an L here.
I need to I need I'm going to gamble. Um,
I'm going to gamble on um on the 20th
because I want to I want to bet on them
leagues. I'm going to get a I'm going to
get a four both score and no draw. Defo. Yeah.
I wonder how many escorts I've actually banned.
I've got to say [ __ ] maybe um
how many escorts have I banged?
A [ __ ] lot. A lot, bro.
I would even like to put a number on it, bro. [ __ ]
thought I'd be about 200 in it, which
that's another thing I've done that
other people, not not a lot of people
have done and no one my age has done it
more than me.
So, I've actually beat some Guinness
Book of Records with some of the things
I've done. Coach more women, bang more
escorts, the people my age. I don't know
about in the world, but I know like my
age, there's no way someone's bang more
escorts than me because it's so easy.
Think about it. It's so easy just to pay
and get a [ __ ] It's so easy.
It's so [ __ ] easy to do, you know?
Like, that's what people don't understand.
That's what people just don't
understand. You know how you going to
lose it? How are you going to pop it?
That's what people just don't understand, lad.
I've banged so many escorts. It is not
even a joke. I'm surprised when I went
for that test. Yeah. I didn't catch anything.
I done it in Newcastle. I've done it in
Nottingham. I've done it in Scotland. I
remember one time I went to go Scotland
on the pool. Yeah.
Didn't get [ __ ] all, bro. Banged an
escort. Went home. Madness. Didn't even
stay in a hotel overnight. Don't know
why I didn't.
Where else have I banged an escort?
Sure. I've done it in other cities.
Manchester. I've done it in Manchester as well.
Yeah, I've done Manchester,
Manchester, Nottingham, Newcastle.
Anywhere else is there. There's one. Oh,
Sheffield. I went to a brothel in Um, yeah.
You You're a longtime viewer, aren't
you? I literally banged her and went all
the way back home. I don't even know why
I didn't stay in a hotel room. I should
have stayed and just went out the Sunday
as well. I don't know why I didn't do that.
No, I don't understand what you mean. I
don't understand the question. And then
obviously I bang two escorts in Amsterdam.
You know, the more you really look at
what you've done that you ain't really
got no reason to complain
half as much. Well, you can complain,
but just not half as much of what you know
the women thing is still disgusting.
But like it's mad to think like
I have done [ __ ] those bro a lot of escorts.
The virgin boy never used to believe me
because he's still a virgin and he can't
afford escorts. And he was like, "Oh,
like why are you trying to convince
people that I'm a virgin? I'm not trying
to convince anyone you're a virgin. I'm
telling you you're a virgin cuz you're
the biggest one going
telling you your version because uh
oh 100% 1 million% bro I had chances as
well like back when I was like 14 but
obviously I I was too nervous. So, back
in the house party days, oh, 100%.
What used to happen is people would go
around [ __ ] the same woman and these
women weren't um these women weren't
picky. They would be they would get with
anyone. So, like people
used to um just [ __ ] that person for
that person. Yeah. But back then it was easy.
Back then it was so easy.
I had my first kiss when I was actually
eight, but now it's just impossible.
Oh, it was lovely. It was lovely, Grezy.
But I would have preferred the steak, to be honest.
I fancy a nice t-bone steak, you know.
I really fancy a nice t-bone steak.
Yeah, it [ __ ] everything up. Yeah.
Yeah. She was a [ __ ] She was a [ __ ]
So, [ __ ] her. I actually fancy a t-bone
steak, you know.
But the butchers is not even open. So, Yeah.
Yeah. At least you got to see waxies.
You can be there. You can if you want,
but I won't be there.
Yeah. But I won't be there.
I was watching this approaching video
yesterday of this guy. He went to
approach this woman and then this guy
tried getting involved. Ah, that's
happened to me before as well in the
street. Yeah, London's full of
[ __ ] Oh, how I don't miss going
out. Yeah, that's happened to me before.
Yeah, London [ __ ] They can't mind
their own business. Oh, I'm so glad I'm
in my little nest of calls. Yeah.
Did you like that little last message I
sent to her? You call that an ownage?
That a That ain't even an onage, mate. I
wanted a nice [ __ ] steak.
I was looking forward to that.
Nice bit of steak.
Nice bit of t-bone steak.
Pe belly was nowhere to be seen though,
Greavvesy. I was playing Franklin.
She didn't even buy the rounds. She
[ __ ] chilly [ __ ] Yeah, cuz there's
two Waxies. There's Waxy's little sister
and there's Waxy O' Connor.
So, she wanted to meet somebody to use
them to friend-zone them. What an evil
[ __ ] And I'm the bully. I'm the bully.
Normally, you get called a stalker,
Grezy. When when when you stand up for
yourself, you're normally called a
stalker, not a bully. Wow. That's interesting.
That's [ __ ] interesting. a bully.
That's a new one.
Yeah. I mean, I think the state thing
kind of made it obvious,
but I still I still gave it a run around. Yeah.
Trying to say about we're not going to
be a night and [ __ ] I'm better than
you in every single [ __ ] way. Don't
tell me I need to go to the [ __ ] gym.
Don't tell me that I need to [ __ ]
that I need to change my hair when there
was nothing wrong with my curly hair.
Wasn't even long. So, it's okay for her
to try and give me a lecture about my
appearance. Greens didn't be a [ __ ] But
I can't tell her to get a boob job and
gain weight. Oh, the double standards,
Grezy. Oh, the double standards.
I'm a bully. I remember before Fraser
told me that he went to meet a woman at
the train station and the woman didn't show up.
The woman did not show up. That is what
he told me. The woman didn't show up.
So, was that woman a bully?
He had to stay there the whole night
with his phone dead because the train
stopped running. He told me, "Bro, does
that make that does that make that uh
does that make that woman a bully?"
Just like that Italian time waster.
Been there, done it, worn the t-shirts. That t-shirt.
What do you do now? So, if you go out
and you approach someone, then what? You
get their number, they want to go on a
date with you, but then what? So, okay,
so say somebody wants to go on a date
with you. Okay, but we know what they're
going to do. They're going to waste your
time. So, I mean, what the [ __ ]
Go and go on dates to pass time.
Yeah. And he was a troll as well. He was
a troll. He was an actual big troll.
That's the maddest thing about it. He
was actually a big troll. So yeah,
why do these women go on dates, Kevin?
Why do these women go on dates?
Why do these women even go on dates with people?
I don't even understand it.
The only skint one is you, Virgin boy.
No one else, mate.
The only the only skint one is you
in your little bed sit.
Bye-bye now. Seems that way, don't it,
mate? Seems that way.
Yeah, seems that way, don't it?
It does seem that way. Definitely with
that Italian one as well.
Yeah, that one was a time waster.
Proper time waster.
That one is like there's not even no
point even going on dates anymore. Even
if you had a date schedule, there's
literally no point even going on a date with anyone, you know?
It's a madness, isn't it?
How you going to lose it? When you going
I've changed my mind. October's my
favorite month. I I like it now. It's a
little bit cold. If I go out drinking
again, I'm going to wear a nice blazer
on my little turtleneck.
Uh on the tubes, you got them up your
ass. Yeah, it's annoying, bro. It's full
of [ __ ] this country.
Like that guy trying to [ __ ] I know
what that's like when someone tries to
get involved. They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
Typical London [ __ ] starting [ __ ]
they can't finish.
Yeah, the country is full of [ __ ]
It's happened to me as well.
It's full of [ __ ] This country,
it's full of proper [ __ ]
That annoyed me watching that, you know.
And then she just said she had a boyfriend. Anyways,
so you got to do you got to deal with a
[ __ ] trying to get involved cuz he's
jealous. And then you got to deal with a
[ __ ] woman pretending she got a
boyfriend. Poor guy. Hey, poor guy. Yeah,
I really want a nice t-bone, bro. But
the [ __ ] butchers is closed. [ __ ] sake. That sucks.
That sucks, bro. [ __ ] Huh?
Yeah, I'm banned on Instagram now for
5 days. So contact for five days. It's annoying.
Hey, a ballet. Peter belly.
Yep. They're NPCs.
They're non-playing characters.
Nonplaying characters, lad.
Valentine's Day is just to poke fun out
of the men that ain't wanted by nobody,
that women ain't choosing up on. That's
what Oreo man said.
Who knows? They've all got the same
attitude as well.
What do these women have got the same attitude? Self projecting.
some different insult.
That big nose thing is getting really
really um really boring now. When are
you going to uh
you going to change up the insults?
Do you know the maddest thing is uh
Kevin? Every single time they waste
their life trying to make me insecure,
they're never getting that. They're not
getting that back. you know, all the
hours that they spend trying to make me
insecure about the way I look when they
when they're never going to make me insecure
ever. They're just wasting their life.
They're going to be sat there on their
deathbed, right? And they don't make me
insecure. They don't make me feel ugly.
I don't know why they keep doing it.
Everybody knows I'm better looking than
everybody on here that's shown their face.
It's madness. They're never getting
that. They're never getting that time
back. They're going to be sat there
like, you know, Virgin Boy and Red Star.
All of this time that they're wasting
for years, they're never going to get
that back. And all they're doing is bothering themselves.
Like, they're not bothering me. They're
not making me insecure. You don't see me
not showing my face. I can show my face right now.
See, there we go, bro.
Oh, apparently I'm boarding, by the way.
Yeah, that's interesting. I didn't know
I was bored.
There we go.
Laughing at me, bro. [ __ ] you. At least
I can show my face unlike you.
Stop laughing at me. That's not nice.
Yeah, I know, bro. They waste their
life. It's like um it's like Virgin Boy
when he was saying about, "Oh, why don't
you bully a man?" Same question goes to
you and your [ __ ] boyfriend.
Why don't you why don't you bully a man
instead of sat on YouTube every day
recording [ __ ] like a loser? Why don't
you Why don't you Why don't you um
you know, why don't you face a man? And
the thing is the thing is, Kevin, is
that they don't bully anyone. They don't
bother anyone. They just make a fool of
themselves by showing themselves up.
That's all they do. They just They just
make a fool of themselves.
They literally don't bother no one. They
don't make anyone insecure. They don't
stop people showing their face.
Yep. You're talking about yourself. Nope.
Yep. No hope of jobless. You're talking about yourself.
I saw the thing where Red Stars try to
desperately convince himself that I'm
bored. I saw that, bro. I've never seen
somebody so desperate to convince
themsself that someone's bored.
I've never known someone so desperate. It's madness.
He must actually be bored.
He's going to give my nose a thumb. Oh,
that's nice. He never done that. The
last three times I went to his virgin area
when he when I went to his skint virgin area.
Sat on YouTube all day recording. That
just goes to show that it's jealousy.
Who the [ __ ] has time to do that all
day, bro? [ __ ] hell.
Yeah. Guess what? The strawberry face
can show his face. You can't show your
face. You're too ugly. That's something
that you'll always have on these people.
That's something you'll always have on
these people is that they can't show
their face cuz they're ugly.
Cuz they're too ugly to show their face.
Yeah. Some madness, bro.
Yeah. He's a virgin. He's just a little lowife virgin.
And I don't care if you show me Bye-bye.
I don't care if you show me some [ __ ]
some [ __ ] disabled girl.
Yeah, all good, bro. Just chilling, man.
We just talk about these little self-reflectors.
I look sick. Do I?
Oh, look how good looking I am compared
to N's legs. Even with a long beard,
I look sick. Not at all. I look fine.
Look at that beard, man.
Virgin boy can't grow a beard.
Virgin boy can't grow a beard. Nah.
Oh, [ __ ] it up, bro.
Yeah, something like that.
I look like I have downs a bit.
Really? Thank you, man. Why don't you
come and show your face?
Oh, really? I'll put the link in. Let's
see if you can show your face. One
second. Don't be rude of me not to.
I look like I got downs a bit.
One second. That's nice for you, man.
Right. Let's see your face.
Come on. We're waiting for you.
I want to see a uh I want to see a
handsome looking man.
Come on. Let's see your face.
You started on me.
No, no, no, no, no. I know. I'm telling
you to come and show your face. I I
know. I know. I know. I'm asking you to
come and show your face. Come on. Don't
be scared. I know. And I'm telling you
you're a fat ugly bastard and you can't
prove me otherwise. And I'm telling you
that you're a fat ugly bastard with no hair.
Woman in Finland bin me off. Don't know
what you're talking about. She wants to
meet me. I'm going to Finland very soon.
Anyways, come and show your face. Come
on, show your face. Stop running away.
So what? You You What's the point of it
then? So you start [ __ ] on people, but
then you can't show your face cuz you're
the ugly one. So you come on here with
your ugly self talking about someone
that's better looking than you and then
they put the link up and you run away.
What a loser. I could never imagine
being that much of a loser.
No woman from Finland's bit me off,
you know. Anyways, show your face
anyways. Or I'm going to block you. If
you don't come and show your face, I'm
going to block you. I want to see your
ugly face. Come on. I need a laugh.
These people, Kevin, that try to call
other people, they're fat and ugly. They
got no life. They can't stand someone
better looking than them. Why do you
think, bro, these people sit on here and
do this every day? They can't stand the
fact you're better looking than them. It
kills them. That's why they do all of
this [ __ ] Oh, you look like this. You
look like Well, you're better looking
than them. They're fat, ugly people. Fat
ugly people that you're better looking
than, you got more money than, and
they're trying to [ __ ] talk about
you. It's madness. What the [ __ ]
More money, better looking, better life.
It's the truth.
God's honest truth, lad. The link's
there, man. The link's there. Uh,
these people can't show their face.
They're too ugly.
Yeah, I ain't got no money, bro. Okay.
Are you going to come in and show your
face or not?
money? Are you going to come in and show
your face or not? I'm waiting for you, bro.
Yeah. So, you're So, you're not going to
come in and show your face? Exactly.
because you're an ugly bastard and I've
got more money than you will ever have.
Again, you don't know what people have.
Which is exactly what I had to tell this
woman in Dubai. I've got more money than
you will ever have. You ain't got
nothing. That's why every single time
people show you money, you run away cuz
you are the ugly one with nothing. Sat
on YouTube, a little keyboard warrior,
all in your 40s cuz you ain't got [ __ ] life.
To my mom's, bro, listen, you can send
letters to anyone. No one cares about
your little letters. Nobody cares about
your letters. You can send whatever you
want. No one cares about your letters.
You ugly man. You ugly no woman no money
man. Ugly no woman no money man. Yeah,
bro. People know that I'm a N. Do they?
Really? Why do you come and meet me
today then? Why do you come and meet me
today then if I'm a N? Huh?
You s little ugly man. Ugly man. This is
what happens with these people, right?
This is what happens when you end up
like, you don't want to end up like
these people, bro. In their [ __ ] 40s,
[ __ ] ugly on YouTube, no life,
[ __ ] ugly, ain't got no money. This
is why they do this. This is why I've
got people that are going after me. They
hate the fact that you're better looking
than them. They're sat at home ugly with
no money, ain't got nothing but an app
every day. Ain't got nothing but a
YouTube app with their ugly selves, ugly
lives, no money. That's why they're
coming here. Yeah, that's you, bro.
You're talking about yourself. No money,
no woman. All of these things I've
already shown, I've already had. You
can't even show your face cuz you're
ugly. So, yeah, you can say no woman, no
money. That's you. That's your life. You
ain't got no money and you've never had
a woman. You're still a virgin.
Yeah, man. That's you. No money, no
woman. That's your life. The 40y old
virgin you life.
>> That's you you're talking about. No
money, no life, no looks, ugly as [ __ ]
That's you, bro. No one else. That's
yourself you're talking about. Sat on
YouTube and ugly no hopeer talking [ __ ]
to someone half your [ __ ] age. I
mean, bro, like, you could sit there and
try to talk about other people's face,
but you can't even come on and show your
face cuz you're too ugly. I love I love
having that over these people, right?
You can't show your face because you're
an ugly bastard and they can't prove me
wrong because what I'm saying is the
truth. What I'm saying about them is the
truth. They're sat on YouTube. No life,
no money, no woman, no hope, no job.
These are all these people in their 40s.
It's their 40year-old selves that
they're talking about. We're lying about
a woman in Finland. Mate, we're not all
ugly like you and skint like you. We can
actually go out and do things, mate.
We're not all ugly and skint like you
little bastards sat on YouTube, no
money, no life, no looks. You got me
[ __ ] saying it now. Basically, this
this community, Kevin, right, is where
people come on when they failed in life.
40, no life, no woman, no hope, no
money. They come on here and try to talk
about other people.
I can't go out unless I win a bet. I can
go out right now if I wanted to. I can
go out right now if I wanted to. No
money, no life, no future, no job, no
prospects. That's them. That's literally
themselves they're talking about. They
use this community to talk about
themselves. It makes themselves feel better.
Yeah. I can't go out unless I win a bet. Delayed.
I can't go out unless I win a bet. But I
can go out right now if I wanted to.
Funny enough, I'm actually going out in a minute. Yeah.
Well, I can't go out and spend £100.
Oh, bro, if you hear yourself,
I can't go out and spend £100.
Why can't I go out and spend £100, bro?
What the [ __ ]
Why can't I go out and spend £150? Why
not? We're not all skint
allint like you, matey.
We're not all skint, matey. Anyways, why
are you not coming up and showing your
face? Is it cuz you're too ugly?
Oh, [ __ ] Go a minute. Why are you not
coming in? Too
miserable. You are
It was raining again. Oh
yeah. Repeating is your lives. Sat on
YouTube repeating every single day. Yeah, man.
Yeah, that's you.
That's you. So, you're not coming in and
showing your face then?
So, you're not coming in and showing your face?
Oh, man. It's just so comfy, this combination.
So, you're not So, you're not going to
come in and show your face.
So, you're not you're not you're not
going to come in and show your face then
because you're too ugly. Okay. Interesting.
LJ doesn't have no money. He's got fools
like [ __ ] He's got fools like [ __ ]
LT and other people believing that he's
got money, but he doesn't have money.
He's the definition of skint. He doesn't
have money. Just like none of these
people on here have got money. So, yeah.
Daily walk. Yeah. You know how it is.
The guy literally has nothing. It makes
me laugh, you know, bro. Like people on
here actually cuz when have I ever said
that I'm rich. Yeah. I said I can go out
when I want.
Looks is not everything. You keep
telling yourself that if it makes
yourself feel better about the fact that
you people are ugly.
Yeah. Yeah. It's so mad cuz like you
people in your 40s, you got no money,
you got no life, you got no looks, and
you're trying to talk about me, bro.
My bets on I won't show. Well, bro, your
bet is wrong. Well, your Okay, I can bet
you I bet you £1,000 right now that I
will show and I want £4,000 if I don't.
How about we put £1,000 on it?
Yeah, let's put £1,000 on it that I will
show. Bro, I went to the guy's city last
month and he didn't show up. Why is he
going to come to London? Use your
[ __ ] head, bro. Why am I not going to
show? I was in his city last month. He
didn't come out. So, I want my £4,000
tomorrow. Yeah, simple.
Let's bet on it then. Do you actually
really want to bet? Do you Do you
actually really want to bet? Okay, I'll
bet you £1,000 then.
Okay. So, I want that bank transfer
tomorrow when I show up and he doesn't.
Yeah. He said he's going to come on my
live stream in Crystal Palace and I need
to go to Crystal Palace.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. So, you you're going
to give me my you're going to give me my
money tomorrow? Yeah,
you bet me a one. No, let's bet a
thousand. Why you not? Why? Why? Why
don't you bet a thousand? Let's bet a
thousand. Come on, I want to. Nah, man.
Let's do a little bit more than that.
Let's do a thousand. Let's bet a
No, no, no. Let's bet a thousand.
Nah, bro. Let's bet a thousand. Come on.
What? You don't want to bet a thousand, bro? Why?
Let's bet a thousand.
I will give you £1,000. I'll give you
Of course, I will. I'm not going to bet
if I don't mean it. I will give you £1,000.
Oh, another thing is, bro, I you know,
and I'll tell you about the Terry thing,
by the way, in case you didn't in case I
don't think we've spoke since then. You
know, when I was mad and stuff, I said I
was going to go to Terry cuz he was
pissing me off and stuff. Do you
remember he was pissing me off? Maybe
you don't remember, but yeah, he was
pissing me off and [ __ ] And then the
reason I didn't go is because I calmed
down and realized what you all do on
here. So like I admitted it. I said,
"Yeah, I'm not going today because of
what you people do. You all take L's and
forget you took L's." You know what I'm
saying? So yeah, like that's that's it.
So that's it, bro. Which I should have
done a bet to be honest because we all
know like if you actually are serious
about this bet, I will give you £1,000.
It's not a problem.
It's not a problem at all.
That's what we need to start doing. We
need to start doing this betting, bro.
But yeah, I knew that he weren't going
to show up because he didn't show up
last time. But you people like to forget
that. So, you know, you like to forget
L's that you've took.
Especially Mark Samson. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah. Especially that Mark Samson. Yeah.
You love to forget L's that you've took.
I've took more L's than anybody, bro. I
went to Mark Samson's area two times.
The last time I showed up to Terry, he
didn't show up. I went to [ __ ] Nons's
area um three times. He didn't show up.
But you don't you don't you don't forget
that, do you? And bro, I want this crime
to show up tomorrow cuz I'm going to
smash his [ __ ] face in. I'm going to
smash his [ __ ] face in. Are you also
forgetting that these people that have
took L's from me have actually begged
you to do their dirty work? Red Star
Lots. Isn't that funny? Isn't that funny
how these people, these same cowboys
have begged you to do their dirty work?
You know what I mean?
Bro, LJ does not have money. I don't
know why he keeps pretending that he's
got money. He does not have money, bro.
I could go out right now and buy two
2,000 pair of shoes. That doesn't mean
that I have lots and lots and lots of
money. He he he m he wants you to think
that he's got money. He doesn't have
money. There's nothing about him that
says that he's got money. Anybody can
buy a pair of trainers, bro.
You know what I'm saying? He has not got
no money. I don't know why he he might
like to convince you that he's got money
and bro, there's nothing rich about that guy.
Same thing with [ __ ] Launch Legs.
£13,000 for not living a life for three
years, bro. You wouldn't even tempt me
to give my life experiences away for that.
So that's it, bro. And I know he's bank
manager. I'm just telling you, he ain't
got as much money as he says he does cuz
he doesn't have money. Well, cuz he buys
what, three 400 pound trainers, bro.
Anybody can do that. You could even do
that on benefits. You know what I'm
saying? There's nothing. He likes to
betray a life that he doesn't live,
which is something that I I don't do.
You know what I'm saying? I'm honest
about everything. He doesn't have money.
What? Because he went to because it took
him two years to save up to go to Vegas,
that means he's rich, bro. Come on. Get
Think about what you're saying. The lies
that he says doesn't even make sense.
Oh, I've got six properties, bro. It
doesn't even make sense. Anything he
says does not even make sense.
You know what I mean?
It just doesn't make no sense, lad. Oh. So, yeah.
Be trading for tomorrow. Nah, cuz
tomorrow's not happening. It's the same
thing with you [ __ ] See, this is
what I don't understand with this prime.
Yeah. He says that he's took a W. So,
why does he keep coming on here saying,
"Oh, I'm going to catch you when I catch
you." He's doing this is what makes him
look like a tip because he comes on
here, right, and he says, "Oh, I'm going
to catch you when I catch you. I'm going
to do this. I'm going to do that." But
then when you're actually in the guy's
area, he shits it, which the reason I
called him out is cuz he kept trying it
with me again. So, I was like, "Okay,
well, you want to take that W that you
took back and then it's just the same
round and round and round in circles
again with you people, bro. It's madness."
Like if I if I gave somebody a proper L
like that, bro, I would just never
bother with them again.
So I mean, is it the fact that he wish
he'd done something? He wish he hit me
because nothing he says makes sense.
Oh, I didn't hit you because you're
disabled, bro. If that was the case,
then he wouldn't even be trying to meet
you again. He wouldn't even be bothering
with you again.
You know what I'm saying? With nonlegs,
I just get addicted to the stupidity and
the simp. It's funny as [ __ ] you know.
I shouldn't even be bothering with that virgin. You know,
madness. It is a madness. It honestly is
the biggest madness ever.
Yeah. Yeah. Excuse after excuse after
excuse. Excuses. I've heard all of this
before, mate. Yeah. You've gone to this
place unannounced. It's excuses, mate.
Listen, I was in Birmingham for almost
24 hours. That excuse doesn't wash. That
excuse does not wash. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. I've shown money as well, funny
enough, but you probably forgot about
that because it doesn't suit you to
remember it. Yeah, I've shown money as
well, funny enough. Yeah, more money
than any user ever shown in cash, but
you don't seem to remember that cuz it
don't suit you. Um, yeah, that's that's
just an excuse that you use. Oh, there's
no there's no there's no advanced
notice. No, no, no, no, no. [ __ ] off
with that [ __ ] Get the [ __ ] out of
here, bro. When T T T T T T T T T T T T
T T T T T T T T T T T T T T T T T T T T
T T T T T T T T Tiger and Timmy came to
London, was was there any notice? No,
there wasn't no notice. No, there
wasn't. And yes, actually, there was
notice to be honest with you because I
said I was going to go to Birmingham. I
said to Monty, I was going to go to
Birmingham for the past four or five
hours. Actually, yeah, there was no
there was notice actually. Yeah, there was notice.
You know what I mean?
I make the most excuses, bro. You're
making excuses. Oh. Oh yeah. Well, um,
you come unannouncing. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, bro. Stop talking [ __ ]
Just like when I went to [ __ ] bomb.
He was watching the whole time. It's
just excuses with you people, bro.
Anyways, I want my £4,000 tomorrow.
Anyways. Yeah. When I show up, I want my
four grand tomorrow. Yeah. And you're
not getting your,000 because I'm showing
up. So, yeah. Yeah. Simple.
Yeah. Remember, remember that. Yeah.
So, I want my four grand tomorrow,
please. Yeah. Thank you. I want a bank
transfer. I'll give you my bank details. Yeah.
See, you can't even bet a grand, bro,
cuz you know you're going to lose.
That's the thing. You know you're going
to lose, lad. Well, I'm going to go live
and he's going to tell me when he's in
Crystal Palace. As soon as he's in
Crystal Palace, I'm going to go there
and I'm going to [ __ ] give him a good
oldfashioned hiding, bro. A good
oldfashioned hiding. He's not even
bigger than me, bro. Is he forgetting
that all of this [ __ ] two years all of
this [ __ ] he talks about was two years
ago, bro? He's not even bigger than me.
He's not even bigger than me, bro.
That's the maddest thing. He didn't say a time.
He didn't say a time, matey.
Look at that lovely little coat.
Keeps me warm in the winter.
I'm a littlemani tracksuit. And yeah.
And you know how you said about how you
can't beat up women and you can't shout
at women and stuff. Okay. Well,
yesterday I didn't beat up a woman. I
didn't shout at a woman. I was trying to
get her from the pockets.
I was trying to get her by the pockets,
but she clocked on. So, I just thought
I'd waste her time. I could try it with
that Pakistani one as well, but it's
going to be hard to get her out because
she would only eat halal things. I'm not
interested in fighting. I'm not
interested in violence. I'm just
interested in having some free food.
you know, give some of them [ __ ] a bit
back over the years, you know. I mean,
that I feel like is acceptable, you
know. And someone was like, "Oh, re,"
this woman was like, "Oh, revenge is for
losers." And I was like, "Bro, it's not
about revenge. It's getting a free
meal." I mean, we're benefiting from
getting a free [ __ ] meal, mate. It's
not about getting revenge. It's about
getting a free meal. You know what I'm saying?
Right. But um yeah,
the time is um when he comes. He never
actually gave a time, but I'll be live tomorrow anyways.
This guy thinks he's going to beat me,
bro. He's going to get his ass whooped.
It's not even a joke.
It's not even a joke, mate. Like, you
caught someone off guard
and then you're like doing madness.
Yep. I'm scared. You keep telling
yourself that if it makes you feel
better the fact that you're skint lad
keep saying it. It doesn't make you any
less skint calling other people it.
Yeah. It doesn't matter if it's for me.
I'm going to go there. You know
I never said I've got all of this money.
Apparently LJ's got all of this money.
Yet he sat indoors all day begging for
money. The lifestyle doesn't add up to
the finances. And when the lifestyle
doesn't add up to the finances,
it's questionable, you know.
It's very very very questionable.
Yeah. Well, then why is he starting
again? Okay. Okay. Well, if he's gave me
such a big L, if he's gave me such a big
L, then at the end of the day, why is he
coming back still trying to meet me
then? That's the end of it, isn't it?
So, bro, you need to tell yourself this.
You know, you need to tell yourself
this, not me, bro.
Skin doggy. Anyways, you keep calling me
skin is not going to change the fact
that you are skin.
It's not going to change the fact that
you're the one that's skin. You calling
other people what you are is not going
to change the fact that's you, bro.
I don't run my mouth behind the screen.
I've not brought He's the one that
started on me. So I said, "Okay, I'll meet you." Yeah,
bro. The guy is not a big man. I don't
know who you think he is. Yeah. This was
like 2 and a half years ago, bro.
Firstly, he caught me off guard. We're
going to see tomorrow, aren't we?
You call people skinn cuz you're skinn yourselves.
That's why you always bring up money.
It's cuz you you people ain't got no
money. That's why you always bring up
money cuz you ain't got none. That's why
you always tell people like that they're
skin and they're skin and they're skin.
It's cuz you are skin. It's cuz you've
got no money. That's what it is, bro.
That's why you keep constantly calling
people skin cuz it's a real reality of
your own benefit life. That's the only
thing it can be for people to keep
bringing up money, bro.
Yeah. It's got to be because they've got
none. We could literally be having a
normal conversation about something and
then they come on here and start
bringing up money. Like it's a madness, bro.
It's like LJ, he's got no money. He
likes to think that, oh, cuz he can buy£300
cheap trainers that he's got money, but
believe you me, he has no money. And I
don't know what would give you the
impression that somebody that begs off
of men would have money. He literally
does not have no money. Uh, actually I
don't live with my mom and you don't
know how. And bro, even if I lived with
my mom, that doesn't not make that
doesn't make anyone's skin. You know, I
literally have more money than you and I
proved it more multiple times. And every
single time I show you money, you run.
So at the end of the day, you literally
have been show money and you've run
away. Somebody that skin don't run away
that many times. Same old conversation.
Just because you look in your bank
account and you see zero, it doesn't
mean that we're all skin. Just because
you and L J and other people have got no
money, it doesn't mean that we ain't got
no money. There's nothing about you that
screams you've got money. It's the same
thing with L J. What? Because you buy a
cheap pair of trainers. That does not
mean you've got money, bro. I can go to
the shopping center right now and spend
well over two grand. That does not mean
I've got loads and loads and loads and
loads of money.
you what what do you get out of
convincing people that you've got money?
You don't have nothing. You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. Again, bro, I I spend it on
getting more women than you will ever
have. I have been with more women than
you. You know what I'm saying? I've
spent it on a life that you will never
have because you don't have no money. I
had a few grand. I have more than a few
grand now. And I spent it on a life that
you will never have because you've got
no money. You know what I'm saying? You know,
simple. I won't talk about my financial
circumstance. Go self-reflect your
skintess on other people. We all know
that you people have got no money.
That's why you keep bringing it up.
You're all old. You're all ugly. You're
all skint. And I'm not even bringing
this conversation up anymore. Anyways, LT
um and £39 is not a week's wage to most
people. So, try again. And again, I'm
not getting into it with you little
skinned people, you little
self-reflectors. You can keep talking
about yourselves. You are the ones that
have got no money. You're the ones that
have never had a life, never had a
woman. You can keep talking about
yourselves, bro. You can keep talking about yourselves.
You can keep self-reflecting your
skinnness onto other people. It doesn't
change the fact that you're skin
yourselves. You can keep self-reflecting.
No one cares, bro. Keep self-reflecting
all your life. No one cares.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I don't know anything.
Yeah, you're right. You're all
millionaires. You've got all this money
and I'm skinn. Oh, pardon me, bro. Yeah,
you are the ones that constantly bring
up money. It's because you ain't got no
money. That's why you bring up money all
the time because you are skint law J. He
is skint. That's why I don't go on the
law. That's why I don't go on the
[ __ ] paddle anymore because it's just
a bunch of skint people with no money
self-reflected on to you every day.
Skint. Skint. When he sat there with no
money, happened to go to Vegas after 3
years of saving up. That is skint. It's
just skin people that call you skin.
It's pointless. Absolutely pointless. A
bunch of people with no money that never
made it. That's why I don't go on the
panels. That's exactly why I don't go on
the panels anymore.
That's why I don't even go on the
panels. It's just the same old [ __ ]
You know, it's just a bunch of skinned
people with no money that never made it
in life. All all all these panel consist
of right is a bunch of sorry ass
middle-aged people that ain't got [ __ ]
all that tries to self-reflect onto
other people. That's what I mean.
They're just skin ugly no lives that
self-reflect on YouTube every day cuz
they ain't got nothing. People don't
People don't care about the panels
anymore. People don't care about the
live streams anymore.
You know, it's ridiculous. It's embarrassing.
You know, it's madness. You don't know
what people have and you don't know what
people don't have. So, you're talking
about yourselves. At the end of the day,
if you're the ones that constantly keep
bringing it up, it must mean that you
are the ones that asking yourselves.
That's the only thing it can be. And
then you're asking people where their
woman is. Again, we're not talking about
this anymore. You have been shown money.
You have been shown women. You have been
a You've been shown a better life than
you would never have. I'm not even
getting into this conversation anymore.
You can keep self-reflecting. I'm not
even going to block these accounts. I'm
just going to let them keep typing. You
need to sort yourselves out. You need to
get yourselves some money. You need to
get yourselves a life because every
single time you keep coming on here
self-reflecting, it's not going to
change the fact that you are all of
these things. You know, you've been
doing it for years and it's not going to
change the fact that you are the ones
that are skin. You are the ones that's
never been with a woman. The amount of
times that you keep saying this, bro,
it's not going to change the fact it's
your reality. You can say that I'm skin.
You can say that I've done that. Bro,
listen. Yeah, he done the money game. He
done me at the money game. But guess
what? In them years,
do you know what I'm saying? Yeah. At
the end of the day, let me tell you
something. 13 grand. Do you know what I
was doing in them three years when he
was saving that 13 grand? Going out,
banging [ __ ] traveling, going to
restaurants. I wouldn't trade up for 13
grand. The fact that it took you two
years to beat me at the money game just
proves that none of you have nothing.
That's all the evidence I needed. All
that the evidence I needed is that I
done you people at the money game for
years. That shows up what you people
really have. And you'll pretend that it
won't it never happened and no. And you
go on about, oh, it was ages ago when
it's the past. You know, he's still got
a woman, mate. I've had more women than
him and I've never had a disabled woman.
I've been with women that he wishes he
could get. And guess what? I wouldn't
trade [ __ ] three years of life
experiences for 13 grand, mate. No
[ __ ] way. But you talk about money
cuz you ain't got no money. This is what
it is with you 40. Let me Let me tell
you what it is with you middle-aged men.
Yeah. You're sat on YouTube, you ain't
got no money, you got no life, you got
nothing. You ain't even got hope. and
you see someone that's better looking
than you, half your age, more money than
you, a little bit of hope, and you go
mad for it. Oh, you're skin, you're
this, you're that. You see, you see
somebody that's got hope and it and it
kills you. That's what it is with you
people. You people don't like the fact
that someone's younger than you, better
looking than you, got more money than
you. So, if you can bring somebody down
to your level, it seems to make you feel
better about this. the fact that you are
skinned. You are the ones with nothing.
You are the ones that are old and ugly.
If you can make someone If you can make
somebody feel like you're middle-aged,
no money skin asses, you feel it makes
you feel better about yourself. That's
what it does. You hate the fact like
think about it, bro. Look how many
people there are on this community,
lads. Look how many people there are on this community.
You know, my last date told you that. I
was thinking n talking about yourself.
Look, look at this, bro. Why do you have
all of these middle-aged men obsessed
with you? It's cuz you're better looking
than them. You got more money than them.
It's a bit like that what that Ronald
Pump said, more money, better looking,
better life. That's why they come on
here every day. That's why they come on
here every day doing this because they
hate to admit that you're better than
them and you got more money than them.
They're trying to bring you down to
their skin level. Just like this doggy
G, just like all of these other people,
they call people skinned. It's because
they're skinned. They're the ones with
no money. Just like L J. They're the
ones that have got no money. Did you see
the other bro? Did you see the last time
I was on the panel? [ __ ] trying
to show me [ __ ] trying to sell me 40 grand.
You know, he Sorry, £40. He tried to
show me £40.
It's because these people have got no
money. No matter how many times you say
it to them, it doesn't process in their mind.
You know what I mean? These people have
got no money. They show themselves up
when they got shown six grand. They all
ran away because they ain't got no
money. They have nothing. I'm trying to
say this in like the most English way
possible. You know, they're sat there
fat, ugly old men with no money, sad
with their lives, coming on YouTube
every day projecting. And it's also what
they do every day on here as well. They
ain't got no money. Bro, think about it.
If these people really had money, why do
they run away when I show them six
grand? Where was all their money then?
That's evidence. But they don't like to
they don't like to remember that because
it shows them to be bad. Because like I
said, they're narcissists on here. This
is exactly what I'm saying.
You know, they're disabled narcissists.
So it doesn't matter. Like, yeah, you
got all this money, bro. So why do you
keep running away every time you get show money?
Because you ain't got no money.
It's funny in a way, bro. It is. It is
funny in a way, you know. You know what
I mean? It is funny, but it's immature,
man. It's about time we started growing up now.
You know, if you don't like somebody,
just stop going on their channel. I
think we should just grow up now. I
think everyone should grow up.
You all got all of this money. Yeah, of
course you do. You You're sat on YouTube
every day calling people skint cuz
you're skin. Your skin ugly old men that
ain't got a life.
You know what I'm saying? Ugly old men
that ain't got a life. sat on YouTube
all day talking about people that they
don't even know. Yeah. Your life is so
You got all of this money, bro. Yeah.
You got all of this money.
You've got all of this money. Yet you
sat on YouTube every day calling people
that you don't know skin. Yeah. You got
all this money, bro. I'm so jelly, man.
I hope I'm like you when I'm older.
I hope I'm like you when I'm older, lad.
Yeah. These people are just
self-reflectors. All they do is project.
They're fat, they're old, they're ugly,
they got no life, they see somebody
younger than them and better looking
than them with a bit of hope and it
kills them. That's what it is. Cuz think
about it, bro. If you ask if you ask the
question why these people go for you,
they'll make up some narcissistic excuse
like, oh, you said stuff about women and
kids. But they like that. They like a
reaction. People like toxic drama. You
know, the real reason that these people
go for you is cuz you're younger than
them. You've got more money than them.
You're better looking than them. You got
more freedom than them. That's why they
go for you every day. That's why they
will waste their life on you every day
even though it has no effect. What they
do has no effect, but they'll still do
it every day. So, I mean, you got to be
logical about You have to be logical
about it, you know,
cuz I'm the youngest on it. Well, yeah.
K doesn't even come on it anymore. So,
you got to think you're the youngest.
You're probably better looking than all
of them because they don't show their
face. You've got more money than all of
them. You got money to do what you want.
You just The way I see it is you can
literally go to um
you can go to a pub, right, on a
Saturday. Yeah. You can dress up and you
can go to a pub and you can maybe get a
number. You can maybe get a kiss. They
couldn't even do that. They're skinn.
They're ugly. They're too scared to
leave the house. just the simplest
things that most people wouldn't think
twice about doing. These people can't do
that. They're ugly. They got no money.
They got no And it's only money to an
extent, you know, like it's,
you know, I don't have loads and loads
and loads and loads and loads of money,
but I have enough money to do what I
want to do.
So, the these people don't even go out
their house. And why did I need to win a
football bet? Because when I went out on
that Sunday, I spent a load of money
that Sunday and that Monday cuz it was
my mom's birthday. Yeah. That's called
life. Yeah. These people don't even go
out for a drink. These people don't even
leave their house.
You know what I'm saying?
[ __ ] spent a lot of [ __ ] money,
bro. So, yeah.
So, you know, it's like you they they
don't like the fact that you're younger
than them and that you're better looking
than them and you've got, you know,
you're not skin. I don't even think it's
just about the having more money than
them because that's just like
that doesn't really
you know what I mean? It's like but it's
because you're not skint like well yeah
it is more money than them because
they're skinn terms of that yeah it is
because you're not skinn like them. So
yeah it is that you've got more money
than them because these people are skin.
So yeah more money better looking better
life. Yeah the guy was right. So yeah
do you know what I'm saying bro? And you
talk like you know like anyone's life,
oh they've got someone got 13 pounds or
bro, you don't know what people have.
You know, you can keep trying to call
people's skin all you like. No one
cares. We all know it's self-reflecting
now what you people do. It's just self-
projecting every day,
you know? It's no one cares,
Like even I'm not biased. Even I'm not
biased, bro. Like when nonsleg shown 30
grand, I'm not going to sit there and
say, "Oh, 30 grand's nothing. 30 grand's
nothing." Like [ __ ] Lee and Wales
trying to say six grand is nothing when
I could literally buy him and his house
was six grand. Like, you know, like I I
just said that it's not a life-changing
amount of money and it took a lot of
discipline to save that money. I
couldn't have done it. You know, I was
living the life for 3 years, so I I
wouldn't know what it's like to stay
indoors saving that kind of money. Yeah.
It's not a life-changing amount of
money. It's a handy amount of money.
That's what I was saying. But people go
on like it's a million pound because
it's who's showing it. It's who's showing it,
you know, like that. The thing is,
right, is that Yeah. It's it's who's
actually showing the money. It's not
what the how much the money actually is,
you know, cuz they're all biased, which
ties into the jealousy again. You know
what I'm saying? So, you know, that's
why they do all of this [ __ ]
I was looking on my [ __ ] bro. And
Oh, you Oh, it's nothing. Oh, 13 grand
is nothing. Are you sure about that? I
thought it was a million pounds.
But anyways, I was looking uh what I was
doing the past four years, and my life
has been better. I can tell you right
now, I've had a better life than all of
these people in this community, where it
ain't even no joke. I was looking at the
restaurants, this, that, the other. You
know, at the end of the day, bro, I've
had a way better life than these people
will ever have,
you know, and it's it's a madness. It's
not even a joke, lad. Like, it's not
even a joke.
It's not even a joke, mate. Not even a
joke. And it's not even anything to
laugh about, bro. you know.
Yeah. I don't understand the point of
all of this anyways.
Why do you just worry about your own
lives? You know, I don't understand. You
You say that people are skinned. They
show you money, you run away. What's the
whole point of all of this? If someone's
skin, then get on with your own life in it, you know?
[ __ ] hell, bro.
It's just self projecting.
I'm starting the gym soon anyways. I'm
going on holiday. So, you'll all be
you'll all be left to it anyways, bro.
And then you say about how like I'm
trying to justify the fact that I can't
afford to go out. I can afford to go
out. I can go out whenever I want. You
think I can't go out and spend £200? Of
course I can, you idiot.
But I'd rather not because I've done it
a million times.
So, you know, I never even done it even
when I had the house went out every
week. So, and you don't even spend that.
You spend what about 100 maximum?
[ __ ] Bro, I can't afford to go out,
man. Have a word with yourself.
You're just looking silly now. You know, bam.
Uh, just the same old [ __ ] Same old self-reflectors.
Same old middle-aged people calling
people skin. Yeah, just same old [ __ ]
really. Uh, Monty got Natalie G
arrested. Oh, did you see that, LT?
Did you see what happened with Monty and Natalie?
Oh, yeah. Did you Did you see that?
You didn't see that? Oh, damn. Yeah. He
She started like hitting him and stuff.
She smashed his [ __ ] mouth in and
then he got arrested. Yeah.
She's a horrible bastard. When she's had
a drink, apparently she was flashing her
tits out. He tried to get off YouTube.
She started attacking him and then he got nicked.
Yeah. Oh, you didn't hear about that?
Yeah. How did I miss that bit out?
But all of Yeah. But you're all grasses
on here though, bro. You're all grasses.
L was trying to get me banged from a
chicken shop. That's Grthon. I don't
care what anyone says. That's Grasson.
Nods Legs grasses. Red Star grasses.
You've all been grasses, bro. You've I
don't know her channel. I actually don't
know her channel. It was on his channel,
bro. I would have I would have hit her
back. I would have hit her. I would have
[ __ ] I would have smacked on a Ras
Clark face, brother. You mad.
Yeah, but a lot of these people grass.
So, he's just doing what they do. It's
like I'll give you an example. I'll give
you an example, LT. Yeah. Yeah. Listen,
listen, listen, listen, listen. You
know, when people said they were going
to grass on um Nons legs, I said, "Yeah,
grass on him." Yeah. Yeah. Grass on him.
Yeah. Do it. Do it. try and get his
money stopped. Yeah, do it. I was saying
do it. Why not? You like to They like to
grass on other people, so do it back to
them. They like to grass and get the
boys in blue involved and then try to
get people's money stopped. Yeah, grass
on them all you want. Go for it. You've
got my permission. You've got my
permission. But then they'll try to call
you the grass. That's that that's how
they're so narcissistic.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. I said, "Go and report him to the
DWP, bro. Go get his money stopped.
That'd be a lovely day to get someone's
money stopped." They [ __ ] reported me
[ __ ] to the benefits. I had the [ __ ]
calling me up two times. Yeah, do it.
Do you know what, bro? I I've really got
myself to blame to be honest, you know,
when it comes to this community, you
know, at the end of the day, lad. Like,
it's I've really got myself to blame.
You know, these people have been jealous
for years. You know, they're they're
clearly jealous of something. You know,
the evidence is there for them to do
what they do every day. I need to just
go to a gym and come off this [ __ ] bro.
And just focus on this holiday now. You
know what I mean? This is this is
ridiculous, bro. We're [ __ ] we're
getting old now. And you know, this is
this is pathetic, bro. This is pathetic.
You know, it's it's it's crazy, Grezy.
It really really is.
And it's madness.
That's why we come to these um
come to these conclusions, lads. I mean,
but yeah, I can't go out and have a
drink every week cuz I'm skinn. Oh man,
I'm so skinn, bro. Can you help me? I'm so skinn.
Yeah, I'm so skint, bro.
I think it closes early on Sundays,
don't they? Oh, yes.
I forgot about that.
Can you help me? I'm skin.
I can't afford to do anything. I'm so skinn.
Life experiences over money any day of the week.
Yep. Life experiences over money any day
of the [ __ ] week.
Yeah, he did. He called the police on her.
I don't give a [ __ ] about him anyway.
He's a snake. So calm going back. He's a
[ __ ] snake, man. Oh, did you see that
Ricky Milling then trying to put his
[ __ ] body up on his [ __ ] thing,
bro? Oh, slap that guy up, bro. You
know, one of them little skinny little
white Do you know what? Yeah. Well, he
should come to Crystal Palace tomorrow.
I hope he comes to Crystal Palace
tomorrow and I'll [ __ ] knock the [ __ ]
out. Did you see it? Don't know what the
charge was. We haven't heard anything
since she's been locked up, but we know
that she got locked up and that's it. We
The police was there and everything, but
we we haven't heard anything since. You
know that Ricky Million account?
You know, do you remember that Ricky
Millan account trying to trying to flex
his little no muscle?
Do you know what I'd love to do? Do you
know what I'm going to do tomorrow? I'm
going to give him a Simone spike, bro.
That's what I'm going to do to this
[ __ ] prime tomorrow. I'm going to
give him a Simone spike.
You know, that's what I'm going to do,
Greavves. I'm going to give him an
Simone spike. And if you don't know what
that means, it basically means this. You
do this and then you dip them in the
[ __ ] throat. This is Simone Spike.
God bless you, Marga. May he rest in
peace. But yeah,
a good old Simone Spike.
Yeah, they're lethal they are, mate.
That's how you could that, you know,
that's that's actually a good finisher.
You know, it's like any bouncer. You
give somebody a nice a nice Simone
spike, bro, they're finished. You don't
even need to be strong,
you know? That's a good finisher,
you know. Um, whenever he comes, why
don't you come and I'll smash your ugly
face in as well, you [ __ ]
I'll smash your ugly face in as well,
you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Cha chap chap cha
a chap choo.
Yeah, I'll smash your [ __ ] face in
your bongo. Come on. Come on, you [ __ ]
I'm going to go get some chicken, I
think, from the chicken shop.
Nah, these people won't hit back. They're cowards.
Yeah, I got bullied. Yeah, come to
Crystal Palace tomorrow and I'll bully
you. Yeah, come come to Crystal Palace
tomorrow and I'll bully you. You ugly man.
You ugly bastard.
Yeah, you should come tomorrow as well
with your little boyfriend Terry. Why
don't we all come tomorrow, bro? Why
don't we all Why don't we all come
tomorrow? you, Ricky Milling, All Night
Spaz, the [ __ ] lot. Why not? Why
don't the lot come? You know, why don't
The [ __ ] lot. Yeah.
Anyways, listen, [ __ ] Why don't you
come tomorrow? You [ __ ] ugly man that
can't show his face. You ugly
40year-old. Oh, you just want to be a keyboard warrior?
Yeah, I won't be showing. Okay, bro.
Yeah, I won't be showing, bro. I'm not
nons. You know, I've actually shown up
to people multiple times. You don't
actually realize the danger that I put
myself in because you you like to forget
stuff, don't you? You actually like to
forget stuff. See, you sit there and
say, right, that oh yeah, you know,
you've you've you've said sorry to Prime
and no, but listen, bro, I've put myself
in danger numerous times. I've literally
I have literally right went to meet
Terry. That could have been a big [ __ ]
I've gone to meet Bomb. I've gone to
meet Mark Samson. Do you realize Yeah. I
have gave people many, many chances to
do something. You I don't think you
actually realize that I have gave people
multiple chances to actually do something.
That's what separates me and Nles legs.
And he's got a bigger mouth than me. So
this is where it doesn't make any sense.
Like you sit there and say, "Oh yeah,
you've took hours." But bro, I put
myself in a lot of danger multiple times
and it was up for you up to you people
to do something. You know what I'm saying?
So you you seem to forget these things.
I think you seem to really forget these things. you know.
Oh, the nose. Bro, listen. You can't,
bro. There's nothing wrong with my nose.
You're fat and ugly. You can't even get a bird
talking about my nose when you're fat
and ugly. Oh, bro. We all know that I'm
better looking than all of you people.
So, I don't know why you're talking
about my looks when it's obvious that
I'm better looking than all of you
people that have shown your face. And
you know, it must be hectic being you
every day trying to talk about my looks
when I'm better looking than all of you.
And again, that's also what kills you as
well. That's why you come online and
hate every day. Stop coming online and
hating every day. If you're better
looking and you've got all this money,
start showing it and stop hating every
day. Stop being a hater.
O, did you watch that video I sent you?
LT, Valentine's is just a day that it's
not wanted by anybody.
It's I It's a day where to make to mock
the men that ain't wanted by no one. Listen,
but what I'm trying to say is, yeah, you
say that I'm this and you're saying that
I'm that, bro, but these people have had
chances to do things multiple times. And
we're not talking about people coming to
my house. We're talking about Bob. We're
talking about Mark Samson, you know.
Yep. I showed up to Trevor Dawson. He
used an excuse. I said, "If if I'm not
really there, why don't you walk 5
minutes up the road then if I'm not
really there?" And you know how far that
was? That was [ __ ] Middlesbrough.
[ __ ] it. That was some mileage, mate.
That was some mileage. And I still don't
get credit for it. I mean, [ __ ] bro.
What the [ __ ]
What the actual [ __ ]
I might get a McDonald's today, actually.
Nah, I'll get some. I don't know what I
don't know what to get. [ __ ] knows.
Everywhere closes at 5, it probably just
get some chicken.
Yeah, just get some chicken.
Yeah, they're not worth anyone's time.
They're not worth anyone's time, bro.
You know, the moment the moment they
stop coming on here, they're hating. The
moment I'll say, "Okay, maybe they're
not jealous of something." Or t,
you know, when they keep showing
themselves up the way they keep showing
themselves up, it's clear as day that
they are jealous of something
cuz otherwise you wouldn't waste your
time. Simple. I'm not going to keep
repeating myself, bro. But that's how it
is. I don't know what I want today to eat.
Yeah, I want a T-bone steak today, but I
can't get it, bro, cuz the butcher's
closed. Oh, [ __ ]
And there's nowhere to get a steak cuz
obviously it's Sunday, so the butcher is
closed. I wanted one today, bro. You see
what I done to that [ __ ] LT? I showed
her who's boss. Um,
no. I can't afford it. I'm skinn. Yeah,
I can't afford it. I'm skin.
No, I'm completely skin.
Oh, yeah. There is that place that's
doing a roast. I might go Oh, yeah. I
might just go get a roast.
What time does it close? What time does
it close? Hold on.
Yeah. Yeah. I might go for a roast
actually. Oh [ __ ] I forgot about that.
Yeah, I'm going to go go for a roast, I think. Yeah,
like I said, you keep coming on here
self-reflecting your skintess every day
is not going to change the fact that
you're skin. Remember that. Remember
that when you were in your deathbed?
Yeah, but normally I don't like going
Sundays because it's too packed and
you're lining up one hour. But it should
be good now. It should be okay now. It
should be okay now. Fingers crossed.
Yeah, I'm going to go I'm going to go
carry get a roast, I think. Yeah,
it's not going to change the fact that
you are skin. Remember, Greasy, why do
these people call me skin Monty man? Cuz their skin
cuz their skin.
Do remember that.
I go to bed at like 7:00 in the morning,
you know? I watch Man and stuff.
Yeah, I know it's mid, but that's the
only thing I can [ __ ] get cuz that's
the only thing that's [ __ ] open.
Yeah, we know it's mid, mate, but that's
the only thing I can [ __ ] get. So,
yeah, matey. And it should be Yeah, it
should be all right.
It is mid, but what else are you going to get?
Everywhere's closed. It closes at 5.
Don't fancy Indian. I've not had a roast for ages.
So, give it a little whirl. No. [Applause]
Greasy, do you think I could go out
drinking every week if I wanted to? Of
course I could.
Yeah, I never had anxiety in my life.
Talking about yourself.
Talking about yourself again,
little L's bum boy. Never had anxiety in
my life. I wouldn't I wouldn't have been
to all of these places and pulled the
women that you could never if I had anxiety, matey.
Do you not understand? Do you not Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, I can't I can't afford to go out
drinking every week apparently. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Going out drinking is about
£100. But yeah, I can't afford to go out drinking.
Sucks to be me.
Sucks to [ __ ] be me.
Yeah, man. I'm so poor.
[ __ ] hell, man.
I'm so poor.
I might go to Fab Fabrics, you know, at
some point. I might go to Fabrics.
Head to Hawksmore.
You're having a [ __ ] laugh, are you,
mate? I actually could go I could
actually go to any restaurant I want,
but you know, I'm saving money. I'm
going on holiday in two months. Can't be
wasting that sort of money, mate.
No, I've already got a blazer.
I've already got a nice gray blazer.
Nothing wrong with it.
There's nothing wrong with it. Who's that?
Yeah, it's about £126.
Jesus Christ. [ __ ] me, bro. £126
that steak was just for me.
Oh my god. That's a madness, bro.
I don't need a new blaze. I've got a
nice one. A nice gray one. [ __ ]
Yeah, it's expensive, bro. It Yeah, I've
got that on video as well. I was like,
Virgin Boys never had a Hulks more.
That's why I said I'd rather have the
life experiences than have [ __ ] I'd
rather have the life experiences than um Yeah.
Not not the navy one, the gray one.
Um, I'd rather have the life experiences than [ __ ]
have 13 grand in 3 years. That's what
I'm saying, bro.
These people not want to [ __ ]
progress on or something.
I still got my little stonies as well.
Virgin by one. I was thinking of giving
Virgin Boy a Stony, you know. I've got
like a royal blue one. Obviously, they
look like [ __ ] because they've not been
dry cleaned. They need ironing and dry
cleaning. I was thinking of giving
Virgin Boy maybe the blue one, like the
royal blue one, cuz it will suit his
virgin hair color. And maybe he might
actually lose it. He might lose that
V-card. He might actually get laid.
You know, you always be always be a
believer in the Stony.
The first time I bought a Stony is the
first time I went out in a Stony is when
I met my mama and that was the first one
night stand I had in London. So, who
knows if he plays his cards right, he
might get laid,
you know, with the Stony.
You never know, mate. What do you think?
Like a little gift from me to you. You
know, the me to you bears.
Maybe you'll get laid. Maybe we'll
actually lose his virginity and get some sex.
I've got blue, I've got green,
I've got another shade of blue, I've got
navy. They all need dry cleaners. Just
got ain't round just ain't got round to
dry cleaning them yet.
Virgin boy. I can't afford that, mate.
The Hippodrome used to pay for Peter
Belly's little stonies. Oh, how cute is that?
Oh, that is so cute.
Do you remember
[ __ ] They need to be dry cleananed. I
need to go to [ __ ] Strapford and get
them dry cleananed. There's there's a
specific shop that I go to. So,
uh, red. No thanks.
Nah, [ __ ] that, bro. [Music]
So, I know when I go out drinking again,
I'm going to really really enjoy it,
bro. I'm going to be lethal. I'm going
to be lethal when I go out again. When I
eventually go out again, I'll be [ __ ]
But yeah, I got a lot of stonies, bro. I
got £1,200 worth of stonies.
There's that thing.
Might hit up Fabrics.
Might hit up Fabrics. I don't know.
I'd rather just save money and build my
money up, bro. Like, I want to There's
places I need to be going and [ __ ] bro.
Like, I need to learn now at this age. I
want to do other things other than this.
Like I'm I'm over it, bro. I'm over it, you know.
No, when I I don't think I would even do
it again. I can't be bothered with it. I
already know what it is, bro. The more I
look on what I've already done, I was
like, bro, there's just no point in any of it.
You already know the result, lad.
I want to go to Miami. Um, LG, I think
I'm going to go to Miami, you know,
maybe next summer
or something like next summer or
something. I need to start building
money up, bro. I can't be going out
[ __ ] I don't even enjoy it anymore.
I need to I need to start really doing
things, bro. You know what I'm saying?
God bless you then.
Yeah, bless you. I just can't be asked
with it anymore, bro. I really can't be
asked with it.
Even if I win a football bet, bro. I
just don't even go out.
I just want I just want it to try and
build the money back up. I don't [ __ ]
I don't even want to go out anymore
drinking, bro. I'm bored of it, lad.
[ __ ] bored of it.
I'm so bored of it.
It does get boring, doesn't it?
I'd rather make myself really, really
bored, build the money up, and then go out
if I even want to go out again. Probably
probably won't even go out again. saying that, bro.
So, I don't know. I can't be asked.
It's going to have to take a long time
for me to want to go out again, mate.
It's going to take a long time for me to
even want to go out again, bro.
Been there, done it, worn the t-shirt. So, yeah.
But I do want to do a little bit of
Liverpool Street again, bro.
[ __ ] those. [ __ ] those. [ __ ] those. Do
you see what I done to that woman? Um,
LT, what you got to say now, bro? What
have you got to say now, bro?
What have you got to [ __ ] say now? Huh?
You can't say I was violent or I hit a
woman. I was just giving them a taste of
their own good oldfashioned good good
taste of their own medicine.
She was being a [ __ ] Being a [ __ ]
I've already had it.
I'm going to go for a roast.
LT likes to uh LT likes to defend women
cuz that's an advice you'd give to a
brother. Oh, you should go to the gym.
You like she was trying to be a [ __ ]
She was trying to give me a lecture
about my appearance when nah [ __ ] I'm
better than you. Nah, [ __ ] I'm good
enough for you, bro. Who are you?
[ __ ] Angelina Jolie.
Are you [ __ ] Angelina [ __ ] Jolie or something?
No, you're [ __ ] not. You know,
I've had to tell a few of these women
about themselves in the past week on
Instagram as well, talking like they're
better than people. Yeah,
I've had to tell a few of them about themselves, bro.
An American, somebody in Dubai. I mean,
what the [ __ ] bro?
When she was in the pub, I was like, "Oh
[ __ ] I kind of want to go pub and
drink, but at the same time, I don't." So,
yeah, exactly. Yeah. No, I'm not going
to do any of that stuff anymore, LT. I'm
just going to stand him up. I'm going to
use them for a steak, you know.
So, that's it.
That's all I'm going to do now, bro.
This is what I was going to do to her.
[ __ ] it. She was being a [ __ ] That
advice you you you give to um you give
to a brother. Oh, you should go on a
waitress. Like if not like if you was
asking, right? Okay. Okay. Let me let me
use this example. If you was asking how
to improve your appearance, people will
say, "Oh, you should eat healthy or you
should go gym or you should do this, you
should." If you're asking for advice to
improve your appearance, then that's a
completely different matter. You know,
people can always improve. But when
someone's trying to be judgmental when
there's literally nothing wrong with
you, like if I if I didn't go out right,
if I had a haircut just now, if I had a
haircut now and I wanted to go out a
week later, I'm fine. If I smell good
and I'm clean, you look fine. You're
good enough. They're not to tell you
what you should be looking like. You're
not asking for advice. You're not asking
they're they're not you never asked to
be manipulated and given a lecture about
what you should look like. But I mean,
if you ask if you're asking for advice,
it's different. Obviously, that's
completely different. But we wasn't.
You know, some people don't want to go
barbers every week, two weeks. What if
someone's [ __ ] saving up to go on
holiday or they're saving up for a new
car or whatever? They just don't want to
go barbers every week. You know what I'm
saying? Like, who who are they, bro?
Don't go around start acting a [ __ ] to
people and cry when people do it back to
you, bro. You know what I'm saying? And
I didn't go out my way to do it. I just
thought, "Oh, I've got an opportunity
here. Let me [ __ ] one of them over and I
was and I was actually going to be
benefiting from it as well cuz I was
planning to get the steak.
Yeah, simple, bro. It doesn't matter.
I'm better looking than her. Who is she
to not wanting people? I'm better
looking than she would ever be, bro. She
ain't even got no tits.
So, bro, it doesn't matter. Yeah, I'm
better than her in a million different
bro. I will always be better looking
than her from the from the from when I
was born, bro. I was better than her
from when I was born, bro. From the very
start of when I come out my mom's
vagina, I was better than her, bro. You
know, so think about it.
And that's And that's a thing, bro. And
that's a thing.
So, I'm better looking than her. I'm
[ __ ] She ain't even got any tits. Who
is she to start telling people that she
doesn't want them? You're better than
her in every way. And the only maddest
thing is LT, I didn't even like her. I
don't I approached her cuz she was the
only one in the bar. I didn't like her
at all. So, think about it. You got you
got people that you don't even like
that's doing this cuz you imagine the
ones that do that you do like.
So, it doesn't matter, bro. You don't It
doesn't matter anyways. And Okay, fair
enough. And I stated the reasons I don't
like you cuz you got no tits and you
look anorexic. So, then is it? And this
isn't even somebody that I liked. I
still I weren't going to go meet her.
Well, I was going to meet her for the
steak, but apart from the steak, before
I even had that plan, I was like, I'm
not going to meet someone for a drink
cuz I didn't actually like them. You know, simple. So,
this is why I don't deal with these
[ __ ] I see it a very I I see it a
very different way than you see it.
You know, they're going to end up lonely
in their 30s and no one wants them
because all in their 20s they thought
they're better than people.
You know, it's mad. Do they not learn
from each other? Like they ain't [ __ ] I
don't know why they like think about it,
bro. In them four years when I had the
house, I was better than all of them.
You want to you want to you want to come
listen, bro? You're making over three
grand a month and you're doing nothing.
You know how how many people would kill
to be in that position? You know, like
all of them four years, bro, they were
working, bro, and they had less than you
every month. And you you got a house and
you're earning more than them and all of
that money is disposable, bro. You're
way above them, bro. You are way above
them. Like, we're talking like in the
past and stuff, you know? Like, think
about it like that, bro. You're better
than them even financially if you
actually think about it. And you're also
better looking than them, too.
that. Do you know how mad that is? Think
about it, bro.
You're like a 1% that had that. You understand?
Isn't a Finnish one?
Yeah, she she said that she'll meet me
if I go to Finland. Yeah, she's all
right. But we're not talking about her.
Yeah, she's all right. We talk sometimes
when I message her, but I don't I can't
be bothered anymore with it, bro.
Uh, boring, boring to me. So, that's the
thing, bro. Like, who do they actually
think they are?
You know, the thing is, right, LT, you
know, I'm objectively good-looking. You
know, when I when I put like effort into
myself, I'm object I'm objectively
good-looking, not subjectively. um
objectively and you should actually know
what that means. So when you get these
women that have got no tits thinking
that they're better than you, that's a
big [ __ ] you. That is an actual big [ __ ]
you. Do you know what I'm saying?
Like I could understand if somebody was
the [ __ ] I could understand like
someone's a model, they're racking in
money, they've got loads of Instagram
followers. Bro, I could get it. I could
be mature enough to get it. But bro,
these women ain't [ __ ] the ones that
think they're better than you and
they've got this attitude. But the thing
is, LT, it's like I said on my on my
video, bro, where does the attitude come
from? Men have options. Men have money.
They don't think they're better than
people. You don't understand how mad it all is.
Just cuz they've got desperate simps
doesn't mean that you you go around
being a [ __ ] Go ask all the men in
Thailand that's got auctions. They don't
go around their personalities don't
change. Yeah, they're more picky. No
one's saying that you can't be picky. Of
course, you can be picky. If you got
options, you're going to be picky. Yeah.
But there's but there's a difference
between being a being picky and being a
[ __ ] You understand that? You know what I mean?
You know what I'm saying, bro? Like what
what is the reason that they like men
don't change when they've got money? I
went to Middles, bro, and I was
considered rich and I never thought I
was better than anyone. Imagine that. I
went to Middlesbrough and I was probably
considered probably a millionaire to
them. Obviously I'm not here but you
know what I mean to Middlesbrough I did.
You know what I'm saying? I never
thought I was better than no one. I like
the attention from the women when I was
in Newcastle. Don't get me wrong. I
weren't I weren't [ __ ] off the
attention, bro. But like I didn't think
I was better than no one, bro. And think
of that. These are average people with
average wages in London with attitude
like that. That's what makes me die.
That's that's that's the funny thing
about it, bro.
Is they ain't [ __ ]
And then you'll get somebody I see a
video here where this guy, right, he
approached um John Cena. He was [ __ ]
with John Cena for a little bit. And
even John Cena was nice.
Think of it. John Cena, all that money,
probably can get any woman that he
wants. And he doesn't have an ego. He
doesn't have an attitude.
I'm sure you've seen that. And this is a
[ __ ] a millionaire, you know? So why
the [ __ ] do these women think they're
better than people? I don't get it.
Maybe it's part of their sick,
narcissistic, twisted ways. You know
what I mean?
It's like people will not like you for
stupid reasons. Like there's even stupid
reasons why people won't like you,
you know, cuz because you're not living
up to their Romeo and Juliet expectations.
I see where John Cena, bro, this guy was
[ __ ] with he done it two times and
John Cena was nothing but a gentleman
and this is somebody that's got money
and this is someone that can get any
woman he wants. So what? You know what I'm saying?
I see that, bro. I see it a few times.
He done it. He stalked him a second time as well.
And you got these women that think
they're better than people, bro. It's a madness.
That's why I stopped being Christian,
LT. That's why I don't go to church
anymore. Because there's no good women out there.
There's no good women out there. That's
why I don't go to church anymore.
I don't even go to church anymore, bro.
Because of that, I don't go to church.
No, I don't even That's why I'm not Christian anymore.
I used to be Christian. But
all women are the same. And Valentine's
Day is just a day to mock people, mock
the men that nobody wanted. you know,
mock the men that don't ain't wanted by nobody.
Let's let's let's create a holiday to
mock the men that ain't women ain't
choosing up on.
The men that ain't wanted by no one.
Yeah. Let's let's make let's make a
holiday. Let's make a holiday to mock
the men that ain't wanted by no one.
You know, that's why I'm not Christian
no more. I used to be Christians.
I used to believe in Jesus and but nah,
[ __ ] that, bro. Yeah,
I know what you do, Ali. You come back
from a night out with your little
hoodlims and you laugh at me. You laugh
on my live stream in it. You type trying
to like patronize me like what this guy
does here. You copy my sayings and you
laugh with your little mates and you
laugh with your little mates.
Yeah, don't you? You laugh with your little mate.
I know what you do when you come back
from Fabrics for a little night out.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, you are a virgin and you asking
Yeah, you are. You are a virgin and you asking
Yeah, you're talking about yourself.
>> Yeah, you're talking about yourself.
But yeah, I'm not interested in violence
or threatening anyone or but um
if you find like I said LT, if you find
a little loophole to [ __ ] these women
over and you can benefit, then do it.
Obviously the state thing being one
And they're just [ __ ] on purpose.
They are just [ __ ] on purpose.
They're not even They're just They're just [ __ ]
That's what they are. They're just [ __ ]
I lost that thing [ __ ] on Reddit. I
need I need to try and find that before
I go for this roast. That's going to
annoy me, bro, if I can't find that.
>> Anyways, I'll be back later. Yeah. We're
going to finish roast be back later.