Right. Hopefully this [ __ ] shows up
today cuz I'm off after today, matey.
I'm off the disabled community, matey. Yes.
Yeah, let's hope this country ain't
wasting time today.
Let's go. Weasel.
I don't want to be on there any longer
than I have to be.
with these little projectors. These all sell projectors.
This come better show up today, matey. Yeah.
I had a shower in days, you know, man.
I always have a shower.
If I get a [ __ ] If I get an infection
in my [ __ ] willie
before I get an infection in my willie. Jesus Christ. Yeah.
Get some epoids. That's That's what I [ __ ] need.
That man was like, "Oh, no.
If you like that, you should keep
trying." No. Why should I keep trying? I
shouldn't have to keep trying. You know,
I've been up and down the country. I
shouldn't have to try ever again in my life.
I shouldn't have to. I shouldn't even
have to speak to someone else again.
I've tried a million times. I shouldn't
have to keep trying.
Whe it's one month, two months, I
shouldn't have to. I've tried more than
anyone in the [ __ ] world. It's madness.
It's madness. Why you'd even suggest
keep trying to be honest?
Cuz if trying was going to work, it
would have worked by now already. It's
[ __ ] obvious. It's completely [ __ ]
I'm [ __ ] trying. Just [ __ ] off. You
mad? [ __ ] that. Why would I try when
I've tried more than anyone in the
world? That's ridiculous.
What do you want me to be [ __ ] 40 and
keep [ __ ] trying or something? You
mad? [ __ ] that.
No, I'm good. Thanks.
I'm good. Thank you.
Someone must be live or something. Must be.
Yeah, I'm coming off this [ __ ] anyways
after today. So, I'm just going to own
this little [ __ ] cuz yeah, got to be s
on YouTube with low lives all day, every
day that self-reflect. It's about time
one of us got a life. You know what I'm saying?
These people clearly never going to get
a life. So why I'm on here today to meet this [ __ ] So yeah,
had a nice Philly steak burger. at like
3:00 in the morning. [ __ ] man.
Oh, some cheese stuck in my [ __ ] mustache.
But keep trying. I should have to keep
trying. I've tried more than anyone in
the [ __ ] world. I shouldn't have to keep trying.
Yep. Program for me.
That man was like, "Oh, if you felt the
way I do, you'd keep trying." And why
would I keep trying when I've already
tried a million times more than anybody
in the world? No way am I going to keep
trying, bro. What the [ __ ] What the
[ __ ] bro? What is it going to be if all
of a sudden the next time you go out? Be
logical about this [ __ ] man. Be logical
about this [ __ ] It's never going to [ __ ] change.
[ __ ] about go out. It's never going
to [ __ ] change with these [ __ ] Never.
It's why I don't bother anymore cuz
they're all the same.
Women are all the same. Grezy.
All the same.
Women are all the [ __ ] same.
I hope this [ __ ] comes out. Oh, I had a
Philly cheeseburger. Greasy. Philly
steak cheeseburger at 3 in the morning.
The cheese got stuck in my mustache. You
know the cheese sauce.
I haven't showered for like five days, bro.
Don't know what what he's talking about
making stuff up. I don't entertain madeup stuff.
I don't know. I don't entertain madeup
stuff. So, don't bring it on my channel.
Don't bring made up rumors on my channel
cuz they don't even get they don't even
get attention. Greavvesy should know
that now, don't you, Grezy? Greavves
been a viewer for a long time. Yeah.
Yeah. Have you thought that maybe
they're making up stuff or No, they're
making up stuff. This is why I'm coming
off this [ __ ] tomorrow. I'm leaving you
people to it. At least for two weeks. At Yeah.
At least for two weeks. Grezy. Jesus Christ.
I didn't go to bed until like 7.
I went to bed at 7:00 in the morning yesterday. Greasy.
It's depressing, bro. It's depressing life.
Is the person live, mate?
Nope. I ordered it.
No. What is that? Yep. Yeah, man.
What happens when you give up with life?
Yeah, that's what happens when you give
up with life. When you had too many bad experiences,
that's what happens. There's no right.
Nah, you're not descended into madness.
You've just given up with life. Should
have gave up a long time ago. Should
have left a long time ago as well.
And then you got Ant-Man saying, "Oh, if
he felt the way I did, he'd keep
trying." There is no keep trying. We
We're past that now. We're beyond that
Nope. I don't drink anymore.
We're beyond that now. We think we're
past that. We're past that stage now. I
think we're well past that stage. What
do you think?
We're up up and beyond that now. No. Nope.
Well, I'm not taking these [ __ ]
advice because why would you keep
trying? You've tried more than anyone in
the world. You don't have to try. You
should need to try. You shouldn't have
to waste any more time or any more money.
You shouldn't have to try anymore. You
shouldn't have to waste any more money.
You shouldn't have to waste any more
time. You shouldn't have to go in the
barber chair again and get your haircut
again. And wear your nice clothes. You
shouldn't have to do any of that stuff.
We've done it a million times. We're beyond that.
We're very, very beyond that now.
No, I'm all right. Thanks.
My underpants stink. I might send them
to um Greasy via the post.
My underpants stink. No, I'm all right. Thanks.
I'm going to go I'm getting out of bed
now to go for a piss.
To go for a piss.
my smelly boxes if you want. We
know why am I going to cut my own hair
and I haven't. And it's not if I have
truly given up.
I have truly given up my life
cuz nothing changes. Nothing gets
better. So there's there's no point
doing anything. There's literally like
no point even doing anything. Is that right, Grezy? [ __ ] sake. Yeah.
But we wait. [Music]
Oh my god, I got cheeseburger.
I got cheese sauce stuck on my mustache.
No, thank you. I'm all right.
I'd rather just rot.
I'd rather just rot, matey. I'm all right. Thanks.
God doesn't exist.
You don't exist.
I [ __ ] wish I did. Jesus Christ. Do I
I [ __ ] wish I [ __ ] did.
The only thing that's bad about them
shared houses is having to share a
fridge. That's why I bought my own
is sharing a fridge. That's the only bad
thing. I couldn't share a fridge with anyone.
So, I bought my own fridge.
No, a bathroom ain't even that bad.
That's not even that bad, bro. It's a
fridge. That's bad. A shower is That's
nothing, bro. Shower is nothing. It's
just someone else on a shower.
The The worst thing is sharing a fridge.
I couldn't share a fridge. So, when I
was at that house, Greezy, remember in
the winter, I'd keep my stuff outside. I
wouldn't even put it in the fridge. I'd
actually leave my stuff outside. Do you
remember in the winter I'd leave my
stuff outside cuz I don't want to use
that disgusting fridge? disgusting
monkey fridge that they would use. So I
used it in the winter. Then in the in
like March, I got myself a fridge. So
couldn't share a fridge. I would keep my
milk like outside
cuz I need to buy a fridge in the winter
cuz it was it was cold enough outside.
I couldn't share a fridge, bro. I
couldn't share a fridge.
That that fridge, mate, was disgusting.
You'd open it and it smelled like
someone's ass. Smell like someone's Oh my god.
Oh, it was disgusting.
The thought of it. I still remember
just sat in with my smelly boxes. Virgin boy.
Don't know why Virgin boy keeps calling
me big nose. I think it I think it makes
him feel better about the fact that he
knows that he's the ugly one that can
only get disabled people.
You know, I've talked about my nose a
lot, doesn't he? For somebody that
wastes all his life on me every day.
It's mad, isn't it? You know, I've
talked about my nose a lot. Jesus Christ.
Is it supposed to make me insecure or something? Jesus.
For somebody that wastes a lot of time
on someone every day, he sure likes to
talk about my my nostrils.
Yeah, I'm just going to spend all day on Reddit. That's a Oh Yeah,
that's what you do when you're at rock
bottom. The only thing you can do is try
and start a life somewhere else.
The only thing you can do is
start a life somewhere else when you're
at rock bottom grievy. That's all you can do.
I can't believe I've still got [ __ ]
money left. That's madness.
It's madness, bro. Madness.
Madness. Greasy. Madness.
My bollocks are smelly, greasy.
My bollocks are smelly. You know what I
should do? Go to an escort and get her
to suck my dick now.
There would be no chance of that happening, mate.
They're saying no.
They're start giving that [ __ ] behavior
that they always do.
That's what they would do.
Don't let these [ __ ] women win. You remember
Let's hope this comes out today. [Music]
Oh, Franklin, you almost died. Yeah.
Where the [ __ ] is that Joe gone?
Always disappears for a little bit and
then comes back. You remember
Oh, is that red? No. Yeah.
Don't know why this Izzy's ex-boyfriend
is still messaging me.
Stop being a keyboard warrior.
Has he been doing videos again?
Has he been doing videos again? Huh? I'm
going to be owning this prime today if
he comes out.
I'm going to be holding this prime today
if he comes out and smash his [ __ ]
face. And this is one of the reasons why I'm live.
And I want my four grand as well.
Well, I bet £1,000 to LT that this
cunt's not going to show up. So, I want
my four grand.
Where you at?
Well, considering it's Monday and
considering I've given up in life, no.
And I don't even get out of bed most days. No. So yeah. Yeah.
It's not the problem. Money is not the
problem. It's women and the bad
experiences that are the problem.
Yep. I've got money. [Music]
Not as much as you, but yeah. Still. Yeah,
bro. I got some [ __ ] [ __ ] stuck in my
[ __ ] beard. Look, I had a burger last night. Look.
And I got some cheese stuck in my beard.
Oh my god. It's crazy, bro.
Just can't be bothered to shower. I
can't be bothered to do nothing. It's depressing.
Depressing being in England. Depressing being here.
Probably need to shampoo it off to be honest.
That's nice, man. That's nice.
No, same old [ __ ]
Nah, I'm all right, thanks.
No, I'm all right, folks.
300 quid in your your current account.
Oh, that's funny, bro. Yeah.
So, we just got to got a shot today or what?
Yep. This new area, women, the bad
experiences with women, it's everything.
Nothing's wrong with it.
Nothing's wrong with it, man.
But I'll wait for him today anyways.
Yeah, this new area, the experiences of
women, it's enough to make anyone depressed.
It's enough to make anyone depressed, you know.
This area is depressing.
Bad experiences with women is
depressing. We're seeing reality for
what it is now. And it is [ __ ] depressing, bro.
I don't need I don't need depression
tabs. I need better experiences. I need
better life experiences. I don't need
depression tabs. I need better life experiences.
which I never got in 4 years. So, I
don't need depression tablets. I need better experiences
cuz how you feel is normal. Depression
tablets are for people that are
depressed for no reason.
You know, you're not depressed for no
reason. You have legitimate reasons. So,
unless you fix the root of the problem,
which you can't because of the bad
experience of women, there's no point
taking any tablets. It's like someone
taking anxiety medication. There's no
point someone taking anxiety medication
if they're drinking every day and their
[ __ ] their sleep cycle's [ __ ] up
cuz they need to fix the root of the
problem. And my problem is these bad
experiences with women that can't be
fixed. So, it's got nothing to do with
it's got nothing to do with depression tablets.
You know, you've got every right to feel
the way you do. It's completely normal
after your bad experiences. So yeah, sometimes.
And it's not even money. That's the
thing. The problem ain't even money.
That's the thing. It really isn't.
Just the bad experiences with women, all
the time wasting I've had in my life.
It's bad, bro. Really, really bad.
Never change. It will never change. Nah.
Yeah, I heard about that guy. I didn't
even know who who he was
when I've heard about it.
But it's completely normal. It's not an
imbalance in your mind. It's completely
normal after all the bad experiences
you've had with these women. It's
completely completely normal to feel
this way. You don't need tablets. You
need better experiences.
Yeah. Cuz it's not about money.
It's about the bad experiences. Both
what I've had, the piss taken, the
[ __ ] the hear when I've got a
boyfriend a million times, [ __ ] when
they don't, they're just [ __ ]
Yeah. A lot of millionaires killed themselves.
Yeah. I don't even know who he was, but
I heard about him a few times. Yeah. So, yeah. Oh, nice.
No, they can't. No, it's not they can
be. They are evil.
No, it's not that they can be. It's that
they are all evil. It's not that they
can be. They are. There's no can be
about it. They are. They're evil scum of the earth.
The evil scum of the earth. It's not
they can be. It's that they are.
All of them. So
get out your [ __ ] car. Franklin. Franklin,
Sorry, I just played some Franklin. But
yeah, as they can be evil, they are all
evil. Evil [ __ ] [ __ ]
That's what they are.
Evil nasty [ __ ] That's what all of them are.
That's why I don't bother with them no more.
You know, well, that's probably cuz your
nan's very very old.
I mean, I'm sure I mean, you'll probably
find some old women that aren't evil,
maybe in their 70s and 80s, but majority
of them are.
I mean, yeah, an old [ __ ] woman might
not be, but yeah,
that's why I don't go out drinking
anymore. That's why I don't go out trying anymore. Yeah.
anymore. Tried anymore.
Did you just get through the piss out of? Nope.
My land's dead on both sides. So yeah, man. [Laughter]
That's like catchy [ __ ] saying, you know, bro.
>> Yeah, I know. I can't wait for it to end, bro.
I can't wait for it to finally end.
Yeah, I just can't wait for it to all be over, lad.
Finally, you know. So, yeah.
Yeah, I need to come off this [ __ ] after
today. after this um crime doesn't show
up or shows up. I can't be arguing with
these bongos every day. [ __ ] madness.
How How am I doing? Same old stay in
bed. Don't do anything.
Same old life, bro. Same old depressing life. Yep.
But this is what watch what's going to
happen today. He's not going to show up
and no one's going to say anything
cuz you know they're biased. So that
not at all.
I finally made a new channel. I finally
These old [ __ ] found me. So
what I would do is it's the north.
It would do. It's the north land.
Oh yeah, it's cuz it's the north.
Whenever I used to go up north, it would
always used to rain.
It would rain and it would stop.
Every single time I used to go up north,
it used to rain and not stop. I remember
I got caught in the pissing rain before
in Newcastle, mate, for like 4 hours. I
was stuck in the [ __ ] rain. I was soaked
cuz I couldn't get back to
Middlesbrough. It was a madness.
H the [ __ ] we used to get up to. A
greasy. [ __ ] we used to get up to. No,
there is no specific time. He just said
that he's going to come on here in the evening.
So, we're waiting for some updates.
Hey, Cory's not ugly. Cory just looks normal.
Cory doesn't look that bad.
It doesn't matter if I don't look like
any of them Mongs. I don't have anybody,
so I might as well be as ugly as them.
I might as well look like them.
And you didn't mention the virgin either.
Yeah, but you didn't mention the virgin,
Timothy. What about the virgin in the bedsit?
The skinned virgin in the bedsit. You
didn't mention him. Skin bastard.
with a fat ugly girlfriend.
The skimp bar with a fat ugly girlfriend.
A hiccup. That must be the McDonald's
from last night. Grezy, that must be the McDonald's.
When's Nons going to lose it?
Timothy, when do you reckon nonlet is
going to lose that vcard?
When do you reckon he's going to lose
that [ __ ] vcard, mate?
I got a I got I got a milkshake. Yeah.
When do you reckon he's going to he's
going to pop it?
When do you reckon he's going to pop
that V card?
When do you reckon he's going to pop it?
When do you reckon he's going to lose it? Just hungry.
What? What else would it be other than
I'm hungry? What a silly question.
He will never get laid. Virgin boy will
never get laid. He will never lose it. Yeah.
Yeah, I hope he I hope he never loses
it. He doesn't deserve to ever have sex.
He deserves to die a virgin.
And I don't give a [ __ ] about some
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] disabled girl
that he shows. I'm [ __ ] telling you,
you're a virgin. I don't care about any
other [ __ ] I'm telling you, you're a virgin.
Uh, no I didn't, bro. I'm staying in bed
all day today. Well, well, until Prime
comes out, then I'm going to meet him
and smash his face. But no, I've give up
with life, Ben.
Oh, yeah, the butchers is No, I don't
think the butchers is open today either.
It's not open on Sundays and Mondays.
Yeah, I'm just staying in bed today,
bro. Just like every day
cuz this life don't change. So,
I'll be in bed all day.
I never used to wake up at like 12,
1:00. I used to wake up 8:00 in the
morning at the old house. 8 9
But yeah, it's too depressing, bro.
Life's too [ __ ]
Yeah, that sounds nice, bro. I'll be in bed depressed.
Lucky you, bro. I'll be in bed depressed.
I don't even think I'll eat today to be honest.
No, I don't even think I'll eat. I might
not even eat today.
Bro, I'm not addicted to gambling. I
barely gamble. You don't need to tell me that.
You don't need to tell me that, bro. I'm
not addicted to gambling.
You don't need to tell me that, daddy.
I ain't gambling. I've got no gambling urges.
I ain't played that [ __ ] for [ __ ] a
long time, bro.
If he had sex with his girlfriend, he
wouldn't have been stalking all of my
sloppy seconds for wank material. I
don't think he slept with his girlfriend somehow.
And yes, I am jealous that he's with a
disabled dwarf. That's fat. Yeah, I'm
very, very jealous. Yeah, you got me,
bro. Yeah, I'm the one stalking all of
these sloppy seconds and he's not the
one stalking mine. Yeah, bro. You're
right. Damn, you got me.
I'm jealous. Very, very jealous.
Yeah, I'm the It's almost as if I'm the
one stalking his sloppy seconds.
Well, he doesn't have any sloppy seconds
cuz he's the virgin, but it's almost as
if I'm stalking all of the people that
he's met. But I'm the jealous one, huh?
You learn something new every day.
Yeah, I don't really gamble anymore,
Ben. I can't afford to gamble with what
I want to do, bro. Like, the only thing
I gambled on is the football. The last
thing I gambled on was the football. I
put 120 on two teams and it returned 380. So,
but yeah, I'm I'm jealous, bro. I'm very very jealous.
If he's had sex with his girlfriend,
then he wouldn't be stalking all of my
ex flings for wank material.
I don't think he slept with his
girlfriend somehow. I don't think people
in normal relationships
I don't think people in normal relationships
still cover people sloppy seconds. And I
don't think a woman would allow that
unless they're disabled.
So the question still never really got
answered in it. I don't think he slept
with her. I think he's still a virgin.
I know he's still a virgin.
He might be able to pull the bull over your eyes.
That's why he stalked all of my sloppy
seconds. He stalked somebody in America.
He stalked somebody from New Zealand,
but he has sex all the time with his girlfriend.
I don't think so, buddy.
I don't think so.
And he spend all his life wasting it on
me. But I'm the jealous one. I know.
Very, very jealous, bro.
I'm very very jealous of somebody that
lives in a bed that lives in a bedsit,
that's got no bed, that's got no money,
that's had no life experiences for 3
years. I'm very very very very extremely
jealous, bro. Don't know what I'm going
to do. What am I going to do, bro?
Let me ask God if he exists. God, how do
I end up like somebody in a bedsit with
no teeth, with a disabled girl,
with no money in a bedit? How How do I
end up like this person? God
God might be able to give me the the answers.
You know, the thing is you you know, you
say that I'm the jealous one, but he's
the one that's got a channel stalking me every day.
So that really shows that that really
shows up the jealous one because I I I I
respond to it because to me it's funny
sometimes you get addicted to the
stupidity but at the end of the day you
know he's the one that spends all his
life stalking me and obsessing over me.
I don't do it to him.
I just I'm just addicted to the saying
virgin boy in the skinn bedset.
This is a little saying of mine.
Yeah, the posters did nothing to him. I
know. No, it done nothing to him, bro. Nothing. No.
Nah. No. It done nothing to him, bro.
Nothing at all. He didn't run to the
police screaming he weren't a fighter.
He didn't leave his bedit for 3 weeks.
He didn't stop going to an event for a
month. No, it done nothing to him, bro.
Obviously. Don't know. That's why he
went running to the police and crying
because it clearly done nothing to him.
Yeah. Duh. I mean, who goes running to
the police when nothing happens to them? Yeah.
Again, you people remember what you want
to remember. You're a waste of time. And
this is exactly why I'm coming off this
[ __ ] after today when I smash this
cunt's face. And cuz,
and that's what made me laugh when he
says, "Am I trying to convince people?
Why would I want to convince a biased
audience? You people already show what
you're about. You remember what you want to remember.
You forget what you want to forget. You
It's a biased audience. Could you
imagine, bro? Yeah. Going to watch a WWE
match and all of the fans are biased.
Would Would you want to fight? Would you
want to get in that ring when all of the
fans are biased? It doesn't even It
doesn't even make any sense.
These people are severely severely
jealous of me, bro. Because it's so
weird how you've got, and hear me out.
This is the reason why I say this. Yeah.
You have got so many middle-aged men
that gravitate towards you. And by you,
I mean me. Don't you think it's looking
a bit dodgy?
You've got all of these old men lining
up, gravitating to have their say about
Peter Belly. It's jealousy. That's what
it is. It these people are jealous of
something in life,
you know, like they and only know and
only they know what of because, bro,
look at people on here. Yeah. No one
gets it like me.
That's the only reason I say that
they're jealous is because how they act
and you know that they don't do it to anybody else
because it's jealousy. Bro, who would
waste their life all day every day on
someone that they're not jealous of?
Think about it.
A normal person would understand it, but
and then and then their reply is always
going to be, "Oh, what are you jealous
of?" Well, if you're not jealous of
somebody, then you would stop your [ __ ] every day.
So, it's obvious,
but they sit all online all day
bothering people at their age. It's bit
concerning, isn't it? If they done it to
other people, then I'd be like, "Oh,
yeah. They're just trying to [ __ ] with
people. They're just [ __ ] up. They're
not jealous of anyone." But when they
only go for one person the way they go
for me, and then you have to look at
yourself and think, "Okay, you're
probably better looking than them and
you're you're younger than them, then it
starts looking dodgy." Do you understand?
It starts looking a bit dodge.
It starts looking proper dodgy.
One second. Someone sent me a voicemail.
N what part of I've given up my life do
you not understand?
I have given up my life. I'm not going
anywhere on the weekend.
What part of that do you not understand? So yeah,
uh he said in the evening, but I'm
waiting for some updates.
Oh, I've been looking for you, Joe.
Yeah, I know you're away at the weekend
most days. Just lying here depressed,
haven't showered for 5 days.
Uh waiting for Prime to come because
you're supposed to be meeting me today.
I'm going to smash his face in. So yeah,
just the same old [ __ ]
same old boring life, but we're waiting
for this [ __ ] Yeah,
I went out Sunday to get a roast, but it
was too busy, Joe. I saw pregnant
people, people with kids.
Oh, it's a trigger. Yeah, he said he's
coming to London today, so we'll wait for him.
Yeah, it's such a trigger.
Antman's like Antman was like to keep
try I'd keep trying. It was dating apps
approaches. I'd have to I couldn't just
give up on women. Well, I've given up
women. There's no hope.
What the [ __ ]
Why would you want to keep trying when
there's no hope in this country? You'd
be wasting your time and you'd be
wasting your money. There's literally no hope here.
So why would you why would you keep
trying when there's literally no hope?
That sounds foolish.
I mean, yeah, you can speak to people
online and hope you get proven wrong.
But you think I'm going to go and waste
my money and my time going to the
barbers talking to people that's just
going to pretend that they've got
boyfriends when they've already made it
very clear. They've already made it
clear that there's no that they're not
interested in this country.
I mean, that's the whole point of
breaking a cycle. What the [ __ ] Some madness, bro.
You know what I mean? There's no I'm not
doing it. I'm not going out and I'm not
speaking to anyone. You can [ __ ] right
off. I've done it a million times.
Million trillion times. I'm not doing it
again. And I'm not going on them dating
apps either. They'll waste the time. So
yeah, I shouldn't have to try ever
again. I've tried more than anyone in
the world. I should never have to try again.
So what what is it going to suddenly be
different the next time you go out? Is
it suddenly just going to be different?
Oh my god. Stop repeating yourself. Stop
living in the past. Remember you said
stop living in the past.
Stop living in the past. We're not
talking about before. We're talking
about now. And he's supposed to be
meeting me today.
Go back to your [ __ ] nonslegs's
[ __ ] channel. Go back to your boyfriend.
Go back to your [ __ ] boyfriend nonslegs.
But I'm away anyways after today. So
after I own this clown again.
I don't see the point in entertaining a biased audience.
What's the point of entertaining a biased audience?
What's the point of making a show for a
biased audience? What's the fun in that? You know,
look at your comment that you've just
said about what did posters do? Posters
made the [ __ ] run to the police and stop
going out his house for 3 weeks, but you
forgot that because it doesn't suit you.
But you forgot that because it doesn't
suit you. See, you people don't remember
the L's that you you don't want to
remember the L's that you take and you
come back on here like nothing's
happened. You need to get a life.
That's the last thing I'm going to say
to you people as well when I leave later
for a little bit, couple weeks or so
that you you need to get a life.
Really, really, really need to get a life.
He'll do the world of good.
stop going to the bars and well yeah I'm
done bro I'm I've not been out for like
when was that Sunday maybe
no I don't think it's a month it's like
3 weeks I've not been out and we're only
in September So
yeah, I've completely completely lost hope.
Completely lost hope.
There's no trying again.
Something was going to happen. It would
have happened by now.
Yeah, he's got a disabled girlfriend. Congratulations.
Yeah, congratulations. He's got a
disabled girlfriend who he's never slept with.
What color medal do you want? Gold, silver,
just any Coca-Cola.
I I want you to see that. Yeah.
No, I'm not feeling sorry for myself.
I'm going by my life experiences.
There's nothing to feel sorry for. I'm
going by my life experiences. Yeah.
He said he's coming in the evening time. Yeah,
I got some McDonald's suck of my mustache. Yeah.
No, when he when he's when he gives me
that thumbs up, I'll Yeah, simple.
What you got, man?
My boxes are smelly, Joe.
I think I really um I think I really
have given up
this time, bro. 100 million%.
I generally believe I really have Yeah. D
back on Reddit. Don't worry, I don't
make any posts anymore. So people can't stalk me.
So people can't stalk me. Mhm.
Like I said, I'm for a couple of weeks
after today. Anyway, so
it's just weirdo behavior on here, man.
Time and time and time and time again. Yeah, man.
It's mad I don't go back into gambling.
It's mad like, you know, being depressed like this.
Yeah, I have my moments. I just don't
even entertain the idea anymore.
all of your enemy.
Well, how am I supposed to get nonchs
when you know for a fact,
you know, for a fact that, you know, I
can't get my hands on him? When are we
going to grow up and stop playing these
silly little games?
You know, like I said, I'm going to show
virgin legs up, you know, when he keeps
doing these videos and it just goes to
show how much of a skint virgin he is.
The more of these people do it, the more
they show themselves up. You know, I've
gone live today cuz I'm I'm meeting this
prime. He wants to meet me.
Too many bad experiences with women.
Yeah. Too many bad experiences with
women. That would get you depressed.
When you got a history like mine, that
would make anyone [ __ ] depressed.
That would make anybody depressed.
It's enough to make any [ __ ] depressed, mate.
I don't even go [ __ ] thingy anymore.
Don't even like going cinema anymore
doing anything cuz you just see couples and [ __ ]
It's depressing, bro. I generally have
lost hope. There's like no there's not
even no trying anymore. There's nothing. Yeah.
It's bad. It
is a country designed to annoy you and
piss you off.
Well, neither is going up and doing
anything that's going to change. Well,
it is. At least you're going to save
money. At least you're going to save money, right?
Leaveable going out and doing anything change anything.
Well, neither is going out and doing
anything's going to change anything. All
it's going to do is waste time and waste money. So, yeah.
Uh because I don't want to waste it.
Because I don't want to waste it,
you know. Why would I want to waste money?
I don't want to waste money anymore. You
know, simple. So,
so yeah, that's where we're at.
It is a country designed to piss you off.
It's designed to annoy you in every way possible.
Got something yesterday that I'm not
going to disclose cuz it's personal. But
it is it is designed to annoy you. And
you know the thing is if you was a bad
person in your younger years, you would
have been awarded. This is what I need
to tell my nephew when he's a bit older
to understand that in your life you want
to be a nasty person because if you're
nasty, God award you when you're older.
If you're nice and it doesn't even mean
giving money, it means like anyway
you're going to get shat on. Your life
experiences are going to be bad. God's
going to punish you. So you always need
to remember to be a scumbag [ __ ] and
then you'll get rewarded in life, you
know, especially men, especially if
you're a man as well. So obviously this
dedicated to [ __ ] nephew is going to
be a man. So you know you need to be a
nasty you you need to be a scumbag
otherwise you're going to have a [ __ ]
life. That's what I'm going to say to
him cuz it's the truth.
It's the truth.
I got I got given a I got dealt a bad card.
Yeah. I used to give people money. I
used to help people out. I've been dealt
a bad card. So
that's why I need to um I warn people if
I can help one person cuz have you
noticed have you noticed that all of the
bullies are in I know some bullies that
are married with kids. Yeah. I know
people that are actual I've known people
growing up that were actual like
horrible people and they're all married
with families and then all the good
people. I know some guy in Liverpool who
immigrated to New Zealand. He's back in
Liverpool and um he's depressed on £300
a month. Um you know he has [ __ ] all he
literally has nothing to live for and he
was he was okay
know we we still talk to this day. So as
a man you need to be a horrible nasty
person otherwise you're not going to get
what you want in life. Sounds backwards
but it's true.
You know what I'm saying? You need to be
a nasty, horrible, horrible bastard.
Otherwise, you get took the piss out of.
That's what will happen.
It can be with money. It can be with anything. So, yeah,
it's a dog eat dog world.
That's why I will cut. That's why I
don't mind starting a life somewhere
else cuz I don't give a [ __ ] about leaving like
like family behind and that. I don't
care. I generally don't give a [ __ ]
I've got no ties here. So, it's simple.
I got no ties keeping me here. So,
it's not a problem at all.
At all. At all.
That's facts, bro.
That's what you need to do.
I eat dog. Are you a [ __ ] [ __ ]
What are you asking stupid questions for?
It's a figure of speech.
Oh, look at this on Reddit, Joe. Another
woman that's obsessed with with her ex
that cheated on her.
Yeah, dog eat dog world is a figure of
speech. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's a figure of speech.
Whoa. Another person that's not over
their ex. We've heard that one before.
We've heard that one before, Joe. Oh
[ __ ] I've just read this. Someone
that's not over their ex.
They seem to like a lot of cheating
people, don't they?
I would never eat [ __ ] That's disgusting. Uh
Someone's not over there.
That's funny, bro.
No, it's not really funny. [ __ ] madness.
They're obsessed with their exes
that cheat on them. That's good. [Music]
Nah, I probably won't eat today
to be honest.
No, I probably won't eat.
Well, he didn't even eat for 5 days.
[ __ ] madness. I probably won't even eat. Too depressed.
Yeah, they don't like normal, confident
men either. My videos prove that.
Yeah, they don't like they don't like
normal confident people either, do they?
Yeah. Good for me, bro. That's on me, is it? Good.
I know my life experiences. I know what
I've experienced with these women. And
that's it. That's the end.
And the fact that you continuously being
mocked as well. So
definitely definitely is the end.
Yeah, they don't like normal confident
men. I prove that in my videos multiple
times. I was actually watching some my
approaching videos last night.
[ __ ] madness, bro. I used to be a
crazy confident bastard. Never changed anything.
This is completely normal to feel like
this. I mean, it is normal considering
dating apps don't work. It's actually
very normal. It's what people used to do
back in the day. That's probably how
your mom and dad met on the street. It's
very, very, very normal. Actually, when
dating apps don't work, it's very, very,
very normal. And what's even more normal
is doing it in the bars and clubs and
them still pretending that they've got boyfriends.
I mean, it's very, very, very normal,
especially in a place like London.
It's very, very [ __ ] normal in a
place like London.
Yeah. Do they? Yeah. November.
Oh, yeah. I heard that one before.
People meet through hobbies. Yeah, I've
heard that one before.
Yeah, I've heard that one before.
Yep. Heard that one before.
I've heard that one before. Many times.
Yeah. Meet people through hobbies and
Yeah, I've heard that one before.
Oh, you meet people through friends.
I've heard that one as well.
I've heard a lot of [ __ ] over the
years. People like to say a lot of
things, don't they?
They say a lot of things, don't they?
People say a lot of things. You know,
you people say a lot of things, don't
you? A lot of things.
You say a lot of things.
And the only way to not be tormented is
staying in bed.
Staying in bed is like the only way to
not be tormented.
You're not going out and stuff cuz you
just get tormented.
It's a country designed to annoy you in every way.
I'm the only one who can't find anyone
really. You can't find anyone. Loads of
people I know can't find anyone. I mean,
there's a lot of people that can't find anyone.
But I mean, there's a lot of people that
I know that's got no connections to each
other that can't find anyone.
I don't know, man. I don't believe you.
I know loads of people that can't find
anyone that has got no correlation to each other.
I don't know, man.
Yeah, cuz they're like me. Yeah, yeah,
yeah. Anyways, I'm blocking you now. Bye. So,
Yeah, bye-bye now.
It's actually the end of Peter B. It's
not the end of Uncle Bad Touch. It's the
end of Peter Belly.
Uncle Bad Touch retired ages ago. Baby, you're
10 steps forward on a 100 steps back.
I'm really starting to stink, bro. Which
is why I've got like no flies on me.
Like a dead fox.
Oh my god, I hate that, bro. Yeah.
Well, I mean, I go to a shop
occasionally, but that's about it.
I feel like a lot of these people that
wake up one day and then just think that,
oh, this never happened. That never Barely. Barely.
And it's not a good thing, it's a bad thing.
You see [ __ ] couples and [ __ ]
children and [ __ ] It's a bad thing,
bro. What the [ __ ]
That's a bad thing. So yeah,
I mean I ate McDonald's out of competit.
No, I just want to die. I just want this
life to end. It's too depressing.
This life is too depressing. Having bad
experiences, being mocked.
It's too bad. It's the end, bro.
It's the end of Pet River.
So that's where we are basically.
B on Instagram for like 4
I take any code yet? I don't think I have
because life clearly ain't changing. You
know, I don't know how Ant-Man can sit
there and tell me to keep trying when
I've tried more than anyone in the
world. There's we're beyond that. You
know, there's a there's there's there
there's a certain stage you get to,
right? And you're beyond that.
Just cuz you woke up one day, it doesn't
mean all of this stuff never happened.
It's not, oh, you try again. It's like,
no, you don't need to try again. You've
tried a million times. You shouldn't
have to try again. You should not have
to try again ever in your life
because of how much you already have tried, you know. So,
and the fact that you get mocked as
well. It's not even like you can go
cinema in peace.
It's not even like um
you know you get mocked. It knows how to
annoy you. This country it's designed to
mock you and annoy you, you know, with
weather, with the women, with
everything, waiting around for things.
I watched this um black guy approach
this woman on Instagram. I think it was
two days ago. And this guy starts uh
this guy starts to it
this guy starts this this guy starts
trying to get involved. And just
watching [ __ ] like that annoys me cuz
it's happened to me before as well. He
was just trying to be a [ __ ]
He was just trying to be a [ __ ]
[ __ ] And even watching it annoyed me. So yeah.
Yeah, I will try again. Three weeks in counting.
Three weeks in counting. I definitely won't.
Definitely definitely won't.
Three weeks in counting. Definitely not
going to try again.
I mean, unless you count going on Reddit
talking to people as trying, but in
terms of like approaching and drinking
and getting my haircut, nah.
No [ __ ] way.
I don't even go on dating apps. No way.
So, I actually won't because I know if
something was going to happen, it would
have happened by now. Doesn't matter
what people say.
You know, all the times you went
Manchester, all the times you went, you
know, at the end of the day, it's all it
all points to the fact that if something
was going to happen, it would have already happened.
There's no two ways about it. It would
have happened by now and it would have
happened very recently.
No, I get my haircut every month.
No. Well, I used to. Oh my god. I've got ages now. Look.
Got some cheese stuck in my bed. So yeah,
getting long, man. I can probably not up now.
Yeah, I can probably not it up now.
No, I definitely won't try again. I definitely won't.
I proved my point.
There's this black guy in America and he
said that Valentine's Day is a is a day
to mock the people that ain't wanted by no one.
It's to poke fun out of men that ain't
chosen by nobody. Huh? I just joined his community now.
But in a way, he didn't help himself. So
like, he deserves [ __ ] But I actually
tried everything. I tried my hardest. He
never tried nothing. So I mean, he he he
kind of brought a lot of it on himself.
He actually brought a lot of it on himself. So
you can't even really give that guy
sympathy. You can laugh at him, but you
can't even give him sympathy
cuz he could have easy done stuff, you
know, like he's 36. He could have used
escorts. He could have actually tried.
He never tried. See, I've tried everything.
Yeah, I might be 10 years younger than
him, but I was in a position where I
could try everything and I tried
everything. So, I mean, you know, we're
two different people.
I put myself through hell and back. So
he doesn't deserve any sympathy. But
what he's saying is the truth, but he's
Could you imagine actually trying?
Imagine he actually tried. I think he
would have killed himself. He would just
be like that other black guy. He would
have killed himself.
He would have killed himself, bro. If he
tried, he would have killed himself just
like anyone else would have killed himself.
I don't know. He said he's coming in the
evening, so I thought I'd just stay
live, wait for some updates, see what So, yeah.
And then you have to hear other people
progressing in life.
It's like torment.
It is literally like torment. The time
wasting, the piss taken. I've been
through it all. I've been through it
Think about it.
That man's not tried 10% of what I've
tried and he left.
And not even 10% of what I tried and he left.
Yeah, it's a little bit far, but I can
get there in no time.
You know, it's uh he he tried not even
10% of what I tried and he left.
So, if you weren't planning to leave,
then you would have to give up. What
What would you do? There's nothing else
you can do.
There's nothing else you can do. So, you
have to give up.
I'm [ __ ] going to shower.
I'm going to [ __ ] smack the [ __ ] up
then put my smelly boxes in his face.
[ __ ] silly [ __ ] But yeah,
it's so mad I've got more money now than
I did when I had the house. I just don't
have as much money coming in. But it's
not even a point.
I missed the old house, you know, man. I
missed the meals cooked.
It was funny with the people.
Now it's depressing here.
Money or no money, it's [ __ ]
depressing here. And I was still bad
when I was at the house as well.
But I just had like so many jokes with
people. It was fun, you know? So
now I'm just isolated having to think
about my bad experiences every day.
What a life, eh?
What a [ __ ] life to live.
What a [ __ ] life.
Yeah, I like the house, bro. It's not
even just the money. It's not even just
the money, bro.
It's not even just the money, bro.
You know, money doesn't mean anything.
They don't like Obvious. I've still got
money. I've still got money, bro.
Like, it's not about that, you know?
Yeah, you might get it slower, but
slower is better than no. So, bro, it's
like it does it doesn't even matter about that.
You know, I obviously got kicked out of
the house for a reason. So,
you know, like you got kicked out, there
was a reason for it. And everything
happens for a reason. You know, it's just [ __ ]
And it's not friends. It's not friends.
It's not friends cuz I've got friends.
It's not friends. It's the bad
experiences with women.
I was still [ __ ] in the house, but it
was just nowhere near as bad cuz Yeah.
Will they [ __ ] How will they [ __ ] give
me another house like that? That was one
in a lifetime, bro. That was one in a lifetime.
Will they [ __ ] give me a house like
that? Must be mad, bro. No way. [ __ ] hell.
Well, four bedroomedroom house. Yeah. I
don't think so, mate. I don't think so.
It's good house though. Yeah.
It's not It's not even just a It's not
even just the money, bro.
It's not even just the money, matey. Yeah. Obviously,
I was never going to leave, bro. When my
mom kicked me out, I was never going to
leave. No way was I ever going to leave,
bro. I was staying there forever, bro. [ __ ] that.
I I like the area, you know, in the
winter, the big room. I liked it there.
No, I would never I would never ever
left if I didn't have to, bro.
cuz she wanted to Oh, [ __ ] She wanted to downsize.
It was nothing because of LT. Even
though he tries to make out that it was
him. My mom never moved because of LT or
anyone on YouTube. She just wanted to uh
she just wanted to downsize.
Why? London is basically Rumford.
I mean, Runford is basically London. So,
it's basically London, bro. Some people
consider it London.
It actually is considered the London
Burough London. It's not that far. What
the [ __ ] Most people move out of London
because they can't afford it. So,
I should have died in that house, bro.
To be honest with you, I should have
died in that house. Nope.
No, it's not a city. It's a town. So yeah, [ __ ] it.
Yeah, it's depressing, Joe. Very depressing.
All these bad experiences with women,
the piss taking. Oh, Joe, did you see
what I done to that woman? It was funny,
ain't it? Well, no, it's not funny cuz I
wanted a [ __ ] nice steak. Couldn't
get a steak out the [ __ ]
Well, Ephro airport's not in London, so yeah.
E4 is not in London.
What's it considered again? I remember I
forget. It's near slow.
Yeah, I was trying I was going to get
her to a restaurant and then just walk
out with a just walk out,
but she weren't having none of it. She
was being a [ __ ] so I thought I'd be a
come back to her.
No, Heathphro is not London.
Mate, it's not London. I know I'm from
Well, your ticket's wrong because if you
look it up, he is not London.
It's not London, mate.
Trust me, it's not London. It's past
Elen and Elen's past and and Alen's barely London.
I don't know why it says it's London
because it ain't London. Maybe they
might just say it's London.
Bro, I'm not wrong there. I know about
the city that I'm from and Hephro is not London.
It's past Slow and Slow is not London.
So, how can it be London? Sorry.
Where's Prime? Don't know, man. Still waiting.
This guy's going to get really hurt
today, bro. I'm not even joking. I'm
going to smash his [ __ ] face. Shouldn't
have said London. Keo is definitely not London, matey.
As soon as you go past Elen, you're out
of London. Elen's like greater London. I
don't even I don't even think Elen
classes as London.
Nope. I don't even think Elen classes as London. Was it? No.
See, I was trying to get a steak out of her, Joe.
He lives in Birmingham.
Just like I've been saying all along.
Did you see what happened to NatJ?
[ __ ] a woman hit me, I'd kick her [ __ ] ass.
I would kick her [ __ ] ass, bro.
I would kick her [ __ ] ass, bro. I
don't even care, you know.
I'd love for a [ __ ] in London to
start on me today, bro.
I'd love for an old [ __ ] to [ __ ]
start on me today.
I really, really do.
I hate this country and I hate the
[ __ ] in it.
I mean, yeah.
If that guy wanted to try and get
involved, that's happened to me before
as well when you got some random
[ __ ] tries to get involved. Yeah,
it's happened to me.
It has happened to me. It happened to me
when I was doing an Uber.
I parked the bike and I just went and
approached this person. This random
person tried getting involved, trying to
start walking up toward me. Bit of [ __ ]
Oh, nothing's changed then, has it? I'm
watching these guys approaches and it's
like, "Oh, nothing's changed, has it?"
Women still saying they've got
boyfriends and you still have these
[ __ ] men defending, not even
defending women, trying to get involved
because they're jealous they can't do it themselves.
H seems things really don't change, does it?
So what what are you supposed to do? Try
That's annoying, bro.
It's like that [ __ ] Morgan. I'd smash
her [ __ ] face and I'll kick her in a
I don't give a [ __ ] who like I I said
this [ __ ] as well, bro.
You know, it doesn't matter who they
are. I'll smash the [ __ ] face in. I
don't care. I don't give a [ __ ] if it's
a woman. I don't give a [ __ ] I don't
give a [ __ ] if it's a woman. And I don't
give a [ __ ] if it's a [ __ ] man. You
know what I mean? Yeah.
Yeah, I won't be eating today, I don't think.
Why do you think people ban on Reddit, Greasy?
Is it because the truth hurts? Yeah,
that's what it is.
Yeah, that's what it is.
I mean, I post stuff saying that how do
you get over the fact these are your
experiences with women and stuff and
then they just bad you. Yeah.
And they shadowban you as well.
They shadowban you.
That's what they do. They shadowban you.
type on Instagram for 4 days. That sucks.
That [ __ ] sucks. [ __ ] Oh yeah,
his ex still texted me. He's obsessed,
bro. He's never going to come to London
and do anything. I don't understand the
point of it.
He's just proven himself to be a keyboard warrior.
That's all he's doing when he's
messaging me on Facebook like this. He's
just proven himself to be a keyboard warrior.
These men are really going to get
themselves hurt one day, Grezy.
They're really, really, really going to
get themselves hurt trying to act good
for women. You know, they really are one
day, bro. I'm telling you, they really are. Yeah.
He's just jealous cuz I had Isabelle before him.
We just genocide Isabelle before him. Grey,
that's all it is, mate. That's all it is.
Look, he's still typing away. What the [ __ ] You know,
cuz he actually blocked me then. He
actually unblocked me, which don't make
sense cuz you're not even with her anymore.
He's not even with little Isabelle. Yeah.
Closest you got to having her was
following her home and sleeping on her
floor. Literally nobody wants you. I
said ah that's that's what she told you.
That's what she told that's what she told you.
That's what she told you, buddy.
That's what she told her. her at the
time boyfriend. Uh
yeah, she didn't tell you about her
kissing me, doing her makeup, stripping
in front of me, shagging on the floor.
She didn't tell him that though, did
she, Grezy? Nah,
you'll never get the full truth,
you know, from a woman. You never get
you never get the full truth.
Yeah, I admitted I followed someone home.
Yeah. Okay, bro.
I said I said to him, "Anyways, when you
coming to London, big man?
You know, you've blocked me, then you've
unblocked me. So what?
These men that try to look good for
women, it's mad. And I don't give a [ __ ]
if she was your girlfriend. I don't give
a [ __ ] I'll smash her in and I'll smash
you in. I don't give a [ __ ] Yeah. Do
you understand what I mean, silly [ __ ]
Well, you [ __ ] Well, you [ __ ] unblocked me.
Well, you [ __ ] unblocked me. So what?
How was How was your Valentine's this year, Grezy?
How was your Valentine's um this year?
I think I probably forgot it was
Valentine's [ __ ] this year to be
honest. Still in that house when I
But it's a way to poke fun out of the people.
Nope. Same old how it how it would always be.
Same old same old sad song. Just like
forever. Forever and always. Valentine's
Day is just a day to poke fun out of the
people that ain't chosen by nobody. Greasy.
It's a day to poke fun out of the people
that ain't wanted by nobody.
Did you know that? Yeah.
It's a way to poke fun out of people.
It's not even funny, bro. To be honest,
Valentine's Day is just a day to poke
fun out of the people that ain't wanted
by no one.
Have you watched that black guy in
America? You should start watching him, Greezy.
You should start watching him.
Feel like I need a good hangover again,
man. I've not drunk for like a month.
I haven't drunk for like a month, bro.
Maybe I'll never drink again.
Already tried it. Tried it a million times.
I've already tried that. I've got
designer clothes. I've been to the
barbers. I've got nice after shave. I've
already tried that. They've all got boyfriends
and they're all piss takers.
Yeah, I've tried that already.
I've still got lots of designer clothes.
I've tried that a million times for the
past four years. No results. Thumbs down.
Yeah, I tried that. I've got loads of
approaching videos. You must be new to the channel.
Yeah, you must be new to the channel.
Well, if you're new to the channel, boy,
I've got some stuff to tell you.
I've got a lot of stuff to tell you. If
you're new to the channel, mate,
we've got a lot to tell you. What we've
been up to for the past four years.
How you doing, notorious man? I haven't
drunk or approached for like 3 weeks.
Depressing, bro. Depressing.
I completely give up in this country.
No, I can approach. Fine. It's their
standards. They're stuck up and they're
westernized. It's them that's the
problem. I don't need to learn to talk
properly to these stuck up women.
They're the problem, not me.
And there's no right or wrong way to
approach. You approach somebody just as
like you talk to a friend. There's no
Jedi mind tricks.
Nope. There's no right or wrong way. You
must be new to the channel. Welcome to
I've got a lot to tell you.
Um, there's no right or wrong way to
talk to someone. It's the same as how
you would talk to a friend.
You're new. Um, so where do I start?
I've approached 7,000 women in about 4 years.
Yeah, I've approached about 7,000 women.
I'm not going to attack you cuz
obviously you're new here. But uh yeah,
literally there's no hope in this country.
Like Notorious, I don't think I will
ever ever try again.
Generally don't think I'd ever try
again, bro. Three weeks in counting.
I don't think I will ever try again,
bro. It's the end, I think. Definitely.
But yeah, welcome to the channel anyways, man.
Boy, we've got a lot of stuff to tell
you and show you.
Get some nice clothes and get a haircut.
Oh, it's funny you should say that.
Did you say wear some nice clothes? Did
you say wear some nice clothes and get a haircut?
Funny you should say that. We've been
doing this for four years.
Yeah. Gay gay jokes again. The gay jokes
again. Grow up.
Yeah, they Yeah, I have tried them. They don't work. Yeah.
Oh, look at my hair. It's so long and nice. Oh,
my hair's so nice when you comb it.
I never asked money for a [ __ ] I
don't know what you're talking about.
at what time he's going to come on here
and tell me
he's going to come on here and we're
going to arrange it.
Yeah, it's a it's a different game now, mate.
If you got Snapchat or anything, I'm
more than happy to show you my
approaches and show you my experiences,
but to be honest, it probably won't suit you. So,
yeah, to be honest with you, it probably
won't suit you.
I never offered to give Monty a [ __ ]
He's talking [ __ ] That's why they think
I'm ignoring it. Because it's [ __ ]
It's immature. It's [ __ ]
It's not even believable. That's why I
ignore it because it's pathetic.
Yeah. Used to Yeah, cuz back in the day
you could meet people from dating apps.
You could meet people back in the day.
It was easier back then.
Now it's just impossible.
Do you know what's so mad? Like if you
actually sit in this position now four
or five years later, you know, when
you've been lied to your whole life, you
would actually think, oh yeah, you just
go out and speak to someone, it's going
to happen. That's what I used to think.
Well, I didn't me I didn't offer that. So, yeah.
That's why I'll never meet him again.
That's why I'll never be his friend
again because he just makes up [ __ ]
and he snakes people all the time just
like in Discord. That's why I'll never
meet him again.
You're not Oh, you're not long HMPP. How
long was you in prison for?
That probably explains it.
Yeah. Get a haircut and go and speak to
people. Huh? If only it was as easy as that, eh?
And it's so bad looking back now, 5
years later, you've been lied to your
whole life. It's crazy, is it? You've
actually been lied to your whole life.
Wow. You actually got lied to
thinking that we was going to meet
someone and [ __ ] It's madness. Uh,
that's not good, is it?
Look at my [ __ ] hair. I'm looking at
my hair in the mirror, bro. And you got
these [ __ ] projectors trying to say
that I'm bored.
Jesus Christ. Like, these people need to
stop putting themselves down.
These people need to stop putting themselves down.
Why do these people put themselves down
every day on YouTube? Just mad.
Looking at that [ __ ] hair, bro. What
the [ __ ] Red Star and that. All he does
is put himself down every day.
I never owed no Barbber's money. I've
already explained it and I'm not
explaining it again. So yeah,
low lines on here. I've already
explained the story about a million
times. So yeah,
when are you people going to stop doing
it anyway? It's coming on YouTube
calling people skin. We need to start
thinking of some new things now, bro.
Some new sayings.
How much is a haircut? About £37.
So you So you go out, you spend £37, you
spend £100 drinking just to get told I
have a boyfriend and buy a million women.
That's the reality of it.
That's And then it literally never changes that you
because I never said I owed a barber 40.
If you listen to it properly, you would
have heard. I'm not explaining myself.
I'm not explaining myself, bro. I'm not
explaining myself. If you want to make
up things and take things out of
context, then that's on you, bro. I
ain't explaining myself. Simple.
This is why I don't join LJ's live
streams. It's just for the
self-reflection and a load of questions.
That's why I don't even well I don't go
on any channels except Virgin Boy
sometimes to laugh at him.
That's why I don't go on that channel
that [ __ ] channel. This bastic [ __ ] boss. So yeah.
What the [ __ ] is that? A leaf. Yeah.
But yeah, I've got a lot of um yeah,
I've been basically approaching a lot of
people up and down the country for
years, Billy. Seems most of them got boyfriends.
I combed my hair, bro. Do you like it?
I combed my hair.
Do you like it? It's got some volume and
[ __ ] Balding my ass.
[ __ ] bald in my [ __ ] ass. Crack,
you don't know how much money I have.
Oh, you're that [ __ ] from yesterday.
Oh, bye-bye now. Oh, I just closed door.
You're that [ __ ] from yesterday.
Bye-bye. Go self-reflect on LJ's
channel. Go back to where you got dispatched from.
Don't come on my channel, you projecting bastard.
Yeah, a bit of time.
Yeah. Well, I mean, I basically I
basically am in prison anyways. Really,
if you think about it,
look at that virgin boy can never grow
that. I mean, I basically am already to be honest.
Yeah, that Tim Alg that's a
self-reflector that's come from uh LJ's channel
talking about people that they don't know.
They love talking about people that they
don't know every day in it. Don't know
what they have. Don't know how much
money they have.
They sure love to self-reflect. H these people
do you in I'm going to [ __ ] do you in mate
I want to [ __ ] do you in this cup Hey, Yeah,
I got something today to cook. Probably
just cook that
cuz it's just there. Just because it's
just there, you know?
Just cuz it's just there, man.
You know what I mean?
You know, October was kind of a good
month. I liked October, you know, kind
of getting drunk and that. I don't know.
My favorite month is October and March.
I do like October though. It's It's the
time you can start dressing up a little
bit nice, you know?
kind of like it bit in the middle.
They're my favorite seasons in the middle.
Don't know. It's just seems
winter is too [ __ ] whatever [Applause] you
Skin in the sketch. Yeah.
Yeah. You should You told me to get nice
clothes, Billy. Do you want to see some
of my clothes?
I'll show you some of my clothes if you
want, bro. Do you want to see some of my clothes?
Well, you're 18 months too late. Do you
want Do you want to see some of my
clothes? I've got some clothes and some
new stuff. You know,
I got some clothes. They do need dry cleaning.
But they'll come out brand new when they
have been. I promise you.
I got clothes to last me two years, bro.
Just cuz I used to have a lot of money.
I've got Stone Island jumpers. I've got Reese clothes.
More than enough clothes, bro. Which is
This is what I was thinking of
yesterday, Joe. It's like it's not
there's no really excuse. There's not
really an excuse why you didn't find
anyone. You had money. Like, you still
have money now, but like
let's talk about back then. You had
money. You had clothes. You had looks.
You had personality. You was young.
You know, you asked there's nothing.
There was no real reason why you didn't meet anyone.
It's not even like people could say you
were skin cuz you weren't even skinn,
you know, and you basically were a
landlord. You weren't lying when you
said you were a landlord until you lost
that case in court. You was a landlord.
So, there's not really any there's not
really any excuse for it.
You weren't skin. you weren't, you know,
on benefit like you weren't not doing anything.
So there's not really a there's not
really no the common No, it's them. No,
it's them. I've put my approaches up. I
have shown, you know, them pretending
they've got boyfriends. I've shown
people arranging to meet me and then not
meeting me. No, it's them. It's
definitely these women. 100% it is these
women because we're not even just
talking about approaches, bro. We're
talking about messages when you even got
their numbers and then they took the
piss out of you. No, it's definitely
them. Evidence don't lie. Evidence does
not lie. The the problem is them.
Literally, the problem is literally
them. So bad that is why I don't even
try anymore. If I thought for a second I
was lying, I'd be out today approaching.
The problem is literally them. It is
literally them. I have shown normal
conversations where I was supposed to
meet people, they didn't show up. They
started acting like a [ __ ] I had
there's conversations where I was
supposed to meet somebody and all of a
sudden they couldn't get over their ex.
That is them. That is literally them.
Yeah. A few times it might have been me.
Maybe six or seven times it might have
been me out of them for seven years.
Yeah. Yeah. Probably there was sometimes.
93% of the time it was then. It
definitely definitely was then. You know,
I was wrong maybe seven or eight times,
but not all of them times, bro. I've got
messages, I've got approaches, I've got
everything. And there's nothing that can
be critiqued because that's why they
don't get critiqued, cuz there's nothing
wrong with them. That's why people
resort to making stuff up. You see,
you'll find with these people on Reddit,
they don't want to see these messages.
They don't want to see these approaches.
They want to resort to making stuff up
because they know that it's they dismiss
your struggles which proves that you're
right because you've documented
everything. You've literally documented
everything. It's not even it's not even
up for debate. There's no there's not
it's not even up for debate. You've got
the evidence. The evidence is there and
people want to dismiss it. So, I mean,
if they want to dismiss it,
you know, then they can do that. But
there is no there is no no it is them
and all of the times that I've been
wrong. I know when I've been wrong. I
know when I've been wrong and 93% of the
time it wasn't me. I mean it's not it's
like why are we having a debate when the
evidence is there?
It's like going to court, right, being
up for murder and saying that uh well,
the common demeanor is damn and it never
happened. And then there's literally
video evidence of you stabbing someone.
What What What do you think the court is
going to What do you think the judge is
going to do? What do you think the judge
is going to do? So So
I mean it definitely definitely
definitely is them. I mean that that
woman that I stood up on Saturday, she
was a [ __ ] She was a [ __ ] She was
trying to give me a lecture and tried to
make me insecure and then tried to be
stuck up and be a [ __ ] towards me. So I
thought, "Okay, I'll [ __ ] with her." And
people were saying, "Oh yeah, but
revenge is for losers," which is true.
But the whole point was to get something
out of it, which was the free steak. I
was planning to get the free food out of
her. So I mean I mean that's what the
whole point was. The whole point was I
was actually benefiting from it, but she
didn't fall for it, so I had to just
give her a run around.
I don't know. A lot of them are
probably. Yeah. Or they're probably with
some drug dealer that's just come out of prison.
Yeah. A lot of them are still single. Probably. Yeah.
I mean, I've shown you evidence. I've
shown you approaches. I've shown you
messages. I don't know what more
somebody can show you,
you know. So,
no, the problem is definitely them. It
definitely definitely definitely is
them. 90% of the No, no, let's just say
90% of the time it is them.
But you want to say they're not, but the
evidence don't lie. I mean, the evidence
literally does not lie.
Like, the evidence literally does not
lie. Bro, you're talking as if you've
not been shown actual evidence. You seem
to try, you seem to like to dismiss it.
So, and it doesn't matter if they're
still single or not. It's how they've
acted towards me.
I mean, like I said, I've got people
I've actually arranged to meet and then
they've on the day they've not met up.
We literally arranged to meet. How you
going to How you going to talk your way
out of that one?
How are you going to talk your way out
of that one? You know,
how will you talk your way out of that one then?
Cuz they're piss takers. Simple. So,
it definitely definitely is them.
I see them do it to other men. See, the
thing is you you sit there, right, and
you say about how, oh, yeah, like the
common demeanor is you, but isn't it
funny how every guy that I watch goes
and does approaches get the same thing?
I have a boyfriend. I'm not interested.
You are too young for me. You are too
old for me. Isn't it mad how all of
these people get the same stuff
and it's not just you? If the common if
the common um demeanor, I don't know how
to pronounce that word, was me, then
this would not be happening to other men,
men. It would be happen to no one else
but me. But it clearly is cuz I'm
watching it happen to other people.
Okay. Well, what about when other Okay,
then. So, so if they So, okay. So, let's
go by your logic then. So, let's just
say that what they're in a relationship.
All of the stuff that I'm showing you is
not true. Them saying that they're going
to meet and then they don't meet and
then acting like [ __ ] I mean, it is
true because I've shown the evidence.
So, even if they are in a relationship,
that doesn't change the fact that
they've acted that way towards me. That
doesn't mean anything. Just because they
might be in a relationship a year later,
I have got literally the messages. I
have got the approaches that I have done
and I know what I've experienced.
So that's that, you know.
So that doesn't really mean anything
because they they could have [ __ ] a
million guys over and then got with one finally.
Okay. Well, no, it's them again. You're
dismissing all of my struggles again.
This is what people on Reddit like to do. No,
it is literally them. Do you want me to
put all of the evidence back up again?
No, it is literally them.
Just because they have [ __ ] someone
over and then got into a relationship,
it doesn't mean it's not them.
You know what the [ __ ]
And then relationships don't even last
long anyways cuz people know what
they're like. Just like that. USA is
that guy will break up with her soon
when they finally realize what she's like.
It is them 100% them. That's why I
refuse to waste any more time, any more
money, anymore going to the barbers. I
refuse, you know. So,
if I didn't think it was generally them,
I would have been out by now. You know,
we're not even in winter. I've never
stopped for this long. Never. only in
January and February maybe, but not now. So, yeah.
No, it is definitely definitely
definitely definitely definitely
definitely them. 1 million% it is them.
The fact that I see other guys doing the
same thing and getting the same [ __ ] is
a red flag. It's like it's not like you
see these other guys not getting it.
Then I'd be like, well, if these people
are in the same position as me and
they're approaching and they're not
getting the [ __ ] I'm getting and maybe, just maybe,
it could be me, but they're getting
exactly the same [ __ ] as well.
Because it is these women. That's what
it is. It is these [ __ ] women. That's
what it is.
I watch this black guy. He's got his
[ __ ] together. He's not ugly. He goes
around London approaching women. I have
a boyfriend. I have a boyfriend. I'm I
hate watching it. It annoys me just
watching it. I have to stop watching
him. But oh, it's big Peter Belly that's
the problem. Yet you got some guy that's
got his [ __ ] together that's not even
ugly and he's more confident than me as
well cuz I don't really do them anymore.
And he's getting exactly the same thing.
Isn't that a thing? Hey, he's getting
exactly the same thing. He's got an
Instagram channel just like these other
guys in America. Isn't it mad how so
many guys get the same thing? But no, it
can't be these women, can it? No. No. It
can't be the fact that they're stuck up
with unrealistic expectations. Nah, it's
got to be the guy, you know?
Come on, man. Have a word with yourself.
You're not stupid. So, stop acting like you're stupid.
Like I've seen other guys, they get the
same thing. Just because they get with
one guy in the end doesn't mean
anything. What about all of them other
million people that they [ __ ] over?
What? So just cuz they're with one guy now.
So no, it is them. It definitely
definitely is them.
And the fact they can't critique
anything I do yet I ask them to do it.
It just goes to show when they have to
resort to making stuff up, it's it it
just goes to show
they resort to making stuff up because
I'm right. That's why. Cuz if they if if
I wasn't right, then they would critique it.
Yeah. Because he was probably a [ __ ]
and a pedophile and just come out of
prison. Duh. Obviously.
So, yeah. Probably cuz they're a
[ __ ] pedophile. Women seem to like
to go for them people. So yeah, probably. Yeah,
maybe the guy's a millionaire. Who knows?
But it doesn't have anything to do with
me. It doesn't have anything to do what
I have experienced and I will keep experiencing.
Like it doesn't matter. The whole point
is who cares? It's not going to benefit
my life. It's not going to change my
experiences. So why do I care what other people do?
Yeah, I generally do believe that. I
generally generally generally do believe that.
Yeah, I wouldn't say if I didn't believe it.
So, yeah, I generally generally do believe that. Oh, [ __ ] Hiccups.
I generally generally do believe it. Yeah.
But it doesn't really matter either way
because it's not going to change the
fact of what I've experienced and what
I'll continue to experience if I try
again. These people have got no relation to me.
Waste of time really comparing yourself
to other people.
Why compare yourself to other people?
It's not going to change you, is it?
But you seem to dismiss a lot of the
stuff that they've done. That's how you
know that you know you're wrong because
you're you've dismissed literally
everything that they've done. The piss
taken, the leading on. Like they done
this. It's it's in black and white paper.
It's in A12 paper, bro. What they've
actually done. But then you still go on
to talk about other people that has no
relation to me. It's ridiculous. It's
absolutely [ __ ] ridiculous madness.
That's why I don't even go out anymore.
It's too depressing seeing it, bro.
So, yeah, I generally generally do
believe that. Yeah,
like I said, it's a country designed to annoy you.
Nah, I think you know what I think is
sad that you dismiss people's struggles.
That's what I find is ridiculous. I find
it's ridiculous how you dismiss people's struggles.
Like I've shown you them leading on
pretending that they've got boyfriends
and stuff and you still resort to
talking about other guys that have
nothing to do with me. So it just
doesn't make no sense.
I know what they're like. I've known
what they're like for years, which is
why I don't bother with them. You know,
that says it all. When somebody like me
has given up, that says a lot, you know. Um,
no. I just want you to understand what
where I'm coming from and why I've given up.
Then you resort to talking about other people.
So, it's just ridiculous because we all
know that most men struggle. It's not
like most men don't struggle. Most men
struggle says it all.
So, at the end of the day, yeah,
doesn't matter if I'm a grown man or
not. It doesn't matter. I've tried
everything. I could be a [ __ ] 15y
old. It doesn't matter. Credit is where
credit is due.
You know, you give credit when credit's
due. It doesn't matter if someone's
grown, 15. It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter, mate.
So, you can't have sympathy for people
because they're what? An adult. Is that
your way of thinking? That's ridiculous.
You can't have sympathy for people cuz
they're grown. Get out of here, man. Get
the [ __ ] out of here.
And all of these women that have gone on
dates to pass time and [ __ ]
I know what they're like. I know what
the these women are like, which is why I
don't waste my time on them anymore.
I'm just happy I got a lucky escape with
the house and I got some money out of
it, to be honest.
So, I'm just so happy, bro, that I don't
have to ever try her ever again.
It's like what M. What else can you do
but keep trying? You can't keep trying.
Keep trying is not an option.
It is not an option. We don't know what
the option is, but that is not an option.
Don't just wake up one day and think all
of a sudden it's going to change.
You know what I'm saying?
No, you should give people sympathy for
the fact that they've spent loads of
money. They've been up and down the
country. They've had to deal with [ __ ]
with these women. Yeah.
these [ __ ] [ __ ] shitty [ __ ] women.
You know, the most mocking thing, J, is
when you hear Oh [ __ ] man. is when you
hear The most mocking thing is when you
hear someone's having a baby.
I don't know if that used to mock you.
He used to mock me. I don't know. I
don't know if you have kids or whatever,
but he used to mock me. And he would
always mock you at the right time. I noticed that
it was always at the right time.
It's like this country knows your next
move. It's like this country knows your
ex your next move.
It's so weird. Like it's like it knows
what you're doing and knows what you're thinking.
Imagine I went to gambling now and I
lost all my money. I'd be [ __ ]
Imagine that. Imagine I went gambling
right now and I lost all my money. I
would be [ __ ] up properly.
No, just the fact that they're [ __ ]
other people and letting other people
come inside them and degrade them and [ __ ]
No, I don't want kids. But it's just
it's still it's still the point. That's
what I'm saying. I don't even want kids,
but it's still the point.
It's like it knows your every move.
This country knows your every move. It's
like it's watching you. That's what it
feels like. This this annoying country.
Just this annoying ass country, you know.
So, no, I don't want What the [ __ ] So,
no, I don't want kids, but um
because they're still having sex with
people and they're still giving people
what they're starving you of. That's why
they're still like
you're giving people what they're
starving you off. And obviously you've
got a history.
So you need to take your history to the
grave with you. You know I have to take
that to the grave with me. You know how
how I tried more than anybody in the world.
Do you know what I mean?
Yeah, it does. It's annoying, bro. Cuz
it's the fact How do you have How do you
have kids? You have sex, right? You have
You have sex. So, you've got kids, so
you have kids when you have sex. No. So,
it's just to poke fun out of people.
It could be anyone. It could be a
[ __ ] YouTuber. It's just a way to
poke fun out of people
that ain't chosen by nobody.
You know what I'm saying? It's just a
way to poke fun out of people
that ain't wanted by no one. Even though
you're good-looking and you got money,
but it's madness, isn't it? Just one of
them things, eh?
It's a way to poke fun out of people
that ain't wanted by no one.
This is why I'm saying to This is what
I'm saying, bro. This is why I'm going
to say to my nephew, you need to be a
[ __ ] You need to be a [ __ ] in life cuz
God will reward bad behavior.
God rewards bad men.
They reward bad men.
Remember that with women, with life, you
know, it's true.
So it's just like you're alive to be
mocked. That's basically what it feels like.
It's too late. It's too late.
And just because I don't want kids, it
doesn't change the fact that they're
[ __ ] people. You know what I'm
saying? And having kids. You have to
[ __ ] somebody to have kids.
So, you know, it's still sex. So, at the
end of the day, yeah,
it's too late to become bad. You had to
do that when you was younger. You had to
be a bully when you was younger. So, yeah. Crazy
is it crazy
because all of the people that I've
known right from childhood like all the
[ __ ] and bullies and stuff they all married.
Married with married or they've got kids
and then the people that I know that
weren't bad or depressed, they're worse
than me. Doesn't that tell you something?
Cuz that's their life, bro. That's their life.
That'll always be their life. Yeah.
It's funny how you don't egg me on to
play online roulette anymore, is it,
Joe? You used to egg me on to play
online roulette, but not anymore. Yeah,
cuz it's [ __ ] rigged.
Cuz it's rigged. That's why.
They might have gone to jail, mate. But
they might have gone to jail, but yeah,
one second. They might have gone to
jail, but I bet you they've got nice
birds. I bet you they've got nice girlfriends.
I mean, yeah.
They've gone to jail, but they probably
have nice girlfriends. They're in jail
and they've got girlfriends. There's
people in jail that have actually got
girlfriends. Most people in jail have got girlfriends,
and there's actually people in the
outside world that don't have anyone.
There we go. One second.
Oh, you little [ __ ] What time you
going to be there?
>> I say you're still coming.
>> Yeah, I'm still coming.
>> All right, cool. Um,
>> yeah. What time you going to be there?
I reckon half six.
>> Half six. Yeah. Okay. I'm coming and I'm
going to go live. Yeah.
>> Yeah, that's fine.
>> that's fine.
>> Put Put your Put your Put your camera on now.
>> I'm in the hotel now.
>> You're in the hotel where
>> I'm in the hotel now. That's all you
need to know.
>> Yeah, but where where are you?
>> I'm in the hotel now. I'm not I'm not
>> But where are you?
>> Listen, I will go live. I I will I would
even come and show you exactly where I
am. I'm not bothered.
>> Okay. Good. Good. Yeah.
>> I'll see you there. 6 6:30. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Don't be late.
>> I'll be there. Crystal Palace.
>> Yeah. I I'll tell you exactly where I'll
be. I'll be One second. I will be
on Park Road where it meets White Horse
Lane. There's a there's a chicken and
grill place there.
>> Okay. I'll see you there. Yeah.
>> All right. Cool.
>> Yeah. Right. Kicked him. 6:30. Right.
So, it's going to take me roughly about
an hour and a bit to get there. So, I
don't need to leave just yet.
So, anyways, back to what you were saying. Um,
yeah, there's people in jail that's in relationships.
So, I mean,
yeah, there's women in relationships. So, [ __ ]
So, yeah, I'll see you. What do you say?
6:30. Yeah. Yeah. It takes me an hour a
bit to get there. Not a problem at all.
So yeah, anyways, these women
they they go they go they're they're
they're in relationships with people in jail.
So actually it's not the opposite
going to go out and it's all of a sudden
going to change.
That's so believable, isn't it, Joe?
that one day you're going to go out and
all of a sudden it's going to change. Huh? Yeah. Right.
keep trying. For what reason?
Keep trying. For what reason?
Yep. Are you still on YouTube? Yeah,
let me see how far it is actually.
Nah, you know what? I can't be bothered
to meet him. I'm going to give him the runaround.
Nah, I can't be ass meeting him. Sorry,
mate. I can't be bothered. I changed my mind.
Nah, I changed my mind, mate. Sorry. Yeah.
Oh, but it's okay for Terry to do this,
and it's okay for Arsenal Mark to do
this. Hey, that's not nice. You let
Arsenal Mark get away with it.
Yeah. Do you know what? I'm not even
going to waste my time, bro.
Yeah. I'm going to be like Arsenal,
Mark, and Terry. I might get some more I
might get more respect for it. Nah,
I know, man. I know. I know. I know.
I I know. I know. I'm just being Arsenal
Mark and Terry. I'm just being Arsenal
Mark and Terry. I'm not [ __ ] going to
[ __ ] Crystal [ __ ] Padis. You [ __ ] mad.
Not worth my time. Oh,
it's not worth my time, bro.
Not worth my time.
And hey, can you stop talking about it,
please? Can you forget about it?
Yeah, I know, man.
Nah, I'm not going. I can't be asked.
a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
Ah, no. He's not giving me money. No.
Why am I comparing myself to others?
Because you like to do it a lot.
You like to do it a lot.
Think about it. I got no mention going
to Nonleg's area. I got no mention going
um Mark Samson's area, Tererry's area.
So, yeah, I'm not wasting my time again.
Yeah, I'm all right, bro. I'm good.
I'm just doing what you people do.
Nothing more, nothing less.
And to be honest with you, I'm [ __ ]
28 next [ __ ] month. [ __ ] going all
the way somewhere to meet someone on
YouTube that I don't know for a fight to
entertain a biased audience. Well,
you're right, thanks. I'd rather sit
down and play Franklin. It sounds like a
much better idea.
God, my mom would be so embarrassing me
as well. It's embarrassing, bro. Very very embarrassing.
Very very very embarrassing. And the and
the most madest part is that they're all
biased on here anyways.
You're all biased.
You all you all take sides anyways. So
why am I going to waste my time and
waste my money? It doesn't make any
sense. [ __ ] that.
I know him. I don't know his name. I
don't know how old he is.
Come on, man. Stop giving me stick. You
let [ __ ] Mark Samson get away with
[ __ ] You let Terry get away with [ __ ]
You let Nons get away with [ __ ] [ __ ]
hell. Let me get away with [ __ ] for
once. You let all of these people get
away with [ __ ] not showing up.
Yeah, I know, man.
Yeah. See, in this in this situation,
you can't win because if you don't go,
they're going to say you bottle it. And
if you do go, they're just going to
forget you went and just go against you
anyways. So, at the end of the day, you
can't win either way.
You can't win either way. A wise man
learns from his mistakes. And I know
what you people do on here.
You people have been bottling it for
years. For [ __ ] sake, you people have
been bottling it for years.
You people have been bottling it for [ __ ] years. So,
and it's embarrassing as well, bro. Very embarrassing.
No, I won't. No, I won't.
You've always been losing, doggy. You've
been losing since you come out your
mom's [ __ ] I didn't get no respect when
I went to Mark Samson's area two times.
I didn't get no respect when I went to
Nons's area three times. I got no
respect when I went to Terry and he
never showed up. Yeah, you can [ __ ]
do one. That little [ __ ] manipulation
tactic ain't going to [ __ ] work. You
can all get [ __ ] Yeah.
Damned if you do, damned if you don't.
Uh, damned if you do. No, I don't need
to stop doing anything. I don't need to
I don't need to stop doing anything,
mate. I can do what I want when I want.
I will do what I want when I want. If I
want to call people out and waste
people's time like you people do, I'll
do exactly that. You people have been
doing it for years. So
I know show is forgotten easily. Really?
Is it actually? But that's interesting.
I'm not me.
>> And I'll bet you Oh, what did that man
just say? Yeah, cuz it's If I'm alive
then Yeah, it's
cuz it's my birthday
and I'm not letting you in. Bye-bye.
Yeah, you're saying all of this now, but
you wasn't saying it then. So yeah,
that is effort, bro. I'm not I'm not meeting you.
Don't care who you are. I'm not meeting you.
I'm not meeting you, mate. So yeah.
Yeah. My birthday is the 27th of October. Yes.
Nah. You people will never show anyone
respect. That's one of the reasons why I
don't waste my time on you people.
I've already beat people in [ __ ] fights.
Nah, you people are biased. You're a
waste of our time. You're a waste of our
time. I've already beat I've already
beat people in [ __ ] fights before.
Two people I've beat two people in fights
and no one never brings it up. They like
to make up stories. Yep.
No, I was supposed to be meeting him
today, but I can't be bothered. So, yeah.
You know, you're never going to catch me off guard.
You're never going to catch me off guard.
You're never ever catch me off guard.
But there's no point even saying that
cuz you're never going to catch me off guard.
No, I don't need to do anything.
Letting me off so easy. Bro, listen.
You're never going to be catching me off guard.
Yeah, I'm not wasting my time on some
[ __ ] loser like you. Yeah,
not [ __ ] wasting my time and some
[ __ ] loser like you, bro.
Let's just think about it. What do you
gain? Nothing. I go and I smash this
[ __ ] up. What do I gain? Nothing.
Literally nothing. I'm giving these
people what they want. Time, attention,
[ __ ] They're all biased anyways. I
get literally nothing out of it.
You know what? Right. No, I don't want
anyone's money. I've got my own money.
Credit by a bunch of biased people. I
don't need credit from biased people.
No, I don't get credit from a bunch of
biased people. And I don't want anyone's
money either. So, I don't even know
where I was going with that. But maybe
if LT sends me £500, I'll go and do it.
If if he if LT right sends me £500, I
will go and do it.
Talking about yourself again, you're not
on my channel. You won't. You know what?
You give me £500 transfer and I'll do it
100 million% on my on my on my [ __ ]
on my [ __ ] dead ad. I think that's
fair, you know. I think I think that is fair.
I never I never lost to Slug and this is
exactly why I don't waste my time losing
to Slug and this is exactly why I don't
waste my time.
So if somebody wants to if if L not
somebody LT if LT wants to give me £500
I'll go and do it
100%. So then at least I know that if
these people want to be biased and I've
got £500 simple
and it can't be anyone. It has to be LT
cuz I don't want these, you know, for I
want LT to do it for a reason.
I'm not going.
No, he lives nowhere near me. And he's
So yeah, and the and the thing is he's
nowhere near me either. If he was near
me, like say he was up the road from me,
then I would do it. Yeah, because I mean
it's up the road, but he's literally
nowhere near me going on three different trains.
No, thank you, bro. I'm good.
No, I'm good, bro. going on three
different trains to fight someone on
YouTube for a biased audience.
Sounds silly to me.
Um, I can I can do what I want. I can do
what I want. You people seem to do what
you want. You people seem to do what you
want, so why can't I?
You people seem to do what you want, so
why can't I?
Can't you afford uh Are you
self-reflecting money again? Talking
about money again. Self-reflecting. Yeah. Nah.
Yeah. Yeah. I've got no money, bro. Self-reflecting again.
self reflecting again.
Yeah, I'm all mouth, no bite. Yeah, you
keep telling yourself that.
I don't care what any of these people on
here think of me, bro. I don't give a
[ __ ] They're all biased. You're all
biased anyways. I gain nothing. I
literally gain nothing.
Like, bro, it's [ __ ] free trains
away. I can't be asked. It's over an
hour away. I can't be bothered, bro.
I can't be bothered. That's nowhere near
It's not even anywhere near Stratford to
entertain a bunch of biased audience.
Anyways, you keep talking about skin,
I'm just going to keep ignoring it. The
more you keep talking about skin, the
more it shows you are skin. So, I'm
going to let you keep self-reflecting
your skintess onto me because every
single time you bring it up, it shows
you got no money. So, I'm going to let
you keep bringing money up because you
ain't got none and I'm not even going to
reply to it anymore. So,
if he comes to my area, then obviously
I'll smash his face in. That's
different. But I'm not I'm not taking
free trains. I can't be asked.
I don't need to do that for a biased audience.
audience. But yeah, if he's in my area,
then obviously, yeah, of course. What
the [ __ ] I have to, you know. So
there that's a different that's a different story, you know.
So obviously that's a different story.
That's only a walk. But I'm not going to
waste my time and waste my money and
doing all that traveling when we know
what you people are like.
So I'm not doing that, bro. For a biased audience.
You don't need to know where I am.
You don't need to know where I am. Don't
worry about where I am.
You don't need to know that.
He should know where I am.
Okay, then I'm boiling it. Okay, then simple in it.
Yeah, these people think a lot of things.
These people think a lot of things. So yeah,
anyways, I'm not entertaining this anymore. So yeah,
think about this. A man in his 40s
trying to meet somebody on YouTube.
Yeah, he claims that he's got a family
and claims that he's got kids. What a loser, mate.
What a [ __ ] loser. Trying to meet
people on YouTube that you don't know.
What a sad sad bastard.
I think my meeting people days are done
on here, matey. Matey Joe.
Done all of this [ __ ] before with like
the [ __ ] bomb and that. It's
embarrassing, man. It's embarrassing.
Trying to meet people on YouTube that
you don't even know. You claim you got
family and kids.
Get a grip, son. Yeah.
There we go.
I hate this thing on the roof, bro. And
it keeps bugging the [ __ ] out. Loyal as [ __ ]
No, I'm not under the bed. I'm on top of
the bed. On top of your mom. I just
banged her and came inside of her. Oh, [ __ ]
Nope. Not even having a takeaway.
I'm on top of your mama's bed, bro. Just
finished shagging a [Laughter]
Yeah, I'm scared, bro. Very scared.
Why is it so slow, man?
Yeah, I'm very scared, man. Can you Can
you send me some money?
Can you send me some money?
Yeah. Can you send me some money, bro?
I'm really really skinn.
Yeah. Yeah. Can you send me some money?
Yeah. Can you send me some money,
please? Bro, do you know what? Yeah, let
me be real. Yeah.
I will never ever accept money off of
anyone. You know why? I'll never accept
money off of anyone cuz I'm not freaking
like LJ. I don't need anyone's money.
I've got my own money.
I don't beg I don't beg for money. I
don't I would never accept money from no
one except LT. That's a different
reason. But I don't need anyone's money
because I've got my own money. I'm not
skint like LJ.
I don't [ __ ] need any of your monies.
I've got my own money.
Yeah, I'm skin.
I'm skin. Oh, is this thing going to
send or what, man? What the [ __ ] is
going on with this [ __ ]
Yeah, I never accept money off no one,
bro. Got my own money.
That's how you know that LJ skin cuz he
accepts money off of London people. That
means you skint.
These people call people skint cuz they're skin.
That's why they talk about skin every
day cuz they're skin. Cuz I've got a
reason why I don't go out and I don't do
things because of my bad experiences.
And what are these people's excuses?
Why are they sat on YouTube every day?
What's their excuse? I I've had too many
bad experiences. I've gave up with life.
Nothing to do with money. What's these people's excuses?
Obviously cuz they're skinn.
They're sat on YouTube all day cuz
they're the skinn ones. Obviously, bro.
Otherwise, they wouldn't be on here all
day every day. Unless they're depressed
or they're saving up for something. So,
which one is it? Are you depressed or
you saving up for something? Are you skinn
there's got to be a reason, you know? So mama
I might have a shower, you know. I might
just have a shower. Maybe.
Doubt it though. Doubt it. Doubt it.
feel all smelly, you know. Yeah.
Kind of need a shower, bro. Nope.
Nope. Not at all.
I need to have a shout though. Yeah,
I could go today and smash that prime up
if I wanted to, but bro, there's no
point. There's literally no point.
There's literally no point in it, bro.
I'm going to cook up some bacon, I think, later.
Some nice bacon and some nice coke.
Could I get a takeaway? >> Yeah. Yeah, it's pointless.
I'm going to have a shower. Yeah.
Bye. Be back later.