Game one on off.
Anyways, last live. Anyways,
this is it
for like at least a couple of weeks. So,
I'd come back, so [ __ ] it.
Why the [ __ ] not? Yeah.
[ __ ] it up.
Yeah, I'm gone, bro. After I'm gone for
a couple of weeks.
Yeah, I said I was going to come back
before uh Yeah, I'm done. Yeah, well,
I won't be live tomorrow.
I've been thinking about this community
a lot, bro. You know, over the past
couple of days and stuff and just how
it's just full of just low life people
that ain't got no life, calling other
people what they are every day. It's
icky. It gives me the It gives me the
[ __ ] EB jebies. It's a proper freaky creepy community.
Nope. The butchers was closed,
so I'm going to go get it tomorrow.
Yeah, it's just a place for the weirdos, little self-reflectors.
I mean, I don't even go on certain
people. I don't even go on anyone's
channel anymore cuz every time I go on
LJ's channel, it just gives me brain damage.
Yeah, it just gives me brain damage.
[ __ ] Legit, bro. It gives me brain
damage. I'm not even joking. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. So, that's where we're at in
it. So, I won't be um
back for like [ __ ] ages, bro.
That all. It's a weird community, bro.
Nah, I didn't bother
cuz there's no point entertaining a bias community.
Try one more approach tomorrow. No, I'm
good. Thanks. You can if you like, but I
won't be doing it.
Nah, no point entertaining a biased um community. Yeah.
I got to get state tomorrow.
Going to get a nice steak tomorrow, matey.
A nice steak tomorrow.
And that's that.
Yeah. I'm not about that life, bro. Yep.
Whatever you say.
Uh-huh. Nah, I just don't want to
entertain a bunch of um biased people.
N waste of time entertaining a bias pe
bunch of biased people.
Pointless. Waste of time. You get
nothing out of it.
Yeah. I bowled it from Prime. Yeah.
Funny how you people never call Terry a
bottle job or Mark Samson a bottle job
or Virgin boy by a bottle job. Huh? What
do you know? Eh,
buyers to the max. buyers to the max.
But I called him out. Uh actually no, he
come on my live stream uh starting
actually. Um so no.
Yep. I sh again. You keep telling
yourself that. Uh actually no. He
started it by coming on my live stream.
So um no. And even if I did call him
out, bro, how many of you people have
called me out and I've turned up and
you've not shown up?
Stop being biased.
Stop being biased. Yeah, I called him
out in Birmingham and he didn't come out.
Yeah, I called him out in Birmingham cuz
he kept joining my live streams and I
was in Birmingham and I called him out
and he didn't come out cuz he's not about it.
Bro, you people are Bro, you people are
keyboard warriors. Do you do you want me
to explain to you how you people are
keyboard warriors? You want me I'll
explain how you're keyboard warriors.
Okay, I'll explain how your keyboard
warrior is because a you know where
people live yet you'd rather stalk them
and harass them every single day, right?
But you'll never go in anyone's door.
I've traveled all over the country. No
one's meet me. I've gone to specific
people that's called me out and they've
not shown up. Yeah, you people are
literally keyboard warriors.
You are literally keyboard warriors.
Yes, you are. Generally are. And you
[ __ ] knew where I lived as well. So
yeah. No, you people generally are
keyboard warriors. All you do is sit
behind the keyboard, self-p projecting
every single day of your lives.
Yeah, that's that's what you people are.
You keep So, well, you did know where I
lived. You knew I was in Stratford. You
did know where I lived. You knew I was in Stratford. So
yeah, it's a madness. Yeah, it's a
madness, bro. I could not that come out
silly, bro. But there's no point because
all of these people in here are biased.
All of these people in here are biased.
There's no point. They're all biased, lad. There's literally
the You know what I'm saying? They
literally they are biased on here.
There's literally no point
with these people.
There's no point with them. None at all. At all. Yeah. Some madness.
And Yeah. He had a chance to meet me
when I was in Birmingham. Funny. You
don't bring that one up. You only
remember what you want to remember.
You only remember what you want to remember.
Yep. You only remember what you want to
remember. Typical YouTube, isn't it?
Typical YouTube community. Yep.
Yeah, typical YouTube community.
Yep. You Yeah, that's excuse you use.
Yep. Yep. Just like when Timmy and Tiger
come. That wasn't arranged. But if I
never showed up, I wouldn't have heard
the last of it. This is why I never
went. Like me, two years ago, I would have went.
Two years ago, I would have went.
Yeah. Two two and a half years ago, I
would have went. Definitely would have
went. But then I realize how people move
on here. Like, you know what I'm saying?
Now we we know how these people move on
here. I just had some egg and bacon.
No, you're not banned.
We know how people move on it, so it's a
waste of our time. I mean, obviously,
unless they're very close to you, then
obviously then you got no excuse. But
taking free trains to entertain a biased
audience? Nah, I'm all right. Thanks.
A biased audience.
Imagine that. A biased audience. Yeah.
Went to Nons three times, no one ever
mentioned it. Went to Mark Samson two
times, no one ever mentioned it. went to
Trevor Dawson. No one ever mentioned it.
What do you know? Eh, what a biased audience.
Biased audience. Biased audience. Biased
They remember what they want to remember.
Yeah, sounds about right.
Yeah. I just had some eggs and bacon.
Yeah. He was in London, but he was
nowhere near me. Yeah, but he was
nowhere near me. Do you know how big
London is? Yeah. Nowhere near me. I was
in Birmingham. He didn't come out. I was
in Birmingham, funny enough, last month
and he didn't come out. And don't give
me all it wasn't a Reigns [ __ ]
because, okay, let Timmy was on my live
stream. Timmy was on my live stream last
month and he didn't come out and he was
actually there. But yet, no one brings
that up. So, if you want to make it, if
you want to use excuses for Prime, if right?
You know, if you want to use excuses for
Prime, okay, well, you can't use you
can't use excuses for Timmy and no one
ever mentions it to Timmy.
I can do what I want. It's only what you
people do. Why can't I do what you
people do, Joe? Why not? Why not? Why
can't I do what you people do? Why? Why?
Why can't I do what you people do? Timmy
seems to do it. Mark Samson seems to do
it. Why can't I do what you people do?
That's not fair.
Bit rude, isn't it? We got Mark Samson
that calls people out and doesn't show up anywhere.
That's okay. We got Timmy that calls
people out and don't show everywhere.
Don't show anywhere. Well, why not?
Biased, isn't it? Bit biased.
Bit rude, isn't it? Uh yeah,
yeah. These people are these people are
biased on it proper. And the guy weren't
anywhere near me either. That's the
thing. He wasn't even anywhere near me.
You're going on like he was near me. He
wasn't anywhere [ __ ] near me. Uh
Mark Samson got away got away with it
for years. Timmy's got away from it for
years. So why can't I get away with it?
You know, it's only weird when it's
somebody that you don't like doing it.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah. So simple.
I was just watching some porn Jo. I was
watching this pilot get a [ __ ]
That really [ __ ] with someone's head. Don't it?
Does anybody else like this weather?
This cool, cold weather? I love it,
mate. I love I love September. I love October.
It's the best time to have a drink, I
think. Not too hot, not too cold, just
perfect. Nice and windy and dull outside.
I don't know. There's just something
about this weather.
Why did this [ __ ] come up?
Yep. But I can't believe Ant-Man
earlier. Like there's there's no trying
now. There's nothing. There's literally
nothing. There's no keep trying. There's no nothing.
But I can't believe we're already what?
We're already October next month. So two
years ago that would have already been a
year. What the [ __ ] That's madness.
That is crazy, bro. But yeah, October is
the best month in September
along with November. They're the best.
That's the best season.
That's the best season, man.
I put my hair in a top knot earlier,
you know. Yeah, kind of. But I've
already been there before.
Yep. Story of your lives.
I can't wait to get out of here.
Yeah. Like now, Greg, it's getting a bit
cold and it's getting a bit windy. It's nice
and it and it and you want to go to the
gym in this weather cuz it warms you up.
He was in London, but he was nowhere near me.
Yep. Same. That's what I said. March and October. Yeah.
But you can wear a coat, but it's not
too cold, but you can dress up cuz the
thing is with summer, you can't really
dress up nice. I don't like summer, bro.
I like it just like this.
Cold mornings, going to the gym. I don't
know. I like it like this. I don't like the heat.
I don't like the heat, bro.
>> Yeah, there you go. You already know.
But yeah, I don't I don't agree with
Ant-Man as like trying is the only thing
you can do. I don't I don't agree with
that. I don't agree with that.
>> Nah, I don't agree with that, bro. You
don't wake up one day and think, "Oh
yeah, the next time you go out, it's
going to change." Like, nah.
Honest to God, nah.
I don't agree with that. I don't agree with him.
Well, what what do you mean by nothing changes?
Yeah, I had some bacon. I had some egg.
Um, I mean, well, nothing's going to
change because it would have changed by
now. Nothing's going to change. So, best
get used to it.
It's never going to change. So, best get
used to it.
Best get used to this life. It's never
going to change. What What What is there
to say anymore?
Cuz you're not going to convince me that.
You're not going to convince me that
that the next time I go out, it's going
to be different. Joe, you're not going
to convince me that. And Antman's not
going to convince me that. There's no
way you're going to convince me
that it's going to be different the next
time I go out.
Sorry, bro, but you're not going to convince me.
So, I don't think you can. So, yeah. Yeah.
So yeah, that's where we're at basically.
Trying is not an option in this country,
bro. It ain't an option. So yeah. Yeah, exactly.
I've tried an unhealthy amount. So
yeah, it's not going to be different the
next time you just go out.
I have smashed her face in.
If I saw that USA, I would have smashed
her face in and she didn't even [ __ ]
hit me. She didn't even put her hand on
me. I would have smashed her face in as
well. So you would you would have seen
what I would have done to her.
So yeah, it's never going to change. Never sadly. So um
some people are just not made some
people are just not made for anyone.
Some people are just not made for anyone.
Yeah, I would have smashed her face if
she done that to me. It's like if I saw USA now,
I probably would just give her one bang
in her mouth to be honest with you and
that'll be the end of that.
But yeah, they're liars, bro. You're not
going to meet anyone. No way.
You might as well take the L.
Take the L. You tried your best. You
failed. Now we're leaving. So, hello.
Just take the L. Yeah.
And Ronty says that I can't get laid yet
I've had more sexual partners than him.
That's what I don't understand. I've had
more sexual partners than him.
So yeah, just take the L
and move on from it. Simple. That's it.
You're not going to meet anyone clearly.
randomly like Yeah. So just go out. I
don't even tempt I'm not even tempted to
go out and drink anymore, bro. And like
I said, it ain't about money. It really isn't.
I've got more than enough disposable money.
>> It's not about that, bro. It generally isn't. You've
Well, the main difference is you've laid
for 75% of them. He hasn't.
I don't get what you mean.
So yeah, you're not going to meet anyone.
Well, it will be different in Asia. It's Yeah.
When women in different countries start
being [ __ ] to me, I just send them
my dick cuz I know they can't do
anything. They can't call the police.
They can't do anything,
you know, cuz
obviously they're in different
countries. So they can't do anything.
Yeah. I feel like after them many
experiences, you should just give up, do
something else now. Yeah. Germany.
Yeah, it's not going to be different
this time. You know, I'll go out for my
birthday cuz it's my birthday and I get
birthday money, but um that's that'll be
it, I think.
Good old October. Yeah.
Another year older. Yeah.
I know man's life could be around. It
could be this. It could be that.
But it's not going to change.
No, I'm just going to go out with my sister.
Yeah, I'm just going to go out with my
sister, I think,
and get wrecked. But yeah, I probably
won't go out until my birthday to be
honest. And that's like a [ __ ] month away. So,
it ain't even It's not even about money.
It's about I need to think about what
I'm actually doing. You know what I'm
saying? I need to think about what I'm
really doing now.
We've been there. We've done it. We've
tried. We never got anywhere. We failed.
God knows what reason we failed for, but
we failed. So, yeah, that's it.
That is it. Yeah. See,
I just my sister cuz we we saying we're
going to go out, but we never end up
doing it. So, I just said on my
birthday, yeah, we'll just get [ __ ] So,
I just don't see it worth it anymore.
Yeah, he can do what he wants.
He'll be wasting his time because the
neighbors are not going to do his dirty work.
I mean, he can do it, but it'd be pointless.
So, no, you can [ __ ] off.
You can [ __ ] off, Prime. I'm not interested. Bye-bye. So, yeah,
it's so weird how I feel so much older
in like just space of a few years.
So, yeah. All right. Oh,
porn is addicting, bro.
You know, I'm not aged at all. I look completely fine. [ __ ]
Uh, I look completely fine, matey.
Thank you very much, matey.
No, I haven't aged.
I haven't aged at all, mate.
I had a shower earlier with my [ __ ]
B in my top knot.
Is that all? [Music]
No, I haven't. It's just cuz I'm depressed. Yeah.
Yeah. Oh, [ __ ] I've been dead now.
[ __ ] Oh, [ __ ]
It will never change.
These women make people age.
They're depressing, aren't they? Yeah,
but you'll find someone.
I do feel like getting drunk, though.
I'm not going to lie, bro. I feel like
hammering the Guinnesses
cuz of um
cuz of it being uh
[ __ ] um yeah the weather it is no
Yeah, it's not going to magically
change. And it's gotten worse as well.
It's gotten worse, too.
It's also gotten worse.
I mean, when I go out drinking again,
whatever, it's just going to be cuz I
really want to get [ __ ]
There is no hope. There generally is no
Cuz if there was hope, you would do it
sober. Yeah. Okay, you might get drunk
and do it drunk cuz you're drunk, but I
mean, it's there anyways, but at the end
of the day, like, if there was hope,
then you would actually do them sober.
Yeah, I see people sober all the time. I
don't do it because there's no hope.
Uh just because I would just I'd rather
just save the money. I'd rather just
save the money that I've got and put it
towards other [ __ ] That's why.
And the more the longer you go about
drinking, the more you enjoy it when you
do eventually drink.
So that's the goal. Yeah.
Yeah. But I'd rather save myself. I'd
rather save myself for my birthday.
I don't need money. I've got my own
money. I don't know how many times I
have to tell you this.
What age did you stop going out drinking?
I was like, "Yeah, I think it's been the
past eight months I've stopped." I
stopped going out regularly about 8 months ago.
Yeah. About 8 months ago.
Yeah. So now I can go out less and save money. Win-win.
I do like [ __ ] October though, man.
I had two one night stands in October.
Not last year. The year before. Was it
last year? No, it couldn't have been
last year cuz
No, it was the year before that.
So, I tried and I failed. So,
Yeah, it's about it's about £8 a pint.
Yeah, it's about £8 a pint. Yeah,
but it's not even that, bro.
5 club entries,
bro. The club entries here are like
[ __ ] 20 quid. 20 to30. You mad.
You mad, bro. [Laughter] Yeah.
Yeah, it's true.
I have so many good memories in the
past. That's why, you know,
One sec, bro. What's up?
He don't want to know. She don't want to
know. She don't want to know you. Yeah.
But yeah, that's where where we're at, bro.
Very hard to get a woman in this country.
You know what makes me laugh, Timothy
John El? Is that you go on Reddit,
right, and people make it seem so easy.
Oh yeah, just go on Tinder. You'll get
laid on Tinder. How's Tinder?
It's like they they they they sell you a
lie. They lie to you, isn't it? Madness.
Go on, Tinder. Yeah, true. Yep.
It's the truth in it. Yeah.
So, how do you get laid in this country?
You don't, do you?
You don't, matey.
Oh, I heard about L. I'm losing £450.
That is lovely. Lovely stuff.
You lost 450. Oh, lost those.
Yeah, my my mom actually told me. I
didn't even know. Yeah, that's lovely,
mate. That's why these people call other
people's skin. Cuz their skin
tim That's why they call people skint
cuz their skin It's obvious, isn't it,
bro? It's so obvious.
They call people skin cuz they're skin.
No, I think it just popped up or something.
That's why they call people skint cuz
they're skint. Do you not understand
Timothy John Eldridge? They call people
skint cuz they're skin.
Do you know that? [ __ ] hell, bro.
Get with the times, lad.
You need to get the [ __ ] times, man. No,
he just watches him sometimes. See, I
can't watch them because every time I go
on that channel, right, I get brain
damage cuz they're all retards. They're
just [ __ ] mongos. That's why I can't
go on that channel, bro.
Cuz think about it, Timothy. Yeah.
Why are these people on it all day,
every day? Me, I'm saving money. I can't
be bothered drinking, you know? I'm I'm
saving up to do [ __ ] So, I mean, I'm
taking a break from things.
They're on YouTube all day, every day,
and they've done nothing in years.
They're online all day, every day cuz
their skin. It's obvious.
It is [ __ ] obvious.
Don't call me for skin cuz they're skin. Hello. Yeah. Yeah, true.
You stop going out drinking around 25.
Yeah, it's lovely, bro. It's lovely.
Yeah, I know.
I know. That's why I don't go on it
anymore cuz they're just self projectors.
They're all They're all ugly fat people
that ain't got a life, ain't got no money.
You stopped at 25. I stopped that well 7 months ago. So yeah,
I used to be out like
two times a week, three times a week.
Yeah, I used to uh
Oh, you a lot, Dad.
Yeah, you a lot.
How many times did you used to go out a week?
I don't think he went out as much as me.
I used to go casinos Thursday, win money, then
[ __ ] Well, no, I never used to do two
days a week cuz I couldn't do it cuz of
the [ __ ] that the hangovers.
I couldn't do it cuz the hangovers.
No, I don't think I did used to do two
cuz of I used to do Thursdays and Saturdays. Sorry.
Yeah, I used to do Thursdays and Saturdays
cuz I had to take a day off cuz I used
to cuz I used to drink just I used to go
straight on the rum. So obviously when I
drink rum I'm [ __ ] for like two three
days. When I go on the rum I'm [ __ ]
for like two three days.
So yeah, I was [ __ ]
Uh but I never used to drink beer and I
used to just drink rum.
I used to go out every week, bro.
I think it was sometimes two two days a week.
Yeah, it was fun, bro. Lush.
I used to go to different cities every week.
No, I used to go to different cities
every week, lad. Yeah.
Never had to work. Never had to do
anything, bro. No work, no nothing.
Never had to work or do [ __ ] all.
It was lush. Yeah.
These people don't hate me. These people
are jealous of me.
That's what they are. They're jealous of
me, bro. Think about it. I'm young. I'm
better looking than them. I've got more
freedom than them. I can do what I want to do.
Do you understand, bro?
Nope. Never had to work in all of them
years. Am I me [ __ ]
Who's that voice? some [ __ ] bro.
Nah, it's cuz I got a brain
unlike you and I've never had to be
someone's [ __ ] like you.
So, yeah. And bye-bye now. Do think
about it, Timothy Eldridge. Yeah. Do you
not find it very mad how all of these
middle-aged people cling on to me? They
gravitate towards me and no one else. Do
you not think that's very strange?
Because what it is with these people is
they wish they were young like me. They
they wish they weren't ugly and they
wish they weren't skin. Is that a better
way to like
say instead of blowing smoke up my ass?
Um and because they're old, they're ugly
in the skin, they see somebody younger
that's got hope and then they go mad.
That's what happens.
Why do you think this Jamie Thompson
stalks me? Why do you think all of these other people
gravitate towards me and no one else?
Have a think.
Have a think. Have a think, bro.
You know what I mean? Oh yeah.
So I used to go Yeah.
I used to go to casinos every week as well.
I used to go casino every week.