out.
Had to get my chimney t-bone steak.
[ __ ] out. Going out is so depressing,
bro. Oh my god. I said I work on a [ __ ]
I'm on YouTube. I swear it's like
therapy sessions, bro.
Yeah, man. I [ __ ] said I won't
[ __ ] go on. I swear it's like therapy
session and [ __ ] every single time you
go out. It's so depressing.
Like I had to go far out today as well.
My old area.
Yeah. Sure is a depressing life here in
England. That's for danger.
That's for danger. It's a [ __ ]
depressing life here.
The same people, the same westernized
people, the same [ __ ] Oh my god,
bro. Same delay, same waiting around for things.
So bad, is it?
Have to do some dry cleaning, get some sting,
but now anyways.
They went to the old house.
See what it look like. [Music] Yeah.
Yeah, I get you, bro. I get you.
don't just listen to something.
Yeah, this is a depressing country, bro.
The more you go out in this country, the
more you come back depressed. I swear to
God, bro. I swear to God, you come back
depressed. It's so depressing.
It's so depressing being in this
country, bro. I swear to God.
Country designed to annoy you and get
under your skin. There was some delays
as well today. The trains and they
didn't stop the right places and [ __ ] Yeah.
It is a depressing country. Therefore,
woman who's never had to try anything
trying to give you advice.
Oh man, that is that is that is very
comical. A woman that's never had to try
anything in her life trying to give you advice. Insane.
Insane. You see, the thing is, right, if
these people went through these
struggles yet, they'll be like, "Okay,
fair enough. Fair enough." But they've
never had to try anything. Like, I
understand, you know, you're 28 and you
know, you've never been in a
relationship. You've never been with a
um you've never been with a guy and
stuff. I get that. But the thing is the
difference is and what will always be
the difference is you've never tried anything.
Cuz if you tried, you would feel exactly
the same way as I do.
Anybody would feel that way because
that's the right way to think. Don't be
negative. It's the right way to think.
It's not being delusional.
That's what it is. You know, there is no
hope for you here. You will It's
supposed to have got easier as you got
older. A lot of people complaining that
you know as when you you know sort of as
you get older it's hard but it should
have got easier as you got older because
you know people you would have thought
people's standards would I don't know
people would just look more to settle
down well but
um no it's even harder as you get older
which is insane.
So, when does it have a sort of um when
does it have a cut off point,
if you will? When when did when does it
have a cut off point where the [ __ ]
where the [ __ ] stops? When does the
[ __ ] ever stop? You know what I'm saying?
You know, when does the [ __ ] ever stop?
And I was going to say every year is the
same, but every year is not the same
because every year gets worse. Well,
actually, every year is not the same.
Every year gets worse. Um, so
just went to the butchers, got a t-bone
steak, had to do some dry cleaning,
come back [ __ ] depressed as [ __ ]
Wish I never went out. Same old England.
Roll on November, eh?
Roll on November.
Roll on. I can't wait.
It's a Scorpio day like me, bro. I can't
wait to get the [ __ ] out of here. You
really don't know, bro, how how much I
really want to get out of here. This
country, this depressing country.
Feel like you're being mocked, took the
piss out of every day. [ __ ] that, bro. I
want out of it.
And then when I come back, I'm going to
speak to this person from Finland and
basically like need to understand what
they actually really want before I start
wasting money and wasting time going
over there. Cuz this is no life for anyone, bro.
This is really no life for anyone in this country. But yeah,
no life here, bro. Slow life here.
It's no life here, bro.
Um, yeah. We went butchers, went dry
cleaning, went to see my old neighbor.
Had some stuff to do, bro.
Yeah, I just used this for like I just
used this for um therapy. I used this
community for therapy.
I was actually all right today until I went out. So, yeah.
Yeah, bro. It's depressing as [ __ ] And
that's with my Sony's and the dry
cleaners as well. It sure is a
depressing life here in England.
Sure is depressing.
You notice that every single time you go
out as well, there was delays.
Things didn't stop properly.
It's so depressing. The further you go
out, the more depressing it is.
At least I've done some exercise. At
least I went out. So,
roll on [ __ ] November.
Roll on November.
It's never going to change, bro. This
country ain't never going to change.
I got some homemade burgers. I got some steak.
Uh, we're ignoring self-reflecting comments.
Yeah, self-reflecting comments we're ignoring.
Speaking of skin, I'm having a 20 pound
T-bone steak today. What are you having?
Speaking of skin, I'm having a juicy fat
20 worth of T-bone steak today. What are
you having? I mean, that's the best
reaction you're going to get. But yeah,
you keep self-reflecting. I'm I'm not
reacting to self-reflecting comments
about money. We don't do that on our channel.
You can go back to LJ's.
Yeah, you can go back to LJ's. We don't
have self-reflecting on my channel. So, yeah.
Oh, really? Anyways, I'm going to ban this account.
I got a nice t-bone steak to eat today,
Grezy. Nice t-bone steak. Yeah.
Yeah. People on Reddit keep saying that
my person's out there, Grezy.
That's all they keep saying on Reddit.
But my question is, where were they four
years ago? If they're really there,
where are they? Where is this person, Grezy?
Let me ask Grievy cuz Grievy talks a lot
of sense. So, let me ask Grievy. They're
not on dating apps. They're not in bars.
They're not in clubs. They're not in the
street. They're not in libraries.
They're not in shopping malls. Where is
this mysterious person?
Where is this mysterious person, lad?
Where was this person, Grezy? I haven't
found them in 4 years. Where could they possibly be? Uh,
can't be in this country. It can't be here.
It certainly can't be in England.
Can't be in England. Surely to God, they
can't be in England. Everyone in
England's got boyfriends. That's
ridiculous. They're not in England.
Everyone in England's in a relationship.
So they say, but you know, so they say.
Yeah. Mrs. Wright is nowhere to be seen.
See, I wonder what these women would
think if they tried for years and they
got nowhere. Greavvesy, I wonder what
they would think. I wonder how they would feel.
I wonder how they would feel. What do
you think they would do if they had to
try for years and got nowhere? Do you
think they would still have hope for themselves?
Nah. No way.
I think if they were still alive, they
probably would have just gave up.
Cuz at this point, it's delusional. It's
not even positivity. It's it's delusional.
I mean, look, Grezy. Yeah.
You can say to yourself, "Oh, yeah. I'm
going to go out on Saturday and I'm
going to go out and I'm going to meet
somebody that's not been doing all of
these things that they've been doing for years.
What's the chances of that? Just just
think about it logically. Let's just say
that we wanted to be positive and forget the past
and say, you know, we're going to go get
a haircut. We're going to put some nice
clothes on and we're going to go out and
try and find someone that's not been
doing all this [ __ ] for years. You think
it's logical, bro?
I don't think it's logical, bro. You know,
I don't think it's logical. I think
that's delusional, bro.
And I said to Antman, "Yeah, I get what
you're saying. Like, the only thing you
can do is try, but the the problem with
it is is trying doesn't work.
And we're going to be [ __ ] 40 before
we know it. And we're still going to be
in the same rut until you leave. This
ain't going to this ain't going to stop.
in this country. You know, I just went
to the butchers today and it was
depressing enough just going to the
butchers. Just going to the butchers and
it was depressing enough, bro.
I had to go butchers and do some dry
cleaning and see my neighbor and [ __ ]
So, yeah. Like, so
that was depressing enough as it is.
It's a country designed to annoy you and
get under your skin. That's what it is.
It generally is that.
So, I'm going to have to see this what
this person Finland's intentions is
before I waste my [ __ ] time, bro.
Before I waste my time.
Cuz this ain't going to stop here, bro.
It ain't. It ain't. It ain't. It ain't.
And it should have got easier as you got
older, Jay Willow. It should have
actually got easier, but it's actually got harder.
And I don't have the energy for it anymore.
You know what I'm saying, bro? It's just
I don't have the energy for it anymore.
You know, everyone just looks [ __ ]
stuck up. Everyone just looks stuck up
outside. They're all [ __ ]
Yeah. I went back to my old area where I
used to live. Oh, I miss it so much,
man. Like the pubs and [ __ ]
I said to the neighbor, "Oh, yeah. You
can come to this house." I gave him the
address. I said, "You come to this house
next week. You can come over for a
cuppper if you want."
But yeah, and the problem is Jay Willow
is when you go out and you see these
women, you're going to end up
approaching and then you're back in the same cycle.
So that's what I'm trying to say. It's a
country designed to annoy you and [ __ ]
with you. That's what I mean.
Cuz there was one on the bus I could
have approached, but I was like, "Nah,
can't be bothered." And then if I had
done it, then it would have made my
situation worse. and then the same
problems. I think it's worth not knowing
in my case it's worth it's not knowing
is a better thing than getting the same old boring
because you know how you become
self-conscious because of these women.
These are the ones that make you feel
the way you do. It's no one on YouTube.
People on YouTube can write anything.
People can say stuff. It's them. They're
the ones that make you feel that way. No
one else. No bomb. No [ __ ] red star.
know no one.
It's your experiences with women. You know,
you don't have the energy for it
anymore. You know what I'm saying? But I
don't have the energy for the [ __ ] anymore
and they sort of dismiss my struggles as well. So
they sort of dismissed my struggles.
So don't see the point in wasting money
going out anymore. You know,
money that could go towards something else, you know.
Think about it, right? Say you go out
and you get pissed with that money you
you you you know you you're going to
spend going out and getting drunk. You
could have went to a steakhouse.
You could have bought a you know pair of
trainers or you know you could have put
it towards something. Do you understand
what I'm saying? You could have put on a
on a bet that gives you a buzz. Just
depends how you look at it. So yeah,
but I done the right thing today. I got
a nice T-bone steak, got some mushrooms,
got some homemade burgers.
[ __ ] expensive. It was [ __ ] expensive, bro.
Like I just got the Xbox and Franklin to
be fair, bro. Good investment. Good [ __ ] investment.
Good investment, lad.
You know, it gets it gets to a stage
where you need to grow up.
Whether you just learn it or you learn
it the hard way.
You understand? Like I feel like some
people like me need to learn it the hard way.
It's never going to change in this
country. It will never ever change in
this country. Think about it. Jay Widow,
say you done football bets. Yeah.
If you kept losing football bets for
years, would you carry on doing a
football bet? No, you wouldn't. It's the
same thing with this. Um,
if I had to pick two, don't know.
probably body and loving to be honest
if I was to say uh yeah
but this Xbox has helped this Franklin
has helped it was a good investment this little setup
but they're just not interested in this country
so I'll just go to Finland if this
person is being serious then I'll just
go to Finland. [ __ ] it. I don't care. Go
there, you know, a couple of times a year.
If it means this [ __ ] ending, then it
will end in it. Simple.
But I need to know that they're not
wasting time. But I mean, I could just
go and approach there anyways. But don't
get it twisted. If I was in another
country, I probably would approach. I
probably would, you know, doesn't matter
what other country I'm in. Of course, I
would approach in another country, bro.
Even if it is a westernized country, but
I ain't westernized. I'm not I'm not
wasting my time here, bro. I'm not
wasting my money here,
you know? I'd rather build my [ __ ]
money up than [ __ ] waste it.
And it's not because I have the money. I
don't have the money. I do have the
money. I do have the money, but I'd
rather do other things now. I know what
it's like. I know what happens.
Do you know what I mean, bro?
[ __ ] 28 next month, bro. [ __ ]
getting old. What the [ __ ] Going to
keep doing this [ __ ] forever.
Wow. They literally just miss
everything. I don't understand this
thing with Reddit, bro. You show them
like women taking a piss, women being
stuck up, and they just they just miss
it. They literally just miss everything
you show them. It's madness. I mean, if
if if being shown something can't change
someone's mind, then they I don't think
anything else ever will.
They literally just ignore everything
that they're shown. The madness,
it's crazy. They got like no bad words
to say about women. Um, you know, I'm
speaking to this woman on Reddit and I'm
literally showing her my experiences.
Like I understand that you're 28 and I'm
28 as well, but I've tried more than you
would ever try. So I mean at the end of
the day, why are you making excuses for
them when I'm literally showing you what
they're doing over text, flaking, piss
taking, they're literally taking the
piss. I'm literally showing you what
they're doing and then they just miss
everything you show them anyways.
Whether they're a s, whether they're a
[ __ ] woman, it's a madness, bro.
And I don't know why they keep telling
me that there's hope.
I don't know why people are still
telling me that there's hope when there is none.
Cuz four years try and prove it. Four
years try and prove that there is
absolutely no hope. But they still tell
you you got hope. So madness
Yeah, it's a madness.
I'm so glad I gave up.
I want to cook this t-bone shortly.
Oh, [ __ ] I forgot the lemons. Oh. Oh,
do I need lemon?
Kind of. Got salt, black pepper. Um,
yeah, I do. I need everything with it.
I've not paid that much for a steak and
not have [ __ ] the lemon with it, you know?
Yeah, maybe I can't be bothered. Yeah, I
just used a salt and Yeah,
cost me [ __ ] 20. It did Yeah.
I'm going to cook on a pan. I'm going to
cook on a pan then grill it. I'm going
to pan it, then grill it
to crisp up the fat and that
my dry cleanings cost me £30.30 [ __ ] pound.
Yeah, I had to I had to take the stonies
for the dry cleaner. I said to the guy,
"Can you um get rid of the stains?" He
said he'll try his best. So that's 30.
Said, "It's £32, but can I get in cash?"
I said, "I'll give you £30 in cash." He said, "Deal?" Yeah.
I mean, I don't go out drinking anymore,
so I've saved a lot of money just
getting the steak, you know.
Know what I'm saying?
I don't know. I think it's like
toothpaste stains, but it should come
out. I said I'll come and collect it
Saturday. So, you've got Don't rush it.
take your time with it,
you know. So,
it's so funny how these women that say
they say that there's someone out there
for you, but that woman's never them, is
it? Isn't it funny that woman's never them?
Funny, Greasy. That woman's never them.
Isn't that funny, Gregy? That woman's
never them. It's some other woman. It's
never them, is it?
Yeah, about this.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] They are evil.
They are evil bastards.
They are evil bastards, bro.
I laugh at these people that try to call
me skin, but they don't know nothing, bro.
It's madness. They call you skint cuz they're skin.
They call you skint cuz they're skint.
Do you remember that, Steven Howard?
But yeah, they call you skin cuz they're skin.
Uh uh uh.
These people all skin.
That's why they try to call other people
skint cuz they're skin.
It's obvious, isn't it, bro? It's so obvious.
They call people skin cuz they're skin.
They don't know about other people's
life. They don't know what money people have.
They don't know nothing, bro.
But they seem to talk like they know
everything about you. So yeah. Yep.
She don't want to know you. She don't
want to know. She don't want to know. You
You don't want to know.
Don't want to know.
You don't want to know. You don't want
to know. You don't want to know.
You don't want to know. Yeah. >> Yep.
That's what they do.
That's their life.
Whilst I'm [ __ ] saving. I mean, yeah.
I got a t-bone steak.
I'm going to do it in a minute. I think
I'm going to prepare it in a minute.
This is a monstrous steak, mate. That's me.
Right. Let me let me see the steak.
Anyways, I'm getting a bit hungry now.
I haven't ate today. Oh, I said the McDonald's earlier. That's it.
That's our little [ __ ]
That's our little [ __ ] pet thing. You
should know right now,
boy. Get in the bed. Virgin boy.
Virgin boy. No money in the bed. Oh,
now let me let me show you what you've
been missing out on in them three years.
Virgin boy. I'll show you what you've
been missing out on.
That 13 grand, mate. Show you what
you've been missing out on. One second.
Right. You ready, Grezy? [Music] All
right. One second.
See, when I had that McDonald's last
night, I never forgot about you. Did I?
Them chickens were nice.
One second, man.
Um, let me put up on top of the pack.
No. Get in the seat. Mate,
look at that. Look at that bit of t-bone, matey.
Look at that bit of t-bone.
You're trying to [ __ ] that woman over.
It made me really fancy a t-bone. Here
it is. One second.
Look at that.
You have to bash it proper.
You have to spin it out, you know.
Oh, mate. I'm going to have some fun with that. Right.
Some I'm going to have with mushrooms.
Oh, you [ __ ] [ __ ] Who done that?
Who Who the [ __ ] Who done that with a [ __ ] salt?
You [ __ ] idiot.
The salt has just [ __ ] gone
everywhere. I had to wipe it off. Who
the [ __ ] done that with that salt? What
the [ __ ] man?
[ __ ] idiot. I didn't know that. Hold on.
Who the [ __ ] done that, bro?
That's not the same with the black
pepper and the garlic. One sec.
There we go. Lots of salt on it. Lots of
salt on the fat.
>> Stop calling me [ __ ]
Okay, I think this one's normal.
Virgin wife can't have that. He's He's
skipping the bed.
He's skipping the bed.
He's getting the bed in all. So high.
I'm just going to throw
bar is the best but you know
will do it will do its magic.
I'll take it.
One second, bro.
Then I need to grill it as well.
Just one second.
putting on the pan and then putting it
on the grill.
Something like that. These mushrooms
I've never shot my [ __ ] fingers off
doing this, you know. No, not on the barbecue.
That's another thing I miss about the
house. We have some of the last barbecues lately.
One second. Just chopping up some mushrooms.
Some mushroom meanings by trying to
mate. It's not bad [ __ ]
>> Right. What happened to put all the mushrooms on?
It's quite a big mistake.
I'm going to demolish it, man. You don't even
I'm going to demolish it.
Nice holiday burgers too. That'll be for
a later day. We'll
be for a later day. L
these are lovely mushrooms though. They
just sort of
they just sort of
they just sort of um
you know they just look so fresh. Look.
Look at that.
Love these steak mushrooms.
You like it? Yeah.
Ooh, the P.
Oh, the P. Ready.
Oh, lovely. Look at that.
That is lovely, lady.
That is absolutely
Tuesday t-bone. Hey, Grezy.
I need to poke I need to I need to poke
I need to poke the knife in the t-bone.
groups a bit like how Valentine's the
day to poke fun out ain't wanted by no one.
Isn't that right?
Tell you poke fun out of that chosen by nobody.
Why did I make you laugh? It's not
funny, bro. It's bad.
We need a lot of butter for this.
We need a lot of butter for this, mate.
For these mushrooms
or steak as well, cuz I'm going to grill it.
Cook it. good at
half of it. Yeah, that's >> Yeah, that's lovely.
T-bug is the best.
Do we do this every Tuesday? Grezy Tuesday. T-bug.
Should we do it every Tuesday? Huh?
Every Tuesday, eh? Yeah.
Yeah. Tuesday football bets and Tuesday t-bug. Imagine that
because it rhymes Tuesday t-bone.
That's lovely, bro. Yeah. Oh.
Did I win some money? Nope. I don't need
to win some money. I've got money.
Oh, we're not talking about money again,
are we? Jesus Christ.
Why don't I win some money? I don't need
to win some money. I've got my own Yep. Sure am.
So, I'm going to cook half of it and
then grill the other half of it.
up where it's so big it [ __ ] Nope.
Anyways, why are you asking me if I want
some money? I don't need to win money.
I've got my own money.
You didn't answer my question.
This is how you know with this community
a lot of a lot of projection.
A lot of projection come goes on in this community.
A lot a lot of projection. No offense.
Yeah, it's projection, bro.
No, I said we can do football bats every
We can do football bats every Tuesday.
>> Yeah, I'm paranoid. Yeah.
>> No, because I know what you're getting
at. It's just the same old [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying?
I just know what you're getting at. It's obvious.
What you'll get?
It's obvious what you're trying to get
at, what you're hitting.
But yeah, I went out today, bro. It was
depressing as [ __ ]
I saw like women and couples depressing.
Well, there you go then. Jobs are good in that.
Yeah. Anyways, it was depressing today
going at Timothy
butchers, dry cleaners.
Had to go and see an old neighbor.
Oh, look at that. Cooking up lovely.
Look at that.
That is cooking up lovely.
And then I'm going to grill it in a bit.
Oh, look at that.
Put some holes in it.
Make someone dead. Yeah.
So, I'm going to do this for about
maybe 10 15.
I'm going to finish it off good and
maybe a little bit more than that actually.
Quite a big steak, but either way, it
needs to end in the grill.
I like mine weld on medium. So,
so nice, man.
Virgin boy skin in the bed with no money.
You're not going to be [ __ ] mad. This
is what skin boy in the virgin bed suit
has been missing out on for [ __ ] years.
Yeah, I went back to that old house today.
Still [ __ ] boarded up and [ __ ] mushrooms on.
had to go to the halal butchers to get
the mints because in the the nonhal in
hal butchers the mints um it breaks right
oh [ __ ] almost went in my eye
wrong one wrong one sec
Hold it up.
Yeah. The old house.
>> No, they won't. It will be left there for years.
>> Not even. It will be left there for years.
You can't get T-Bone in the supermarkets.
This was £20 and you can't get them in the supermarkets.
You can't get them in the supermarkets.
>> No, no one's going to be in the house.
They just going to They just left it.
Open it up. Yeah. One second.
Oh my god. Virgin car.
Can you imagine a virgin boy trying to see?
I love see I saw I loved your comment
earlier bro and you was like oh yeah
it's going to change and that your
luck's changing it will never change
if anything was going to change it would
have changed in 4 years
I don't think there's anything people
can say about that I mean
it's the truth is Yep. Right,
let me put the mushrooms on.
They're consol with a spoon. Yeah. Heat.
Nah, I couldn't be bothered like
couldn't be bothered.
Couldn't be bothered.
Got nervous now. Didn't get nervous at
all, bro. Just didn't want to entertain
a biased audience.
Been there, done that, won the [ __ ] yellow t-shirt.
Nah, bro. Not even that. Been there,
done it, won the t-shirt.
water yellow t-shirt.
That's the way I see it. You live and
you learn, bro. Yeah.
A big old bastard.
This steak is a big old bastard. Greavves.
>> No, I weren't even going to get
battered. It weren't even getting
battered. It's the fact that I know
what's going to happen. I'm going to go
there. He's not going to show up or he's
going to show up and I win and then
everyone's going to pretend it never
happened. It's a waste of my time. And
it's also very embarrassing.
It's actually very very embarrassing as
well, you know, going on two trains to
fight some weirdo over YouTube,
especially when the [ __ ] audience is biased, you know.
So now it's not I just don't want to
entertain a bias audience. I mean,
just that's all it is.
For real. That's all what it is, bro.
>> No, but it's not the same though. It's
not the same because I have history with
these people and I know exactly what
they do. So, you know, London Taylor can
say I'm scared all he wants, but bro, it
ain't even that. I ain't scared of no
one. It doesn't matter what they look
like. It's just I know what's going to happen.
And this Don't this guy Isn't this guy uh
Isn't this guy married with kids or something?
That's what makes it worse. Isn't this
guy married with kids apparently?
That's why you can barbecue kids.
>> Yeah. He says he's married with a kid.
That's a madness, isn't it? He said he's
married with kids and he's on YouTube.
That is crazy, bro.
That is funny. Yeah,
but he still comes on here starting and
it's just the same old [ __ ] wasting
money trying to meet people. It's just a
point. It's just pointless, you know.
It is actually pointless, bro.
I'm cooking a nice T-bone steak up.
This is the best season, you know,
coming towards October.
I'm going to put this on the grill in a bit.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ]
Oh, I need I'm going to have an egg with
it as well.
>> Oh, that's another thing.
>> An egg. I'm going to have an egg with it.
Or should I? >> Yeah. That's another egg. Nope.
Don't you [ __ ] multitasking here.
I'm multitasking here, lad. So, sorry if
I don't uh reply back straight away, but
no, I haven't looked at him. He's a snake, mate. [ __ ] Jesus naked. Yeah.
This kitchen is going to be very disgusting
after all of this.
Bobby, Peter, Betty will clean it up.
See, I told you I think of you, bro.
when I do my little um McDonald's videos.
Leave that away now.
This t-bone will do me right.
We can put the [ __ ] on the drill now, can't we? Hopefully. Yeah.
Come on, mate. See you.
Oh, there is there is
[ __ ] People see that lovely mate. Watch out.
Sorry about this, Grezy, mate.
Sorry about this, mate.
Oh, that is smell. [Music]
Sorry, mate. I'm multitasking here.
Yeah, I like mine just like that.
Let me flip over a couple more times.
used to be pink
but no blood.
That's how I like mine.
One second, bro.
I really need to multitask here.
Oh, you [ __ ]
>> SP my [ __ ] finger. Bastard.
Oh, [ __ ] That's hot.
What the [ __ ] bro? No way.
I need to focus.
Need to focus when I'm doing this kind
of [ __ ] maybe.
Ow, my [ __ ] finger. One sec.
Oh, that's lush, mate. That is lush.
That is looking lushy.
One second. Please
be ready in a minute. [ __ ] up, bro. Now
mushroom should be ready in a minute. Bro, cold water.
Right now it's time for the egg. Lovely.
Sometimes that can be a [ __ ] Give up.
That can be a [ __ ] sometimes, mate. [ __ ] bastard. [ __ ] bro.
Oh my [ __ ] finger, bro. Yeah, that's
one sec, please. off.
Why is that so hot?
That hard on that thing is boiling, bro. What's that? [Music]
The safe is
quite big. So
why I can't do that?
should be just right.
No bloody, no nothing.
But you want to see it, G.
Should be right. Let me have a little
taste. Let me do a little incision here.
Don't mind if I do. Mhm.
[ __ ] [ __ ] B state, buddy.
Oh, the helicop stuck. Oh no.
Oh, the head's all stuck now.
I don't know why that's still bloody when
one second, bro. I'm trying to get this [ __ ] egg.
on the plate. There we go.
There we go. I'll show you if you want.
There we go. Lovely.
It's hard because you don't want to
overdo it because once you overdo it, it's disgusting. [ __ ]
That is beautiful though.
That is beautiful.
Oh my [ __ ] finger, bro. That [ __ ] hurt.
Been wanting you for the past couple of
days, mate. We're trying to use that
[ __ ] [ __ ] weren't we? for this.
That's a lovely bit pink but no blood.
That's just how you want it, bro. Like this.
You want it like that bit, but no blood. [Music] No more.
I need to start eating my Mhm. Money
bad. I need to watch out.
Stop [ __ ] mocking me, man.
Your boy skin in the bed. And
after you cut this, bro,
you finish it with your hands.
Right up in there, bro. M
nice and pink, but no blood.
I used to kill the B. Oh, sir.
The reason why
you have this is because
to be able to eat this, you need a good
set of nashes.
You need a good set of nashes,
which he doesn't have. Lovely skin. Skin skin.
Oh man, that last
get right up in that B.
You need to strip it.
Need to strip that [ __ ]
They love me, baby. Would
you like to see the bone groove here?
Would you like to see the bone
if you like?
There is that demolished [Music]
The only bad thing I hate about cooking
is wash up,
but it's worth it.
>> Oh, bless me. Greasy,
me grievy, king's puppies all sat around
the table having a nice bit of piggy
sandwich watching the sideman Sunday.
>> Oh, what a lovely sight.
Is that a lovely site?
Me and you, King King's puppies
lady with a nice bit of pork.
Rice bit of roast pork Christmas Eve
watching the Sideman Sunday.
I hate that. Oh, [ __ ]
That was lovely.
Bad people in general.
You're set to
have to go wash up.
Well, bless you.
Grezy trolls me all the time. He's not
my friend. He's just mocking me.
I grievy. You're just mocking me.
Hate to wash it up, bro. I really do
hate to wash it up as it
Do you actually believe it?
Now it might come across, you know,
sometimes a bit obsessive and what not
greasy, but it does make you wonder, you
know, is he ever going to pop that V plate?
You reckon he's ever going to lose it?
You reckon he'll die? One.
I reckon he'll die. I
>> never going to lose it, mate. You ain't
lost that 31 years of age. You're not
going to [ __ ] lose it now. You You
[ __ ] skin virgin.
How are you going to lose it? How are
When you going to lose it? When you
How are you going to lose it?
When you going to lose it
is an even bigger question.
It's hard to do this washing up cuz I
burnt my [ __ ] feet up.
Hate washing up, man. It's stinking, bro.
Washing up is [ __ ] stinking.
I haven't took my to my codings today.
This kitchen's quite small compared to
the other one. So, it's harder to do the
wash and up.
You know what I'm saying?
How you going? How you going? myself.
I know you're bad and you know your
[ __ ] virgin self, mate. Don't give me
that [ __ ] [ __ ] You've had sex.
You never had sex. Little virgin.
The typical virgin.
Nasty little virgin skin.
[ __ ] throw you. [ __ ] throw you.
You know what I'm saying?
I [ __ ] bro you just skip and I'll
[ __ ] bro you.
I'll [ __ ] you.
[ __ ] with me.
[ __ ] [ __ ] with me. You [ __ ] virgin.
Have you seen that Ricky Milling Snake?
I said, "Have you got anything to say?"
Do you know why these people grieves
you? Do you know why why these people
switch? You know, just like Ricky Mill and that
you want to know why these people switch?
You understand? You don't understand why
they do it.
I could tell you the W, bro.
L I can tell you
I can tell you literally why they switched
a Okay. And then
[ __ ] hating on you. Well, we can tell
you why. Greavves.
Tell you why. If you want.
It's because what it is with these people, right?
Is these people in here,
they're compulsive gamblers.
So they're very very old. They're very
very ugly. They got no hope. And that we
can both agree on and they got no hope.
So when they do their balls in and
they've got and they've got no money to
do anything, they then start coming on
here and saying that you're this and
Peter Benny's this and Peter Benny's
that because I'm the I'm the person that
they go for because obviously I'm
younger than them. I'm better looking
than them. I've got hope I'm like them.
So that's why they all gravitate towards
me. Have you ever ask yourself, why have
I got so many
so many old men?
So many old men gravitate towards me.
You not think that's a bit dodge how
you've got so many old men that don't
know you, gravitating towards you.
Does that not dodgy to you?
Does that not seem a bit dodge?
It seems very dodgy to me.
So, it's cuz they've got nothing. So,
they like to try to tell other people
that they've got nothing because they're
the ones that have got nothing. You know,
it's like, you remember what I used to
say to Monty?
Remember what I used to ask Monty Gy?
Why do these people call me skin?
It's because they're skin. You remember
when Monty used to say that? Cuz these not skin.
Do you remember?
Do you remember? They used to say that.
Yeah. Cuz these are skin.
Yeah. Do you remember [Music] these scenar
Get off the kitchen when you eat.
No, I like movie. I like Dobby. Dobby
the house elf.
What about you?
I like Dobby the house elk.
Who do you like?
That's my favorite little character. I
assume your little favorite character is
Stitch, not I. Dobby the house elf. >> Ow. Um, let me
do a little bit.
>> Get a [ __ ] job.
Stop [ __ ] sitting in your [ __ ]
bed sit all day and get yourself a [ __ ] job.
Get yourself [ __ ]
who you are, man.
that [ __ ] man.
>> Get [ __ ]
used to boy.
Don't care, mate. Don't care.
Don't care what the [ __ ] you're going through, Dad.
through in life, mate. You get a little job.
Get yourself a [ __ ] job. S
Why are you working?
Why don't you get a job?
Why you working, sir?
Why do you think?
You might be able to move out that
[ __ ] [ __ ] bed.
If only you got yourself.
Is that right?
I don't care what you
What do you think about that?
So anyways, when are you um when you
come around to watch Sideman Sunday with
me, Grezy? Me, you, and King
and King's little puppy.
You never know.
You will never know until you get a job.
You will never ever know until