That's why that is okay. Good old AirPods. [ __ ]
Oh, zero. Lovely.
Yeah. Oh, someone's already joined. That's fun.
a second person will be even funner. You know,
I don't want anybody on my on my live stream,
you know. I don't want nobody on my live
stream. Just me talking to myself.
I don't want anyone else on here
cuz everyone else has got a life.
You're still on YouTube,
Frank. You're still on YouTube, lad.
You can't even take a day off of
YouTube. I've been off of YouTube for a
couple of days. I have quit YouTube.
I thought I'd come live and talk some
[ __ ] before I go get some food.
Still on YouTube, Grezy. Jesus Christ.
Still on YouTube.
Doesn't matter, bro. You should quit
YouTube like me. I was off YouTube for a
[ __ ] few days, bro. I'm coming off
again [ __ ] forever. Probably after
this. Yeah, I'm getting a McDonald's. I
got some Monopoly vouchers.
So, I got a Monopoly voucher.
Nah, bro. I was off YouTube for a few
days. It's so mad, Greavves. You know,
when you're off here like even for like
two days. Yeah. Your brain is just like
normal. Yeah. Where? I don't come back
every day. I've not been on YouTube
every day. I don't come on YouTube every
day. I don't go live every day. It's so
mad when you come off this year for like
a couple of days. Grievy, you actually
your brain feels normal. Like when you
come on here, I swear you get brain damage.
I swear you actually get brain damage
when you come on here, bro. Like
whenever you go on that L channel, you
actually become brain dead like them.
That's why it's good to come off of
this, you know, you come back and stuff.
Yeah, Shagger. That's That's good for him, bro.
You sure got that? Yeah. Yep. I've got a
few vouchers. I got breakfast one as well.
You're going to laugh at this,
Greavvesy, and you're going to think I'm
taking a piss, but I've signed up. I've
applied to um work in the adult industry.
Not even not even joking, bro. I was
watching this porn last night and it was
really [ __ ] with my head. And then I
realized like let's think logically
about this, right? If you can't beat
them, join them, right? And all of your
problems are going to go away, you know?
It's not about money. It's about like
the fact that, think about it, bro.
you'll be able to be like them porn
stars and obviously you'll get paid for
it as well.
So, I mean this will stop all of your problems,
you know, and you can and you and you
can work your way up. Think about it.
Yeah. No one no one cares, Shagger.
No, nobody cares, bro. I don't know why
you're bringing that that [ __ ]
irrelevant version up, but um yeah. So,
the problem with it uh Grezy is um
um the thing is is that um basically
like that's the only thing you can
really do if you're staying here long
term because obviously the approaching
is always the same. I have a boyfriend,
[ __ ] and that and we're just going to go
round and round in circles. I've still
not gone out. I'm still not drunk. I
think my drinking days are finished.
Honestly think they're finished. I think
my going out days are finished as well
to be honest. Like going out drinking
and [ __ ] So I feel like you know
joining the adult industry will stop all
of your problems
to be honest.
Not Brazes. It's not Brazes obviously.
You can't just join Brazes like that
[ __ ] but I mean like there were lower
ones and you know you can work your way
up. So I feel like it's a good move to be honest. So,
yep. We'll always bite my nails.
So, I feel like that was the right move
to be honest. Otherwise, you know, we're
just going to go round and round and
round in circles, bro. And it's not
normal, you know.
Yeah. Just I think it's almost been a
month since I've got out, you know, drinking.
Yeah. You already know they will, bro. I
feel like it's the best move cuz that
porn really does [ __ ] with your head.
But I was watching this thing yesterday,
Grezy, where she gave the um teacher a
[ __ ] for better like grades
and it weren't like Johnny Sins or
anything like that where you know it's
fake. It's too good to be fake. Like I'm
not talking about obviously is fake but
it's not where it doesn't look fake.
Does that make sense? It's like with the
Johnny Sins one and all this HD porn
[ __ ] right? It's you can tell that it's
not even believable, you know? Like
Johnny Sins and [ __ ] I can't watch that
cuz it just looks too proper.
Whereas them vintage ones, they I don't
know if that's a word, proper. Whereas
these vintage ones, they're just so natural,
you know, and and you question yourself
like, does it actually happen? would
does it actually happen like that? So
I thought [ __ ] it. I'll just apply with
nothing to lose in it. So
I think that's the right move to be fair
and I'm single as well. So you know I
don't believe in people that are porn
stars and married cuz
it's just weird. Like I know it's their
career and [ __ ] but it's weird. It's
[ __ ] weird. So I've got nothing to
lose. I got no ties here. single. I got
no children. So, you know, it's better
to start. You need to start thinking of
yourself, you know,
and I thought that was the right move to
be honest. So,
I mean, maybe I'm built for it. You
know, I've got that [ __ ] video.
Remember, Greavvesy. Maybe I'm bought
built for it. They say that you should
do something that you love, right? And
not just for the money. Well, that's
something that I would like to do, you know?
Oh, Greavvesy. Me, Lady, Greavvesy,
Greavvesy, uh, uh, King's Puppies all
sat down watching a side men Sunday,
eating a roast lamb and roast pork with
pigs and blankets.
Oh, what a lovely sight.
Me, Greavvesy, King, Lil King,
Laneany, all having some roasting with
some lovely pigs and blankets
watching a Sidemen Sunday. A bless.
That's a lovely side, bro.
But yeah, I ain't drunk for ages, bro.
Can't be asked with it. Can't be [ __ ]
with it, bro.
Yeah, I just can't be bothered with it anymore. Greasy.
Makes me tired thinking of it.
So, what they're going to do is they're
going to email you and ask you to send a
picture of your erect penis. Yeah,
but this [ __ ] Reddit is [ __ ]
Grezy. [ __ ] mods.
The mods ban people because they like to
feel in control because they've got no
control over life or their own life.
They have to feel powerful. So, they go
on this Reddit and they ban people who
disagree with them or people are not
even doing anything wrong because at the
end of the day, it's they don't um
they can't they have to be in control,
you know? They have to have that control
or they go mad. They're proper losers to
be honest and they keep shadowbanning
me. So I'm going to have to I use a VPN
anyways, but they still somehow ban me
and they'll be having a conversation
with someone and then bam, you're banned.
[ __ ] madness. See, the thing is with
like YouTube, they can't ban people like
that. You can do any videos you want on
YouTube, like to an extent, and you
won't get banned. Whereas Reddit, they
love banning people.
Yet they're the virgins sat in their
mom's beds with nothing and then they
try to critique other people. It's mad, isn't it?
It's mad, isn't it, Grezy? It is mad.
It is a madness, bro.
Do you know if you can use the Monopoly
vouchers online or you have to go in and
scan it, don't you?
You can use it online. More than just eat.
I don't know if you can. I'll just go
in. I've got six nuggets.
I'm going to have six nuggets, chips,
and a Coke.
I'll just go up. It's up the road for me
anyways. Six nuggets, chips, and a Coke.
That's all I'm going to eat today.
Yeah. Haven't ate so far.
Oh, them homemade burgers. I had grievy.
I didn't tell you. I made some homemade
burgers. I got some mints and I and I
pressed the burgers and I was making
some homemade burgers. Oh, I made some
lush homemade burgers. I marinated them in onion
and then um onion and black pepper and
[ __ ] And I was hungry at like 2:00 in
the morning. I went back down and made some more.
I had all that, dude. How much that
mince [ __ ] cost me? 12 [ __ ] pound.
It cost me that [ __ ] mint.
12 [ __ ] pound.
12 [ __ ] pounds, bro.
[ __ ] me. But they were nice burgers.
They were lush.
Them burgers were lush. No rubbery, no lumps, nothing.
You come around some one time, Greg,
I'll make you a burger.
You and King.
Yeah, the burgers they were nice, but
the mint was £12, but it made like four
huge burgers. But they were big burgers though.
Yeah, big burgers. Yummy.
What did I have yesterday? I had a curry
yesterday. Here I am.
So yeah, that porn [ __ ] really [ __ ]
with people's heads.
You just know that that little gay boy
Red Star is um
sat here watching this.
Yeah, I need to LT called me yesterday.
I need to say to him, bro, if you want
to call me Yeah. you want to talk about
normal stuff, we can talk about normal
stuff, bro. Stop mentioning these
[ __ ] weirdos on YouTube to me. This
these [ __ ] skint people that ain't
got a life. I don't care about them,
bro. I'll go live when I want to go live
and talk to [ __ ] normal people. I'm
not [ __ ] I don't care about self-reflectors.
Same people, same [ __ ] You know what I
mean? Like, it's boring as [ __ ] bro.
It's why you don't really see me on
there much anymore.
Pointless as [ __ ] [ __ ] pointless.
Tomorrow I need to pick up some dry cleaning
and that's it I think. Yeah, madness.
What do you think of Reddit? Graves,
man. [ __ ] bro.
Why is it a waste of time?
So what? They don't give good advice. No.
I kind of thought like, bro, this is
never going to change and it this women
[ __ ] So, I thought, you know, the best
thing to do is just um
the best thing to do is, like I said,
join this this porn industry thing. Try
to join this porn industry thing.
Like, Grievous, you think I don't go
out? You think I don't go out drinking anymore?
anymore? But because I'm skinn, bro, I'm
not skinn. I've got money. But you know
when you get into the habit of saving
money, even like last year, you just
don't want to spend it.
You just I'm over it, bro. I'm proper
proper over it. I swear to God, I'm
proper over this drinking [ __ ]
proper proper over it, lad.
I'll probably go out like every two
months if that. I just can't be [ __ ]
with it anymore, man.
It is boring as [ __ ] bro. Ain't it
get boring, bro?
It is boring. It is boring.
Do you want to see how the beard getting on?
Don't want to see how the beard's
getting on, bro. It's getting long.
It's getting longer.
Look at that hair.
But I'm going bald apparently.
I'm going bored apparently. Sheesh. Wow.
I didn't know I was going B. Like that's
that's news to me. Oh [ __ ]
See, the thing is, Grezy, you see why
I'm normal now?
You know why I'm normal now? Is it
Greasy? Because I've not been out for weeks.
And you know, the longer you do
something, the more you sort of forget
about it. All of the bad experiences,
the make believe boyfriends. See,
because I've not gone out for a long
time, you see. But if I went out today
or if I went out tomorrow,
it would be exactly the same thing.
So it's a catch. It's a catch 22.
It is literally a catch 22.
That's the [ __ ] up thing about it.
That's the whole [ __ ] up thing. So
cuz if you risk talking to someone
again, the same thing happens again. You
see what I mean?
So, it's like, what the what the [ __ ] do
you do? You know,
there was a few people I saw [ __ ] the
past 3 days and I didn't even walk too
far, bro. I didn't even speak to them
cuz I'd rather not know. It's that bad.
I'd rather not know because that way if
I don't know, see, this is how [ __ ] up
it is. If I don't speak to them, then I
don't know what I don't know can't hurt
me. You know what I'm saying? Whereas if
I do speak to them, the same thing
happens again and again and again. So
it's like you can't win. So that's why I
said like the industry is
is your best bet.
Joining the porn industry. Yeah. Thought
that was good, man. I thought that was a
good move. me a lot of people don't approve but
just say I actually went and approached
that person in the shop cuz you imagine
who I actually went
and then you got this woman saying that
she goes on three
three dates a month but she can't find anyone
Which then goes back to Joe's point,
right? Is that they're saying, lad, um
they are um what's it, bro? Um so, you
know, Joe, right, that says, "Oh, but
like they're choosing other men. They're
choosing other men." But they're not.
Cuz think of it, Grezy. How many dates
do these women go on? And how many guys
do they reject until they finally get
with someone, leaving all them other
guys in transit? If some [ __ ]
going on three dates a month, bro, and
they still can't find someone,
then it's kind of like, well, isn't a
problem the women then in their standards?
Think about it. There's three there's
three dates a month. They go on with
dates for three different guys a month
that ain't being chosen. These guys
ain't being chosen. And then it takes
them like six months to a year to then
finally find someone. So that's why I
just joined. That's that's why I'm
trying to join the [ __ ] pool industry cuz Yeah.
Yeah, man. So that's that's it. So yeah,
[ __ ] for me. Imagine me getting free
dates. Do you know what I would have to
do, Greasy, to get three dates a month?
Do you know what I would have to do to
get three [ __ ] dates a month?
Jesus Christ, bro. I could go out
drinking every week. I wouldn't even get
a date a month. I'd be lucky if I was to
get one date a month, let alone [ __ ] three.
say that though. I've had like two dates
in a month before, but that's like rare.
Yeah, man. The dating game is just not
worth it anymore.
It's just not worth it anymore, lad.
The dating game. Mackie Dukes.
Six nuggets and chips.
I have to buy the chips and the coke obviously. Of course. [Music] Oh man.
Hey man, I don't go on um anyone's
channel anymore, Slim. I barely really
come on this YouTube thing anymore,
dude. I think every time I come on it, I
get brain damage.
And you'll notice that when you when
you're off here for like two days,
you're thinking, "What the [ __ ] What
the [ __ ] was I doing them past couple of
days, bro? They they actually give you
brain damage. I don't know how you go on
that L's and you speak to them mongos.
Them self-reflective mongos. You're
crazy, bro. I can't even go on that
without getting brain damage.
Don't see the point.
I just don't see the point in their
channels, bro. I don't see there's no
meaning. There's no substance behind any of it.
It's just a bunch of [ __ ]
old people that ain't got nothing trying
to talk about other people every day on
YouTube. It's [ __ ] weird, bro. It's
so creepy. It gives me the eje.
That's what it gives me, bro. They creep
me out, bro. It's creepy.
It's a creepy community.
I don't know how you got on that
channel, bro. [ __ ] hell. [ __ ] that.
They give me the [ __ ] creeps.
You're crazy, man.
Nah, it's not an eye opener because I
already knew that's what he looked like.
No, I already knew. I already know what
these people are about, bro.
Like that red star and that. That's why
I don't bother with them because I
already know what they why they do what
they do. That's why I don't bother with them anymore.
Nah, it's not even an eye opener. I already knew.
They give themselves away. You know,
think about it, bro. They're sat on
YouTube, right, every day calling people
skin, calling people this, calling
people that. If they had all of this
everything to life, they wouldn't be
doing that. It's obvious, bro. It's not
eye opener. It's I knew it. I knew it.
Just like I know about that Red Star and
all of these other people. They That's
why I don't bother with them.
you know. So,
so no, not an eye opener at all. I expected it.
Yeah, I um I applied to the adult
industry. Um Slim
Yeah, I applied to this adult industry.
I thought it was a good move.
No, they're going to email me and ask me for it.
Then I'm going to have to go to the studio.
>> Yeah, I thought it was um Yeah, like I
said, it's a good mood. A good move. So
yeah, it's a small company. It's not
like Brazes. Obviously, you have to work
your way up, you know? You can't just
join [ __ ] brazes cuz the way I see it
is Slim. Yeah, I've not been out for
I I've I've not been out for about 3
weeks, Slim. I haven't drunk. I talk to
you normally cuz you you you seem normal
on here. I haven't drunk for 3 weeks. I
haven't gone out because I feel like you
get to a certain age. Well, it's not
just a women [ __ ] It's just I think
people stop at 27, 28 anyways.
And I just can't be [ __ ] with it
anymore, bro. You know what I'm saying?
I can't be bothered with it anymore. The
going out, the drinking, getting the
same old [ __ ]
Like, it's not bad. This is what I was
trying to explain to Greasy is that, you
know, the past couple of days I've gone
out, I've I've seen people that I like
the look of, but I haven't even spoke to them
because me not knowing is better. It's
better for me not to know,
you know? You see, that's how bad it is.
Where most people would regret it, I
just would rather not do it.
So, it's that's how bad it gets, bro.
Most people will see someone and if they
don't approach them, they regret it. But
with me, I already know the result. I've
done it [ __ ] 7,000 times. So
that's [ __ ] bro. It's so mad for it
to be the other way around
cuz they're not Yeah,
I know. And where I've not been out for
weeks, it doesn't really bother me much
anymore. But as soon as I speak to
someone again, the same thing's going to
happen again. And then we're going to go
around in circles again. This is the
problem. So I thought obviously you
joining the adult industry,
it's a good move. You know, it's like I
was watching the porno yesterday, bro,
and it was really [ __ ] with my head.
And I was like, if you can't beat them,
join them. You get paid. You got no
kids. You're single. you know, there's
nothing stopping you from at least even
trying to do it. Cuz the thing is is Yeah.
And people think it's about money, Slim.
It's not. It's not about money, bro. I
could go out every week if I wanted to.
I might not be on as much money, but I
still have money. I still have enough
money to do what I want to do. But I
just don't see the point in it, you know?
So I think I saw about three people I
like the look of. But no, I just I just
know already what's going to happen. But
then it's a catch 22 Slim because
obviously you're like
if you're like 28, 29 and you want to
meet somebody and you want to settle
down. How you have to speak to people,
but then if you speak to people, the
same thing happens again. No one's
interested. And then the same thing just
happens again and again and again.
when I go out for when I go out for a
drink again. I don't know when it's
going to be, but
[ __ ] knows, bro.
It's mad. I don't know. It's so Yeah,
just the industry is a good way.
I messaged a few numbers I had last week
if they wanted to meet up, but nope.
Nah. So, basically, I've got no new
numbers now I can try on. The only one
I've got is that one from Finland that
said she'll meet me.
So, I mean, that's sort of like that's another
that's really who I've got. I don't have
anybody else and I don't want to go out
and get new numbers
cuz for what reason? What am I doing the
same thing for, bro? I'm tired of it. You know,
so yeah, that's the thing. A little Yeah,
but I do want to go out again at some
point and drink and then have a nice
meal at the end. Go go go to a nice
curry housey, you know, like a nice a
nice curry house.
Oh, bless you.
It's cute, isn't it?
Nice little curry house after
I feel like a six I feel like a six week
break is incoming, bro.
I mean, it's okay for [ __ ] breaks and
[ __ ] but this it's just going to start
all over again when you go out. You know
what I mean? Grievously, it's just going
to start all over again.
What I don't understand is how these
women say they can't meet like normal
guys and [ __ ]
I mean, you could go out and drink and
not approach, but let's be real, you're
going to approach someone,
you know? It's like you can't just go
out and not speak to anyone. That's
ridiculous. So, it's like it's just
what the [ __ ] does someone do in this
country, bro? You know, what does
someone do in this country? That's ridiculous. Who knows?
Lord knows. Greasy. Lord knows.
I don't know, bro.
And also, here's another [ __ ] up
thing, Slim, right?
The more you try, the more you lose hope.
I know it sounds crazy, isn't it? The
more you try, the more you lose hope.
Think about it, bro.
What used to happen with them gambling [ __ ]
them gambling um
people used to stop gambling for ages
and then went back to it. Yeah. The
more you try the more you lose hope.
I know it's [ __ ] It's so mad, isn't it?
They want people to have hope, but the
only way to have hope is not trying.
It's [ __ ] madness, isn't it? It
really, really is a country designed to annoy you.
But like I said, it's that's why we've
done the the porn thing.
The gating the dating game the
the dating game is just not it's just
not worth it. But
[ __ ] hell. Getting a bit hungry now. Greasy.
It is a mad one. that
cuz it generally is like you
you try and then you lose hope even the
more you try. It's mad.
I know. It's crazy. I feel like if you
if you stopped for like 6 months, right?
I feel like you'd have hope again.
generally feel like you'd have hope again
because obviously you've forgot about
all the [ __ ] that's happened in the
past. So that's the only way to get hope
is never trying again.
Oh, it's mad. It doesn't make no sense, does it?
Yeah, it is a badness. It is a badness.
The more longer you go about trying, the
more hope comes back. And then when you
try again, you lose hope again.
Cuz you see the reality of it. You see,
that's the problem.
It's like taking It's like taking a
break from gambling.
It's like taking a break from gambling
and then going back to gambling. It
doesn't make no sense. That's not really
breaking the cycle. That's just taking a break.
Do you understand what I mean, Grezy?
It's like it's like say you was taking a
break from being a compulsive gambler
and you went back to gambling. It
doesn't really make sense, does it?
Unless you went back with limits. But
the whole point of breaking a cycle is
not to take a break from something. It's
to stop breaking the cycle. So,
so yeah, if you went out again and you
tried again, the same thing would happen
and then you're back in the same rut
again. Unless you want to stop drink,
unless you want to drink and not talk to
anyone, which is impossible, like I said. So,
What does one do? Eh,
as you're older, the breaks get uh
longer as well. So,
I mean, yeah, you know, you can go out
and have a drink and enjoy yourself, but
you're not going to drink and not speak to anyone.
That's not going to happen, bro. You know
because when you're out again, you're
going to be under the impression that
you've got hope again.
Cuz that's what people tell you that you
got hope. But there is no hope. That's
the whole point. There is none. Yeah.
What do you want me to do, Greavves? You
go on the street every day and start
talking to people.
What do you want me to do? Start
approaching women every day?
What the [ __ ] bro? Who's got time to do
that? I ain't got time to do that, bro.
I ain't even I ain't even got the energy
to do that.
So, do do you want me to [ __ ] go out
on the street and start [ __ ] you
know, that's the reality of it. That's
the reality that no one tells you. So, yeah,
the more you try, the more you lose
hope. It makes sense
in a way where
I used to I was watching Manchester
something about Manchester.
Oh, I used to love going Manchester and getting drunk.
Then I realized I've done it about a million times.
Oh no, it's a mad one.
Manchester was fun, bro. Manchester was fun. Yeah.
You want to be the cameraman for the porno, Greasy?
You want to be the cameraman?
You want to be the cameraman? Yeah.
Yeah. This porn video just [ __ ] with
my head, Gregy. She just gave him a
[ __ ] for like
She gave him a [ __ ] for um
to get better grades.
[ __ ] madness. It's [ __ ] It does [ __ ]
with your head though, don't it? It does
[ __ ] with your head.
Stuff like that can [ __ ] with your head, bro.
It does [ __ ] with your head, eh?
He was like, he was like, "C C minus,
okay, B." And then just before he came,
he's like, "A a [ __ ] madness, bro. [ __ ] madness."
He was he was he was he was putting the
the alphabet as he was getting a [ __ ]
[ __ ] It was madness.
[ __ ] hell, bro. It's depressing,
isn't it? See,
if it was something like couples having sex,
it wouldn't be as bad.
I watched this porno before when the six
black guys was banging this white woman
and I was watching it again yesterday.
Do you remember? Do you know when that
was Do you know when that was made,
Greasy? That was made in 2012. 2012
I Peter Belly was 14.
I was only little. [ __ ] I was only
little in 2012. Those were the Skype days.
201 [ __ ] 12. [ __ ] me. What? 13 years ago.
13 [ __ ] years ago, bro. [ __ ]
Yeah. She got gang banged by these six
black guys. It was mad.
It's [ __ ] mad. music.
You don't watch Paul News.
And it's and it's unhealthy because it's
like if you got into a relationship with
someone, you would expect that.
That's why watching porn is like bad for
you because you expect that.
It's [ __ ] It is bad. It is bad.
It is bad. Yeah.
[ __ ] depressing, bro. See, I feel
like back in the day it wouldn't be as
bad cuz you could probably meet women and stuff, but um
you could probably Oh [ __ ] Franklin
died. You could probably meet women and
stuff. So, back in the day, it probably
weren't as bad, but now when you can't
even get a conversation out of someone,
it's kind of like your um it's kind of [ __ ] Um,
you know what I mean?
It would be very rare for somebody to
like you that much to do that to you,
mate. You know what I'm saying? So,
it is bad, bro. It is bad. Porn. You know,
you can't even get a [ __ ] Oh, another
thing greaves as
I looked up why people went out why
people stopped going out clubbing and a
lot of these people like, "Oh, with the
dating apps now, it makes it even easier
to hook up with someone." I started
messaging these people, G. I said, "Oh,
I've got a bone to pick with you. What
[ __ ] apps are you [ __ ] talking
about? Apps are easy to hook up with
people. Dating apps don't even work."
No. None of them replied backwards. I
said, "You what? Dating apps make it
[ __ ] easy. The reason we went out in
the [ __ ] first place is because they didn't work.
Why else do you think we [ __ ] went
out spending [ __ ] £200 every [ __ ] week
or whatever it was?" Because [ __ ]
dating apps don't work. We got a [ __ ]
bone to pick with you.
Still going on about dating apps when
they've been dead for like six [ __ ] years.
I swear people on Reddit just type [ __ ] don't they?
I swear I swear people on Reddit just
type [ __ ] for the sake of typing [ __ ]
What do you think, Grezy?
Well, let me see this.
on the guy on the N.
So I get free S. I still get free
chicken slacks when you buy a Philly
cheese steak meal or a chicken. So you
get free selects with it again.
Don't mind if I do, boss.
I'm ordering a McDonald's. Don't mind if
I do, boss.
Don't mind if I do.
Uh, the only thing I don't have in them
is pickles. How do I get these? No. No.
I need a mill. What the [ __ ]
So, how do I get these nuggets?
So, how do I get these nuggets, lad?
Right. So, how do I get these free nuggets?
One second, please.
So, how do I get these nuggets then, [ __ ] Right.
So, how do I get it then? Yeah. Okay.
Okay. Well, I've got breakfast. I've got
a breakfast thing.
I've got a breakfast thing. Yeah.
voucher and I've got a nugget voucher.
So, I've got two vouchers.
Does that make sense? Grezy.
So, I've got a breakfast one, which I'll
probably get in the in the morning. So,
I've got a breakfast one and I've got a nugget one.
So, I'll definitely have to use them tomorrow.
Does that make sense? Right, lovely.
Oh no, I just put picked the wrong [ __ ] one.
I just put picked foland zero. No, no,
no, no, no.
Well, it doesn't matter because I I got
Coke anyways. I just picked the wrong [ __ ] drink.
I might cancel it. One sec.
Got to cancel it. Hold on.
I don't think you can.
It doesn't matter. I've got coke anyways.
Oh, I think they're already at the restaurant. One second.
Yeah, you can't even change it. Lucky I
got coke in it, Grezy.
Otherwise, I'd be [ __ ] up.
W I'll be [ __ ] up.
I need to go cinema on the 26th to watch um Strangers.
You seen it, Grezy? Oh, [ __ ] hell.
You've seen it in it, Grezy.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Yeah, you've seen it. It greasy lad.
Strangers chapter 2. So, I need to get
my dry cleaner out tomorrow.
[ __ ] sake. Going to do some food shopping.
I need to really start saving some money now. Matey [ __ ] Fanta.
Let's go. We
Right. I'm gone. I'll be back later. Yeah.