Sorry, mate. I'm um
thinking I'm thinking of bringing out
some merch, you know. Yeah,
I'm thinking of bringing out some merch,
but not selling it. not selling the merchandise cuz you know
not [ __ ] skin like L J. But you know
I'm thinking of bringing out some merch
and just sending it to people. Now what
I wouldn't want any money for it or
anything just like you know
you know selling it to people and stuff
giving it to people. Sorry.
Yeah. So, I'm thinking of like, yeah,
bringing out some merchandise,
but like I said, I'm not selling it cuz
I'm not skin like L J. But, you know,
I'm just give it. I don't mind just
like, you know, just just giving it.
Just giving it, you know. Um Yeah, man. [Music] Yeah. [ __ ] hell.
The one a small football bet, by the
way. [ __ ] tiny [ __ ] football bet.
Only had 20 pound on it. Yeah, I know,
right? [ __ ] can't.
But better than nothing, is it? So,
but I'm thinking of like bring out merch.
I'm bringing out No, do you know what it
is, Greasy? I've been out all day. No,
I've been out all day. Me? It's just
obviously I'm not going out drinking. I
won a football bet, by the way. I put 20
pound on it, returned 60. I mean, 2040,
but4 in it, I guess. So,
It's better than nothing, can it?
Yeah, pretty much. Yeah, [ __ ]
Darlington scored in the last [ __ ]
literally the last second.
So, it's better than nothing, isn't it?
I had to go collect my dry clean and I
had my um stonies dry cleananed,
so I had to go pick up the dry clean and
cost me [ __ ] 30 quid. So
yeah, that's that's that. Um
and yeah, I'm thinking of bringing out
merch, bro. But um giving the merch away for free.
Yeah, giving the merch away for free, bro. Yeah. So, um,
you want to see the stonies? I got them
dry clean. Lovely, bro. You want to see
them? Yeah. So, basically the merch is
going to be called
uh it's going to be like t-shirts and
hoodies. It's going to be virgin boy
skin in the bed with no money in it. I
feel like that's my little that's my
little uh slogan.
when you're going to lose it. We can
like we can literally like uh
wear on the nights out and [ __ ] bro.
You know, you want to see my dry
cleaning, my little Sony's.
Oh, they're lovely.
Look, I picked them up from the dry
cleaners and they're lush.
Look how lush that is, bro.
Look how [ __ ] lush that is. Ow.
Oh, by the way,
look, the stain's gone. Got rid of the stain.
No stain. Press stonies.
So, oh, what happened to you, mister?
Now, this is the this is the one I was
going to give Virgin Boy. Now, it's been
dry cleananed. Believe you me, I've just
picked up from the dry cleaners. That's
why it's looking so fresh. No stains, no
nothing. Cost me a lot of money. This
this mate, I was thinking of giving it
to Virgin Boy.
What do you think? Oh, if you in case
you're wondering where little where
little badges are.
Here's a badge. The badges are there.
Like, oh, I don't mind [ __ ] you
know, giving it to Virgin, but look,
it's been dry cleaned.
I know you were saying about them, you
know, being secondhand and stuff. They
look that way cuz they were crunched up.
But look, I can It's all looking really fresh
right now. Virgin boy.
I think of like giving you that.
>> Like what do you think?
See what I'm saying? That's a lovely one.
That's my favorite one. That's my
favorite one. That one. But I don't mind
giving it to Virgin Boy, man.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Yeah.
Yeah. Them Stonies are looking clean,
bro. Oh, gorgeous. So, that football bet
basically paid for the dry cleaning.
What a lovely site.
Just put the rollers up on the [ __ ]
badge, bro. Know what I'm saying? Yeah.
In the bed. [ __ ] with no money in it.
Skin in the bed. [ __ ] with money in it.
Kid in the bed with no money.
>> Yeah, man.
What do you think of the stone, Greasy?
They're looking lush, aren't they?
Yeah. They didn't look secondhand.
They just needed dry cleaning.
That's all they needed is [ __ ] dry
clean and they've been sat there for [ __ ] months.
That's what the problem with them were,
you know? There wasn't they weren't
secondhand, you silly goose.
They just needed [ __ ] dry cleaning.
[ __ ] sat there for [ __ ] months greasing up.
So yeah, the stain. It got rid of the
stain. I like the electric blue, you
know. It's quite uh it's quite loud.
Greavves. It's quite loud.
When I go out drinking again, I think
I'm going to wear that one, bro.
I don't know. Yeah, something like that. Madness.
Yeah, the guy insisted I paid cash. So,
I paid cash. I was like, "Okay, whatever." You know?
Oh, there was this [ __ ] today.
Grezy, you can never go out in this
country without coming across a [ __ ]
She was an old woman, by the way.
And the the the bus the bus come
the bus came basically. And um
yeah, the bus come. So,
so the bus come and
basically you know how the bus like
stops in front of you but the bus
stopped in front of me and she literally
rushed to get in the on the bus before
me. I was like mate
the bus ain't going anywhere.
There's so many [ __ ] in this country.
So many [ __ ]
It's unbelievable. You can't even go out
and experience something normal, you
know? You can't even have a normal day
without coming across a [ __ ]
What's your favorite Stony Greavvesy?
Mine's got to be that blue one. No, that
blue one is lush.
That blue one is lush.
Got to be that. It's got to be that that
royal blue one. I think there's got to be
it's got to be in it.
Wish I had more football back, but
I didn't really want to risk losing any money.
Yeah. Didn't want to risk losing any more cash.
[ __ ] Yeah. I was watching Timmy's video
yesterday, right? When he's playing that
roulette and it's like really, bro, some
people never learn, do they?
They never ever learn. Has he not
learned about the machines by now?
[ __ ] hell, bro.
And he's still doing this [ __ ] at what,
41, 42. It's [ __ ] crazy, isn't it?
You know, you should have your
priorities straight at like [ __ ]
27, 28. Some people are even younger.
And he doesn't have any, you know?
It's mad. It is actually madness, bro.
It is mad. It is mad.
You were a fool, mate. You were a fool.
Oh yeah, whatever that st Whatever the
[ __ ] that st was [ __ ] went good.
Screw it up.
Darlington scored on literally the last 20 seconds.
[ __ ] You know, I bad.
Nah, not really, bro. I've got plans.
cuz I'm leaving soon. So, I'm all good, bro.
I'm all good, lad.
See, I ain't been out for a few weeks. I
ain't drunk for a few weeks. I feel good.
Yeah, feel good. I'm leaving. So, it is
what it is, bro. It's not my problem anymore. So,
it's not my problem no more, bro.
I was watching um I was I was uploading
some of my videos on my other channel to
show people on Reddit like um and I
think last time I went to Manchester was
Mother's Day. No, it wasn't. The last
not the last time I went Manchester, the
time before that I went Manchester was
Mother's Day. It was literally Mother's
Day, right? and [ __ ] um
I remember coming back on on the train
saying, "Oh, I got four numbers."
I think I said I got four numbers or something.
And yeah, I won a football bet as well. Sorry again.
It's [ __ ] up. Queeny really [ __ ] up. Did it
too. So proud of me for not going out
for three weeks.
Will I go out next week? Nah.
Pointless. [ __ ] pointless, bro.
When I When will I be out again? I know.
I'd like to say the last the next time
I'll [ __ ] go out is my birthday, but
I don't know. Who knows?
[ __ ] knows, man.
So, you get into this like routine of
saving money and you like saving money
and then once you want to save money,
you don't want to spend money. This is
what happens. You see,
but I mean I got the gms. I got the dry
cleaning page for today. You know, could
easily go out if I wanted to, but
nah, it's no point.
[ __ ] lush, mate. Calms are lush.
So, what I would probably do, right, if
I was to go out today, I' i'd do the
Sunday as well. So I do today and I
would do the Sunday. So like
what I do is like I dress up and groom
myself on the Saturday and then I'd go
out on the Sunday with like the Stony.
So it's like I do I would just do like I
do I would just do like two days. So, but yeah,
that's my fave.
One second. I'll be right back here.
Yeah, that's the thing. Greavesy, I bet
you miss them days, don't you? Gambling
in the casino.
Huh? I bet you miss them days.
[ __ ] gambling in the casino and
buying some stonies with the winners. Don't you
Yeah, there were good days, bro. Good days.
>> So, what are you going to are you are
you going to are you going to wear the
merch then? Did I give you the merch?
Are you going to wear it? 100%. Yeah.
Will you wear the merch, Grezy? Yeah.
You have to wear the merch if I bring it out.
in a [ __ ] bed.
I'm going to I'm going to have like
black. I'm going to have white. I'm
going to have like the, you know, [ __ ]
virgin boy in the bed [ __ ] with no bed
and no money in it.
No, you have to wear that one. You have
No, you got to wear that one.
You've got to wear that one, bro.
If I went out Saturday and Sunday,
Grezy, how many numbers do you think I'd get
on the Saturday and the Sunday?
How many numbers do you reckon I'd get?
What in both of the days? Nah.
More than that, [ __ ] probably like 10.
Nah, man. Probably like [ __ ] 10. No,
not three in two [ __ ] days. Been
[ __ ] more than that. Do you want me
to go to Waxies today, Greavvesy with the Stony?
Do you want me Do you want me to go to
Waxies with the Stony on?
Yeah, Grezy, is that what you want?
with a [ __ ] Sony on.
Bless me then, Grezy.
Yeah, with the Sony on you ball.
in the bed with no [ __ ] bed
in the bed with no bed and no money in
it. It's catchy saying it.
Catchy sayings. Catchy sayings. chop. Oh, Franklin.
>> You like that little voice, Squeezy?
A lot of people like that little voice.
Why don't I buy any more stonies, Gezy?
Because Peter Belly don't have Stone
Island money anymore.
Yeah, Peter Belly doesn't have Stone
Island money anymore. That's right.
That's funny, is it? Grieves.
Oh, that's so funny.
Oh, I still need to have my nuggets for
Macky's, but instead I got cooked a
plate of piggies.
Yeah, I had some piggies.
I need to go cinema on the 26.
Then I need to I need to go cinema on the 26. Need to
might need to go twice. I don't know what's on
some stuff to do.
Some stuff to do. Yeah,
we can't all sit around being a [ __ ]
virgin. You know what I mean? Rey, mate.
We can't sit around being a [ __ ] virgin, mate.
Deliveroo contacted me saying, "Uh,
yeah, we've got your application." But,
bro, I applied for them like 3 years
ago, four years ago, and they still
ain't [ __ ] reply back.
They still ain't [ __ ] reply back. the So, oh [ __ ]
[ __ ] absolute [ __ ] they are. But
that's what they are. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Is that right, Grezy? [ __ ]
My little bones are hurting me.
It's quite quiet today for Saturday. I
went around the pub and stuff. Quite quite um
quite quiet, eh? H. Yeah,
it's quite quiet.
I guess people don't have any longer.
No, it's not even raining here. The
weather's actually decent to be honest.
But [ __ ] no one's out and the roads
were quite clear.
Yeah. Do you like it when I go out,
Grezy with the little stony on?
It's quite cute, isn't it?
Yeah, it's quite cute.
Yeah, I don't think I could give Virgin
boy that one. That one's my favorite
What do you think, Greasy? Stone Island
with the little man bun. What do you
think of that? Cute.
Do you think that's quite cute, Grezy?
That's quite cute, isn't it? Greasy.
No, but a man bum with a little with a
little Stone Island greasy. Little Stone What?
with a little stone island. Grievy.
Oh, do you remember Timmy yesterday on
the on the roulette um cheering because
he was 90 pound down? Greavesy. He was
cheering because he was 90 down. Imagine
cheering cuz you're 90 down.
What the [ __ ]
That's [ __ ] hilarious, isn't it, bro?
Sharing about being [ __ ] 90 pound down.
That's funny, isn't it? He's like, "Oh,
I'm 90 pound down now." Yes. What the
[ __ ] I couldn't believe what I was watching.
Oh, another thing. I was enjoying that
roulette video. You know, that roulette
video that he was that he made,
Greavves. I was actually quite enjoying
that and then all of a sudden it disappeared.
All of a sudden it [ __ ] disappeared.
was wondering what the [ __ ] happened.
Yeah. What the [ __ ] N.
This detox jaw does feel good. Greavvesy.
you know, you get a piece of mind that,
you know, you actually get a piece of
mind. It's nice, you know, it's nice,
you know, when you when you um when you give up.
It is nice when you give up, you know.
Just feels good, man.
It feels so good when you give up.
Well, I'll be back later. Yeah.