Oh my [ __ ] god. Right.
Timmy is such a [ __ ] self projector.
[ __ ] hell, man. Showing 300 [ __ ]
pound. What the [ __ ] is wrong with
showing [ __ ] showing 300 [ __ ] pound.
Oh my god, these people really are
[ __ ] I'm not even going to say the word. It's just
it's just [ __ ]
It's just self projecting.
That's what it is.
That's what it is, matey. It's self It's
self It's self projection. That's what
it is. What these people do on here.
Look at Timmy. Yeah. [ __ ] gambling on
a [ __ ] FB. Yeah. And then he's trying
to say I do that [ __ ]
Self projecting. Who the [ __ ] chose
[ __ ] 300 pound
madness, bro? Absolute madness.
You know what? Yeah.
It actually makes sense.
It actually makes sense to be honest why
these people call other people's skin.
It really does. It makes sense now, man.
You know, if I'm watching Timmy, it
really makes sense. It's cuz their skin,
isn't it, matey? Yeah.
That's what it is.
It's usually good. Yeah.
I'm so tempted to go out today, bro.
Only because of how good them Stonies come out.
But no, I'm good, bro.
I'm all right in my little nesticles. Yeah.
money in it.
To be fair, I do say that though cuz
it's just catchy sayings
and he is actually skin. Like that's not
even me self projectoring. No, he is
actually a skin bastard. But like you
know [ __ ] these people actually sell projectors.
They actually sell uh you know
I know you're watching.
I know you're watching, man.
You know who you are. An FB
in the bedet with no money in it.
That's [ __ ] hilarious, bro.
showing 300 pound. That is hilarious, man.
That is hilarious.
And I'm fing what? >> Yeah.
Yeah, mate. Yeah.
Yeah. [ __ ] you. [ __ ] baby. Fine.
What are you doing? version, isn't it?
Look out for the merch. It's coming soon.
So, I need your um I need your address
so I can send this uh I can send this
stone island to you. Yeah.
I mean, I've never been so
happy about a 39 win before,
you know? Never been so happy about a 39 pound win
because it's like buying the Stonies all
over again from brand new. Never have I
been so happy about less than a 40 win
cuz it shows all the things that you
can't afford. Can't afford Stone Island,
mate. You ain't got the money.
So, I thought it'd be nice if you give
me your your address.
I I'll send you send you the jumper
with the badge. I've got the badge to it
as well, you know. Yeah.
You can't afford Stone Island.
It's a bit out of your price range. You
had charity shops. Skid bastard. Oh, what? Yep. So yeah, dollar
Timmy such herself. And yet the
I need to get a battery for this [ __ ] controller, man. Good ball. nothing.
Why am I still alive? Because I want to
be still alive. Is that a problem with you?
Is that a problem with you or what? H
Why are you still alive?
Why is Timmy showing 300 pound on
YouTube? You know, everything Terry says here
is about himself. Skin done your balls
in. That's literally if you watch his
videos, yeah, you realize that he's
literally just talking about himself.
Now, obviously all the people on there
talk about themselves like when they try
to call you skin and [ __ ] but you know
what I mean. It's madness.
He's a proper self projector in it.
Per cell projector. Yeah.
Yeah. I got my stonies dry cleananed.
Thinking of donating one to virgin by
skin in a bed sit with no money in it.
You know me, mate. You know me.
Always thinking of other people.
You know, always thinking of other people, lad.
I can't believe Timmy's still playing them machines.
What madness of that?
That is a madness.
These GTA clips are so addicting, bro.
They are so [ __ ] addicting. Madness. What? Oh,
Yo, man. I got my [ __ ] um I got my
Stone Islands [ __ ] um
I got them dry cleananed.
Yeah, I don't know. Both teams discards
there. I only put £20 on it and they
returned 60. I mean, it paid for the dry
cleaning. The dry cleaning was £30.
So, I've I've never been so excited to
win 3040 pounds in my life.
You know, it paid for the dry cleaning,
the the the free Stonies and the Ralph Lauren.
So, I mean, you know, they look brand
new. So, you know, it's Yeah, I've done
a double both teams. Arlington scored in like
the last 20 seconds literally. So,
yeah. So need to collect £60. Yeah, man.
It paid for the dry cleaning. It's funny
as [ __ ] Oh, literally.
I was so tempted to go out today cuz of the stonies.
But nah, [ __ ] that, bro. I ain't going
out, bro. [ __ ] that. Nowhere.
We got three stone. He's done.
I'm on Ralph. I should have had more on
that. Both teams to score in it, but
I didn't need any more money. I didn't
need to. I don't need any more money, so
I just put 20 pound on it. But I should
have put [ __ ]
I should have put more on it.
always the way I do it.
Yeah, I'll go and collect it whenever
when I'm near a bookies cuz I'm going to
go out my way to collect it, you know.
So, I've won four bets out of seven.
I've done seven bets this season and
I've won Yeah. But yeah,
why is no one coming on the chat, bro? It's dead
on. It's weird, isn't it?
Yeah, usually. But I'm saving money,
broke, and I've got money, so I don't
need to try and win any more money.
I only do that if I ever get like short
money or something. But I'm all right
with money, so I don't need to um
I don't need to put 100 pound on two teams.
I just put 20 pound on it.
[ __ ] 20 [ __ ] pound, bro.
But I wouldn't put any more on it on I
just done it cuz the bookies was next to
the cash point. I had to pick up the dry cleaning. So,
you know what I'm saying? I just thought
I'd stick 20 on it. So,
>> you remember that one where I put 120 on
it and it returned 360? That was a nice
win, bro. 380 from 120. That was a nice
win. That was like [ __ ]
3 weeks ago
pretty much. Yeah. A win is a win
cuz uh the dry cleaning was like £30. It
was expensive as [ __ ] So, you know, it
pays for it. So, at the end of the day,
bro, it's some free money is free money,
bro. 2030, 40. Who gives a [ __ ] you know?
[ __ ] like three hours of work. Two
two hours of work. That's what it is.
Yeah. Do you remember that, bro? I
actually went in the bookies with 160,
but I lost 40 on the roulette and I just
put 120 on two teams, but I wish I just
put the 160 on the two teams. I should
just put the 160 on the two teams. Doesn't matter.
>> Nah, bro, you wouldn't because they're designer clothes.
They're designer clothes. They're four
pieces of designer clothes. So, it's
worth it. It's worth the 30 pound.
Yeah, because they're they're expensive clothes.
They're worth like £1,200. Like 12
fingers are worth £1,200. So
I thought I could go out for some
Guinnesses today, do some approaches,
but that's only cuz I saw the nice Stone
Island jumpers. But no, I'm done with
that [ __ ] bro. Done with that [ __ ]
No. Three of them are Stonies. One of
them is Ralph LM. No.
And they had stains on them as well. So, and yeah,
I like that royal blue stony. I was
thinking of wearing it just getting on
the drink, but I really can't be asked
for a little while, bro. Yeah.
We really can't.
She don't want you.
I was thinking of giving one of the
stonies to the virgin.
Yeah. Still [ __ ] off. Yeah, bro.
And I need to save money as well. I
can't go out waste the money now as
well. That's another thing.
I've got things to do, places to be. So, you know,
yeah, I could have easily went on the
piss today. The good old pisseroo.
Good old piss a rube.
Yeah. So, do you reckon I should give a
stone island to Virgin boy?
Do you reckon?
Yeah, maybe he might get laid. He might
lose his virginity.
You reckon I should? He might actually
finally get laid. Skim bastard. Yeah.
Yeah. You might get laid in it. Might
finally lose that replay. Lose rec.
When you going to lose it? How you going
You want to see the stonies, bro? Show
them if you want.
They're [ __ ] sexy, bro.
So, winning that £39 was like paid for that.
It's like I just It's like I got given
free stonies, you know, like brand new Stonies. Oops. Sorry,
my bollocks is almost showing.
That's the first one.
lush it was before. Now look at it. It's lush.
Then you got this one.
Absolute lush. Look. No. No [ __ ] No
stains. No nothing.
No stains. No [ __ ] all, bro.
Is that a little hole? Oh, that's a bit
fluff. See, look. Obviously the badge is
there. See what I'm saying? Look, this
is personally my favorite,
but I was going to give this one to
Virgin Boy cuz it's the oldest one.
Look at that. That is lush.
Remember I had like a stain here and
they got rid of it. Oh, that is sexy,
bro. I can't lie to you. I was actually
thinking of going out today and sending
it in that. Bro,
look at that. It's [ __ ] sexy, bro.
You reckon I should give it to Virgin Boy?
Now, most people prefer this one, but I
prefer that one. But I'm thinking of
giving Virgin Boy this one. You might
finally lose it. Might finally get laid.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah, that's that's my favorite. The
royal blue one, but they're they're all
nice. They're all nice. And I got a
green one as well, but I don't think the
green one would suit Virgin Boy.
I don't think the the the I don't think
it will suit Virgin Boy.
come out brand new. So, and that's why I
liked running the football. It pays for
the dry cleaner.
You know what I'm saying? It pays for
That one's the nicest. The bright one,
is it? Yeah. I don't know. There's just
something about that one. It's just
sexy, is it? Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, man. I was thinking of wearing
that today and sending it, bro.
Looks so nice. Crisp.
That was worth30 any day of the week.
They're [ __ ] £300 jumpers. One of
them was over £300,
so they were worth it in my book, bro.
30 [ __ ] quid.
Oh, I got Ralph Lauren as well.
They actually do last forever, don't they? them stonies jam ball
in in the bed.
No, no, no, no, no. I don't know what
what's with me in that, bro.
You like the other stony the the other
blue one? And the other blue one's nice, too.
They're all nice.
They're all [ __ ] nice, bro.
Yeah, that old one's the best. Well,
that's the one I was thinking of giving Virgin Boy
might get laid.
They're all nice though. They're all nice.
All of them are nice. I got a green one
as well, but I just put that one in the washing machine.
That's the one where I met USA Izzy. The
first day I bought the stone. That was
my first Stony.
That's the first one I bought
and the first time I went out in it and
approached in it. So yeah,
[ __ ] virgin. That's why he's still a
virgin. Cuz of what he wears. That's
what I'm saying. That's why he's still a
[ __ ] virgin, lad.
That's why he's still a [ __ ] That's
what I'm saying. That's why he's still a virgin.
He's [ __ ] never going to lose it.
He's never ever ever going to get laid.
This is what I'm saying. I don't care
about this disabled girl that you keep
showing. I don't give a [ __ ] I'm
telling you, you're a [ __ ] virgin.
Ignore the [ __ ] audience. Ignore
everyone. I'm telling you, you're a
[ __ ] virgin [ __ ]
Nothing but a virgin can simple.
So yeah, my Saturday was all right, mate.
Collected my stonies, collected my gums. £139.
I've had worse uh I've had worse Saturdays, mate.
Yeah, I've had worse ones.
So, I've had uh
I've had worse Saturdays, mate.
Yeah. And had a rush dinner cooked for
me as well. So, I mean,
so mate, yeah, I got some roast beef I'm
going to eat in a minute as well, mate.
So, I've had worse Saturdays.
He will never
I need to watch this GTA. boy
in the bad [ __ ] with all bed in it.
You call a full stony e mate. No, really.
Uh, stop watching the Virgin.
Stop watching the Virgin. That's all I
can say to you. I mean, the only reason
I'm addressing the Virgin cuz I got my
Stone Islands out the dry cleaners today
and they come out looking really nice.
so nice that I fancied going out
drinking today even though I'm not going
to do that because uh yeah just just not
going to do that but you know it made me uh tempted. Yeah.
No, I've had a roast dinner today.
No, I had a roast dinner and I got some
more roast dinner. I'm going to have
some more in a bit.
I got beef and pork roast dinner.
Yeah, I won £39 today on the football. Yay. £39.
I won 39 [ __ ] pounds. Wow.
[ __ ] 20 pound both teams to score
[ __ ] 39 [ __ ] pound. What the [ __ ]
I know. Peter belly should have had 400
pound on it. I know. I know. You don't
need to tell me. It's um [ __ ]
At least I picked the right teams. Look
You know, I've been doing them both
teams to score for years. You know,
I was watching a video of me coming back
from Manchester on Mother's Day when I
went to Manchester the second last time
and I done a 40 both teams to score
there as well. Returned 120.
Like I even done it back then, bro.
I'm going in a bit anyways. [Music]
I'm feeling sleepy, you know.
Oh yeah. Well, technically we did meet twice.
want some nice beef. SC.
So do I. I'm having some beef cooked for
me right now. Well, kind of warmed up,
huh? Yeah, ma'am.
You've never had a woman.
You've never been with a woman.
You're still a virgin.
No, women are [ __ ] One sec.
Uh that's uh that's um
that's Timmy, huh?
Yeah, that's Timmy, by the way.
No, it's Timmy.
Timmy, why are you showing £300?
300 [ __ ] pound.
That is insane. So,
I need some beef.
weighs more than my whole body. I'm not even fat. Self Oh,
that was lovely. Oh, man. M
last last lo last lo last lo last lo
last lo last lo last lo last lo last lo
nice can't be a joint beh Virgin boy
skin in the [ __ ] bed. [ __ ] We
[ __ ] dead in it.
There's nothing [ __ ] more catchier than that.
I'm going to wear that. I'm going to
make a video, make that some merch, and
start wearing it. Yeah. Anyways,
I'm going. See you.