I'm back. Yeah. What's up? really.
Nah, they've never even had sex.
They're still virgins, lad. Nah.
Hey, Frank. I stayed in today. Uh 140 on the football.
I done a 20. Both teams score no draw.
So yeah, I paid for the dry cleaning.
And my stonies are looking very fresh. I
was going to go out drinking, but I was
like, nah, can't be asked.
No, I can't be asked, lad. But
yeah, I know I won £40,
but it paid for the dry cleaning. The
dry cleaning was uh £30. So yeah,
don't know when I'll be out again. I
just can't be bothered with it anymore.
Frank, you know the I've got a boyfriend
[ __ ] I can't be asked with it anymore.
I can't be [ __ ] anymore with it, bro.
What do you think would happen if I went
out drinking today? Frank
You know, I like the weather like this.
I like the weather like this. Me.
Yeah. March and October is my favorite
month. March and October.
No, I like it. I like it like this.
The weather's nice like this.
No, I like it like this. Yeah. [ __ ] Yeah,
pretty much. Yeah, that's what they are.
Is it? I just can't be bothered.
I don't know when I'll drink again, bro.
I don't know, man.
I'm going on holiday soon, so I'd rather
just save money towards the holiday.
I just can't I just don't I just can't
justify it anymore, bro. Wasting the
time, wasting the money. I just can't
justify it anymore.
You get what I mean, don't you, Grezy?
Yeah. I just can't justify it, bro.
She don't want you.
She don't want to know you. Do you
remember Timmy celebrating being 90 pound down?
>> That's funny, bro.
Oh, I want to double both teams to score
today. Steven Howard, but I only had 20
pound on it. Returned £59.
Yeah, I know it's not the best, but
I don't know what I don't even know why
I done the bet to be honest.
But yeah, I know. I know. I know.
Yeah. So, if you had 80 pound on that,
that would have been
Yeah, about two something. Yeah, it is
what it is. It paid for the dry
cleaning, so the [ __ ]
Yeah, I weren't going to bother, but I
just The bookies was next to the shop,
so I just thought I'd put 20 pound on it.
I just thought Yeah, I just put 20 pound
on it, bro. [ __ ] it.
What you got in here? Nope. I had a
roast dinner today. I already told you
the stonies are looking so lush. It
would have been so It's so rude I didn't
go out in the stonies today. Approaching
is it Greavvesy?
How rude of me, huh?
How rude of me, Grezy, not going out
today in the stony approaching.
How [ __ ] rude of me. Yeah.
It's getting [ __ ] cold in that.
Why is Timmy showing £300?
[ __ ] hell, man. 300 [ __ ] pound.
That is hilarious, bro.
She don't want to know you.
I'm almost one month sober. Yay.
Well, I don't know why you're asking me
cuz I barely gamble, but um
yeah, I put £20 on two teams today. £159 back.
So, I paid for my dry cleaning.
I don't know why you asking me, bro. I
don't gamble that much.
Wrong channel. You need to watch Timmy.
He's the one that gamles.
So, I won 39. Yeah. Brilliant.
Yeah, that's a lot. E,
but bro, I don't play them machines like
what Timmy does.
Nah, not not for a month.
I got my Stone Island jumpers out the
dry cleaners today. They look fresh as
[ __ ] And obviously the football bet
paid for it. I was like, I should go out
today and send it.
But I never bothered. I can't be
bothered with it anymore.
Been almost a month now. Yeah.
The last time I went out
was that Sunday when I met that Finnish
woman the day um few days before my
mom's birthday. I was just bored so I
went out on a Sunday and um
yeah, I ain't approached for ages. cuz I
can't be bothered with it cuz it just
makes me feel worse. Any anytime I
approach it makes me feel worse.
That's why I try not to do it, Bob. I've
seen some people I wanted to approach
but I never done it because it would
just make me feel worse. That's why I'd
rather just not do it.
I'd rather just not do it.
No, I don't want to put more on because
I don't need money. I've got money. I
don't need to win any more money.
If I'm ever short money, I will. But yeah.
Yeah, Bob. So, like I don't if I
approach it will make me feel worse.
Basically, the more you try, the more
you lose hope.
So, but the more you try, the longer you
go without doing it, the more hope kind
of comes back. And then as soon as you
go out again, the same thing happens
again. Or as soon as you approach again,
the same thing happens again. So it's
just a non-stop cycle.
That's what I found as well. So
So I got no like numbers.
You know what annoys me is when you'll
message a number that you've got from
like two months ago and they ignore you
and then they'll change their picture.
Do you know what I mean, Bob? Like
they'll ignore your message, but then
they won't even block you. They'll just
change their picture. I just can't be
bothered with it anymore, you know?
So, I don't know.
It is bad.
What does one do? Eh,
they give their number and then they
ignore and then they change their
picture is madness, bro.
Sick of it.
It's expensive as well.
I have not had sex.
Last time I [ __ ] an escort was an
escort. Yeah. It's just like the whole
the whole thing is exhausting. The whole
dating game is exhausting. It's like a
job in itself. But yeah, you get these
people on Reddit that say, "Oh, thank
God for Thank God for dating apps and
dating apps don't even work." I don't
know why people keep going on about
dating apps when they don't even work.
Oh yeah, thank [ __ ] for dating apps.
Dating apps. Yeah, dating apps. And then
dating apps don't even [ __ ] work.
I don't get it.
I don't know, bro.
Yeah, I ain't had sex for few months.
But people on Reddit say it works, Bob.
Yeah. Okay. One second. I'll give you the link.
[ __ ] knows, bro. [ __ ] knows.
What do you think would happen if I went
out tonight approach him?
What do you think would have happened,
Bob, if I went out approach him today?
You reckon I would have found someone? Yeah.
So many simps.
You never know.
Well, I bet they said that four years
ago, though, didn't they?
I bet they they told me I never do four
years ago and here I am.
Still in the same situation. I mean,
just think about it. Four years ago, right?
Four or five years ago, they probably
told you that, you know, you're going to meet someone
and uh but you can't even hold a day a
week. I've already took two weeks off of
YouTube. You can't even even take a day
off of YouTube.
I mean, Rob Bills, I mean, it's been
going on for four years, so
I guess I I know. I think I know.
I I know. People might not know, but I
know because you've you've been doing
this for years. So,
um it's not just not going to happen the
next time you go out. But we think that
I mean, the longer I go out, I'll
probably think it again. I'll probably
think, "Oh yeah, you never know. You go
out again." Yeah, I probably think it as
well to be honest. Um but
um but when you go out again, the same
thing will happen. So at at the end of
the day, yeah,
I probably think it as well to be fair. But
give it another two weeks, I'll start
having hope again because I haven't done
it for so long. And then as soon as I go
out again, same thing happens again.
It's a cycle. That's what I'm saying.
I'll try again. I'll let you in.
Yeah. It doesn't matter, bro. You can be
well spoken. You can have money
like I had. Dude, it doesn't make a
difference, bro. You're still not going
to meet anyone. You can be decent
looking, well spoken. You're still not
going to find someone.
Doesn't matter what the [ __ ] you are, bro.
Yeah. I don't know. It's [ __ ] up. >> Hello.
>> Why are you showing £300?
>> Hello PJ. My name's Tony. I'm from
Dating UK. We had a concerned call that
you are a virgin and you can't get laid. We are
>> the only the only the only virgin is you and legs.
>> Yes. Anyway, would you like would you
like would you like
>> Bye-bye. Bye-bye. Yeah.
Yeah. He's he needs to grow up though. I
had to kick him. So yeah, that's where
we're at anyways with these uh with the
women and [ __ ] It will never change.
I'm just thinking of never trying again
and just like waiting for my holiday and just going.
That's what I just might start doing
with my money now. Just going on holidays.
That's what I might start doing with my
money, I think.
I don't know.
Yeah, that's our brain telling us that
you never know, you know. You never know. But
what's the chances? You know, what are
the chances like? Nope. November. So, yeah.
I don't know, bro. Who knows?
Yeah, another country would work. No, if
I was in a Listen, bro. If I was in
America right now or I was in Canada or
any westernized, even if it was a West,
I'd be out now. I would be out doing it
now just because why the [ __ ] not? If I
was in any other country now, I'd be out
now, bro. I'd go out every week.
Um, there's this woman from Finland I
speak to, Bob, and she replies and stuff
and she says she'll meet me if I come over
and stuff. So, obviously that's an
option. That's the last time I went out
on that Sunday. Yeah, that's the last
time I went out on that Sunday. It was
[ __ ] expensive, bro.
No weekend. So,
but yeah, if I was in another country, I
would I would try, bro. I would try in
another country, but
it's just I'm just fed up with it here, you know?
And there's so many simps on Reddit as
well, Bob. Like they literally that's oh
what's wrong these women self-reflecting
you're skin this onto me again to me
that's not going to get you anywhere in
life self projector um this person was
saying about how like oh them women let
you down gently and I know they done any
everything but let me down gently like
they literally have been [ __ ] on
purpose. See the thing is um Bob is it's
not about people saying that they got
boyfriends. It's not about any of that
[ __ ] It's about what they actually do
when they give you their number. Like
the games, the leading on the [ __ ]
I ain't got time for it anymore, bro. I
don't want to deal with it anymore, you
know? It's not It's not even that. It's
the whole when you get the numbers and
the mind games. And bear in mind, I'm
[ __ ] 20 [ __ ] eight, you know, like
next month I ain't got [ __ ] time to
be dealing with that [ __ ] anymore, you know? So
you know how is it? Who knows?
All you do is all you do is is talk
about money to me because your skin
showing £300. You really are skin
showing 300 pound.
Talking about yourself again. No money,
no personality. Talking about yourself.
What have I told you about talking about yourself again?
It's not going to get you anywhere in
life talking about yourself. You don't
know how much money I have. You don't
know anything about me. So, you must be
talking about yourself because you don't
know anything about me. Literally, you
don't know what money I have. That's
what makes me laugh with these people is
that they keep bringing up money cuz
they ain't got none themselves. Trying
to talk about what other people that
they don't know have. It's laughable.
That's why I don't even block the comments
cuz everything they do is they they talk about themselves.
It's common on here to me. You know,
they they talk about money cuz they
ain't got no money. That's why it comes
up, you know, in their mind because they
ain't got none. S on YouTube all their
skin talking about other people's
financial circumstances, but they don't
know what anyone has. And that's what
makes me laugh. That's the thing that
makes me laugh the most is they don't know anything. You know,
I've got more money than you will ever
have, but you wouldn't even believe it.
And then when you get show money and
then when you when you get show money
you run away as well. So I mean what
what's the whole point of this? You know
you've also seen me so show money. If
I'm boring then [ __ ] off you skin
bastard. Yeah I'm boring. So [ __ ] off.
Stop watching me there. No one's forcing
you to be here. You're the one coming on
here calling yourself skin cuz you're
not talking about me cuz I know how much
money I've got and you know you are not
you are surely not talking about me. I
know that for a fact you're not talking
about me. So why don't you get yourself
projecting ass off of my channel?
You and [ __ ] Okay, let's look at
Timmy. Yeah, he's playing these FOB TE's
at 42 years of age and he's showing £300 on YouTube,
bro. Come on. It's so obvious Timmy's
talking about himself. It's so obvious
Timmy's talking about himself. You see
how many gambling videos he put up
yesterday? He's still playing them
[ __ ] Bob T's at [ __ ] 42 years of age showing£300. [ __ ] hell.
But yeah, City said like, you know, if
you find me all of these things, you
need to come off of YouTube and stop
watching me. Stop stop calling yourself
skint on my channel. It's not nice
talking about yourself like that. You
know, this is for people to come and
join and talk, not for you to talk about
yourself because all you're doing is
talking about yourself and it's quite
nasty to see, you know, no money, no
personality, you're talking about
yourself and it's not nice to talk about
yourself like that. You know,
you know the thing is Timmy, right? You
know all of this [ __ ] you done the gambling.
You do realize that like
you do realize that you should have
grown out of this by now to me. You're
still doing this [ __ ] gambling [ __ ]
When are you going to get your
priorities straight? You know, because
people people have done it, you know, in
the past. I've done it. I gamble. I've
gambled more than you'll ever gamble.
I've gambled more money to me than you
will ever gamble. And I've drunk more
than you. That's probably why I'm so
bored of it. But you know, there's
actually a time where people grow up and
stuff. You know that. But you don't ever
seem like you're ever going to grow up. So,
and trust me, Timmy, I have gambled more
than you. I've lost more than you and
I've won more than you. Yes, I have. You
might be older than me, but bro, bro,
you was not getting [ __ ] three and a
half grand a month for not working for
[ __ ] 3 years.
You know, I've got a lot more life
experience than you. And then you're
still gambling in that way. So it makes
sense why you call other people skin cuz
you're talking about yourself. Obvious.
Obviously, but you know. So yeah. So yeah,
why do these people project their
skintess every day on to me?
Madness. Why they self-reflect every day? Crazy.
It's crazy, isn't it? Strong self-reflectant.
>> All right.
yourself reflecting your skinlessness.
>> PPJ, I can show you 200 coins. I've show
Can you show me 500 quid? Yes or no? A simple question.
>> I've shown you over£500.
>> No, no, it's not about the path. Not
>> You're bad. I'm not having the same
conversation over and over again. There
you go. You're banned. Same
conversation, same argument. Uh, yes, I
can. And I have. I've shown you £1,300
and you ran away. Bye-bye.
See, nothing um nothing hard about that.
Do you know what it is with Timmy? He's
skint. That's why he's coming on YouTube
calling other people skint again is cuz
he is skint. It's so [ __ ] obvious,
bro. It's so obvious. Can I show £500?
Of course I can show£500, but I'm not
going to show you nothing and you're not coming in.
Yeah, I'm kicking because he's he's
repeating himself. It's the same argument.
Yeah, I'm kicking because just like I
just kick L because they're not going to
self-reflect their lives on my channel.
They're not self-p projecting their life
on my channel. So, yeah, I did kick him.
Can I show £500?
You asked, "Can I show £500?" Oh,
[ __ ] hell, bro.
You got shown £1,300 last time in the
pub and you ran away, which is the only
reason I done it is cuz I was drunk. I'm
not showing you nothing. So yeah,
I ain't showing you [ __ ] all. Yeah.
So yeah. Anyways, Timmy, why are you
still gambling like that? Anyways,
that's why I don't go on these channels,
bro. Cuz it's just self-reflecting central.
That's what it is. It's self projecting
like LJ calls people skin cuz he's skint
same as Timmy.
Oh, let's take out somebody half my age
that's better looking than me. Oh, wow.
You know, that's what they do. They do
this stuff because you're younger,
better looking, more money. That's why
they go for you. That's why I've got so
many of these middle-aged men obsessed
with me, Frank,
is cuz they they gravitate towards me
because I'm everything they wish they were.
Even though my life's not perfect. I'm
not saying my life's perfect, but to
them, my life is perfect. They're sat at
home, ugly looks, [ __ ] all old. None
of them got any money. That's why they
all gravitate towards Peter Belly. Why
do you think they all gravitate towards Peterbelly, bro?
and no one else.
Do you not understand?
They don't do it to anyone else. They do
it to me.
So, just want to tell you that. Anyways, so yeah. Yeah.
I don't play roulette. I think I play
roulette like once every three months.
If that I don't even [ __ ] play this
[ __ ] anymore, bro. Oh [ __ ] Oh yeah.
Why is Timmy showing 300 pounder?
Nah, mate. I can't afford it. I'm skin.
It's sad. It is sad what these people do
like on here. Do you not think it's sad
what they do? A bunch of middle-aged men
that have got fuckle to their name. [ __ ]
all in their life coming on here trying
to make other people feel like them.
It's crazy, isn't it? You know,
all cuz they're fat virgins that's got
nothing in their life. So they come on
here cuz they're sad with their lives.
is [ __ ] up. >> Yeah.
boy skin and red
[ __ ] money in it. All right, Stephen
Howard, I'm bringing out some merch. Yeah,
like t-shirts and hoodies and stuff and
there's going to be like virgin boy
in a bed sit with no bed and no money in
it. I'm going to have like a little like
I'm going to make some merch and give it away.
And there one's going to and the top's
going to say when you're going to lose it.
When you're going to lose it.
Just some of my little sayings that I
made for Virgin Boy cuz he's a big
virgin. He's a big virgin.
He's a big big big virgin. [ __ ]
He is a [ __ ] big virgin.
Anyways, Timmy, do you wanna
Do you want to join, Timmy? Do you want to join?
Do you want to join Timmy?
Wonder where Monty's gone.
Yeah, I'm not as rich as you. You keep
telling yourself that, Timmy. The only
one that's bringing up money is you. cuz
you ain't got none.
You're the only one talking about money.
No one's talking about money. You're
talking about money because you ain't
got no money. That's why you're bringing
it up. Cuz you're skin.
Your skin, Timmy. Just like nonslegs.
Just like [ __ ] LJ. That's why you
bring up money. Cuz you ain't got no
money. Cuz you're skin. It's obvious.
It's [ __ ] obvious.
What other community brings up money,
bro? What other community brings up
money? None. Only this community, cuz
they ain't got no money.
They ain't got none. Yeah. That's it.