Judging boy,
why would you do that? How comes it
doesn't let me It doesn't let me exit
the home screen.
Nah, my thing's [ __ ] bro.
It doesn't let me um
change it. It's [ __ ] weird.
One sec. I don't know why it's done
that. It's not letting me exit the home screen. [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
Why is it?
It doesn't let me exit the [ __ ] thing.
That's so weird. [Music]
There were no [ __ ] bed in it,
bro. I've got some catchy sayings, bro.
You like them?
Of course you do.
Stop letting me exit the [ __ ]
thing. I don't know why.
Don't want to me.
Come on. Project your skis onto Peter
Belly like you always do
cuz you got no life.
You joining me
wants me to show him money again. It's
not happening, matey.
I ain't showing you [ __ ] all. Yeah.
Come on to it.
I'm not showing him anything anyways.
I've shown these people money time and
time again and they always run away. I'm
not showing him [ __ ] all anyways, lad.
Yeah, I know. I'm never showing money
ever again, bro.
Yep. That's why I'm never ever like
showing anything ever again, lad.
Exactly, bro. Exact. I'm not showing
nothing, bro. I'm not showing you £500.
What the [ __ ] Wants me to show him
£500. I'm not showing you nothing.
I am not showing you [ __ ] all.
You can [ __ ] right off. [ __ ] right off. I'm in. Yeah.
The Reddit mods ban people to feel
powerful in it, uh, Wadley.
They have to have power. They have to be in control.
They literally have to be in control.
You know what I mean? Yep.
But apparently I'm skint and I'm a
virgin. You learn something new every
day, don't you?
What do you mean not in the real world?
of course I have. I've shown money. I've shown women.
That Ricky Milling account makes me
laugh. He's such a little batty man. I
said I said about a million times. Yeah.
If you got anything to say, say it to my
face. Stop typing behind the keyboard.
Stop being a keyboard warrior.
Come on. We [ __ ] outgrew that [ __ ]
you know, years ago.
Well, I'm sick of them. I'm sick of
them. No, they literally ban anyone that
disagrees with them. Them mods literally
ban anybody that disagrees with them.
They ban anybody that disagrees with them.
anyone, not even just me. They literally
do. They need they need that control. If
they ain't got that power, they go mad
cuz they got no power in real life cuz
they're [ __ ] moms.
[ __ ] sat in their mama's [ __ ]
basement still [ __ ] virgins. Probably
eating popcorn every [ __ ] day. Yeah,
there's a lot of simps
on that Reddit though. A lot of simps.
A lot of simps. Yeah,
they need that power. Else they'll go
mad without that power, bro.
Have you seen that Ricky Millington account?
He used to come on here and I said,
"Listen, you little [ __ ] [ __ ] Don't
[ __ ] come on here and lick my ass and
then [ __ ] start slagging me behind my back."
Do you know what I'm saying? And then he
stopped um then he stopped coming on.
Yeah. Then he stopped coming on here cuz
I said, "Don't come on my chat trying to
lick my ass, you batty man. I've seen
what you've been writing, you little
[ __ ] You sad little bastard.
And he just stopped. Now he just talks
[ __ ] behind my back now. So yeah,
he's the definition of a s as well. He's another s.
Probably never seen a probably never
seen a woman naked, but talks about me. Hilarious, it
don't tell you, I show you.
I don't tell you, I show you. That's the difference.
I'm going to make some popcorn in a minute. Yeah.
I can't believe this woman says that she
can't find someone, but she goes on
three dates a month. You go on three
I ain't been on a date for like 5 months.
So, you get three dates a month and you
can't find anyone. What's wrong with all
of these guys? There can't be something
wrong with all of these guys.
That just goes to show that the problem
is them because it takes them so long to
find someone yet they've been on these
dates and they can't all not be
compatible. You know, one or two or but
you know what I'm saying? It's just like
the [ __ ] you going three dates a month?
That is insane, bro.
I don't go three [ __ ] [ __ ] dates a month.
Oh, [ __ ] I think I've only had three dates this whole year.
Three maybe. Is it three?
Well, four, but that weren't really a day,
I think. Wait,
I think it has been three. Yeah.
Or am I missing one? No, it's been three. Yeah.
So, that just goes to show you that like
what it's like here in it.
It's [ __ ] in it.
I can't believe I've not been out for
almost a month. [ __ ] hell, bro.
I'm a crazy [ __ ] ain't it?
What is it with Timmy showing £300? [ __ ] hell.
I've said a million times I'm never
showing money ever again. So I don't
know why he's asking me to show £500.
I'm not showing you [ __ ] all. You can
say I've got no money. That's on you,
bro. I know what I have. I know where
I'm going in November. That's all that
matters, you know. So
you want me to show you money so you can
run off again like you always do? Yeah. Get [ __ ]
We need you on this community, mate.
It's already [ __ ] dying. I don't want
you running away again.
You know what I'm saying? Madness. madness.
This woman was like, "Oh, yeah. I wasn't
already I already weren't interested in
the guy and shit." So I said, "Why did
you go on a date with that guy if you weren't interested?
Wasting people's time again.
Madness. [ __ ] madness.
It is mad. [ __ ] me. [Music] Legend boy
skin in a bed is so [ __ ]
>> I love that, bro. I can't stop saying
that, man. It's stuck in my head.
It's stuck in my head, bro.
skin in the bed she actually is
in the bed. [Music]
bro. Told you it's coming. Coming, bro.
The match is coming, bro.
She didn't come out once. No one. [Music] Oh [ __ ] Oh no.
>> Oh [ __ ] I said I just grow up there.
I need to [ __ ] grow up.
Where's that [ __ ] popcorn?
Did you hear the popcorn? Popcorn.
Oh, it hurts. Oh no.
Should have been 130. I think it's burnt.
Where am I? Okay.
I'm trying to make this bastard popcorn.
>> Uh, it says 2 minutes. It's not 2
minutes cuz I just put it on for 2
minutes. One minute for extended paper. [Music] [ __ ] hell.
Get in the box. That's it. [Music]
Back there is oak.
Oh, hopefully it's not burnt. Oh, lovely.
I just made myself some popcorn.
How are you going to lose it then? Stephan, listen.
We're going to make an alcohol.
to make that version come lose.
You with me, Grievy?
We're going to
make that virgin.
Who's with me?
Who's with me, man?
We're making them [ __ ] lose it,
aren't we, mate?
Yeah. Who's with me?
Who's [ __ ] with me, mate?
Some of you were virgin. You got virgin boy.
I might do a video to Virgin Boy.
What different groups? I need to do a
video to Virgin Boy.
Yeah, I need to do a video to the virgin.
>> All right, PJ, you on Tinder?
>> Yeah. All right, PJ. Yeah, I'm a virgin.
Are you on Tinder?
>> Um, no. I've got your mom.
>> No, no, no. My mom doesn't do um
secondhand [ __ ] um Pakistani kids,
mate, I'm afraid.
>> And you're a Pakistani PJ. So you don't
she never do you?
>> I know you're Pakistani.
>> So when are you going to stop being scared?
>> Yeah, you you've got a beard what looks
like Bin Laden.
>> That's how much of a Pakistani you are.
>> Tell me. Um so when are you um when you
going to lose your duty?
>> I've already lost a bit, mate. When are
you going to cook us a cubby PJ?
Pakistanis normally can cook good covers.
>> Well, I'm atheist. But
>> no, you're not atheist. You're a
Pakistani, PJ. You
>> I was tell I was eating I was eating
pork today. How can I be a Pakistani?
>> Pakistanis do eat pork. They're full of
[ __ ] They're the biggest hypocrites on the planet.
>> No, I've lived with Pakistanis.
>> Yes, they do eat pork, PJ. They make out
they don't. They don't. Do you know how
corrupted they're [ __ ] Islamist?
>> Yeah, but I've lived with
they don't stick to their own religion
properly. me. I've lived with Pakistanis. >> Pardon?
>> I've lived with Pakistanis. I had Pakistani.
>> You are a Pakistani PJ. And your mom is
you. You know, there's nothing wrong
with that. You're still British.
>> It's just it's just PJ. Instead of
investing your time moaning about the
trolls, why don't you cook a good curry pack?
>> When are you going to stop being so
skinn? Um, how can I be skinn PJ when
you can't show me 500 quid and I can
show you 500 quid now and bank?
>> I can but I'm not going to.
>> Because you haven't got any money.
>> Okay. I haven't got it. Okay. Do you
remember last time? Okay. What about
last time you'reimmy I've owed you every
money. You got shown money all day.
>> You got shown money and you ran away
doing it. You're a virgin.
>> You are trolls on here. You are talking
about yourself again. Pakistani you
about yourself again. You got so money
in March and you ran away cuz you never had it. >> PJ grand in
>> No, you did not show three grand. No,
you [ __ ] did not. Everybody saw you
run away in the park. Show money now.
>> Everybody saw you run away and I'm
owning the crap out of you. You don't have
£300. [ __ ] showing£300.
any money cuz you got no
money talking about yourself. I won't
take you backeping
talking about yourself.
>> I mean I mean PJ nobody on YouTube has
ever had to have a sub off their barber.
>> Timmy, do you not think it's funny how Iimmy
But ever asked for a sub for a haircut.
>> Timmy, do you not do you not think it's
funny how I've been seen with more money
and women than anyone?
>> PJ, you isn't that the funny thing?
That's the funniest thing, isn't it? In your head.
>> It's in my head. Okay.
>> Because you've been shown the woman.
>> Self projector.
>> You're the biggest self projector I've
ever come across. Projecting means PJ.
>> Yeah. You what you're doing? Because
Yeah. What you're doing.
>> I got to say, so what? So what? So how
am I self projecting? What does it mean,
PJ? So you mute your mic cuz you don't
know what it means. Now you're going to
look at a dictionary.
>> [ __ ] clown.
>> Selfjectoring is what? Self-jecting is
what you do. self.
>> Anyway, you're going to make us a curry,
PJ, cuz I want to know how to make a
good curry and only Pakistan.
>> You never seen you with women. We've
never seen you with money.
>> PJ, I've just shown you 300 co show you
200 pound coins like the
500. You haven't got virgin and that is
why you're moaning on YouTube. [ __ ] me.
>> Let's get Let's get to the point, PJ.
The reason why you can't get a woman is
because you look like 300. Nobody like [ __ ] ter
you haven't got £300. Okay, I don't have
300 just like when I showed you money
last time and you ran away money cuz you haven't got
>> every time I've shown you money, you ran
away. That's why I don't waste my time.
>> I'm explaining I'm explaining to you I'm
going to explain it to you again cuz you
keep talking over me. I'm not showing
you money because every single time I
show you money, you don't have it and
you run away. Which is why I don't show you money
because you run away every single time
you get show money. That's why I don't
waste my time anymore. You're like the
last time in a pub cuz you're self
projecting. You're talking about
yourself. Thank you.
You can come back in now. [ __ ] sake.
I've had more women than these people,
more money than these people, and they
still talk [ __ ] It's [ __ ] bro.
Right. We all know Timmy, right? He's
still playing them [ __ ] machines in
these [ __ ] 40s.
Self projecting, bro. It's all self
projecting on here.
It's all [ __ ]
All of it is self-reflecting. That's why.
It's so funny. He's asking people to
show him money, but every single time
people show him money, he runs away.
I really don't understand it.
Um, yes, I have been in a relationship
and I have shown more women on here.
This is why I don't bother with these
people no more, bro. This is why I don't
bother with these people on here anymore, bro.
It's [ __ ] mad [ __ ] this. I have
been in a relationship. And again, using
excuses again. This is what I mean with
these [ __ ] [ __ ] people now. They're
You know what? I'm not even going to let
this bash the cup anymore, bro.
You can go self-reflect on another channel.
Oh, another email. Just self-reflecting
every time. These people got nothing
better to do than to talk about
themselves every day. Skin as them,
lonely as them. Oh my [ __ ] god.
Everything is themselves.
But they're so mongos. They don't even
realize it. They're [ __ ] Mongs, bro. Yeah.
Never been in a relationship, bro.
You've never even been laid. Oh [ __ ]
[ __ ] You've never even seen a woman naked, bro.
You got your own [ __ ] life self
injecting, bro. Nonstop.
Yeah, I'm ignoring you now. Anyways, to me.
Yeah, I'm ignoring you now. Anyways, you
can self-reflect your skintess on another channel. Okay, Timmy.
So, you really want me to show you £500? Yeah.
So, you really really want me to show you £500?
Is that what you want? Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ]
Okay. I 500. One second.
Oh [ __ ] I didn't even message them. Timmy SC.
Why you worry about money?
This woman saying, "I've never been in a
relationship. I've never even been
kissed." I do get a lot of matches on apps.
Is this [ __ ] for real?
What I'm reading?
There's a lot of women that claim they
they're virgins and stuff.
What the [ __ ]
That doesn't make sense.
It is mad.
So, this is how you know it's [ __ ]
because they'd rather be virgins than
give anyone it. Look, this is like the
fourth person I've come across that says
that they're a virgin. They never kissed anyone.
That's cuz you're too picky.
See, that's what I'm saying with these
women. They'd rather go with no one than
anyone less than perfect.
You see what I mean? It's [ __ ]
It's actually actually [ __ ] madness, bro.
That is [ __ ] Really [ __ ] up.
I don't understand how these women can be virgins.
[ __ ] me, bro.
Yeah, of course I own him. I always own him, bro.
Cuz it's just self-p projection with him.
You understand, bro? It's always
self-projecting with him.
Oh, for [ __ ] sake. I hate this [ __ ]
Reddit thing, bro. [ __ ] off. Virgin boy. [Music]
Oh my god, bro. Virgin
skin stuck in a bed [ __ ] with a money in it.
What's it purpose?
Right. I'll be back.