You
know, quite chilly today, isn't it? It's
[ __ ] cold yesterday some reason.
Anyways, I'm off of YouTube again after today,
but I'm off again. Just very [Music]
cold. Very cold, man. Yeah. [ __ ]
March. Last last say that last April was cold. So
yeah, so March could easily be cold. Yeah,
but whatever. Let me slowly start off.
tried bagging my whole [ __ ] IP. One
sec. My whole [ __ ]
IP don't work though.
I know, man. Proper obsessed. It's
dangerous. It's dangerous, bro. I'm I'm
off of YouTube after today, bro. For a
little bit again. I was off for a week.
Proper proper obsessed. Weirdo behavior.
And they do it even when you They do it
even when you don't reply to them.
They do it even if you're not on YouTube
and you don't reply to them. You listen.
Like what I was saying to you, bro, is
that with Timmy, yeah, they used to do
it to Timmy because Timmy used to react
in a funny way in it. So they used to
just come on his live stream and [ __ ]
with him. But with these people, even if
you don't react to them, even if you got
banned from social media, they would
still do it. [ __ ] jealousy is a
disease, bro. It's a very, very serious
disease. Kills a lot of people, bro.
I don't know how somebody can be so
jealous of somebody that they barely
know. It's [ __ ] mad. Absolute
madness. Making up stories that the
virgin knows where I am. You don't know
where I am. And you will never know
where I am. And you would never get
information of where I am. And even if
you did know where I am, you're still
not going to come on my door. So why
would you even want to find out where
someone lives? It's weirdo behavior,
bro. That's why I don't come on here
much anymore, bro.
That's why I don't really come on here
much to be more to be
fair cuz of the the the stalking the
weirdos. I've never had so many people
obsessed with me, bro. No one else has
had it. No one else has had it. Not one
person else has had it. Not even Timmy,
bro. And Timmy's been on here since 2012
from what I hear.
So yeah, it's a bad lad. One second.
seconds as well.
Strange cuz he wish it was him [ __ ]
them and not me or him kissing them and
me. Sad, bro. It's just sad. I don't
even know how people can laugh at
it. Weirdo behavior, bro. Proper weirdo behavior.
I put weirdo behavior there. Weirdo
behavior. And he'll sit there in his
virgin kitchen with his virgin bed sit
going on about the same [ __ ] stories
over and over and over and over and over again. You
know, so weird. [ __ ] hell. It's
weird, man. You never meet somebody with
autism. That's all I'm
saying. You never meet someone with autism,
bro. I mean, it's not unheard of people
to do this, bro, but they don't do it
over and over and over and over again.
These people have got some mad interest
in me, bro. And it creeps me the [ __ ]
out. That's why I come off of it for a
little bit. Like Jamie Thompson, Red
Star, Sean, they're all obsessed with
me. I don't know what what I've got that
they don't. Maybe more money, better
looking than them. I don't know what it
is, but it's something, bro. It's so
strange. It gives me the ick. Gives me
the ick, bro. It makes my skin crawl. [ __ ]
weirdos every [ __ ] day, bro. You
could be gone for 10
years. Yeah, bro. He's suffering
anyways. I'm living in his head rentree.
Listen, bro. I'm living in his head
rentree. Every day he can't stop posting
about me. I'm already He's already
suffering cuz I'm living in his head. I
couldn't imagine somebody living in my
head every day where I have to
[ __ ] where I have to um where I have
to keep posting. The [ __ ] is already
suffering. [ __ ] me, bro. I made the [ __ ]
run to the police about me three times.
I've made the [ __ ] keep posting stuff
every day. He's losing. He been losing.
He's been suffering, bro. [ __ ] hell. That's nothing
new. And I said to Chase yesterday,
"Have you got a
printer? Have you got a printer?" Cuz
Chase is done with him. You remember
Chase? Chase was originally my friend
from years ago. And then Sean met him
because again, he's an autistic weirdo
that can't make his own friends. I said,
"Bro, do you have a
poster?" Anyone's got a poster, bro?
post them, send them to me, and I
[ __ ] print them and send them to me,
lad. Bro, I would I would literally hand
post them. I'll put them all over the
train station. I'll put them all over
the village. I'll put them all over
every single pub that he has been to in
the past. So, he won't be drinking there
no more. And I'll put and I'll post them
in places that I haven't shown where
I've posted them as well. So, yeah, it
be it'll be ace, bro. you
know, and that's it, bro.
Yeah, some madness, bro. [ __ ]
hell. But you do realize that even
that, how can you get them to
me? You'll have to put them in a You'll
have to put them in a place in London
and show me where they are.
No, I don't really gamble anymore. Just
been approaching women nonstop. Got some
numbers, replies and all that [ __ ] But
I'm I'm chilling out this week, man. I
need to go watch that film in the
cinema. I ain't got round to watching
yet. So, have a little twoe detox cuz I
went on it straight, bro. [ __ ] madness. So,
yeah. Yeah, you just print them out and
show me where you've put him, bro.
That's it, man. [ __ ]
I on a 90 pound football bet
yesterday. I want to watch the Daddy Dia
film, but I'm not in a rush to watch it.
But at the same time, I want to watch it
to get out of the way. But I'm really
looking forward to this horror film
coming out on the 28th. We've got
basically two weeks, and it's on my
calendar, man. It's on my calendar. I'm
straight watching it, bro. Um
um it was a double both teams to score
atington versus Newport and Colchester
versus Portbal and Newport got their ass whooped
5-nil. Yeah, I got my passport two days
ago. So there's been content to be
having, bro. There's content to be having.
Yeah, the bet was um Liverpool let me
down. They just needed to score [ __ ] 350 350
quid. [ __ ] me, bro. I can't believe no.
Yeah, gambling [ __ ] Anyways,
um see, bro, I just need to I'm going to
do my last few attempts of trying in
this country and then I'm out of there,
bro. But it's been good with them women
recently anyways, man. I've just been
sending it Thursday, Saturday, the week
after that. It's been good, man. Son,
I'm all right, bro. We'll go out next
week. Not this week, though. We need to
chill it this
week. Had a nice curry
yesterday. Curry. Oh, it was sucking it,
bro. It was [ __ ] ace,
man. I don't need to save up money,
mate. Not me. I've got
money. Uh, only three countries out of the UK.
Yeah, but I was watching, funny enough,
you used to say that because I was
watching some [ __ ] traveling videos
yesterday. I was like, "Bro, I need to
travel, man. Whilst I'm young, I need to
literally travel before I get old,
bro. I wanted to live that life, bro.
I'm watching it." Yeah. And I'm
thinking, bro, I'm [ __ ] I wish that
was me. And it can be me as well, bro.
I've got no
excuses. But I was talking to somebody
in the pub like two weeks ago and he
reckons that the first place you should
go to is Thailand just to go there. But
anywhere really. But
yeah, I need to a few things. I need to
go to gym and then leave, bro, and [ __ ] Like, yeah. Nope.
27. But still, man, I said I
don't I don't need to save up, mate.
I've got savings. I've got savings. Not
me. I've got savings,
man. Why is it so cold yesterday?
Bro, that's as far as that
goes. Doesn't matter how much I've got.
I'm not saying my business on
here. I don't tell my business, bro,
like that. I don't mind talking about
the gambling and whatever, but I don't
tell my business. Doesn't matter how
much I've got. Well, I've got nothing
apparently can um to these people that
call people [ __ ] skin every [ __ ]
day, you know? Apparently, I've got
[ __ ] nothing apparently.
Nah, not me, mate. Not for
Thailand. You can get a flight for for
£500 to about 900. Nah,
mate. But apparently I'm skimp, bro.
So, you got a bet for me? I need to
really stay away from the gaming, bro.
It's been a [ __ ] month. Yeah, he will
say that to try and get my attention. He
doesn't know anything about me. He
doesn't know where I live. I hate Man
United. He doesn't know anything. So, he
will make up things to try to get my
attention. You don't understand what
these people do. It's like when somebody
comes off of YouTube, right, for let's
say four days, they'll be like, "Oh, he
got nicked. He got nicked." They do it
so you go back on arguing with them.
It's a low IQ troll attempt. It's been
going for It's been going on for years
now. This virgin doesn't know anything.
Yeah. How can he call a property that's
not even mine and then tell them where I
live? It doesn't even sound believable.
He doesn't know where I am. He will
never know where I am ever. And the only
thing he knew, the only reason he knew
about that girl was because I said it
about eight months ago. Try again, virgin. You're obsessed.
Simple. Um, probably two weeks to be
fair. I'll probably stay there two
weeks, man. I think two weeks is
solid. No, he is saying that he knows
where I live, but he doesn't know where
live. He's he he's trying to say that I
live in 96 Albert Square. No, I don't.
That house got took a couple of months
ago. A B the only reason you knew about
the girl is cuz I said it eight months ago.
So, and he's saying that he's calling up
that he's just pretending to be me.
[ __ ] hell. I swear to God, bro. Yeah.
Out of all of the times, about maybe
three times, maybe I've been in love, I
have never been even 1% obsessed with
somebody the way that virgin is obsessed
with me. I swear to God, bro, the amount
of times I've been in love, the amount
of times I've been fluctuating on
someone, I have never been obsessed the
way that virgin is on me. I swear to
God, bro. I tell you that for no
pennies, lads. No, he wasn't. He
doesn't. He barely knows me, bro. He met
me when I was a child and I didn't want
nothing to do with him because he's just
a weirdo just like Chase. Yeah, I was I
met Chase. I've not met him in real life
years and years and years and years ago.
And then Sean met him once. I think he
met him twice. And Chase don't want
nothing to do with him now. Even Chase
don't like him. I speak to Chase every
[ __ ] day. You met me when I was a
[ __ ] child. You You don't know me, Virgin
boy. How can you be in love? Um, I'm not
going to answer that question. Nice try,
though. Um, yeah, that's it. Uh, well, I
guess I should answer it. Uh, have you
ever heard of love at first
sight? Yeah. You don't need a girlfriend
to be in love. Go get some Go get some
life experience. Go get some life
experience. But anyways, this guy
doesn't even [ __ ] know me, bro. He
hasn't seen me since I was [ __ ] 18
years of [ __ ] age. That's a [ __ ]
child. You're a [ __ ] child when
you're [ __ ] 18, bro. This virgin
doesn't even know me. And he makes up
stories. He's a [ __ ] weirdo. He needs
to go get off of YouTube and go get laid
and lose his virginity. Not [ __ ]
making up [ __ ] stories about [ __ ]
people. You know what I'm saying? It's weird.
Well, it [ __ ] of course it basically
is. It basically is. Love at first
sight. Nah. Nah. Well, either way, you
haven't seen me for like almost 11 years
and you're still obsessed. That's like
you, right? Meeting
somebody 10 years ago and still being
obsessed, bro. Well, 11 years ago. Let's
just say 11 years ago, right? And still being
obsessed. No, bro. That's [ __ ] weird.
It doesn't even really matter the age to
be honest. That is weirdo behavior. Does
he not understand?
Right. Yeah. When somebody does not want
to know you anymore, they don't want to
know you. But he doesn't seem to grasp
that with his autism. [ __ ] weird,
bro. [ __ ] weird. Weird freak, man. You
know, it is. It's weird. It's obsessive
because he's never had any real friends.
Because he can't go out and make friends
because he's got autism. He can't go out
and get normal women because he's got
autism. Why do you think he's fluctuated
on my sloppy
seconds? You know that one from [ __ ]
Manchester [ __ ] Morgan cuz he can't
get anything himself. He's still a
virgin. Like I literally had [ __ ] 12,
bro. I got 12 numbers in the past week.
I've got dates scheduled. I've had
replies. I've had the [ __ ] lot, bro.
You know, you can't even simply make new
friends. That's how bad his autism
is. It's bad, bro. It's [ __ ]
bad. You know, I didn't call him bab
names. I done that on the video as a
[ __ ] joke. And anyways, bro, why are
we talking about 10 years ago? Who's the
one that's still obsessed? Listen,
listen. [ __ ] all of that [ __ ] Anyways,
yeah. Who is the one that's still
obsessed? This virgin is. This virgin is
the one that's still
obsessed. 10 [ __ ] 11 years
later. 10 11 years later, bro. This
virgin is the Oh, it technically is 11
years. Now we're in a new year. This is
the same virgin that's still obsessed. Not
me. [ __ ] [ __ ] all
that. And I just like and I found like
all of the stuff weird. Like when he
would say that Sheer Cole was attractive
to fit in. Well, I didn't know. It's
when he started saying, "Oh, um, if you
don't like Shervel Cole, you're gay."
He's just copying like copycat like
[ __ ] insecure cuz he's a deep down
homosexual [ __ ] and other things like
he just thought he would
know. He knows everything and he really
knows knows it all. goes, "Fuck all
really like this." He thinks he would
know everything and he doesn't. You
literally couldn't even go
out with that [ __ ] virgin normally,
bro. You literally wouldn't be able
to. But yeah, saying Chev was if you
don't find Co attractive, you're gay.
That's just copying. That is just
straight up trying to fit
in black guy. Black guy. He's not a
He's Indian and he's uh he's one of my
associates. Why do you want to know?
He's one of my [ __ ] associates, mate.
Don't call him [ __ ] friends. Eh. Yeah.
I've never heard of that, mate. I would
give that sh a strong 5.5. I don't know
about you people, I'd say 5.5 maximum.
Nothing special about
her. But it's not that there's anything
special about her. Oh, did he? Good for
him, man. Nice. No one
cares. Anyways, we're going to stop
talking about this Virgin now. Anyways,
we spent enough time talking about this
kind of He's not even worth talking
about. He's not even worth your breath. So, yeah.
Yeah, man. We spent enough time. But I
rate um She Cara a solid
5.5. Nothing special. Literally nothing
special. It's not the way she looks.
It's the name, mate. It's a trend. It's
literally a trend that people copy each
other. Yeah. Go on then, bro. Start a
roulette channel. Go for it, man. [ __ ] it.
I might do I'm going to do a 10 pound
bet on Saturday. I
reckon£10. I'm going to do a 10 pound bet.
Never feel like that's perfect.
Yeah. 10 pound bets
per Stay away from him, mate. I've spat
on two machines the past week. Even
though it was only like 2030 pound, I've
been spitting on these machines, mate.
I got videos of me
spitting spitting on
it. That curry was so lush yesterday,
man. Can't beat a nice Chinese curry.
Eh, soft beef. Hey.
Yeah, I need just do some content on
this channel, man. [ __ ] what the name audio
is. If you [ __ ] replying to [ __ ] virgins,
bro, I don't know how people can lose
gambling, right, and they don't get
affected by it. I literally don't understand
how they can lose. Like me, I lose 20
pound, I go [ __ ] mad. I don't know
how people do it. I don't know how
people lose and be okay with it. I mean,
it's okay if you won the day before or
the day after before. Okay. Then it's
like, okay, whatever. I don't know how
people it don't affect
them. And then I have I end up having
the same conversation. People be like,
"Oh, it was only 20, but it doesn't
matter the amount, the
20. It doesn't matter that it was only
You know, it doesn't matter about it was
only 20 pound, bro. Like, it's not the
actual quantity of money. It's just
losing is annoying on them machines.
It's hard to explain to people. They don't understand
it. I was supposed to go cinema
yesterday. It ruined my whole day and it
was only 40 quid as well. You
know, it's like it makes your blood
boil. It's like you've got a demon
inside of your body and there's no way
to calm down. And it's not ADHD. It's
not ADHD because I've accepted the women
[ __ ] now. I've accepted how it is and
whatever. You know, it doesn't bother me
anymore. So, it is gambling. And then it
even though people was trying to say all
along, oh, it's not gambling. It's not
gambling. It's not gambling. It's not
gambling. It [ __ ] well was. It
[ __ ] well was, mate.
No, I'm even if I expect to potentially
lose, it will still wind me up. No
matter what mind no matter what mindset
that I go in with, it will still annoy
me. It will still piss me off because
even if you go in and you expect to
lose, say you are up 10, 20 pound, you
try to win more and then you lose, it
will still wind me up. It doesn't matter
if you expect to lose, you don't want to
lose, you want to win. It can't go the
other way. Simple. That's it. You
know, well, yeah. Well, obviously it and
yeah, obviously if you won, then you
win. Um, then I'll be, oh, I just lost.
Then I would be like, oh yeah, okay, I
lost. It happens. Yeah, it wouldn't
bother me then. But it's when it's
continuously losing and losing and
losing, it's like, no, something's not
right. Something is not right, man.
Something is not [ __ ] right here. But
I didn't lose a lot of money this month
anyways. It was just like periods of
time. But got my passport sorted, got
all my bills paid, so this month was better. So yeah. Yeah,
man. But the only time I really do it is
when I'm drinking. I always go to the
arcade before going home. Yeah, that's
the one I was playing. And it keeps
giving me [ __ ] 10 to one.
Yeah, that's the one I was playing and
it kept giving me [ __ ] 10 to [ __ ]
wonder. But I just normally gamble
before I go home. I never do it. Like
this is this is like typical,
right? I go out drinking and
then I go out
drinking and then get some [ __ ]
whatever. Eat, get some [ __ ] get
some scram. And then I'll go to the
arcade with like 150 and try and win on
like fish and friendly. That's my
routine. I always do it
before. I always do it before
um I always do it. Sorry. I always do it
after I always do it just before going
home because it will ruin the
mood. And then if I win, I just get like
an escort or something. But
yeah, I just get an escort or something.
But it's hard to not gamble when you're
when you're drinking, bro. It's so hard.
I find that the
hardest. Yeah, I had like two pound on
20 and it hit [ __ ] 10 to [ __ ] one.
Yeah, it hit 10 to [ __ ] one, bro.
doesn't give me confidence, mate. I'm
I'm confident even when I'm not [ __ ]
drunk. I just don't get tempted to
gamble, man. I got like three numbers
sober [ __ ] last
week. Yeah, man. There's a few things I
need to do, bro. I need to go actually a
gym. I need to do this sort of job
thing. I'm not going to tell anyone what
it is cuz JR is on here. And yeah, man.
I just need to put some content on the
channel. I need to give up gambling,
bro. It's not for
me. Yeah, but it's like a triple
zero. Gambling is not for me, bro. It
seriously is not for me, bro. It's not,
man. It's bad. It's really
bad. Birming's bad, bro. But I'm still
going to do a football bet on Saturday.
Like I'm trying to do a double. I'm
trying to do a triple. Yeah. Both teams
to score no draw. But they're [ __ ]
hard to get in,
bro. I remember before. Yeah. I'll never forget it,
right? It's back when I was 19. Yeah. I
didn't know nothing about football. I
didn't know I don't know anything about
football now, though. I put I swear to
God, I on six teams. Yeah. I put one
pound on six teams. I won 75 quid. I was
like, I wish I had [ __ ] more on it.
And back then, money was worth a lot
more. And back then, when you're
younger, money's worth a lot more. Even
though I had a fiverr on it. Oh my god.
And I won £75 off of a [ __ ] pound. I
was like, that's never going to come in.
It was Bolton, Peter
Ba, Bolton, Peterbor, Charlton,
Bradford. I remember some of the I
actually remember some of the teams. I
actually saved it for many years. My
first my first football bet win £75 for
a [ __ ] pound. I wish I had more on
it, bro. I wish I had more on
it, you know. Yeah, that's what I was
doing. I was doing middle section.
That's what I was doing. Yeah, that's
what I was doing as
well. But um
Yeah. Yeah, bro.
What do you think about football bets?
They're [ __ ] hard to win, bro. I
mean, I lost 90 pound on one the other
day because of Newport, but they're just
hard to win, isn't it?
Yeah, they're hard to win,
man. They are hard to win. [Music]
Yeah, they are hard to win,
bro. What do you think about the football
bets? I bet you wish you had more in it, though. It
wow. Maybe that's why I need to stop
doing the over 1.5s, eh?
Yeah, that's that's over that's more
than one goal, isn't
it? So, anything that's two goals, isn't
it? So, 2-0 1-1. That's what that means, right?
Yeah. Seems easy, doesn't it? I just do
both teams to score [Music]
me. I don't know, bro.
Football's hard to win on.
Yeah, it is hard to win on gambling,
bro. On the football. I just play Frankie.
Frankie. Frankie. That's why I was like [Music] Frankie the
[ __ ] I never liked slots until I played
that [ __ ] fishing frenzy. I used to I
never used to play anything but roulette
until I played that fishing
frenzy. Oh. Oh [ __ ] I forgot to tell
you. I actually got a video. Yeah.
There's this woman on a mobility
scooter and she's playing slots on her
mobility scooter. I was like, "But me,
how addicted can someone
get?" Yeah, she plays it on her [ __ ]
mobility scooter. What the [ __ ] I see
it. I swear it was some old
woman. She looked like Mrs. Wicket from
Mr. B. And then she's [ __ ] on the on
the mobility scooter playing [ __ ] slots. Madness. Yeah, it's mad. Yeah,
man. So, I normally do go out drinking
every week cuz I just like pre-drink,
but yeah, I watched it when I was younger. Yeah. Yeah. a young
kid. Yeah, man. And
Spongebob. Yeah, I want to watch that
Danny Dfield, but I'm not in a massive
rush to watch
it. Um, but because I was out yesterday,
so I was like, "Oh, there's a showing,
but then the gambler just ruined
it." But I'm definitely watching that
lady in the that woman in the yard.
I'm definitely watching that woman in the
yard. We have got 15 days to
go. 15 days to go.
A 15 days to go. Ain't
bad. It's not bad. Yeah,
man. Well, you don't like Mr.
Bean. You don't like Mr. Bean, bro.
I've got 80 I think I got 91 numbers
now. So, I'm building it back up since
my uh phone got stolen. I don't think
I've got any American
numbers. Maybe one or
so. Yeah, I maybe have one American
number actually. Not sure. Yeah.
Five. I've got [ __ ] 91, mate. Most of
them are [ __ ] women as
well. Sean can do that. Virgin Sean can
do that. Hey, Lord J can do
that. [ __ ] Virgin Sean can do that. Nah,
bro. Could you imagine that Virgin
actually had the numbers that I've got
here on my phone? He'd be like messaging
them all weird [ __ ] and that [ __ ] reject.
Yeah. Yeah. Or
reply. When are you drinking again? I
don't know when I'm drinking again. [ __ ] knows,
man. Um I already tried three times, but
the virgin didn't come out.
But the virgin didn't come out of his
shitty little tent
beds. And why is he so insecure about
where he comes from? Oh, probably
southeast London. All No, you're from
Kent. No, no, you're from Kent. Nothing
to do with London. You're from
Kent. Even Cuden. I know the area, but
not where the Virgin lives to do
address. You know, even Cuden is not
London. You do realize even C is not
London and he's like, "Oh, in that case
you're from Essex." I'm from Essex.
Okay. So I was born in Leighton Stone,
lived in Leighton for 13 years. Then I
moved to Straford 14 years. Then I lived
with my mom for what? Year and a half,
two years. And where am I now, [ __ ]
Back in London. But that makes me from
Essex. How does that work? No, you're
from Kent. You are from Kent. Stop being
so ashamed of where you come from.
You know, you don't need to be insecure.
And and he pop a comment here for
validation. Sh, no, it's London. No, no,
no, it's London. No, it's not London.
They don't even sound the same as
London. It's nowhere near London. London. Yeah.
Yeah. And And yeah, that's it. It's not
London. Yeah. Doesn't matter. You are
actually from Kent. Like where where my
mom lives is about 5 minutes to what's
considered London. You literally live in
Kent. For you to come to London, it
would take you about 30 minutes. But you
say that you live in London. Where my
where my mom lives, you're in London in 5
minutes. So like what the [ __ ] You're
30 minutes away from London. You're from Kent.
You are literally from [ __ ]
Kent. Yeah, just like most of the places
in [ __ ] England is a [ __ ] out. It's
not just London. Loads of
places. Loads of places are a [ __ ] up,
man. I like Newcastle, man. It's so easy
to get women in Newcastle. It's easyish
in London, but uh But Newcastle
is sorry. And go where? Leave London to
where? Leave London to go where? Well,
the whole of the UK is [ __ ] But
yeah, I can't believe that Sean is 30
years of age. Still a virgin. [ __ ]
still a virgin. That's impressive at 30,
bro. [ __ ] beat me. Never been on a
plane and he's never been
abroad. What the [ __ ] is going on with
your [ __ ] life, Virgin
boy? Never been in a in a relationship
with somebody that's actually [ __ ]
normal. Uh, I haven't decided yet, but
somewhere, you know, that's the madness. That's so [Music] [ __ ]
Yeah, that's a
madness. Come to your city. Where is
city? I was even going to go to Glasgow
or [ __ ] Blackpool on Saturday, but I
can't be bothered with England no more.
Well, I'm Scotland now. Still England to
me. Still the UK. I need to be leaving now,
bro. I need to be leaving England, bro.
[ __ ] it. I've already done the UK. I
don't need to leave. London's got
everything. You can stay anonymous, you
know. I don't need to leave London, you know. Yeah.
So yeah. Well, what what city do you
live in? You haven't told
me. I want to get this nice Ammani
tracksuit, but the weather is so
unpredictable, man. Got this nice
[ __ ] I want to get this nice Ammani tracksuit.
Yeah, I've already been to Bristol, but
not on a night out.
Yeah, I've got a friend from
Bristol. Funny enough, there used to be
this guy on PlayStation uh called Aaron
Cox, and he was from Bristol, and he
sounded like a right nightmare. That's
how he used to talk. And uh yeah, he's a
compulsive [ __ ] liar, bro. I tried to
follow him on Instagram the other day.
He blocked me. I've been to
Bristol. Oh, I've been to Bristol, man.
I think I've been there
twice, but not for a night out. I went
there during co as well.
Bristol. Yeah, that's a southwest
western. That's the west country. That
is he sounds like a
right. That's how he talks.
500 CH. That's
nice. It's nice,
mate. That's nice,
Yeah. Yeah. So, Dave, what do you reckon
will happen if I go out Saturday
approaching? What do you think will
happen if I if I go out approaching on Saturday?
Davey, what do you think will happen?
I don't need a ring, man. Bro, I do
good. I do well by myself,
bro. I do very well by my [ __ ] self,
bro. I pulled two weeks
ago. Not with me, they don't, mate. I've
pulled by myself many
times. Lack of life experience. Maybe
for you, buddy, but I've pulled by
myself many [ __ ] times.
many [ __ ] times,
bro. Pretty much all the times I pulled
was by myself. Stig one on my birthday. Morgan
[ __ ] [ __ ] one that gave me a
[ __ ] in the alleyway. That Scottish
one. They do reply. What are you talking
about? They never reply. They [ __ ]
do. I got [ __ ] numbers last week.
They've all replied. I'm eating one
soon. I'm just busy this week. Nah, bro.
Every time I've pulled, I've done it by
myself. That wingman [ __ ] is like, nah,
bro. It's fun sometimes to go out with
someone. Sometimes I do go out with
someone. I went out with someone last
week. Um, you
know, they give you a number to get rid
of you. No, they don't, bro. I've got
many numbers and I've met loads of women
and I've had loads of them reply and I'm
meeting a couple meeting a couple as
well. So, yeah, speak for yourself,
buddy. But I've pulled many times by
myself. Bro, speak for yourself, man. Speak for
yourself on the street. Maybe go by your own experiences.
Yeah. I've always, mate, that time I was
in Manchester, I pulled. It doesn't
matter if it's led to a relationship,
mate. I've had sex. I've had women. It
doesn't matter whe it's led to a
relationship or not, mate. Even if I was
in a relationship, you would still tell
me that I'm not in a relationship. So
what's the point, bro? The whole this
whole projection [ __ ] is boring because
bro, even if I was in a relationship,
you would still tell me that I'm not in
a relationship. Just like when people
come on here and call me skin. Yeah, I
show money, they still call me skin.
Allow it, bro. It's
boring. And I need to be single for the
next year or so as well because I'm
going traveling. So I have to be single.
I will have to be single anyways. Well,
for at least six months to be
fair. So, I'll have to be single for
like six to eight months anyways. So,
what would have been a problem of me
even dating someone even if I got the
chance? But yeah, bro, that [ __ ]
about, oh, they get creeped out if you
approach. No, they [ __ ] don't, bro.
don't. No, they [ __ ] do not. I've
always done better by myself. I've
always. Always. But like I said, it is
fun to go out with someone
sometimes. Uh why does why can't you get
girlfriend? Why can't you get a
girlfriend? Answer was this question,
man. Instead of coming on my on my
channel projecting, why can't you get a
girlfriend? And just as I explained to
this Davey, right, even if I did have
one, you would still tell me that I
don't have one. Just like when you get
shown money time and time and time
again. The thing is with you people, you
need to worry about your own [ __ ]
lives. You know, I I read a comment, I
think it was two days ago, saying, "Oh,
um, PJ seems um perfectly capable of
working. Why doesn't he work?" And I was
thinking in my head, I didn't reply,
"Why don't you work? Why are you
claiming benefits? Worry about your own
lives." And I didn't reply to it. I was
thinking, "What the fuck?" Just asking a question, mate.
Just ask asking a
question. No, we're not. We're not
repeat. You are a mong as well. Yeah,
stop calling yourself a mong, bro. I
don't need a job, mate. I earn enough
money. I've got a life. I've got a job.
I've got plenty of money. I'm all sweet,
mate. I am all [ __ ] sweet, you
know. You know, that's the next thing, bro. You
know, I find that a lot with you people
in this community. It doesn't matter.
I'm going to tell you what I do. Like,
do. Yeah. Speak for yourself, Radner.
Speak for yourself, buddy. Speak for
yourself. Like, yeah. You're talking
about your own life, bro. Stop
self-projecting. It's what you people
are good at. And I've told you about
I've told you a million times, bro. Self
projection is not good for your mental
health. You're saying it seems like I
get I struggle to get women to like me
long term. You're probably sat there
still a virgin. You don't even leave
your house. It's boring now, bro. Stop
reflecting. Stop rejecting. It's like
all of these people that used to sit
there, right, and and stick up for
women. Me, I don't care. It doesn't
bother me now cuz I don't care about it.
I'm be I'm we're that ship has sailed.
Yeah. But these people are the same
people that don't leave the house. The
same people that don't speak to women,
but they will defend women. How the [ __ ]
would they know what they're like? Like
I remember when I used to chat [ __ ]
about it like few weeks ago. Yeah. I
used to go like, "Oh, they're this,
they're that, they're that." And it's
like, you got these people on YouTube.
But these people on YouTube have got
absolutely no life experiences. Like,
they've got no life experience. They
don't go out and meet women. They don't
have no friends. They have no life
experience. But they want to preach to
you about what women are like in your
own city. Who would know it better than
you yourself going out every week? I
never I never called everyone a virgin.
I said that Sean's a virgin cuz he is a
virgin. And I've also said that Timmy's
a virgin and potentially Bob. I never
called everyone a virgin. And a lot of
you I said a lot of you probably are
virgins. Yeah. Which is maybe I don't
know 45% of you probably are.
Yeah. I never said everyone's a virgin.
When have I said everyone's a
virgin? Yeah. I said that Sean's a
virgin and I said that Timmy is a
virgin. You know, but you what makes me
laugh about you? Oh [ __ ] spit myself.
You people try to preach about to other
people about women, right? But you are
not the ones that go out every day
interacting with women. So who would
actually know more, me or you?
Who would know more, me or you? That's
the question you need to ask yourself.
Who would know more about women? Me or
you? Me, obviously. You
know, because for a lot of people
because for a lot of people, what you
say is what you are. Okay, fair enough.
So, I'm skinn even though I've shown
thousands and thousands and I showed
money the other day. I'm a virgin
apparently even though that I've made a
porno and I've been in bed with women
and hotel rooms with women and seen
kissing women. Doesn't make any doesn't
make any sense. That doesn't make any
sense, bro. How could I be deflecting
when I've literally proven
otherwise? The [ __ ] bro? I've shown the
most money than anybody on this
community. I've shown the most women.
I've shown I've had sex. I showed money
a year ago. No, I showed money last week.
Right. The same day that I got my
passport done. And guess what? None of
you people could show me anything as per
usual. Anyways, we're moving on now
because we're not going to go back and
forth with this, man. Go get a life. So,
yeah. End the story. End of
conversation. I know what you're trying
to do. It's not going to
work. I try,
man. We're not going to get people wait raiding.
Oh, how Oh, did he? Oh, did he actually?
Oh, did he? Where is it now? Um, it's in
my bank account because none of you
people. Anyways, we're not going back
and forth with this anyways. We're not
going back and forth with this anymore.
Um, anyways, uh, Baz showed more money
than me. Really? I didn't see how much
money did he
show? Oh, I think he did, actually.
Yeah. No, yeah. Yeah, I think he did. He
showed like six, seven grand. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I do actually remember. But
the point is No, no, no, no, no. But the
point is, none of you people showed me
any money. None of you people that call
people skint showed me any money. Where
was all your money? You're the ones that
are coming on here calling people skint
every day. Then when people show you
money, you've got nothing to show
yourself. I'm not showing you nothing
ever again. Right? I tell you the reason
I showed money the other day and Grievy
will back me up on this because he was
on he was on the live stream. Timmy come
on. I was pissed and he was keep saying,
"Oh, you got no money. You got no money.
You got no money. You got no money. You
got no money." It was pissing me off.
Yeah. And I was drunk. I was like,
"Okay, let me go withdraw some money." I
showed £,100. It was just over a grand.
Yeah. And that's it. Oh, you left the
stream. And guess what? None of these
people could show me nothing. Surprise,
surprise. I'm not showing you nothing.
But I I can't even remember that, bro. I
was drunk as
[ __ ] Yeah. But anyways, I'm still
Wonder Money game, bro. No one's showing 12
grand. Anyways, we're not going back and
forth about this anymore, man. This is
autism, man. This is repeated. I'm not
doing this. Yeah. Don't take it on
another channel. It's boring, bro. Grow
up. You need to grow up in your heads.
You people in your like 30s, 40s, and
all you do is go on about money every
day. And then when people show you
money, you can't show nothing yourself.
Like have a word with yourself, man.
Like grow up. Like literally grow up,
man. I think a lot of people in this
community, Grezy, need to seriously grow
up. It's embarrassing, bro. And to think
these people are older than me as
well. [ __ ] embarrassing,
bro. I'm alo dependent.
I'm alcohol dependent. [ __ ] hell, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, bro, that's just like
that's just self
projecting. That's just
self-reflecting. Greasy. I'm going to
put some content videos on my channel,
bro. Um, either this week or next week.
try to build the channel
up, you know, like put some actual
content on this on this channel, bro.
I'm not alcohol dependent, bro. The
[ __ ] I drink like once a week. I'm not
drinking this week, though. No, not this
week. Oh [ __ ]
You're okay though, greasy boss. Your
your sayings made me laugh, bro. You was
like, "Oh, Peter B's parents left him in
nesticles. They flew away and left him in the nesticles." Oh
man. Yeah. Flew away and
left. Oh, that's ace, bro. That's cool.
No, I think Greavves is a pretty good
gun. Me, I think he's I think he's very
uh very mature for his age. Oh
man, I think Grezy wants to see the posters.
I mean, even if you do posters of this
little virgin, it's not going to stop
long term. Like, the only the only way
this virgin will stop is if he's dead or
in prison. That's literally the
only like that's literally the only way,
right? Cuz if you do posters, bro, I'm
not worried about the police. I don't
give a [ __ ] about the police and the
police probably wouldn't even come again
anyways. But then it will stop for like
2 3 weeks and then he's obsession like
then people you don't understand why people get
sectioned you know you don't understand
why people get sectioned there's a
reason why people get sectioned like
people like Sha need to be sectioned
they need to be incarcerated because
their autism is so bad that it they're a
danger to the
public that's why I said dead or in
prison or sectioned
You know, these are the same kind of
people, bro. They'd get a restraining
order and they'd [ __ ] break it. Trust
me, they would break it. They would actually break
it, you know? It's autism and jealousy
is a [ __ ] horrible disease. I mean,
autism is it is
like common to have forms of it, but I
mean, not like that, mate. Not like that. [ __ ]
madness. That is cold. Why is it so
cold? [ __ ] freezing, man. [Music]
I need to get a [ __ ] drink, bro. Like
a Coke, not an alcoholic
drink. Birthday to it. But nah, not
today, bro. [ __ ] weather [ __ ] I need
to detox as well. [Laughter]
Whoever. Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
No, I think Gre is a pretty good
cat. I think me and Greavesy will get on just fine. [Music] [Laughter] Oh, me time.
9:37 boxes like that.
Well, let me go get this drink and um
I'll be back later. And then tomorrow
I'm done, bro. I'm not going to be here
for a little while.