What a [ __ ] [ __ ]
Well, soon ran away and I said, I'm
going to make a dating profile of you.
These [ __ ] Oh my god. I'm going to
make a dating profile of them, bro.
One second, lad.
So, I told them as well, bro. What the
[ __ ] Hey, bro. These two were pissing
me off, bro. Yeah. One sec.
Let me make sure I got the right number here,
please. One minute, please.
Yeah. So these [ __ ] here, I called them
in. I said, "Why are you come why are
you on my phone trying to troll me? Why
are you on my phone trying to [ __ ]
troll me, bro?" Do you know what I said?
I said, "I'm going to make a dating
profile of you now.
You've never had a girlfriend. You're
still a virgin." What the [ __ ] You know
what I said, bro? I said I said they
were trying to troll me in it. I said,
"Listen here, [ __ ] I'll talk to
women how I want and I'll meet you
tomorrow." And he didn't want none of
it. So, hold on a minute. You've come on
my phone messaging me and I've never
I've not messaged this person for like a
year. And they said, "Mate, if you've
got a problem with what I say about
women, you silly little [ __ ] [ __ ]
with your little speech impediment. Come
and meet me tomorrow. Come on." And then
they were still trying to take the piss.
I said, "You know what I'm going to do
now? I'm going to make a dating profile
of you and I'm going to get you I'm
going to get men to message you and send
you dick pictures. See how much you're
laughing then you silly little [ __ ]
Stop [ __ ] belling out my phone, bro.
What the [ __ ] I'm just chilling, bro.
Playing a bit of Franklin and I've got
these [ __ ] stupid little [ __ ]
Oh, the weather and it bro. You're messaging me.
They're messaging me, bro. What the [ __ ]
I'm chilling, bro. I got this dick. I
don't even know who the [ __ ] they are. Oh, well,
you [ __ ] little [ __ ] Don't start
something you can't finish, you [ __ ]
monk. [ __ ] you know what I mean?
Not something you can't finish. You know
what I'm saying, bro? What the actual [ __ ] bro?
Who the [ __ ] are women? You little
[ __ ] s. You're on my phone. What the
[ __ ] He was messaging me, bro. What the madness?
What the actual [ __ ] You've come on my
phone starting on me. You and your ugly
woman. So, I've started on you and a
woman. Yes. And I will meet you tomorrow.
What the [ __ ] I'm lying in bed
chilling, bro. Imagine that. You're
chilling. Yeah. Playing a bit of
Franklin. You got these two [ __ ]
messaging you out of nowhere. I'm
starting on you and I'm starting on your
woman. Yes, I am. Come and do something about it.
You know what I mean?
Don't start something you can't finish.
It's a madness, bro. [ __ ] absolute
madness. You're the one that needs to
get laid, bro. You're messaging man on
[ __ ] on a Sunday with your [ __ ]
clap ginger [ __ ] who I can't even
[ __ ] remember approaching.
You know what I'm saying? You're the one
that needs to get laid, bro. You're
clearly bored. Like, what the [ __ ]
I'm starting on you and your [ __ ]
ugly girl. Even I think they're just
friends. I said, "Yes, I'm starting on
you and I'm starting on a woman." Yes,
because you've messaged me first. Yes, I
am. Yes, I [ __ ] well am. And what are
you going to do about it, you little
[ __ ] dick? And I'll slap you to next
week, you silly little [ __ ] Watch when
you got all them nasty [ __ ] men start
[ __ ] messaging you now. Why are you
messaging me, bro?
You know, you [ __ ] absolute [ __ ]
So many [ __ ] in this country, bro.
I swear to God. What the [ __ ] is wrong
with people, man? Imagine that. You're
just lying there chilling, bro. [ __ ]
I approached this person from [ __ ]
when the Euros was I think the it was um
Do you remember when the Euros was? Um
do you remember when the Euros was
happening last year?
You remember last year
the Euros and you remember last year
Euros? Yeah. Um yeah, the Euros.
I can't even [ __ ] remember why I even approached them.
Oh, I gave him my number cuz I was
scared to say no. No, you did not. Shut
up. Why are you messaging me? I don't
know who the [ __ ] you are.
What the [ __ ]
Oh, you started on women. Does that make
you feel really proud of yourself being
a s? Is your mom proud of you for being
a s? You've messaged me trying to take
the piss out of me. What the [ __ ]
Trying to like these people need to grow
up, bro. These people really need to
grow up. They're older than me. They're
older than me. like you're you're
[ __ ] with someone on a Sunday that
you don't even know. They haven't even
spoken to for like a year and a [ __ ] and
a half. I deleted their [ __ ] number
when they're [ __ ] messaging me
like, "Get away with yourself, man. You
silly little [ __ ] [ __ ] You started
on me and I'll start on you and I'll
start on your woman, which is your
friend, and you will do nothing about
it. There's no point blocking me. You've
messaged me. You've got me in a bad mood
now, dickhead." Do you understand?
You've got me in a bad mood now, [ __ ]
Like, what the [ __ ] I'm lying there
chilling, bro. They've got me in a bad
mood. These [ __ ] stupid little
[ __ ] So, I'll give you one more
chance. Are you going to meet me or I'm
going to or am I going to get these men
to send you dick [ __ ] I'm going to
make you change your number cuz you put
me in a bad mood now, [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? Do you know
what I'm [ __ ] saying? So, what what's
it going to be, [ __ ]
Are you going to come and meet me so I
can [ __ ] slap your [ __ ] head in?
Or am I going to make a dating profile
of you and make you change your [ __ ] number?
Bear in mind, you've you've started on
me. I don't know why you're [ __ ]
messaging me. Who the [ __ ] are you? You
know, you want to be a [ __ ] I'll
make a prime example of you, you [ __ ]
And I mean it, bro. I feel that strongly
towards it, bro. Like, I get it, bro. If
you're in a bad mood, trust me, I get
it. We all have these tempers. Yeah,
people have different, you know, tempers
and stuff. I I'm not slagging you for
that. But if you're going to start
something, at least finish it. And don't
run away, [ __ ] Don't run away.
Don't start something you can't finish.
What the [ __ ]
It's madness. It's a [ __ ] madness, bro.
What's the point, you know?
[ __ ] messaging me, bro. What the
What the [ __ ] lad?
Why are they messaging [ __ ] random
people, bro? They don't even [ __ ] know.
Some people really need to grow up, don't they?
Going around being a [ __ ] starting
[ __ ] they can't finish. What is the
point of it?
Honestly, what is the point of it, bro? madness.
Some people really need to grow up, eh?
Oh, you starting on the web, bro. You
You literally started on me. You started
messaging me. I don't know who the [ __ ] you are.
[ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] Go suck
your mom, bro. You know,
starting on somebody that you don't even know.
It's so mad cuz you're bored cuz you
can't [ __ ] each other cuz you're little
dicks or some [ __ ] bro. And you're on
my [ __ ] messaging me.
What the [ __ ]
I don't know why they do this, bro. I
really don't know why they do this madness.
Oh, there was this [ __ ]
there was this woman that I approached
[ __ ] last year, you know, the Euros.
And I said, "Oh, do you want to come
Nando?" Because we arranged to go
Nandos. And she never replied. So, a
year and a half later, I get this random
message with her sending me a picture of
a guy trying to take the [ __ ] piss,
like trying to take the piss out of me.
and saying, "Oh, I want to bum you and
that." I called him up and saying,
"Listen, why are you randomly messaging
me being a [ __ ] I don't do this
keyboard watch [ __ ] If you want to meet
me, I can meet you tomorrow." And then
they started like just trying to take
the piss. And then I said, "Listen,
yeah, you and that [ __ ] slag of
yours." Cuz they were winding me up.
Come and meet me tomorrow and try and
troll me to my face. And then they was
like, "Oh, they're starting on the
women." I said, "I'm starting on you and
I'm starting on a woman." Yes. come and
do something about it because you've
messaged me for no reason, [ __ ]
[ __ ] ugly bastard messaging me now.
Come and meet me tomorrow. You're
messaging me like, "What the [ __ ] bro?"
out the blue. I'm chilling in my bed.
Yeah. And this little dickhead's [ __ ]
messaging me. Yeah. I'm starting on a
woman. Yes. And I'm starting on you. So,
come and meet me tomorrow, big man.
Well, actually, I'm finishing it. But as
usual, they run away. So, I said, "You
know what I'm going to do? I'm going to
make a dating profile now and I'm going
to get all of these men now to start
messaging that number and you're going
to change your number then. So, it
wasn't worth it in the end, was it? You
know, it wasn't worth being a [ __ ]
starting something you can't finish
really because now you're just going to
have to change your number or at very
least you're just going to have a load
of [ __ ] dickpicks sent to you. Don't
[ __ ] come on my phone trying to take
the piss out of me. I'm not one of these
little [ __ ] Yeah, you understand?
It's [ __ ] annoying, bro. Who the [ __ ]
do they think they are?
I'm starting on a woman. Yes. And I'm
starting on you. Come and do something
about it. You know what I'm saying? I'll
meet you anywhere you want. I'll give
you my address right now. It's not a problem.
[ __ ] stupid little wanker. I suck
your mom, bro. I mean,
I don't know why they're messaging me,
bro. What the [ __ ]
What the [ __ ] bro?
really really bored. Oh my god. You must
be really bored.
Really really really
bored to be doing that, bro. Like
must be really really bored.
Must be really bored in it, Tanny man. [ __ ] neighbor.
And then he says, "Keep threatening
young girls. [ __ ] you message me.
I was lying in my bed and you messaged me.
You've messaged me out of nowhere, you
stupid silly little [ __ ] And then when
I said I'll slap both of you up because
you're trying to troll me. Oh, keep
threatening your girls, bro. You're
messaging me, [ __ ]
So to god, if you didn't want a [ __ ]
response, you wouldn't have [ __ ]
messaged me, would you? Yeah.
Yeah, dude. This [ __ ] trying to troll me
pissed me off, bro. I'm going to do a
video on this. So, you messaged me
randomly trying to get on my nerves cuz
you're a [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] And
then when I tell you to come and meet me
tomorrow with your [ __ ] slaggy friend.
Um, you you you you're saying, "Oh,
you're threatening women, mate. Yes, I'm
threatening you and I'm threatening a
woman. Come and do something about it.
You're messaging me. You're starting on
me. You're trying to troll me. So, I
want to meet you. What the [ __ ]
No, it's not LT. It's nothing to do with
LT. I was like, [ __ ] you've messaged me.
I've not spoke to you in [ __ ] a year
and a half. You've messaged me, you
stupid little [ __ ] Yeah, you have
messaged me for no reason. I don't know
why you're messaging me.
They've messaged me like, you've got to
be really, really bored, bro. The only
thing I can think of is they probably
tried to [ __ ] each other and the guy's
got erectile dysfunction. So he was that
[ __ ] bored he had to message me. You
know you're bored, bro. Bro, that's how
you know mother's your bored, bro. You
have got to be bored, bro. Trying to rub
it in. Why would she rub it in? I don't
even like her. This was [ __ ] year and
a half ago. You have to be really bored
to be doing that, bro.
No, I don't. I think they're friends. I
don't think they're together. And they
wouldn't rub it in, bro. This was some
[ __ ] dead thing from a year and a
half ago. What the [ __ ] that you know
you're bored, bro. You're sat there with
your friend and you got nothing better
to do than to message somebody from a
year and a half ago trying to get on
their nerves, which yeah, you did get on
my nerves. And then when they ask you to
meet and troll them to their face, oh,
you're threatening your women, bro. You
message me, you stupid little downey.
So, what I'm going to do is I'm going to
make a dating profile now and [ __ ]
um I'm going to make that person change
their number now. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying? [ __ ] stupid
[ __ ] I'm going to make them change
their number now. I'm going to get guys
to send her a load of dickpicks.
Yeah. Simple, bro. I was lying in bed,
bro. No, bro. I don't like these little
[ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] [ __ ]
messaging me, bro. You're trying to
message me. Take the piss out of me. I
said, "Come and take the piss to my
face. Come and come and take the piss to
my face, you silly little cunt."
Oh, it was just this just this random
[ __ ] woman from a year and a half ago
with some guy. They started messaging me
out of the blue trying to start taking a piss.
Yeah. And then I defended myself and
then all of a sudden,
yeah, troller. Yeah, 100%. Yeah, 100%.
Stupid little [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
messaging down my [ __ ] phone like a
silly little [ __ ] you know.
I don't get it, bro. Why the [ __ ] you
messaging me, bro? What the [ __ ]
Nothing, bro. It was just like, who the
[ __ ] do they think they are randomly
messaging me trying to take the piss?
Who the [ __ ] do they think they are, bro?
And then they blocked me.
Um, the number is
it's just like it's annoying, bro. Don't
message me, bro. Trying to take the piss. 07 0745333093.
And they can call the police as well,
above, cuz I've got their [ __ ]
messages where they've been messaging
me. And I told her back. I told her to
grow up as well. [ __ ] stupid little
[ __ ] Oh, keep threatening young girls,
brother. You messaged me, you [ __ ]
And I told you to come and meet me
because you were trying to troll me, [ __ ] Yeah.
See what I mean, bro? What the [ __ ]
What a [ __ ] madness.
someone message me now.
No. Yeah. Did you get it, bro? Yeah.
like randomly. Yeah. Messaging me out
the [ __ ] blue.
Like I swear to God, out the blue, bro.
What the [ __ ]
That's how you know that they're bored,
bro. That you just know that they tried
to [ __ ] and they couldn't [ __ ] Like
honestly, bro, you just know. Yeah. That
they were trying to [ __ ] You just know
that they were trying to [ __ ] right?
And he couldn't get his small dick up.
So there's like, "Oh, let me just [ __ ]
with somebody randomly."
Like you you you just know, bro. Like
that's literally the only way is some
two people. It's a Sunday night, bro.
Yeah. You're with a friend, you're with
a boyfriend, and you're messaging some
random person who you don't even [ __ ]
know. What the [ __ ]
You know what I mean?
I could probably find their full name to be fair. Yeah.
Yeah. Good, bro.
Good. Yeah. Some guy was there on the
phone to her, bro. I think he said it
was her friend and that. I said, "I'll
meet you both tomorrow, bro. Come and
meet me tomorrow. I'll meet you. Come
on. I'll give you my address now if you
want. I'll give you my address right now
if you want.
She said she's calling the police.
Calling the police.
She's calling the police, bro. They
started messaging me. Yeah, keep calling
the [ __ ] [ __ ] her about the police.
Yeah, call the police. Yeah, I've got
the messages of them messaging me,
trying to take the piss out of me. Yeah,
go on. Call Tell them to call the
police. Yeah, tell her to call the
police, silly little [ __ ] slaggy Yeah.
Yeah. Keep calling her, bro. [ __ ] hell, man.
Yeah, keep doing it, bro. [ __ ] [ __ ]
with that number. They started messaging
me out the blue, bro. The [ __ ]
You must really really be bored.
I'm going to tell her say hi to YouTube as well.
Said say hi to YouTube, honey.
I said say hi to YouTube, honey, cuz I'm
going to put that [ __ ] out there. So,
everyone's going to get a number now.
How about you just leave people alone
and just don't bother them? What the [ __ ]
>> Oh, you're picking on your girls.
You're picking on your girls. You You're
messaging me, [ __ ] and I'm asking
to meet both of you so you can try and
try me to my face, which you can't do
cuz you're a little keyboard warrior.
Stop being a keyboard warrior.
Stop being a keyboard warrior. You know
what I mean?
Madness, bro. Ain't it [ __ ] madness?
It's mad, huh?
It is m
I'm telling me to get laid when he's
messaging my phone at 9:00 at night on a
Sunday. You know what I'm saying? What the [ __ ]
You're the one that needs to get laid,
bro. You're the one that needs to
seriously get laid. And amen. [ __ ] madness.
What the [ __ ] lads? What the [ __ ] madness.
Anyways, I'm gone. See you.