Oh, lovely.
Lovely bit of hope. M M.
This is nice.
This can't be
a lovely popcorn.
No, not at all.
I remember what I said by where
I'm coming off after today.
Yeah, I'm coming off this [ __ ] after
today, bro. Same atmosphere. same atmosphere. For real,
it's the same people.
Why are you ever trying to come on here?
There's the same atmosphere.
It's the same people every day goes there.
I'm coming off this community, bro, cuz
it's the same people every day. Same repeating people.
Same repeating skin people.
You know what I mean?
Just having some popcorn. Sorry, man.
Popcorn is so yummy. I love popcorn.
These people will never leave me alone. Ghosty,
they'll never leave me alone.
I think they're jealous of me or
something, bro. What's your opinion?
I think they're jealous of me, bro. I've
got loads of middleage people
gravitating towards me.
I think they're jealous of me, lad. M
like I said, I'm not entertaining it no more
because what I say is the truth.
You see what I mean? Close to what I say
is the truth.
Them keep doing this they're showing
themselves up for what they really are.
If they keep doing this, it shows what they are.
So that's why I just I'm just not entertaining it, you know?
I don't want to let them look like the
jealous ones, the obsessed ones. I'm not entertaining it.
You know what I mean?
I'm not entertaining it. Huh?
Cuz what I cuz what I say is right.
What I say is right about them. And I'm
not projecting. What they're saying
about me can't be right. Because if that
was the truth, they would they would
leave me alone. If that was the truth
that you was this, that, and the other,
they wouldn't do all of this. The fact
that they do all of this, it proves that
it's themselves they're talking about.
And yes, you're right. It is projection.
100%, bro. Self projection. Mhm. Everything go
skin. That's skimp.
Everything with these people is self projection.
Ugly skin. [ __ ] M. Everything is bro. Mhm.
Let them embarrass themselves.
Don't um don't give them air time, man.
That's what I'm doing. Mhm. Anyways,
no. I told you I'm done. I don't care.
Did you not watch my video? I said I'm
done, bro. I don't give a [ __ ]
Don't bring it on my channel. Like you
said, I'm this, that, and the other.
Right. So, if I'm this, that, and the
other, then you will never entertain me ever again.
Yeah. I'm not interested, bro. I don't
care. I'm not seeing it, and I'm not
going to see it. Don't bring it on my channel.
If I'm this, that, and the other, then
you're going to stop going on about me. Simple.
And if you cl Well, it says it all then. Yeah.
It's the joys of being better looking
than these people, isn't it? Joys of
being better looking.
I'm coming off here after today anyways. But
it's creepy. It's a creepy community.
Does anyone still do Gandom videos? No,
I don't see the point of this [ __ ] whole community.
It's just a bunch of [ __ ] losers in their 40s.
with no money and no life talking about
other people. I don't actually
understand the point of it. I'm just
eating some popcorn.
Yeah, I'm just eating some popcorn, man.
I love salted popcorn.
I'll be at the cinema again Friday. But yeah,
they are obsessed on here. No,
you are my you.
If I'm all of these things, then these
people are not going to do any more
videos or any more community posts.
If I'm all of them negative things,
they're not going to they're not going
to do that anymore. And if they do, then
it's it's then it's they're talking about themselves,
which would explain why they would waste
such time. It's quite smart if you think about it. So, yeah. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
You can't beat a nice Coke and a nice popcornie. I [Music] stop
just went to Amsterdam just cuz I went.
What the [ __ ] [ __ ] obsessed.
These people need to be [ __ ] sectioned.
Imagine going on a holiday the same.
Imagine going to the same place as me
just cuz I went. [ __ ] hell. Jesus Christ.
That's crazy. Is it
just cuz I went m
cuz I went.
What do you m [Music] [ __ ]
You people really need to call it a day.
You really need to call it a day. Some
of you people, bro,
obsessed on YouTube every day calling
people what you are yourselves. What do
you get out of it?
I don't get why people
[ __ ] do this [ __ ] man. [ __ ] so mad.
I've never had so many people jealous of
me. I don't know whether to feel that
happy about it or
I don't know if I feel happy about it or
creeped out by it. I'm not entirely sure, but
No, I don't get wound up at all.
No, I don't get wound up at all. Wound
up on what? A bunch of self projectors.
People talking about themselves don't
wind me up.
You don't wind me up. You're talking about yourselves.
What's winding somebody up? Is somebody
talking about you whilst they're on
holiday for 11 minutes? That's what you
call winding someone up.
having to [ __ ] talk about someone for
11 minutes whilst they're on holiday in
a video. That's That's definitely wound up.
You don't mind me up, bro. You people
talk about yourselves
every day. Skin, ugly, m You talk about yourselves.
I just think it's sad to see people talk
about themselves like that.
It's horrible to see people talk so
low of themselves.
It's depressing, bro.
People putting themselves down,
calling themselves skin, calling
themselves moners. It's horrible seeing
people talk about themselves like that.
Yeah. YouTube's your whole life.
Yeah. Only to people where only people
that ain't got a life but YouTube like
you and him. Yeah. Only to low lives
like you and him. But not in the real
world. Nah. Things are fine, bro. Got a
better life, got more money, got more
life experiences. YouTube's not my life
like it is yours.
Nah, YouTube's not my life like it is
you little mongos.
Sat on YouTube every day for a living.
Says a lot about your life. Oh, wait.
You ain't got one.
Sad little mongos. That's why people
don't come on here anymore and entertain
you little mongos
much anymore because you're just all
self projecting little mongos
sat on [ __ ]
YouTube [ __ ] mongos.
I ain't got a [ __ ] life, man.
Sh YouTube ain't going to lie.
So when are you people going to get a life anyways?
When are you people going to get off of
YouTube and get a life? You virgin boy
lo J followers. When are you actually
going to get a life? Go get laid.
I might go out on Friday. Maybe
you people are sat on YouTube waiting
for people to go live all day.
You are sat on YouTube all day waiting
for people to go live.
Nah, your life ain't better than mine,
mate. No, it [ __ ] ain't. If your life
was so good, you wouldn't be on YouTube
now. Type him.
Nah, your life ain't great, mate. Trust
me, it is not a lot better than mine. I
got more money than you. I'm better
looking than you. I'm younger than you.
No way. Is your life better than mine?
Nay. You wish it was.
Your life ain't great, bro. That's why
you're sat on YouTube waiting for me to
go live every day. Trust me, your life
ain't that great. That's why you people
do what you do. because you ain't got a life.
It's not reacting. It's not being wound
up. It's telling you what you people do.
You people don't have a life,
you know. Yeah. All you have is YouTube.
That's yourself that you're talking
about. Again, self projecting.
Everything you do, you talk about yourselves.
That's your life. You're on YouTube
right now speaking to me. You're talking
about yourself. You ain't got nothing in
life. You middleage [ __ ] p you
[ __ ] old pensioners, you got nothing.
You got no money. You got no friends.
You've never been laid. That's why you
come on YouTube every day cuz you've got
nothing and no one.
That's why you do it. That's literally
why you people can't get off of YouTube
for one day. I've been off of YouTube
for days, weeks. You can't get off of
YouTube because YouTube is all you have.
Literally, that's the difference. You
can't take one day off of YouTube. I'm
coming off of here for weeks before
YouTube and projecting as all you little
[ __ ] mongos have, matey.
Yeah, you're laughing at me. Why are you
laughing at me? I'm better looking than
you. I'm younger than you. Nope. You're
laughing at yourself,
you know. No, no, no. You're laughing at yourself.
And it's the same thing as Virgin Boy.
The more you do this, the more it shows
your life up.
The more you do all of this, Yeah. it
shows what you're about. It shows your life.
The more you come on here and you do it,
the the more it shows your life.
You know, I'm sinking, bro. I'm better
looking than you will ever be. You can't
even show your face.
Again, self projecting,
bro. Again, self projecting
was like we was talking about earlier. Self projecting.
You can't show your face cuz you're too
ugly. Self projector. All you people on here are
is old skin, ugly, no life, no money, no
job. That's why you come on here self
projection every day.
That's your lives, fat and ugly. That's
why you come on here. Because if you
wasn't, you wouldn't come on here. If
your lives were great, you wouldn't be
on here. You're fat, ugly weirdos. They
don't fit into society. Just like the
people in LJ's, Jimmy Jazz, all of these
people. Fat, ugly virgins. No money.
That's why they're coming here every
single day calling people skint cuz
they're the ones that are skint with no
money. Ugly old gamblers. Ugly ass
[ __ ] virgins. Ain't got no life to
piss in. Ain't got a pot to piss in.
Ain't got [ __ ] all. That's why they're
sat on YouTube all day every day. No
content on their [ __ ] channel. No
nothing because they're life's losers.
That's what they are. Simple. Ugly people
rafting. You people have never worked a
day in your life.
You fat ugly mongos who want benefits.
You're not fooling no one, mate.
You're not fooling no one. You ugly
people sat on YouTube every day. Do you
know what this should be called? The
ugly community. The ugly skin community.
Cuz that's what you people are.
Ugly ink skin ain't got a life.
ain't got a life. That's what you are.
It's all This is what it is with these
people, right? The fat, ugly skint [ __ ]
all come together and go for the person
that's younger and better looking than
them because they're fat and ugly. Fat,
ugly, rejected bastards. Never been seen
with a woman. Think of it. I've been
seen with more money, more women. You
little mongos have not been seen with
nothing cuz you ain't got nothing.
YouTube's your whole life.
You ain't got nothing. [ __ ] jobless,
ugly, no money. And then you [ __ ] try
and come on here and talk about other
people that you don't know. All cuz
you're skint and ugly and fat and old.
That's why you come on here every day, bro.
My life sits on here, bro. I've got more
of a life than you will ever have,
bro. I've had a girlfriend and I've had
more women than you fat ugly people. Why
have none of you fat ugly people ever
been seen with a woman? Same question to
you fat ugly people that come on YouTube
every day. It's self projection. All
they do is self- project. No, I don't
sit at home and I don't go anywhere. I
go out every single day. You fat ugly
people have been sat on YouTube for
years with your ugly selves. You don't
go anywhere. You just talk about people
that's got a better life than you.
You're fat. You're ugly. You're skint.
You don't go nowhere. That's why you
talk about other people. I ain't
projecting, bro. I've done more in three
years than you've done in your whole
life. If I don't want to go out drinking
for a couple of weeks, that's on me.
Do you know what I'm saying? I'm talking
about you people. I'm talking about you
fat ugly people. I've been seen with
more money than you. You ain't been seen
with more money than me. I have been
seen with more women than you. You's
never been seen with a woman. I'm
talking about you fat ugly people. I'm
talking about you fat ugly people that
are on YouTube every day. I'm not
talking about me. I'm talking about you.
I'm talking about the fat ugly rejected
skinned weirdos. Yeah. You don't like
it? Yeah. The truth hurts. Yeah. The
truth hurts. The truth hurts. The truth hurts, bro. Yeah.
I haven't been I haven't been out
drinking for months. I was out three weeks ago.
And what do you do on YouTube? On
[ __ ] YouTube projecting your ugly fat
lives onto people. And what have you
been doing on [ __ ] YouTube with no
money, no life? Every time someone talks
about you people, you don't like it.
You're a bunch of middleage ugly people.
That's why you can't join the hangouts.
You ain't got [ __ ] all to your
middle-aged ugly lives. That's why you
can't come in the hangouts. It's the truth.
I show women because I can get women and
I'm not ugly like you people. I showed
women cuz I can get them unlike you.
You're too ugly. You people are too
Yeah. So what? I can go out now if I
want to. I show women cuz I'm not ugly
like you and I can get them. I'm not
ugly and old like you. You people are
part your sale by date, lad.
You know what I'm saying, lad? You're
post by date. You're all ugly. You all
skin. You're all ugly on YouTube. And it
proves it every single day. I've had a
girlfriend. You've never had a
girlfriend. Stop self-projecting.
Stop self-projecting. I'm not. Why don't
you be quiet, you [ __ ] ugly [ __ ]
You are skint, you fat, ugly skinned
bastards. That's why you always run away
when you get so money. You always quiet
when you show money. Cuz you are the
skinned ones. You are the skinned, ugly,
self-p projecting little lowife little
weirdos that can't even leave your
house. You know what? I'm going to
change the title of this video. Yeah,
[ __ ] it. I'm going to change the title.
Let's talk about this community. You
people have never had a girlfriend.
You're too fat and ugly. Fat, ugly
little weirdos that come on here every day self-projecting.
You ugly skin [ __ ] montas.
No life, never had a girlfriend. That's
you people. That's you ugly people. All
I'm saying is I've been seen with women.
I've been seen with money. None of you
ugly people have.
None of you ugly people have been seen
with money. None of you ugly people have
been seen with women. None of you ugly
people that sit on YouTube all day have
never been seen with any of these things
because you don't have it.
You're self-projecting ugly fat skinned
weirdos. It's the truth. It's not being
nasty. It's saying what what you are.
Skin ugly losers with nothing.
Fat ugly peep. Yeah, you are stinking.
That's why you've never been seen with a
woman. You are stinking. That's why you
can't get laid.
Because you are ugly. Ugly bastards. And
this is why you go for me. This is why
you go for somebody half your age.
Because you people are ugly. Ugly and
fat. Just like Bomb, just like Graycat.
Stinking ugly fat [ __ ] bully victims.
That's literally you. That's literally
you people. You're talking about
yourselves. But okay, I will prove that
I'm talking about you people cuz I'm
going to put the link out. Let me put
the link out and I'm going to prove I'm
talking about you people. Okay, I'm
projecting. Okay, fair enough. That's your opinion,
right? I'm going to prove to you that
I'm talking about you people. Fat. Okay,
let me say it again. Fat, ugly skin
ain't got no money. I'm going to put a
link up. Yeah, one second.
I'm going to prove I'm talking about
you. One second.
I'm going to make sure I'm talking about
you skinned ugly fat middle-aged weirdos
that's never seen a woman naked. One second.
Look, I need to close this. Right. I am
talking about you people.
Talking about the fat, ugly weirdos that
can't get off of YouTube. The mongos.
I'm talking about you fat ugly mongos
that can't get off of YouTube. Come on.
Come on. You [ __ ] skin ugly fat
mongos. Come on. Let's have it [ __ ]
Come on. Let's have it at you fat ugly
bongo that's never been with a woman.
Let's have you. Come on. No more typing.
Everyone's welcome in the hangouts. I'm
going to prove I'm talking about you.
You fat ugly little bongo that ain't got
no money. You skinned people that can't
get off of YouTube.
Come on. Come on. You fat ugly skin
mongos. What you waiting for? Come on.
Exactly. Cuz you ain't got nothing. Woo!
I won again. Yeeha! Got the skin
self-reflecting ugly old men again.
Bye-bye. Thank you. Woo!
Rick Flair kind of woo. Woo! These
people ain't got no looks. Nobody
scared to join the hangouts. They can't
even join the hangouts cuz they're too
scared and too ugly.
They're [ __ ] too old and too ugly.
They're too old and too ugly. That's why
they can't try to hang out. They're too
old and too ugly. If who's why they want
to every day? Oh, I've had more women
than you will ever have, matey. Self
projecting. You're the virgin, not me.
You are a fat ugly virgin. It's not me.
I'm not the fat ugly skinned virgin like you.
Exactly. You can't show nothing cuz you
ain't got nothing. It shows I'm talking
about you people.
I'm not talking about myself. I'm
talking about you fat ugly [ __ ] that's
never been with a woman cuz you're too
ugly. I'm talking about you people.
I'm talking about you fat ugly [ __ ]
that ain't got nothing, no money.
Woo! Got you by the balls again. No
money, no life, no looks. Woo! Whoa!
No money, no looks, no life. And you
can't prove otherwise. And you can't
show me nothing. You know when someone
says yeah they can't tell you nothing.
These fat ugly skinned [ __ ] ugly people
no money no girlfriend can show me nothing. Sorry but
got him by the balls again. I've got
more money and better looks. They're
joined. They're scared to join the hangouts.
They ain't got nothing.
They ain't got nothing. These fat ugly
weirdos ain't got nothing.
No. Win the prize for not having a
girlfriend. I've already had a
girlfriend and I've been with more women
than you. Self rejecting again. You're
scared to join the hangouts.
I've got more money. I've been with more
women than you. What are you talking
about? I win the prize for having more
women than you and not being scared to
join a hangout. You're too scared to
How can we take people serious that are
scared to join a [ __ ] hangout, bro?
Come on. This is getting ridiculous.
Never in my life, bro, have I been so
scared and so bullied that I can't join a hangout.
Oh, Jesus [ __ ] Christ, bro. We need
to stop this [ __ ] today. I'm so much of
a loser that I can't even show my face
and show money.
Jesus Christ. Hey, bro. Guess what,
Vice? I'm not I'm not blocking these
accounts, lads. I'm going to let them
keep self projecting. I'm going to let
the fat ugly mongos waste their life
ejecting and we're going to change the
subject. That's what we're going to do
now cuz they've already showed they're
not going to join the hangouts. They're
too much of a loser. Ain't got no money,
ain't got no looks. So, yeah.
Anyways, moving on. And I'm not even
going to block them either.
I'm not even going to block them either keep typing.
and keep self-reflecting their life.
These quite ugly people. Anyways,
what better have you got for Saturday,
Steven Howard, man?
Jesus Christ, that was lovely, bro. You
doing any bets?
You know what? No, I did one last week,
actually, didn't I? Yeah.
I'll pick a good one for us if you want,
bro. I'll pick us out a good one if you want.
Fleetwood and cold chest is a banger.
No, bro. The [ __ ] butcher [ __ ] closed.
Oh, it's Tuesday today as well. Oh,
yeah. I said about Tuesday uh Tuesday
t-buds. Yeah. No, bro.
No, I will get one tomorrow. I'll get
one tomorrow. Yeah, tomorrow I'll get one.
>> Yeah, I'll do one. Yeah, I'll get up
tomorrow, bro. I'll be up nice and early.
Yeah, lovely, bro.
Like I said, I'm not blocking these
self-reflectors. We're just going to go
on to a complete different topic.
We're not addressing these fat, ugly
people anymore that's scared to join a
hangout. So, yeah. Colchester and Fleetwood.
We're not We're not listening to these self-reflectors
anymore. They ain't got no life but
YouTube. So yeah, Fleetwood and Colchester.
Fleetwood and Colchester, bro. Oh [ __ ]
Oh, I can open it. Oh, [ __ ] hell.
You're going to [ __ ] break, lad.
Yeah, bro. Do that bet. Yeah.
Yeah. Do that bet, bro. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Yeah, bro. Um,
and the other team, I'm not sure, bro.
Yeah, these little fat, ugly little
skint mongos just want a reaction.
They're not going to get one. Your next attention
attention. What I mean, what attention
you going to give me?
Yeah. I mean, but what attention are you
going to give me?
We're going to let these little self-
afflectors keep typing out about their
own life. Bless them.
Cuz we all know that the reality is
these people in their 40s and they ain't
got nothing. That's why they're sat on
YouTube every day cuz they ain't got
nothing. They're just fat ugly mongos.
They're not even worth reacting to these
little skin mongos.
They've been proven what they're about multiple times.
I mean, you're going to give me
attention. I mean, what are you going to do? So, yeah.
So, yeah, I'm going to pick the other
team as well, Stephen. However, I'm not sure yet.
Yeah, man. We're not blocking these
people. We're leaving them on here.
We're leaving these little
self-reflectors on here. Let them
self-relect their skintess. Let themsel
reflect their ugliness and their loneliness.
They'll realize um when they're on their
deathbed that all this projected and got
them nowhere, you know. So yeah. Yeah.
So yeah, I'll pick another one as well, lad. Yeah, man.
They've already got the link. They're
not joining. So, until they join, I'm
not entertaining them. I'm not even
reading their comments. They can keep
self-reflecting all they want. I'll put
the link out again.
But yeah, until they um
they can keep self-reflecting all they like.
I'm not entertaining them until they
actually want to join the hangouts.
Then I'm not I'm not I'm not replying to them, lad.
I'm not replying to these fat ugly bully
victims. So you going to you going to
come in the hangouts or not?
You going to come in the hangouts or not?
I feel so sorry for these people. Fat,
ugly, no life, never been with a woman,
no money. I feel so bad for them. I feel
bad for them, bro. Part of the reason,
you know, that's part of the reason why
I'm probably not going to even block them, lad.
You know, I've been seen with more
money, more women, more friends, better
looks. Do they not realize that self
projection is not going to change that?
I don't know why they do it.
These people been, you can tell they've
been bullied hard in their life, bro.
You can tell they've actually been
bullied so badly in their life. Maybe at school.
Jesus Christ. You can't even talk
properly. Yeah. Well, I'm talking now.
You can't even join the hangouts.
Yeah, I can't talk properly yet. You're
the one that can't join the hangouts.
Okay. Yeah. Stop self projecting.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. None of you
people have ever been with a woman. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Not anybody
in the world. I'm talking about you ugly mongos.
You ugly mongos have never been with a
woman. You ain't got no life. You got no
money. You've never been with a woman.
I'm talking about you mongos. I'm not
talking about people in the world. I'm
talking about you fat ugly mongos.
Anyways, why aren't any of you joining
the hangouts? What the [ __ ] There's a
link there. What are you scared of?
Scared to show your face cuz you're
ugly. scared to talk cuz you're
disabled. Can't show money. What a life
you people really, really, really have.
These people are such mongos.
Anyways, I actually am blocking them by
the way. They're ruining the chat, bro,
with a self projecting. The links there.
Yeah. All it is is just a bunch of
40year-old losers. They ain't got a
life. You do realize this, my [ __ ] All
of these people are just middle-aged
[ __ ] losers with nothing in life.
They got [ __ ] all in their life.
Literally, bro. They've literally got
nothing. Honestly, bro. Like, do you
know the only reason I've not been out
for a couple of weeks, bro, is just
because I've been like saving money and [ __ ]
It's only really because I've just been
saving money and just on a detox. So,
you know, I do it a couple of times a year.
Just I don't know. you get into the
routine of it. But it just shows what
these people really are, bro.
It really does. They ain't got nothing.
Seriously, bro, they ain't got nothing.
You know what I mean?
They're just jealous of me. That's what
they are. They're just jealous of me.
You can understand why I think that way,
don't you, Mike? If I'm being a bit OTT
and you know you think I'm talking about
you think I'm talking a bit of [ __ ] then
you know let me know bro just let me
know and um
just let me know and you know I'll
we'll see in it
just let me know and I'll [ __ ] be
like yeah I don't know man it seems it
seems these people are jealous just
because how they will just sit there and
do what they do all day every day to
someone that they don't know. Got to be
jealousy. It's got to be jealousy with
these people. I mean, what else is it,
bro? Like, what else is it all trolling aside?
You got someone on holiday can't shut up
about me, keep talking about me, you
know? What is it? If it ain't jealousy,
right? Like, come on.
It's [ __ ] madness.
These people are so jealous, man. It's unbelievable.
>> They need to get a life.
>> Hello, PJ. How you doing, lad? >> PJ.
>> Yeah, I'm all right.
>> Good. Good. Why are you upset tonight?
>> I don't know, man. I just think these
people on YouTube need to get a life.
>> Why? Why? What? What? Why they've got no
life? Can you explain to me why they
haven't got a life?
>> They just ain't got a life, do they?
>> What do they do? Just sit there all day
moaning like Lord Jay? >> Yeah.
>> You like Lord Jay's definitely skinned and he?
>> Yeah, you're skinned as well.
>> Am I? Yeah, I am actually skinn PJ now.
I've only got £249 left to my name. >> Why?
>> I'm skinn PJ. I can't help it. I've done
I've done my bollocks in. I've lost it
all in the casino this afternoon. >> Really?
>> Yeah. Ain't got a pot to piss in, lad.
But you know, you said you're doing
really well. You know, you said you're
doing really, really well. Yeah. And
you've saved some money. Can we have a
look at some of this money you've saved,
please, to prove that you're not lying?
>> I can't do that.
>> Why? It's cuz you've got them, isn't it?
>> No, cuz every time I show you money, you run away.
>> Nobody can run away.
>> It's about time you people started showing stuff.
>> I've shown my money, PJ.
>> It's about time you started showing stuff.
>> You look on my last stream.
>> I want to see women. I want to see
money. I want to see women. I want to
see money. Well, I've just shown you
money, PJ. I've admitted I've got £249.
I can't help it if I got no more than
that. I'm skint.
>> So, how much did you lose?
>> I lost about four and a half grand this afternoon.
>> Stop talking [ __ ]
>> I'm not talking [ __ ] PJ. I'm in a real bad way.
>> No. How much did you lose?
>> No, I didn't really gamble today. I I I
gambled a little bit on the pub
machines. I made about [ __ ] 25 quid.
I didn't get involved and [ __ ] off.
>> So, you've got 240 So, you've got 240 left.
>> No, PJ. I've got a lot more than that.
I'm taking the piss. But PJ,
>> how much do you have then?
>> I've got about I've got over five grand,
PJ. That's all you need to know.
>> Yeah, of course you do.
>> Okay, PJ, I've got PJ. I've got this the
statement right now. If I can block out
my account and bring that state in my
account balance, PJ.
>> So, I've already owed you by showing
money. I don't want to destroy you and make you
>> Well, yes, I do, PJ. And you can't
handle the jealousy.
handle the jealousy. I love it, bro.
>> Well, you are jealous, PJ. You got about
the people being jealous, but you're
jealous. I've got five grand in your skin.
>> Yeah, I'm jealous, bro. I'm so jealous. Yeah.
>> Yeah, you are jealous. You fuming, didn't you?
>> You don't have five grand to me.
>> Yes, I do, PJ. Cuz you're jealous. Cuz
you keep telling about it.
>> Five grand. Of course you do. How would
have you got 5,000?
>> Why are you jealous of my £5,000, PJ?
>> How would have you got five grand,
>> PJ? It's for you to know. This is for me
to know and it's for you to find out.
>> No, you don't have five grand. That's
>> Yes, I do, PJ. And it breaks your heart.
Don't break my heart, my achy achy
heart. I've got no PJ.
>> No, your skin.
>> No, but PJ, come on, bro. I'll show you
some money, right? And I I'll give you a
deal. I'll show you what I've got now,
right? And I'll show you my building
society if you can show me at least a
grand. I've already shown you a grand before. >> Pardon?
>> I've shown you a grand before.
>> No, no, no, no. PJ, that
>> Yes, I have. I showed you before and you ran away.
>> PJ, today's a new day, PJ.
>> No, no. Yeah, yeah, it is a new day.
It's about time you show me too bad. Yeah,
>> cuz you're self projecting, PJ, cuz
>> Okay. How much do you have on you now?
>> Well, you you're going to have a look
now, PJ. Now, I'm going to do my side of
the deal, right, PJ? and I will show you
£5,000 if you can show me at least
£1,000. That's being cash, PJ. It can be
on a bank statement or something live
stream. Just cover your account number,
you know. Don't dox yourself. Obviously,
you've done that before. You know, go
from there. So, you ready then, PJ, to
see the money? Do you want to money, PJ?
I'll even count it out. There's 500 in
cash in notes, PJ. Yeah, in paperwork.
Right. This is my bum change. This is
the only bum ch I've got money, but this
is my bum change. It's basically money I
can spend, PJ. Yeah,
>> bum change. Have you ever heard of bum change?
>> So, there we go. Camera's on the wrong
way. So, you've I've docked myself yet
again. Get the [ __ ] in there. Here you
go, PJ. Are you ready?
>> Yes. Good. 500 then. And I can even
count it all out, PJ. Stage by stage.
And there's £246
in there, PJ.
>> So, you are £700.
>> I've shown you over about £723
there. Can you show me £1,000, PJ?
>> You have to show me two grand.
>> No, no, no. PJ,
>> show me.
>> You have to show me two grand.
>> I'm not all about in cash cuz not not
every [ __ ] [ __ ] has money in the
house, PJ. It's not smart. Even if you
just do what?
>> You have to show me two grand. >> Pardon?
>> No, no, no, no. PJ, I won't show you any
more money unless you can show me £1,000.
>> Cuz you ain't got
>> I guarantee you, PJ, you haven't got £1,000.
>> You ain't got it in it. Yeah,
>> PJ £226 on live [ __ ] stream, man. And
even docs my beautiful looking face. >> So,
why can't you show me £1,000, PJ?
>> Because I've already shown you money before.
>> No, no, Cuz you're [ __ ] skin. You're
just bullshitting. You're trying to show
off to the internet, aren't you?
>> Yeah, I'm skin. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, aren't
you, DJ? You're jealous.
>> Yeah, I'm
>> PJ. I don't blame yourself. All you got
to do is have a bank statement, own us
all. Prove you've been saving money.
>> I've already owned you all multiple times.
>> You haven't owed no one, PJ. I've
>> I've owned you all multiple times.
>> You haven't owned no one, PJ.
>> I've shown you six grand,
>> PJ. That was [ __ ] 5 months ago. It
don't count now. It's gone.
>> I showed you six grand, you know.
>> Okay, PJ, have you got the six grand
today? Yes or no?
>> Mate, it doesn't matter. I made you run away.
>> PJ, it doesn't matter.
>> PJ, have you
>> I showed you six grand and you ran away.
>> No one ran away, PJ. You're selfjecting again.
>> No, you ran away. Why did you run away?
>> No runs away. You ran away from Prime and me.
>> You ran away from me. You self.
>> Why are you taking the fiberactic cable
so seriously, bro?
>> So, Timmy, why are you skin?
>> Why can't you show me a grand?
>> Because I don't need to show you a grand.
>> Cuz you haven't got a grand, have you, Peter Belly?
>> Okay. I haven't got a grand. Okay.
>> Well, I know you haven't got a grand cuz
you'd show it right now on your bank statement.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> I You keep telling yourself that when it
comes to money, I don't
>> I know, man. He needs to get laid. Do
you know nonslegs and Timmy? They need
to get laid. They're going to die
virgin. Heavy my £5,000. Ain't you l
nons and timmies going to die of virgin?
They're going to die one. If
>> me and Nons legs donate you 40 quid, PJ,
that's more money than
>> I've already got over a grand OB7. I've
already got over a grand and I'm not
showing you nothing cuz every single time
>> every single time every single time you
get shown money you run away. RB7 I've
already got over £1,000 and I'm not
showing you nothing.
I'm not showing you £10, you know. So,
and I and I never lost a subleting house
and I've got other ways to make money as
well, mate. So, try again. And I've got
more money than you and I've got over a
grand. And I'm not showing you skint
people nothing. I'm not showing you skin
self-reflecting people nothing because
every single time you get shown money,
you run away. And also I didn't lose the
house cuz of you people. I lo I lost the
house four years after.
Nope. Don't do that either. You don't
know how I make money. So exactly. I've
got more money than you will ever have,
Skid Boy. So don't even come on here and
start talking about what people have and
what people don't have. You people ain't
got nothing. Every single time you get
show money, you run away because you
ain't got nothing. You don't even have 1.2 grand.
And that's not what I do. You don't even
know how I make money.
Bro, you ain't even got money. You skin
bastard. Bro, you ain't even got money,
lad. You ain't got nothing. You're
skint. Every single time you get money,
you run away. I know you like to forget
that, bro, but no one else forgets it.
You ain't even got no money. And bro, I
didn't lose the subleting house because
of you people. You little skinned people
on benefits that can't show nothing. No,
I'm not showing. Listen, nature guy, I'm
telling you why I'm not showing this
Timmy nothing. Because months ago, I
showed him £1,300.
Yeah, I showed him £1,300 and he ran away.
He literally ran away. So why would I
waste my time again?
It's about time these people started
showing stuff. Their face, their money,
their life. It's about time these people
started showing stuff.
Do you know what I'm saying, bro? Do you
know what I mean?
It's about time these people started showing money.
So, and I don't even do [ __ ] delivery
jobs. You don't know how I make money,
bro. Listen, like I've said, if I've got
so if I've got so less money, why every
time I've showed you money, you run away?
Why have I made you run away at the
money game multiple times? Then, why
have I kept making you run away? Because
you ain't got no money. Okay, I'm on
less than minimum wage. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. So, why is it every time I
show you money, you run away? because
you ain't got none. So you can come on
here every day and call people what you
are yourself skint. But it's not going
to change the fact that you are the
skint ones. You have been shown money
multiple times and every time you get
shown money, you run away cuz you ain't
got none. Cuz you want benefits. You're
on £300 a month. You're £300 a month
boy. Cuz you ain't got no money. That's
why I don't show you skint
self-reflectors with nothing money
because you're talking about yourselves.
You're a waste of our time. You skid
little bongos of benefits are a waste of
our time. That's why. You know what I'm
saying, bro? You're a waste of our time.
You people have got nothing. We don't
need to waste our time showing you
nothing, bro. I've got money right here.
I've literally got money right here. And
I am not showing you nothing.
I'm not showing somebody that ain't got
nothing. Buddy, I'm not playing your
self-p projecting games.
We got a bit of bum change here. I'm not
showing you [ __ ] all. It's about time
you Skint [ __ ] started showing stuff.
You get me, lad?
You know what I'm saying? But uh
actually, it's about time. Well, wait.
I'll tell you how. How much did I show, Timmy?
Um, no. I'll be real. How much was it?
It was £1,200.
So he has to show me £2.4,000,
not £500. He has to show me £2.4,000.
You know, all of this your skin show
money and stuff. It's just self-p
projecting games. It's boring.
It's boring, bro. Bro, you don't even
have 1.2 grand. You ain't even got none.
That That's That's more embarrassing,
bro. That's why you've never had a
woman. Cuz you are skint. You don't even
get 1.2 grand. That's why you're still a
virgin. Self projecting. That's why
you're still a virgin. If you've got all
of this money, why don't you come in and
show us your money, Mr. Rich Boy that
ain't got nothing. Okay, let me put the
link up. Right, let me put the link up. Come on.
And another thing, let me fun fact
anyways for this little weirdo. Firstly,
I don't get 1.2 grand a month. I get
more than that. and I get more than you
because you ain't got no money and I put
the link up and if you want to show me
money, you can. If you want to come in
and show me money, we'll play the money
game. Yeah. Firstly, you don't have no
money. That's why you're still a virgin,
firstly. And second of all, let me tell
you something about London. Do you want
to know a fun fact about London? Do you
people want to know a fun fact about London?
Yeah, you you don't pay nothing. You
ain't got nothing, you loser. Come in
the hangouts and show us your money now. Listen,
come and show us your money now. Stop
talking [ __ ] and come on. I'll show you
your bank statement. Come on. Come on.
You come in now and show us your money.
that you don't have, loser, because you
ain't got no money. You come in and
we'll talk. I'll show you my bank
statement. I think I can't be any more
fairer than that. Listen, let me tell
you something, [ __ ] Anyways, because
this is lack of life experience since
you want to talk about 1.2 grand, 1.3
grand. You do realize that most people
in London by the time they've paid stuff
off, they don't even have 300 pound for
the month. You wouldn't know that
because you're on benefits on 300 pound
a month. But you do realize all of these
people that are on 2.5 grand a month,
they don't have anything by the time
they've paid everything. You do realize
that if you weren't such a benefit loser
skin scared to join the hangouts, you
would know that you skint bastard. Yeah,
they have to [ __ ] pay rent, bills,
dental fees, you [ __ ] [ __ ] So the
time they get paid, by the time they've
paid everything off, bro, they're lucky
if they've got £300.
And you know how I know this stuff? Cuz
I've looked into this. I have looked
into this. If you got £1,200 a month,
anybody in London would think that
you're a [ __ ] baller.
Everyone in London would actually think
that you're a baller. If you had £1,200
disposable money, even in London, bro,
people would think that you're falling
because people that worked are not even
left with that after they paid everything.
But because you're on benefits and you
ain't got no money, you don't know that.
You don't know how the real [ __ ]
world [ __ ] works. Skint bastard.
You skin self-projecting bastard.
I'm talking about delivery, bro. [ __ ]
I ain't [ __ ] done a delivery job for [ __ ] years.
[ __ ] years. Months. I'm talking about
years. Months and months and months.
Bro, I make [ __ ] money without having
to [ __ ] do anything. Worry about your
own lives. Your own skin benefit lives.
Stop talking about other people that you
don't know. Worry about your own skint
benefit lives. You understand what I mean, bro?
worry about your own skin poverty lives
that you live and stop trying to talk
about other people that you don't know.
You know what I mean?
And let me tell you something, bro. I
was on £700 a month before years ago and
I still got more [ __ ] than you. I
could have [ __ ] £100 and I'd still
have more money than you people. Well,
saying that I would anyways because you
ain't got no money, but do know what I mean.
Listen, listen, listen, listen, bro.
Bro, they are skint. They're
self-reflectors. They are skint.
They've got nothing. That's why they
come on here every day. I know I'm
right. I know I'm right because they are
nobodyies with nothing. That's why they
come on here because they're nobodyies.
They've got no money to do anything. I
wanted to take a break from the [ __ ]
drinking. Take a break from the
drinking. Chill out. save a bit of money
for other things, which I do three, four
times a year regardless. Do you know
what I'm saying? But these people are on
it all day for years cuz they ain't got
nothing. They ain't got no money.
They're sat on YouTube [ __ ] no money.
[ __ ] skint fat ugly people that ain't
got a life trying to talk about other
people they don't know.
[ __ ] £100 to your name. Ah, [ __ ]
that, bro. £100 to your [ __ ] name.
Well, let's just hope you get paid soon
then, isn't it?
[ __ ] £100 until when?
And another thing, bro, like I was just
saying to you, even if somebody gets
three grand a month in London or two
grand a month in London, they're worse
off than someone on benefits. When they get paid,
when they get paid, oh [ __ ] bro,
they're going to have less than someone
on benefits after they've paid
everything. You [ __ ] idiot. If
somebody is is working in London and
they're left with £1,200 at the end of
the month, I would be very, very surprised.
Most people are left with like £300,
400, 500, 600.
People that work are not left with that
kind of money every month after they've
paid everything. You [ __ ] So in the
end, the people that work are worse off.
But again, you wouldn't know that cuz
you're on benefits. So,
but unless they live with their parents,
then obviously that's a different story.
But you know, it shows they don't know
anything about life. They don't know
anything about life, bro.
You know what I mean?
And I got 1,600 this month and I got
1,600 last month
cuz of um you know, I won some football
bets and [ __ ] So what? Why? Why do you
care what people get anyways? Huh?
I don't do no [ __ ] delivery jobs.
What the [ __ ] You don't know how I get
[ __ ] money. I don't even work. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
You people have got some serious issues
on this [ __ ] So, how much do you get
paid when you get paid again, Bob? These
people in this community have got some
serious issues, lad.
Uh, no. I just won that football bet,
but that's for my haircut and [ __ ] I
need to go get my haircut soon. Yeah.
So, how much do you get paid at the end
of the month anyways?
Yeah, but you're on £300 a month. You
ain't got no money, bro. I've literally
put the link up for you and you can't
even join. You ain't got no money.
You're skin. I don't know why you're
laughing. Yeah, I won some football
bets. You ain't got no money. I put the
link up and you can't even join. I said
to you, I'll play the money game with
you one more time. I'll embarrass you
one more time. If you really want to get
embarrassed, I'll do it one more time.
I'll do it just for you. Show us all
your money. Show us all your money.
You can't because you ain't got no
money. Just like most of the people on
here, they ain't got no money. Just like
Timmy. Just like you. You ain't got no
money. That's why you go on about money.
Because you ain't got none.
You know what I'm saying, bro? It's
because you ain't got no [ __ ] money.
Cuz you ain't got none. It's so obvious.
You know what I mean?
It's [ __ ] a madness, bro.
You talk about money cuz you ain't got
none. It's so obvious.
You ain't got no money.
Sad as [ __ ] man. And then you got to
grow up and get a life. Some of you people, bro.
Yeah. Not anymore, bro.
Yeah. Not anymore, bro. I don't have
that kind of money anymore. But I've
still I've still got a couple of grand.
Yeah, I've still got a couple of grand.
But not like that, matey. So what? It
doesn't matter, does it? So what, bro? Yeah,
I've got a couple of thousand, bro.
That's good. What the [ __ ]
These people ain't got nothing. Obviously
there's skin on here. Bob, listen.
What's What's their excuse? I'm on a
detox. I'm trying to save a bit of money
for something. That's why I've been on
it. I'll be out again soon. I'll be out
drinking again soon.
These people are on YouTube all day,
every day. Cuz they are skinted. You
understand? All day every day. For what
reason? I already told you my reason. The [ __ ]
You would love two grand. Yeah, man.
Bro, it was hard trying to get that
money back, but I done it
cuz I'm too lazy. I don't want to work, lad.
Yeah, I've got about I've got about two grand
and a bit, but that's it. I don't need
to show money to anyone. I'm not showing
nothing to these skinned people.
But um yeah, I used to have a lot of
money, but I don't anymore. So simple.
Cuz I'm going some, you know, the thing
is I'm going somewhere New Year's Eve as
well. I'm going out of London New Year's
Eve. Like it's not the fact I could go
out every week if I wanted to
and make the money back if I really
wanted to, but I can't be bothered with
it, bro. Like that's, you know what I mean? Well, yeah.
You don't need to know what car I drive.
So, you get you get £1,300 a month, Bob.
You know this guy here, this stupid
little [ __ ] trying to say £1,200 a
month. £1,200 a month for a single
person is still good. And I get more
than that. Secondly, and that is still
good because most people that work are
not left with £1,200 at the end of the
month. Most people that work have got
nothing. They've literally got [ __ ] all.
You know, you know that time they pay
their rent, gas and electric, they've
got nothing again, unless they live with their parents.
The whole point is you do not pay rent.
You do not pay rent.
And if you have £1,200 after your bills
and [ __ ] that is still a decent amount of money.
You live in a shared house and don't pay bills.
If you if you if you've if you don't
have to pay gas and electric,
right, and you and you're left with £1,200,
then I mean, at the end of the day, bro,
it's still okay, you know?
How is £,200 hardly anything? It's even
decent in London. What are you talking
about? See, this is how you know these
people are fantasists.
This is how you know these people on
here are just complete and out of fantasists.
They really, really, really are. I mean,
there's people out there that live off
[ __ ] 80 pound a [ __ ] week.
50 a day.
[ __ ] knows, man. [ __ ] knows.
I don't know, bro. I don't know.
It's only money at the end of the day, bro.
And I used to go out every week, twice a
week, even before I had the house.
And I was on like 800 pound a month. How
I done it, I don't know how I done it,
but I done it.
So, it's not because of that. I still
have money if I want to go out.
I done it before I even when I was on
less money, bro. And I used to get like
when I used to speak to LT, I used to be
on like £800 a month. And I still used
to go out and I still used to drink. I
don't know how I done it, but I did. Simple.
Do you know the thing is you know the
bad thing about this is no matter what
money you get, you always adjust to it.
You can get 1,200. You think that's a
lot. You can get three and then you
don't. You can get three grand. You
think it's a lot and then you don't.
No matter what money you get, you
adjust. That's why it doesn't really
matter what what people get, what people don't get
because no matter what you get, you just
get used to it anyways, high or low. So,
it doesn't really matter. There was a
time, bro, I was getting three grand a
month and that weren't that was getting
to the point where that weren't even enough.
You don't need to know what I do. It's
none of your business what I do.
Yeah, I kind of missed the pubs as well,
bro. I might go out on Friday. I don't know.
I might go out on Friday, lad. I might.
I might. I might.
I might, bro. I don't know.
I don't know, man. No, I need to go
cinema on Friday because I can't be
bothered with it, bro, anymore.
The [ __ ] women, the [ __ ] I can't
be asked with it. I can't be annoyed
with it. I got money here so I can get
my hair done and [ __ ] I just can't be
Ah, the strangers chapter 2. Yeah.
So, how much how much? So, okay, Bob, do
you think £1,400 um is enough for the
month for a single person?
Do you think that's enough for a single person?
Nah, it's not as easy as that, bro.
It's not as easy as that. These women
are stuck up. It's not as easy as that.
No, it's not as easy as that, bro.
It's really, really not as easy as that.
It's not as easy as that, lad.
Okay. What about 1,600?
Off the bills and stuff. Yeah.
Yeah, that is enough. That's got to be enough. 1,600,700. Yeah.
just I won some football bets and stuff.
So, it built it built my um it built my
money back up
like what I I knew what I was doing. I
was careful, you know. I knew like to
win some football bets and be careful
and stuff. So, then I'll have even more
when I decide to go out and then the
money will last longer. You see? So
I mean there's tricks to there's tricks
but it is it is a yeah
but what I was saying lad is um
yeah it's not as easy to pull
They're all stuck up [ __ ]
here. But I mean, I do want to go out
for a drink anyways. You know, they are
just they're just [ __ ] to women here. So,
you know what I mean?
But I don't give a [ __ ]
You know how it is, isn't it?
Yeah. So it's good, isn't it? 1,600.
It's all right. It 1,500,600.
That's what you need to do. You need to
sort of like try to build your money up somehow.
But yeah, it's not as easy to pull here,
Bob. The women are just [ __ ] here. So,
proper like time wasters and [ __ ]
You've seen some of my approaches
before, haven't you, Bob Bills? You've
seen some of my approaches before. No.
Why not try Chinese? H
You've seen them before, ain't you, Bob? My approaches.
Oh, I've got a mad one. Do you want me
Do you want me to show you? I've got a
mad one. Yeah. That I got from 3 years
ago. I might upload it and Yeah. If I
I'm going to show you it now. Yeah. I'm
going to upload it and show you it now.
I'll show you it. Yeah.
This is what we're dealing with in this country. One second.
So what you think £1,500 for the month is enough? Yeah,
depends. It Yeah.
And the thing is when you go out, you
need some money. You need to build up
money cuz you don't know who you're
going to meet. And if you need to go on
a date and stuff, that's why I like to
like I always stop for like 6 weeks,
three times a year to try and build
money up because you just don't know,
you know, emergencies and stuff. I mean,
I've spent, like I said, I've spent £700
on a night out before, so
back when Peter Bennett was rich. So
obviously that would never happen again
because it's ridiculous. But you get the
point, bro. More the long along the
lines of like maybe 200.
I'll show you anyways, bro.
All right. Want to send you a Yeah.
Get in the bed. [ __ ] with my Bish.
One second. What the [ __ ] Virgin boy.
There you go.
You need to show me at least a grand.
Who the [ __ ] that [ __ ] think he is? Hey,
boy. The best shin
in the [ __ ]
Skin in the bed with no b.
Do you like that? Grezy
skin in the bed s in it, mate.
See, that's one of my approaches from years ago.
How you crazy? How you going to lose it?
See, Bob, they're they're just not
interested in this country.
They're just not interested in this country.
They're not interested in this country, are it?
Yeah, if you have like two grand in your
bank, you can go out drinking every you
can go out drinking every week in it
once you've built up a bit of money. Yeah.
Lost the wall in it.
They just aren't interested in this country. Bob,
can't believe you got £100 left. What
the [ __ ] did you spend your money on, bro?
What the [ __ ] did you spend it on?
But it's long now. Like I'm trying to
save but it's so long, bro. Like trying
to save is so long. She said, "Oh, I'm
not interested in getting to know anyone."
Yeah. She just said, "Oh, I'm not
interested in getting to know anyone.
They're just not interested in this
country, Mike. And it
Yeah, but the thing is I've got to like
I got to save now, bro. You know, the
thing is it's so [ __ ] it's so long to
wait around for money now. Oh my god,
it's [ __ ] long, bro.
See, back when I used to do the sublet
and it used to be different dates when I
used to get the money. But it's so long
having to wait around for money, bro.
It's [ __ ] long. But it's all right.
You know, it's life in it.
Once I go out again, I'll be going out
every week, so it's all good, bro.
Oh, it is so long though, bro. like [ __ ] hell.
This just like month to month in it.
But the reason I can save is cuz I've
saved many times before. So
yeah, I've saved many times before.
So it's not a problem to me, bro.
I get birthday money as well. So,
I'll be all good, bro. Don't you worry about that.
It's such a benefit though. You know,
when you don't go out drinking, you save money.
No [ __ ] from women. you're more
stable because you ain't drunk. It just
seemed like a win-win. You know, if you
give up for like six weeks and then go
back to it.
I had to do it before, bro, to [ __ ]
build my [ __ ] money up even when I
had the house.
You should do it. You should do it three
times a year, lad.
And I got Yeah, you got Christmas coming
up as well. So
So I just like would rather the money
for like other things
in case, you know.
Oh, I used to waste a lot of money
gambling, but I used to win a lot and I
done good stuff with the money, you know.
So, how much? So, you get £1,300 a month
and how much and how much bills have you
got out of that? How much bills you have
come out of that?
What? You get £1,300 a month?
>> Yeah. [ __ ] You get more than me then.
You get more than me.
Yeah. So, you get more than me. See,
with me, I I'd rather
It sounds mad, but I'd still rather not
have the house, you know?
Okay. Yeah, it might take a little bit
longer to save and whatever, but I mean
I don't know, man. I don't really care, you know? Yeah.
What OCD do you have?
Yeah, but you can still go out drinking
with £1,300 a month. Yeah, but
Yeah, but you can still go out with £39
a month, bro. What the [ __ ]
Yeah, I knew somebody that had that OCD.
Yeah, I knew somebody that had Yeah.
So, if you got no bills, how come you
only got £100 left?
What the [ __ ] did you spend it on?
I'd rather just build my money up before going out.
I don't know. I'm funny, bro. I'm just
funny like that.
I just like to have like [ __ ] you
know what I mean? Money. So, I'd rather
just build it up.
I might go out next month. I don't know,
bro. It's October, is it? Next month.
It's my birthday next month. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, I've been living off like 50 pound a week.
No, I'm not going out Friday, bro. Nah,
I need to build some money up.
I'm going away soon as well. I'm going
away on November. I don't. Nah, bro.
I'd rather build my bank account up a bit more.
I'm just funny like that, bro. I swear
to God, I'm funny like that.
And I'll enjoy it more as well. So,
let's say 6 weeks. Yeah. No,
that Finnish woman's gone quiet. Greasy.
That woman from Finland's gone quiet.
Yeah, she got a bit quiet.
Why is that? Go and ask her, bro. Don't ask me.
Don't ask me, lad. Ask her.
What kind of anxiety have you got, Bob? Yeah.
[ __ ] women, mate.
So, what you get like panic attacks? I
don't really get anxiety, mate.
Nah, not really, bro. Nah.
Yeah. I don't know when I'll be out again, bro.
I've only got two bills that come to £50.
See, Grezy, you don't believe I can
save, do you?
Does it Doesn't it make more sense what
I'm doing, Greasy? building money up
before I go out again
just for like other priorities and [ __ ]
I think it makes more sense, don't you?
Yes, it does.
It doesn't make sense, bro.
There's so many negative mongos on here,
isn't it, Grezy? So many negative mongos.
I might give Greavvesy one of my little stonies.
What do you reckon, Greavvesy?
I don't have any.
You want one of my lovely stonies? waves. Eight.
Let's get in the bed. Sit with no bed,
no money on it.
Why don't you want my little stonies,
Grezy? They're a lovely fit.
Greavvesy, these people said I'll never
have over a grand again.
Little do they know, hey, Grezy. Little
do they know.
Isn't that right, Grezy? Little do these
people know. E, little do these people
Isn't that right, Grezy? Little to the
little do these people know.
Grezy, do you think I've got over a grand?
Let's ask uh let's go ask Grievy. Greavvesy,
do you think I've got over a grand? We
uh do mate. Well, I've got 2K so
so you know Greavves. I got two grand. So,
I mean, it's good enough, isn't it, Reeves?
Why would I not have much more over a grand? Greavvesy. Huh?
Why would I have much more regret? Who's that?
Virgin boy is it?
Ain't that virgin boy? Is it
ain't that virgin [ __ ] Is it
ain't that virgin boy?
Is it greasy? That virgin [ __ ]
That ain't that skint virgin [ __ ] Is it
[ __ ] in the bed sip?
Greasy's watching the side, man. Yep.
Yep. Greavves is watching the sideman. Everyone
Greavves is watching the side men.
Boozy, why are you watching the side men? Huh?
Why do you keep watching the side men?
You like that little laugh, Grezy? Hay. [Laughter] ice cream. >> Yeah. anymore.
>> Well, guess what, Grezy? I'll be saving
some money here. Do you want to know how
many vouches I've got?
I've got a lot of vouches. Look, we
look how many vouchers I've got.
Look how many McDonald's I've got.
I'll be saving some wonder. [Music] movie
in in the [ __ ] bed. No bed in it.
Excuse the bed.
No. No. It's given the bed with no bed.
No bed with no money in it.
That's the one. Gre
in the bed sitting no bed. No money in it.
We don't pay no money in it. Busy
keeping the dead [ __ ] with no money in it.
You like that, Greavves?
Come on, Greavves. You like that, don't you?
Come on, Grezy. You like that, don't
you? Come on, Greasy.
Cover grievy. Don't take the piss, mate.
You like that, don't you?
Get in the bed [ __ ] with no bed in it.
I like Laney. You know,
Laney is a good woman. Do you like Laney? Yeah. [Music]
She helped me out, you know, with the
house and stuff. She said, "Oh, you've
seen me all right and stuff." I said,
"Yeah, mate. When I used to have it, I
don't have it anymore to give."
Do you know what I mean, G? It's a bit different when
you know you you don't have it to give anymore.
Oh, bless you then if you want to go out
and get on the vodka. Oh, bless.
Oh, bless you then if you want to go
Bless you then if you want to go and get
on the vodka. Oh, bless. Bless you then.
Yeah. So, I won't be spending no money tomorrow. Not
cuz I've got that McDonald's um thing, don't I? Yeah.
So that's nice. That is nice, bro. You know,
right, I'm gone. Yeah. Be back some other time.