[Music] My toe.
Yep. Hold on. All right. ate a burger. Nice
burger. I think you're doing Wednesday.
Well, not this this week, but like next week.
Yeah. Sending it. [ __ ] Wednesday,
birthday, [ __ ] Saturday. But oh,
I have to go to [ __ ] safe
houses. I don't know, man. Just like
something to do, but the weather's kind
of [ __ ] is
it? Be very interesting to see. I've heard this.
That's what I meant by like it's
um trying to find someone. It's like um
needs to make it literally like an
actual job. It's like an
actual Well, it's pretty much a
full-time [ __ ] job really, but you
don't get paid for it. That's what I
always used to think a lot of the times
when I used to go out. I used to think
ra like it's actually a madness. Like
it's actually like it's the same as
actually cuz you're going out and
sending it. Yeah.
You're going out sending it, bro. And
[ __ ] you don't get paid for it.
That's the thing. It's so not bad. Yeah.
be chilling straight. One minute the
weather's good and the next minute it's
[ __ ] sky. [ __ ]
hell. Your [ __ ] mind,
man. Make up your [ __ ] mind.
You know what somebody said to me before
that like to go
out two weeks in a
row approach like just send it two weeks
[ __ ] you know that two weeks in a
row. That's hard though.
not hard to do if we got
like we ain't got social anxiety like us
but like harder than you can actually
um be tired when as in like you will get tired very
quickly especially when you're not
drinking you get tired very [ __ ] quickly
after like the fifth or sixth month. But I went
out when I went out and I approached on [ __ ]
um last week. I think it was maybe the
week after. I can't remember exactly. I
got like two numbers. I was just
sober. We both replied, but be it be interesting. But
um Oh, imagine you done it like every
day for like a whole month. [ __ ] me.
[ __ ] me, man. That That would be long.
We should do it like every day from now until
April. Hey, bro. How you doing, man?
Yeah, I just been out sending it. Got
some numbers, got some replies, got some
dates scheduled. But I'm thinking of
sending it like Wednesday, Thursday,
Saturday, but not OB. I'm not going out
this week. I need to chill this week,
man. I got um stuff to do, but got my
passport sorted and that. But I don't
know, man. It' be interesting. But it's
so tiring. That's the thing. It's so
tiring. Not like I was just saying
before you join. It's not social anxiety
like that Virgin's got in Orington. not
that well that virgin as but um it's
more like you get tired of of doing it
after I get that one number so I'm like
oh [ __ ] this I'm ready to
drink and then you could do it every day
every other day but you'd be very [ __ ]
exhausted you'd be very exhausted but
you'll be very confident at the same
time because you've done it every day
so I mean you can do it once a week on a
Saturday drinking but you're not going
to be as confident as unless you do it
like every day, you know, but it doesn't
matter whether you're confident or not
really, does it?
So, it'd be interesting, is it? That's
what happens when you've got too much
time on your [ __ ] hands, bro. You've
got too much time on your
hands and you got no [ __ ]
responsibilities. You think of these mad
things like just as like a hobby. It's
[ __ ] It's mad, bro. It actually is mad.
It is actually mad,
bro. But what I was saying just before
you joined is it would be like a full-time
job. And that's, you know, the only way
to get someone in this country is making
it a full-time job. It's [ __ ] up, bro.
It's crazy, man. It is actually
crazy. I wonder how people with jobs do
it. Like me, I don't care anymore. It's
like a hobby to me. I don't really care
like whether I get a win or not.
Say that there's people out there that
work here, like a 9 to 5 job, and they
want sex and they can't get it. Like me,
I'm not asked anymore, but I'm saying or
they want a relationship. How do they get
someone? How do they get
someone? Um, approaching has got me
well, it has sort of got me a girlfriend
cuz I was kind of seeing someone. So,
actually, it has. And it's also got me
laid. It's got me more than not approaching would.
So it got me. If I didn't approach, I
would be a virgin. So I mean that says
it all really. Sex is better than
nothing. And I was I was meeting
somebody multiple times. Multiple times.
And there was chances I could have been
in a relationship as well, but I just [ __ ] it
up. Yeah, obviously.
But I could do it every day, approach
every day, but I'd
get When did I do it? I think I done
it not last Tuesday, the Tuesday before
that, I think I got two numbers. And
then when I went out again and done it,
I just [ __ ] smashed it, bro. Like
literally. Cuz you know when you do it
the day before, you're more confident.
Cuz when you go longer without doing it,
you have to do it again and like pluck
up the courage and then once you've done
the first one, they become easier, lad. So,
look. So, yeah, but it's like a hobby thing, you
know? I was thinking of doing it every
day until April, but it's going to be
expensive, man. I'm not going to be
drinking, but I'll just go
like, it's very tiring, bro. It's
tiring. It is tiring doing it sober. It
is cuz after like the fourth or fifth
one, you'll be like, "Oh, [ __ ] this."
Oh, you got a number and you just go on
a drink, bro. Cuz it's just boring,
isn't it? At least when you're drinking,
you listen to music and that, you
know. But yeah, you wouldn't be able to
do that if you got like a
job. You'd be
[ __ ] No, I just go around central.
Me, I just go around central just just
approaching people. I think I got three
numbers sober in the past two weeks. I
got a lot more drunk. But
yeah, it is fun, bro. You
know, it is good. It is
good. There's pros and cons to doing it
on the street and there's pros and cons
to doing it in a club. Pros on the
street is no one else has got the balls
to do it. You might meet somebody that's
not into drinking and they've got
hobbies. no cop blockers, you know, but
obviously when you do it sober on the
street, it affects you more like when
it's the same old same old. So there's
there's there's pros and cons to it. I
don't think there's no right or wrong answer with
it cuz I approached this this woman as
soon as I come out the train station. I
think it was two weeks ago. It's the
first maybe a week ago, I can't
remember. It's the first one I done. The
first one I done, I got a number. The f
very first one I done. Bear in mind I
had done a solo approach in vug in ages
and we're still talking and that so
we're planning to meet as well so it's
good. That was the first one I done and
it was dead dead dead and I think it
took another 10 to get another number
but again it's on the street sober. So
um but realistically it's not worth it
man. Like it's not it's not worth
putting all that effort in to find
someone. You're best off just to go to
Thailand really man. cuz it's
just I don't know man. It's just boring
and it does get
boring. The sex is not even worth it
when you get it
anyways. Or Brazil or you go like
Thailand or Brazil or somewhere like that.
Yeah, it is tiring bro. It is tiring.
Imagine that every day for a month. [ __ ]
hell. Every day for a [ __ ] month.
Surely to god, bro. If you done it every
day for a month, you'd find you would
you'd um you'd hit it. You would hit it,
bro. [ __ ] more than once. I'm sure you
would. But it's it's just hard, bro. It's
hard. Oh man, it's
hard. It's long,
man. Yeah, it's all right if the re if
the weather was good, dude. Back when I
met that 19year-old, the weather was
good. So, I used to just go out like
every day cuz the weather was
good. The weather was banging, bro.
Booming every [ __ ] day, bro.
What the [ __ ] Why is it so
cold? Open the [ __ ] door.
Oh, so yeah, man. That's it. Yeah,
Anyways, yeah, I'm on a detox, man, this week. [ __ ]
detox. Get my head on as well some
point. I mean, or you can just go out
once a week doing it, but Yeah, your [Music] best.
Yeah, but then you missed the press. It
is hard, bro. It is hard. [ __ ] hard,
bro. It is hard, bro.
All of my best successes have been on
the street, so it's hard, isn't it?
I don't know, man. It's like 5050,
bro. Hello, Tripper. I've been out
sending it the past two weeks. Been
getting numbers, kisses, got some date scheduled.
Yeah, I was just talking about like I
was thinking of just approaching like
every day for two weeks.
Bro, it'd be [ __ ] hard, man. Not as
in hard to do. I can do it easy, but
like it'd be be [ __ ]
tiring. It would be very It would be
very [ __ ] tiring,
bro. Like Wednesday, [ __ ] Thursday,
Saturday. Yeah, it's mad, bro. It's mad.
It's mad. I'm not going I'm not on
the Just been chilling, man. Drinking,
going out, approaching, gambling
somewhat. Just been just the same old really,
man. Yeah, just the same old
[ __ ] What about
you? Just the same old, man. I can see
nonslegs is still obsessed with me. Got your cupboards.
Yeah. When's that? Is that St. Is that
St. Patrick's Day? Oh, yeah. St.
Patrick's Day soon, isn't
it? Patrick's Day is a
Monday. Yeah. The the drinks are£3 pound
on St. Patrick's Day. This pub that I go
to, it's£3 pound a Guinness. Three pound [ __ ] Guinness.
That's cheap as chips, bro. [ __ ] Yeah,
man. You need to stop calling yourself a
m fake beck. It's no good for your mental
health. You calling yourself a manta.
I'm better looking than any everyone on
here that's shown their
face. Nah. Nah, mate. We're talking
about how you need to stop calling
yourself a M because it's no good for your mental
health. Like, think about it, man. Like,
you comment on YouTube every day calling
yourself a ma. That can't be good for
your mental health, man. Calling calling yourself these
things. Yeah, lovely Guinness,
man. Let's stop talking about Guinness,
bro. Today, bro. I actually fancy one
today. King Jay is much better looking
than me. Is he really? Is that why I've
had more women than him? Is that why he
has to resort to singing and I've never
had to simp a day in my life?
Yeah. He's much better looking than me
yet. We've never seen him with a woman
and he always has to simp and he still
gets no women. I've never had to simp a
day in my life, mate. And I've got more
women. I've had more women than him and
I get more women than him. Yeah. Simple.
How about that one? If he was so
good-looking, why the [ __ ] is he on
YouTube, right? I don't get rejected
every day. I've had women. I've been had
women. It's on my YouTube channel. Me
getting sex, me getting dates. Mate,
listen. Don't worry about my mental health.
Yeah. He's so good-looking, yet he has
to beg Sarah Louise. Do you remember
that Sarah Louise horse looking
[ __ ] Triple H. He was telling
her to suck his dick. Does that sound
like somebody that gets women to
you? Does that sound like somebody that
gets women to you. It doesn't sound like
It doesn't sound like anyone that gets
women to me,
bro. Yeah, bro. He hasn't had a [ __ ]
woman since [ __ ] Anita, bro. About that one. Yeah.
Yeah. Anyways, bye-bye
now. Stop calling yourself a M. It's not
nice. don't like people to uh to talk
about themselves on that
trip. It's not nice, man. It's not nice
to call yourself
hunter. No, I fancy going out for some
Guinnesses, bro. But I'm not I'm on a
detox. And I'm I got my shorts here as
well. But now you're talking about
Guinness Triple H. I'm [ __ ] uh I'm
[ __ ] tempted now, bro. Don't [ __ ] tempt me,
bro. [ __ ] sake, man. I love Guinness.
I love Guinness after a nice beef curry.
You know, like a Chinese beef curry. Oh,
[ __ ] me. And then you have a nice
Guinness afterwards. That's what I'm
into now. The Chinese curry, it's better
than the Indian curry because with the Chinese
curry, it's like succulent beef. And I
prefer beef than lamb and chicken. So, I
I love a nice beef curry. Very tender.
Very steamed. Oh, [ __ ] hell. It's
lovely, mate. fills the stomach right
up. Stop talking about Guinness. You're
going to make me [ __ ] get on it, man. I love Guinness.
Yeah. Good old Guinness. Good old
Guinness. I got my passport. Triple H. I
got a brand spanking new passport, mate.
Delivered two days ago. It's [ __ ]
lush, mate. Got it all by myself.
Yeah. Why can't just be like a normal
community? You go live, people have a
normal chat. They can't, man. All they
all these people know how to do is hate.
But I know why these people do it
though. I know why these people do it.
Cuz think about it, bro. Most most
people in here are very old in their
30s, 40s, alone, no mates, no money, no
confidence. So what they do is they just
come here and have nothing better to do
but self-reflect their own existence
onto other people. It's mad, isn't it?
Crazy. It is actually crazy,
bro. It is
mad. Go gym. They hate it. Get a steak.
Hate it, bro. You know what I'm saying?
It's mad, man. Like, you would have
thought these people are older than me
and they've got nothing better to
do than to hate. It's
mad. It is mad, bro. It is [ __ ]
madness, bro. You don't see me going like these
people, you know? It's [ __ ] madness,
bro. It's madness, man.
today, man. You're a [ __ ] ton you are,
bro. A lovely
goodness. Thursdays on my day, bro. But
we need to be saving,
man. Yeah, I've got some numbers, bro.
They reply. I've got I've got some meats coming
up. Um well well there is something you
can do. You you have to go out and approach every
day. That's what that's what you can do.
You can go out on the street and approach every
day. And yes, it's very tiring because
I've done it
before. That's all you can do,
bro. Um was I wrong about women? Um, no.
I wasn't wrong about women. I still
think they're [ __ ] I still think
they're stuck up. I still think people
defend them for no reason. But I
accepted it. It's never going to change.
I'm never going to change it. Winging
about it is never going to change. So
why complain about it? No, I don't think
I'm wrong. I just realize that it's
never going to change. So that's what
we're faced with. It is what it is.
So, no, I wasn't wrong about women at
all. Hell no. Like, they they have it
way easier. They have to exist. All they
got to do is exist and get any man they
want. What we've got to do is we have to
make it a full-time job to even find
someone. No, I don't take back anything
I said. I just don't really care now and
just use it as a hobby. I I use
approaching as a hobby and I've got
other things going on now. So, I don't
really care, man. I don't really care to
winge about it. It is what it is. It's
never going to change.
You just make do with what you got, man. Is it?
It's man. Happy as
love. And that's the way you got to see it, man. Like,
yeah. Yeah. Them ones on Instagram are
not real, bro. They use
filters. Well, I've accepted the fact that it's
like the baiting game is rigged against
men. Like, okay, I'll give an example.
In order for a woman to get sex or to
get a boyfriend, all she's got to do is
go on a dating app and she can get she
can get anything she wants. Let me
rephrase that. I would literally have to
go out every single day and approach for
probably about two weeks just to get a
date. Go figure. So, I would have to
literally go out every single day and
approach and approach and approach and
approach and approach just to get a
date. They get the dating game is rigged
against men, but it's never going to change.
So, what are we going to do, bro? We
just I'm doing things that kind
of improves my odds, you know? I go out
on the street approach and no one else
has got the balls to do it. Well, there
are some people that do, but they're
very far and few between. So, I just and
I know that I'm going to be leaving
England at some point anyway, so I don't
really care, bro. Like, it is what it is,
man. Doesn't bother me no
more, you know?
But no, I wasn't wrong about them. And
and and this is very interesting. What
what I was saying as well is that you
people that defend women, you don't deal
with women. I'm used to it, so it
doesn't bother me anymore. But you
people probably have not spoke to a
woman in probably over a decade. So when
you're sat there defending them and
saying, you know, they go for
personality and they go for these
things. When was the last time you
actually went out and you spoke to a
woman? And that would answer my
question. So that's what I mean. But
it's all good. Like people being at
home, not leaving their house, being so
quick to judge you, and them in your
shoes, and they probably haven't spoke
to a woman for [ __ ] god knows how
long. You know, it's universal, man. It
doesn't just happen to one person, you
know? Even when it's this guy um
approaches on Instagram, he gets the
same old I've got boyfriends, but you
just deal with it because it's never
going to change. So, what's the point,
bro, moaning about it and getting angry
it? It's very very much universal, you
know, in these westernized countries is
what it is. People just
Yeah. And that's
it. I wasn't wrong about
them. I was wrong about where I went
about as in like, you know, you can
leave the country, you know, you can get
escorted, you can go out and enjoy just
drinking, you know, and whatever happens
happens. But as far as them being like
stuck up and No, no, they still are.
They still are. But there's a way to go
about things. You know what I'm saying,
bro? I've accepted that, but I can't
accept the gambling.
I lose 20 pound, I go
mad. No, I'm not back to moaning, bro.
Hell, I was on YouTube yesterday. I'm
not moaning, bro. I went out on [ __ ]
Saturday. I [ __ ] I didn't moan on the
Sunday. No, I don't moan anymore, bro. I
anymore. I I will say what I think, but
I won't moan about it, you
know, because again, it's never going to
change. What the [ __ ] you know.
Yeah, you've watched me for years and
I've never changed. Well, guess what? I
have changed this time, bro. But I I'll
never change. Like, every time I lose
gambling, I go mad. Like, even if it's
20 pound, like, I will go [ __ ] mad,
bro. I spat on two machines last uh this
week and it was only 20 pound. That is
impossible to accept. That's what I'm
saying. That's impossible to accept. You
know, it's a madness, bro. It actually
is a madness. Like, I can go in right
now with 20 pound loser massive machine.
Like, it's crazy, bro. It's [ __ ]
annoying. That is [ __ ] annoying, bro.
I can't I can't be the only one then.
You know what I'm
saying? You know, it's [ __ ] up, man.
Yeah. You know, I never change. Of
course I change. I just told you, bro, I
don't give a [ __ ] I go out to drink cuz
I want to drink. It's like if I go out, right?
Yeah. You drink. Say, for example, I'm
going to do approaches, but I want to go
out just to drink anyways. I just want
to go out to drink anyways, but I'm
still going to approach. If I get some,
I get somewhere. If I don't, I don't. end of you
know. But no, I'm not wrong about women.
No, I'm not wrong about women at all.
Why would I be? You know, my videos
prove everything cuz they are [ __ ]
They are [ __ ] But you know what? What
do you want me to do about it, bro? Moan every [ __ ]
day. I'll just get on with it, bro. You
know, I still think like there's a big
double standards when they tell people
that people don't owe them anything that
like I still think there's a massive double standards
and yeah. Yeah, I still believe all of
that, but we know all this anyway.
So, so yeah, bro.
Yeah, but I've accepted that in this
country it's very very slim you're going
to get anything longterm. So you're out
for fun until you can leave. You know,
there's so many other things you could
be doing. You know what I'm saying, bro?
I got my passport. I didn't renew my
passport for no [ __ ] reason, did I?
I didn't renew my passport for no
reason. So, think about it,
bro. Yeah, that's it. And Yeah. Yeah,
man. Yeah, man. And you should
Yeah. Yeah, bro. I'm taking a break
anyways. All the 20's gone without
Doesn't matter, bro. I've had sex. I've
traveled to places. [ __ ] it. I'd be,
bro. Listen, listen, listen. It doesn't
matter. Do you know how many people
waste their life in a
relationship? Three, four
years. Like, why why does it bother you
if I'm in a relationship or not? Even if
I was in a relationship, you would tell
me I'm not in a relationship. So, why
why does that matter to you, bro? Like,
I've shown money. You still call me
skin. I've shown I'm better looking than
everyone on here. They still call you
ugly. So, why would it matter, bro? Did
I meet that [ __ ] 19year-old about 11
times and I was basically seeing her and
I [ __ ] her more than once and she
sucked my dick more than once? Why does
it why does it matter to you if I'm in a relationship or
not? Because the thing is what I'm doing
soon I can't even be in one anyways
because I'll be traveling. So, you
know, more to life than [ __ ] relationship,
Dad. No, it really, really doesn't. And,
like I said, even if I was in a
relationship, you would tell me I'm not
in a relationship. So, it doesn't
matter, bro. It doesn't matter. You
know, it doesn't like that's the only
thing you middle-aged people have on me
is that you're 27 and you've never had a
relationship when you people are
probably 47 and you've never even had
sex. You've never even seen a woman
naked. Like, it's it's all
selfreflecting, you know, and and
finding things that you can find on
people. And this is why I don't really
come on here anymore. I find every time
you come on here it's just the same old
just different places man different you
know cuz all of these people that come
on here and call you they're in a worse
position in life than you are and you
will ever be mate trust
me look at this bro I don't come on
YouTube a week over a week I have about
five different people that are obsessed with
me you know it's it's [ __ ] up
The obsession and jealousy with me is is
crazy. It's It is insane, bro. It's
mad. I actually fear for my own safety,
to be honest. It's [ __ ]
weird. Yeah, this is what I'm saying.
Self-reflecting monous skin. See, they just
self-reflect. This is why you don't
really like catch me on here much
anymore, bro. I come in here, put my
head on for a couple of days, and then I
leave because it's just the same
middle-aged losers that have got nothing
going for themselves that like to try to
bring other people down to their fat,
level. Skin, fat, ugly, no life. That's
why you don't really see me on here,
bro, for a week, two weeks. You only see
me on here for a month. It's pointless.
It's pointless, bro. It's actually
actually it's pointless. Unless you're
putting like content on your actual
like main channel, they just
self-reflect. They want to be you
because they're fat and ugly and they
got no life, but they can't. So, they'd
rather hate on you. That's what they do. They're
[ __ ] Like, and the thing is, bro,
it's not even new roast that we're
hearing, bro. It's the same old [ __ ]
Yeah. I've been hearing since I've been
on it for about six years. Your skin.
your skin. It's so boring, you know?
It's not even like it's new like roasts
that they that they say, bro. It's just
the same old repeating and then they
wonder why like this person don't come
on and that person don't come on because
they're boring as
[ __ ] All they do is
self-reflect their skin lives on
everyone else. And you would have
thought, right, that they would have got
bored of it, but they never do it. you
know, but I'm gone from I'm gone from
tomorrow for a little bit
anyways. Too weird, too creepy.
Listen, hold on a minute. I get bullied
off. Yeah, nice try. Nice bullied off.
Hold on a minute.
Right. Yeah, you you bully me off. No,
you you use the right word. uh the right
letter. Sorry, B. You bore me off
because you're [ __ ] boring. You just
repeat the same [ __ ] over and over and
over again. And because I don't want to
give you little sad little retards
attention, that's you bullying me off.
[ __ ] out of here,
man. Look, even this comment here. Look,
I've seen this guy as well. Let me let
me let me read this comment up if I can get it. Right. Right.
Listen, hold on, bro. Where is it?
Hold on a minute. One second. One sec.
One sec. One
sec. This is what I'm saying. If I can
get the comments on. Look, this is what
I'm saying. Now that LT has stopped
going after him and decided to be
buddies with him, which is very strange
to after what Big No said about his
child. Repeating again. It's pretty much
useless knowing where he lives now.
Sadly, unless It's pretty much useless
knowing where he lives now. Sadly,
unless LT wants to do something. Um,
hold on a minute. Shouldn't he be
telling Sha to do something if he
apparently knows where I live? And
shouldn't he himself be doing something
if he apparently knows where I live? You
know, no one's doing your dirty work.
Like, you can bring up LT all you want.
And what people have said about these
kids 10 years ago, nobody cares. LT is
on a new channel and he's never coming
back on this community. Yeah. Which is
good. Which I shouldn't even be on it.
You don't know where I live. And even if
you did know where I live, you still
wouldn't go in anyone's door. So stop
going on about LT, LT, LT. If you know
LT won't do nothing, why don't you come
and do some of them? See, it's stupid,
bro. These keyboard warriors, these sad,
fat, ugly people have been doing the
same thing now for [ __ ] years, and
they're so boring. They're so boring.
You know, they can claim that they can
they bully people, but these people will
never say anything to your face. They're
keyboard warriors. They're the bully
victims. They are the ultimate bully
victims. And this is why they spend all
their years on YouTube and they ain't
got a life because they've been
neglected, bro. They've been rejected
their whole life. They're skinn. They're
fat. They're ugly. They're hopeless. And
that's why they're on here, you know.
And he doesn't even know where I live.
Yes. Telling other people to go to But
he doesn't even know where I live.
That's the funniest thing about it. And
if you claim that you do know where I
live, why haven't you come on the door?
Why isn't any of your obsessed followers
come on the door then? If you apparently
know where someone lives, that's the
first thing I would be doing if I
[ __ ] knew where someone [ __ ]
lived. Obviously, you
know, and this is why I come off here.
This is why I don't waste my time on
these little rejects, these little
obsessed, jealous people. I don't even
waste my time on them anymore. This is
why I'm gone after tomorrow again
because it's the same old same old same
old boring repetitive
[ __ ] You know it's it is so boring.
Like it really really is you know same
[ __ ] people that are jealous of me.
You know I've seen this for the past two
years now bro you know.
So, I'm going to get after today. So,
they can carry on being upstairs talking
to themselves about me every day and
I'll be keep living in their head. So, that's
lovely. They don't know where I live
anyways. They don't know where I
live. They will never know where I live.
A and B. Why the [ __ ] are they even
trying to find out where I live? They're
never going to come the door. They're
anything. Yeah. Yeah. Stop talking about
yourself. Yeah. You bully me. Yeah.
Okay. That's why you can't show where
you are and you hide behind a keyboard.
Yeah. Okay, buddy. Because you bully me.
Yeah. I'm almost 30. But you've been in
your 30s and you're still a virgin. And
everything I say about these people,
right, it proves it. They come on here
every day and they keep doing what they
do. They prove it. Sad sati s s s s s s
s s s s s s s s s s s s s s sadistic
little sad little [ __ ] virgins that got
nothing to their lives and that's what
they do every day. And that's and when I
say this stuff about them, they get
triggered. I'm 30 and I've never had a
woman. Brother, you're in your 40s and
you're still a virgin. How about that
one? You know, and this is exactly why I
don't come on anymore, you
know? Really? What do you want somebody
to do? Sit on What do you want me to do,
bro? stay on YouTube every day arguing
with these pathetic little keyboard
warriors, these pathetic little virgins.
Why would I need to do that? I already
live in your head. I don't I don't need
to come on YouTube every single day
arguing with you. I've I already I'm
already living in your head. You've got
a whole channel dedicated to me. You
don't need my presence. I'm already
living in your head. The job's done. Me
existing is owning these people every
day because they don't shut up about me.
They're jealous of me. Look at what they
do every single [ __ ] day because
they're jealous. Because they're fat,
they're ugly, they're skinn, you know, they're autistic,
clearly, you know, I don't need to come
on here every day
arguing with sad people that are not
worth my time, you know? And that's it.
Yeah. But yeah, I'm done again after
today, bro. 100%.
They can go self-reflect their fat, ugly
lives every day on their YouTube
channel. I told you what I told you what
it is with these people, bro. Sad, fat,
ugly, hopeless. They see someone that's
better looking than them, got more money
than them, and it kills them. It's like
what somebody said before, there was an
account on it called Ronald Pump, and
he's like, "You're better looking than
them, you got more money than them, and
it kills them." And that's literally
what it is. That honestly is to God what
it is because if you was better, you do
better. But he's right. Better looking,
more money, and it kills them. It does.
It does. It does. I agree with him. You
know, you do because if these people
were better than you, they wouldn't
waste their time on you every day on
YouTube. They want to be you. They're
jealous of you. You know, jealousy is a
disease. You know, it's a it's a [ __ ]
horrible disease. Jealousy, it kills
people. It's It's [ __ ] up, bro. and
autism. Obviously, autism and jealousy,
I'd say probably is the main main thing.
I got a passport thing here, you
know, just think about it, Gary. Yeah.
Okay. I need to this website is that
even if you don't react to these people,
have you notice how they still do it?
Have you noticed? Right. Even when you
don't react, well, we don't react to
them anyways, but e even if you don't
react to them, have you noticed how they
still do it? Like, you could literally
be gone for a year and they would still
do. Yeah, bullied, mate. How can you
bully me, bro? You can't even show me
where you are. You can't even show me
where you are, you little keyboard
lawyer. So, how can you possibly bully a
man like me? You claim that you've got
my address and you're not willing to
come and do anything. The only one that
gets bullied is you. So go laugh at
yourself, mate. Listen. Yeah. Every
single day that you post about me and
you talk about me is me bullying you in
your head when you can't shut up about
me. You can't show me where you are. You
can't meet me. So the only one that gets
bullied is your fat self. So come by now
and go self-reflect on another channel. It is
lush. You know what self-reflector.
Anyways, as I was saying, Gary, yeah,
even when you don't um react to these
people, have you noticed how they still do
it? Have you noticed how they still do
it? Even if Yeah. You could not come on
the internet, bro, for like a
year. A whole year. And they would still
do it. And they would still do it
because they're [ __ ] jealous of me.
That's what it is. They're jealous of
me. They want to be me.
You know, you've got some [ __ ] ugly
ratfaced [ __ ] skinned virgin in his
little shitty kitchen [ __ ] going on
about me for [ __ ] 10 minutes. And I
didn't even say two [ __ ]
words. I didn't even say two [ __ ] words,
mate. It's a [ __ ] madness,
bro. Madness, bro. I feel sorry for these people.
I really do feel bad for these little virgins,
bro. I feel bad for
him. What could anyone do on a Thursday
at work or something? [Music]
I think eventually I'm probably just
going to leave and probably not come
back to be
honest. Probably to be honest with you,
bro. These [ __ ] virgins on this
community, man. It's
crazy. You would
have I could literally never imagine
somebody living in my head like that. I
I swear to God,
bro. I could never
ever imagine being obsessed with how
this person gets like it's mad, bro. Is
it? It is a madness.
Uh yeah, Morgan still going about my sloppy seconds. H
boring just you're boring me now, mate.
You've said all of this stuff
before. Yeah, big nose Morgan. We've
heard all of this before. Any new
content? Oh, just the same old
repeating. Your boy been out. You're
sending me to sleep, mate. You're giving me a
migraine. Oh, you're boring me
now. You're really boring me now, man. It's
boring. You need to sort out your
jealousy and you need to sort out your
autism. It's getting very, very, very bad again.
Literally go to the general practice,
bro, and go and sort out your autism and
go and sort out your jealousy tendency
tendencies because um they're really
starting to affect your life again, bro. It's
bad. You really need to stop. It's
getting it's getting bad now. It's
embarrassing and I'm starting to feel
bad. I don't like the fact that I'm
living in these people's heads.
Again, no, no, no,
no. We've heard him a million times
before. You're B. Yeah, it's so boring.
He needs to go and seek help for his
autism and his jealousy before it
[ __ ] ends up killing him. It's [ __ ] mad,
bro. Like, we've heard the same old
Listen, I don't want nothing to do with
you. Britney does not want nothing to do
with you. Move the [ __ ] on with your
life, you [ __ ] virgin. I don't know
how many times you have to. And the
thing is, Gary, right? Yeah. is they say
that when I'm the one who's triggered,
but but they're the ones that react to
me even when I'm not even on
YouTube. So, they know all about being
triggered because listen, you you live
in their head. Whether you're on
YouTube, whether you're not on YouTube,
you are living in their head. They're
posting and posting and posting even
when you're not even on YouTube. And how
I know because people tell me about
this. You live in their head on YouTube,
off of YouTube. That is some [ __ ] achievement,
bro. You know, that is some [ __ ]
achievement. It's an achievement, bro.
To me, that's a madness, man. I swear to
God. Yeah. And they're made up stories
as well, Gary. They're madeup
stories. They're madeup stories.
They're just made up stories as well. He
needs to go and [ __ ] get laid. He's a
[ __ ] virgin. He He expects people to
believe, right? Because he's got this
downy the wolf ugly girlfriend that
somehow that proves he's he's had sex.
Okay. Well, ask yourself this question.
How the [ __ ] does this little virgin get
to have sex with her when he's on
YouTube every day stalking me in his
kitchen? In his little bedsit shitty
little kitchen. Your virgin kitchen
doesn't even make sense, bro. There's
not enough hours in a [ __ ]
day. It's so weird, isn't it?
I want to know why other people don't
get this treatment. Bro, I'm like the
only one. I have a bunch of people
obsessed with me. It feels good at the
same time, but at the same time, it's
kind of scary, you know? Timmy don't
have it. Monty don't have it. Other
people don't have it. Yeah. Go
self-reflect. Go let Let it sink in that
you're a little
virgin. Yeah. and let it sink in that
you're a little virgin and you've never
had sex and you can't get laid. Yeah.
And then go back on my YouTube channel
and you will see that I've had more
women than you and I've got more money
than you. Let that also sink in down the
drain. You [ __ ] virgin. And this is
all you get when you come on. Like I've
never known so many people to be jealous
of me, Gary. I've never known so many
people to be jealous of me. And and
before you say they're not, well, they
are because look at all of these people,
bro. Listen, listen,
listen. Yeah, bro. They're jealous. They
are jealous. Cuz look at Timmy. Yeah.
Look at Monty, right? Look at some of
these other people, right? Yeah. They
don't get the same treatment. And if
they do get the treatment, they don't
get the treatment when they're not on
YouTube. I've got about five, six people
that are obsessed with me. So, yeah. What? Yeah.
Like, yeah. Suicide
Mark. Yeah. But not the way I've got it,
bro. It's crazy, man. I've never known
so many people to be so jealous of
someone. That sounds That's just mad to me, Gary.
To me, that is just so mad. I don't know
about to you. Like, I know you're a fake
account and that, but I've never known
somebody to be jealous of one person. So
many people to be jealous of one to be
person. I've never known it. I've never
it. It's crazy, man. It's [ __ ] crazy.
I'm coming off YouTube again after today
for my own safety, bro.
They're such weirdos. Oh my
god. [ __ ] hell,
man. And you know how you know it's
jealousy as well? Um Gary, because think
about it, right? If you are calling
someone skin and you are calling someone
ugly, which is what these people are
themselves, would you sit there wasting
your time on them every day? Now, think
about it. Think about it. Would you be
wasting your time pretending to be them
on phone calls, trying to find out where
they live and stalking them every day if
you truly thought you were better than
them? No. So the whole thing contradicts
itself. They know you're better looking
than them. They know you got more money
than them. They know that like
everything about you is better than all
of them despite them projecting their
mness on you, despite them projecting
their skintess on you. You know, if you
was really all of them things, they
would put their middle finger up to you
and be like douches. But they can't. So
there you go, man. You got the answer.
You know, they're jealous of you, bro.
That's what it
is. That's what they are. They're
jealous little skin little nobodyies
that never made it. And unfortunately,
now they're too
old. And he doesn't even know where I
live either. He doesn't even know where
I live. That's the thing. And the only
reason he knew about that girl was when
I still had the house like 8 months
ago. Yeah, you are. Yeah. Stop talking
about yourself. It's not nice. It's not
good for your mental health. Stop
calling yourself a [ __ ] keyboard
warrior. It's not good for your mental
health. Yeah, just like when you call
yourself a bunch every day, it's not
good for your mental health. But
anyways, bro, like uh the only reason he
knew about that is because I said it
about 8 months ago when I still had the
house. You don't know where I live and
you will never know where I live, you
sad little [ __ ]
virgin. And why is he so ashamed of
where he comes from? I'm from Southeast
London. I'm from Southeast London. I'm
from Southeast London. You're not no
part of London, Virgin boy. You don't
sound like us. You don't look like us.
You are no part of us. And then he tries
to tell me that I'm from
Essics, even though I'm from East London. You
know how does he He didn't know. He
didn't know the electricity went out.
The electricity didn't run out. What the
[ __ ] are you talking about? All of this
stuff. I'm going to tell you something
as well. here. When I'm gone, I'm going
to be live again later. I'm going to let
everybody know that um obviously you
shouldn't believe these people anyways,
but you are. Anything that they say them
making it up to try to get me back on
YouTube to argue with them and it's not
going to work. So, I'm going to tell you
that before my last
live. Yeah. Yeah. How he did. Yeah.
Listen, listen. These are all things to
try to get my attention because he's a
sad little lanky toothless nobody,
right? And I'm going to say this on the
last live stream today when I'm gone for
probably like a few weeks. Yeah. They're
going to make up all kinds of things to
get me back on arguing with them, right?
I I'll tell you the science behind these
low IQ people, right? Say you're off of
YouTube for two days, right? They will
make up stories like for example, you've
been nicked. So then you come back on
YouTube arguing with them and giving
them attention. It's not going to work.
And I'll tell you all of the things that
they're going to lie about and all of
the things they're going to make up to
try to get me back on YouTube. But I'm
not coming back, bro. [ __ ] off, man. Not
for a [ __ ] long time. You know,
they're [ __ ] weirdos. They're freaks,
you know? It's
mad. Yeah. [ __ ] weirdos.
Absolute [ __ ] weirdos,
man. You don't know where I live and
you'll never know where I live. Why do
you even want to know where I live? You
weirdo. You [ __ ] creepy little
virgin. Why the [ __ ] do you even want to
know where I live? You [ __ ]
creep. You know, you [ __ ] weirdo,
man. [ __ ] You will never know where I live.
[ __ ] weirdos. You need to get off of
YouTube and go get laid, [ __ ] virgin.
You might be a happier
person. Uh, and don't go on about this
fat ugly girlfriend that he's never
slept with either, but that's no proof of nada. Yeah. Damn. Good.
Yeah. Why do I fancy a drink today, man?
I think that [ __ ] Triple H got me in
the [ __ ] mood for it,
lad. But like I said, I don't really
want to go out [ __ ] Thursday, man. [ __ ] you,
bro. What do you think? Yeah.
Nah, I do love I mean I could actually
go like with what I'm wearing, shorts,
coat, and that, but
nah. Nah. [ __ ] that,
bro. It's my lucky day.
It's your lucky day.
Yeah, bro. But I need to be saving
money. I can't I can't keep going out
spending [ __ ] two 300 quid, bro. You
know? Yeah. I need to get my hair done
as well. I'm not doing I'm not going out
today, bro. Hell no,
[ __ ] I'm tired,
bro. Oh, [ __ ] you can. It's [ __ ] cold,
bro. I'm wearing shorts and [ __ ] t-shirt and
now I could go out,
but I don't really fancy it, bro. I
don't really I don't really want to be
wasting money, bro.
But it is quite
tempting. It's crazy.
It you grind a month like skin show skin
boy virgin boy. You wouldn't be able to
go out every
week if you was like that [ __ ] virgin
cat. Know what I mean Gary? If you like that virgin
[ __ ] [ __ ] virgin
sh. Virgin sh. That's what I call him.
He is a [ __ ] virgin. [ __ ] d virgin. D
virgin. Like a
virgin. I mean, you can call Peter belly
a virgin all you want, but I mean
there's videos of Peter Belly pulling.
There's videos of Peter Belly in bed with women. Yeah.
Yeah, it's all
good. You back in virgin
can. Yeah, I could go for
Guinness B's going into the city and
that. Oh, it's long,
bro. It's long. It's long,
man. It's long enough.
Is it raining out there? Give it a little
Well, yeah, I
would. It is [ __ ] raining as
well. Yeah, you know what? I'd bring
[ __ ] nonss along with me so he could
finally lose his [ __ ] vidinity. But
do you know what? I can't do that, Gary.
Cuz you'll scare them away with the ugly
face. With that ugly face that he's got,
the [ __ ] rat face and the social
anxiety. You [ __ ] cop lot me. The little
virgin, you know? [ __ ] hell. Could
you imagine that [ __ ]
greasy? It's like what I say, mate. I'd
rather have a [ __ ] Pinocchio's nose
and have that ugly face that you've
got. You know what I'm saying? with his
social anxiety and his autism. He'd cop
lot me, mate. You imagine that [ __ ]
greasy [ __ ] balding rat in a club
with his autism ruining it for everyone
with that with that ugly face that he's
got. [ __ ] that, bro. With that ugly
face. Could you imagine? [ __ ]
hell. No, man. I can't imagine that.
Yeah, I would give it a whirl. I
would could give it a whirl. I would if
it was the week after. I would, mate.
Yeah. Give it a
whirl. Oh, I love it, bro. I love
it. I love it. And what? Find a new mama,
Gary. So, Gary, what happened to my
mommy and daddy?
So what happened to my mommy and daddy then
Gary? Yeah, I'm all right. Debating
whether to go for a beer today or
not. Only problem is it's raining.
Planted a few Guinnesses could give it a
whirl. Yeah, I would give it a
whirl. Give it a little whirl. But
uh yeah, it's raining,
man. And I'm not I just want to stay
in. Yeah. I don't think I'm going out
this week, mate.
I don't think I'm going out this week,
man. I need to get a haircut as well. So, where's
long? Well, if I went out today, I'd be
going out in shorts, trainers, and a
coat. Yeah, I don't even need to save. I
just can't be bothered wasting money in
this country for a little bit, man.
I don't need to say for it. But [Music]
um but yeah, like I want to
man, not necessarily just about saving, but
yeah, if I went out, it' be in shorts, a
top, and a coat, so I'd look a bit of a
[ __ ] I kind of need a haircut as well.
I probably look a [ __ ]
mate. Don't know, mate. I'll just bring
my card. Just bring my Just bring I'll
just bring my card to be
honest. Yeah, I bring my [ __ ] card,
man. That's it.
Yeah, bring my card. One second.
Someone's following me on Instagram. Hold on.
Yeah, I'm kind of tempted to go out,
man. I don't know. So, I just call my
friend. Um, yeah, man. I don't know [Music]
whe the thing and it's
[ __ ] like [ __ ] to put on my hair
or maybe I could give it a whirl, you
know? But I don't know. It's expensive, man. it
like no point going out it
um just get your old numbers up and [ __ ] it. [ __ ]
me. [ __ ] me, bro. [ __ ]
me. I can just do some approaching on the street.
I could do some approaches on the strip, guess. Oh
man, it's [ __ ]
long. Yeah, I could do some approaches
on the strip, but I'm wearing these old shorts, man. [Music]
I don't know, bro. How
much? Not more than 30 quid, right?
I might do it, you know. I
might do it, but I'd only be saving in one p.
Um, and it is perfect.
Um, it's just wrong though, is [Music]
it? I've actually got some hair products
as well. Manchester, maybe.
Maybe. I don't know.
GA. Most people are
blocked. GA, most people are blocked.
You [ __ ] fat old
man. Yeah, most people are blocked. And some
people some people on
LS, why don't you take the H and [ __ ]
off you little keyboard warrior. One of
them keyboard warriors, you just will
never meet anyone. And I'm not arguing
with you either, mate. So don't even
waste your [ __ ] time, man.
Yeah. You're a sad bastard. The fact
that you're in your 40s and and you're
on here is sad as [ __ ] man. Like,
that's sad. Like, you're on you're in
your 40s and you're on here trying to
wind people up. You're sad [ __ ] man.
You are sad bastard. You really are a
You are a sad
[ __ ] Oh, my cheap phone. I've got a s
I got a Samsung Fold uh said
66. Yeah, it's a cheap phone, bro. Yeah,
a 2,000 phone is cheap, isn't it?
Yeah. Yeah. Bad signal. Yeah. Yeah. Oh,
really? Actually, that was the Wi-Fi.
The Wi-Fi [ __ ] Yeah. I got a cheap
phone, bro. Even though the phone's worth
£2,000. Yeah, the phone's worth two
grand, is it? But it's a [ __ ] phone.
Yeah, man. [ __ ] phone. Yeah. Yeah. [ __ ]
phone. Why do you get a life, bro?
You're in your 40s. You should get off
of YouTube, man. It's really sad, you
know, you being on here and all. Sad little keyboard
warrior. Sad sad little keyboard lawyer.
You are good, man. You're in your 40s
and you're on YouTube. Get a
life. Get a [ __ ] life, man.
Yeah. My phone is so cheap, man. It's
the best Samsung going, but it's the
cheapest, isn't it? Yeah.
Yeah. I'm debating what to do today.
Um, I got the passport back, but I got no [ __ ] beans. [Music]
So, don't use don't use red anymore. Try again.
I sit I I got here all day. I was off of
YouTube for a week. What are you talking
about? I was on you I was off of YouTube
for a week, mate. I've been off of
YouTube for weeks. You're the one who's
on YouTube every day, bro. You're a
sadder, man. Get a
life. No, I'm just going to chill
today. Could go out and give it a whirl.
Guna could go out and give it a little
whirl. Be a bit pointless though,
but I don't know what to do,
bro. Nope. Oh, was it, mate? Nope. Okay.
Well, I'm going I'm coming off of
YouTube tomorrow, bro, for another few
weeks. So, is that going to be a strike?
I've got other things in life, but
YouTube, mate, unlike you, Gula. You're
a sad bastard, man. I can't even take
you serious. Do the ch. Oh, [ __ ]
me. Sad bastard,
man. Jesus Christ, man. You are. You
know what I'm saying? [ __ ] sad
bastard. But why why are you on YouTube
every day anyways, GA man?
I'm just I'm debating whether to go for
a Guinness today. Well, a few [Music]
Guinnesses. I'm a sad news. Okay, good.
You're the one that's on YouTube every
day. So, how can you call me a sad news
when you're the one who's on YouTube every
day? You're the one who's on it every day,
bud. Yeah. I think I'm going to go for a
few beers, man. [ __ ] it. Give it a
whirl. I would now I
would. I would. Yeah. Right. Let me put some socks
on. I'm not getting into no club. So,
I'm just going to rock the old shorts.
Oh. So, yeah. I'm just going to go for
some Guinnesses, get some [ __ ] add
to the numbers, find a potential um
candidate for baby Peter. Well, we've
already got some potential ones, but we
need more potential ones in case they go
[ __ ] So, yeah. Um, not a prime
candidate for Baby P
today. Some of them. So, we need to try
to find a candidate for
baby. I'm so funny in [Laughter]
it. Oh, so yeah, I got a [ __ ]
headache, man. I'm poseable.
going out in shorts like a [ __ ]
mug. What the [ __ ] am I doing,
bro? I only got to stay in the pub
though, which will be
about [ __ ] 50 probably about 30 40
quid. Yeah, I want to spend more than that.
They don't. No, no, no, no, no. Listen,
Guna. They don't like No, no, no, no,
no. Sean, no. They don't like Shan. The
only reason they say they like Sha is
because they don't like me. Nobody likes
Sha except the same three people, four
people that don't like me. Yeah. So, no,
most people don't like him. And mate, I
don't really give a [ __ ] because after
today I'm gone anyways for a little
bit. So it doesn't bother me anyways,
bro. Like [ __ ] no one
cares. Literally, nobody gives a [ __ ]
bro. You know, no one cares about that
virgin. This place doesn't mean nothing
to me. Like the thing is, Gona, this is
not my life. When I'm off of YouTube,
Shan's still obsessed. You're still
obsessed. The people that watch Sean,
they're still obsessed with me. I don't
give a [ __ ] You think I care, mate?
Whether I'm on here or off here, you
people will always be obsessed with me.
It's actually a sad site. Actually is a sad site,
bro. It actually is a sad site. It's a
sad state of affairs. I feel bad, man. I
actually feel bad for you being obsessed
on YouTube every day. It can't be good
for your mental health, man. It really can't. you know, you know. But
yeah, anyways, I need to get ready and
that. I'm going to go for a few beers
and go for a few beers
and Yeah, man. Send some approaches in the old
shorts. [ __ ] hell, man. It's going to
be quite long.
Yeah, it's going to be quite long,
but quite fun as well. So, yeah.
Anyways, I'll be back with approximately
hopingly about three numbers
hopefully. But yeah, I'm going to do it
more like night game. This is going to
be like a different session. Just a pub
crawls on the strip on a
Thursday. Should be good, man. Should be
good. What What am I going to spend like
30 40 quid? [ __ ] nothing really in
it. You be laughing, bro. Bob's your
[ __ ] uncle in it. So, anyways, I'm
gone and I'll be back.
Um, yeah, later. Anyways, in a in a
Bizzle. Bye. I'll be live later. Uh,
very later. Bye-bye now. See you.