I said to this guy on Instagram, yeah, I
that I'd rather kill myself than try again.
That's [ __ ] madness, isn't it, bro?
You know. Yeah. Just saying that is crazy, bro.
Like I literally, he said to me, right,
he said, "Trying is better than nothing.
You might miss out on an opportunity if
you don't try." I said, "I've tried more
than anyone in the world. Nothing's
changed in 5 years." Then I said to him, um, yeah, man, by yourself.
Oh [ __ ] I got a message here. Yeah.
I don't know what the [ __ ] I was thinking, lad.
I don't know what I was thinking, Frank,
when I said I was going to go out yesterday drinking.
[ __ ] that, bro. I don't know what the
[ __ ] I was thinking. That's too
depressing, bro. [ __ ] that.
Hell no, bro. I'm going to cinema tomorrow. Yeah, man.
New film out tomorrow.
always come out Fridays on it.
Just this horror film.
Yeah. I don't know why I thought I was
going to go out drinking. [ __ ] that.
To get more back. Like the thing is,
yeah, it gets to a point. Yeah.
It gets to a point where trying makes
you lose even more hope.
The more you try, the more you lose hope
into a point where you completely lose
hope, which is basically where I'm at.
I've completely lost hope. So
yeah, I think we're we're there by now. So yeah. Yeah, man.
Yeah, I've completely completely lost hope.
Yeah, it's winter. It sucks, isn't it? I
hate winter, bro.
I'd rather kill myself than try again.
Is actually bad to say that. Do you think
you know? Yeah.
No, I would actually rather kill myself
than try again, bro. That's how bad
That's how I feel about it.
That's how I feel about it, bro. It's so
depressing. It's not extreme. It's
depressing, bro. Trust me. Like, even
talking about it is depressing. Like, I
was having this conversation with
someone on Instagram about this. I said,
"It's too depressing, bro.
It's not extreme. It's [ __ ] depressing, bro.
Going out every weekend to get rejected,
thinking that there's hope for you when
there's literally no hope. I don't know
how many times someone has to fail until
people just admit there's no hope. I
don't understand why they're still
trying to tell you you got hope. I mean,
you're 20 [ __ ] eight next month.
You know, fair enough if people telling
people to move on with their life, but
they're acting like you got hope. You
don't have no hope.
Is it enough?
>> Yeah, man.
But they try and make it seem like you got hope.
It's mad, ain't it? You know,
nah, there's no being positive. Not
after my experiences. There's no being positive.
There's no way you can even be positive.
You're just delusional. If I try to be
positive, I'm being delusional.
Be positive about what I know exactly
what's going to happen if I was to go
out tomorrow trying. I know exactly what
would happen. Whether I was negative or
whether I was positive, I can tell you
exactly what is going to happen. It's
not being positive, it's being
delusional. Me trying to be positive is being delusional.
And the truth is not [ __ ] even
negative to begin with. To be honest,
there's no being positive.
No, I can't. It would have happened by
now. If there was any better that was
going to happen, it would have already happened.
No, it would have already happened by
now. I heard this five, six years ago.
You still meet the same shitty women,
the same people that play games. You
still see the same [ __ ] men outside.
It doesn't hold nothing. I heard that
five, six years ago.
Nothing's changed. Literally nothing has
changed. Every year when we get into
winter, we're having exactly the same conversation.
Think about it. We're having exactly the same conversation.
Societyy's not changing for anyone.
Like, what the [ __ ]
We're having the same every [ __ ] year
we have the same conversation.
So, how does the future hold better days?
What? You're going to go out one day and
all of these women are not going to be
like this? So, you're going to go out
one day and all of these things that's
been happening to you for years is going
to stop happening.
Sorry, I don't buy it.
Sorry, I don't buy it, bro. I'm not
buying what you're selling me because it
doesn't make sense.
So one day you're going to go out and
all of these experiences you've had with
these women is suddenly going to stop. Really?
You really really think that? Bro, you're delusional.
Just like I was delusional today,
thinking me going out [ __ ] tomorrow.
[ __ ] that, bro.
No, bro. That is depressing. [ __ ] that.
No way. [ __ ] that.
No, I'll never find peace.
You can't find peace when you've had so
many bad experiences with women. It's
over, bro. Generally over. Oh,
that's it. That's that.
Nah, there's no better days ahead.
No, there's no better days ahead. No
way. It would have happened by now.
What happened? If something was going to
happen, it would have happened by now.
100 million%. I'm sticking to my guns.
I'm out of here. [ __ ] it.
Do you know what I might do on my
birthday? I might just go for a meal or
something. I might not even go out
drinking. [ __ ] this. Depressing as [ __ ] Yeah,
for one, mate. Oh, you can [ __ ] off your
self-reflector. Repeating bastard.
How you over there? You can [ __ ] right
off, you little self-reflector. Repeating bastard.
So yeah, every winter, every year, we
have exactly the same conversation. So
my question to you, Frank, is why is
nothing changed in five years?
See, I don't block people that have a
different opinion. I I I'd rather just
question them cuz you said the future
could hold better days. How exactly
could the future hold better days?
Give me some sort of example. We've been
through this now for 5 years and there's
no signs of anything changing. So, what
what what's going to happen?
Yeah, man. I might change. I don't need
to change. I'm fine. Don't have any
addictions. Don't drink anymore.
Got money. I'm good, bro. I'm I'm good.
I'm good. Going on holiday in November.
I don't need to change. Women need to
change. People need to change. I'm good, bro.
[ __ ] American women. I [ __ ] hate
these Americans, bro.
I hate these [ __ ] Americans, bro. I
swear to God, I hate [ __ ] Americans.
I [ __ ] hate their [ __ ] 911 asses, bro.
I [ __ ] hate their 9/11 asses.
I swear to God, I hate them, bro.
We changes people, do you?
I didn't know that. That's interesting. What?
Yeah, bro. I can't believe I was
actually thinking of going out. You
know, I'm surprised I don't gamble anymore, bro.
Like play roulette or anything. Nah, surprised.
I used to gamble a lot, bro. When I used
to be depressed, the bad experiences,
but now I don't even do it.
There's no hope in this country.
There's no hope in this country, bro. No hope.
I know what I'm doing, bro. You don't
need to tell me what to do. I know what I'm doing.
It's so depressing.
How you think there's better days to
come? You're [ __ ] delusional.
Something was going to happen, it would
have happened by now. Facts.
And that last Sunday I went out and
tried was [ __ ] expensive, by the way.
It was [ __ ] expensive the last time I
went out as well.
Just to get nowhere. Same old England.
Nothing changes, isn't it? It's such a
depressing country, bro.
It's so depressing being here. I can't
wait to leave in November.
I swear to God. [Laughter] Yeah.
depressing country, ain't it?
Yeah. One day you're going to wake up
and you're going to leave your house and
all of the things that's been happening
to you for years is going to stop. You
see how it doesn't sound believable?
Frank, you see how it doesn't sound believable.
It just don't sound believable.
Yeah, right. Yeah, right. Yeah, bro.
I hate these women, bro.
I wish I gave up a few years ago, bro.
I really wish I gave up a few years ago, lad. Really did. Yeah.
Yeah, man. But things like this change
like that, man. No way. Amen.
What do you think will happen if I go
out approaching tomorrow? Frank,
what do you think will happen?
Yeah, man. Give us your prediction. Let's
say soon on that.
No one can answer that.
I can answer it.
I can answer it. So, you've had nothing
but bad experiences for four or five
years and you think the next time you go
out is going to be positive.
So all the times you've gone out for
years, it's been negativity, bad
experiences, people playing games, stuck
up people. I mean, I can answer it. I
could answer what happened. And if you
want to put a bet on it, we can bet. I
don't mind. Let's bet £1,000.
I don't mind.
I mean, I I can answer it. I'm positive.
I mean, it would have already happened.
Uh, if something positive was going to
happen, it would have already happened by now.
No, it would have happened by now. If
something was going to happen, it would
have happened by now. I stick to my
guns. There's no bad experiences for 5
years and all of a sudden things change. It's like
It's like the color of a Scooby-Doo toy.
Scooby-Doo's been the same color for
[ __ ] 5 years. One day he's not just
going to change color. No.
>> Yeah. It's like the Scooby-Doo toys is
not going to change color. You know what I mean?
Well, this has been the same for 5
years. This has been the same for 5 years,
funny enough. It's been exactly the same. For years.
Nah, it's been the same for [ __ ] years, bro.
This has been the same for years. Games, [ __ ]
Funny enough, right, you're speaking
about lowering your standards. I'm
speaking to this woman in America. She's
38 and she's got one kid and she's
picky. She even said in her own words, she's picky.
Yeah. In her own words, she said she
said, "I'm picky. Yep.
No, she just said that she's picky. Bye-bye.
No, she just said in her own words she's picky.
No, she hasn't.
So, you got a 38y old with a kid that's
picky. So, I mean, I think the West is completely done.
You see, the thing is there's a lot of
women nowadays that are 27, 28, and they
haven't even kissed anyone. They haven't
kissed any Like a lot of them, I've come
across a lot of these women that are virgins
um haven't kissed anyone because they
would rather they'd rather have no one
than have anything less than perfect.
So, they just have never kissed anyone.
Some of them have never even been on a
date. some of these people that will
post him because unless the guy is perfect
um they're not interested. So then this
is what happens, right? They look for
Mr. Perfect, but Mr. Perfect don't
exist. So they go through their whole
20s trying to find trying to find Mr.
Perfect. And if Mr. Perfect Superman
does exist, they don't want them. So they will
go through loads of these guys that are
not good enough for them because they've
got unrealistic standards and then they
hit the wall at about 32 33. So then at
32 33 they then want to settle down but
then men only want them for sex then and
then they will just pump and dump them.
And the same thing happens repeatedly.
Yeah. They never learn from each other.
Like it's mental, bro. How like you can
find a [ __ ] woman, bro. That's a 27,
28y old virgin by choice
because they're so picky. It's [ __ ]
It's a madness. It's a [ __ ] madness.
It really, really is bad.
And I don't go for these American birds.
It was somebody off Reddit
[ __ ] So yeah, that's what happens. They
look for Mr. Perfect, but Mr. Perfect don't exist.
It's a madness, isn't it?
their standards is [ __ ] unrealistic.
That's why they're such stuck up [ __ ]
but no one would ever tell you that. So, yeah.
27 28 never kissed anyone. What the [ __ ]
So, think about it, Frank. Right. So, we
need to look at this realistically,
right? So, say we do go out and we get a number.
Uh, there's no point in saying ifs
because it's never ever going to happen.
There's no decent birds. They're all the
same. They proven they've been all the
same over the years, so that's never
going to happen. But think about it.
Think about it realistically.
It's not about whether people have
boyfriends or not. That's Think about
it, bro. We go out tomorrow, right? and
we're going to get a number in it. Yeah,
we're going to go out and we're going to
get numbers. Um, but then the numbers
are not going to reply or the numbers
are going to reply and lead us on. And
even if that said number goes on a date
with us, we're not Superman. So, because
we're not Superman, they're not going to
be interested. So, then they waste their
time and then they waste your time.
So, everyone's a loser. So, it just
makes absolutely no sense in even going
out because even if you do find someone,
let's just say you're lucky enough to
even find somebody to even want to go
out with you, they're just going to
waste your their time and yours.
Completely pointless. And then what's
going to happen is you're going to feel
like [ __ ] even more.
Just it's just a waste of everyone's time. So, so yeah,
you might as well just give up. Yeah,
cuz once you um lose that hope, you can
start moving forward with your life. You
can start moving forward. Once you've
lost that hope,
you can start progressing. You see, cuz
it's the hope that drives you mad.
You know what I'm saying?
Even a couple week.
What do you mean, bro?
There's literally no point even going out.
There's literally no point even trying. D. Yeah.
Yeah. We'll never change.
And you know what's so [ __ ] up, lad?
Nah, my luck won't change. It has
changed. I'm leaving. I'm leaving. Um,
I'm leaving, bro. Simple.
Think about it, bro. It's not about a
debate. It's not up for debate. You
know, you have gave these women years
and years and years to prove they're
different, and none of them have. So,
what even is this conversation, bro?
What even is it? What's the point of
even a debate? What's the point of what
we arguing over? You've gave them several
different uh you gave them several
chances to prove that they're different,
and none of them can. So, I mean, that's
the end of that. So yeah,
they all prove they're the same.
Despite people claiming that they're not
the same and they're all different, they
all seem to be the same. All the ones
we've met just seem to be all the same.
Isn't that a thing?
Same staff, same mannerisms, do the same
things, say the same things, play the same games.
You know what I mean?
But there will
uh I mean yeah there is light at the end
of the tunnel. Go to Sidland. Leave
England. Give up. Travel the world. I
mean yeah by giving up. If you give up
then yeah but not if you keep trying.
It'll just keep making you more and more
and more depressed.
So that's what will happen.
There's no solution to this. It would
always be the same unless you leave. So,
which is what I'm doing. So, November.
So yeah. Yeah. There's no light at the
end of the tunnel, bro. No way.
Nah, the West is well and truly finished. [ __ ] man.
It's well and truly finished.
Oh, and I'm not and I'm not mixed race.
I'm white. I'm fully white. There's
nothing mixed race about me, bro. I'm
more white than you.
No, I think it's I think it's just
there's too many stuck up [ __ ] in
this country with unrealistic expectations.
That's what I That's what I think it is.
Like honestly, what I think it is is
that they're just they've got unrealistic expectations
cuz it's like even the rare time you get a date,
right, they've got this unrealistic
expectation in their head what the date
has to be like. And when it doesn't um
live up to the expectations uh
and it remains unfulfilled. They uh um they um
they say they don't feel the vibe. So
yeah, it is when I think it's they're
too stuck up with unrealistic
expectation. That's my opinion on it. Yeah.
That's what I think it is. Yeah. That's
what I That's what I think it is generally
cuz I've had one night stands before,
you know, years ago and they said, "Oh,
you you look good. You you're
good-looking. They kiss you. They
[ __ ] get with you." You know, it's
not your [ __ ] looks.
Unless it is your unless it's because
you don't look fully white. That's the
only thing it can be.
It's either the West. I mean,
no. But then white people struggle as
well. I don't know.
The rest is finished. Simple.
Cuz white people also struggle. So I
mean people that look fully white whiter
than me, no beard, you know. So I I
don't [ __ ] know.
I think if you I think if you didn't
meet somebody 3, four years ago, you're Scrooge McGooged.
Basically, if you didn't meet someone 3,
four, 5 years ago, you're screwed. So,
but obviously because I because I don't
look fully white, it probably doesn't
help. So, it makes it even worse. So,
yeah, I know it's a madness. So yeah,
it's [ __ ] bro.
It is [ __ ]
I had chances years ago and I didn't
take them. Now it really is finished.
I'm not sure what time I'm going.
Why are you asking that anyways? Why do
you want to know what time I'm going? But
yeah, like I had some chances a few
years ago and I didn't take them. So
I don't know, bro.
Don't know what time I'm going every
time I wake up. Yeah,
I did fancy a Guinness though.
I fancied a Guinness [ __ ] earlier, but nah.
Yeah, easy for you to say. It's [ __ ]
depressing, bro. Having to sit there
thinking of your experiences with women,
it's it's [ __ ] minging, bro. It is [ __ ] minging.
I mean, that says it all. A 38y old with
a [ __ ] kid. Someone that's almost
[ __ ] 40 years of age is being picky. Madness. Yes. Oh,
you literally went to Amsterdam just cuz
I went to Amsterdam.
I went I went there.
I went to Amsterdam. You went to
Amsterdam. But I went to Amsterdam before you.
M I also went to Amsterdam.
I mean it doesn't matter what what
anyone done or what anyone didn't do. I
went to Amsterdam and you somehow ended
up in Amsterdam.
You somehow ended up in the exact same
place that I did.
Same not only the same country but the same city.
And then you went back.
Um, I'm not sure. Seems a bit dodgy to me, mate.
I've never known someone's first uh trip
abroad to be Amsterdam.
I went to Amsterdam as well.
Then somehow you ended up in Amsterdam.
What's the chances? today.
What's What's the chances?
I went to Amsterdam, then somehow you
ended up there.
Amsterdam of all places.
I mean, think about it, right? Amsterdam
of all places.
You went to Amsterdam of all places. You
could have went Australia. You could
have went America. You could have went Spain, Greece.
Harris, you could have went Germany,
but you ended up in um in Amsterdam.
I don't know.
A city where
people go to smoke and [ __ ] escorts.
Normally they go there to smoke.
I don't know, man.
Sounds like a bit of a copycat to me
if you was to ask for my opinion, mate.
Bit of a
bit of a copycat.
And you you traveled exactly the same
way as me.
I I took the Euro Star as well.
I took I took the Euro Star to Amsterdam.
M. So did you. H
I don't know.
Seems a bit dodgy that mate. Seems a bit
because I I also went to Amsterdam. You see?
And somehow you're there as well. There's 240
47 countries you could have went to,
but you somehow ended up in Amsterdam.
What's What's the chance of that?
What's the chances of that?
Can someone Can somebody tell me what
the odds are? running 147.
Yeah, I stayed in a boat. It was called the boat.
Yes, I did. And you know I did, mate.
You copied my [ __ ] holiday. Copied me.
You [ __ ] copied me, mate.
Just like when you said Sher Cole was
attractive, you were saying it to fit
in. You wanted to fit in with the crowd.
You don't want to be You don't want to
be left out.
You don't want to be left out, mate.
You said if I didn't find Sher Cole
attractive that I was gay. Yeah, that's
copying because funny enough other
people used to say that to each other as
well. Yeah, you copying, mate.
You're a copycat.
You know, I remember you saying to me
that you like dogs. Oh, sorry. You
don't. You don't like dogs. You like cats.
I can see why now, mate. Because you're a copycat.
You're a you're you're a copycat, mate.
The only thing that you can't copy is my
beard. Because you can't grow a beard.
And I've got teeth. You don't have
And I'm not balding like you either.
So that's that that's complete different thing, mate.
You copied my holiday.
[ __ ] You copied my holiday, mate. You um
I don't brush my TV.
Um, are you okay, bro? I brush my teeth
every [ __ ] day.
Virgin boy. I don't brush my TV.
Virgin boy and Ben with no money in it. 13 grand.
in two years is [ __ ] nothing skin. I
used to spend five grand a month.
You think that 30 grand's got anything
on my life experiences, mate? When you
were sat there in that bedit with no
money, no bed, no sex, no life, I was
eating steak, wearing stonies, living a
life that you couldn't afford
because you didn't have it. Do you remember?
You didn't have it to show because you
don't have no money. So that's why you
was waiting for three years, mate. You know,
you need to stop copying my holidays. [ __ ] creepy.
going to make some hot chocolate. I think
Someone says they're jealous that they
can't cold approach the way I can.
Well, I mean, mate, I've been doing this for years.
thing is funny as [ __ ]
Oh, you want the link? Okay, one second.
Got a nasty blind spot on my nose, you know.
£1,200. Talking about yourself, I get
more than £1,200 a month from mate.
Have a house. Have savings.
I've had more women than you. Don't live
with my mom. Try again. And I get more
than £1,200 a month. I've got more than
1,200 right now. Now, does that make sense?
Self projecting. What you actually mean is
£300 a month, no woman, no car, no life,
no friends, which is about yourself.
Again, you've got me confused with yourself again.
In your 40s, no girlfriend, no money, no
life, no friends, which is yourself.
talking about yourself again. Self magenta.
I know. It's the same It's the same
40-year-old virgins that come on my
[ __ ] bro. I don't know. I know, man. I
know. I know. They [ __ ] ruin it. It's
always the same 40year-old virgins that
come on here. The same skinned people
with no money. The losers that self
project. It's always the same losers. I
know, bro. I don't know why they do it.
It's [ __ ] weird, man. It [ __ ] up the
whole [ __ ] chat.
It's just a bunch of [ __ ] 40-year-old
virgins that ain't got nothing that self-reflect.
Oh, really? Come back. Sorry, man. Just
saw that. Come back.
This guy probably doesn't even have 1,200 pound.
Again, it's just self-reflecting.
This is what they do on here. They self project.
These people in their 40s, very ugly, no
money, no life. Everything that they
they list about other people is themselves.
Never been with a woman, can't get laid,
very fat, very ugly. Everything is
themselves. That's why whenever I tell
them that, they get more mad. Like
basically this, let me tell you again,
this community has been found by a bunch
of losers. Old, ugly, no friends, no
life, no future. So what they do is they
come on here and project their life onto you.
Know what I'm saying, bro?
Know what I'm saying, bro? It's a
madness. They're just a bunch of fat,
ugly losers that ain't got a life and
they self-reflect the fact that they're
too old to change their life.
You know what I'm saying? They're the
ones sat on YouTube fat, ugly, ain't got
a life, can't get off YouTube. And I
proved that a million times. And because
they fail in life, they take it out on me.
So, I just it's what it is, bro. It
u just to answer your question, bro,
nothing's going on, bro. Just chilling.
I was going to go out tomorrow, but then
I was like I just thought it's best not
to go out.
Yeah, it's just best not to go out, man.
It's too depressing.
Especially when you already know the result.
It's so depressing, bro.
cuz I already know what's going to happen.
I feel like I'm at the stage now. Yeah,
100%, bro. I didn't think it was going
to last that long, but it obviously has.
I definitely think I've lost hope now,
bro. 100 million% I've lost hope now.
100% I have lost hope. All hope.
Yeah, bro. [ __ ] about time. Jesus Christ.
Yeah. Like I said, I know I should have
gave up hope sooner, but you know, but yeah,
I was going to go out tomorrow and drink some Guinnesses.
Nah, I'm not betting on the football either. Nah.
Yeah, I've completely lost hope.
Like now, I used to have that annoying
voice in my head saying, "Go out, try.
You never know. it's going to change. I
I know now, bro. I know it's never going
to change. And it has actually been a
month now. And I'm still not even trying
to cuz I know deep down it's the thing
is the more the more you try,
the more you lose hope and the more
depressed you feel.
So, it's the catch 22. Do you know what
I mean? Because it will never ever ever ever change.
You know, that's it.
It's depressing, bro. It very very depressing.
Nah, I don't gamble anymore.
I don't gamble anymore, bro. No.
What happened there?
the [ __ ] bro.
Could you imagine? I actually lost money
gambling now, bro. I'd actually kill
myself, bro. I'm not even joking. If I
actually lost money gambling now, I'd
actually kill myself, bro.
[ __ ] that. Like, do you remember them roulette days?
Do you actually remember them roulette days?
Jeez, [ __ ] that, bro.
Yeah. No one can be more of a creep than
you, old man.
No one could be more of a creep than
you, you old man.
You old weirdo. Get off of YouTube. Get
a life. Yeah,
but now it's a month. Now it's a month.
I'm definitely definitely definitely definitely done.
I am definitely done, bro. One million%. [ __ ] that.
No, I am [ __ ] done. 1 million%.
[ __ ] these women, bro. [ __ ] them.
They're [ __ ] evil [ __ ] See, I
didn't contradict myself this time, bro.
I stuck by what I said. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Depressing [ __ ] in it, bro. Yes.
Why my belly make noise? I'm not even hungry. Jeez.
I need to go. I need to um I need to do
something different with my dates. Uh I
haven't been on a date for 6 months, so
I don't know what you're talking about.
And yeah, you need to do something with
these dates. When you get them, you need
to not go on them because they've got unrealistic expectations.
Like, they literally go on a date with
you to waste your time and their time
because they've got unrealistic expectations.
Like I said, the past two weeks, I've
come across 27 year old virgins, 28-y
old virgins that are women, and they're
virgins complaining that they can't find
anyone. Why do you think they can't find
anyone? Because they've got unrealistic expectations.
So, they'd rather have no one. They
haven't even kissed anyone. They write
posts saying, "Oh, yeah. Can you help
me? I can't find a man. I'm a virgin."
And they are actually being serious.
So, and obviously there obviously with
them they've got unrealistic expectations.
It's [ __ ] in it, bro. It's this this
society is [ __ ] I swear down.
So, yeah. And I've not been on a date
for 6 months,
so I don't need to do anything
different. I don't do anything wrong on
any of these dates. It's the women that
are the problem.
One million [ __ ] percent it is. 100%
it is. One million trillion [ __ ]
percent. The amount of [ __ ] text
messages I've shown what they've done.
They literally do what they do on
purpose. And I'm not going to argue and
go back and forth. I know they're the
problem. I'm not going on a [ __ ]
plane for [ __ ] 12 hours for the fun
of it, you know? Nope. They don't want
men with um money and success cuz I've
got money. And back then I had money. I
had my own house, had my own job, so
never made a difference. [ __ ] Absolute bollocks.
Nope. Wrong again.
I still have money now, but you know
what I'm saying? Like I I used to have
money coming out my ass. I used to [ __ ]
out money. Never made a difference. And
when I said to him I was a landlord, I
wasn't lying. So nah, even that's not
enough. That's what I'm saying. I can I
can like I can actually play
I can actually play two sides of a coin
cuz I've been somebody that's like had
no money and had no job and had no house
and then I can be somebody that's got
money enough money.
Okay. And then I can be somebody that's
got loads of money. This job and I've
got my own house. None of them makes a difference.
It makes literally not one bit of
difference whether you've got money,
whether you're successful. It is a load
of bollocks, mate.
Cuz when I was when I used to go out a
year ago, I was in probably the I was in
the minority of people my age that had money.
Never made a difference. Never made one
bit of difference.
So you can be successful. You can have
money. It's not going to make a
difference. They're not interested. Simple. So, same [ __ ] not successful.
I used to have a lot of money, bro. A
lot of money. Still have enough money.
Still have enough money. I still still
there, bro. But like I what I mean is I
used to have a lot of money, bro.
Never made a difference. Never made one
bit of difference.
Had a house. Used to go gym.
So was never skinting 4 years. Never
made any bit of difference.
Not one bit of difference was found. Uh,
I've been in so many different stages in
my life and it's never made any difference.
What John is up to nowadays, man. So yeah,
I had a house, had money, used to go to gym.
So never made a difference.
Not many people ever asked me what I
done either. So
yeah, it doesn't matter if you got
money, bro. I mean, I'm sure it matters
if you got millions. Maybe if you had
like millions then
but I had a lot of money bro so
doesn't make any difference. You still
get nowhere. Same depressing [ __ ] I
can't wait to leave you know.
Really can't wait to get out of this
country bro. Seriously can't wait.
It will never change. It's just
depressing living here. There ain't no life.
That's [ __ ] madness, isn't Dad.
Yeah, it is a depressive life.
I [ __ ] hate women, bro.
Does any of you people have regrets in your life?
Let let's let's get into deep
conversations here, right? Has any of
you people ever had any regrets
in your life?
And if you have any regrets,
how many um what were they?
Have you got any regrets or
I was actually speaking to somebody
about this um earlier?
I've only I've only got one regret in my
life, bro. That'll take to the grave with me.
Don't know how many regrets you people have.
Does any of you ever have regrets?
We're talking about regrets in life.
What's your biggest regret in life?
Tell us what's your biggest regret.
That's the topic. Anyone
do you want to know what my biggest
regret was? Is
not going to America the first time I
booked it to go and [ __ ] beat that [ __ ] up?
Yeah. Literally, bro, that's my biggest
regret in life.
The first time, not the second time I
actually went the actual first time.
Biggest regret, bro. Oh, please,
please don't go. Don't go. She was like,
"Oh, don't go." You remember the
19-year-old? She was like, "Don't go.
Don't go. Don't go. Don't [ __ ] go."
Talking me out of the [ __ ] [ __ ]
Biggest regret, bro. That's my biggest
regret, I think.
Here, not so much. Cuz
I don't know, man. It made me travel,
you know, this community and stuff. So
if it wasn't for this community, I don't
think I would have traveled as much. You know
Yeah, she wasn't. She's It's not She
was She is a skank buff.
[ __ ] M as well.
Can't believe the [ __ ] we used to get into.
You think it's funny, ain't it, Steven Howard? Nah. Yeah.
Do you want my number?
I've noticed not many people come on my live anymore.
Like that nickel though.
These women are ignor, isn't it?
that one. And why am I hungry again?
I'm always so hungry in the winter, bro.
It's cold weather makes me so hungry.
Someone told me to get off of YouTube
and live my life.
I should take their advice in it.
Did you see what happened to Rice?
Oh, it's too funny, bro. What happened to Rice? Mad. Yeah.
Yeah. He's [ __ ] in that rice. Jesus Christ, bro. Heat.
the [ __ ] I got in the alleyway.
Steven Howard, do you remember the
[ __ ] I got?
I really want you, but I don't think you want me.
But I don't think you want me. [Laughter]
boy. Skin in the bed [ __ ] with no bed in it.
Skin in the bed [ __ ] with no [ __ ] bed in it.
My skin in the bed with no bed in it. So bad. Bro,
I really want you, but I don't think you want me.
But I don't think you want me.
She gave Peter Belly a [ __ ] A buddy.
Do you remember that O'Neal was Steven
Howard O'Neal's W Street?
Oh, that virgin's mad, mate. He's a
[ __ ] mad virgin, ain't he?
Virgin boy. That virgin boy.
Oh, Nils Water Street. Okay.
Do you reckon people still go in there?
Yeah, they must do. I used to I used to
be there [ __ ]
twice a week.
Nah, not really, bro.
You see what happened to Rice? Madness.
Why do you miss Monty?
[ __ ] rice, man. He's going to get
killed. You know that rice.
He's going to get killed.
What do you think? That rice is going to
get killed in it.
When's Virgin Boy going to lose it? When
are you going to get late?
I'm going to end up in prison. How do
you uh how do you work that one out?
Why would I end up in prison? So matey,
it's very hard to go to prison nowadays.
I'm going to end up in prison.
Good one, bro. Good one.
Why would I end up in prison, lad? Huh? Russia. Yeah.
Stephen, how would you store that?
So why um am I going to end up in
prison? We should watch Side Men Sunday.
Steven Howard, do you want to watch Side Men Sunday?
I can't get over that though. I really
want you, but I don't think you want me.
Why would you suck someone's dick in the alleyway? [Laughter]
Why would you so sick of that anyway?
Oh, the side men. Why
I like the side men? Um, hide and seek videos.
Yeah, but giving somebody a [ __ ] in
an alleyway is kind of mad. Huh?
She was drunk as [ __ ] bro.
But I don't think you want me.
He back, bro.
We need Monty back.
We need money. [Laughter]
We need money on here, man.
I can't get over, bro. He's going to get killed.
Have you ever listened to a song before
and it reminded you of someone? Steven Howard.
Why am I hungry again?
No, I'm just asking Germany. Virgin money.
No, I'm just asking, bro.
I told um
do you remember when I told Laney about
USA is he Steven Howard?
chicken. What kind of chicken?
I already had McDonald's today.
Yeah. Let me get like some grilled
chicken or something. Oh.
Yeah. Do you remember the whole LT thing
when her and LT was when LT was warning
her and stuff? Who was behind it all?
Can't stop laughing at that, bro. Like,
who was behind it all?
Who was behind it? Or do you reckon?
No, but like who was behind it all? Yeah,
the oldest woman. Yeah, she says she
likes to drink early before all the
[ __ ] come out. I was dead. She said
before all the [ __ ] come out.
Reddit is full of trolls, isn't it?
Not me, mate. [Laughter]
How did it go real?
I love it, man.
I love it, bro.
How How did it How did it get real,
though? Like what part of it? [Music] I'm absolute.
These people are skin.
These are skin. I miss Monty, you know.
I actually miss Monty, bro.
I actually miss Monty.
Yeah, I miss Monty.
I miss Monty. Bro,
I used to say, "Why do these people call
me skin?" And he says, "Because these
are skin." Do you ever see Stephen
Howard? Cuz these are skin.
It used to be like reverse, it
boy. Screaming the no, no money in it. Virgin boy,
you're [ __ ] driving me mad. Virgin boy.
[ __ ] driving me bad. You [ __ ] can't you?
Should I play some online roulette? Steven Howard. No.
No, I don't play that [ __ ] bro. Skin little bes in it.
Why is Reddit so addicting, bro?
No, I'm not I'm not playing it, bro.
he's giving me
a little um saying
she getting murder and in it.
You [ __ ] virgin.
[ __ ] in your little bank with no
money in it. Skin virgin. Yeah.
Do you know what?
Nah, I've got some money here. I could
show you some money, but I don't want to.
I don't show self-reflective money.
I don't show skin people money. You can look
you can you can you can hear it. I don't
show skin people money.
Skin self-reflected people money.
I let them keep self-reflecting.
It's funny that way mate.
I ain't virgin in the bed.
We [ __ ] it.
5 nights. Yeah, you people you call
people skin cuz you're skint.
Yeah, there Max.
You call people skin cuz you are the
skin ones. You're sat on YouTube every
day self projecting cuz you're skin.
That's why you spend all day every day
on YouTube cuz you are skin
and you project on to other people.
That's why you talk about skin every day
cuz you are skin. Take to no one.
You people asking,
have you noticed that's all they talk
about even on large A is people being
skin. It's cuz they're skin.
These are skin.
Oh, I won the money game. I showed six
grand and I made you all run off.
I showed you six grand and I made you
all run off. You didn't know what to do
with yourselves. I won the money game.
I've already beat you at the money game.
I sold six grand and made you all run off. Oh,
and the winner is Peter B.
Not that he's in a bench with no [ __ ]
one or bed in it. You know what I mean?
boy with no money. Okay,
let me ask you this question, Stephen
Howard, and I want I want to give you I
want you to give me an unbiased unbiased
uh opinion. You know, don't just agree
with me because you hate tonight. Now,
I've got a question, right? Oh [ __ ]
If virgin boy's got all this money, why
has he got no bed, living near a bed
sit, no teeth, no designer clothes, no
life experience? Why is he still a [ __ ] virgin?
Answer me that question. If he's got all
this money, why has he had a [ __ ] life
for years, but he's got all this money?
This doesn't matter, does it?
No teeth, no designer clothes, no bed, no house,
no travel experience, no restaurant. But
somehow he's got all this money.
Pet is the skin one.
You [ __ ] skin, you
ain't got that man. That's why
that ugly girlfriend
you [ __ ] rat face virgin little [ __ ]
I'm making myself some hot chocolate.
Some hot cocoa.
Do you reckon he'll lose it though? See
now you reckon he'll lose it.
Maybe one there will pop that cherry
no longer be
a baby one there will get laid.
We can only open cray that
you got that
[ __ ] nasty virgin. [ __ ] pick
virgin up and throw him.
Well, I'm gonna [ __ ] do [ __ ] income.
I can't believe he copied my holiday.
He copied my holiday. I can't He went
there cuz I went there. Oh, that's so
cute. You're a little copycat.
He's a little coffee.
You're a little copycat.
A little coffee.
You little coffee cup.
You little copycat.
You little copycat. He's such a copycat.
Because the thing is, Stephen, I also
went to Amsterdam.
What's the chances that he ended up in
Amsterdam as well?
Cuz I went to Amsterdam. You see, [Music]
and somehow you ended up there.
Somehow you ended up in Amsterdam.
I also went to Amsterdam, but
you you somehow ended up there as well.
You somehow ended up in Amsterdam as well
cuz I I went to Amsterdam.
You're a little copycat.
Just like when you said she comes
attractive. You copy him. He's copying the crowd.
He didn't want to feel left out.
He just didn't want to feel left out. Lesson Little copycat.
You went to Amsterdam because I went to Amsterdam.
Not because you wanted to go, you [ __ ] virgin. Yeah,
you ended up in Amsterdam because I went Amsterdam.
got a beard like it.
I know it's a bit scruffy, but
I think it's all right. I think it's pretty cool. You Amsterdam. Copycat.
You'll copy that.
You said Chev is attractive.
You know, you you look tuffy cat.
I don't see what is attractive about this person.
I can't see the the attraction.
Can't see the attraction, mate.
Doesn't look attractive to me.
I might do a video on nonslegs, you
know. Nons the copycat.
I can I should do a little video.
Would you watch it if I did a little
video? I just wanted to know how you
ended up in the same place as I did.
It's not about where you stayed or where
you didn't stay. It's about the fact of
you being in the exact same place.
In the exact same place.
You know what I'm saying?
I I I want to know these things
cuz I'm interested.
I'm going to do a little video. Um, yeah,
but I'm going to do a little video. I'll
be back here in about 10 minutes.