Get the [ __ ] in there, son. I'm [ __ ] waiting.
>> I'm [ __ ] waving, bro.
Wait. Let them go. Let them go. And I'll
[ __ ] do it. Let them go there. Yeah,
they will go. They'll walk.
I'm looking at them two there. I'm them
two. Them two over here. Look them.
We'll do all of them. When my friend go
[ __ ] do all of the [ __ ] you know
what I'm saying?
That's the way, man. Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Go do it.
Go and do it.
A black one, bro.
>> I got eight numbers today. [ __ ] eight
numbers. Go on.
Go and do it, bro. I [ __ ] got eight
numbers today. Do it. Do it. Go on. Go
on. Give it back. Do it back. Go,
>> bro. You saw me do [ __ ] I don't know
about [ __ ] five in front of you, bro.
I got eight numbers. I got [ __ ] eight
numbers. This is my lucky number. Go on.
Do another one there. Go on. Hey,
Charlie. We're in the [ __ ] spoons.
Go on. Do it. Do it. Go. Go.
Yeah. Go, bro. [Music]
I would do it, but I don't want them to
see me do it. No one's already done. Go
on. Do it now.
Charlie with Parkland. Go on, bro. Go
on. Go on. No. Go over. Go over. Go
over. Go over. Go over. Hey, Charles,
man. We out here, bro.
Go on then. Go. Go. Go. Go on. Go on.
>> Go on. Go on, bro. I see you earning your
[ __ ] [ __ ] How many devils?
>> My gosh,
Charlie. Guinness is a [ __ ] goat.
Guinness is a goat now.
>> You going to do it?
>> You're scared, is it? You're scared, bro.
Listen, me and Charlie met once, but we
weren't on a sesh. Me and Charlie needs
to be up for a sesh. Me and Charlie's
I'm telling you, mate.
All right, Charlie. Listen, we need to
be up again. I come to not once I let you say
listen bro you you going to do it I'm
going to do it in a minute I'm going to
end up [ __ ] doing it but hey Charles
I'm going to end up doing it and you
going to do it you going to do it
>> do it brother do it
I don't [ __ ] fight. I don't feed him
in front of you.
>> I wouldn't have any.
>> Just do it. Just do it.
>> Just [ __ ] do it, bro.
>> He's scared.
>> Go on. Go. I've got eight numbers. Go
>> Just [ __ ] do it.
>> I will do it. I've done so many here,
bro. I've got eight numbers,
>> mate. You're going to do it. Go on.
>> You got do
[ __ ] eight numbers. I got eight
That's a bad You should do it. Come on.
They're waiting for you, bro. Come on.
Guinness. Guinness. Guinness.
Hold on. Hold on.
Just do it. I've already got eight
numbers, bro. I'm chilling, bro. I'm
waiting for my friend, bro. Just do it.
I would do it if I was you. [ __ ] it.
Might as well. Go. You're going to die
in the end anyways. We're going to die
in the end, bro. scared.
>> I don't want I don't see I don't want
anyone else to see me somewhere else.
>> What are you drinking?
>> Guinness. I'm drinking Guinness. Listen,
I'll do the blonde. You do the black.
>> I like
I'll do the blonde.
>> You do the black. >> Yeah.
>> Wait. I just You know the thing is one
can't see me.
Chill. Chill. Chill. Chill. Okay.
I got the number. I got the number, bro.
[ __ ] nine numbers. We got nine.
>> You got nine. I am back. Oh, bro. I am
[ __ ] You got nine numbers. I swear to
God, we got nine, bro.
That was mad. That wasn't mad.
got nine numbers. This guy tried cop
blocking me. He was a dirty bastard. He
tried cop blocking me. It never worked though.
>> [ __ ] nine numbers, bro. I broke my
record. I have actually broke my record.
Where the [ __ ] is this [ __ ] I'm waiting
for him, bro.
Bro, I swear to God, [ __ ]
I got nine. I broke my record. Done.
I'm [ __ ] mad. I am. I'm a crazy bastard.
He was trying, bro. He was trying. He
was trying. Sorry, man. Sorry, boss.
>> Hey. Hey,
>> I got nine numbers, bro. I'm [ __ ]
mad. I'm a crazy bastard. Hey, bro. I
swear I broke my record. I broke my record,
bro. I swear to God. I broke the record.
They weren't having it at all at all,
mate. They having it at all.
I'm here, man.
>> M I'm [ __ ] screaming, bro.
Oh, man. [ __ ] fingers falling.
Hey, you know, Guinness is the go, is
it? It's the go drink.
Oh man, it's rude, isn't it?
That's just London though. It's full of
rude people. Get used to it, man. Man.
Oh, brother. Sorry, boss.
Why does no one in London speak to each
other, man? [ __ ] madness,
bro. He was like
1% away from cocking me, [Applause]
>> bro. I mean, it's
Bro, what the [ __ ] The guy is outside.
>> Where the [ __ ] is this guy?
[ __ ] quit blocking me, bro.
>> Sorry, brother. Sorry, man. Sorry,
>> Where is he? Where is he?
>> Come inside. Come.
Come on. You can't.
Come on, buddy.
Checking his ball out.
Oh, how you doing? Good. Long time. Long time. Huh? [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] hard. Yeah. No. No. No. [Laughter]
>> We're going to We're going to get some more.
>> Baba. We're going to get some more.
We're going to get some more. Yeah. >> More. Good.
Good, bro. That's my friend,
>> bro. We're going to get some more,
>> bro. No, listen. Listen, you remember
last time, bro? You remember last time it?
>> You love it, though. You love it. You
love it. It be honest. You love it, it like it
approaching and [ __ ] bro. in it,
bro. You love it in it. It
got a number just there. Bro, the guy
tried top rock to me and [ __ ] He tried
so hard. Almost. What?
Behind. Behind. Behind the two behind
us. I've got the number. The blonde. The
blood number. I've got the blood. I
didn't like the [ __ ] kiss and [ __ ] there.
Let's have a baby Guinness. You want a
baby? Baby Guinness.
>> Baby Guinness. You want straight away or?
>> When do you go to Thailand, bro?
>> I'm going to Thailand in November, bro.
>> Oh, next month.
>> Yeah. No. Month after month, >> bro.
Bro, do you want a Guinness straight? Do
you want a baby Guinness?
>> Oh, after.
>> Sure. Sure. Baby Guinness. Well, now
[ __ ] now, bro. Listen, you think it's
so funny, is it? You think everything is
funny, but it's not funny, bro. You
think it's funny, is it? Is it?
>> Nah, it's not funny, bro. You can't even
speak to someone. I got nine numbers, bro.
Huh? I'm on YouTube. Say hi to everyone.
>> Yeah, say hi. Yo, everybody. You What's
up, brother? Yeah. Look, we out here, bro. Turn on.
>> Oh, bro. I've been on this. If my first
Guinness, I had to be first.
>> Who's watching? >> Huh? Say again.
>> 15 people.
>> Yeah. Who? >> 15.
>> Random people.
>> Yeah. No. Like people that follow people
that support this channel.
Well, listen. Me and you, we go. So we
go way back. Me and you go so bad lot of time. Remember
>> because you always
>> you love it in it. Yeah.
>> I always reject me when I
>> No, I [ __ ] don't. Bro, you remember
my birthday? Remember my birthday? When
is my birthday?
>> You remember you come with me in it? Yeah.
>> He's scared. He won't do it. You won't
do it. Yeah. Listen, listen. Remember
when you come out on my birthday? When
was my birthday? Remember my birthday?
When was my birthday?
>> October, right?
We going out again. 27th of October.
Tomorrow, bro. How is it tomorrow? Next month.
I had a one night on my birthday.
Remember two years, bro? Two years went to
school. I [ __ ] the [ __ ]
bro. You know what I mean?
When's your birthday again? When's your birthday?
>> Dude, 1979
in. How old are you? >> 28.
>> How? You're 99. 1995. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, [ __ ] You're older than me then? >> You? >> 27.
>> 97. I'm 28 next month. How old are you?
How can you be 28? You're born 95. How
can you be 28? No. 96 96. So you're 30.
No, you got me. You have to be 30.
>> How I forgot my
>> You must know when you're [ __ ] born.
I was born 97 October 27th.
Like we need a [ __ ] Guinness shot,
brother. That's what we need. We need a
[ __ ] baby Guinness.
We're going to down that [ __ ] bro.
>> You remember one of my tennis
scared, bro? Every time you're scared. Why,
>> brother? Why are you scared, man?
>> My my landlord,
>> we're [ __ ] waving, by the way. We're
[ __ ] steaming. We are we are
this is you know
the next round is yours. Yeah. First
round is mine. Next round is yours.
Let me get two baby Guinnesses.
Thank you boss. Oh man.
11. Next one is you. Yeah.
>> Oh, it's all happening.
>> But what happened to
>> Yeah. He don't come out anymore.
You remember it? You remember it?
>> Yeah. Don't come out. He's a [ __ ] man.
>> Yeah, but I haven't heard from him for
like 2 years. Remember New Dem.
But we're going to do the Guinness shot
together. Yeah, we're going to do the
baby Guinness shot together.
>> Look at it. [ __ ]
>> Three. Three.
All clear shot.
You like it, Charlie? Do you like it?
Charlie, look at me, bro. I'm [ __ ]
That's the baby finish. Yeah. Together. Together.
Yeah. Count. We need to count. We need
to count. Yeah. One, two, three,
>> we're going. Remember, I'm going. We're
living there, bro. 100%.
>> How long?
>> Ever. Forever. I've never told you that. >> Yeah.
>> My friend lives there now. He's never coming.
>> Go. Go. Do it. Do it. Behind you. Behind
Go. Behind you. Go. You had a shot. Go.
How many times? Good.
I got nine numbers. Say [ __ ]
work, bro. [ __ ]
>> in the street. >> No
clubs or clubs. Pubs clubs club. Make sure
>> and the other one I don't know on the
street they weren't having any of it, bro.
You getting it? Do it. Go. [ __ ] it. Bro,
listen. Listen to me. You only live once.
Only. When we're dead, we're dead. Think about
>> do them three. Go on. Go. I got three.
I've got three numbers here. Just in this place.
Yeah. Go on. [ __ ] it. You've got nothing
to lose, bro.
I beat my record already. I'm [ __ ]
way, bro. [ __ ]
Hey, I would never get it.
>> Kill it, bro. Kill it. Kill it.
>> I done it sober.
>> I mean,
you Scott, I pull your [ __ ] I do it.
Just do it, you [ __ ]
You can come
>> somewhere, bro. Where we going? Where we
>> No. Can come here. >> Huh? >> Here. >> Yeah. >> [ __ ]
I'm going after here, bro.
We need to send it, bro. Do them three
over there. Do them three over there. Do
it. Wait. Wait. You do it.
>> I've done, bro. I've done like [ __ ]
five here already.
You know these people on YouTube,
they've not got no life. Tell them
they've got no life, though. They're sat on,
no life, no confidence. Sat on sat on
[ __ ] YouTube. They got no life, bro.
They're [ __ ] ugly bastards.
Ugly bastards. That's what they are.
Go out with me. Come out with me. Yeah.
Stop being a sad bastard. They got no
life, bro. On YouTube.
>> What do you What do you want? Guinness.
Not out, bro. We're finishing goodness
again. No. Navy Guinness.
It's okay. I'll buy a skinn.
If I buy you this skinniness, are you
going to go and do it?
You're a [ __ ] bro. You're a [ __ ]
This guy is a [ __ ] bro.
>> Hey, this guy is so scared, bro. I told
him to go and speak to them women behind
us. He won't do it. He's scared. My
friend, bro, do it.
>> Bro, I gave him a baby Guinness. I
bought two Guinness for us. He won't have it.
Huh? Do the killers. Get
>> through the killers. Let's
go. I'm getting you the killer. I'm
getting you the killer. Yeah, you're
going to [ __ ] do it. Yes, you [ __ ]
walk. What? What do you want? Yes.
>> Okay. Two Guinnesses and two tequilas.
>> No, mama. Listen. Two Guinnesses and two
tequilas pints. Who giveth page and who
the shots? Got no [ __ ] excuse. Yeah. [ __ ] 22. [Music]
He ain't got no excuse now, bro. Tell
him he's a [ __ ] He doesn't do it. He's
>> Yeah, there you go. 23 cost me in the trouble.
I got you a Guinness and I got you a
[ __ ] tequila shot.
It cost me£23. I've I've just spent 40
[ __ ] pound on you. Hey, bro. I just
spent 40 pound on you, the [ __ ]
Listen, bro. 40 pound I spend on you to
[ __ ] go and speak to someone because
you're you're going to
>> You're here in it. You're here. I'm
going to leave you here. Going to leave
you here, bro. I got you and I got your [ __ ] straw.
There's no excuse. There's no excuse
now, bro. I spent 25 [ __ ] B on you.
>> We are [ __ ] bro. We're fast.
Two Guinnesses, two shots, and we're
going to do them [ __ ] over there. Tell
them. Tell them. Tell them. We're going
to do it. Yeah. We're going to do it.
Oh, where the [ __ ] are these [ __ ]
Oh. Oh, they're still there. They're
still there. See, I'm limited to what I
could do, bro. I'm limited to what I can
do because there's people here watching
me and that
>> I'm kind of [ __ ]
>> Bro, we are actually [ __ ] Listen,
we're actually [ __ ]
bro. There's your Guinness. Go.
Cheers. Cheers. There you go.
>> Lovely. And there we go. We got the tequila shots.
>> We got the tequila shots. Hey, we need
to sit somewhere, bro. What's up?