Just lovely. Oh.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Need to get some food. I'm starving.
Oh, I'm home now. What happening? Oh.
Oh, man. My phone walking all the way
back. I walk all the way back. Oh, what the
I've got a funny story to tell you.
stories telling you
I didn't believe it
I'm you probably won't believe me just
due to the fact that I'm one sec.
I'm just make this bed.
Hello many days sunshine
guess where Peter B ended up be mate. Yeah.
10 numbers. 10 [ __ ] numbers. You
bastard. You crazy bastard.
Oh my goodness. I'm a crazy bastard.
L got 10 numbers. How the [ __ ] someone
get 10 [ __ ] numbers, bro?
This duvet is a bit damp still.
What else can you really do?
Unless we put it back in.
Yeah, I'm to be fair.
I'm [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Oh, mate.
It's a bit damp. Sorry. I need to put it
back in one second, bro.
So, went out today. I got I got 10
numbers. I got 10 real [ __ ] numbers,
bro. Oh, imagine that.
Imagine that. 10 real [ __ ] numbers.
Oh, man. I need to get a I need a
McDonald's. Me, bro. I'm starving, bro. Sorry.
So obviously I don't go to drink much
anymore, do I? So
Oh my god.
I need to put one second.
Need a McDonald's, man. I need a [ __ ] M.
Not even not even joking. I've got dead,
bro. another [ __ ]
So the story is once again we put this
pillowcase in on and then
I'll tell you ordered this McDonald's
and then I'll tell you the story.
Hey darn it,
that's the lottery. So, um,
one second. Let me just order this that off.
So, story is we're doing a football bet tomorrow.
Honestly, honestly, I'll tell you the
story. Yeah. One sec. So, basically,
one second. Let me just order this mac.
I'll tell you the story, bro.
So, the story is One second. Let me just
get this McDonald's.
I need a McDonald's. Bro, I'm starving, bro.
I'm really [ __ ] I'm so drunk. It's
not even funny, bro.
Obviously, Virgin Boy ain't drunk cuz
you can't afford it. He's a skint bastard. So,
one second, please. I better get rid of me.
Now, will they tell you?
Um, I'm really drunk.
Oh, four McDonald's nuggets. Lovely.
I'm now walk
the s my jeans broke. I need to buy some
new jeans as well.
Obviously, Virgin Boy can't do that cuz
he's a skin bastard. Um,
please just give me a second, bro. Please.
And I'll be with you.
I don't want no pickles.
That's it. So, we got that.
Please. One second. Okay. So five. No.
[ __ ] sake. I don't want
I want large coke. That's what I want. Yes. Lovely.
So I want one second, please.
One second. What is that?
Virgin boy in the bed [ __ ] with no bed.
No money in it. Upgrade.
No. Okay. Okay. So, I went out today. I
got 10 numbers and bro, I went to this
brass house, which is this escort house.
You're not going to believe me, bro. And
I said, "Listen, I'll give you £100 um for
um for a [ __ ] no condom, and I get
to finish in your mouth."
And they were like, "Okay, fair enough."
So, she was midway uh give me the
[ __ ] sucked her tit, suck my balls,
suck my dick, whatever. And she's like,
"Oh, you can't finish your
deal. That's what I paid you for."
She weren't having none of it at all. at
all. I was like, "No, I gave you money."
"Yeah, you have to do it." And then the
guy come, I was like, "No, I want my
money back." "No, no, no." He's like,
"You got to leave." "No, no." I want my
money back. And he was getting all assy
and [ __ ] I was like, "No, you give me
my half my money back or I'm going to do
your windows and I'm going to smash the
whole place up, bro. It ain't a joke."
Yeah. It's not about the money. I don't
care about 50, 60, but bro, you're not
going to take the piss out of me. It's
principal at the end of the day, bro.
It's principle. you're not going to take
the piss out of me, bro.
Give my money back now. I'm going to
smash the whole place up. And he weren't
having none of it at all. At all. I went
to the kebab shop. I was like, "Brother,
you got a hammer? Give me a hammer. I'll
give you the money for the hammer. I'm
going to smash this whole place up. Bro,
this guy's taking a piss." I was looking
for a brick, stones. They weren't having
none of it. The guy come out. I'm going
to leave if I smash the whole place up.
Um, and then the guy's like, "Yeah,
okay. Hey, we can give you £50 back. So,
I was like, "Okay, fair." I got half my
money back. So, I mean, suck my dick.
Suck my balls. But, bro, don't take the
piss out of me, bro.
Don't care what you're about. You're not
taking a piss out of me. Simple, right?
Remember that, bro. You're not taking a
piss out of me. That's that's that's the
that's the that's the moral of the
story, bro. I don't care how much the
money is. The people in the street were
like, "Oh, don't don't do it for £100."
I was like, "Bro, it's not about £100.
Yeah, you're not taking a piss out of
me. I'm going to do your whole windows
in. If you don't give me half my money
back, whatever. I'm going to smash your
whole windows in. So, what way is it
going to be? Your whole windows going
through or you going to give me give me
half the money back? Give me half the
money back. We'll shake hands. We'll
move on. Like, don't take the piss
the piss out of me. Yeah. Um I don't
care who you know. I don't care. You
know what I'm saying? And I'd rather die
than someone take the piss out of me.
Cuz at the end of the day, we've got
we've got one life. We'll live it and
then we die in the end. Don't take the
piss out of me, brother. And he knew in
the end cuz there was people on the top.
They weren't enough to do. I was like,
"Bro, I'm going to smash the whole
windows in." So don't try like sleeping
and that cuz the windows are going in,
bro. But I swear to God, the windows are
going in. If he doesn't give me half of
this money back, the windows are going in. Simple.
And yeah, he come out and said, "Yeah,
okay. They will give you half the money
back. Fair enough. So that's it.
Yeah. He weren't going to give it back,
bro. No, that's a piss state. The
windows were going to go through, bro.
Yeah, the windows of the door was going
to go through. Um, so
yeah, it's a madness, bro.
I don't care who you know, bro.
That's the thing. I don't care who you
know. The windows are going in, bro. And
even if I need to do it cowardly, I'll
do it cowardly. Like, if you don't want
somebody coming in your mouth, that's
fair enough, bro. But at the end of the
day, you got given £100. It's not about
people have got their different prices.
You got given £100. I don't want to wank
myself off. Yeah. If I wanted to wank
myself off, I would have wanked myself off. So
that's it, bro. Simple. Cuz I said to
your neighbors as well, I'll do the
windows in, bro. Like, I don't care who
they know. I don't give a [ __ ] And at
the end of the day, the only reason it
didn't go in in the first place is cuz I
couldn't find a brick. I couldn't find a
hammer, bro. I was trying to find a
[ __ ] object to do the windows in.
Like, go to jail. I don't give a [ __ ]
bro. Go in jail over smashing the
window, bro. Then so be it, bro. You
can't let people take the piss. It's not
even just about money, bro. It's not
It's not about the money, bro. It's
about the fact that they're trying to
take the piss. So,
in the end, yeah, the guy just gave the
money back. So,
it's fine. Whatever, bro. Give him my
half money back. That's fine, bro.
Which lesson was it supposed to be? See,
I'm not a [ __ ] but don't take the
piss out of me. That's my whole story.
piss. You know what I'm saying? Like, that's it. What's that?
All right. Uh, she was okay.
Yeah, she was all right, mate. Yeah, but
she weren't she was good, bro. But like,
don't take the piss out of me, bro.
About take your£100 and take the L. Are
you mad, bro? your windows
like I'm giving your you give half the
money back I'm putting your windows in
simple cuz it's norally less than 60 I'm
going to do the windows in simple bro so
like and they I think they were getting
shook in it like the people upstairs are
getting scared of that in it I was like
bro I'm going to do the windows in like
it's not a joke just cuz I'm dressed as
like a casual smart man bro don't think
I can't act like a road man and [ __ ] you
know what I mean
yeah I'll [ __ ] [ __ ] can do the whole
windows in, bro. It's not a joke, lad.
The whole windows will go.
But he was all right in the end. Like, I
don't care if you're from South America.
I don't give a [ __ ] bro. You're windows
are going to go in, brother. I do not understand.
Uh, so where's the um Oh, lovely. They're here.
Oh, wow. They're here. I've order I'm
ordering some Mackey's. The Mackey's is
on its way.
Oh, friend. We go and get uh stop
talking about yourself. No
self-reflecting on my channel, buddy.
Yeah. So, the guy come out and he said,
"I'll give you half your money back." I Okay.
Got your sucker tits. That's fair.
See, I'm not a violent person, but I'm
not having people take the piss out of me, bro.
I was like, "Oh, you're gonna You said
no. You don't tell me where to go. you
And at the end of the day, right, I was
like, listen, okay, he's not going to
give the money back. If he's not going
to physically give the money back, then
I'll just do the windows in which is
going to cost him 300. So, it's like, it
ain't it ain't a joke, bro. Like, yeah,
I could have stayed there, but the guy
the people was living above them,
they must have told them as well that
like the windows are going to,
you know what I mean? So, it's it's one
of them with it.
And that ain't my style, bro. Like, I
don't even like to fight or get into
violence or whatever. Like, I met a lot
of cool people today, but like don't
take the piss out of me. Like, if
someone's giving you £100, they're
coming in your mouth, bro. If someone's
giving you a seven, if someone's giving
you £70, they're not coming in your
mouth. It's simple. If someone's giving
you that kind of money, they're coming
in your mouth. So, like, it's
they're, you know, at the end of the
day, they're coming in your mouth, bro.
You know what I mean? There's no [ __ ]
misunderstanding or anything. And like,
I don't want to wank myself off. So,
it's just the things you got to deal
with. This is partly why, bro. Honestly,
I don't go out anymore.
Um, because of this reason, like the
negativity, the [ __ ] and stuff.
Like, I can't be annoyed with it. But
yeah, you offered half my money back.
Fair enough. So, take the money. And
man ain't going to jail, bro. Man ain't
going to jail over criminal damage.
I don't care who they know. Simple.
Like, it's that it. That's it, bro.
Like, you need to put your foot down, bro.
It was like the USA Izzy thing. She
didn't know who she was [ __ ] with.
That's why she played all of this victim
and better to death cuz she didn't know
who she was [ __ ] with. That's it. You
had to take the piss out of people. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no. You know what I'm saying?
Like, you're lucky, bro. You're lucky.
Like, really, really are. At the end of
the day, you don't know who you're
[ __ ] with. And I'm not even a big
person. I'm not about I'm not
I'm not claiming to be strong. I'm not
claiming to be this hard Mike Tyson, but
I'm not going to have someone take the
piss out of me. Simple. Like, I think
that's fair enough. And that should go
for like most people. You know what I mean?
Like listen, do you know that USA is he?
Listen, let me tell her something, bro.
Mother's life, bro.
Listen, listen. Let me tell you
something. Between me and you, Between
me and you, bro. She's so lucky I didn't
go that first time, bro. And I got my money back.
You don't go, bro. No. Listen, bro.
Someone's going to get killed. Like I
know you I know you find it funny and
it's all laugh and I would as well, bro.
To be fair. You might as well. Like the
McDonald's or um you know you whatever
it was. It's me or them, bro. I don't
need people on YouTube, bro. I don't
need people on YouTube backing me up,
not backing me up, whatever. I just know
that it was me or them, bro. Simple.
And the only reason I didn't go that
first time though is because at the end
of the day, I was being begged not to.
That 19year-old was like, "Don't go. I
beg you, don't go." And I was like, "No,
this little [ __ ] needs to be taught a
lesson, bro. She needs to be taught a
good oldfashioned lesson. Don't take the
piss out of me, bro." And at the end of
the day, it's the same thing today in
the brothel. I don't need to argue or
try and snatch my money back. I'll do
the whole windows.
Simple. Like, you give me half my money
back. my money back or I'm going to do
I'm going to do the windows in. I don't
care who you know. You don't know me,
bro. Simple. You don't know me. I don't
need to know who you know. You don't
know me, bro. So, at the end of the day,
when I do them windows in, where you
going? You don't know me. Where you
going? You don't know me. It doesn't
matter if I know you are. I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
You know what I'm saying? Like, you only
live once, [ __ ] And your your
life is not to be took the piss out of.
Your life is to
That's all I know, bro. And it goes for anyone. Simple.
Don't take the piss out of me, mate.
Simple, man. Want to give me half my
money back? There. Good. 20. That's what
you're supposed to do. Good. Good. It's fair.
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. You know what I mean?
Yeah, you're not going to
escort thing was mad though. It ain't
even funny, bro. It was madness. You
don't give £100.
You don't give someone £100.
Yeah. To give you a [ __ ] to come
unless you're coming in their mouth.
You know what I mean, bro? Like, no,
bro. You're not doing that. The windows
were going to go in cuz there's like a
window right next to the door. It's like
you got I was going to do the window in,
bro. Like, I said to them as well. I
said to him as well, um, you know, um, the whole,
you know, it's it's like a downstairs,
so the windows next to the door. I went
to the [ __ ] kebab shop. I was like,
bro, you got a hammer. Give me a hammer
now. I'll give you the money. Give me a
hammer. And I'm doing the windows in.
Simple. And he's, "Oh, no, brother. We
have no We have no I was like, give me a
hammer." I was looking for brick,
stones. I was looking for everything, bro.
I chucked like a thing on the window,
bro. I chuck like a
[ __ ] cuz you're not going to take my
money and mug me off, bro.
You're not going to take my money and
mug me off. Give me half my money back.
You gave me half my money back. That's
it. Shake hand.
Um, and it's not about the money, bro.
Like, I'm not The people upstairs had
nothing to do with it was like, "Oh,
yeah, just take it as a 100 pound loss."
No, bro. I'm not taking it as a 100
pound loss. No, brother. I'm not taking
that £100 loss cuz they know really and
truly if that window went in right they
would have had to pay 3400 to get that
window fixed and they don't know me so
where they looking for me bro they don't
know me they don't know my name they
don't know anything so what they going
to do that's why the guy had to come out
bro cuz if he didn't give it the window
was going in
so give him yeah give me half my money
bro you suck my dick you suck my balls
sucked your tits you give me a [ __ ]
whatever bro you're not going to take my
whole money, bro. You mad?
Yeah, it's fine, bro. It's what it is,
bro. That is It is what it is. We don't
need to do no extra [ __ ] bro.
And the people upstairs had nothing to
do with us. I'll take your £100 loss.
Well, I'm just going to let someone take
a £100 off me. Are you mad, bro? So, I'm
just going to let someone take the piss
out of me. You mad? And then the people
up the stairs must have told the people
downstairs and that's why they come
outside. Bro, the window's going in.
Simple. like [ __ ] [ __ ] man.
Yeah, it worked out cheaper as well.
Don't take the piss out of me, bro. We
can meet halfway, but that's it.
Isn't funny, it's [ __ ]
cuz their windows went in, bro. and
whole and the whole neighborhood would heard it.
Anyways, we got 10 numbers.
No, I think we saved like 20. No, it was like £20.
I think it was about 20 we saved. So,
no, I weren't going to have that, bro.
I'm not having that. I'm not having
someone take the piss out of me, bro.
Money, no money. We already have it from
these [ __ ] women in this country. We
always have we have these [ __ ] in
this country. We're not going to deal
with your [ __ ]
So you save 20 pound. It's fair enough.
Like don't don't take the piss. Do not
Someone a [ __ ] like you're doing. Let
them come in your [ __ ] mouth. End of.
What's the extra [ __ ]
What is the extra [ __ ] I said if you
don't give I'm calling the police, bro.
I said I'm calling the police. I'm doing
your windows in, bro. So, what are you
doing? What are you doing, bro? What are
you doing? They're from South America. Yeah.
And that's the problem with it is at the
end of the day, bro. Like, I'm not going
to let someone take a piss.
I'm not having it, bro. I'm not having it.
We already deal with these
as it is. We're going to do a 100 pound
football bet tomorrow.
Yeah, I got half the money back. I just
wanted half the money back. So, I saved
20 pound to be fair.
But you got given £100. You're already
sucking someone's dick. Let them come in
your mouth. What's the whole problem
with it? And this is partly why I don't
really go out much in this country
anymore, Taylor. This is part of the
reason why I don't really [ __ ] with it.
Cuz [ __ ] like this, like, it would have
ended up bad. If they didn't give the
money back, it would have ended up bad, bro.
Give half the money.
You suck my dick. Suck my balls. Fair
enough. We're even. Done. Even though I
got the last half, but you know what I
mean? Like it's just like it's just
madness how [ __ ] up. You know, it's
like the first woman I approached today
was a stuck up [ __ ] as well. Even though
I got 10 numbers, she's like, "Oh, uh,
yeah. Um, I'm engaged." I was like, "Am
I supposed to know you're engaged?"
You're just all like [ __ ] bro.
Cuz you did suck my dick and all of that, but
so I was like, "That's fine." Cuz the
whole extra payment is coming in their
mouth. So if you give somebody £100,
right, it's that you come in their
mouth. Um, that's part of like the 4050,
right? It's coming in their mouth cuz a
lot of people don't like doing it. So
she was trying to say, "Oh, I gave her £100."
And they like, "Oh yeah, well we're not
going to come in your mouth. So give me
half my money back then." Simple. Which
a [ __ ] without coming in the mouth is about 70.
So I paid 60 and I didn't come in the
mouth. So that's like the whole point of
it was like at the end of the day,
right? like you
to to to blow job and come in their
mouth if they even allow it. So I I just
gave you 100. You're not going to take
£100 and then [ __ ] chuck me out of this place.
So it's just all negative.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Then she
weren't having it. Yeah, exactly. That's
what I'm saying. She weren't having it.
So I was like, "Okay, give me half my
money back. Give me my money back." I
said, "Okay, we'll give you half the
money back." I said, "Okay, give me half
the money back."
Simple. So, she gave half the money
back. So, he gave half the money back, rather.
Yeah. But they couldn't because they
already sucked my dick and sucked my
balls. So, I mean
I mean I just took half to be honest. It was fine.
But they were really trying it on, bro.
They were really trying it on.
No, half fine, bro. I mean, it's like 70
pound [ __ ] with no [ __ ] condom.
Like, no, he weren't. He was the same
size as me, to be fair.
What do you mean? I sucked her tits.
Yeah, I sucked her tits. I kissed her.
It's fine, bro. I don't mind. I'll take
half back, bro. But you're not taking
£100 and not letting me finish in your
mouth. That was the whole point of it.
Right or wrong? Do you understand? So
yeah, I sucked her tits. [ __ ] she
sucked my dick. She sucked my balls.
Um but like yeah, you're not taking all
my money, bro.
Cuz obviously I didn't want sex. So yeah.
at the end of the day, I couldn't really
ask for the whole I mean I could have,
but I mean just take half the I mean it
worked out cheaper anyways. So [ __ ]
with no condom. Let them call your
mouth. It probably been about 60 70
only paid 50. So yeah, bro,
bro, that's why they were [ __ ]
himself. Yeah, it's not worth £100, bro.
What the [ __ ] [ __ ] worth a [ __ ] £100. So
if I only paid 50 60 to get that then it
was worth it at the end of the day. But
not 100 bro that's next level bro. I
don't even think people paid that for sex. So
my McDonald's is almost up.
Yeah. She was trying to rob me, bro.
It's all right, bro. Half half is fine.
And then anyway, she still sucked my dick.
She still sucked my dick. Her mouth went
on my dick and my balls and I stopped
her tips as well. So I thought it was
fair enough. But that was a nir windows
was going in, bro. Trust me, their
windows was going to go in, brother. And
if I had ever I have to if I had to end
up in the police, I would have ended up
in the police. It is what it is. YOLO.
You only live once.
That USA is bro. She's so lucky I didn't
go that first time, bro. She would have
got baded up, bro. You think that's a joke? So yeah,
where are we? 60.
Oh, lovely food here. No, it was worth
50, bro. I still got what I wanted, but
not what I really really wanted. So
I'm saying finishing. You can't finish
in someone's [ __ ] mouth. What the
[ __ ] is that all about, bro?
That is a madness, bro. I did finish. I
just didn't finish in about.
That's the whole point.
There you go. You all right, man? Uh 66. >> Yeah.
>> Drinking. Thank you, brother. Yeah. [ __ ]
Yeah. The whole [ __ ] windows was
going to go in.
The whole windows was going to go in.
Bro, I can't believe that. That's a madness. [Music] Oh, lovely
foody foody foodie.
I love these. Lucky. Yeah. Yeah.
I was going to do the whole window
again, but you don't believe me. You [ __ ]
Listen, let me tell
you, if I went to America for the first
time, I was going to America.
You know, you think it's funny and
stuff, right? But here's the thing. I
wouldn't have been here now.
Let's let's let's just [ __ ] stop
laughing at everything. Yeah. Let's
actually be adult about this.
Let's actually be serious about this right now.
If I went the very first time, I was
supposed to go.
The very first time somebody would have
ended up dead, bro.
China man. China. I didn't know it was China, man.
I would some I wouldn't be here now or
they would be here now. Oh no.
Oh free nothing.
No, seriously. We would have. What?
It's not funny, bro.
That China man, bro. We got money to
spend. We got money to burn.
Who cares? We got the same numbers.
Who cares, bro? We got money to burn, bro.
Now the thing is
Stephen Al about money. Yeah. No,
the reason I don't show these people
money is cuz they're projecting. See,
when I went to the pub and show and
spent money, spent 40 quid. Who cares,
bro? It's only money.
People are people.
Just like that£100 was only money. But
you're not going to take the piss out of
me. It could be one p. It could be £100.
I don't give a [ __ ] You're not going to
take the piss out of me.
Hey, bro. Who cares?
It's only money. We can't take it with
us when we're dead. So, live your life
to the fullest.
You made a complete mug on me, didn't
he? That's nice for man. But that guy,
bro. Yeah. I said, "Give me half the money back.
Give me half the money back, bro.
Yeah, I bought him drinks because I was
trying to get him to approach, but he
was too scared.
I was I was listening to a song two days
ago. It reminded me of USA. I don't know
why, but it just did. He remind
USA is he bro? Why?
Oh, Macky's lovely.
Yeah, he ain't got no balls. I got 10
numbers today, bro. [ __ ] 10 [ __ ] numbers.
Nice, bro. and some
[ __ ] 10 [ __ ] numbers. You p them.
You know what? I love Charlie. I love
Unworthy Cop. Charlie is a [ __ ]
legend. I love Charlie. Charlie's a good
guy. Big up.
You know what? I was laughing saying
that rice thing.
Rice got [ __ ]
Yeah, I'll take half my money back. Give
me half my money back, bro.
So I can say that you stuck my dick,
bro. You stuck my DNA. You're not going
to take £100 like me, you [ __ ]
You see that guy that tried to cop me?
You see that guy from Echo that tried
coping me? the [ __ ]
So that's why I don't show money. Steven Howard,
you see how much I spent in the pub
today and whatever.
It's what it is, bro.
there cuz I don't show these people
money for the selfs
this That was [Music]
I got Philly burger, nuggets,
[ __ ] drink, [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] bastard.
Mom sitting in a bedroom with no bed, no
money in it. Oh,
they all waste time.
I want to batter up that USA, bro. I
want to batter her up, bro. Stupid
little [ __ ] She didn't know who she was
[ __ ] with. Please, he's stalking me.
He's stalking me. [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] J.
She's a [ __ ] J. He's a [ __ ]
about that life, [ __ ]
USA is not about that life.
I drunk today. Then I went on the rum course.
So that move what? I was gonna [ __ ] her
up, bro. Stupid little [ __ ]
Yeah, I said, "Why did you take my offer?"
Huh? Why did you take my offer four
months ago, [ __ ] So, I'll come
to you and tell you about yourself in
front of your boyfriend,
[ __ ] [ __ ] skank. Little [ __ ] You [ __ ]
Cuz you like using that [ __ ] word. M
that USA is a [ __ ]
That's what she is a [ __ ]
[ __ ] her. That's what she is.
She's not my mama.
Pet can't get attached anymore because
he's already found his mama.
that one cuz he's already found his mama [ __ ]
I was supposed to go cinema.
Which one, bro? There's been a lot of white knights
and they all [Music] One, bro. Banger.
I'm not sure, bro. Her ex never said
nothing to me. I would have [ __ ] her up
in front of her ex.
I would have smashed her face in in
front of her ex.
[ __ ] Izzy. USA is he? Yeah,
she had the right ones, but she's a [ __ ] in it.
I am fat.
Oh, I'm eating these nuggets.
That USA is a [ __ ] though.
She's a [ __ ] bro. She ain't about that.
She tried to take my kindness for weakness.
The pop my friend
because I'm not a skin virgin like virgin boy.
in a bed [ __ ] with absolutely no money
and no bed in it.
Can't believe he copied my holiday.
Germany can't believe that he actually
copied my holiday. He copied my [ __ ] [ __ ] copycat. Copycat.
He went to Amsterdam because I went to Amsterdam. [ __ ] copycat.
You reply to it. No, he didn't reply.
He's a copycat. Little copycat.
copying people's holidays, mate.
We need to get that USA, bro. We need to
get that USA.
We need to get that USA, bro.
Oh, mate. We need to get USA, bro.
Yeah, he went on the Euro Star as well.
I also went on the Euro Star.
He went on the Euro Star, bro. He I also
have been on the US Star. He's a little
copycat. Ah, you little copycat.
Then I'm going to I'm going to I'm just
going to I'm just going to strangle him.
You little copycat.
Now it's time to watch the Sidemen Sunday. One second.
Oh, there we go.
Oh, lovely. I'm back home now. Lovely.
Yeah, I know. That's what I'm saying,
mate. He He little copycat, is he? He's
a little copycat.
He's a little He's copying the crowd. He
wants to fit in, don't he? He wants to fit in.
Bless him then if he wants to fit in.
Oh, bless to fit in with the crowd.
You little copycat.
I got 10 numbers, Buzz. I got 10 numbers, bro.
I had an I had an escort who tried to
who tried to um [ __ ]
who tried to rip me off, bro. I had an
escort that tried to rip me off. So I
gave her £100 and
I was I get to finish in your mouth,
right? She's like, "Yeah." So she sucked
my balls, sucked her tits, sucking my
dick. Then she was like, "Oh yeah, you
can't finish in my mouth." I was like,
"What do you mean?"
She weren't having it at all at all,
bro. The guy come. I was like, "You
[ __ ] mad. I want at least half my
money back." Cuz she was already sucking
my dick in that. They Oh, no. You got to
go. You got to go. And at this point, I
was like, "I'm not going to sit here and
argue and try and force my money way
back." I was like, "Bro, if you don't
give the half the money back, I'm going
to do your [ __ ] windows in, bro." And
there was like kebab shops near the
place. The security guy that was running
the brothel, I was like, "Bro, I'm going
to do the windows in." And the guy,
there was people upstairs
that lived above. I was like, "Bro, you
know the windows are going to go in, in
it, so there's like no point you trying
to like sleep cuz, bro, you're going to
get woke up. The windows are going in."
And then the guy come out saying, "Oh
yeah, we'll give you half your money
back." I was like, "Okay, fair. Fair
enough." Bro, the windows were going to
go in, bro. I was going to smash the
whole I was going to smash the windows
in, bro. But I was asking a couple of people
like if they had a hammer.
Yeah, I finished. But I didn't finish in
their mouth. So
yeah, man. This country just gets worse
and worse. But I mean, at least we got
10 numbers in it. So probably won't go
anywhere cuz I mean, it's good old England.
It is what it it is what it is.
I'm steaming, bro. Really steaming. Really [ __ ]
It's not even a joke.
But at least I got I can't believe I got
10 numbers. I must have been on it, bro.
It's a little copycat.
Oh, you copycat. You're no copycat. Are you copycat? Little copycat.
Yeah, I broke the record. 10 numbers. I
don't think I've ever got 10 numbers
before, bro. one area. Nah, never bro.
Oh, you don't copycat. You don't
Ah, you don't copycat. You don't
Oh, why is Jane subscribing to me? [ __ ]
off, Jane. You [ __ ]
That USA is a continent it.
So if I went the first time I was
supposed to go Steven would you do realize
one of us would not be here now
laugh all you want but we all know it's
not funny is it? Yeah.
We all know that none of it's funny,
mate. Cuz it wouldn't have been funny,
bro, would it? So, you're laughing now,
but it ain't funny, is it?
We're doing a £120 football bet tomorrow, matey.
Oh, yes, sir. We are.
Are you some cheesy pickup lines today,
boss? Cuz I'm a crazy cat.
Steaming. Steaming. Steaming. Oh, [ __ ]
Bro, it's not funny. One of us could
have been dead.
Us could have actually been dead, bro.
And you're sat there laughing, man.
Where's my little ear pod gone?
Nah, it wouldn't have been funny, bro.
One of us would have been dead, mate.
One of us would have been dead. Oh,
you're doing a treble, are you?
Oh, Virgin Boys on a video. Virgin Boys
on a video. Virgin boy.
No money in it. No, mate. You copied me.
You copied me, mate. No, you you copied
my holiday. Just like you're going to be
going [ __ ] Thailand next, you little copycat. No, mate.
Oh, of course he was, mate. Of course he
was. A a singer you liked was playing in
the Netherlands, wasn't he, mate?
Yeah, of course he was.
Of course he was, mate. Yeah. No, mate.
No, mate. Right. Listen, listen, listen.
I'm going to reply back to this cup. I'm
going I'll be back tomorrow. I'll be
back tomorrow. When I wake up, I I'll go
live tomorrow. Yeah. I'm done now. I'll
be back tomorrow, bro. Yeah.