Franklin, stay outside,
get back in the car. You been really annoyed lately. Oh,
sorry, man. It was It was a late one last night.
Oh [ __ ] man.
Wait for fig tell them all about it. You know
what's the date?
Monday, isn't it? Oh, [ __ ]
No trying to get a [ __ ] Chinese then.
It's not even [ __ ] open.
Oh, [ __ ] me.
Oh man, [ __ ]
I feel [ __ ] man.
Got some vouchers. McDonald's.
Obviously, we could probably anywhere to
be honest with you because we're not
skin like the virgin virgin in the bed.
No money, no bed in it. But, you know, I
don't know that is still quite nice,
especially if you got you know, a couple
of vouchers, you know, lovely vouches, you know. Yeah, man.
No, I I don't care about it enough to
hate. I Bro, what happened the other
day? I I expected it. You know, get 10
numbers, one reply. That's just England.
That's just westernized women for you.
What's there to hate? It's the same old
[ __ ] You expect it. It's the same old
boring [ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] bro. So, you know,
I don't give a [ __ ] bro, about it.
Are you still singing over women? Are
you still defending women?
You still defending them.
I already know what I need to do, bro. So
that's that's the end of it.
It would never change you. It would
never ever change you. So, I'll be out Saturday
cuz I didn't get this haircut for no [ __ ] reason.
I was going to do a video about um the
expense of dating as well. Um in this
country, it's not just about the time
and the effort that goes in, it's
actually about the money. You know them
uh you know that Friday, Saturday,
Sunday in the mall drinking. I spent about £400.
It's disgusting is it really mate? It's
disgusting how like you do you know the
way I see this [ __ ] is that like bro you
know with four or 500 you can go on
holiday you know that
that's the thing you can actually go on
holiday not obviously Thailand or
America or [ __ ] Australia but I mean
you can go on a holiday. So, I mean, the
fact that you can leave your country
with the exact same amount of money as
you would spend over a weekend, I think
that's [ __ ] up, bro.
You know, I think like, yeah, the um the
crisis is definitely real. The living
crisis, that is insane. It's like 200
pound. Yeah, you'd think, okay, yeah,
200 pound whatever, you know, maybe even
250, but £400 really, bro.
Like it's [ __ ] madness. It is
just to get rejected by women. It's
[ __ ] up, isn't it? Yeah. Expensive, eh?
Can't even justify like the prices and stuff.
That's mad, isn't it, bro?
That's probably why the skint virgin
ever done it cuz it was too expensive.
That's why he was just happy to say his
skin little shitty little virgin gay bedset
to be honest with you.
Fair [ __ ] play. I couldn't do it for
three years, mate.
I couldn't [ __ ] do it for three
[ __ ] can't do it for three weeks,
mate. Hello, three years.
So, credit where credit is due to the virgin.
I must say, bro, I must [ __ ] say. So,
I give credit when credit's due.
That's [ __ ] bro.
It's like every time you go out, when
you eventually go out, you're spending like4500 pound.
That is insane, bro.
No, no, no, no. This person.
Oh, yo, Joe, guess what? I got a story
to tell you.
Never guess what I done
just about to go to New York for
Christmas. You'll never be able to do
that. I mean, I I could go if I wanted to.
Um, I mean,
that's a fake Joe, I reckon.
Let me see if that's the real Joe
there right now if I wanted to. What are
you talking about? It's got to be a fake Joe.
One second, brother. Let me investigate.
What the [ __ ] bro?
Yeah, definitely a fake one.
Doesn't let me look.
Yeah, that's definitely fake. J
think it's got to be.
do it because Joe uh Joe's not a hater
like that. Um I can go to New York
anytime I want. Um I can afford to
go whenever I want to. And I have had
more women than you would ever have. So
get your facts right. I knew that wasn't
the real Joe. Our Joe is not a hater
like that. He's he's a good [ __ ] you
know. Ask Greavesy. I've had a
girlfriend and I can go America whenever
I want to. I've already been and I could
go again if I wanted to. So, I mean
that's [ __ ] that.
So, yeah. Self- projecting.
Going to New York for Christmas. You
really think that's a lot of money?
What? You a couple of thousand pounds
that you're probably paying off for?
Yeah. Okay. Go self-reflect on another channel.
Always self-reflecting with these
skinned people. Why do they get live,
man? You know, I host live streams for
[ __ ] normal chats, you know?
Not [ __ ] self-reflecting bastards.
You know what I mean? [ __ ] hell, bro. Selfrelectors
to the max. It's [ __ ] They ruined the
[ __ ] They ruined the um They ruined a life.
Yeah, bro. No one's ever had a
girlfriend. Just like no one's ever had
money yet. They've shown you thousands.
Just like no one's ever had a woman,
they've shown you so many women. Yeah.
They don't have none of the things that
they've already shown you. People that
actually don't have it yourselves. Which
is why you come on YouTube self
projecting every day cuz you ain't got
no [ __ ] life. I actually have a story
to tell. That's why I'm actually live. But yeah, I'm saying [Music]
there sad people in it. Sad self projectors.
ain't got no [ __ ] life.
But yeah, that is the big thing now
obviously is obviously the expense of
obviously going out. It's like it
doesn't it's just not worth it, bro.
So saying that it was probably about 400
close to 500. [ __ ] hell, man.
You couldn't do that just on benefits.
You could do that just on benefits. No
way. You couldn't do that just on benefits.
[ __ ] no, bro. That's madness. Cuz say
you get paid a payment of like 600 600
700. You go out over a weekend and then it's gone. So no,
that's [ __ ] that is crazy, bro.
But yeah, the point is you can go on
holiday with that money that you spend
over the weekend.
Doesn't matter if it's France, doesn't
matter if it's Germany, doesn't it's the
fact that you can leave your country
with the exact same amount of money as
you would spend going out enjoying
yourself. That's the thing, you know,
that that's what really makes it [ __ ] up.
I don't know.
It is. That is [ __ ] up when you think
about it. That's all I was saying
yesterday to think. I can't believe
that, bro. Like, what happened like that? Which,
like I said, this is why Grezy I was
just saying this. Yeah. So, you know,
when I went out on Friday and went to
cinema on Saturday and had a ro on
Sunday, I spent about£500, bro. And what
I was basically saying is that it's kind
of crazy how you can leave your country
with the exact same amount of money. You
can go on holiday without money. Not
America, not Thailand, but you can still
go on holiday and go on an adventure
with that buddy
the same money you spend going out
drinking. Do you not think that's [ __ ] up?
Like you remember when people used to go
on caravan holidays, right?
and they used to take the kids to
caravan holidays and they stopped doing
that because obviously um the travel
agencies could compete with their prices
and then people just ended up going
abroad instead of going to the caravan.
So that's why most people go abroad
nowadays which make that is like meh you
know but the whole like you could
actually leave your country yeah with
you know less money than it would be
going on a night you know having a
couple of days for a week on a weekend
that does that not seem mad to you bro
that is insane bro to
Don't know about you guys.
Someone made a fake um JF account.
Yeah. But I mean that's also part of the
problem with the dating as well is
obviously the expense.
And that goes for anyone, anyone that
works, anyone on benefits, cuz I mean
most people can't afford to go out
drinking. So, which is why
they don't do it in London. I mean, you
know, in London especially like when
it's like [ __ ] £8 a pint greasy, you know. So, yeah.
Bless you though, Grezy. You downloaded
the app yet?
Downloaded any of the apps yet? Bless you.
Bless you then, Grezy. A bless you. If
you're looking for Mrs. Right. No.
Well, bless you then if you're doing the future. Oh,
well bless you.
Bless you then if you want to find someone. Oh, bless.
Oh, bless you. Then you're going to have
the same problems as
as I have.
To be fair, London's probably the worst
place for it to be honest. There all
just stuck up people here. Stuck up NPCs.
You know what I'm saying? like
playing a bit of Franklin. Franklin,
I think you'd be funny in a pub. Me,
Grezy. You going out for a good
oldfashioned piss up.
What do you think, Grezy? A good
Good oldfashioned piss up.
A good oldfashioned piss up movie. You
never know, you might like it. Oh [ __ ]
Hey, I'm just lying in bed chilling
having a cup of tea in my Spider-Man blood.
Oh [ __ ] man. Oh, I had some roast lamb
um at 5 in the morning, Grezy. It was
still very tasty.
Lovely leg of lamb. Yeah.
I still feel [ __ ] hung over, mate.
Still feel [ __ ] hung over.
I wonder who that self-reflector was.
That fake Joe accountant.
Never had a girlfriend. Self projecting.
I swear most of you self projectors are
just old people who have no life and
their lives have been ruined. So they
come on here every day because you got
to understand Greasy. You know when I'm
on here sometimes I come on here at the
end of the day. I don't even watch
anything. These people on here from the
time they wake up to the time they go to bed.
I don't know how they stay awake that long.
Ah, bro. These people truly have got no
life on here, man. Telling you. truly
have got no life
from the time they wake up to the time
they go to bed.
That's mad if you think about it. They
really have got no life.
Same atmosphere on here is it gives
the same atmosphere. Franklin,
what are you doing with your little hands?
What should I eat today? H
I don't even know, you know.
No, no, no, no, no.
I could do that. I could do 40 nuggets.
I could do it easy.
Do you want me to do a little video in
McDonald's and do it for you? Greezy,
I could do that quite easy. I think 60
would be hard though.
60 would be I don't think I could do 60.
I thought I could do 40, but I don't
think I could do 60, bro.
Oh, bless Grey then if he wants a woman.
bless you then, Grey. She want a woman. A [ __ ]
Yeah. 60. I don't think I could do 60 to be fair.
Although I I kind of fancy some grilled
chicken today. Greavesy. Some Pere.
Oh, Franklin's gone flying.
Franklin went flying. Greasy. [Music]
Do you know what? Maybe I was going to
say I could get a t-bone, but I don't
think the butchers are open on Mondays.
No, Sundays and I don't live anywhere
near there anymore, but still. No,
I don't think they are.
Get a job. What do we mean? Get a job.
What do you mean get a job? You know,
you know he's not currently working. You
know, no, don't care, man. Get a job.
Get a [ __ ] job, mate. Get a [ __ ]
job. Don't care, mate. Get a [ __ ]
Are you proud of me, Greasy, for working
in the past?
The skint virgin in the gay beds could
never work. You ain't got it in him,
mate. You ain't got a day's work in him.
That's why he's always skint.
You know, I'm just a windup, Grezy. You know me.
I got a secret to tell you, Grezy.
Yeah, I got a secret to tell you.
I got a little secret
now. Wait until uh Joe comes. Ah.
Oh, can't believe that lamb was [ __ ] 36 pounder.
36 [ __ ] pound for a bit of lamb.
That is a madness, bro.
Do a 100 nuggets, Grezy. If you do If
you do a 100 nuggets, I'll give you £1,000.
Okay with you, boss.
Yeah, you do 100, I'll give you £1,000.
That sounds like a good deal, doesn't it?
Deal is a deal, mate. Yeah, you do 100
and I'll give you um a,000 quid
and 50 notes.
do it. I will I'll send you the money. One second. Right.
Look, I had a great conver. We met for
drinks on a Tuesday. I met USA on a
Tuesday to be fair. And I felt we
clicked. No kiss. But I texted her the
next morning saying had a lovely time
asked if she wanted to do dinner on
Saturday. Wednesday and Thursday came
assume she wasn't interested. On Friday
I went out with someone else. give me.
Yeah, I'll give you £1,000. It's not a
problem, is it? I agree. Despite Fer,
I don't win on a second.
One second. Let me Oh, you dirty bastard, man.
[ __ ] I hate that on Reddit. It's
annoying as [ __ ] Virgin boy.
Oh, I hate this [ __ ] verification
[ __ ] now on these sites, bro. That's
I know. It's bad, bro. It's bad. Well, I
just I just have lots of memories in the
good old wank bank.
I was I woke up today thinking about the
[ __ ] that I got in the alleyway. Yeah.
One second. was
right. Let me message this person.
Yeah, I've got enough in the wank bank, mate.
Do you understand what I mean, bro?
I would have just met the tenants um on
Saturday and went KFC. But the thing is,
Greasy, I've had my hair done and it
still looks good. So, I'm going to have
to give it a little whirl. on um
Saturday I might go to waxies greasy.
You know waxies, don't you
You know axis, don't you Greavves?
Thank you, Graves.
I think Joe's got um a bit of a gambling
problem to be honest.
Yeah, Joe's got a bit of a gambling problem. Definitely, mate. Virgin All
Max is just like a brewery basically.
Greasy. It's basically um
just a just like a pub. Just like an Irish pub.
It's where I stood that [ __ ] up.
Oh man, I'm tired, bro.
I think I went to bed at about 7 in the morning. Grezy,
I've been eating McDonald's since I was
a child. Greasy. I remember my mom used
to take me when I was a little kid to McDonald's.
What's mad at? Oh, I went to bed at 7. Yeah.
Well, I had a little win on roulette. I won £500.
So, I was kind of excited for that, you
know, winning £500.
Wasn't even going to gamble to be fair. But
just thought, [ __ ] it, it
drive 100 pound. So, quite exciting, man.
I think God's trying to tell me
something again. Grezy,
do you know what? I actually am starting
to believe in God, bro. I swear to God,
I'm actually starting to believe in God.
Cuz I mean, like these things, I feel
like everything happens for a reason,
bro. And I feel like it's God saying
every time you gamble, bro, I actually
feel like Yeah. It's like God saying to
you, "Okay, we okay, you tried whatever.
We're going to give you some money, but
now you need to go."
It honestly feels that way. It's like
God letting you win because like you
[ __ ] got 10 numbers and you spend like fucking£500.
So God wants to be kind to you. I
actually am starting to believe in God, you know,
because it used to happen all the time
as well with the gambling. So, I think
I'm starting to think there's something, bro.
Maybe if it's not God, it's something else because,
you know, I only put 100 pound in. So,
just hit a few 8 11s.
Then, you're not you're not going to
believe this, right? I had 50p left and
I put it on the number two and it come
in £18, but then I lost it. But, you
know, cuz I had 50p left in the balance.
So, I mean, I feel like God's really
trying to tell me something here, mate.
I think I think it is true, is it? What
do you think?
So, yeah, got that money coming in,
which is good.
It's [ __ ] up, though. It is.
It's crazy when you look at how [ __ ]
up it is and how expensive it is just
going out. You got the money to go out.
It's not about that. It's
But I don't really want to go out
Saturday, but I'm going to because I
have my haircut. So, I mean, what else
am I going to do? The haircut expenses
out the way. We're not going to use an
escort. We don't really have anything to
lose by by going out. Whereas when you
don't have your haircut, it's like
having to go barbers and wait around and
sit on the chair. Who can be [ __ ] You
know, really, who can be [ __ ] But
because I've got nothing better to do
anyways on Saturday.
What are you going to do? Stay in with a
lovely fresh haircut? Can't be doing
that crazy, can you?
Might as well head to the brewery.
Don't know why I call it that a brewery.
We have some lovely Guinnesses.
But no, the expense of it is like
it is insane.
It is insane. It is. It's bad. It's really bad.
Really bad, bro.
This guy says he gets casual sex. I'd
love to know how people
how people even get laid.
Is London just like the worst place or something? Antman
said, "You've been doing the same [ __ ]
for years, expecting a different result."
He said, "You know, it's not going to change."
It is like a cycle except that we're not
going to do our balls in. We're not
going to do We're not going to go back
to G. Trust me, that was a one-off. That
was the first time in a month. Trust me,
no one's going to do their balls in
cuz if I lose big amounts of money, it's
going to be very hard for me to get that
money back. I'm not stupid. Trust me,
I'm not stupid. Yeah, I know what I'm doing. So,
I'm not stupid, mate.
I don't know why I done it yesterday, to
be fair. I was just lying in bed.
I'm going to do a nice football bet
though on Saturday. A nice10 football
bet. I'm going to do a banging one, bro.
And then go for some drinks and
see what the score is.
The [ __ ] What else are you there?
You're only going to spend about 70 80
pound. So why not?
You would, didn't it, Grezy? Yeah, why not?
I spent a lot of money on his hair. I
spent a lot of money on my [ __ ] skin.
See, it'll be nice if I can get one of
these people to come and meet me. I've
got the money. I had the money anyways,
but I've got even more money now. So,
you know, going on a date, easy. We can
go on a £300,400 date. It's not a problem.
Not that date would cost that much, but
you know what I'm saying. We could do it.
But yeah, I just put £100 in, man. 500.
I was just hitting 811.
[ __ ] It was sick, bro. I thought the
streak was going to continue. Nah.
It's all right though. I was happy with
what I won to be honest.
So, I can go anywhere I wanted. As soon
as that money comes in, my other money
comes in. I can go anywhere I want really.
I don't know, bro. I don't know.
I don't know what to do, bro. It's such
a It's It's just I was thinking about
this last night. This is probably why I
was awake for so long. It's like, what
do you actually do? Like, is it is it
You know what I'm saying?
It's What do you do?
You don't try.
You don't meet anyone. You try. you
still don't meet anyone, you end up
depressed. So, it's like what the [ __ ]
does someone actually do
in this situation,
mine more than anyone because I've tried
more than everyone in the world. So,
it's like you go out and lose more hope
or it's [ __ ] That's the thing. It is
It is [ __ ] up.
I might do a video about this and the
expense of things as well cuz you are
actually in a dilemma.
That's the thing. That's the definition
of a dilemma, you know,
and I had [ __ ] with that escort as well.
So maybe God, oh, we'll just give you
some money for your efforts and trying. But
how many times is this going to happen
until you get the point? Until you get
the hint. How many times is God going to
do this until you get the hint? What?
another million times.
It is It's a hard one. It is a hard one
cuz even if you try, you
you still don't get anywhere and you
just lose even more hope. So,
it is a bad situation to be in. It is
the only thing I could think of is if
you found a really good escort.
That's the only way out of this or
finding someone, but you're not going to
find someone. So, it's like there's no
way out of this situation. You know what I mean?
I don't [ __ ] know, bro. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know what someone
would do. I don't Who knows?
Well, that Malaysian one replied. So,
we'll see if she meets,
but it's just not
I'm happy with that 500 win, bro.
Could do with that money. You know what
I'm saying? So, yeah.
I [ __ ] went on the site. Yeah, it was
another site and it weren't coming up. I
was like, I hope I been scammed there
cuz I could do with that, buddy. Like my
short is dipping into other people's
short. You know what I'm saying? So,
hope I been scammed here, mate,
cuz I need that [ __ ] money. So, yeah.
But I still would have went out this
week regardless whether I won or not cuz
obviously I'm not wasting the haircut. So,
I'm just going to have to do one massive
send on Saturday, bro. Like, I'm going
to have to send it.
Then I'm going to go out on my birthday
with my sister cuz we been planning to
go out for ages. We still haven't gone out. So,
then I feel like Yeah, that's that's got
to be it then, bro. It's got to be it.
There has to be it there, man.
Doesn't matter if you're in profit or
you want your money back or I think
we're in profit. So, I mean, even if you
want your money back from how much you
spent, you spent you, you know, you you
you lost nothing by going out. So, that
way you can kind of justify it.
I don't know.
I don't know what you can do, bro. It's
It is a madness. No,
I need this money though, bro. Need this £500. So,
so I can do what I used to be able to do,
carry on and lose it and then be okay with it.
Cuz I don't save any money and I don't
carry any money over.
Having 6700 in my account is not is not
good enough because by the time I go
out, it's it's over.
That's the end.
And these are by some new Ammani jeans.
I looked them up. They're like 190,
which I'm sure I didn't pay 190 for
mine. They were 110. I'd never pay 190
whether I had the money or I didn't have
the money. That's [ __ ] ridiculous.
I'd pay like 120 or 130 even. May. Yeah, maybe,
but not 190. That's [ __ ] ridiculous, man.
They are good jeans and stuff and I
wouldn't want to wear cheap jeans but I
don't not 190.
That is [ __ ] ridiculous because you
wash jeans sometimes to tighten them up.
Nah, you can't justify 190, bro. 130 you
can. 120 110 120 130.
See the difference with the Stone Island
jumpers is you don't wash them.
Do you understand? You don't wash them. So
they stay, you just get them dry clean
so they stay,
you know, jeans, they're more like you
wash them, they fade. So that's the
that's the difference. Sir,
[ __ ] hell. It's so old, isn't it?
Would you pay 190 for jeansy? Nah,
not 190, mate. 110, 120, 130. Like I said,
but not 190. That's [ __ ] ridiculous,
bro. And I have the money. I can pay if
I wanted to. I'd still pay 300. Well,
no, I wouldn't pay 300 for a jumper cuz
I've already got the jumpers.
Cuz when you wash, you have to wash
jeans now and then, even if you wanted
to get them dry clean to tighten them up.
And mine were 110. I'm there. They
weren't 190 when I bought mine. So, I
just stick to the same brand of jeans.
Greasy. I've always had the Marley jeans
cuz they're um you know the fit. You
know the fit. You know your size. So, I
just stick to the same. And I like the
thing at the back. The Ammani badge at
the back. So, it'll always be Ammani
jeans or none basically.
Ami jeans or no jeans. Simple.
I'll never wear any other jeans. I know
my size so in them.
I don't know what to wear on Saturday.
My little hoodie and my coat or my
little Stone Island jumpers. Greasy. Not sure.
Stone islands are really fresh.
Let's try and get 20 numbers on
Saturday. Yeah, Grezy. Try and get 20 numbers.
No, I don't think we'll get 20.
I don't We We'll probably get five to be
honest, which is still good.
Yeah, it is cold to be honest. This is
window isn't it now? So
yeah, [ __ ] it.
You see what I mean about the haircut
though, isn't it? If I, like I said, if
I didn't have my haircut, I would have
just went to meet the tenants and go
KFC. But no, I've got one loss sending
me before my birthday, I think.
you have nothing to lose.
Whereas like say you had money, right,
and you never had your haircut. Oh, we
got to pay for the haircut. Oh, you got
to sit on the chair. Oh, we got to wait
around. Oh, I can't be [ __ ] bothered.
You know what I'm saying? Where even and
and I got travel as well, so
I don't have no excuse not to go out
on Saturday. No excuse.
See, I tell you when I generally I'm
going to go out. [ __ ] Yeah, man.
What would you do if you was me? You can
see the kind of dilemma I'm in.
Cuz it's like if you don't try,
you're going to try eventually. when you
try, you lose even more hope and you
waste a [ __ ] ton of money
that could be used for other things. So,
this is the problem that we have, you know.
This is the problem.
It's It is [ __ ] up, bro. It is [ __ ] up.
Why is it so hard to date in this
country? For [ __ ] sake.
What? A natural dog or
a [ __ ] ugly woman? Yeah,
I want to get my own dog to be fair.
I don't know.
Yeah, but even they're not interested.
And you're not going to be you're not
going to be happy with that.
I might do a video um
titled Peter Belly's Dilemma.
Good title, is it?
Yeah, you could give up. Yeah,
but you see what I mean? Like I can't
justify spending the money anymore. You
do? You know what I mean, right?
Because this is a proper proper dilemma, bro.
But there really is no way out.
Unless you actually meet someone. That's the thing.
And it's expensive as well. It's
expensive. It's tiring, you know. But
people on Reddit make it seem like it's so easy.
So, yeah, I've got no excuse not to go
out on Saturday, basically.
But we already know what it's going to be.
But, might as well go out and drink anyways.
and other things have happened as well.
I can make money if I want, but it's just like
if you don't learn now, when are you
going to learn sort of thing, you know?
I don't know, man. I don't know.
I just I don't know, man.
I might I might uh wave my white flag,
wave my white flag.
Lovely little 500 pound coming in some
Peter Belly's account.
It's nice, isn't it?
That's all right, bro. That
What would you do if you put £100 in and
you got it to five over 500? Would you
keep going or would you keep playing? I
was like, "No, [ __ ] that, mate."
No, I just take a five in it. [ __ ] that.
No, [ __ ] that. Cuz that's how you get
into cycles. You see, that's how you get
into cycles. Cuz if you lose that, then
you'll be pissed off and then you end up
chasing. It's just not worth it. Just
take the profit and just run.
And if you want to go back to it in a
couple of months, just go back to it in
a couple of months or whenever.
You know, [ __ ] that, bro.
Nah, actually I got to five something,
but I just played it down to five, bro.
Oh, something good. Cuz you never know
when this streak's going to continue, eh?
It's not worth it, bro. It's not worth it.
Virgin boy skint in the bed suit with
absolutely no bed, no money in it.
What would you do without me? Grezy.
So yeah, Peter Belly will be on the hunt
for Mrs. Wright on Saturday. [ __ ] sake.
Me and me and [ __ ] Izzy still talk.
She's a very nice woman, you know. [ __ ] Izzy,
she's nice, man.
She licked my [ __ ]
Can't believe she done that. Yeah,
I love Dobby. I was watching Dobby
before I fell asleep. Um, Grezy earlier.
>> Dobby the house elf.
>> Harry Potter.
Oh, he's so cute. I love Dobby.
You already got kicked down the stairs. Oh.
Um, why? Um, are can I can I answer that
or are you going to let me are you going
to let me answer it? I can answer it if
you want me to answer it. Now, when did
I ever say he didn't show money?
I never said that he didn't show money.
I just said £13,000
for 3 years savings is ridiculous.
Not living life for 3 years for the sake
of £13,000 is not worth it.
So, okay, he showed money that it took 3
years to save. And what? I've shown
money. I've shown better clothes. I've
shown a better life.
So what, bro? Like realistically, what?
13,000 back when I was living a life,
when I was going out, it wouldn't have
lasted 2 months,
maybe 3 months. No one said that the
Virgin didn't show money. I've also
shown money and I've shown designer
clothes, but you seem to forget
everything I've shown cuz it doesn't
suit you. But, you know,
so I mean, £13,000 is not even a
life-changing amount of money in the
slightest. So, I don't even know why you keep [ __ ]
bringing it up.
Do not understand. I've said this a
million times that you can't take money
to the grave with you, but you can take
life experiences to the grave with you.
So, why people is better? Listen, it's
like what Ronald Pump said why people
was jealous of me. You're better
looking. You've got more money and
you've got a better life than them.
Do you understand?
Yeah. A better life, better looking, and
more money. It's not one thing. Better
looks, better life. Do you know some Do
you know the most thing people envy is
people's life? That's what they do. No
one would be jealous of someone having
just money alone. You need a better life
and you need to be good-looking as well.
But yeah, what he basically said, better
looking, a better life. And yeah,
basically that's what it is. He has none
of them things. I'm a million times
better looking. I've lived more of a
life than him. You keep saying, okay,
okay, so one second, Grezy, listen to
this. What I respond back, doesn't he do
videos calling me a virgin?
I mean, doesn't he do videos calling me
a virgin? I don't see you backing me up. Um,
so I mean it took him two year it took
him 2 years after me show money to show
£13,000 cuz he lives in a bed suit with
no money in it,
right? But doesn't he call me a virgin
when I've literally proved I've had sex?
That doesn't make I mean I've literally
released a porno.
So, I mean, he's called me a virgin and
I've not seen you on his channel, even
though I'm not going anymore.
Saying that, backing me up. So, why are
you backing him up? I think I've got a
fair point there, don't I, Gibsy?
Um, I've already been in a relationship
and I've been with more women. We've
been over this a million times.
Um, we've been over this a million
times. I have been with more women than
he has. I have had sex more times than
he has. So, answer my question. I've
answered all of your questions. Now,
answer my question. You're on here saying that
um and I have been in a relationship and
I've been with more women, which how did
I get these women with my looks? USA is
[ __ ] all of these other women. All of
these other women I went on dates with.
I got that from my looks. Now, answer my
question. You're on here saying, "How
can he be in a bed sit with no money in
it?" Because he's showing money. Now he
has gone and called me a virgin. I have
not seen you backing me up on any of them videos.
So what's the score, bro?
£13,000 in 3 years is not a
life-changing amount of money to not
live a life for. If he had lived the
life, right, and he just won 13,000
[ __ ] pounds, then yeah, fair play.
But it's not a lot of money,
you know, in in in the long run.
It really really isn't. I don't know why
you're talking like it's it's a million
pounds. Like, it really isn't, man. And
yes, I understand people some people not
into designer clothes. They don't have
to be. But if you really had all of this
money, you wouldn't be sat in a bed seat
for 3 years not doing anything with your life.
It's simple. Like that's facts, you know?
So, and I've already been in a relationship,
shown my money, been in a relationship,
been with multiple women.
What? So, you're not going to answer my
question then? See, this is what I'm
saying, Grezy. Yeah. You know, when I
say that he's a virgin, he is a virgin.
I don't care if he's got a girlfriend or
not, he is a virgin. And then he tries
to call me a virgin, but I've proved
I've had sex. He has not pro Listen to
me, bro. Like I keep saying to you, as
immature as it sounds, I have proved I
have had sex. It's out there. He hasn't
proved he's had sex. So, which which one
is more believable? Someone that's
actually proved they've had sex or
someone that says, "Oh, well, I'm in a
relationship." someone that's proved
they've had sex.
As illusional as that sounds, I mean, it
is, isn't it? How can you argue with evidence, you know?
So, is this my guy jealous of me or
something? Because you seem to like
taking sides for some reason,
you know? I'm pretty sure he says that
I'm skin and I'm a virgin. Even though
I've shown more money, even though I've
had a better life, have a better life.
And I've also proved I've had sex, but I
don't see you. You you are my in my corner.
Whereas your that this is what I'm
saying. This is what makes me think it
is jealousy with you people. You know,
it's got to be jealousy, is it?
you like it's that's what I mean. This
is why I said it's no there's no point
getting into it with these people. You know,
who cares if he's in a relationship?
I've proved I've had [ __ ] sex.
Which one stands out more?
Okay. Well, I'm asking Okay. Well, then
answer me a question now. Okay, I'm
asking you a question, right? I'm asking
you a question. You've asked me how can
he be skinn in a bed suit with
absolutely no better than money in it
because he it's took him 3 years to save up £13,000.
That is skint in my book. So, I've
answered your question. Now, I've asked
you a question. When he calls me a
virgin, I don't see you defending me cuz
I proved I've had sex. I've actually
proved I've had sex. Not claiming that
I've been in a relationship. I've
actually proved I've had sex. So, I mean,
I don't know what what's your problem,
bro. No one's getting blocked. I'm
giving you the chance to answer. You're
not going to get blocked. I'm I'm You know,
you see how it looks. It looks weird,
doesn't it, mate? Come on. So,
and you're talking about you work for
your money, bro. I've worked I've worked
for my money as well. I've worked a job
you could never even do. Doesn't matter
what the what what it was paying.
I used to go out at 10:00 in the morning
and come back at [ __ ] 11:00 at night.
You would not be able to do that. Yeah.
So, I've worked. Just cuz I'm not
working now at the minute cuz I don't
have to. That's that's my choice. I've worked.
It doesn't matter whether it was minimum
wage, above minimum wage. I worked for
my money. It doesn't matter what it was.
So simple. Doesn't matter what the
amount of money was
because I've got a right to say things
about women. I've had bad experiences
with women. They're not kids. They're
they're not innocent. They know what they're doing.
What do I say that they're stuck up
[ __ ] and they lead people on purpose?
Well, they kind of do. I mean, you're
not going to exactly get locked up. But,
bro, you're talking about people working
for their money. I've worked for my
money. I've had about three different
jobs. Yes, I have.
You know what I'm saying?
Doesn't matter how much I was getting
[ __ ] paid. I still [ __ ] work for
the money I've received. So, you know
what I mean?
You wouldn't be able to that delivery
job that I was doing. No [ __ ] way.
I'd be very surprised.
Well, I have Well, I have had a problem with them.
I think they're [ __ ] I think
they're stuck up. I think they're nasty.
I do think they're all of these things.
They are all of them things. What's
wrong with saying what they are? They're
not babies. They're not children. They
know what they're doing.
I mean, I've proved it by messages what
they do. Lead people on, take the piss
on purpose. They are like that. What
What am I supposed to lie to you?
Because you don't want to hear it.
Do you want me to lie to you because you
don't want to hear it?
They literally are stuck up entitled
[ __ ] They are. They literally are. So yeah.
I stood up. She was being a [ __ ]
Trying to be passive aggressive.
So, she's a [ __ ]
Well, I'm definitely not the problem.
Um, that's why that's what my
approaching videos show. Definitely
definitely not the problem. And I'm not
going to get into this. I mean, I've
I've put my approaching videos out there
because of this reason to not have this
conversation. I mean, there's videos of
me approaching completely normal and
them acting stuck up. So, I mean, that
says everything you need to know. Um,
no, it's definitely definitely them
that's the problem.
Their unrealistic um expectations.
Nah, it's definitely definitely not. And
I love the maybe part because yeah, it
is maybe, but you're wrong because it's
them. The problem is literally them. And
I've been with women and the problem is
literally I must be the only one that's not delusional.
I must literally be the only one that's
not lying. I feel like I am. Bro,
what what what's the problem? Me going
out speaking to them pretending and then
pretending that they got a boyfriend cuz
they're not interested or them giving me
their number and them leading me on. I
mean, I could show you messages again if
you want, but no matter what you're
shown, you're always going to deny it.
I know. I That's why I'm leaving. That's
why I'm leaving. That's why I'm going to
Asia. I know. That's why I'm going to
So I don't have to deal with these stuck
up [ __ ] ever again. That's why I'm
That's why I'm leaving. That's why I'm
doing something about it, you know.
But no, they are definitely definitely
definitely the problem. Especially in
London. 100%. They're stuck up as [ __ ]
Like even on even on Friday when I went
out approaching like they're so up their
own asses. It's unbelievable. No, they
are definitely definitely the problem.
Especially in London. Especially in
London. I mean, they lead people on on purpose.
I mean, there's evidence there. I mean,
I've got text messages. They literally
will lead people on on purpose.
They play games.
That's all they do. So, no, it
definitely definitely is them that is
the problem. 1 million%.
Of course, it's them, bro. What the [ __ ]
And they lead people on as well. That's another thing.
They lead people on on purpose. They
[ __ ] well do.
It's definitely them that's the problem. They're [ __ ]
Skin mon. I like that one, bro. That's good, man.
They haven't come across my channel.
Skin m. Yeah.
Well, I've got a bed and I don't live in a bedsit.
Um, I've had more women than you have, virgin boy. So
shown more money than you have had a
better life than you've had. But yeah,
no, it's definitely definitely
definitely women. I mean, my approach to
show that it's the women, Grezy, but
what with these people? Yeah, it's like
certain people on Reddit,
they dismiss your struggles.
Like you show them like screenshots and
stuff. Um, it shows they dismiss your struggles.
That's what they do. They dismiss your struggles.
Like, you know, 10 numbers are not a
reply. That's very, very normal. I've
had three numbers before and they've all replied.
It's it's literally them. They're stuck
up. I mean, and one did actually reply
actually. So, I mean, the problem is
literally them. But it doesn't matter
anyways. It's pointless conversation
because whatever you're shown, you're
going to dismiss anyways. So I think
like in this case it's just best to
agree to disagree cuz no matter what you
ever get shown, you're just going to
dismiss it anyways.
So what's I don't see the whole point in
this. Doesn't matter who's right or
who's wrong. Any kind of wrong that I
show them doing, you're just going to
dismiss it anyways. If I'm half if even
if I'm half right, Grezy, and I'm half
wrong. to say you're wrong 50% of the
time and then you're right 50% of the
time, they will dismiss everything that
they do. So, it's just a pointless
conversation. It's waste of our energy
really. But the work thing is really
cheeky to be honest with you.
I mean, I I understand what you're
saying and you're entitled to your
opinion, but I have put approaches out
there where I have tried to speak to
people normally and I have tried to get
to know people and when I've tried to
escalate it, they pretend they've got a
boyfriend. So, I mean, that in in some
of them videos would show that it is
them that is the problem. But even
though you get shown a video, you still
dismiss it. So,
I don't understand, bro.
I'm skinn. You don't know how much money
I have and I'm the best looking on here.
But I mean, there's no denying that. But
even though they get shown this, they
will still deny it. And you're saying
I'm ugly when I'm the best looking on
here. And you're saying I'm skint projecting.
What you people mean is you are the skin
ones. That's why you spend all of your
life on YouTube all day every day from
the time you wake up to the time you go
to bed, [ __ ] You wake up and
the first thing you do when you wake up
is you come on YouTube
all day every day from the time you wake
up to the time that you go to bed. We
don't care about what any of you
self-reflectors have to say.
We do not care about you self-p
projectors. The only reason you like you
call people skin and all of these things
is because it's yourselves that you are talking about.
You know, we call it the self um the
self-p projecting channel.
Look, you know, that's when Lord Jes
Asian women are a lot nicer. So, yeah.
[ __ ] yeah, bro. And another thing is
Greezy, right? Even let's just say for
example, right, that I went out on
Friday and none of them numbers replied
because I'm the problem, even though one
did reply. But the problem with it is is
that, bro, I've there's been times
before I've got three numbers and
they've all replied. Four numbers and
they've all replied. Sometimes I've got
10 and none of them's replied. It's all random,
you know. It's all random. You know,
sometimes you get two numbers and two
meet you. It's all random. But the thing
is, it's like we're not saying that
uh none of the time
um I'm wrong. This is this is this is
their misconception. I have shown where
there's been people that's actually
agreed to meet me, like actual evidence
where they've been in a wrong, whether
it's three of them or four of them, and
people still dismiss it and defend
women. That's why you you you're you're
literally banging your head against the
wall. Again, you're calling me disabled,
but bro, you are the ones that are in
your 30s, 40s, sat on YouTube every day self-p projecting.
Everything you say is about yourselves.
This is why no one cares about any of
you little self projectors. If anyone
wants to have a opinion, right? They can
come on here and have an opinion. But
all all of this whole your skin, you're
this. It's all about your own lives.
That's why it doesn't bother anyone. You
people talking about yourselves. You sit
on YouTube all day, every [ __ ] day
calling people what you are yourselves,
skin, disabled, everything that you are yourselves.
You know, you literally wake up every
day talking about yourselves. What life
is that? You know what I mean? Jesus Christ.
So, you're just a self-reflector so you
can [ __ ] off. So, yeah. Anyways,
so yeah, there's been actual like conversations.
I mean, agree with you. I would pull it
up there cuz whether you agree or you
disagree, it's whatever. But these
people just will just dismiss anything they're shown.
So, it's kind of like I'm wasting my own
time as well because anything that
they're shown, they're just going to
defend women because in their head,
women can't do anything wrong.
They can't do anything wrong in their
minds. Even if they're shown that that's
the whole point of the simp.
See, with babies, with children, you
know, when I used to go on this madness
and I used to say stuff about women and
kids, I take back the stuff I said about
kids, cuz kids are innocent, you know?
They're [ __ ] children. They are
innocent. Women are not innocent. So,
it's like it's that's it. Like, they're
suck up. They're [ __ ]
They leave people on on purpose. They
take the piss on purpose. They generally
do all of them things. I don't take back
any of the stuff I said. If I could if I
could erase right
the past and take back things I said
about them I wouldn't take the things I
said back I wouldn't the things about
kids and stuff I would you know
and you know the whole USA Izzy thing I
don't regret that I don't regret that
you know as as delusional as that sounds
bro I don't I feel like that [ __ ]
needed to meet me you know she needed to
meet her match to to get like a taste of
her own medicine. I don't I don't um I
don't regret that.
But yeah, with the kids sharing that I
would Yeah. But not the women stuff. No
way. No way. Because you need to think
of this now, Grezy, that this is still
going on. You know, how can you regret
it? It is still going on, bro. Do you understand?
But the whole like messaging the family
and stuff, no, I don't regret that. That
[ __ ] is lucky I didn't go the first
time I was supposed to go cuz she would
have been dead. It's not even a joke.
It's only for the fact that people was
begging me, "Oh, don't go. Don't go.
Don't go. Don't go." I was like, "No,
this little [ __ ] like it's bro. It could
have." And so, no, I don't take back any
of the things I've said.
you know, when I can finally prove
somebody that when I can actually meet
someone that's actually different, um,
you know, then maybe I would consider,
but I mean, I don't feel like that's
ever going to happen. So, I feel like
we're just going to settle down with a
[ __ ] Frenchy dog and move on with our
life. That's the way it's looking to be fair. So,
I mean, all you've said was mad things.
They've done actions, you know? They've
led you the [ __ ] on. They've said
they're going to meet you, and they
haven't. They've took the piss out of
you. So, what if you said a few bad
things in retaliation to their [ __ ] you know?
That's that's it. I don't take any of
the things I've said about women back. I
don't I generally don't.
And I know that you would have like if
you want to use things about taking
things back, I don't take any of it
back. I mean exactly what I say. Um
but children are innocent. So there's a
big difference. You know, women are not
innocent. So I understand why people
would be mad if you spoke about kids.
What the [ __ ] can a kid do to you? But women are
they are evil. They know what they're
doing, you know?
And no one has proved to be to be
different. Think about it, Gre Grey.
Listen, I went out on Saturday. Yeah,
sorry, Friday. And I spent I told you I
spent £400 or500. Do you think I spent
£4 or500 to say that I told you so? Do
you think I've got that kind of money to
be wasted anymore? You know, no. So,
I mean, it doesn't matter what anyone
says. It doesn't matter what I say. It
doesn't matter what you say. The point
is you've put yourself out there to to
get them to prove that one of them is
different and none of them can prove
that they are different.
Do you understand what I'm saying? What
are you going what are you doing wasting
money to say I told you so? We don't
have that kind of money to keep wasted.
You understand? So
you understand what I'm saying, don't
you? like what's your opinion on it? You
get what I mean, right?
But I don't take back the stuff um I've
said about women. No way. [ __ ] no, bro.
Absolutely [ __ ] no. Cuz
I just don't. I just don't, bro.
I feel like I'm right, bro. my family there.
So I feel like
it's pointless having any of these
debates, isn't it?
Cuz they're never going to stop defending them.
Yeah, like I Yeah, like bro, like seriously, bro,
that [ __ ] is very very very very lucky,
bro. Like, I I did not go that that dream, bro.
Like, you really don't understand. It
would have got bad. Like, look at the
other day with a [ __ ] whole escort
thing and that, bro. And you know,
they're not innocent. None of them were
innocent. They're they're [ __ ] And
even if they're and even if they're
innocent, they're stuck up. So even if
they're like, "Okay, let's just say that
they're not evil or whatever, they're
they're stuck up and they think they're
better than you." So it's like it's
either way, they're not good. They're
not good people at all. So, but people
still will sit there and and and defend them, bro.
Like I've spoke to, okay, listen, put it
like this, greasy, bro. I've spoke to
people normally like people haven't even
approached and you can sense the
entitlement in them.
You can sense the cuntiness in them like
when they're like texting back thinking
that they're better than you. So
the way these people defend women, I
think they've got to be virgins, bro.
You know, like it's like I I like even
people I've not approached you could
just they they just think that they're
better than you.
You know what I'm saying? Like it's like
they they generally do. even if you're
not hitting on them. So,
no woman in [ __ ] knows.
Don't know. Don't care, bro.
But no, children are not innocent,
but women are not innocent. I don't take
back any of the stuff that I said about
them. Never have, never will. Maybe when
I'm proven wrong one day. I mean, I'm
going to go out Saturday. Grievously.
So, let's see if I get proven wrong on Saturday. yeah.
I don't know, bro. I don't know.
I mean, he went because I went. We
already know that.
He's a skinned bastard.
Some guy just come in saying, "Well, how
can he be skin in a bed sit with no
money in it when he showed you money?"
And I said, "Well, how can I be a virgin
when I proved I had sex?" But none of
you people defend me.
So that doesn't make any sense
because you're saying that I'm a virgin
and I've actually proved I've had sex.
I put a porno out there. He's never
proved he's had sex. Girlfriend or no
girlfriend. So like I said, it's like
what the [ __ ] You don't go on his
channel saying, "Oh, well, he's kind of
proved he's had sex." Cuz I [ __ ] well
have. I've shoved my dick down a woman's
throat. I've been in [ __ ] women's
beds. I've had women admit they've had
sex with me and but yeah, I'm the
virgin. So is it like are you like
jealous or some [ __ ]
Like that's why I said like are you
jealous or something? Because it's like
why are you backing a non and it's like
oh right hold on so I've said mad things
about women but he's an actual nons. So what?
So, because I've stated facts about women,
that means you shouldn't defend me. But
it's okay for him to be a nons and you
defend him. Okay, then.
Not yet, bro.
What's your opinion on this women thing,
Shab? I don't I don't think I'm the problem.
Definitely definitely don't. All I do is
go out, try to meet new people, and
they're not interested. I don't know
what is the problem about me, bro. I go
out, I spark up conversations with
people. I try to get to know people.
They're not interested.
They give their number and I got 10
numbers and only one replied, but that
doesn't usually happen. Normally, half
the numbers reply, but it can happen.
You know, you can get 10 numbers and
none of them replied. One replied, but
it's all random. Like I said, it's all
You can't predict it, you know.
They just I don't I don't know, bro. Like,
what's your opinion on the women thing?
I got one reply. I got one reply
and I was confident as [ __ ] I know
exactly what I was saying as well. I got one reply.
But sometimes I've got eight no replies.
Sometimes I've had four, they've all
replied. Sometimes I've had three.
They've all replied. It just It's just all random.
Yeah. But they seem to still think
there's hope for me in this country.
Shabiba, it's a madness, isn't it, lads?
That's what I'm saying. It's all random.
You know, you can get three numbers
and all of them reply and two of them
meet you. You can get [ __ ] 100
numbers and none of them reply. It's all
random. That's what I'm saying.
But they seem to think, "Oh, yeah. Well,
because they didn't reply, you're the
problem." What What did I do that was the problem?
You know, I I looked my best. I done my
best. And I was confident. What What
could have I done? There's nothing more
I could have done, bro. Do you know how
much money I spent in them two? I spent £500.
Luckily, I won money on roulette
yesterday. But bro, I spent [ __ ] Yeah, like4500
in them three days
to say I to tell you that I told you so.
Make it make [ __ ] sense, bro. I'd
love to go on a [ __ ] date [ __ ]
next week. Especially now I've got this
money coming in, you know, another money
coming in. I don't go out to say I told you so.
Yeah, I know, bro. It's a madness, isn't it? But
bye-bye. Go back to LJ's. No J
supporters on my channel.
But yeah. Yeah, one did reply to be fair.
I don't know what the problem is though,
man. Be honest.
Yeah, I think most people would.
I think most people would to be fair.
But honestly, bro, if I if I when I go
out on Saturday, if I get three, four
numbers, two or three of them will
reply. I don't know why these ones
didn't reply, but
one of them replied obviously, but like
I don't know why, but it will go back to
normal next week. But yeah, it doesn't
matter. Like, it's either bro, even if they reply, right?
Even even if they reply, they're just
going to lead you on and play games.
So, reply or no reply, it's pretty much
the same at the end of the day.
It is It is disgusting, bro. Like, even
with that win, yeah, even though I won
500 pound and whatever, it's still like
I was basically saying to Thingy that
it's the problem with it is is that you
got 10 numbers, you know? It's not like
you got three numbers or you got,
you know, if you got three numbers, then
it would be okay. Yeah, you got three
numbers. Who cares? It's only three
people, right? or you didn't put effort
into your appearance, but you did both
of them. So, I mean, even winning the
money back and a bit more, it didn't really
peel the cut on a knee, to be honest.
That is It tells you everything you need
to know about this country.
It's bad, is it? But I'll be out
Saturday again cuz um like I said, I
have my head on. So,
but it is bad. It is. It is bad.
This is Peter Belly's dilemma.
This is the dilemma I'm in, bro.
It's bad. It is bad. It is bad.
It is disgusting.
I know, bro. To be fair. To be hon,
bro. You know what I'm saying? Like
um I'd rather like um like Sorry, I'
like I'd expect I was expecting one of
them to meet, but I did think maybe a
few of them would have replied. I was
expecting maybe three of them to reply
to be fair because obviously I expect
this [ __ ] now. Obviously, I've been
doing this for years
and it will never change, but you know,
it's like that's what it is.
It will never change. So,
it is [ __ ] up. Yeah.
Well, it is what it is. It's just
England, bro. It will never change. So,
it will never change.
So, now I'm in a dilemma now
cuz it's like you don't try and then you
want to try and meet someone and then
you you go to try and meet someone, you
waste a load of money, you get nowhere,
and then you lose even more hope.
So it's like it's like
it's like walking into um it's like
walking into like a jungle. Yeah. With
dangerous animals and every time you
walk in you get attacked.
That's how that's like the the the
that's the that's the way we that's an
example I could say. You know it's like
every time you walk into the jungle you
get your ass whooped
by these animals. You know,
but you need to go through the jungle to
try and meet someone. It's [ __ ] up,
bro. It is. It is. It's not normal, bro.
It's not normal.
But people still say that you're going
to meet someone.
There you go. They are stuck up. They
[ __ ] are, mate. They [ __ ] are. I
mean, I will literally
buy that guy a pint of Guinness because
they [ __ ] are stuck up, mate. They
are. They really, really are. They are
stuck up more than like any other place.
Like I approached this Australian woman.
She said she had a boyfriend. Yeah, they
are stuck up. But it's any country like Italy,
[ __ ] They're all stuck up. They're all [ __ ] Yeah.
Oh, I'm not alone, bro. They It's a
known fact they're stuck up.
Too many stuck up [ __ ] in this
country. There is. They are stuck up.
That's a fact, bro.
A lot of people have gone.
But I made some new friends. See, here's
the thing, Sab. I'm not the problem
because I always make new friends when I
go out. I've got loads of friends
and if he was a problem, you wouldn't
even have friends. I mean, I've got
I make new friends when I go out. You
know, I'm a likable person. But because
women are all the same, apparently I'm
the problem. Even though they can't tell
you what you're doing right, they can't
tell you what you're doing wrong. Trust
me, if you saw me on Friday approaching,
bro, I was a pro, man. So,
but they will always blame you.
They'll never blame the simps [ __ ]
the game up and giving them inflated
egos. Nah, they will never.
But what makes me laugh is that people
think there's still hope here. Shab,
that's what makes me laugh is that
people think there's still hope in this
country that, you know, you're going to
meet someone and stuff. It's crazy.
But I did get one reply.
I mean, I'm going to invite her out this
week. See what see what she's saying. But
it's not good, is it, Grezy?
It should have pissed me off more than
it did. I think it's because the fact
that I know I tried. So if I knew I
tried, I had no regrets. So, you know.
Yeah. I'm surprised I haven't either. Yeah, man.
We do think I was rude. You think I was wrong? Um,
messaging USA Izzy's dad. I don't think
I was wrong. I think I was right. Defo.
I think I was defo right on that one.
When am I going to get this money, bro?
What the [ __ ] sp?
Yeah, she deserved it.
No, she deserved it. She deserved
everything she got, bro.
You know, when I fell out with my mom,
you know, when I fell out with my mom
and this whole thing was going um on
around the Christmas time, but I I was
meeting my the Weather Spoons, you know,
when like the whole thing was going on
with the neighbors and stuff, and I
said, "I don't take back what I said."
And still now I don't take back. She's
lucky I didn't go there and kill her. Seriously,
like you got lucky that never happened. So yeah. Yeah, exactly.
And it's the way she went about it. like
she thinks she's better than me. Like,
who the [ __ ] do you think you are?
And this is coming from someone that's
like [ __ ] technically below average.
You know what I'm saying?
But I mean, that's it's just
examples I'm using, you know? I don't
regret that at all.
All they have to do, Grezy, see this
whole [ __ ] about people that owe people
[ __ ] is just a cover up.
to try and dismiss the shitty things
that they do.
Do you understand, Grievy?
Think about it, Grezy.
Do you not believe in this double
standard [ __ ] You say you don't eat a
woman out, you get called gay. A woman
doesn't want to suck dick. Oh, well,
maybe she just doesn't like sucking
dick. Oh, a woman don't owe you
anything. But a woman has never told a
man don't owe them anything.
So, do you understand, bro? It's all
double standards. That whole women don't
owe you anything is just a cover up.
It's just to try and dismiss the bad
things that they do.
Um, it's [ __ ] up, to be honest. Yeah.
I don't know what I'm going to eat today.
So, if you don't want to eat a woman
out, you get called gay. If a woman
doesn't want to suck your dick, that's completely fine.
Can someone explain that one to me then? Why?
Yeah, it's double standards, lad.
Cuz if a woman doesn't want to give a
[ __ ] right, she's not called a
lesbian. If you don't want to eat a woman out, then
you're gay. Simple.
But we never ever heard men don't owe
you anything. It's always women don't
owe you anything. Why is that? We never ever see.
What's a fair point, Grezy?
What? What I just said?
What? What is what I just said? What bit?
No, you definitely didn't.
What about what? What? What's a fair point,
Grezy? Is it what I said or
what what you referring to?
Well, yeah, I'm in a dilemma now.
You didn't really make a point.
There we go then. Exactly.
Yeah. And and you will never ever It
wouldn't it wouldn't have been your
point, Shia, because you didn't make a
point. You just said something. But
yeah, that's also another thing when you
when it where they try to cover up
women's shitty behavior by saying that
they don't owe you anything. It's always like
it's just like a cover up, bro. Like,
you know what I mean?
Cuz um Yeah.
Yeah, cuz it's found the pawn in London
to eat a woman out. And if you don't eat
a woman out, you get called you're gay.
Like, do you remember [ __ ] uh
Monty and [ __ ] Slegs used to say,
"Oh, you're gay. You're gay. You're gay. You're gay." Um,
and a few other people did as well.
But then, yeah, if a woman doesn't want
to eat uh give a man a [ __ ] that's
completely fine. No problem.
So, it is double standards. Yeah, definitely.
I just think he needs to get laid, me,
I just think he needs to get laid.
H I think he needs to lose his V card.
I'm so cheeky. I like
think he needs to needs to pop it. Pop that virginity, you know.
Reckoning Monty still watches.
I'm waiting for my £500 from the casino.
What a lovely sight. Oh.
Oh my god, my eyes, man. They're heavy.
Virgin boy skin in a bed sit with
absolutely Ben. No bed, no money in it.
What do you think will happen when I go
out approaching um
next Saturday? Shab,
what do you think will happen, lad?
Thank you, mate. What do you think?
What do you think will happen? [Music] predictions, please.
Franklin's gone flying
out the car.
Where is he?
Oh, I can't believe Greavves is older
than me. Oh, Jesus Christ.
Oh, [ __ ] I'm under the electric blankie. Mhm.
Yeah. Anyways, I'll be back later.