[ __ ] it Oh,
Jesus Christ. They need that power. Yeah.
I don't give a [ __ ] Stop bringing it on my channel.
Mention it again.
I'm blocking you. No one gives a [ __ ]
You're not bringing it on my channel.
Stop bringing weird drama on my channel,
bro. One more time. I'm going to block you.
No one cares. You're not bringing it on
my channel. Don't let me cut you off.
Even though I know you're already a troll.
Don't bring it on my channel.
you know, although I want to actually
talk about someone actually.
Well, you're not addressing it on my
channel. So, that's your last warning.
Oh, bro, I put £100 on. I won five.
Okay, I'm blocking you now, bro.
Um, I won 100 and I I put 100 pound in.
I got to 500, bro. Actually just got the
money now to be fair. Yeah, man. Good
little session. didn't record or
anything, but yeah.
Yeah. Put 100 in, got it to five. But to
be fair, I spent like [ __ ] £400 over
the weekend to be honest with you. Yeah, man.
They gave the full amount as well. It
was actually 507
cuz I left7 pound in there because of
the [ __ ] uh
I won't put it I'm not going to [ __ ]
I'm not going to put it back bro. Don't
worry. Um what I was saying is um
they gave the full amount as well. You
know sometimes they take fees when it
hits your bank. That's why I left £7 in
there because of the fees and [ __ ] But
I won't put it back bro. boy. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't I don't really gamble much
anymore, Charlie. That was just like a one off.
Do you know what though, Charlie? It had
a lot of bad reviews. This is why you
should never read reviews cuz I was
reading reviews reviews and people
saying, "Oh, they didn't get paid out."
And [ __ ] like that. I was [ __ ]
myself, bro. I didn't think I was going
to get paid out cuz a lot of people say
they didn't get paid out. They got
scammed and that. So, you can never ever um trust reviews.
You know what I mean, Charlie? You can
never trust reviews, lad.
You're quite concerned to be fair
cuz it doesn't matter if it's only 500
pound. It's money you won in it. Money's
money or so. It doesn't matter. I don't
think they were going to pay me.
Yeah, they did. So yeah,
I had to block that account, bro,
because keeps bringing up someone. I
told you I'm done with these people. You
know, I'm going to prove to you how
they're jealous of me by not being able
to stop going on about me and I'm not
going on any of the channels. I don't
need to. I made a [ __ ]
you know, I I said something and I'll
back it up. Simple. So
if these people can't stop going on
about me, they're the ones that are jealous. Simple.
That's how it is. That's it.
I think that's probably a good shot to be fair.
Yeah, you should try this website. It's
called a spin dog.
You should try it, bro. Yeah.
Had to show them a [ __ ] bank
statement. [ __ ] madness.
Some more people join to this.
I went on that um L J's video self
projecting. I went on it [ __ ]
actually I did I woke up at 1:00 in the
morning. He's self projecting. He showed
trainers, right? And a couple of things
that he was saying about he just hates
the fact that he's skin. Like you can
just tell that all he's doing right is
self projecting he skin this onto other
people every day. And the comment was
like, "Oh, that gives um Peter Belly and
that gives um PJ nostalgia. Bro, that
doesn't give me nostalgia. I would never
wear or buy that cheap [ __ ] And
apparently I can't do it anymore because
my sublet days are over, mate. I've got
money. You don't know how much money
people have, right? The fact that you
people are the ones that keep coming on
here every day talking about money, it
shows you ain't got none.
That's why these people, Charlie, come
on here every day talking about money
because they ain't got none. Think about
it, bro. Yeah. If these people had
money, they wouldn't sit on YouTube from
the time they wake up to the time they
go to bed. No life. Trust me, bro. If
they had money, they wouldn't do that.
Well, I could go out right now and buy
and spend 12, 13300 just like the good
old days, but I don't need to. I've got
enough stuff. Self projecting
projections to the max.
um all the time. You people can't take
an hour off of YouTube, so stop self
projecting. If you people didn't have
YouTube yet to self-p project your
skintess every day, you'd be [ __ ]
You know that LJ video and the comment
that is self projecting. You don't know
what people have. You don't know what
money people have. I could go out right
now and buy four pair of trainers and
four Stone Island jumpers. You don't
know how much money people have. You
only know about your own lives. This is
what I'm saying with these people. They
only know their own lives. They think
their lives are everyone else's lives.
Sat on benefits, £300 a month, no money.
They generally think that everyone
else's life is theirs.
Germany, it's it's [ __ ] up, bro.
Reading this [ __ ] like 1:00 in the morning.
You know what I'm saying? Nah, not even.
We're not talking about women. I'm
talking about you projectors. You little self reflectors.
All you do every day is call people skin
because you skit yourselves. When
something got to give when something got
to give, man? When is something really
really going to give?
You know, how long are you going to keep
coming on YouTube self- projecting your
skittness onto people? When's something
really going to give? Huh?
No, no, no. Answer me, but how long are
you going to keep self- projecting your skintess?
I was going to do a video on this, but
all you do is call people skin because
you're skin every day. It's a [ __ ]
madness. It really is a madness.
that you talk about money every single
day because you ain't got no money. It's
so obvious for people right to sit on
[ __ ] right for people to sit on uh
YouTube from the time they wake up to
the time they go to bed they've got no
money. Don't let them try and tell you [ __ ] otherwise. Yeah,
it's madness. It is actually madness.
But planning the KFC two weeks in
advance, that was pretty funny to be
fair. If that's actually like true.
That's [ __ ] funny.
What did they actually um plan a [ __ ]
KFC two weeks in advance? Oh my god.
I don't know why that just sounded funny.
Oh Jesus Christ.
Jesus Christ, man.
I had a bagel in the morning. I was
[ __ ] hungry. I spent £17 on a [ __ ]
bagel. Jesus [ __ ] Christ. I know.
17 pound. how hungry I was. Boy,
just getting in the bed [ __ ] with no
bed, no money in it.
That's just my saying, by the way. I'm
not going on about it. It's just my
little uh all the little things I say, you know. One sec.
Don't know why they wanted my a [ __ ]
bank statement. It's [ __ ] mad, isn't
it, bro? what these [ __ ] ask for
as soon as it's to do with [ __ ] them paying out.
Oh, here it is. My
weekend cost more than what he spent
where he bought them items, by the way.
Yeah, I'm not even joking. So,
like I said, self projecting. Yeah.
And I'll be out Saturday. So, yeah.
Yeah. what what what he spent on them
new balance trainers and
um the other things. I spent more going
out the Friday and Saturday and the
Sunday. I'm not even joking, but I swear about 40.
You know, if you are going to buy stuff
and start calling people skint mate, at
least buy decent trainers.
You know what I'm saying? [ __ ] hell.
The self projection on here is great.
It's [ __ ] great.
Could buy a new stone item right now if
I wanted to. Could buy some Vapor Maxes
if I wanted to, but I don't need to.
And just because you went to Vegas, it
doesn't mean anything. Let me tell you
something, K. You could go to Miami,
right, for probably about flight and
hotel? probably about 900 pound. I'm not
even joking, bro. So, when he went to
Vegas, all he done was stayed in a
shitty hotel, bro. There's nothing about
that guy that has any money. I don't
know who he's trying to fool. Not that I
even care, but at the end of the day, I
don't know why he comes on there acting
like he's got money when he [ __ ] has
[ __ ] all, bro. Who the [ __ ] wears new balance trainers?
[ __ ] I wouldn't be seen dead in them.
I would not be seen [ __ ] dead in them.
Like it's it's a madness, bro. And the
most I ever spent two training Stone
Islands, etc. Yeah. Was about it was
£1,100, I think it was. I could spend
£1,100 right now.
You don't know about people's lives. You
don't know what people have. You don't
know what people don't have. So that's it. So yeah,
it's just all self projecting. It
doesn't matter what someone gets. 1,000
a month, 3,000 a month, 4,000 a month,
these self-reflectors are still going to
call you skin
cuz they are skinned. You know what I'm saying?
They talk about money cuz they ain't got no money. So yeah,
my Yeah, my weekend definitely cost more
than what he spent.
What he spent right there, bro, was no
more than £300.
I'm telling you right there. Like that's
not even that's barely half of a [ __ ]
p benefit payment, mate. So if you are
going to call people skin, at least try
and flex a bit more. You know what I'm saying?
Like it's so obvious.
I don't think he's on um No, to be fair,
I don't think he's on £300 a month. I'd
say he's probably on about seven, eight
a month. Um he's definitely on benefits.
All of this [ __ ] about owning properties
and [ __ ] it's a load of old bollocks,
bro. You think someone that's got all
this money, right, would, like I said,
sit on YouTube from the time they wake
up to the time they go to bed? They
would not, bro. They definitely would
not. You know, it's so obvious that the
guy has got nothing. That's why he's
[ __ ] calls people [ __ ] skint.
But yeah, never read reviews um
from [ __ ] casino sites, bro, cuz that
was scary, man.
I didn't think I was going to get
[ __ ] paid out. Why do they [ __ ]
write them reviews? I guess they're just
not genuine reviews. Madness. [Applause]
They rejected my [ __ ] withdrawal.
Then I had to show them a bank statement. Oh,
to be fair, this is like
this is how these places need to work, right?
Like personally, this is how I think they should.
They need to [ __ ] when you win,
right? They need to pay you without any
verification, right? And then after you
win, if they still want this
verification, then they should block
your account. And the things they ask
for, bro, they make it like so like a
bank statement. Not everyone's [ __ ]
good at [ __ ] it and [ __ ] So a lot of
people wouldn't even be know how to show
like a bank statement. Do you know what
I'm saying? So it's the [ __ ] that they
ask for, you know, it's
So what h what they should do is when
you win, they should pay you and then,
you know, not close your account. No,
no, they shouldn't close your account.
What they should do is stop you
depositing again until you [ __ ] verify yourself.
That's what they should do.
Cuz it's like you put money in, you win
the money fair and square. You want your money?
Simple. Doesn't matter how much the
[ __ ] money is, you know,
that bagel was [ __ ] delicious, bro. [ __ ] delicious.
>> Oh, grievy, man. I [ __ ] I woke up
here at um 1:00 in the morning cuz I was
stressing over if I was going to get the
money from the casino or not. So,
I got I ordered a [ __ ] McDonald's at
[ __ ] 4 in the morning, but they
cancelled it because it then moved into
breakfast, and I don't like McDonald's
breakfast. So, I ordered a um bagel,
like a salt beef bagel. Oh my god, it
sent me to sleep, bro. It was so nice. A
salt beef bagel. It reminded me of King. Oh.
Yeah, I got my money in the end. But
yeah, I was reading reviews and people
were saying how they didn't get paid
from this [ __ ] casino, bro. And I was
like, I'm not going to be happy if I
don't get my [ __ ] £500
cuz, you know, £500,500 [ __ ] pound,
bro, in the space of [ __ ] 10 minutes. So,
you know, I kind of
Yeah, the money. So,
yeah, the reviews were saying how they
didn't get paid and people got they were
saying they got scammed and that, but I
was like, realistically, you've never
not been paid out, you know?
So, I'll be out Saturday
getting on it and that'll be it until my birthday. So, yeah,
I deserve that win to be honest.
I went through a lot of [ __ ] on Friday, bro. Um,
yeah, I won 500 from 100. Well,£507.
I left £7 in there cuz I thought they
were going to like there was going to be
fees but there was no fees to be honest. So
which was good. I I got the full amount
so it cost me £3 to deposit. So I want
to I won what I got to 504 basically but
still money in it. Still good money for £100. So,
I got to 570, but I was like, let me uh
keep trying here, you know.
Yeah, it was it was good.
Yeah, I was just on online roulette. I
just stuck 100 pound in, bro.
I don't really gamble much now. It was,
but I thought, [ __ ] it. Why not? That
Joe is addicted, man. That Joe is
actually addicted to gambling.
[ __ ] that, bro. I would never do it like
that again. No way.
No way, Greasy. Would I ever do it like
that again? [ __ ] that.
It's a waste of time. I I was just
bored. I think it was like 2:00 in the
morning. I was like, "Oh, let me just
try 100 pound. I haven't done it for a
month. I'm going to do a nice football
bet on Saturday as well. I'm going to do
a lovely football bet, a nice 10 pound
one." And yeah, I'm just going to go out
and drink and [ __ ] And then like I
said, that's me done till my birthday.
I'm probably going to put a deposit on
another holiday to be honest. So yeah.
So yeah, but the reviews on the casino
was bad. people saying how they didn't
get paid and [ __ ] and I was like they
[ __ ] better pay me.
But yeah, like I said, I spent about
[ __ ] £400 over that weekend.
No, it's called Spin Dog.
I spent about £400 [ __ ] pound. This
is the problem. Every time you go out,
you you end up spending ridiculous
amounts of money.
It's just it's [ __ ] up. But obviously
I'm going out on Saturday cuz I don't
need to get my hair done and so it is
just going to be about like 80 pound I spend. So
So why the [ __ ] not in it?
[ __ ] hell, bro.
That [ __ ] bagel was lush. Oh my god,
that bagel was nice.
Oh. Uh, that's the that's the email.
That's the email.
I'm just going to have it there in case
of a short money to try and win some
money in it.
So yeah, I was able to carry over more
money this month, Greezy, because of the win.
Normally I save about 600, but obviously
probably be over a thousand now cuz I
won. So happy days.
Virgin boy getting in a bed with no bed,
no money. What?
One second. Email at [ __ ] sake.
But yeah, anyways, um, sorry, I have to
email them or something. So yeah, I feel
like they shouldn't let you um
you know, they shouldn't um let you
play. If when you win they ask you to
show this and show that because it's not
about identity fraud, f fraud or theft
because you know they they they let you deposit
So, they let you deposit, but
I mean, yeah, even though it wasn't the
worst, I still don't agree with it because
of the fact that, you know, you
you have to show [ __ ] the bank
statement and it ain't easy to do that.
And they know this, you know, you have
to actually go on a [ __ ] browser website. So,
you know, the only places that pay out
fairly is [ __ ] bookies and [ __ ]
arcades. You win your money, they pay
you. Done. Simple.
But [ __ ] with this [ __ ] there's always
But I say casinos are the most dodgy
like actual like cuz they'll do anything
to get out of trying to pay you
anything. Anything and everything. So
just like my mom said, you need to
remember you've never had problems
getting paid out before. So
especially Oh, I tell you which ones are
the worst is the ones that the [ __ ]
casinos have got no company name like
that one in Nottingham.
They don't mind taking people's money. You know
why the [ __ ] do I want to see a bank
statement? Shouldn't they be asking for
that before you [ __ ] deposit?
If I didn't get this money, I was going
to go to to a bookies and smash it up,
bro. Even though it's a [ __ ] online site, right? Um,
still [ __ ] it's the same industry in it.
But yeah, like I said, just don't just
don't ever read reviews
cuz their reviews were bad,
bad, bad. People were saying they didn't
get paid. People saying that they stole
stole money from them.
They paid me and there was no fees. So,
no, no, Oh, no. Virgin boy. What's Yeah.
You want to go out
on Saturday, but I have to.
That's what I was going to.
So, think about that, bro. 400 [ __ ] gone.
And I don't even have a date for this week.
But it's a hookup culture, they call it.
People just want sex nowadays.
Do you know what? I'm putting this [ __ ]
right as the same as these casino reviews.
Definitely. It's [ __ ] what they're
saying on Reddit. Hey, bro. I got my £57
from the casino, Mike.
Yeah, I won £400 on roulette [ __ ] the
other day. Finally got the money. I was
reading reviews and they were saying
about how they didn't get paid and how
the casinos sites a scam.
It was making me quite worried, bro.
So, that must be the same thing on Reddit then.
You know, people saying that they, you
know, you can meet people on apps and
stuff. They must be talking [ __ ] Same
as these reviews. And there was a lot of
these reviews. They had a lot of bad
reviews as well. I didn't think I was
going to get the money, bro. Seriously. So,
it's a hookup culture, Mike. Apparently,
people make dating seems so easy on
Reddit, Mike. It's [ __ ] impossible.
You can't even get a date, Mike. I got
10 numbers uh
on that Friday, bro. I don't even have a
date this week. And I spent about
[ __ ] £400 by the time I was finished.
400 [ __ ] pounds on nothing, bro. But
I'm going to go out on Saturday just
because um I have my hair done and yeah.
So I might as well spend [ __ ] 80 100 pound whatever. Nah, bro.
But they make it seem so easy, Mike.
They they make it seem like you could
just go out and get laid.
[ __ ] 10 numbers I got
and only one replied and they stopped
replying when I said let's meet up. It
will never change, Mike. It will never
change. I've kind of accepted it now
though, bro. Like, it's just never ever
going to change it. I mean, what can
anyone say anymore? It would always be like this
in it. So,
I fancy a t-bone steak. Oh, I had a
bagel at like 4 in the morning.
It was beautiful, man. Nice salt beef
bagel. It was [ __ ] lush. I warmed it
up for 20 seconds.
I kind of fancy a t-bone steak today. Yeah.
I mean, I've just accepted I'm just
going to be single forever. It is what
it is, isn't it?
That it's just what it is, isn't it? Now,
what can anyone say? Huh?
It will never change, will it? Mike, Michael Hunt,
same [ __ ] eh?
I do fancy a nice t-bone, but
I don't live anywhere near the butchers.
It means we going all the way to the butchers.
I pay £15.
Yeah, about 15.
12 to about 15.
And it is Tuesday and I said I was going
to get a T-bone steak every Tuesday, wasn't I?
But that that bagel, bro, hits
different. A salt beef bagel. Oh, mate.
King likes it as well.
Oh, I took King.
Virgin boy can't afford nothing.
I did see one of the videos that popped
up. He was asking me to um show um £300.
Get a grip, mate. I'm not showing you no
money. Do you know what makes me laugh,
Mike? Yeah. Funny you should be on here.
You know, I went on LJ's video where he
was showing these shitty trainers and um
a hoodie and some [ __ ] bottoms or
some jeans and he was saying, "Oh, it's
nice to be able to afford what you
want." Yeah. Yeah. You show him, mate.
you show him, you know, he did not spend
more than £300 on them items combined.
And he's talking about and he's talking
um people not being able to afford
things. And then they were like, "Oh
yeah, this gives uh PJ nostalgia when no
that doesn't give me nostalgia because I
never wore that cheap [ __ ] I didn't buy
that cheap [ __ ] When I buy stuff, I buy
expensive stuff." And he was like, "Oh,
them days are gone um because of the
subletter money." And I was like, "Bro,
I could go out now and spend £1,300 if I
wanted to." Huh? What the [ __ ] These
people, Mike, they don't know how much
money people have. They don't know what
people have. They only bounce off their
own lives. The [ __ ] The most I ever
spent on a single shopping trip was
£1,100. And I could do it again right
now if I wanted to,
you know? Like it's just it's
projection, bro. Think of it, man. Do
you think these people would be on here
from the time they wake up to the time
they go if there wasn't skin? Ask
yourself that question. You know,
come on, man.
Like they asking
He didn't even buy nice trainers.
[ __ ] New Balance. What the [ __ ] bro?
Look, I could go out right now and buy a
Stone Island jumper. Why do I need to?
I've I've got enough that look they look
brand new. What? I can easily go out
right now buy trainers and a Stone
Island jumper. You don't know how much
money people have.
You know, they don't know what anyone
has. They just talk about their own
lives. This is what I'm saying to you, bro.
They call people skin cuz their skin obvious.
You think someone that had money would
be going Portugal every year?
Do you know what I'm saying, bro? Like
if they showed like a Rolex. Yeah. Some
comment made says like if you showed a
Rolex or a car, okay, then yeah, that's
a different story. If someone just
bought a Rolex, then they can say that.
But you spent not even half of someone's benefit money.
You haven't got money. You're skint.
Just because someone goes to Vegas, it
doesn't mean they've got money either.
Listen, Mike. Yeah. I could go to Miami
next summer and the flight to the hotel
would probably cost about £1,000.
800 900. Yes. Yes, you can. Yes, you
can. Trust me, because I've looked into
it, you know, and you just know that
when he was in Vegas, he was staying at
some shitty hotel. I mean,
yeah, I'm going to get a t-bone, I reckon.
Can I be bothered?
I need to stop eating like I'm rich. I'm
not rich anymore, mate. And I'm still
[ __ ] eating like I used to. [ __ ] bagel.
[ __ ] McDonald's. [ __ ] T-Bone
trying to make us [ __ ] They're trying
to make us skin like the [ __ ] virgin.
The skin virgin in the bed [ __ ] with
absolutely no bed. No money in it. Like [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, these people are obsessed. And the
thing I said, Mike, is I'm not going to
go on about them. I'm going to show
everyone that they're the jealous ones.
They're the obsessed ones, you know. And
as And I was right because they can't
stop talking about me because people
tell me. So, I'm I'm right in it.
I want a [ __ ] t-bone steak, bro.
But don't worry, I won't be spending
£400 Saturday. I need to start saving money, bro. [ __ ] sake.
It won't come to 400 a night out [ __ ]
on Saturday. I'm sure it won't again.
It's just scary. Every time you go out
in London, it's scary, bro. The amount
of money. It's like
it is quite scary.
Whether you work, whether you don't
work, cuz you think, where the [ __ ] did £400 go?
Where the [ __ ] did 400 pound [ __ ] go, bro? Oh.
Right. I see you [ __ ] later.