[ __ ] hell, bro.
That money mic really is a [ __ ] ratty.
The actual scenes on it, bro. The actual
scenes on him.
Guy is not about nothing, bro.
projecting his [ __ ] albino life onto other people
when he's the one that lives with his
parents at what 33 years of [ __ ] age,
bro. And he's never lived by himself
and he's talking about people being
[ __ ] skinned. The [ __ ] ugly albino
please, bro. Come on now. Embarrass him.
I hate seeing comments like that, you
know, man. I [ __ ] do
this to be pulled off.
That's [ __ ] nasty, bro. Hanging
guy's a [ __ ] idiot, bro.
Why is he commenting a load of [ __ ]
bro? The guy don't even know me.
This is what I'm saying, bro. Like, all
of this [ __ ] on here. Yeah.
It's just self projection,
you know, with [ __ ]
Michael Basset and all of these people.
It's just self projection.
You know, that's all it is. Because you
think to yourself like, how do they know
so much about someone that they don't
even know? And you ask yourself the
question, it's like, oh yeah, cuz
they're talking about themselves. It's
so obvious, isn't it?
It's so obvious.
Like even with that [ __ ] mic. Yeah. I
can't even show £50,
bro. I spent about £600 in the past
three days. What the [ __ ] bro? You know
what I'm saying? And I can't even
[ __ ] remember what we [ __ ] did to
be honest with you, mate. You just know
that with these people, they're self
projecting, bro. Oh, they're they're projecting hardcore.
Hardcore projecting, bro.
Don't forget this guy's a [ __ ]
gambling addict. So, I was going to
start on him on his channel, but he
[ __ ] he's got no videos or anything.
He deleted all of his [ __ ] No, that's
definitely self projecting, bro.
Definitely definitely self projecting.
I've shown more money than that clown
ever has ever will. I've got more money
than he has now or than he ever will. He
self he self projects.
He's another self projector. I mean,
he's another self projector. That
Michael Basset defo
I can't show50.
Oh my god. Self projecting. Self projectors.
That's what they are. Self [ __ ] projectors.
Just like large a self projector.
Oh, project this. Goodness.
They think everybody has exactly the
same life as they do,
bro. Just Michael. Yeah, just Michael
Basset. I see him on the Virgin's
[ __ ] channel. It just popped up. I
only read his comment just cuz it come
up. He said, "Oh, I can't show £50 until
I get my pip." Brother, you don't know
how much money I have.
You do not know what people have, what
people don't have. I already told you
what I spent the past three [ __ ]
days. This is what I'm saying, bro. With
all of these people, yeah,
it's just self projection with all of
these people on here. They think
everyone else's life is the same as theirs.
Legit, bro. They literally think
everyone has the same life as them. Skin
sat on YouTube from the time they wake
up to the time they go to bed. They
think everyone's like them.
No, seriously. They do it
cuz he is just projecting. That mic is
projecting hard, bro. Hard, bro.
But the guy is in his 30s. He's never
lived by himself. He's never lived by
and he lives in Birmingham. You know, in
in London, you know, you kind of have an
excuse. You know, London's expensive as
[ __ ] The guy lives in the [ __ ]
outskirts of Birmingham, bro. He lives
with his parents in his 30s. Yeah. And
he's never lived by himself, bro. The
guy is the definition of [ __ ] skint. Yeah. [ __ ] mad.
>> Yeah, but it is definitely just self
injection at this point.
Well, it's always been self injection,
but you know,
look, none of these people can prove me
wrong, mate. They're [ __ ] mongos.
They actually are mongos.
They really really are.
Why wouldn't I be able to show £50? I'm
not showing you nothing. No £5, no£10,
no [ __ ] nothing because it's all
projecting with you people. self projecting.
You go on about money every day cuz you
ain't got no money. Same [ __ ] Same [ __ ]
every day with these people, bro.
Same shite every [ __ ] day with these people. Who's that? Yep.
Same [ __ ] with these people.
Oh, that was nice. That sick. Yeah.
Why would I be able to show £50? I'm not
showing you nothing. Is there what's the
actual reason you want people to show
you money again for the millionth time?
Because every single time you get showed
money, you will run away. The community
is dead as it is.
Like, bro, I wish that guy was starting
his [ __ ] before I went to Birmingham,
you know? I would have [ __ ] him up,
bro. If he come out, I swear to God. Why
didn't this guy just start his [ __ ] like when um
why didn't he start his [ __ ] [ __ ] um
before I went to Birmingham, bro? Cuz he
only started this [ __ ] when I come back.
You know what I mean?
The guy would get smacked, bro. In like one [ __ ]
punch, he would get knocked the [ __ ]
out, bro. He's about 5' tall. Yeah, he's
giving it the [ __ ] biging on [ __ ]
YouTube, bro. I'm going to do a video to
this little [ __ ] I swear to God, bro.
Yeah, I swear to God, bro. Come to
London anytime you want. I'll smash your
[ __ ] face in. It's annoying, bro.
Seeing these stupid little comments,
bro. The guy is like a 5 foot nothing as
well. He's a 5 foot nothing. He ain't
got no money, bro.
He ain't got no money. He ain't got to
know nothing, bro. He lived with his
parents in his 30s, bro. Yeah, people in
London has actually got an excuse. You
ain't got nothing, bro. [ __ ] all.
Look at your life, bro. You owe You owe
[ __ ] Lone Sharks [ __ ] money. Yeah,
Lone Sharks boyed off your mother and
you done nothing about it, bro. You're
not about that life. So, stop comment on
YouTube like you're about that life cuz
you're not about that life and you will
never be about that life.
Yeah, if you want to compare me and you
together. Yeah, I've shown more money
than you have. How about that one? You
[ __ ] stupid albino [ __ ] I've shown
more money than you will ever show, bro. Multiple times.
Yeah, they're proper freaks, bro.
Just like that [ __ ] money mic.
Why is your name money Mike? You ain't
got no money, mate. No money at all,
bro. You're skint. You've got [ __ ] nothing.
Yeah. You started You started your [ __ ]
when I come back as well, just as always. Yeah.
Waiting for my pit, bro. We don't all
live your life. Do you understand?
They seem to think everyone lives their life.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
It made me laugh. Like even when I went
on that Lord J video and he [ __ ]
bought them trainers and that hoodie and
that and them them trousers. I spent
double that, bro. Over the weekend. Over
the weekend. I spent double that just
going out. I swear to God, bro. I
[ __ ] swear to God I did
cuz I went out drinking. Then I bought
lamb which was £40. The LEGO L40. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
And that that Monty um blocked me on his
other account, by the way. I'm glad he
did. You know, cuz I will never speak to
Monty ever again. Even if he comes like
running back to me, I will never ever
like be his mate ever again, bro. He's a
snake. [ __ ] bro. Serious.
Yeah. Nobody cares, bro.
Nobody cares. So I don't know why you're
telling me. The only thing I care about
is why that money mike is making
comments like not everyone has the same
life as you. I can't show 50, brother. I
spent over £500 in three days
on [ __ ] basically food, [ __ ]
drinking. You don't know people's life.
You only know your skin life. You only
know the life that you live.
You understand? You only know the life
that you live, bro. No one else's life.
You don't know no one else's life.
Know what I mean?
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] bro. I swear to God.
They don't know anyone else's life. They
only know their own life.
You know what I mean?
I saw a comment saying, "Oh, I can't
buy, oh, those were the days where I
could buy Stone Island jumpers and
trainers." But I could do it now if I
wanted to. I can go out now and buy
myself designer coach. You don't know
what people have. You don't know what
people don't have. You only know about
your own lives that you live that you
project onto others every day because
you seem to know so much about people
that you don't know.
So, I mean, you must be talking about
yourselves at this point. It's obvious, you know,
cuz who who would even write a comment like that?
You know, I can't show £50. Do you even
believe what your is this guy? All
right, bro. That's what they've got to
be talking about themselves. They have
to be worth. They have to be talking about themselves.
There's no other alternative.
I spent just spent £50 in the butchers. [ __ ]
I spent £50 the other day on roast
dinner. I went out drinking. You don't
know what people have. You don't know
what money people have, what money
people don't have.
The community is dead. We don't want any
of you people running away anymore, bro. You know,
[ __ ] the guy's a [ __ ] plonker.
The guy has got nothing, bro. That
[ __ ] money mic.
Probably done his balls in to be honest.
I will never show money on it ever again. Mhm.
>> Think about what you're saying, right?
You try and say that people don't have
money, bro. People saw me in a pub. I
spent £50 on barely two rounds.
But people don't have money, apparently.
Yeah. Yours was they ain't got money.
These people really are embarrassing, bro.
out on YouTube every day, ain't got a
life. Projecting their [ __ ] onto other
people every day. [ __ ] madness, man. Madness.
Tell the guy to come to London. I'll
smash his [ __ ] face in. Simple. Yeah. [ __ ] idiot.
That's what they are. They
don't care who's making videos, who's
not making videos.
Like I said, I'll leave them to embarrass themselves
and show who who the jealous one is.
And by leaving them to make a fool of
themselves, it's proving you right. Really? Yeah.
Cuz the more they do this, like I said,
from what you're telling me, the more
they do this, the more it shows that
they're the ones that are the skin ma,
they're this, they're that. The more
they do this, the more it shows that you
are not these things and they are these things.
That's all it shows. The more they do
this, it shows.
Uh, yep, you are on YouTube again and
I'll fix that for you. Bye-bye now. So, yeah. Yeah,
he's deleted all these [ __ ] videos,
bro. I was going to fart him on his channel, but
yeah, he's gone.
But this guy in real life, he's a he's
another little [ __ ] bag. That's what you
you'll find with these people. Yeah.
People like Virgin Boy, skin in a bed
suit with no bed, no money in it. Um you
know, Michael Basset, you'll realize
that in real life they're proper little
shits. Proper proper little shits in
real life, but online they've got the
biggest mouth. You'll always find that.
You will always find it.
It's always these white little nicky
little geeky little [ __ ] but
in real life they're about nothing.
Same with that Ricky Milling account.
The scrawny little white kid attention
[ __ ] skinny arms. They're all the
same on here, bro. Self projecting.
Um, so yeah, bro. Like they're all the
same on here. Like all the cowards,
cowards, self injectors, they're all the
same on here, bro. For real.
You know what I'm saying? Like that
Ricky Millon, Virgin Boy,
[ __ ] Money Mike that has no money.
They're all the same, bro. I swear to
them, they're all the same. They're all
white scorny little [ __ ] [ __ ] that
ain't about nothing in real life. Do you understand?
You know what I'm saying, bro?
So, yeah, I'm going to come off this
community soon anyways, bro. I think. Yeah,
cuz it just gets weirder and weirder and
weirder and weirder and weirder, bro.
I swear to God,
bro. Why it's so mad, Cory? Yeah. These
people try to tell people that they've
got no money, but they don't even know
me, bro. They don't know what I have,
what I don't have. It's so [ __ ]
how they can just do they not get bored
of self projecting every day
just like this account now. Oh, you
never having a woman excites me. Even
though I've literally been seen with
women multiple times. This is what I'm
saying, bro. It's just pathetic. I'm
coming off this [ __ ] man. No, bro. It's
just money. Listen, bro. Yeah. I just
went on the virgin's thing because it
popped up. Didn't listen to anything. I
just I'm not interested in the comments.
And we've got this money mic, bro,
I'm I don't I can't show50 I'm skinn
until my until I get picked. I'm
thinking, bro, do these people really
think everyone has the same life as them?
They seem to think that everyone's got
their life ski on YouTube projecting,
bro. I swear down they think that
everyone's got the same life as them or something.
They really they must do. They really
really must do.
Like do you have to ask Bro, listen. Do
you really have to ask that? Is this
argument? Bro, I'm not arguing with
them. I'm ignoring them. I don't I don't
retaliate to them. They're the ones
obsessed with me.
Well, I was just talking about that. And
I was just saying, but think about it,
bro. Yeah. We got three people here.
Yeah, Ricky Bington,
the good version in the bed sit with no
bed, no money in it. And then we got
Money Mike. What have these people all
got in common? They're all white little
[ __ ] naky geeky little cowards,
you know? They're the biggest cowards in
real life, but yet on here, you know,
they they're [ __ ] all, you know,
they're all mouth mouthing off [ __ ]
every day. You see what I mean, bro?
They've got no life, bro. You know what?
It's not that they even
It's not even that they um um It's not
even that they come on YouTube every
day. It's what they do from the time
they wake up to the time they go to bed.
Bro, they ain't got no money. Cuz people
that are not skimp don't do this, you know.
They think everyone has their life.
That's the problem with these people,
bro. They're always They're always
jealous, bro. Always jealous. They got
no life. They're sat on YouTube. They're
jealous of anyone that's got a [ __ ]
that's got5 more than them.
There was There was another thing, bro.
I was laughing at you, Cory. I was on
Lord Jay's video. Yeah. I don't go on
that channel anymore, but it popped up.
I don't go on the lives because I just
get brain damage every time I go on it.
Bro, bro, I was on the I was watching a video. Yeah,
bro. I was watching a video. Yeah. And uh
the guy bought [ __ ] New Balance
trainers, trousers, and a Calvin Klein
hoodie. And I'm thinking and he's
talking about how, oh, it's nice to be
able to afford things that you can. And
I was like, "Bro, I spent double that on
the weekend." Like, let's just say
argument say that cost £300. Bro, I
spent about £500 from that Friday until now.
I won some money, by the way, on the
roulette. So, but yeah, bro, like that's
not even half of someone's [ __ ] benefit payment.
And then we got a comment saying, "Oh,
well, yeah, that must give um PJ
nostalgia when he could go out and buy
things." Well, I can do it now. You
don't know what people have. You don't
know what people don't have. We don't
all have your lives. Yeah.
You know, I've been out pretty much all
day, but I'm just chilling now playing GTA.
I'll be out on Saturday.
So, yeah. Like I said, they think
everyone's got their life. So, it's [ __ ]
you know. I got stone islands on that
look brand new. Do I need to buy new
ones? I mean, I can if I want.
So, cuz think about it, Cory. How do
these people know so much about people
that they don't know?
How could they possibly know the ins and
outs of people that they don't even
know? Because they're talking about themselves.
It's obvious, bro.
They're [ __ ] mongos, bro. Like I like
I told you, I just gave you [ __ ]
three people, three examples. You know,
same as that Ricky Millan, bro. I'd slap
the [ __ ] out a hole and back into it again.
Know what I'm saying, bro? I would slap
that [ __ ] silly, man. You don't
understand all three of them.
It's funny how you never get black
people doing this, isn't it? It's funny
how you never get any black people doing
this. It's always these little white
geeky, nicky, lame [ __ ] kids. Ain't
it, bro? It Do you not find that a bit
funny? How it's always these white
little [ __ ] [ __ ] these allney [ __ ] geeks
that Ricky [ __ ] nodd legs [ __ ]
Mike. I mean, you don't notice that,
bro. It's never these black people doing that.
It's never like anything but these like [ __ ]
You know what I mean, bro?
Come to think of it, you know?
Madness, bro. Madness.
Yeah, I won 500 pound on roulette Cory.
Well, over 500 pound technically, man.
So, yeah, just thought I'd give it a
little whirl in it.
They finally paid. Yeah.
My birthday's soon to
go [ __ ] man.
I had a nice bagel this morning. 4:00 in
the morning, I spent £17 on a bagel. Yep.
No one can prove me wrong.
[ __ ] I got seven. Yeah, I spent £17 on
a [ __ ] bagel, bro. I was that hungry.
Yeah, I was that [ __ ] hungry, bro.
[ __ ] Oh, it was so good though. Oh,
bro, you can't beat a nice
salt beef bagel. It hits different
stiffening, bro. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah. So, I've been eating like a king recently.
Haven't bought any new trainers or any
new Stone Island jumpers cuz I don't need any. [ __ ]
They're things that you buy and they
last for [ __ ] years. You know what I mean?
[ __ ] self projection, lad. That's
what these people do.
I might do a video to that money mic, you know. Yeah,
I might do, bro. Something to do. Yeah.
So, yeah, I'm going to go out um on
Saturday. Send it. See,
I kind of don't want to, but cuz I've
had my a haircut.
See, told you it's not about money, bro.
I even want money and I still don't
really want to go out, but
nothing to doing it.
Is this a bugs game?
No, not approaching today. I'm going to
sleep in a minute.
Nah, I'm going sleep in a minute.
Why the [ __ ] would I be going out?
I put £100 on roulette
and I won 507. I withdrew the 507 cuz I
thought they were going to take a
[ __ ] fee. I mean, it's not a perfect
day. The only reason I'm going out
Saturday is because I've had my haircut.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be doing it again
until my birthday
cuz it's a [ __ ] mugs game.
Dating in this country is a mugs game.
Literally is a mugs game.
Just like gambling's a mug's game.
It was online. I was reading these reviews. Yeah.
And they were saying about how they
didn't get paid out and how the site's a scam and det.
And they were saying this [ __ ] and bro,
I was getting scared, bro. I was like,
what if I don't get my money? And I
realized, yeah, you shouldn't read up on reviews because
they were say they were getting bad
reviews, like they didn't pay out and
they they took no fee as well.
Um, no, I think I won on a Sunday and
they gave me my money this morning.
Had to show them a bank statement,
but it weren't nowhere near as bad as
what them [ __ ] reviews were making
out. They were saying how they didn't
get paid and [ __ ] Yeah.
But they paid me, so
um so yeah,
you shouldn't I don't believe in all of
this verification [ __ ] I think if you
win, they should pay your money and then
if they want you to verify, block you
from depositing until you verify.
That's the way I see it.
It's called spin dog. That's the way I
see it. I see it as like if they let you
deposit and you win, they should pay you
out and then they should ask you to
verify if you want to deposit again.
[ __ ] I had to show them a [ __ ]
bank statement for [ __ ] sake
on my online banking. But
yeah, but it's not good anymore
because of um it's not good anymore
because of um it's euros now and I can't
play something that's in euros. I just
can't get used to it.
But yeah, I'm going to [ __ ] do a
video to that [ __ ] money mic, I think.
things are [ __ ]
we've golden [ __ ] it's euros now
I was scared I weren't going to get the
money to be honest. So never read reviews
because reviews are never accurate.
never reviews are never ever accurate.
And it was stressing me out as well cuz
obviously if they didn't give me the
money then I would have lost £100 and I
wouldn't get paid the money that I won
fair and square. So you know £500500
[ __ ] pound bro still doesn't matter.
It's a lot to win in [ __ ] the space
of 5 10 minutes is it? So, I mean,
if they're not paying you, then you're
[ __ ] in it, really.
But I thought realistically, I've never
had a problem with any site paying me,
so I don't think this is going to be the first. So, yeah,
be out again on Saturday.
I'm really getting sick of this [ __ ] brother. Honestly,
it doesn't matter if a lot of women are
out today. They're not interested.
I mean, you learn anything from my experiences.
There's women out every day, but none of
them are interested. What's your point?
I got 10 numbers on Friday. Only one
replied. I invited him out Saturday.
They didn't reply. I mean,
what what does that tell you, bro? Like,
it's a Mugs game.
No, I'm not going out today, bro. I'm
going out Saturday.
And I'll be pre-drinking as well because Yeah.
I mean, there is a lot to lose. I mean,
you're going to lose your time. It's not
going to change. Do you actually do you
actually think it's going to change?
Like do you actually think you're going
to go out and you're going to find
someone that's interested? I I don't.
But I have nothing better to do on
Saturday, so I might as well.
Like it's either that or stay home. So
the best day is Thursdays and Wednesdays.
But I mean, [ __ ]
No, it's not the worst day. Saturday is
not the worst day. It's just not as good as Thursdays.
Saturday, the worst day is [ __ ] The
worst day is Mondays.
Tuesdays are the worst days. Listen,
I'm only going out on Saturday cuz I've
got nothing [ __ ] better to do
and my hair's still fresh. Like if my
hair was not as soon as my hair goes
back, I ain't going out until my
birthday, bro. So So
this will be my last chance to make use
of the hair and the beard and that. And
if I still don't get anything, then I'm
not going out to my birthday. So
well, every day is happy hour except Saturday.
But I don't know why you're encouraging
me, bro. I mean, you know, they're not
interested in this country, so I don't
know why you're egging me on.
I know they're not interested in this country.
That's why I'm leaving,
you know? So, I'm leaving. I'm I'm going
away on [ __ ] November. So
I'm leaving, bro, cuz of this. Don't
know why you would think
no 811 2.
It will never change in this country ever. So,
and I don't even though I've got money
and even though I want money, I still
don't even really want to go out
Saturday. But like I said, I'm only
doing it because I've had my haircut.
So, so I mean,
so it was never to do with the money. I
told you it was never to do with the money. Yeah.
Dating is seriously like impossible here, bro. Really is.
But I deserve that win anyways. I went
through a lot of [ __ ] on Friday with the
[ __ ] escore. It's [ __ ] [ __ ]
The [ __ ] numbers. Only one replied.
[ __ ] bro. It's depressing, isn't it? So yeah.
Oh, you don't know the story? Okay. Well,
I went to the escort house at the end of
getting them 10 numbers.
Paid them £100 to give me a [ __ ] No
condom. get to finishing their mouth.
Halfway through it, they were like, "Oh
yeah, you can't come in my mouth." I was
like, "What do you mean I can't come in
your mouth?" I gave you the money. They
were trying to be assy about it. I said,
"Okay, give me half my money back." Um,
and she weren't having any of it at all.
I said, "Can I give her half?" And give
half my money back. She wasn't having it.
Um, then a guy come I told him, "Get the
[ __ ] out of my face." Like he tried to
get in my face. So I said, "Move yourself."
And then I said, "I want half my money
back." Obviously, cuz I still done shut
with hours. I want half my money back.
It normally cost about 70. I want half
my money back. He says, "No." I said,
"You know, I'm not going to sit here and
beg for my money back. I'm just going to
do the windows in."
Um, no, I didn't even finish. I barely
finished. No, just kissed them. Sucked
[ __ ] done some [ __ ] foreplay.
Sucked my dick. I still want half my money back.
So they gave half my money back. I said,
"If you don't give half my money back,
I'm going to do your windows in."
So I just said, "I'll take half the money back."
Really and truly, cuz it's normally 80
without coming in their mouth. So they
gave me 40, which just call it just call
it 60, whatever, bro. You know what I
mean? But I said
um I said if you don't give the if you
don't give half the money back I'm going
to do your windows in. And then the
people upstairs were like the people
upstairs were like oh like just leave
it. It's not worth it over £100. It's
not about £100. It's about the fact that
they were trying to take the piss out of
me and I weren't going to have it. So I
was like what what do you want it to be?
I don't care. I don't want to be
careful. I I was going to get that money
back. I'm not scared. I would have died,
bro. If I had to die, I would have died.
I'm not having someone take the piss out
of me. I don't care. I'm not scared of
nobody. You're not going to take the
piss out of me. I say the same thing
sober. If I die, I die. You're not going
to take the piss out of me.
So, it's not about being careful, bro.
You don't know me. Don't take the piss
out of me. Simple.
So, I don't care who they know. I don't
give a [ __ ] what they do. You give me
half the money back or I'm doing the
windows in. Simple. Like it's that's it.
Guy come out gave half the money back.
Whatever. Well, you know. So yeah,
you know, they weren't escorts. They
were just normal people.
So well, I'm you're going to take my
£100 and I'm going to leave you with my £100.
Are you mad? Like, what world do you
live in, bro?
Like, people get killed for less.
Yeah, it's not a problem.
It's not a problem at all at all. You
know, we we we agreed we had a deal and
then they're trying to change the deal
when we agreed to it. And then the guy
was like, "Oh, every girl has a
different price." I was like, "No, they do not.
No, they do not. I've been doing this
for years, mate. Trust me, more longer
than you've been in the business. And
it's never £100 to have a [ __ ] and
you don't get to finish. It has never
been that, bro. I know how much these
things cost because I've done it
hundreds of times. Trust me, probably
longer than you've been doing this. So,
just all in all, a negative experience. So yeah,
the country's a joke.
Yeah, she was all right.
But yeah, it's a [ __ ] joke.
[ __ ] joke, this country.
I can't wait to leave, bro. I really
can't wait to leave.
We'll never have to deal with this [ __ ] ever again.
But it's mad cuz sometimes you can get a
really nice escort
that just you pay you get the service no
problems which is how it should be.
There is some you know and they will ask
you there was this one I used to see I
don't know what happened to her she oh
was everything okay how was the service
she was nice and everything but I think
she moved then there obviously was that
Chinese one that was nice so you can get
good ones but
you have to go through a lot of [ __ ]
bro [ __ ] hell there was a lot of rude ones
yeah it's like one and yeah it's hard
but they are out Yeah.
No, never been with an English one. Yeah. Never.
But I'm not going to get an escort on um
Saturday cuz I need to save some money
as well. So I'm leaving soon. So can't
be wasting hundreds and hundreds and hundreds.
Just haven't and you know the [ __ ] up
thing about this thing. Yeah. Is that
whole thing Friday went out Saturday had
a bro it cost me [ __ ] £400.
400 [ __ ] pound to get 10 numbers and
not one single date and then [ __ ] an
escort that thinks they can rob you.
It's a madness.
400 [ __ ] pound. You can leave the
country with [ __ ] £400 [ __ ] pound.
I was saying this to Ant-Man. Yeah. That
you can leave the country with £400.
It doesn't matter. Obviously not Asia.
You can't go Thailand. You can't you
can't go America. But bro, the fact that
you can leave the country with the same
amount of money as you.
Yeah, I did.
Has the same amount of money as um you
can leave the country with is very concerning.
[ __ ] that is mad. I don't even know how
[ __ ] end up spending that amount of
money. So when L does these self-p
projecting videos trying to call me
skin, he doesn't know how much people
have. He doesn't know what money people
have, what money people don't have. It's
just self projection with them.
Know what I mean? So that's what makes me laugh.
But in the end of it, my weekend cost
double what he spent on them clothes and trainers. Huh? So,
your family would never charge me. What
are you talking about? I bought the I
bought the roast dinner.
What are you on about, you idiot?
I bought the roast dinner because I
wanted to buy the roast dinner. We take
it in turns to buy it. I mean,
what are you talking about?
But yeah, all of this [ __ ] bro about
like your skin and all of that, it's
just it's just self-projective at the
end of the day with these people. And
that's what it's always going to be, self-projecting.
The guy bought new balance trainers. Oh
my god, bro. Oh my god. I laughed. I
swear to God, I [ __ ] He hates the fact
that he's skinn. That's what it is. Self projecting.
Who? Bro, you wouldn't see me dead in
them trainers, bro. I swear to God. I
swear to God you would not see me dead
in them trainers.
[ __ ] hell, man.
Yeah, I'll be out Saturday. So,
No, no, no.
Get on the beers, pre-drinks
hopefully. But yeah, I should I should
have had a date for this week to be fair.
It really is a mugs game, is it?
Trying a date in this country is a
[ __ ] Mugs game, lad.
I spent a lot of money, bro. [ __ ] the
barber cost me [ __ ] 50 quid cuz I had
to get my
[ __ ] face wax, face mask.
It's mad, is it? It is mad.
It's just like I, you know, I know
people say that you need to accept it
and t and but the thing is is that like
it's still not normal to accept.
Still not it's just not normal, is it, bro?
None of it's normal, is it? You go out
smelling good, looking good.
You should at least be getting a date.
It's [ __ ] It is generally [ __ ]
It's just such a [ __ ] up thing to have
accept. I don't know. It's weird.
But it will never change anyways. So
that's why we're leaving.
I'm not staying out there permanently.
I'm just going for a couple of weeks. You know,
Vindal, I've just had a t-bone steak,
bro. Are you good?
Are you blind?
I just had a 20 t-bone steak. What am I
going to order within the loop? I had a 17 pound
I had a 17 pound bagel at 5:00 in the
[ __ ] morning cuz I was starving.
Just [ __ ] ate a [ __ ] 20 T-Bone steak
about an hour ago. Why the [ __ ] I'm
going to order a vindaloo? [ __ ]
It's called Spin Dog.
Yeah, man. And I was [ __ ] hungry at
5:00 in the morning. I went to order
McDonald's, like a chicken mac cuz I
don't like the breakfast. And it was
coming and they cancelled it. And then
could order a bagel and bro, I know it's
ridiculous, but I was starving. I was
[ __ ] starving. So I was like, "Yeah,
okay. I want some money. I can kind of
justify a little bit. I'm going to have
to buy this bagel, bro. I'm [ __ ]
I am [ __ ]
starving. And it was 5:00 in the morning.
Oh yeah, bro.
Yeah. salt beef with like butter and Oh,
it's ping, man. It was [ __ ] gorgeous.
You can't beat an ice bagel.
And yeah, it was £17, but you only live
once in it.
It was either that or I had to go
[ __ ] walk into a calf. I was
starving. See, that's the thing. You
know, when you eat once, yeah, like say
you have a roast dinner and that's
enough for the day. It's when you wake
up, that's when you start getting hungry
again. And I woke up at like 1:00 cuz I
was stressing about the money from the
casino. I didn't know if they were going
to pay me or not. So,
I didn't really want to be losing 500 [ __ ] pound. I'm saying Do
I not summon one? Virgin
skin with absolutely no money in it or
no pain in it. Ah,
skin virgin butt. [ __ ] sake. Wherever
the bad [ __ ] no money in One sec.
What a sec.
Why would stay in get exhausting? Saving
money and not having to hear about I've
got a boyfriend.
No, it's actually good, man.
Trying gets exhausting, though. going
out dealing with the same [ __ ]
No, I'm just going by myself.
No, bro. I'm out all the time.
I'm out all the [ __ ] time
just cuz I'm not out drinking. Oh, [ __ ]
I'm [ __ ] tired, man.
Oh, I'm so tired.
All that food in it.
Wouldn't surprise me. Most of the people
in here are fat and ugly.
Fat, ugly, skinned people. They ain't
got a life.
That's why they're sat on here all day, every day.
cuz they go no live on YouTube. Oh. Oh [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm good. I'll be back later.