What happens Saturday?
It will be the same as all the other
[ __ ] other thousands of [ __ ] Saturdays.
The same. [ __ ] idiot. Um, yep. never change.
[ __ ] madness, bro.
How do these people seem to think one
day it's going to change? They're
[ __ ] They're absolutely [ __ ] in
their head, mate. Honestly,
it will never change. Yeah. Mhm.
Almost finished [ __ ] ice cream. Yeah.
It will never change.
This guy was like, "Um, I'm good, man."
This guy was like, "Uh,
see what happens on Saturday." I mean,
yeah, but it's not going to change. It's
going to be the same as all the other
million Saturdays I've gone out. Nothing.
What? It will never change.
It will never ever change.
Cuz here's the thing, Cory. Yeah.
They're saying that it's going to
change, but they're dismissing all of
the five years where it's not changed.
They're dismissing all of the times I've got out. Yeah, man.
>> They seem to dismiss your um experiences. >> Yeah. Yeah,
>> bro. I don't care. I don't know why
you're telling me. I don't give a [ __ ]
And respectfully, you don't bring it on
my channel. I literally don't care. I'm
never going on that channel ever again.
I'm not going on no Red Star channel. I
don't give a [ __ ] about jealous obsessed disabled people.
So, I don't know why you're telling me I
can't give a [ __ ]
I don't give a [ __ ] man.
What do you want me to do? Do a video
back or you want me to argue back with
them or what? I I don't get it. What do
you want me to do, bro?
I I said I'm going to leave them to make
a fool of themselves
to show that they're the ones that are jealous, obsessed,
um ain't got no life. I said I was going
to leave them to it and I have. So
that's it, bro. Let them show themselves
to be the jazz ones. So yeah. Yes. Boy,
I come funny. Nope.
I haven't been out today to be honest. I
just been chilling in bed, keeping warm. Ah, yeah, man.
And I'm not your mate either.
So yeah, just been in bed calls keeping warm.
Na na na na.
Are we out Saturday again getting rejected? Bob,
are we out being rejected on Saturday again? Can't wait.
Can't wait, matey.
It's going to be lush. Uh-huh. Sorry, man. Yeah. Right, I'm gone. Peace.