No, no, no, no, no. Think
I'm going to go out tomorrow and send
it. To be fair, I said I was going to go
out Saturday, but I think I'll just go out tomorrow. Yeah.
Yeah. Might as well.
whilst the [ __ ] hair was still fresh in it
and then that'll be up for 3 weeks. So yeah,
I haven't been out on a Thursday in ages.
How Joe says the past don't dictate the future
[ __ ] beyond me.
It's been dictating it for years so far. area. [ __ ] Yeah. Any
luck in the casino? Well, I don't go to
the casino, so no.
I swear some of you people have brain
damage. Swear to God, some of you people
really have got brain damage.
Why would I go to a casino?
What the [ __ ] bro?
Do you even think before you [ __ ] speak?
The [ __ ] going on in a [ __ ] casino.
What a mad bastard. Yeah,
I won £500 on roulette the other day
online, but I don't go to casinos. What the [ __ ]
So why you asking that? Yeah,
I'll be out drinking tomorrow. So,
do some approaches.
before I give up for good. Yeah. Yo,
I'm going to go out drinking tomorrow, man.
Do some approaches and that'll be it
until my birthday. I was going to do
Saturday, but I might as well just [ __ ]
do it tomorrow.
No, but I know that Ed Matthews is. He's a [ __ ]
I don't watch him, but I know who he is. Me, man. Yep.
Yeah. F. Yeah.
Yeah. I know.
I'm going to be doing some cold approaches tomorrow.
Sober, then get on a drink. Uh,
no. I've never had luck on it. What do
you think's going to happen tomorrow, Cory?
It's going to be [ __ ] like always, isn't it? Of
course it will
maybe get like four numbers or something. Yeah,
I will never have a girlfriend. So
there's no point speaking hypothetically
because it's never going to happen. So
there's no point speaking hypothetically, bro.
There's no point answering a hypothetical question.
Doesn't make a lot of sense, does it?
You know, I shouldn't really even be
going out tomorrow.
Well, I mean, 5 years, it's been the
same [ __ ] for 5 years. It's only getting
worse. So, I mean,
I'd say never
cuz if it was going to happen, it would
have happened by now. That's what I
always say. I don't I don't dis The
thing is I don't dismiss anything I do.
You're on YouTube again.
What? You're on YouTube again? You're on
my live. So you're on YouTube again,
bro. That's an oxymoron, bro. You can't
come on someone's live stream
saying, "Oh, they're live again." whilst
you are also on YouTube. That's an oxymoron.
I mean, I shouldn't even be doing these
approaches or drinking tomorrow to be fair, but
I've got nothing better to do. So, but
this will be it now for until the 27th.
I won't be [ __ ] with it anymore, bro.
Yeah. And you're addicted to YouTube.
You self projector. I'll get you gone.
Hope you YouTube addiction. But yeah,
like I said, Cory, I don't dismiss what
I've been through. I don't dismiss my struggles. So
you you do
you know you do
you can definitely say never in this
country you can 100% say never
cuz you seem to forget the past I don't
you know so no it is definitely never
never 100% not in this country no way.
No [ __ ] way,
cuz it would have happened already.
100%. It would have happened already. It
would have happened on [ __ ] Friday.
I mean I mean
look at what's it look at what's
happened in the past 5 years. Why why
why didn't anything happen in them years
them five years? Cuz you're saying that
I'm crazy predicting the next 50 years,
but look at the the the five the the the
five years. Look at the five years so
far. It's been the same old boring and
it will always be the same old boring. I
don't need to blow smoke up my ass, lad.
Like I Well, I can tell you're not going
to win the lottery. Like, I'm not being
negative. I'm being real, bro. Like, I'm
going out tomorrow. I'm going to send it
because only one of the numbers replied
and I've got nothing better to do. But I
know deep down I'm not going to get
anywhere. But I'd rather [ __ ] do it than [ __ ]
sit at home. I know it's you're never
going to find anyone in this country,
you know, especially London because it
would have happened by now. It's so
obvious it would have happened by now.
So I mean, you can go by the past and
what's happened in the past 5 years and
it's been the same old.
So that's it.
It will never change with these women
ever. I know that for a fact.
So, and let's not talk about how
expensive it is as well.
Going out is so expensive.
That's another thing, Mike. It's so
expensive. like going out drinking
[ __ ] £500 every time you [ __ ] go
out on the [ __ ] weekend. So yeah,
I don't want to go out tomorrow. I don't
want to try tomorrow, but I'm going to
have to cuz I don't want to stay in. So
like I said, that's it until my birthday. So
yeah, it's ridiculous, bro. I won.
Luckily, I won that money under Rouette, ain't it? [Music]
Luckily, I won that money on the roulette. Eh,
but I don't want to waste it. You see, I
don't want to waste it by going out
again, even though I can. So, I'm going
to try and spend
50, 60, 70 when I go out tomorrow. No
more. I don't want to be wasting money anymore, bro. Yep.
They were really nice. I had another one today.
Uh, no he didn't.
Why is it so [ __ ] hard in this
country? like [ __ ] 10 numbers on
Friday. Only one replied. I said to him,
"Let's go out on Saturday." And then
[ __ ] they um they didn't want to go out.
Why is it so hard in this country, bro? [ __ ] man.
cuz you know Joe F says the same thing.
He says that your past don't dictate the
future but it has been predict
predicting it cuz every single time you
go out it is exactly the same [ __ ]
It is always the same [ __ ] every time
you go out. So, I mean, how does your
past not dictate the future? There's no
changes. It's the same old. Boring.
That's why when I don't have my haircut,
I won't go out for like 3 weeks cuz I
can't be asked because it's just the
same old [ __ ] every time.
But what makes me laugh, Mike, is that
these people, right,
seem to think that one day you're going
to meet someone. Like, it's [ __ ] They
actually generally think that one day
you're going to meet someone.
It's [ __ ] up, man.
When you're not, because you would have. So,
I look max on Friday. I got 10 numbers.
Not even a date. Not even a date this
week, Mike. Not even a date.
I mean, doesn't that say it all? You
know, 10 numbers, one reply, not one
single date that's gave you the chance.
Does that not tell you all you need to
know? Or am I missing something? Mhm. Hey baby. Yeah,
you have to go out again tomorrow and do
this [ __ ] again, bro. I can't believe
it. It's disgusting. I can't believe,
bro, I'm having to [ __ ] spend money
out my [ __ ] winnings to go out again
and do this [ __ ] when I shouldn't have
to be going out again.
I should not have to be going out again,
bro, and doing this,
you know, again. I only spent about5 600
pound over the [ __ ] weekend, bro. I
shouldn't have to be doing this [ __ ]
again, you know?
[ __ ] spent a lot of money, bro.
I don't know. We don't know yet. But we
can't even get a date. So, I mean,
can't even get a [ __ ] date. That is a madness.
Hopefully, tomorrow will be better.
Doubted though. Will never change. Yeah. Never.
It will never change here, matey.
No, matey. I've already lowered my standards.
Some of these women were fours, fives,
sixes, sevens. I mean, there's no tens
in London. There's no tens in this
country. There's no 10 out of 10 women
in this country. So, I don't know what
you mean by lower your standards. I
mean, most of them are average,
so slightly above average. I mean,
they're not [ __ ] models. So,
it is a madness, isn't it?
I kind of have to go out tomorrow, to be fair.
quarter my twice a month then I'm done.
Yeah. I won £500 on roulette from 100
which is just basically money back I spent.
It's really not worth going out in this
country anymore. It's not worth the
time, the effort, the money. It really isn't.
But I'll be out tomorrow and that'll be the last
that be the last time. So yeah,
but my people say you'll meet someone. Yeah. Right.
So we'll do it tomorrow and we'll move
on. I think because this is depressing,
bro. Even bringing up the subject is so depressing.
Like it's not even funny. It's so so depressing,
you know, trying to date in this
country. It really is. Nope.
No, no, I'm not saying you're laughing.
It's just depressing, bro.
Really is depressing, isn't it?
I don't want to spend more than 70 80 pound tomorrow
cuz if I'm spending 600 700 again mate I
won't be able to save any money
for my holiday. That's the thing you see. So
yeah, I want I don't want to be spending
more than £80.
I wear my hoodie tomorrow, wear my coat,
where my train is, bluff my hair up, and yeah,
shouldn't have to be doing this [ __ ] again.
I really, really should not have to be
doing this [ __ ] again, bro. should have
got a date out of them [ __ ] 10 numbers.
Yeah, but it's not about that, bro.
Like, I wasn't even expecting to [ __ ]
be in a relationship, but I'm expecting
to get a date out of them 10 numbers
that I got.
Do you not know how disgusting that is?
Like, think about it, bro. Most dates
don't lead to relationships. Most dates
are just like, you go on a date and
that's it. You can't even get a [ __ ]
date out of them 10 numbers. You got no hope.
Simple. There is literally no hope.
I'm doing it tomorrow for the sake of
it. I know there's no hope, but
something to pass time and I get to
exercise. There is no hope and there'll
never be no hope in this country. Never.
You I should be on a date this week. I
messaged the numbers again one more
time. They didn't reply.
Who are you talking about? Nons.
I just think that they think they're
better than they are and they think
they're too good for people that they're not.
That's what I think like Yeah.
And it's such a waste of money going out as well.
Such a waste of money going out.
But like I said, I won't spend much anyways. Yep.
You know, you get these people on Reddit
that say women only want sex.
You can't even get laid.
You can't even get a relationship. You
can't even get laid. You can't get
anything from a woman. They They talk so
much [ __ ] on that Reddit.
Uh nothing. I'm going out tomorrow drinking.
But I need to be careful what I'm
spending as well because at the same
time I am trying to save money.
Just cuz I want money doesn't mean I
want to waste the money, you know?
I don't want to [ __ ] waste money just
cuz I want it, you know? I'd rather save
it and leave. Yeah.
Why did I put the bun in the microwave?
Um, I don't know. Uh, maybe to heat it
up, Captain Obvious. Maybe to melt the cheese.
I mean, may maybe that's why, huh? Who knows?
But the thing is, Mike, they seem to
think it's easy getting laid. They seem
to think that you can just go out and
get laid. It's a madness.
They generally seem to think that you
you can go out and get laid
and not get a relationship. It's [ __ ]
mental, bro. My body count is only about five
at 28. I'm 28 this month. My body count
is five without escorts.
And I've and I've approached about 10,000 women.
It's disgusting, bro.
It is [ __ ]
[ __ ] disgusting, bro.
Going to send it hard tomorrow and then,
like I said, that's me done
until my birthday. So,
what a life, eh? What a [ __ ] life.
I'm going to boil some eggs in a minute.
I don't think you realize how much [ __ ]
I put up with Mike with these women. I
don't think you realize how much [ __ ] I
put up with them.
Like, you don't even know the half of it.
So, we'll try tomorrow. We'll try to get
away with spending
the least possible
and then that's it. Simple.
Hopefully I'll be able to save £800 this month.
it would have been a thousand, but
obviously I'm going to go out and do
some more approaches and [ __ ] So, yeah,
still a good amount of money to go over 800.
Last month was five, this month's eight.
So, yeah, man.
Oh, what a life. Eh,
I should have a date this week.
I should have a [ __ ] date this week,
mate. But I don't.
I want to try and get as many numbers as
I possibly can tomorrow.
I don't know if I can get 10, but we'll see.
Yeah, there's just something about
Thursdays, you know? I swapped Saturday
for Thursday. I'll just go out tomorrow.
Then I can say, [ __ ] I tried.
So, well, I tried [ __ ] Friday to be
fair. Maybe next week I'll go out Wednesday.
just, you know, switch the days up a
little bit. No,
could try Wednesday next week. No, I
want to save myself on my birthday, but
naturally got to detox. I'd rather just
save myself for my birthday after tomorrow.
Yeah, I could be like that skinned
virgin in the bed [ __ ] with no bend, no
money in it. Um, you you're quite right.
You're quite right, mate. Yep.
I can't believe I have to go try it
again tomorrow. I can't believe it, bro.
generally can't [ __ ] believe it.
It's a madness,
but I like I say I can't afford it. I
can't afford it, but I like to have
loads of money in my account. And if I
went out that day, that day, that day,
and I was spending, I'm not going to
have a lot of money in my account. So,
I'd rather have more money in my account
than waste on [ __ ] going out drinking and [ __ ]
So, I'm going to go out tomorrow and I'm
going to spend £50 max.
So, I want to start building up my money,
traveling more in the [ __ ] And
obviously, if I go out, it's going to
stop that. I can go out. I can afford to
go out, but it's I'd rather just have
more money than go out to be fair.
But tomorrow, yeah, we'll do tomorrow. [ __ ] it.
And then that is me dumb.
See, I got a date. I wouldn't mind
spending money on a date. £100, whatever.
You know, it's not a problem once you
have a date, bro. But yeah, it's okay,
bro. We got time to waste. We just don't
have loads of money to waste. So,
wasted time is fine, bro.
They don't always ignore me.
Last Friday was [ __ ]
that was a uh exception, bro. Like they
don't always ignore me at all. What they
normally do is they lead you on and then
drop you. That's normally what they do.
They don't normally ignore.
But go out, spend £50 tomorrow, whatever.
But I had my hair I have my hair done.
So let's just call it tomorrow and then
move on. Think of my birthday, you know? So
they don't ignore most of the time. They
did. I don't know what the [ __ ] what
they were doing. 10 numbers didn't
[ __ ] reply back. But no, they
normally reply. All the ones in
Birmingham replied. What they do is they reply
and reply and then they lead you on and
then when you suggest meeting them, then
you never hear from them again.
Just like that one in Finland, eh?
But yeah, we got time to waste tomorrow,
bro. It doesn't cost me any money to
travel. I want to make use of this
haircut, bro. It's [ __ ] spilly. So,
yeah, it doesn't matter, bro.
They leave you on like saying, "Oh,
where are you thinking?" No, no, no, no,
no, no. And then all of a sudden, oh, I
found someone. Or, "Oh, I'm not
interested in dating." Even though they
gave you their number. Just But they
don't normally ignore. I don't know how
I got 10 numbers and only one replied.
Normally they don't do that. Normally
they do reply. Um
but it it can happen you know. So it's
just one of them.
Tomorrow if I got get a few I will get a
few numbers. I'm sure they will reply at
least half of them
and then yeah we'll call it tomorrow
that we might even be able to get away
with spending you know £40.
Don't forget I want some money. But just
cuz I want some money, I don't want to
waste the money that I want. So,
but on my birthday, I'll spend money. It
doesn't matter. I'll spend [ __ ] over
£300 on my birthday. I don't I don't
mind, bro. But that's a special
occasion, you know. Yeah.
Yeah. I got time to waste, bro. I got
nothing better to do tomorrow. So, it's
just loads of money we don't want to be wasting. You know,
every single time you go out, bro, you
get your hair done, you go out drinking,
you go out eating, hundreds just goes
from your bank account every [ __ ] time.
That's what makes it even worse as well.
The effort, the [ __ ] the money. Oh my
god, bro. [ __ ] you know.
So, they usually just play games with
you or lead you on.
That's what they usually do.
And it's expensive, bro, as well.
God felt sorry for me. So, it's like,
you know what? We'll give you we'll let
you win £500, you know.
Every time you try to do them sessions,
bro, they kill you every time.
Anything you're trying to save up for,
it's [ __ ] annoying.
But like I said, I got a hair done, got
some fresh clothes, got my dry cleaning
done, so I'm not going to be spending
more than £50 tomorrow.
cuz I save 800 this month, I'm happy,
bro. But like I said, if I get a date or
someone's actually serious, then I don't
mind spending money. If someone wants to be serious,
you know, and actually then it's not a
problem. But I can't be wasting [ __ ]
money going out for no reason to get
nothing, you know?
Think about that, bro. Whe someone's
working, someone's on benefits.
Like I said,
it was over£400 I spent on that weekend.
It wasn't [ __ ]
200 pound. 200 pound you can justify.
Oh, you didn't go out two, three weeks,
you spent £200. Easy. Yeah, we're not
[ __ ] fours and fives, bro.
No, we season it ourselves. Yeah.
Yeah, we season it ourselves.
I get £800 in a couple of days as well.
Should be close to 2K again.
Oh, that that win on the roulette was
nice, man. Oh,
yeah. Just like when I tried to go out
that [ __ ] um
that Sunday. [ __ ] hell. It's expensive, bro. So expensive.
I don't mind if you [ __ ] got a
girlfriend out there. You [ __ ] got
something out of it. You know what I mean?
>> What are you doing?
I want to have a holiday as well.
I know that actually
>> then I'm not going to be able to [ __ ] do it.
>> That's what these [ __ ] [ __ ] are
trying to get me to do, bro. They're
trying to they're trying to get them to
be [ __ ] skinned like the virgin.
They're trying to make me skinned in the
bedit with no bed and no money in it.
That's what these cops are trying to
[ __ ] do. I'm not stupid, man. I know
you know your games. You're trying to
get me skin like the virgin
with no money in the bed. That's what
you're trying to [ __ ] do, mate. You
I know your games
the pillar got a long day tomorrow.
I should get £100 for my birthday hopefully. Yeah,
take a break for my birthday. What a
weekend before my birthday. [Music]
Wish me luck for tomorrow.
I'm going to [ __ ] need it.
Just boiling some eggs now.
I think that USA easy thing was once in
a lifetime. You know, some things in life, right?
They're they're once in a lifetime.
So like when I approach you and say, "Is
he like do you want my number?" That was
one in a lifetime.
Stop letting the house was once in a
lifetime. There's certain things that
are only I mean in that way for that
period of time is once in a lifetime. Do you understand? Yeah.
Skin in a bed with no [ __ ] bed. No
money in it.
Get in the B sh no money in it.
They keep asking me to show them [ __ ] money, bro.
They're self-reflectors. I'm not showing
them no [ __ ] money.
Uh, I can't remember.
Don't think it was the same as mine.
I like mine. Medium. Well done. So, yeah.
Well, I'm just saying that was a one in
a lifetime, though.
cuz you could go out for two years and
not get laid. But I remember I remember
this specifically, bro. Before I went to
Manchester the second time, I was trying
in London for ages.
Like [ __ ] ages, bro.
Um over a year, maybe two years, bro.
And I didn't get a fuckle. Used to get
numbers. So you can go years without even sex, you know. So yeah,
then I went to Manchester combat and Yeah.
Yeah. I'm going to try to get some [ __ ] tomorrow.
I already went out, had fun drinking.
Now I actually want to try and get someone. So yeah,
boy. Get in a bed with absolutely no bed
and absolutely no money in it. Oh,
how many numbers are we predicting tomorrow?
Five will recover nicely. Yeah.
I've got time to waste tomorrow, bro.
It's not a problem.
The only bad thing about this, right, is
that knowing it's going to be the same
and you trying is going to make you
depressed is going to make you more
depressed because obviously it's you're
going to be getting rejected all day.
Um, which is what's going to happen. So,
but I can stomach it. You know, I'm a
big boy. So, I can stomach it, bro.
I'm a big boy, buddy.
I can stomach it one more time, you know?
So, it does suck. You can't even get laid.
I don't know where these people on
Reddit, they pretend that you can just
go on dating apps and get laid. They
must be capping, bro. Because it does
not work like that in real life. No.
Oh, do you think Steven Howard
I should go out approaching every day?
Build some money up. Go out approaching
every single day. Oh, obviously I
wouldn't be drinking. I would just be
approaching every day. I mean,
you wouldn't be able to do it. I could
do it. I've done it before. But
I don't know, bro.
So much time and so much money spent
just to get something so normal.
Remember that time I went out all day?
Oh, I ended up in [ __ ] Maiden Head.
Do you remember that time,
bro? I ended up in [ __ ] Maiden Head
on the whole of West London. Oh, it was
a madness, bro. It was a [ __ ] madness.
You know, I was thinking of going out in Maiden Head,
you know, drinking in Maiden Head.
But yeah, remember that time I ended up
all the way there?
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Ended up all the way in Maiden Head,
man. Come all the way back.
Yeah, I've definitely tried more than
everyone in the world. Definitely.
So what is Ant-Man right then, Steven
Howard, that they're just not interested
in this country?
So what is he right when he says that?
Yeah, that's where a lot of them are.
So what is he right when he says that
they're not interested in this country?
Yeah, he is right going from my experience.
No, but is he he's right about they're
not interested in this country though,
isn't he? He's right about that, right? Yeah.
Yeah, he is right about that though.
You know what? Um,
this whole Monty man thing taught me.
Yeah, it taught me to like never go out
your way for anyone ever again. Look
what I done with Monty. I went all the
way to Birmingham, spent money just for
him to snake me in the end over some slag.
[ __ ] that, bro.
Absolutely. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] madness, isn't it?
They're not interested in me and they're
not interested in 90% of other men such
as yourself as well. Sorry, I should
have said that. Yeah. They're not
interested in me. They're not interested
in you. They're not interested in 90% of men.
Yeah. me and 90% including yourself.
Sorry, I should have rephrased that.
So, yeah, it's definitely you as well
and 90% of men defo
cuz think of it, I'm probably better
looking than you. I'm probably more
confident than you. I probably got more
chat than you. So if they're not
interested in me along with 90% of other
men, why would they be interested in you?
I mean, it is the West. I mean, it's
been proven a million times how women
have options and women are stuck up
because of social media. I mean, it's been proven.
It's not about blaming. It's a fact.
It's been proven.
It's been proven that whenever somebody
goes to Asia, they don't have any of
these problems. Sounds like a
westernized problem to me. where as soon
as you go to Asia, you get none of these
problems. No, it's definitely the
westernized women. Definitely,
definitely definitely definitely 100% it
is the women in this country because
isn't it funny how so many other people
struggle that are not I'm not explaining
myself. Anyways, I'm Why are you even
talking about this? I know what I know.
I'm not going to argue. So, anyways, I'm
not going to go back and forth. I know
what I know and I know what I'm doing.
So, you have your opinion. I have my
facts, bro. Why am I not arguing about
this? What the [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm not arguing with some [ __ ]
idiot behind an account that can't even
join a hangout. Waste of my time. Proper
waste of my time. You're never going to
get through to these simps. So,
see, the thing is with people, right,
like this guy here, they don't approach
women. They don't deal with women, you
know? They just sit online. Who the [ __ ]
is that? They just sit online
licking their asses thinking that women
will like them. That's They don't know
about life. They don't know about real
life. So, it's pointless trying to [ __ ]
explain it to simps.
You know what I'm saying? It doesn't
matter whether they're po or they're
[ __ ] not [ __ ] po. It's the fact
that when you go to [ __ ] Asia, you
don't have any of these [ __ ] problems. Simple. So yeah,
these simps, I'm not going to argue with
you anyways. You're never going to get
through to a simp. So I'm not even going
to waste my time trying to convince you
anything. I know I know you think you
know, you know, waste of my time.
Complete waste of my time.
I mean, I've proven it with approaching
videos how stuck up they are. Even when
they've given their number, but yet
you'll still defend them. That's on you,
bro. That's not me, bro. That's You do
what you want to do.
I mean, you do what you want to do. You
defend them. You do what you want. I
don't I'm not bothered. It's not my problem.
I know what they're like. I've dealt
with more women than you probably have
ever and ever will. So, I mean, yeah. So, yeah, that's it.
It to be honest with you, it would be
nice to be like a woman
having all of these simps stick up for
them. I mean, it must be nice being a
woman to be honest. You get simps like
Jay stick up for them. It wouldn't be
half bad being a woman thinking of it.
And these simps, women don't like them,
but then they still defend them. It's
crazy. Like this J, this Jay guy right
here probably has had less women than me
and he still defends them. It's a
madness. Defended women for the sake of
defending women. It makes you look like a loser.
It's pathetic. It really, really is.
The [ __ ] troop hurts.
They defend women, bro. You're not
speaking facts. I put my approaching
videos up there. I put my combos out
there. Do you know what I'm saying? So
you're not speaking facts at all at all
at all. You're not speaking no facts. I
have got approaching videos on my
channel. You are not speaking not 1%
facts. I have proven facts a million
times with combos, approaches. It is
westernized women. It is the women in
this country 100%. So yeah,
and that's it. Simple.
Yeah, I'll be out tomorrow anyways, Bob. You know,
we're not stating the facts at all.
You're not stating the facts at all. Yeah.
I mean, it is the women in this country
that stuck up and entitled and they've
got loads of options.
It's obvious. It's been proven a million times.
Yeah. Okay. Whatever, S. Whatever you
say, S. I'm not going to argue with you.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Whatever you
say, S. I'm not arguing with you
anyways. Waste of my time.
Waste of my time, bro. It's never going
to get you laid. Stop defending the
women. It's never going to make you lose
your virginity. Don't make the same
[ __ ] mistakes of these other guys,
you know? Trust me, you're never going
to get laid. Women don't like you. You
defending women is not going to make
them like you. It's embarrassing, lad.
It's It really is embarrassing.
Defending women is embarrassing. I'm
going out tomorrow approaching. It'll be
my It will be my last time until my birthday.
So, and that's me done, bro.
Until my birthday
cuz I got nothing better to do. Yeah.
Yeah, just like you're going to be
single and you're going to be a virgin
forever. Bit like your life only you're a virgin,
but the difference is you're still a
virgin. I'm not. And you think by
defending women it's going to get you
laid. That's the most [ __ ] up thing. Yeah.
I mean, you're already single and you're
a virgin. Self rejected.
That's what I'm saying. I mean, you're
single right now.
You've never had a girlfriend. You've
never had sex. I have had sex and you're
single and you ti is not going to change
that. Women don't like you. Defending
women is never going to get you laid. I
know you don't like facts, bro. But it's
like you get all of these white dice
like women don't like them. They get no
women, right, bro? I mean, no. It's
these women that are the problem. They
are stuck up. They are entitled. They've
got options. It is the West. I'm telling
you that is the West. And I'm not
arguing with you. You're not talking
facts. You're being a sin. It is obvious
that it is the West because how many
guys struggle? How many guys struggle to
get into relationships? And whenever
somebody approaches a woman, they have
the same thing. I'm telling you facts
that if it was me and not the West, then
all of these other guys wouldn't
struggle. But they do. So, it can't be
right what you're saying. I don't blame
them being in sales. They're normal guys
on Instagram, normal guys I've met. If
it was other people that was the
problem, so many people would struggle.
It's simple. You are a s. It's never
going to get you laid. Stop defending
women. It's embarrassing.
You never even spoke to a woman, bro.
You're probably living in your [ __ ]
mom's basement defending women. You're
like them people on Reddit. It's [ __ ] embarrassing.
Yeah, bro. For real. Like, the thing is,
yeah, you if I saw, like, listen, let me
be real with you. Yeah. If I saw no
other guy struggle and I saw approaches
where people weren't struggling, then
I'd be like, "Okay, there's a problem
with me here." But isn't it so mad how
so many guys have the same problem when
they when they speak to women? The same
boyfriend [ __ ] the same attitude, the
same [ __ ] Isn't it so funny how all
of these men just happen to struggle?
They've got no correlation with each
other. They've got no links to each
But they all seem to get the same [ __ ]
It's definitely westernized women. It's
definitely definitely westernized women, mate. But yeah,
but yeah, you keep defending women, bro.
Let's come back to me in 5 years and see
how how that's got.
It's like as soon as you state facts
right, you get these little simps in
their corner defending them.
But me personally, bro, I think they're
[ __ ] I think they're absolute
[ __ ] It's the way that I look. Oh,
it's the way that I look now. Oh, that's nice, bro.
I mean, I'm a million times better
looking than you will ever be. But sound
like another self-reflector. Self-reflector.
Self-reflector. Ugly bastard.
Bro, you're still a virgin. You're
single yourself. Look at the way you
look before coming on preaching to [ __ ] others. God,
not everyone's ugly like you, bro.
Not everyone's got the same life as you.
Anyways, I'm going to now anyways. Self projection.
I mean, what do you think the problem is, Bob?
You're allowed to agree with me. You're
allowed to disagree with me. I mean, I
put roaches up there,
but they haven't even given me the
chance. I mean, I don't know what more
I'm supposed to do, lad.
I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
What more am I supposed to do, mate? You know,
I don't know what more you're supposed
to do, Bob. H
I just boiled some eggs, man.
Don't know why this guy's defending
women. It's embarrassing to be fair. Yeah,
I can't believe I've got to go out
approach him tomorrow, Bob.
The thing is, yeah, Bob. Yeah,
I should have a date this week.
The mount I tried. Yeah,
last week. I should have a date this
Can't believe we got a date. [ __ ] today.
So [ __ ] up, man.
No, I'm sec
work. I've tried apps. They don't work.
I've tried dating apps, lad.
I've tried loads of dating apps. They don't work for me.
No, I've tried that inad like I said.
Oh, that's so nice of you though.
That's so nice of you to find me. Thank you, man.
You know what's so mad, Bob, is how you
can be decent looking. Yeah, you can be
confident. You can have the balls, but
you still can't you can't even get laid.
How mad is that, bro?
You don't think that's mad? [ __ ]
just brush my teeth.
>> I've never [ __ ] I haven't met
somebody on dating app for years.
This guy is trying to say the way that I look. Oh man,
better looking than you.
Maybe not now, but yeah.
I need to down this goggle it and Yeah, man.
Do you like my hair better like this?
Do you like my hair like this or
you like it more styled?
What do you prefer, man?
No, no, no, no.
I think it's for like this [ __ ]
It used to be washed.
got some um in my gum. So Mhm.
I sure have.
I sure have tried no beard.
I tried that back two years ago.
Uh in a suit. A suit. No beard.
Yeah, suit. No beard. Um
no, I need to be fair.
Uh yeah, I have
tried no beard actually a couple of
times. Once when I was wearing a suit,
never made a difference. Not interested. And um yeah. Mhm.
I don't know what I should wear to
wear my stony my red. I'm not sure.
My hoodie my No, I'm not wearing my tattoos. Um,
I don't know.
Oh, you actually think I'm good looking, Bob?
Oh, you actually think I'm good looking?
I I think that's what makes it worse,
you know, when like you're decent
looking and you score get nothing
and you actually put the effort on.
You get nervous.
I don't get nervous. Me, I can do him but sober.
I can do him sober.
I can do him drunk. I've been doing this
for years, mate. It doesn't bother me.
You know, when I went out and got them
10 numbers last Friday, that was my
first time out in a month. And do you
know how many I sober? I was scared. The
first one I done, I was a bit nervous.
During the first one, I was a bit
nervous, but then after that, I just smashed it.
I was so I messaged and no response was.
What do you mean you messaged? You must
have got her number there. No.
Can you get a number?
You must have got
It's funny you should say tens because I
I don't see tens.
I don't see t me.
I can't believe you find me
good-looking, Bob. You actually find me
good-looking. What do you find
good-looking about me? Huh? Really,
the thing is, right, I've always done
better by myself. So what
you think my face is good looking, bro?
You know what's going to be so [ __ ] up
tomorrow? Yeah. I'm going to look rough.
I'm not going to do my hair. I'm not
going to dress as good. And I guarantee
you I get more success tomorrow than I
did on Friday. quite I mean maybe number
four by that that's about it saying yeah
do you think my face is good looking Bob seriously.
So why do I keep getting rejected then
Bob if I'm good-look? Oh [ __ ]
So why do I keep
getting rejected then if I'm good-looking Bob? Oh man,
somebody said maybe there's too many
stuck up [ __ ] in your country and
that's what the problem is.
That's what they said to me. Maybe too
many stuck up [ __ ] in your country.
That's what someone on Reddit said.
Why don't you tell us what you think?
Salty water is kills.
Oh [ __ ] man.
But what about the other guys? Other
guys do it. Watch out for the other guys.
I'm saying, Bob, that's what you need to
do. You need to watch out for the other
guys. Oh god. Funny, bro.
Can't believe I'm doing this [ __ ] again tomorrow, brother.
I I do I have tried that. Oh man.
Going to take some pain for this man.
Put a gun in it. I have tried that.
They just say interested in this country.
Simple as that, Bob. They're not
interested in this country. Simple as that. Yep.
I've worn a shirt. I've worn a blazer.
Yeah, man. I'll show you a picture of me
in a shirt. Actually, I used to rock him
all the time.
I used to wear shirts all the time.
I'm not interested in this country.
Yeah, man. I used to always rock this.
I got some shirts in my um
I've got some shirts in my um
in my um wardrobe.
I've got a pink one, got a green one, I
got a C client one.
Got an All Saints one. Yeah,
some uh nice stuff in my wardrobe, man.
I always used to rock it.
They just aren't interested in this country.
Antman was right.
Ant-Man was right. They're just not
interested in this country. Simple as that.
Changing the pillow in now.
Yeah. What do you think, Bob? [ __ ] E,
the thing is [ __ ] up. They're just not interested.
Wish me luck for tomorrow, bro. It's
going to be a depressing one.
It's going to be a depressing one. Oh,
it's going to be so depressing, bro.
Can you hold my hand? You and I have a boyfriend. Oh, yeah, bro.
at least wash my bed in tomorrow
if I'm going out. Yeah,
it's not going to be funny. It's going
to be depressing.
Yeah, I'm going to be out all day
tomorrow doing it all [ __ ] day, bro.
It's going to be the same old, isn't it?
I have a boyfriend. I'm not interested.
It's not funny. It's depressing.
Yeah. So, I've tried loads of different hairstyles approaches.
They're just not interested in this country.
This is what I was wear when I met USA. Is he? Yeah.
So, Bob, is is is Ant-Man right? How
they're just not interested in this country then?
Is he right by saying that?
I think so.
I think he is right. Yeah.
What do you think?
I think he's right, bro. Yeah.
Five number is no reply.
We'll see, won't we, man? What's it One sec.
So, when am I going to find someone
then, Stephen Howard?
When am I going to find someone?
Maybe next year or what do you think?
Ah, I can't believe I'm trying again.
[ __ ] hell. I should have got a date
out of them [ __ ]
out of them [ __ ] um 10 numbers.
Nah, you're lying. You're just being
negative. Reddit tells me that I'll meet somebody eventually.
Nah, you're you're just being negative.
He's just being negative. Steven was
Of course, I'll meet someone, bro. Don't
be silly. Why would you think that I
wouldn't meet someone?
Why would you come out with that idea?
He's just being negative. Hey, Steven's
being negative, everyone. He's being
negative. Nancy, what would possibly
give you the idea
that I would I'm not going to meet anyone?
What's What's Why would you even say
that? You're just being negative.
Nah, you're just being negative, mate. Honestly, [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, you need to make a new email.
I'm on Reddit right now. Reddit is addicting, bro.
So, what would make you think that I'm
not going to meet someone anyway, Steven Howard?
People say that I'm going to meet
someone one day. So, but you're saying I'm not.
I was so confident last Friday. We'll
see how I am uh tomorrow.
We're not spending more than 50 60 pound. Yeah, that's that.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's not worth it. No, but I've got
nothing better to do tomorrow, so
yeah, it's not worth it at all.
But I'm not going to sit in all day tomorrow.
Want to try and find a candidate for baby Peter.
And if I still can't, then yeah, we [ __ ]
You think I'm Skint? Steven Howard.
Don't know why these people in here call
me Skint. I'm not Skint.
Because they're skin. They call you
skint cuz they're skint.
Yeah. So obvious.
They call you skint cuz they're skint.
Is that right? Steven Howard.
I have money but not loads and loads of money.
Like before, mate,
any money I win, I just like keep it
to a side, you know, and be careful with
it cuz I don't get as much money
anymore. But as money, you know,
like that £500, as soon as I won that
£500, bro, I was like, "Yeah, I'm
keeping it, bro. [ __ ] that. I'm not
spending it. I'm not wasting it. Put
that toward another holiday."
But tomorrow is just going to be basically
a continuation from last [ __ ] Friday.
Yeah, bro. I'm thinking, how have I got
so much money for someone that's on like benefits?
Got like 2K and I don't get that much in
benefits and it's from like the football
and the [ __ ] roulette and [ __ ] So,
don't forget I won that 380 when I went
out that Sunday. Probably about H 11:12.
Yeah, I'll probably stay out late
tomorrow. I'll be wearing my trainers.
I'll be out at like 2:00 p.m. 1:00 p.m.
2 p.m. I'll bring my charger with me as
well cuz I'm going to send it hard, bro.
Cuz then I'm done until the 27th. So, cuz Yeah.
Yeah, that's how I've I have money
because of um the football and that and
it we won. We done good on the football,
didn't we? I'm probably actually about
£1,000 up to be honest cuz we did. Like
I said, we won on the football.
These are all my footballs. The first
football £80 to 281. Second one 80 to 230
one. Then the other one I think was £100
lost. Then I think I lost another 80.
Then I put 20 pound the other day. I won
50. Then I put 120. Won 380. Then
obviously 500 on the roulette. So that's
Yeah, that's that's over a thousand.
They don't show me signals. They're not interested.
Yeah, that's the thing. They don't show
signals cuz they're not interested in
this country. But we got nothing better
to do tomorrow. For the sake of 50
[ __ ] pound, it's worth it, you know.
So yeah, the football like when I went
out that Sunday last month, if I didn't
win that football bet, I'd have about
200 pound left. Lucky I won the football bet
and it returned 380 cuz I would have been pretty um pretty fat.
Put it that way. I'd be pretty fat.
See, I'd go out tomorrow in my tracksuit
approaching. But the thing is
I would do it in my tracksuit, but then
it's it's getting in places.
Like I might want to get into a place
and they don't but then I could always
bring my bag with me, but I've only got
a yellow bag. H
just wear the [ __ ] tracksuit in it. [ __ ] it.
Most my hair a bit. Most my hair a bit.
Yeah, [ __ ] it. I would
give it a whirl,
but then it's [ __ ] trying to get in
somewhere with the [ __ ] tracks,
which is going to be the problem.
I don't really want to be carrying a
yellow bag. Do I have another bag?
I'll just go out in the tracksuit. I
don't give a [ __ ] bro.
With a bear t-shirt. I don't give a
[ __ ] Good enough, man.
What do you think? I've got a few things
to wear, Bob. I can wear the tracks do.
I can wear the Stone Island. I could
wear the Ralph Lauren 200lb top. Uh,
I don't know.
I feel like the track we were rocking it, bro.
H. But then, like I said, it's trying to
get in somewhere.
You can get into pubs and [ __ ]
What do you think?
really. Well, it's not negativity, it's
reality. To answer your question,
um, it's not negative. I mean, I mean,
that's the part of why I'm leaving this
country because this country is
negative. It's a depressing country to live in.
It's a depressing country to be in.
I'm trying to think I should wear tomorrow.
I don't make it my reality. I went out
on Friday trying to meet new women to
get a date for this week and didn't
happen. So, I mean, I don't make it my
reality, do I? Really? So,
Um, do I have a bag?
No, I've got a food bag, but I don't
have a bag to put the jeans in.
I really want to rock that tracksuit, man. Um,
Can someone help me with what I should wear?
I don't have a bag.
Unless I figure I don't have a bag.
And I might want to I might have to wear
[ __ ] jeans to get in somewhere.
That's the thing. [ __ ] sake.
I'll show you a few things I could wear. Yeah.
I don't know, man. The tracksuit is
[ __ ] banging though, man.
Trust me, bro. It seems to pull [ __ ]
The tracks do.
I'll show you, bro.
Right. So, we got this tracksuit here.
I'll show you the things we can wear.
Got this tracky,
which to be honest with you, don't need
to watch it. It's clean.
So, we got this tracksuit,
which trust me, you might not think it
will get [ __ ] but it'll get [ __ ] bro.
You got that tracksuit, the black one.
It has to be the black one. Um, or
I've got so many clothes.
Or we could wear
this, which is £200, by the way.
This with Oh, I need to buy some new
Ammani jeans as well.
>> That's another thing. I can wear this with this.
I could wear this with this.
Oh, I could wear this with any of the Stony's
badges on there.
Nothing needs ironing, bro. They're all
fresh, dry cleananed.
I'm thinking this tracks suit me.
I'm thinking the tracky, bro. It doesn't
need ironing. It's fresh from the dry cleaners.
I don't know, man.
I'm thinking the track suit, you know, bro.
It's all iron, bro. It's fresh in the
dry cleaners. You silly goose. Look.
I ain't want it yet.
I think the tracks, dude, man.
But then again, it's getting in places.
That's a [ __ ] problem. I was thinking this
with a teddy bear t-shirt.
I don't know. That looks good. That
That does look good though, to be fair.
Which blue one? This one? This one? This
one? I don't know.
Nah, women like the [ __ ] look, bro. I
had my best success when I was wearing this tracksuit.
Not at all, bro. Not at all. I mean,
okay. So, what was the reason I didn't
get a date this week? Look at what I was
wearing uh last week. Look what I was
wearing last week.
Look what I was wearing last week, bro.
Turtleneck, blazer, nice hair, nice
face. Still got [ __ ]
Yeah, you might as well just wear this,
bro. Doesn't matter. You might as well
look scruffy. cuz it's not going to make
a difference. I I do better when I look
[ __ ] like [ __ ] Whenever I look like
[ __ ] I do better.
Yeah, man. I'm thinking this. You know this tracky.
What? The stony. Yeah, that looks good
though. See, if I had a bag, I could
wear this. approach on the street
wearing this and then change into
something like this when I go into like
a club or something.
I'm a [ __ ] crazy bastard.
But obviously I need to carry the bag
with me. That's the thing.
But then what was the excuse why I
didn't get anything on Friday then? Bob,
this is nice though. This is like £200,
bro. This is class.
I mean, I could just wear this and I
think I would wear this and that to be fair.
>> Yeah, man. I don't know.
I like this teddy bear t-shirt. Cost a
lot of money.
I'm not sure. I don't know.
Look, see, just rock it with a
tracksuit, man. Obviously, I wash my
hair and that, but I [ __ ] look sick.
I look good, man.
I actually got complimented on the
tracksuit before. People like it.
I don't know.
We'll have to figure out tomorrow.
I could get into places. I I would just
wear the tracksuit here. Uh
I got so many clothes.
Peter Belly used to have a lot of money.
No, it's a it's a top man. It's designer Ralph Lauren.
But I don't know, man. Oh, [ __ ]
You know, life could actually be worse
to be honest, man. I mean, I've got
money. I've got some nice clothes. I got
a nice bed. You know, some people have [ __ ] nothing.
I just want to meet someone now. I'm
getting older, you know. I just want to meet someone
and then that' be good. Because think
about it, bro. I'm not struggling
financially. Yeah, I don't have as much
money as I used to have, but I'm not
struggling financially. All my bills are
paid. So, I've still got time. I've
still got money to [ __ ] do stuff. So, I mean,
trust me, like, when I lost the house, I
thought it was going to affect me more
more than it actually did.
And I didn't think I was going to like
have money again. But it's like I should
be able to meet someone. I've got
I'm not perfect, but I'm still good
enough to [ __ ] be able to date,
but I can't find anyone. So,
what I need is I need a bag.
That's what I need. I need a black bag
to where the tracks do and then change.
I don't know. Oh, I like the track.
No, I never tried it.
I don't know, man.
You like the Ralph N top? That cream top
is so nice. That £200.
I need a bag. And then if I can put if I
can put the other clothes in a bag, then
all I need to do is change.
cuz I can't figure out what I want to wear.
In Thursdays, I always go out on a sesh. So,
I don't [ __ ] know, man.
I don't know. I don't know.
Like I said, I would just wear the
tracksuit. I like the tracksuit.
So, I like the black tracksuit.
We done so good on the football, didn't
we, Steven Howard? Yeah.
But the Ralph Lauren cream top is nice as well. No.
[ __ ] Mo, man.
Unless I could go. Unless I went out on
a [ __ ] Sunday, but I can't afford it,
bro. I can't afford to be wasting money.
And I don't want to be wasting money.
That's the I don't want to be wasting money, bro.
So, we could wear the tracksuit on the
Sunday and [ __ ] just chill and have a
roast dinner, but I don't want to be
wasting money, bro.
Uh, I don't know, man. I don't know.
just go out on the I mean, I'm just
going to have to go out in the track on, you know,
wearing the tracksuit
and see if I've got a bag or something
to put my other clothes in a bag.
That's the only thing I can do cuz I
can't make up my mind what I want to wear. So,
uh, what's my fault on older women? Uh,
older women are not interested.
That's my fault. They always use your
aids as an excuse.
Tracksuits are good for like if you're
just going to like pubs.
Um just like pub calls and stuff,
but that Ralph end top is nice with them jeans.
It's like, you know, my Ammani jeans
broke. The button broke, but I've still
got the belt, so I could still use the
belt. But the actual thing broke, the
actual um button, so I need to buy some
more I need to buy some new Ammani
jeans. But the thing is, I'm not paying
190 for them cuz I can't justify it, you
know? I'm more than happy to pay 130 um
you know, 130 [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm more than happy to pay 130
or 120 or whatever, but I can't I can't
pay 190, bro.
Nah, they've had it anyways. I've had
them for over a year, bro. I've had them
since last Was it last Christmas?
No, it was the Christmas before that
because obviously I wasn't Yeah, I was
living in Stratford that No, I had it.
No, no, no. I think I had it.
No, I think I've had it. Yeah, almost.
Yeah, almost two years. No, they've had
it, bro. They've had it. They I've had
them for two years, bro. I don't need to
get I I'll just wait for them to go on
sale. 120 130 I don't mind paying that
but I can't pay 190 bro
and and it has to be them jeans because
I like them jeans I don't like any other
jeans I like the money bags at the back
I know my size I don't want any other
jeans but I can't pay 190 it's ridiculous
because you wash them and [ __ ] so it's
like why am I paying 200 almost £200 for
a pair of jeans
makes me sound like I can't afford it
when I can. Trust me, I can. But I just
don't want to,
you know, waste money on it.
Um, they're 32.
Yeah, I'm 32 and me.
But yeah, we really do need to try and
find someone tomorrow, bro. Seriously,
this time is running out. So yeah,
as soon as I wake up, as soon as I wake up, bro.
How comes you watch the side men, Bob Bills?
How comes you watch the side men?
So yeah, I'm gonna
wear the track and put the other clothes
in the bag
and then change basically.
I [ __ ] better meet someone tomorrow,
mate. with all this [ __ ] effort.
But yeah, and then
you watch the side men, you know the
YouTubers, the side men,
do you know who they are,
KSI and stuff?
See, I get what Antman means. Like, you
go out doing it because there's nothing
else you can do. Yes, if you've already
got your haircut, but if you haven't
already got your haircut, that's what
longs it off for like weeks cuz you
can't be bothered paying for your head
and sitting down for an hour. That's why
like But yeah, I'm going to go out
tomorrow cuz there's nothing else to do.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, we done good on the football, bro.
We done really good on the football
the past two months.
That 120 to 380 was lovely.
That was [ __ ] lovely, matey.
Do you know what? I've had it before,
Bob, where I've tried to speak to
someone and they've just like got up and left.
So rude. Like they've literally just got
up and left, bro. Yeah,
I'm not even joking.
So rude, is it?
God loves a try, eh?
When's the National North League playing again? Steven Howard, you know,
I don't think I'll be gambling again
until I'm short of money.
Well, I wasn't short of money on [ __ ]
Sunday. I just wanted to try 100 pound
on the roulette
to be honest.
It's impressive that I won, right? And I
didn't do my balls in. Like, I won, but
I didn't really put any of it back.
Isn't that right?
So obviously I got my money back
and more of the money I spent on the
Friday, but I don't want to waste the
money again. I don't want to just waste
£500 because, you know, I won £500.
I want to spend like 10% of it, bro, and
just try and build the money up and
there's there's no need to do that extra
[ __ ] I've already gone out once. I
don't want to go out again.
It's mad. You really do need to like win
money to be able to go out this cuz say
you get say you say you go out on a say
you get paid. Yeah, Bob. Say you get
like £600 from the government and then
you get £100 a week. Yeah.
The thing is is that
if you try to say you go out on a
weekend, that money is done for, bro.
You'll probably have about £200 left.
So, it's like
it's very hard to be able to
and you wouldn't be able to date with
that kind of money as well. Whereas, if
you got like 1.7 1.8,
you can obviously date. You can go out
drinking, you can [ __ ] if you meet
someone, it's enough money. You know
what I mean?
you got like5600, you know,
and I get £800 in a couple of days as
well, but I I still need to build my money up
because I might want to go on another
holiday. There might be something I like.
The money's so hard to get. I don't want
to be wasting it, bro. That's the thing. You know,
I'm not going to get good luck. It's
going to be the same. It's been the same
for five years, but
something to do in it.
I'm not gonna have good luck, bro. It's
always going to be the same here.
But it's something to do in it.
I don't give a [ __ ] bro. Like, the
thing is, yeah, I just
love to go to bed knowing I tried.
As long as I can go to bed knowing I
tried, I can sleep well.
That's all I need to know is I tried
and then yeah, no regrets. So,
but the thing is
Yeah, man. But the thing is, I've had women.
I've had women. That's the thing. I have
Oh, 50% [ __ ]
But I've had women, though. That's the
thing. I've been with women. died.
Yeah, I've been with women.
I used to kiss women. I've slept with
women. But now, bro, can't even get
anything. But we'll see you tomorrow,
eh? Do you think it's possible that I'll
go out tomorrow and not get even one number, Bob?
Nah, I don't think it's possible, is it?
It's not possible for me to go out and
not get a number, is it? Nah.
Can you approach? Um,
can you approach sober?
Can you do it sober approach? I come. [ __ ] it.
get more numbers than [ __ ] 10 from
this message. But if I can get four or five numbers,
happy days. Simple.
Because it's quantity,
it's quality over quantity. You know
what I mean? Yeah.
Reddit is [ __ ] Why do I keep
banning people? It's annoying. Ring boy
skin in the bed sit with absolutely no
bed. No money in it.
Yeah, I'm still here, bro.
Reddit sucks, man. They just ban people
for no reason. I'm going to give up
Reddit, I think. Um,
One second, Mom. Anyways,
I'll be back live tomorrow
when I come back from the sesh. So, yeah. Be