Yeah, man.
really want to follow that guy on
Instagram, you know.
Welcome back, bro. You can't even take
an hour off of YouTube. I don't know why
you're talking about other people, bro.
You're on YouTube from the time you wake
up to the time you go to bed.
up to the time you go to bed, bro. Don't
try to take the piss out of other
people. You can't even take one day off of YouTube.
So, make it make sense. You want you
listen, as soon as I've just clicked
live, you're on here straight away. It
says it all. You ain't got a life, bro.
Don't talk about other people when you
can't even take [ __ ] 5 seconds off of YouTube.
[ __ ] self projector.
Has anyone got a nice um Instagram
account to follow this person on? This
guy's been trying to [ __ ] with me. Yeah.
And he's not accepting my follow
request. I might need to catfish him still.
Trying to cut fishes, bro.
Yeah, man. I'm put all this [ __ ] like
out there, man, to prove a point.
Yeah. I don't know how I want to do it, though.
Sorry man, I'm still going out Saturday.
I said I'll do that today, but I can't
be bothered. I'm tired as [ __ ] But I'll
still be going out Saturday and that'll
be me done. My bad. Yeah, man. Sorry, man. you know.
Nah, I can't be bothered. And it wasn't
tonight. It was today.
So, listen properly. I'll be out Saturday, though.
And then, like I said, that'll be it
until the 27th.
No, I just don't want to waste the money anymore.
I just can't justify wasting the money.
I'd rather just book another holiday.
So I just I just can't like Saturday
when I go out Saturday I'll be spending50 60
80 maximum. I don't want to be spending
more than that. I can't justify it.
I just really really can't justify it anymore. So
then obviously on my birthday will be a
different story. I mean, if you go out
like once if you go out like once or
twice a month, then it doesn't matter.
You can spend whatever. If you're doing
it every week and then you just spent a
load of money, it's just like nah, got
to be annoyed with it. So
yeah, I just would rather not to be fair.
So, but I'll definitely be out Saturday
though. Don't watch that.
Don't you worry about that one, matey.
Yeah, I really want to get into this guy's profile
for trying to [ __ ] um troll me.
How am I going to do it though?
Cuz I know he'll accept a woman's
request cuz you're a stimp.
Let me see if I know anyone on Instagram
that will follow him.
I can make a fake account, but the thing
is it's just going to dodge in it. Stop. Um [Music]
[ __ ] him, man. [ __ ]
So, yeah, that's where we're at basically.
Just cuz you win money, it doesn't mean,
you know, you should go out and [ __ ]
just waste it again,
you know? It's like you just can't
justify it anymore. So,
spending all that money, you don't even
have a date. It's [ __ ] disgusting.
Like I said, we'll do Saturday, then
we'll do the 27th, 25th, actually, not the 27th.
That's it, I think.
See, I wouldn't mind if it wasn't
expensive. Then I'd be like, "Oh, well."
But it's the cost of it as well.
Whether you have it, whether you don't
have it, it's just it's not you can't justify it.
£80. You can justify £100. You can
justify £200 for a weekend. You can
justify, but not any [ __ ] more than that.
What these porn ads keep popping up?
I don't know how you get rid of them.
They're like ads. [Music]
I don't know why you're saying like
you're trying to take a piss by saying
welcome back when I've literally been
off of YouTube for weeks before
and you people can't even take a day off
of YouTube. So really, you're just
taking the piss out yourselves. You're
not taking the piss out of me.
You know, you're literally just taking
the piss out yourselves.
Not even one day off of YouTube in
years. That's a madness.
And then they think everyone's skin just
cuz their skin is [ __ ] They think
everyone's got the same life as them.
Do you know what I need to do? I need to
see a therapist, you know, cuz that's
basically what I use this community for.
It's just therapy.
It's just just like therapy sessions
really, isn't it? If you think about it,
I might just get a therapist.
Uh, makes sense, huh?
Does make sense.
Whereas these people use it to project
their life onto others. But I mean, I
just use it for therapy sessions.
Could have a nice Chinese today, I think.
Oh my [ __ ] arm, bro.
Woke up at [ __ ] two. Jesus. Yeah,
these people still stalking me every
day. I don't know. I don't go on the channels anymore.
Will never do it again.
Yeah, probably are though. To be fair,
that's their life.
Their life is stalking on YouTube.
That's all I have. So, yeah.
I'm going to send it on Saturday. Send it Saturday.
I think my hair still looks good. My
beard still looks good.
And then I will be done.
500 for a weekend.
moves about 400 450.
Yeah, I calculated it for [ __ ] for nothing really.
cuz I'm literally just going out
Saturday to try to meet someone.
So, last week was just cuz I really
wanted to go out and still meet someone,
but this week is just going to be
because I just want to meet someone. So,
I'm not going to I'm going to try and
spend the least amount of money as I possibly can. So yeah,
[ __ ] that, man.
I can't believe I haven't even got a
date this week. That is insane, bro.
Of all them approaches. Damn.
[ __ ] damn, bro.
That is a madness to be fair.
I would have took a nice state, bro,
that never went anywhere and I would
have called it evens. But
that is [ __ ]
Really, really [ __ ] Sorry to be a
repeater, man, but it's mental
how somebody can look like that all
fresh, smelling good, confident, and
haven't even got a date this week.
>> But to be honest, you know, the more
this [ __ ] happens, the more I care less and less.
Might even try a different place on Saturday.
I might go to farmer land. Like a
farmer. Might go to farmerland. Uh
why not? Probably could get there for
like really cheap.
But I mean doesn't really matter where
you go in it cuz England's England.
So still the west, right?
What's going to be able to get back from there?
We can't try to come back from there
though. That's the thing.
Yeah, we'll just stick that on. Listen, you watch [Music] Jesus. But uh
To not have a date for this week is a madness
is a [ __ ] madness, bro. Franklin
Can't owe me a [ __ ] drink, man. [Music]
reality. You never told me no reality, [ __ ] It's not