Sorry, man. I ain't [ __ ] doing it again.
No, I'm all right, bro. I'm think I'm
just going to stay in bed today and play
some Black Ops.
Yeah, I'm good. Yeah.
Think I'm going to go on my birthday to
be honest. I think I'm just going to go
for a meal or something. Get a takeaway.
God, it's such a cycle. I can't wait
until November. Generally, you can't
wait until next month
when I'm out of here. Out of this depressing country.
Yeah, man. I'll be happy then. Next month.
Woke up. Can't be bothered to go out.
No, I'm all right. I'm good.
Not wasting any money. Nope. Can't be asked.
Roll on next [ __ ] month. E J Jesus
Christ. That's come back [ __ ] That's come fast.
Yeah. Roll on next month.
I'm out of this depressing country with
these stuck up women. Thank [ __ ] you know. [ __ ] Yeah, man. Be good.
Not going out today either.
Approaching our drinking. No, [ __ ] that.
Don't know why I said I was to be
honest. I'm not going to. Nothing's
changing in this country.
We've only got just a bit over a month
now, so it's all good. Yeah, man.
you go out, the more depressed you get.
Every time you go out and you try, the
more depressed you get. It's such a
damned catch 22.
Damned if you do, damned if you don't. I
swear to God, it really, really is. But
I mean, I just went out cuz I wanted to
go out anyways, but I swear it's such a
catch 22 every time you go out, you know. [ __ ] madness.
Sorry, man. Why is this not working?
It's depressing. I can't wait to get
out, bro. I swear to God, I can't wait
to get out of here.
Well, that's not working, is it? No.
Yeah, we playing Black Ops, I think.
What a [ __ ] game. I paid for it. I bet.
Couldn't believe that, man.
Couldn't believe Virgin Boy yesterday.
Like I said, there's no there's going to
be no more replies. No more looking on
the channel. That was just a [ __ ] one off.
try and blame me when I've literally
shown approaches, when I've literally shown messages.
I don't know what it is with people
blaming men. I don't know what it is,
but they love doing it.
Delete my videos soon, actually.
So, everyone's seen them already.
working for some reason. I don't know why. Oh.
Dude, I'm going to have some fig to be fair. It's
story. Same old thing after Tuesday. It's so [ __ ] [Music]
dismiss people's struggles, but they
like to dismiss people's struggles. No
matter what you show them, it's [ __ ] up, bro.
They love dismissing men's struggles and
defending women. It's just a society
that we live in. I guess no one has
changed it. Uh sadly. Okay. Yeah.
You go on this [ __ ] Reddit thing, man.
Power hungry mods.
That's what I call them. I call I call
them power hungry mods cuz that's what
they are. They're power hungry.
They need that power. Without that
power, they're going mad. They need that
power. They need Yep.
They need that [ __ ] power, mate.
Still no pass on the numbers. Doesn't
look good, does it?
hope in this country. Seriously, none. I
can't wait to leave. Honestly,
I'm so burnt out by last week, to be fair.
The money spent, even though I want it
back, the energy, the time. Uh, bro, I'm
I'm not trying to repeat that anytime soon.
It's so depressing.
this country, the women in it, the bad
experiences. It's so depressing. That's
why I opted to leave,
you know, because of this problem, you know.
mods need that power.
Without that power, mate. Oh, [ __ ] mad. Yeah. Heat. Banana.
We'll go back to sleep in a bit, I
think. Nothing to be awake for. So depressing.
I should just sleep until [ __ ]
November to be fair.
[ __ ] man. I really should. Yeah.
Them two [ __ ] time last times I went
out. I [ __ ] remember a lot. You know
that Friday, that Sunday. I can't wait
to finally [ __ ] leave here, bro. I
seriously can't wait. Honestly.
Yeah, this [ __ ] country with [ __ ] people
with [ __ ] women in it. Can't wait to
leave finally, bro.
Been so long since the last time, man.
You know, so
rang me at [ __ ] 9 in the morning. I
was sleeping, man. Sorry buddy. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. I don't even think I'd eat
today to be honest. It's so depressing.
[ __ ] hell, it's depressing. Yeah,
[ __ ] bugs game.
That's what it is. Yeah.
same. Well, they are literally all the
same. Just because they might like
different foods, they might like
different programs, it doesn't mean
anything. They are all the [ __ ] same.
Every single one of them is the same.
They do the same stuff, act the same
way, play the same games, all stuck up.
Even ones I've not spoke to. So, I mean,
they literally are all the same.
They [ __ ] well are. Even ones that
I've not spoke to. Congratulations.
Well, hope they reply back cuz I only
got one reply out of 10 numbers. I give
up, bro. I don't know why I even said I
was going out yesterday or today to be
honest. It's too depressing. and I can't
do it. Sorry, bro.
Yeah, that's good, man.
No, it's too depressing. I definitely
definitely give up. I don't even think
I'm going to go out on my birthday
tomorrow. I think I'm just going to go
for some food or something. I don't
know. I'll do something, but it's too
depressing in this country.
I'm [ __ ] burnt out to be honest by it all.
So, I'm not doing it.
I like that talk, bro. I like that talk.
Well, good luck anyways, man.
Yeah, I I speak to somebody from Hungary.
Yeah, I'm I'm speaking to someone from
Hungary as well, but they're on Instagram. What? Yeah.
Yeah, I'm not going out for a very long time, bro.
So, I can't justify it anymore. It's too depressing.
It's way way too depressing, bro. I'm
going going to go into that [ __ ]
pilot depressed mode again. I think
that's what happens every single time
you go out and you try. It's like a
[ __ ] in this country, bro. Last week
I went out, I spent £600, bro. Friday,
Saturday to Sunday. I spent fucking£5600.
Didn't even get one day out of any 10
numbers. I'm not [ __ ] doing this [ __ ]
again, bro. [ __ ] right off. I am not
doing it again, bro.
No, I can't snap out of it. I'm
depressed from the bad experiences.
This is the cycle. You go out, you try,
you get nowhere, you get more bad
experiences, you're depressed again.
It's the same story. Wouldn't you be
[ __ ] depressed if you got [ __ ] 10
numbers last week, looks maxing, and you
spent 600 [ __ ] pound. Would you be [ __ ] depressed?
Luckily, I won the [ __ ] money back.
But it's not the [ __ ] point. I still
had money. It's not the [ __ ] point, bro.
I could have went on another [ __ ]
holiday with that [ __ ] money. [ __ ]
just pissing it away. Got 10 numbers.
Didn't even get one day. And I looks max
as well. [ __ ] no wonder I'm depressed.
Why do you think I didn't go out yesterday
or you know I'm not going out today?
It's depressing as [ __ ] I can't wait to
get out of it, bro. Next month. I can't wait. You know,
10 [ __ ] numbers looks max didn't even
get a [ __ ] date. I got one reply out
of 10 numbers.
One [ __ ] reply out of [ __ ] 10 numbers.
[ __ ] this. I can't wait to leave.
To be honest, I'm probably going to do
something cheap on my birthday, you know.
Yeah, I'm leaving, bro. I'm going
Thailand next month. So, [ __ ] this [ __ ]
It's too depressing in this country.
It's way too depressing. Yeah,
it's way too depressing in this country
with these women in it, bro.
I I want out after last week, bro. I
don't on my birthday. I think I'll just
get like a takeaway.
I don't know.
And I just save my birthday money to be
honest. I don't I don't want to waste
any more money or time in this country anymore, bro.
Sorry man. Time to grow up, you know.
Well, hopefully that number doesn't flake. Anyways,
let's face it. She probably will. Not to
be negative with Nancy or anything, but
I know about these things, bro. I've
been doing it for years. Been through
this [ __ ] for years. Depressing.
It's depressing, bro. Really, really. I
wish I didn't go out. Generally wish I
didn't go out, bro.
I go out last um week, bro.
So, yeah. Going to play some Black Ops
today, I think.
Try to get good at the game.
600 pound can get you a lot of takeaways.
Worth it, bro.
As they say, the juice ain't worth the squeeze. Yeah. Do
600 [ __ ] pound, bro.
So now you said you're going on a date.
I I don't think I'd even go on a date
again, bro. Even if I had
um the chops, cuz we all know how dates
go. I know all of this [ __ ] about dating
now, bro. Been there, done it, won the
[ __ ] pink t-shirt. Do you know what I mean? Yeah.
Yeah, I've seen it, bro.
What makes me laugh to me is how people
think that I'm going to meet someone.
It's mad, isn't it?
They're so delusional. Like, they they
they seem to think one day you're just
going to go out and meet someone.
Jesus Christ. I mean, it is it is funny
how they dismiss my struggles. In a way,
it is funny.
They literally dismiss your struggles,
you know. They literally dismiss your struggles.
Like when you've tried to speak to
someone to me and they say straight
away, "Oh, I've got a boyfriend. Um,
sorry, I'm not interested." Without
getting to know you, getting to know
your personality. Didn't get to know me.
Didn't get to know my personality. When
they've led people on and took the piss
out of people via text. Um, they seem to
dismiss all of these things cuz it
doesn't suit them.
It's like trying on
um It's like trying on new clothes and
they're not suiting you. It doesn't suit
them. So that's why they dismiss all of
these bad things that's happened to you.
By you, I mean [ __ ] me. So stop wasting. Yep.
Yep. Do you know what it is, Timmy?
Yeah. Five years ago, you had a chance.
Four years ago, you had a chance. Don't
get it, don't get it twisted, right? I
have had chances in the past. You know,
I'm the wrong color. I mean, I'm white.
I mean, I'm white. So, I don't know how
I can be the wrong color when I'm
literally white and I look white.
But anyways, so yeah, that's that.
Yeah, it's not even that it would have
happened by now. Like even last week, I
would have had a date from last week as well,
but no dates. So, but yeah.
Uh, no, I don't look Muslim. I look white.
Yes, I am white. And I'm called to
Turkish, which is less than half. Yes, I
am white cuz my dad was fully white,
which makes me white. Yes, I am white.
And people even guess that I'm white as
well. People even think I'm white
because I am [ __ ] white. Yes, I
definitely am white.
Well, no. Just because I don't have blue
eyes and blonde hair doesn't mean I
don't look white.
You know, there's there's white people
that don't have [ __ ] blue eyes. You
do realize that not every white person
has blue eyes and [ __ ] blonde hair.
You know, there's different shades of
[ __ ] there's people that are [ __ ]
Anyways, moving on now cuz I see what
you're trying to do here. So, the point
is I'm white. So, yeah.
So, anyways, but that's not the point.
We're not getting into this.
But yeah, that's that's where we're at anyways.
But yeah, it definitely would have
happened by now.
It would have happened last week as well
when I got 10 numbers.
My arms are hurting me, man.
Jeez, man. Oh, man.
Yeah, nothing will ever change. Yeah.
Nothing will ever change. Yeah. I won't
be surprised if that person goes on a
date with you and waste your time and
their time. Believe you me, they do it.
Believe you me, they do it, lad. You know,
believe you me, they do it, bro.
They will waste your time and they'll
waste their time.
I swear to God, bro. Like, I had a date
in April. I haven't had a date since
But yeah, they're just going to waste
your time to make you feel like [ __ ]
Been there, done it, worn a t-shirt. It never changes
to be fair.
And then it's going to make you feel
even more [ __ ] about yourself. That's
what they do to people. But no one would
ever tell you that. So
hopefully you'll get sex on the first date.
Good luck with that, mate. You probably
won't even get a kiss on the first date.
Good luck with that.
But I hope you do.
I hope you do, man. Honestly, I [ __ ]
cuz I hate them [ __ ] So I really hope
you [ __ ] do, but I don't think so, bro. So
good luck, man.
Yeah. Good luck, lad.
But yeah, good luck, man. Anyways,
hopefully I don't flake last [ __ ] minute.
I won't be out today. I won't be out tomorrow either. Nah,
no. [ __ ] that.
Waste of time, waste of effort, waste of
money, waste of everything. No.
Yeah, I won't be out tomorrow. I'll be
in bed. I'll be in bed today. I'll be in bed tomorrow.
It's depressing, bro. I'm still burnt
out from last week.
It's such a cycle. Such a depressing,
boring cycle that never changes.
So [ __ ] boring, isn't it?
No, they don't. Not in London they
Not in London they don't, mate. Not in
[ __ ] London they don't. So yeah,
they don't. I live in London and I'm
telling you they don't. So just
depressed Joe. I was supposed to go out
yesterday, didn't. I was supposed to go
out today, didn't.
not going to drinking approaching.
Yeah, I've lived in London my whole life
funny enough and I'm from London and I'm
telling you they don't. So
yeah, you don't know London weather than
me, mate. Trust me. Um yeah, I was
supposed to go out yesterday. I was
supposed to go out today, but I'm not
not going out tomorrow. It's so
depressing. I'm still burnt out from
last week to be honest, Joe.
I can't believe the amount of money I
spent. I can't believe the amount I
tried and still no date this week. I'm
just looking forward to next month.
I think you I think you will find uh you
don't lad cuz I'm from London so I know
about London and yeah
I think I'll find that you don't. So
yeah uh just last week to be honest Joe
uh the money spent don't matter that I
want it back. Doesn't matter that I
still have money and had money. It's not
the point. Uh the money wasted, the
effort wasted. There not even a date
this week. Yeah, I'd say at this point
just give up and wait until Thailand. I
think it's not changing in this country.
The past is definitely dictating the
future like it has been for 5 years and
it ain't changing here. So
yeah, I've got a game on my Xbox called
Black Ops 2, which I need to get into.
So I'll just get into that to be honest. So yeah,
I just I just can't believe the amount
of money I spent last week to be honest with you.
for nothing. I went out literally for
I put effort into appearance. I put
effort into approaching. I spent money
for literally no reason.
What the [ __ ] bro? That's crazy.
Jesus. That is That is [ __ ] crazy, bro.
For absolutely no reason. 600
from the Friday to the Sunday. drinking, eating
some breakfast stuff and that just went5600.
I think it was £500
and I didn't even g and that's not
including the gambling. So the gamble
was 100 and that made it 600. Sorry,
500. Yeah, [ __ ] that. I'm not going out
spending that money again
to get rejected. Uh
[ __ ] that, bro. to get rejected by women
and not even get a date. Yeah. No thanks.
I mean, the time I got by the time I got my haircut,
drunk, ate, [ __ ] around. Yeah, it was
about £500 to be fair. Then it made it
six for the gamble and obviously I won
the money, but you know, it doesn't
matter that I won the money.
Nothing to show for it, but like you
say, the past don't dictate the future.
Uh, I don't know about that one. It
seems to me that it really really does
cuz it's still happening at 28 years of
age this month. So I can't wait until
next month to finally leave. To be
honest with you, it's been a long time
coming. Want to leave again. I didn't go
out last night. I was supposed to go out
today but can't be bothered. I'm still
burnt out from last week to be honest
with you. I don't think I'm even going
to go out on my birthday. I'm just going
to do something else on my birthday. I
think it's just too depressing in this country.
Yeah, it's never changing. It's clearly
never going to [ __ ] change. So, I
mean, [ __ ] it. I just wait now until the
month and a half. Not a problem. So,
nothing to show for it. And it's always
going to be like that in this country.
Took the piss out by women, led on by
women, waste a load of [ __ ] money,
[ __ ] [ __ ] Then I had the thing
with the escort as well,
you know. Nah, I'm good, bro. I just
want to get out of this country for real
now to be honest with you. And then the
bad experience with the escort and I was
like I don't want to repeat of last week.
I just don't want to repeat of it going
out trying nowhere. You might as well
just do nothing
cuz in the end you had nothing to show
for it anyways. I should be I should be
on a date this week. So if really what
you're saying is true about how the past
doesn't dictate the future, I would have
a date this week out of them 10 numbers.
I would have a date this week. If if the
past did not dictate the future, I would
be on a date this week. Simples.
But I don't. So, I mean, that's not very
encouraging, is it? It's not very
encouraging to go back out and try
again, is it? When someone's wasted all
of that money. It doesn't matter how
much money. No one cares that he's done
a video. No one gives a [ __ ] I'm not
watching it. So, don't bring it on my
channel. Um, it doesn't matter how much
money you have, whether you want the
money back. It's the whole point of it.
It's the point of like how much you
actually spent and you got nothing to
show for it,
bro. Nobody cares. Stop bringing it on
my channel before I block you. You know,
your second warning, third strike,
you're out. I'm not entertaining these
people no more. I just thought I'd do a
little video replying,
bro. you. One more one more warning. I'm
being nice. I block you. Stop bringing
it on my channel and you're blocked.
Why? Stop bringing it on my channel.
I told you this. Stop bringing weird
drama on my channel. See you. You asked
for it as well. Um, like I said, I'm not
the one that's jealous and obsessed. So,
I'm not going to act jealous and
obsessed like they are. I'm going to let
them make a fool of themselves. as we
were saying. Uh, as we were saying, um,
so yeah, like it doesn't matter how much
money you have or how much money you
know you won or whatever. It's like it's
not sustainable, you know, wasting that
kind of money for no reason.
You couldn't do that on benefits, mate.
You couldn't do that on [ __ ] benefits. So,
looked your best, done your best.
Looked your best, done your best. You
sure don't have a date. I don't know,
Joe. I'm not a believer in the past
don't dictate the future. I'm not a
believer. I have to be real with you
here. I'm not a believer.
Cuz how can you look your best, do your
best, and still not even get a date for
this week? I'm sure if there was some
kind of hope, you would have at least
had a [ __ ] date or two [ __ ] dates,
but there is no hope. And there will
never be any hope in this country.
So that's where we are.
Is there anything in the cinema?
I don't think so.
I would have went to cinema, but there's
nothing I don't think in the cinema. Anything.
So that's where we're at.
Yeah, I am because it's ridiculous. I
mean, what could you blame last week? I
looked good. I dressed good. I smelt
good. I spent money. I've done enough
approaches. I mean, what's the excuse
for last week?
What's the [ __ ] excuse for last week?
There was no excuse not to get a date.
There was literally not an excuse. And
then you got people on the internet
saying that people can get laid,
acting like you could just go out and
get laid. Oh, but then I realized Reddit
is not real life, you know? They just
they just say [ __ ] for the sake of
[ __ ] saying [ __ ] you know? And
that's what made me laugh with uh
nonsense. That's the only reason I
replied to it is because it's like I
need to take accountability for what
speaking to people normally and them
acting stuck up or me getting numbers
and them leading my ass on. Whoop.
Sorry, mate. Don't shoot me. I'm to
blame. You know what I'm saying? Does he
even know the definition of accountability?
You know, working on yourself. What the
[ __ ] is this guy talking about? He
doesn't have no clue what he's on about.
But then again, he is a s. So,
you know, just because I don't lick
women's asses, it doesn't mean I'm a
virgin, mate. I just hate them. I
generally hate them. Like, we do. The
reason I went out last week is cuz I
wanted to go out anyways, but
I was going to go out yesterday to try
and meet someone and today, but then I
realized I just hate them. So why am I
going to try when I hate them just as
much as I hate just as much as they hate me. So
that is depressing. That that weekend
was depressing, bro.
There's no excuse for it as well, you know.
There's literally no excuse for it.
See, it's not like I gambled and that's
what made the money high. Cuz if you
gamble, then I mean that's like more
than 50%. When I used to gamble, it's
like, okay, well, the money's gone on gambling. But
oh, you got like a nice hotel or
something. There's not really anything
to show for that money that I wasted. So
that's that's it really in it.
Still got close to two grand, but I'm
not wasting any of it. So yeah,
and then the escort thing as well was
depressing. So I feel like God let me
win that money to try and tell me something. So
why why you got to waste money again?
Why the [ __ ] you got to waste money again?
But people still think there's hope. Mad.
[ __ ] no hope in this [ __ ] country.
None at all. Cuz
you people, Joe, you and Nex, you like
to dismiss struggles. You like to
dismiss people's struggles and like to
blame the man. That's what you people
like doing. I don't know why you do it,
but you do it. So,
and all of my experiences contradict
everything that you say, yet you still
ignore it. So, I mean, it must be nice
though, to be honest. It must be nice
being a woman. It must I'm It must It
must I'm not showing you nothing. I'm
never showing money ever again to any of
you people. So, there's no point even
asking me. I'm not showing you even £5.
Not showing you two pounds. I got some
money on the side there, by the way. Not
showing you nothing. You're wasting your
time asking me to show money cuz I will
never show money ever again to anyone. So,
you like to um Anyways, it must be nice
being a woman, you know, to be honest,
to be fair to them. They can have a
bunch of simps stick up for them. They
can be [ __ ] They can be [ __ ] and
everyone defends them. It must be nice
to be them to be fair. So, big up them. Yeah.
You going out tonight? That's nice, man.
I'll just be chilling.
Going to get some food from somewhere. I
don't know where.
So yeah, man.
But by about you, man.
No mongos on my channel. No
self-injected mongos on my channel. So
yeah, man. Yeah, go out, man. Tell me
how it goes. I won't be going out for a
very, very long time.
Um, and yeah, I know like I I got my
haircut and stuff and whatever, but I
got the money back.
I got my money back, you know, from and
a bit more. I know it is a waste, you
know, get my haircut. I had to sit on
that chair for an hour, but I done
enough approaches. I proved my point.
So, I don't need to go out again.
So, yeah, there's just no hope for some
people. I think
there's literally just no hope for people
for some people. So yeah,
like I said, the whole escort thing as
well, it's like a kick in the nuts every
time you try to go out in this country.
The country is a [ __ ] joke, you know?
I hate it, man. [ __ ] hate it. So yeah,
think about it, Joe. You know, you can
go on holiday with5600 pound, not to
like Thailand or America, but I mean you
can go on holiday. So I mean, how could
I justify spending that money and
potentially spending that money again by
the time Sunday? What to get nowhere?
It's just nah, I ain't doing it. So yeah,
I [ __ ] actually hate women, bro. I'm
not even joking. I actually hate them.
But people seem to defend them. I don't
know why, but they do. Strange. Strange
how so many people defend them. And
these people have had less women than me
as well. That's the funny thing about
it. They've had less women than me and
they still defend them. So yeah,
what exactly are you going out for? To
get [ __ ] rejected by people that
think they're better than you? I mean,
what the [ __ ]
Wouldn't you know that I I have got more
life experience than
[ __ ] nonslegs? I've been with more
women than him. I've had more sex than
him. He's still a virgin. Would you not
think that I have got more experience than him?
You know, when I used to meet him, I
used to say that they're all the same.
But I used to just say it for the sake
of it. Oh, you know that they're all the
same. I used to just say it for the sake
of saying it. But they generally are all
exactly the same.
They generally generally are all the same.
These women are all the [ __ ] same. I
don't know how people can sit there and
say that they're not when they they the [ __ ] are self reflector.
But my self projector.
No, it's not about that. I did. But the
fact that I got 10 numbers and not a
single date. What does that look like to
you? It doesn't look good, does it?
So what? You want me to go out and drink
and not speak to anyone new? That's
ridiculous because of how expensive it
is. Of course you're going to go and
approach if you're drinking. Of course
you're going to talk to new people and
make new friends if you go out drinking.
What the [ __ ] It's like these women. I
don't understand how they go out, waste
[ __ ] money just to tell everyone
they've got boyfriends. What a [ __ ]
madness. Cuz it's not cheap going out
nowadays, you know? It costs more than
going on an actual holiday.
in London. I don't know about where you
live. So, it's like they go out who goes
out and [ __ ] waste their [ __ ] money,
right? Who out who goes and waste their
[ __ ] money just to tell everyone
they've got boyfriends? It's [ __ ] ridiculous.
Like, I wouldn't [ __ ] go out and
waste money if I weren't going to try to
meet anyone [ __ ] new. That's stupid, bro.
We did have a good time
uh last week until the escort thing and
then until we realized how much it cost
and then the 10 numbers never [ __ ]
got anywhere. So yeah,
so I I won't be out now for a very long
time and I'll need to go to the barbers
again. So and I won't be doing that.
See, when you've when you've had your
haircut, you can just go out sometimes,
but when you've not had your haircut,
you think, "Oh, can I be bothered going
to the barbers and sitting on a chair
for an hour?" And the answer is no.
That's why I delay it so much.
That's why I just delay it so much, bro.
To be fair. So, yeah.
And that big nose thing is getting
really boring now. You need to think of
some new insults,
you fat self-rejecting [ __ ] with no
life on YouTube.
I swear this community is full of
[ __ ] mongos. Honestly,
no, I don't think they're I just think they're [ __ ]
Ah, I just poked my [ __ ] eye there. I
just think they're [ __ ] Me. Yeah,
[ __ ] work on yourself. Why don't they
[ __ ] work on their [ __ ] self? Stop
being such stuck up [ __ ] that think
they're better than everyone.
I forgot to say something on the at the
end, Joe. Um, of my video to Virgin Boy.
Now, before you say I'm gay,
um, would you tell a woman that talks
[ __ ] about Ben that she's a lesbian? No,
I didn't think so. Just just double
standards for you. Just thought I'd add
that in there, but I forgot to add it to be fair.
Also, you got the double standards as well. Um,
so many double standards.
I hate women me, bro. I hate them.
Really, really do hate them. I only went
out last week cuz I wanted to go out
drinking anyways to be fair. So,
and look, look at the palava I had with
a escort with a thing. I don't want to
repeat of it.
I really don't want to repeat.
I don't think I'll use an escort now for
a very, very long time. So
I think your life will generally get
better once you accept your fate.
Um once you accept your fate and you
finally give up, give up, give up, your
life would actually get better. You know that
you holding on to there's hope when
there's absolutely no hope is just
[ __ ] mad. Cuz if you would have met
someone, you would have met somebody
when you had the house
as well. Cuz don't forget, we was going
more um out more then cuz I was younger
then. I can still go out. Well, you
know, we was going out more then. So,
you would have generally just have met
someone by by now. But yeah,
Chinese uh Chinese Izzy is in um
Manchester. She said, "Oh, I should come to Manchester."
It's like, "Nah, I'm not wasting money.
Can't be annoyed with it." [ __ ] Manchester. [ __ ] me.
Yeah, I won't be using an escort again.
So, you ask me if I want a drink and I
answer you and then you ignore me. What the [ __ ] So yeah,
that [ __ ] still owed me a [ __ ] drink
to be honest. Yeah,
it's the same old [ __ ] like it will
always be the same old [ __ ] in this
country with these women.
I just wish people would just stop
dismissing my struggles and making up stuff.
Just mad, but they they do that. So,
oh, you still there, Joe?
I noticed something, you know. Um,
I noticed something. I need to explain
this to you.
Since you love the old house so much,
you know what? I actually learned something.
Isn't it mad how you got more chance of
winning money gambling than getting laid?
But they say that the the odds are
against you with gambling.
Isn't that a [ __ ] madness? I think
we've actually done well on the
gambling, you know, the past two months.
I mean, you got more chance of actually
winning [ __ ] money than actually even getting laid. Imagine that. Yeah. Yeah, man.
What do you reckon would have happened
if I went out today approaching Bob? I
could tell you exactly what would happen.
I could tell you exactly what would happen, matey. Not interested.
No one's interested in this country. [ __ ] it. [Music]
Sorry, bro. I had to block that account
cuz you kept bringing nonslegs up. We
don't entertain them weirdos on my
channel cuz we're not the obsessed jealous ones.
They are cuz they keep going on about us
and I don't need to look on anything to
know that they're going on about me
because that's their life before you
ask. So, we don't need to entertain them people.
Don't even know why I done a video this
morning to be honest. But yeah. Yeah, exactly.
You need loads of Instagram followers.
It's a madness, isn't it?
What's today? I'm going to get I think
a vendal today. had a code for ages.
Going to walk to the shop though cuz I
want to go out and walk today. Yeah.
500 over a weekend. Jesus Christ. I
could have went to [ __ ] Egypt. Yeah.
That's half of the money to go to [ __ ] Miami.
That's another thing I wanted to tell
LT. That's one of the reasons why I called him. [Music] Yeah, man.
You're looking at like 13,400
and if you spend £600,
right, that's [ __ ] half your way
[ __ ] there. So, at the end of the
[ __ ] day, you can't justify spending
that amount of money.
You know what I'm saying?
Like I said, it's different if you
stayed in a nice hotel or,
you know, you met the love of your life
or I don't [ __ ] know, bro. You
gambled and, you know, you can kind of
see where the money went, but we don't
actually know where the money actually
went on [ __ ] [ __ ] you know.
in a red with no money in it
with no money in it. Never.
I would never want to live in that [ __ ]
hole. [ __ ] that. Hate the women there.
Hate the people. Ignorant. They think
their country is better than everyone
else's. Never, bro. I never want to.
I'd rather live in [ __ ] Canada than
live in America cuz
Yeah, I' I'd rather live in Canada. I
would never live in that [ __ ] bro.
There's a cost of living crisis there as well.
The women are worse over there than they
are here. [ __ ] that. So
I wouldn't live there if you paid me,
bro. I was just using as an example. Virgin boy.
No money in it.
>> I'm not going on that virgin channel. I
don't know why the [ __ ] community
post popped up
cuz the thing is Bob, right?
We have a YouTube
calling you every single day. It shows
everyone what they are and what you're
not. You understand?
It shows them to be all of the things
that they are and that you're not.
That's why you just let them embarrass
themselves, lads. You know, it's better that way.
You know, they can self project their
skintess, they can self project their ugliness.
That to me had me [ __ ] laughing, man.
Every time I go on these video, it
reminds you of [ __ ] Monty.
At least got pissed, man. Cheers.
Sorry about that, bro.
Had to go toilet. Yeah, mom.
Yes, I was talking to someone.
That [ __ ] LT called me at like
LG called me at [ __ ] 9 and I answered
it half asleep and I just hung up. Jesus Christ.
I was like, why is that little chocolate
man calling me at that time, man? He's
such a ninking poop.
It's just banter. Okay,
it's just banter.
We're going to do a video to be Aldridge. Tiffy Erdridge.
Nah, no racism on my channel, mate.
Well, I can't stop laughing at that.
Timmy Eldridge. Monty says he's not
funny. He's just stupid.
I know when I put this video up. Yeah, I
buddy. He's going to watch it. Jimmy. [Laughter] Jesus Christ.
Why the [ __ ] is is that [ __ ] Why is
LJ a in Blackpool anyways? What the [ __ ]
Who the [ __ ] goes to Blackpool in the winter?
Yeah, man. [ __ ] hell.
This one on this L J channel.
Oh, another self projecting comment.
Hope PJ doesn't see this. He'll be
beside himself with anxiety and grief
because he can only afford one cause
takeaways. Now, remember what I said
about how um how not everyone's got the
same life as you people. You think that
people have got the same life as you.
You don't know what people have. You
don't know what people don't have.
Another self-projecting comment.
But I mean, yeah. Hey, Greavves. I can't
stop laughing at Timmy Eldridge.
You know, he's something to laugh at.
I'm not going to lie. I find it entertaining.
It just reminds me of Monty. I don't
know why. I've done a video on Timmy Aldridge.
It's just something to laugh at, is it?
man. I was laughing at [ __ ] Timmy
Aldridge um yesterday in bed.
Yeah, I was laughing at Timmy Aldridge in bed
and I think the whole neighborhood heard me. Greasy.
He's so stupid, isn't he? For [ __ ] sake.
I think people like him shouldn't be
allowed on the internet. Greasy.
Yeah, people like him shouldn't be
allowed on the internet. No. Yeah. You
with no bed and no money in it.
I'll [ __ ] afford it, mate.
I'm so glad I didn't go out yesterday
and I'm not going out today. [ __ ] that.
I'm going to get into Black Ops Grievy.
Yeah, Black Ops 2.
Did you hear that? What you say? [Music]
Women are [ __ ] evil.
Evil [ __ ] That's what they are.
I hate them.
I hate women.
They're [ __ ] Greasy.
Greavvesy, do you know why is no one do
you know what the most honest advice
somebody could give Greavvesy?
That you know, you're probably never
going to meet anyone in this country
unless you get extremely out of this
world lucky. No one ever says that. I
wonder why no one ever says the truth, Grezy.
Um, no one ever says, you know, when you
go out, you play at your own risk, you
know, and it's very, very, very unlikely
you're going to meet someone, you know,
unless you get extremely extremely
lucky. No one ever says that. I wonder
why people don't tell the truth, Grezy.
Makes you wonder, don't it?
Or should I go to the Chinese today and
get a nice sabloin chips? Grezy,
what do you think of that, Grezy? A nice sabloin chips. H,
that sounds nice. Subloin chips.
I don't know what I want. I don't know.
Have you ever had a savoin chipsy?
I don't know what I fancy to be fair. Um,
do you remember when I took King to get
bagels? Greasy. Oh, and do you remember
when I done cold approaching with King?
Oh. Oh, do you remember that grievy
when I took King to do cold approaching? Oh,
how cute is that? Yeah, I went cold
approaching with King. I put it on
video. You didn't see it? I've got them recorded.
Yeah, when I took King um for bagels.
I done a few cold approaches with him.
I thought it would work, but it never
Oh, you never had a satellite. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Oh, I get you. I get you. Yeah.
But the past don't dictate the future,
so they say. No, honestly, I don't know
what I want to eat today.
Maybe I won't eat.
I don't know. Oh, I had McDonald's
um last night and I got free chips.
Grezy, I got two chips, six nuggets, and
a Big Mac. A chicken mac. Sorry.
Yeah. And a lovely
I don't know, man. I kind of want a
bagel. Make my make myself a homemade Yeah.
Do you remember Grezy? Ah, they've all got boyfriends.
They've all got boyfriends.
And man said it's always going to be the
same day. You know this. Is he right, Grievousy?
Is he right saying that though,
Greavesy? He says it's always going to
be the same day. You know this
going to be the same there. It's true
though, is it?
He said, "Oh, I had to get my um"
He said, "I had to get my phone fixed.
£150 it cost me." He said, "Well, yeah,
it will never change, will it?"
That's what he said. Gy,
Boozy, that's what he said. He said to
me, "Oh yeah, I just went to get my
phone fixed." He said, "Yeah, I stole
your videos." He said, "Well, it will
never change, will it?" And you'll never change.
That's what he said. She said, "I'll never change."
It would never change, would it?
Well, it would never change, would it?
Uh, [ __ ] Izzy wants me to go to
Manchester and see her, Greavvesy.
But nah, I can't be asked. [Music]
Can't be asked. Yeah,
I know what I want to eat.
I tell you, I've not had um wagger mamas
in ages. You ever had a wagger mama,
Greavvesy? I doubt it. They probably
don't do it in the village that you live in.
Yeah, wagger mama.
Think it's called a chicken capsule
curry, I think. Oh, it's really nice.
Wagam is nice.
I don't know, man. Maybe I'll go to the
Chinese and get like a chicken curry.
I don't know.
I don't know what I want, bro. Oh
[ __ ] with no money in it.
>> What do you think of that goosey skin?
No money in it.
I don't know what I want, bro. I seriously don't.
That's horrible. And you don't know what
you fancy, is it, Greasy?
Yeah. Which would be Waga Mumas. I've
not had that in like over a year. Um,
yeah, I had Nandos the other day. That
was the first time in ages. So, only had Nandos.
I don't think I've had KFC in a while,
but KFC is too expensive to order.
I miss living in Stratford, but when I
used to live in Statford, I used to just
walk to the KFC and just get the bucket. Yeah. Virgin boy
in a bed when I bet my money.
Sometimes the wagon mas can come cold.
Wag mama can come cold.
Uh maybe get an Indian.
I don't know. Maybe I won't even eat
today to be honest. I'm too depressed to eat. Yeah.
to press the eight to be honest.
You ever felt like that? Sure. You have
the person [ __ ] depressing.
All of these bad experiences, eh? Uh,
this feels sick to be honest.
Last week made me feel really sick.
Doing them numbers, no meats.
Yeah, starting to give up forever here. Uh, no.
I like a lamb ticker curry greasy.
A lamb ticker one.
That's That's my favorite.
The thought of food makes me [ __ ]
feel sick, bro. To be honest, I don't
know. I don't want to eat
like I could have something really
small, but that's about it. Yeah.
Skinny little bit
money in it. [Music]
could go to the chicken shop. Maybe
Greavves, you could go for a walk and go
to the chicken shop.
Could go just go to the chicken shop which is
a little while away. It's like 20, 30 minute walk.
I don't know. I don't really fancy eating.
Why would I gamble tonight?
Why would I gamble? For what reason?
Why you asking stupid questions?
No, I'll just go to sleep.
I'll just go to sleep. I'll just play
some games and go to sleep.
No, I'm never getting into that [ __ ] again.
No, I'll never get into that [ __ ] again.
I've got the Xbox. I've got Call of Duty. So,
I'm not a gambling channel. I don't know
why you think I still gamble when I don't.
The only time I really gamble is when I
spend a lot of money and I want to try
and win the money I spent back.
No, it can't be true. Grey,
how much are they charging?
It can't be.
Really? How much?
I can't afford you anymore, Franklin.
Why is it going up?
We can't afford you anymore, Franklin.
Be able to afford you anymore.
Sorry. Is that cute? Easy.
That's a madness. Dude,
just cuz I'm bored, it doesn't mean I'll
gamble, bro. What the [ __ ] No,
I learned my lesson ages ago with the gambling matey.
Greavvesy knows, don't you? Greavvesy. Yeah.
Not for me, mate. I'm good.
Well, I do I'll put£10 on a football
tomorrow. It's Saturday tomorrow, is it?
I'll do£10 on a football. Yeah. [Applause]
Where's the National North League playing again? I wonder. Clear
What the [ __ ]
Well, I'll be back later. Yeah.