on Friday.
Yeah. So, today I just want to stay on
Guinness. Oh, Guinness is enough, bro. I
guess you drunk, bro.
Where? What do you have? Jack Daniels.
Guess is good, man.
Good old Guinness, man.
When did you last drink? Sunday. Sunday. Sunday. Yeah.
I can't deal with the hangovers anymore,
bro. Two days. I'm done, bro.
You don't get him. I wish I never got
him, bro. But me, I sleep. I wake up.
Eat. Sleep. Wake up, eat two and a half
days to one day and off then I'm better.
It's [ __ ] up, bro.
It's probably because you drink cuz
you're used to it in it. I'm fully
young. I'm young as well. I'm young as
well, bro. 27. 27.
Yeah, true. But when I went last time I
went out my area with my mate, I like
whiskey everything. I never had a
hangover. It was mad. Yeah. But what I
do whenever I come back, I take
painkillers, have a bath, eat like
really hot food, and it it sort of
reduces it somewhat. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I always take painkillers
cuz it reduces it, bro. I
mean, what's what's the machine saying?
They're paying out. Yeah.
I wouldn't have put 20 pound in it.
Hopefully I get a bonus.
Go for I wouldn't try but go for it. You
[ __ ] love it, mate. Go piss, bro,
before I put this money in the
machine. That guy was a can. That
Scottish guy was a can, buddy.
We're not violent though. No, he weren't
violent, was he? Cuz you knew, bro. You
knew like he could only step a distance
cuz you would got [ __ ]
up. Look at that. That's a few of these
people. This weather spoons are worth a world. Hey,
how you doing, bud? You all right? Yeah,
good. How are you? Good, man. But I
spoke to two people today. They all
They're so rude in London, bro. I don't
know why people are so [ __ ] rude,
bro. Where are you from?
Don't tell me you're from Leed.
Leeds hate southerners, bro. I swear
that I went to Le once, man.
Where where did you go?
Where did you go for that hour?
Okay. Yeah. Yeah. But where did you used to go?
But we for like a proper [Music]
now. Yeah. Yeah. Bro, huh? Well, I um I
don't support football. What do you
support, bro? You know, you don't get
many Tottenham supporters now. It's
either [ __ ] West. It's either West
Ham or [ __ ] Arsenal. I hate football,
bro. I hate it. I hate it. Yeah, bro.
Well, at least he was friendly. At least
he weren't a
[ __ ] that [ __ ] Scottish guy. He
didn't stick on me, bro. The [ __ ]
bro. Not one little bit, did he, mate?
Not one little bit.
Are you all right?
You look like you're struggling with the bags.
You all right?
Oh, [ __ ] What you been What you been
doing? Somebody pulled the latch off.
Oh, [ __ ] me.
Where are you from? Where you from, buddy? Cardiff.
Welsh people are [ __ ] class, man.
Normally Scottish people are class, man.
But I spoke to one guy downstairs. He
turned out to be a [ __ ] man. Proper
[ __ ] man. I was I said to him, "Yeah,
what drink like or them two drinks for
you?" Cuz like he had like a beer and
then he had like rum and he started like
being a [ __ ] for no reason. He's like,
"Oh, well, it's none of your business.
Why are you putting your feet? I said I
put my feet where a [ __ ] what, mate?
And I say in the same [ __ ] man.
But I didn't expect it from a Scottish
person cuz normally they're friend like
cuz London's got a reputation of being
miserable. Miserable. I'm from London. I
feel like I'm the only person that's not
rude to me, but I generally feel like
that. You know what I mean?
Yeah, they norally and Welsh people, but
he was just a [ __ ] man.
So I put my feet. How are you going to
come to my country and tell me I can't
put my feet on the chair? I put my feet
where I want. You know what I mean?
We've all had a long day, man. We all
have problems, you know? We don't have
to be rude to people. You know what I mean?
Where are you from?
Yeah. You know what? That's one place
I've never been like
Deon. Never been to Cornwall. Never been.
You don't really have an accent to be.
Yeah, that's that. Yeah, that's I feel
like I'm the only one in London. I mean,
I've been to Middlesbrough and it's
literally poverty really. And guess
what? I still didn't think I was better
than anyone. I was still, you know what
I mean? I don't want it. They they give
us a bad name, bro. They do. Cheers,
bro. Yeah, they're all [ __ ] mate.
[ __ ] [ __ ] the
Scottish. I stood for, but I stayed in
the same place. I was going to let him
[ __ ] intimidate me, bro.
You know, no way, bro. You knew if you
stepped to me what time it was. Let me
go on that machine there and I'll
[ __ ] go that day.
Yeah. I'm going to have I'm not having
that. [ __ ] that. Yeah, that's what I'm
saying. Right. Hold on a minute. We got
a be on the ground cuz we're playing
mate. I'm in a pub. Yeah. Scottish guy
tried being a [ __ ] [ __ ] I told him,
bro, I put my feet where I want, bro.
Yeah. You don't tell me where I put my [ __ ]
feet. Yeah, [ __ ] off,
man. You know what? I always would big
up the [ __ ] squad people as
well. Knocked out today. He's being a
[ __ ] man. For no reason. Don't get
him, bro. Yes, you can.
Going. No. Anyways, [ __ ] [ __ ] that guy.
He was a prick.
Anyways, he didn't want no smoke,
Buff. He didn't want no smoke,
Right. I'm scared cuz
Yeah, that cunt's all there. I think
he's gone as well.
[ __ ] All I was trying to do is be friendly, bro.
Huh? I leave my beard here, bro. Come
on. Come on,
mate. You was a [ __ ] B. No, he didn't
make me look a clown. I made me look a
clown, bro. I said, I'll put my feet
where I want, when I want. How did he
make me look a clown,
bro? Come on, Bonus. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on, [ __ ] Come
on. Come on, bro. Come
on. Give me a
bonus. Okay, just give me a bonus. Come
on. Come on. A win, man.
[ __ ] Hey, it
is Come on. Come on. Don't be a [ __ ] all your life, man. You
No. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
Give us a [ __ ] bonus for you,
man. [ __ ] 20 g
spins. We rented our whole [ __ ] thing, bro. Good,
man. Bro, what the actual [ __ ] man?
Come on, bro.
Come on. Yes. Yes. Come on. Don't be
[ __ ] [ __ ] now. Come on,
[ __ ] Come on, you
[ __ ] Frankie, come
out. Frankie, come out,
man. Come on,
Frankie. [ __ ] off, man. Frankie.
Frankie. Yes. Come on, Frankie.
Yeah, pay for some more pints. Frankie,
come on. £25. £25, bro. More Frankie.
More Frankie. Come on, Frankie. Come out, you
[ __ ] Frankie, come the [ __ ] out, bro.
Why don't he come out ever, man? Why
don't this mother Come on. Bonus, bonus,
bonus, bonus, bonus,
bonus. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Come on. B. Oh, what the [ __ ] What's
the point of getting your money back,
bro? This [ __ ] don't give no bonus. Come
on. Bonus. Bonus. Bonus. Bonus. Bonus. [ __ ] off.
Oh my god, bro. Can I play two? Win a pub. That's done,
bro. [ __ ] [ __ ]
man. We're done, bro.
Come on. Don't be a [ __ ] all your life, man.
[ __ ] now, bro.
Come on. Give us a bonus, man. Look at this [ __ ]
madness. You don't even get a bonus to
save your [ __ ] life. annoying, bro.
Look at this. You can't even get a bonus
to save your [ __ ]
life. You can't even get a bonus to save
your [ __ ] life, mate. If your bonus
[ __ ] if your life depended on it, you
still wouldn't get a bonus. Like,
literally, if your life depended on it,
you still wouldn't get no
bonus. Lose. Lose. [ __ ] lose, man. It's
annoying. Look, even if your life
depended on it, look, lose, lose, [ __ ] lose,
man. [ __ ] bro. That's [ __ ] annoying,
bro. I just [ __ ] broke the C. It's [ __ ] annoying.
[ __ ] I just hurt my [ __ ] hand, [Music]
bro. So, they say we got different
opinions on that
one. Listen, mate. You're a little troll
in your [ __ ] in your little [ __ ]
mommy's house. Shut the [ __ ] up. Yeah,
everybody. Yeah. that saw the video
would know that I own the [ __ ] Yeah.
Stop trying to [ __ ] sir. When you're
the [ __ ] one. When you're the [ __ ]
one. Yeah. That's hiding in mommy's
basement. Shut the [ __ ] up. Go watch
back if you didn't see what happened,
you little [ __ ] It's [ __ ]
annoying as [ __ ] bro. I swear. I feel
like smashing his glasses on his [ __ ]
head. I swear to God.
It's just ruined the whole day,
bro. Hey, bro. I swear to God, it's just
ruined the whole day, bro. [ __ ] ass,
man. Go down. It's ruined the whole
day. Yeah, bro. Listen, stop talking
nonsense. Yeah. Bye-bye now, you little
[ __ ] Yeah. Go suck your mom. It's just
ruined the whole day. This is what I'm
saying. It literally it makes you It
ruins a whole day, bro. Someone's on his
phone, bro. But he doesn't want to. It
honestly just makes you ruin It ruins a
whole day. I swear
down. Ruins the whole [ __ ] day, bro.
It ruins the whole
day. It literally ruins the whole day. I
don't know about you, but it ruins the
whole day. Even if it's£20, it [ __ ]
does. It literally ruins the whole day.
Like I don't know about anyone else
here, but it ruins my whole mood, my
whole body, my whole [ __ ] day, bro.
It does. It [ __ ]
does. It [ __ ] does, man. It
does. Honestly does,
bro. It's so [ __ ]
annoying. It's so [ __ ] annoying. I
almost just [ __ ] broke it with my
fist, bro. It just went back on. It's so
[ __ ] annoying. [ __ ] annoying. It
[ __ ] is. It [ __ ] is, man. Even if
it's £20. It's so [ __ ] annoying,
bro. It's not even funny. It's [ __ ]
annoying, bro. I swear down, bro. If it
weren't a place that I went to all the
time, I just put this glass through it.
It's [ __ ] annoying,
bro. I just told Eggman about it as
well, bro. Same old
[ __ ] Same old [ __ ] [ __ ] man. It
doesn't matter if I'm okay for money.
It's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
Yeah. No, I'm not going back to this.
This is [ __ ] annoying. It just puts
you in a bad mood. That's all it does.
It puts you in a bad [ __ ] mood,
man. You know what I
mean? It's so [ __ ]
annoying. Yeah. [ __ ] off, Joe, you
little [ __ ] [ __ ] off, you little dick.
Yeah, [ __ ] off you little [ __ ] [ __ ]
off, mate. About about winning back in
the cookies. [ __ ] off,
mate. Silly [ __ ] [ __ ] It's [ __ ]
rigged as a [ __ ] Yeah, may as
well stick another 20 pound in. I'm not
doing it. [ __ ] off, man. I want to stick
another 20 pound
in. It's [ __ ] rigged as [ __ ] I want
to smash this whole pub
up. I swear it's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
Yeah, I promise you. I've already done
the bookie call, bro. Yeah. No, he's still
here. He's still here,
mate. It's just ruined the whole day.
Like, I just want to go back home. Yeah,
I know. They're trying to make me It's
not going to work, bro. It's not going
to work. Yeah, I know. It's not going to
work. It's just ruined the whole day,
the whole mood, the whole vibe. That's
literally what it does, bro. I swear to
God that's literally what he
does. Nah, I don't want to talk to him,
bro. I don't need to talk to
him. [ __ ] mug told him about himself
when I was over there. I don't need to
talk to the
[ __ ] about what, bro. This is annoying.
It just ruins the whole vibe, the whole
mood, the whole day. This is what I'm
trying to explain to you, Joe. It ruins
the whole mood. The whole vibe. the
whole day. Doesn't matter if it's just
£20. Do you not understand? The quantity
of money is irrelevant. Do you not
understand this? I don't know how many
times like I want to smash this glass
across that wall, bro. I swear it's [ __ ]
annoying. It is. It is [ __ ] annoying,
mate. I swear
down. It is very annoying, bro. Nah,
mate. You can't forget it. It's
impossible to forget it. It's [ __ ]
annoying. God, man.
Yeah, he's gone now. Anyways, man.
[ __ ] Scottish prick. [ __ ] [ __ ] I
told him about himself. I said I put my
I put my leg on the chair and what? And
what, bro? And I'm not moving. That's
what I said to him. And I'm not [ __ ]
moving. How did he own me, bro? Who's
the one that didn't go in whose face?
You know, [ __ ] silly little [ __ ]
man. All of these little [ __ ] wannabe
trolls that sat there with their [ __ ]
mummies. Yeah. You don't have a friend
to your name. Stop talking about
yourself. Yeah. Stop self-reflecting,
you [ __ ] [ __ ] It doesn't matter if
it's a 10 or 20 pound bug. Yeah. I stood
there, bro. I sat there with my feet up,
bro. And I said, "I'm not moving." Yeah.
That's what I
said. Yeah. And he wanted to be a
[ __ ] [ __ ] He wanted to be a
prick. Yeah. I stayed where I was. What? What, bro?
Right. But who come to who, bro? Come on
now. Allow it, man. Allow it, man. [ __ ]
off. Yeah. No, I'm scared of you. You
[ __ ] haggus eating [ __ ] we
Scottish [ __ ] Yeah. You didn't owe no
one, mate. Cuz I had my feet up against
the [ __ ] thing and I stood where I was.
Yeah. Yeah. You want to talk an
attitude, but you don't want to like,
you know what I'm saying, bro? Like,
[ __ ] off, man. He's like, "Oh, it's a
long day." He was just being moody. He's
I don't tell you where you should put
your feet. I said I put my feet where I [ __ ] want,
mate. I will put my feet where I want.
It's my country. I do what the [ __ ] I
want, bro. They see different. They No,
no, no. Listen. What is Steven Howard?
They want you to get into a fight with
somebody so you get nicked. No, he's
gone now. He's gone. He just walks out.
Yeah. They want No. They know the
reality, but they just want you to get
nicked. That's what it is. Yeah.
That's what it is, bro.
Yeah, bro. You're boring now. Shut up,
man. You're boring now. We're not
talking about this anymore anyways.
We're not talking about this
anymore. Yeah, he thought I was saying I
wasn't. No, I was trying to be friendly
and then he come with an attitude. Yeah.
And he tried saying, "Oh, well, I don't
tell you about your feet being on the
chair." And I said, "I'll put my feet
where I want." That's what I said. Yeah.
Cuz I'm not a [ __ ] I'm not rude to
people for no reason. And I stood there
and I stayed there. What do you want?
What more do you want me to do, bro?
What do you want me to do? Start
smashing the man in his face with a
glass bottle? Like, bro, come on. No.
Yeah. No. cuz he had a rum and coke and
he had a beer. So I said, "Oh, is that
all for you?" That's what I said to him.
Yeah. You don't know where I am. Try
again. You don't know where I am. You'll
never know where I am.
Yeah. I was No, I was being I was being
normal to him and that's
it. And that's it, bro. Like Yeah. And
he was just being a
dick. Well, I said I'm, you know, he
said, "Oh, I don't tell you." I said,
"I'll put my feet where I want." Yeah.
What more did I want? What more did you
want me to say? [ __ ] off, man.
I need to keep it
moving. Nope, it's not. And you don't
know where I am. and you'll never know
where I am. I need to send his
approaching a bit as well,
bro. It's not even funny. It's [ __ ] annoying,
bro. [ __ ] 20 gone on the machine. It
literally controls your whole mind, your
whole mood, your whole body. It
literally does, Grezy. It does. It does.
It controls your whole body, your whole
mind. It literally does. It literally
What's the time for I need to Right. So,
what I'm going to
do I need to bounce in a bit anyways cuz
I need to get to more places and I'll be
back later tonight. Defo and
uh he didn't want no smoke, bro. He
smoke. He didn't want no smoke, [ __ ] Believe
that. I listen, bro. I'm not a [ __ ] to
people for no [ __ ] reason.
Yeah. Anyways, I'm keeping it moving in a bit.
Anyways, yeah. Who? I didn't hide, bro.
What the [ __ ] Man didn't hide anywhere.
How did I hide? Yeah, I stayed where I
was and I said, "I'll put my feet
wherever I want to." What did you want
me to do, B? I was shocked why he was so [ __ ]
rude for no reason. I was like, "Okay."
I stayed where I was. I stood my ground.
These people always make up stuff,
mate. You know? [Music]
Sorry about that. I was just talking
about the the guy I spoke to like 20
minutes ago. He's just a [ __ ] I was
just talking about the guy I spoke to 20
minutes ago. He's just a [ __ ] for no
reason. Did you hear it? I swear to I
swear I just said to him, "Yeah, or them
two drinks for yourself as like a
conversation and he's just being a
[ __ ] for no reason." Like what the
[ __ ] You know, oh, do I do I ask you
what why you put your feet? I said, I
put my feet where I want, mate. Like,
you know what I
mean? Don't know why people are so rude,
bro. Like, it's a
conversation. It's a madness, bro. It's
madness. [ __ ] Scottish
prick. He's the one that went running
out the pub, bro. Not me. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Let me see if this guy's a bit
friendlier. How you doing, boss? Boss.
Boss, how are you? You okay? How's your day
going? Yeah. What you up to?
A few trips around London walking. Oh, nice, mate.
Nice. Say again.
Oh, fair. Just going for a few drinks
now. Yeah, just going for a few drinks now. Yeah.
Yeah. Fair enough, man. That's what
life's all about, bro. Just chill. I was
bored today. I thought I'd just go out
and have a few Guinnesses. You know, let
me go. I just said, "Yeah, I was bored
today, man. I thought I'd just go out
and have a few Guinnesses." You know,
it's boring, isn't it? You know,
you like Guinness, so why are you not drinking it?
Oh, Guinness is the best drink, man.
It's It's good for you as well. It's got
iron in it.
Yeah. Yeah. Where you from, man? the north.
Manchester. Ah, you know what? I need to
go to Blackpool. I've never been there,
you know. I've been all over the
country, but I've never I've been to
Manchester, but I've just never been to Blackpool. Just Yeah.
Yeah. You you sound very stubborn
though. You sound very southern. You
don't really have like an urban accent, you know.
You was born in Lancaster. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
You sound more [ __ ] subbing than me, man.
Yeah. What team do you support?
Okay. Yeah, I bet on them sometimes. Yeah. Yeah.
So, do you live in London
now, Kingston? I've never been there. I
heard it's good night out. It's like
what? 30 minutes from London. But never
been. Never been. Never been. My friend
always invites me. She's like, "Oh, come
to prison. Come to prison." I just never
go, man. [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Kingston. I've heard
of it. I've just never been, bro, to be fair.
Um, so I'm from East London.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. From East London. Born
and bread, man.
Yeah, man. Love East Thunderb.
I don't have the cockney accent, right?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's more like
That's like more Yeah, bro. I don't
speak bro. Where would you think I was
from if you heard me talk?
Cuz some people say that I sound like
I'm from Manchester, but I'm not. I'm
not. I'm not from what? From Manchester.
Southeast. Southeast London. Really?
Nah, never been south, man. Never been south.
Now Cotney is like two for a power,
mate. That's how they talk. I don't
[ __ ] tweet like that, mate. But I
don't talk road either. [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah, exactly, man. It's It's good to
meet friendly people. I spoke to some
guy about about half hour half hour ago.
He was a complete [ __ ] He wasn't like,
"Oh, I'm drinking my drink. I'm not in
the mood." And no, he was just being a
[ __ ] man. [ __ ] a
minute. But that's that's a reputation
London has. Everyone here is so [ __ ]
rude, man. You know, except me. I feel
like I'm the only one from London that's
not rude, man. You know it's what? In London. Yes. Yeah.
Yeah. They're all Do you want my
opinion? They're all [ __ ] That's what
That's what my opinion is, mate. They're
all [ __ ] [ __ ] in London. In London.
But yeah, I need to do there's two
places like so I used to travel every
week to a new city every week and
there's two places I've never done and that's
mainly Glasgow and Blackpool. That's
like them. I've been
lead [ __ ] Manchester, Liverpool,
Bristol, [ __ ] Cardiff if you name it. Yeah.
rough area. Yeah, wonderful.
Yeah, it's wonderful.
I've been to Scotland. I've just never
been to Glasgow. I've been to Edinburgh,
but I've never been to
Glasgow, but uh yeah, so I I have a rail
card. So I Well, I used to have a rail
card. So every week I used to say, "Go
here. Go there." Because you get 33%
off. [ __ ] you know people people love
London but when you've lived in London
your whole life you get bored of it man
you know what I'm saying you you want to
go different play I got my passport two
days ago this year I want to do Thailand
I want to do America again I want to do
I want to do a few countries you know
before I'm 27 but I want to do mad stuff
before I'm 30. You know what I'm saying?
Say again. I don't work at a minute. No,
bro. I don't I just fave for anything I
get. I just try and save, literally.
Yeah. What do you do?
You're retired. No. How old are you?
How old? 75. Wow. Respect. Respect.
You don't feel Yeah. You're as old as
you feel in it. You know what I mean? Yeah. 35.
Yeah. What's your name, buddy?
Bob. What? That's in Robert. Yeah.
Peter, man. Nice to meet you, bro.
Bam. Peter. So, we got both. We got old
fashioned names, man.
They do call me Pete and I think it's so
[ __ ] annoying. It's so cringe. Yeah.
[ __ ] know what I mean?
Yeah, I've got a friend that's called
Bob. Well, a friend of a friend of a
friend called Bob. Yeah, it's short for
Robert, is it? Bob short. So, your your
name is Robert? Yeah. Yeah.
[ __ ] Yeah, we got old school names,
buddy. Got old school names.
But I like my nickname is Peter Belly.
So because my name So because my name's
Peter, people call me Peter Belly as
like a nickname. So they just it's
something that I
always Yeah, it's just a nickname basically,
man. So many people are rude in London
though, man. Like I spoke to one guy
just he just blacked me just trying to
start a conversation. He just blacked
me. I was like what the [ __ ] man? I wish
I was around in your day. You know what?
I wish I was I wish I was born in the
1980s. You know why? Better horror
films, better games, better society, no
Instagram, no dating. [ __ ] I would have
I would pay good money to be to to to
not be born in this day and age. Yeah.
Yeah. So, how do you compare your day
and age to now? You can see a big
difference, right? Like, you go out,
everyone's on their phone. They're like
glued to their phone. But back then,
there was no smartphone. So, how could
they do it? [ __ ] [Music] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah. This generation's [ __ ]
man. It's it's it's crazy, bro.
Everyone's just addicted to their
phones. You tried to start a
conversation with me, they're [ __ ]
rude. Oh, man. It's crazy.
Even back in 2009 when I was younger, I
noticed there was a big difference.
House party stuff. You don't get that
anymore because what [ __ ] up this day and age was
was it was it was Instagram. That's what
[ __ ] everything up. Instagram and
dating apps. People had egos. people
because what it is is people will log on
to Instagram and they will look on their
phones and they will see that oh this
person's living a good life this
person's living a great life but it's
not their whole life they're only
showing their best life and then when
people try to compare it to that it's
unhealthy bro you know it's not Yeah. Why not?
Yeah. It's just unhealthy. It's just
like the only social media you realistically should
have is Facebook Messenger, WhatsApp,
that I feel like that's the only thing
that is somewhat healthy, you
know? Say again.
early. What What year? 2008. Because it
was made in 2007 in America, but people
in England didn't really know about it
to 2009. That's when people started hearing about it. Probably 2008.
2006. When was it made then? Because I
thought I was under the impression that
it was it was made in 2007.
Well, it might be. Yeah. Yeah.
Cuz it used to be because it used to be
BBO. So back in 2008, 2009, it used to
be BBO [ __ ] it used to be Bibbo MSN.
And then everyone started thinking, oh,
have you heard of that uh Facebook in
2009? So everyone went on Facebook and
then everyone stuck there. Yeah, it was early days. counselor. Okay. Yeah.
You should get on Facebook. Yeah.
Facebook's not that bad.
You done it. You done it. [ __ ] me, man.
Yeah, it's bad. It's like It's not even
just that. It's like I was just saying
to you, the best horror like I love
horror films. Like, it's I I'm a horror
film fan. And the best ones was in the
1980s. Even the new ones that come out
now don't compare to the ones back in
the 1980s, the 1990s. No way. Which you
would have think it's [ __ ] up because
techn technology is better nowadays. So
you would have thought it would been
better. Nah mate them Chucky films
1980s. All them films 1980s them Stephen
King it's 1980s bro. No what? I
knew. Oh you knew. Okay. Yeah.
Yeah. It's [ __ ] man. You're famous,
bro. You're famous.
[ __ ] me, bro. I I just wish I was born
in the 1980s. But I lived a bit of both.
Like I said, 2008, 2009 was this mad
difference. But when do you ever see, oh, wow.
stuff was better now than it was back
then. You never hear it. Everything was
better back then. Everything. I mean,
like you get my like smartphones that
are out nowadays and stuff, but back in
your day, you wouldn't care cuz you you
didn't know any different. You know what
I'm saying? You back then you didn't
know any different. It's like in 20 30
years they're going to bring something
new out, you know? second. Yes. Okay.
What are you getting at? What you Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. And how old was she?
So, did you did you uh met her or No. Okay. Fair.
Yeah. No, I've been to Bristol before,
but I've never I've never been on a
night out there. Never. Never. I need
to, but I just never have. Yeah. the Norwegian. Oh, [ __ ] Yeah.
You sound like a crazy [ __ ] You
do. Crazy [ __ ] You
So, when did you last go to um up north?
When did you last go back? Just speak co. Yeah. I just
Wimbledon. Wimbledon. I've been to
Wimbledon once. I went to uh go on a
date there. I had a roast dinner with
this woman and guess what? She was a
[ __ ] And she was absolute [ __ ] I've
been serious. It's [ __ ] a [ __ ] Hey,
I [ __ ] had to go I had to go I had to
I was I went from Stratford to Waterloo
and then Waterloo to Wimbledon. She was
a [ __ ] honorable old [ __ ] And that's
the that's the first time I the first
time I went. We had like a roast dinner
and [ __ ] Yeah, man.
Yeah. Yeah, I know it is. Yeah.
Went to this pub and she was a
vegetarian so kind of awkward, you know. Yeah. [ __ ]
Robert, I'm I'm going to have to go in a
minute, mate. I need to go and uh see someone, man.
Yeah, man. It's nice meeting you,
Cheers, man. It's nice to meet people,
friendly people in London that actually
are not [ __ ] cuz I feel like like cuz
I'm I've traveled all around England.
I've been to like poverty areas and I
feel like wherever I go I'm not I don't
think I'm I've been to okay I've been to
Middlesbrough I know black has got bad
reputation [ __ ] yeah every other house
is is is boarded up and the people there
were so friendly and I don't I don't
think I'm better than anyone but in
London mate you speak to your own people
they're better than you I can't I can't
deal with it man
Yeah, like I said to you, they all
[ __ ] I'll be I'll be with you. I'm Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Um, yeah. I'm like 15 minutes away from
Stratford. Yeah, that's what I'm used
to, you know, [ __ ] Yeah, I'm used to it.
Have you ever been to Thailand?
No. really. So, my friend's been three
times in a year. He's coming back next
week. He He loves it.
He [ __ ] loves it, mate. He He's He
says the women are easy. The
[ __ ] The weather's good and it's just
gambling. Like, the thing is I feel I
feel like with England it's [ __ ]
because the weather's [ __ ] The women
are [ __ ] and there's gambling
everywhere. I gamble a lot. So
everywhere I go it's like temptation
women [ __ ] women [ __ ]
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. But it's
like you never been Thailand.
Have you been America?
Have you been Australia?
Okay, fair enough.
There. You're well traveled then, right?
The west what? Where's that? The car
being Yeah. [ __ ] They're mad about
it, bro. They're [ __ ] mad about it,
man. But listen, Robert, I got to go,
man. I got to keep it moving. Nice to
meet you, man. Thanks for speaking to
me, man. And uh yeah, it's it's it's
good to find likeminded people around in
London that actually enjoyed London. And
listen, I'm the only
50 50 years. Well, you definitely lost
an or accent. You definitely have. You don't sound
You was born here and you move.
Yeah. But where in Lancaster? Was it
Preston or [ __ ]
No. When I Yeah.
You're You're basically from London.
Robert, listen. I I need to keep it
moving, buddy. Nice meeting you. I need
to be I need to get not to sound rude. Yeah.
Yeah. You're basically
southern. Yeah. You're basically you're
southern. You're southern. You sound
southern. Okay. I'm going to make it up
for you. Listen, nice to meet you, man.
Have a good day. Don't fall over being
too drunk and get home safe here, bud.
Nice to meet you, huh? With a [ __ ]
pipe, bro. I I would I would I would
stay on all day, but I got some [ __ ]
to get. I got some women to get.
You're going home. How about you come to
nightclubs? You want to come
nightclubs? Come on,
man. Why don't you come now? Why not,
man? I'll pay for your
drinks. I'll pay for your drinks, man.
It's like 5 minutes away. Huh?
Yeah. So, what social media do you use?
I'm going to add you on Facebook and
then one day we're going to go to a
nightclub. Me and you are going to go to
a nightclub. Yeah. We're going to go to
a nightclub. Me and me and you. If it's
not today, it's going to be next week. Yeah.
Okay. I got his I got his I got his
Instagram. I got his I got his Instagram
cuz he's a [ __ ] leg. I got his
leg. Hey, he's a [ __ ] legend, bro.
There we go. Man, I didn't think the
first person's Instagram I'd me get was
an old man. Oh, [ __ ] I literally did
not think it was going to be that,
bro. That's some madness,
bro. He does. Right. I'm going to go to
next place anyways, bro. So, I'll go
live in a bit anyways.
big listen. I'll I'll keep it moving.