Uh
da da da da da da da da
da da da da da da da da.
I'm back. A lovely curry.
Now I'm drinking some hot cocoa.
Oh, what have you done to Mr. Migay?
What have you just [ __ ] done to Mr.
McGay? That was very horrible of you.
That was very, very horrible of you.
Yeah, I just had a lovely curry, mate.
As you do. As you [ __ ] do, mate.
Skinn virgin going on that.
The skin bastard going on that.
No, we're playing a bit of Franklin.
Bit of Franco. You know how it goes, you know. >> Yeah, dude.
Yep. And you're on YouTube again on a
Saturday night. So, same thing goes back to you.
You're obviously not out with your
mates, mate. If you're coming on my live stream texting,
it's a Saturday night and your point is what?
So, what if it's a Saturday night? It's
Saturday night every week. What What
does that mean? You know, what does that
Doesn't matter if you've been going
live. You're on my live stream right
now. So, why are you on my live on a
Saturday night? The same question goes to you.
Same [ __ ] question goes to you.
>> Right back at you.
>> Yeah, it means I've got no life. Well,
you're on it texting me, so you must
have no life. Self- projecting. You're
on my live stream texting me, so you
must have no life. Yep. Projection.
Yep, that's you, Monti. No life. Yep,
that's your life. Who you're talking
about? Not even going to block you. I'm
going to give you a platform to
self-reflect on because I feel sorry for you. Self rejecting.
Not everyone's got the same life as you.
No woman. Yep. That's you. Baldi, you. M
you. No friends. You. Yep. Carry on
talking about yourself.
You're forgetting something.
Yep. Go a hairline. That's also you
talking about yourself on YouTube on a
Saturday night. What a sad overweight.
That's you again. Self projecting.
That's you. You're talking about
yourself. Everything is about yourselves.
Autistic, no woman overweight. That's
you. That's you. Bunters. Ugly people
that can't get off of YouTube.
Mate, listen. You're on YouTube on a
Saturday night self projecting because
you got nothing. Literally, that's your
life. Come on. Tell us about your life.
Autistic, overweight, no woman, no
friends. Yep. That's your life. Keep
talking about yourself. Keep typing
about yourself. I'm not going to block
you. Tell us all about you.
Yep, that's you again. Keep talking about yourself.
No life. Can't take a day off of
YouTube. I'm I'm going to listen for
you. No life. Can't take a day off of
YouTube. Too ugly to show your face
because you know you're a manta. I'm
listing some. I'm helping you out here.
Come on, man. You must know about your
own [ __ ] life. You know what I'm saying?
You've never had a woman. Peter Bell has
been seen with more women than you, more
money than you, more friends than you. I
say that when I'm looking down. Peter
Belly's been seen with all of these
things. And the fact that you're sat on
YouTube on Saturday talking to me, it
proves you're a loser. You can't get off
of YouTube. Self- projecting.
Self [ __ ] projecting.
Yep. That's you. Never had a girlfriend.
I've had a girlfriend. Talking about yourself again.
Talking about yourself. Self projecting.
Self-reflecting his own life onto me.
That's Listen, why don't you come on
camera right now and show everyone what
you look like? Would you join the panel?
Would you join the panel? You won't cuz
you're too much of an ugly bastard.
You're an ugly manta. That's why you
can't come in and show your face because
you're an ugly bastard. Exactly. You m
[ __ ] off you ma. You can't show your
face cuz you're an ugly bastard. You're
a manta. That's why you can't show your
ugly face. You're just going to break
everyone's screen, bro. I'll send you
the link, bro. Anytime, man.
There we go. Come on, you fat ugly bun.
No, I'm not mad. I want to show everyone
the manta. Are you going to join or not?
You can't cuz you're too fat and ugly.
You can't even join the link. You
anxious little boy. You anxious little
boy. You anxious little keyboard
warrior. You can't even join the link.
You anxious, terrified little keyboard
warrior. You can't even join. No, you're
not backstage. No, you're not. Do you
want me to screen record?
Mate, you're not backstage. Do you want
me to screen record it? Okay, I will
screen record it now. Right,
you're not backstage, you bun. Right,
let me screen record this. Hold on. This
guy is not trying to join at all. Selfector.
This fat ugly [ __ ] that can't get off of
YouTube is definitely not backstage.
Where is it? Hold on. You [ __ ]
There we go. Screen recording now. So,
show everyone that you're not backstage.
Why do you get off of YouTube, you
[ __ ] fat ugly pig? Go get a life.
When are you going to get a life, man?
When are you going to get a life, you
fat ugly pig?
Right. There we go. When are you going
to get a life, you fat ugly pig? Get off
of YouTube. Go get laid.
You [ __ ] [ __ ]
Going to ban you now. Anyways, I'm going
in the chat. Bye-bye. Get off of YouTube
and stop self projecting, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] Go get a life
whilst you still come.
That's good, is it? Yeah, man.
No, no, no, no. One second.
What the [ __ ] Same reason you can't get
off of YouTube.
Yeah. Same reason you can't get off of YouTube.
You [ __ ] [ __ ]
Same reason you can't get off of YouTube, matey.
I mean, I'm on YouTube cuz I'm not going
out tonight. I'm [ __ ] chilling
playing some Franklin.
Is that a problem, mate?
You can't get off your YouTube.
I know, man. And the last time I went to
your area, you didn't turn up. So, we're
evens, aren't we, lad?
Like the last time I went to your area
and you didn't show up. Remember that time? Uh,
but quite well, actually.
I went to your area and you didn't turn up.
The last time I went to your area,
I haven't been back since, to be honest.
Had no reason to. You remember when I
went to your area, you didn't show up?
Oh, you're funny, man. You really are funny. Yeah.
When you Terry, when are you going to get alive?
I mean, I don't need to do this [ __ ]
again where I come off of YouTube for
two, three weeks. I've already done it
before and when I've come back, you
people have been on here every day. I
don't need to do it again.
But if you really want me to,
your life is better than mine, Terry.
Okay. You're a [ __ ] You're ugly.
You can't even afford a new pair of
trainers. I don't think your life is
better than mine, Terry.
I really don't think your life is better
than mine. I mean, you can't even afford
a new pair of trainers,
Terry. You Your life is not better than
mine, Timmy. Your life is not better
than mine, mate.
No. No. Your life is really really not
better than mine, son. Trust me on that
one. Trust me on that one, son.
You're a [ __ ] You're ugly.
You can't even afford a new pair of trainers.
Nah, mate. Your life ain't better than
mine. Trust me.
You know, if you tried going to a pub or
some sort of bar, they'd [ __ ] bully
you, mate. They'd bully you [ __ ] off.
Do you know what I'm saying? Your life
is not better than mine, mate. Trust me, it isn't.
Yeah, you are single. Yeah, you are single,
Terry. You are single.
You don't even have kids. You make up
lies that you got [ __ ] kids when you
don't even have kids.
You are You are the biggest mug. You're
a [ __ ] idiot. [ __ ] you can't even
afford a new pair of trainers. You that
skin. [ __ ] hell, man.
You will always be single. That's your life.
[ __ ] me, man.
>> You know I've got a second channel,
Terry, right? That no one knows about.
Yeah, really, Terry.
Are you the one stalking me on Reddit?
We all know. Yeah. That like [ __ ]
if I was to turn up, you wouldn't show
up, Terry. We all know that. I could say
me, you, LT, and Mark Samson would show
up. And the only ones that would show up
is me and LT. We know this. You know we
[ __ ] know this, mate.
You don't have a life, Terry. Shut up.
You ain't got a life.
You ain't got a life, baby.
I'm just [ __ ] in bed chilling, man. I
can't be bothered to go out today. [ __ ] that.
going Thailand in November. Terry, you
bet you're jealous. I bet you wish it
was you going.
Then I'm gonna go on holiday next summer.
You can't afford these things, can you, Terry? No.
Oh, [ __ ] sake.
So, why didn't you show up last time I went?
Okay. So, why didn't you show up the
last time I went to your area when
you're the one that called me out?
Okay, I didn't show up. I admit that.
So, why didn't you show up?
What do you want to that then? H
spot to Antman in a while. Terry
Yeah. Okay. So, you're a [ __ ] that we
all laugh at. And do you know why I keep
coming back on it? Because you you laugh
at yourselves. That's the whole point,
lad. Like, you you laugh at yourselves.
That's why I come back. Because if you
really bullied anyone, they wouldn't
come back, you know? Like at school if
someone's being bullied they like Terry
you can't laugh at anyone. You're a
[ __ ] You're skinn you're ugly. You
couldn't laugh at anybody. That's why we
come back because it's funny because you
couldn't laugh at anyone. Terry, you
could not laugh at anybody at all. Like
you met me and you couldn't even do
anything. You lost the [ __ ] fight for
[ __ ] sake. I ran across the [ __ ]
road and you couldn't even beat me and
then you walked off. We all listen. We
all know why. We all know why you didn't
come out last time. Because you knew you
was going to get beat. Just admit it.
You knew that you was going to get beat.
That's why you didn't come out. It's
It's f Listen listen.
It's the same as Lord Jay. Let me let me
let me digest this to you. Yeah. When
you met me, you thought that you was
going to win. You didn't win. You knew
you couldn't beat me regardless who won.
You knew you couldn't beat me, right?
And that's why when I came to your area,
you did not come out cuz you knew you
weren't going to win. Simple. That's
simp. It's the same as L J, right? With
L J. He didn't think anyone was going to
answer the door. He didn't think anyone
was going to stand up to him. He didn't
think anyone was going to try and meet
him again. And because you match the
same energy, that's why he doesn't he
would never come for me ever again
because he know he knows he won't win.
Simple. Just like you know you won't
win. That's why you did not come out
when I last went to your area,
you know. So, it's it's simple. Okay.
Okay. If that Okay. If that's the case,
right? If you beat me, you wouldn't have
called me out again and didn't show up.
So, uh why? Because the black guy was
saying, "Oh, yeah. No, no, no, no." So,
I said, "Okay, we'll get him off me
then." Simple. You did not beat me.
Everybody knows that you didn't beat me, mate. Oh [ __ ]
So yeah, that's why cuz you knew you
weren't going to win,
Terry. Terrible traders.
That's why you knew you weren't going to win.
So you could never beat me, matey.
You could never beat me. Never, never, Potter.
I was begging strangers for help. The
guy come over because he came over, you
know. That's it,
Timmy. That's it. You could never beat me, man.
You could never beat me, mate. Never.
Nah. You're like the skint virgin
living and out of London.
You know what I mean, mate?
That's what you're like. That's what
you're like, Terry, mate. Yeah.
And what's your problem with people
talking about kids? Isn't that what you
wanted is people to talk about kids? I
mean, you like the reaction. Don't you
troll for a reaction.
So, I don't really We need to get to the
bottom of this [ __ ] really because
um he showed me £13,000. Um I've showed
more than that. And also £13,000 is
nothing to say for 3 years. And in them
three years, I was living a better life
than him. better restaurants, better
women, better travel history, better
clothes, £13,000 in three years is no
money at all.
So, I mean, I don't know why you're
going on like it's a million pounds.
£13,000 for 3 years and not living life
is not a good amount to save. So,
I mean, bro, no one cares whether it was
13 grand or not. That's [ __ ] for 3
years to save for 3 years, bro. I could
save that £13,000. I could save realistically
like being realistic. Realistic
like being 100% real.
Probably about 7 months.
I could probably get that in about six,
seven months. Yeah, I'm only joking.
About six, seven months. Not 3 years,
bro. Three years of not living life to
get 13 grand is not worth it. It's not
even worth a year's life experience, lad.
Terry, Terry, Terry, £13,000.
Do not live life for 3 years is no money, right?
Back in my garden days, I used to spend about
3,000 a month, 4,000 a month.
Trust me, mate, it's not really a lot of money.
I mean, it's a decent amount of money.
£13,000. So, you just won £13,000.
Well, it's nowhere near as much as
you're making out to me. Anyone would
think the [ __ ] showed [ __ ] a billion pound.
So, okay. Okay. Did Virgin Boy show
restaurant? Did Virgin Boy show designer
clothes? Did Virgin Boy show
him to places?
[ __ ] no he did not. I did. So what
what's your [ __ ] point? You know
I could get 13 grand in about 6 months
if I wanted to. It's not even a joke,
bro. Seriously, it's not even a joke.
Yeah, about about that.
About six, seven months.
Uh, it's part of life experience.
The guy's not even ever He's never even
been to Scotland. The only place he's
been to is [ __ ] Amsterdam. Just cuz I
went there. He copied He copied me. Little copycat.
Little copycat. I want to tickle him,
you know. I really want to tickle him.
Give him a little tickle. Little copycat.
You know, he's a copycat. [ __ ] off,
Terry. He's a copycat. You went
Amsterdam just cuz I went there. [ __ ]
skin bastard. Skin [ __ ] bastard.
You know what I mean? [ __ ] right off.
You know what I mean? I know. I didn't
care about 13,000 [ __ ] pound. You
know what? [ __ ] 13,000 [ __ ] pound.
It's cuz these stupid people kept
spamming my live stream. That's why I
[ __ ] reacted to them. You [ __ ]
idiot. You know.
Yeah. Living on benefits. You don't know
how much money I have. You don't know
how much money I have. You do not know
how much money I have. I can get money
whenever I want. I can make money
whenever I want. You don't know
anything. And bro, you showed Bro, I
showed Bro, we're not talking about six
grand, bro. You've been shown money multiple times.
No. 13 grand never almost had me crying
because it's not a big amount of money.
It's not a big amount of [ __ ] money
to have to have not lived life. He did
not live life for 3 years in order to
get that money. I would not trade a year
of my life experiences for £13,000.
Do you understand? I will not trade a
year's life experiences, let alone three
years of life experiences. Cuz think of
it, right? You know, on my phone, I've
got places that I've traveled to where
I've gone to, restaurants that I've been
to. Yeah. That'll take to the grave with
me if I die tomorrow. Why am I going to
trade that for 13 grand even for a year?
Bro, come on. It's not worth it. Um,
so I've got so much [ __ ] on [ __ ] I
hate the fact people have a girlfriend.
You talk polics and I hate the fact
people have a girlfriend and a life.
Well, he has a disabled girlfriend who I
would never get with even if I was 20
Guinnesses down. So, no, I don't hate
the fact that someone's got a disabled
girlfriend who doesn't [ __ ] I promise
you I'm not jealous of some [ __ ] that's
got no teeth with a disabled girlfriend.
It really really doesn't make me hate
anything. I I assure you, mate. I It
really really doesn't make me hate
anything to be honest with you, mate. I
would never get with anything as ugly as
that. You know, it's the same as um
Monty was trying to say about how I
can't get laid. I said, "Listen, I I
said this to him earlier. I was like,
"Bro, the two women that you've been
with are stinking.
I would not go near any of them. 20
Guinnesses [ __ ] down. They are
[ __ ] ugly. Natalie G, Kaye, they're
both [ __ ] ugly hoes. I'd rather have nothing.
I'd rather be a [ __ ] virgin. I'm I'm
not even just saying it. Do you know?
You know what I'm saying? So, yeah.
Why the [ __ ] would I be jealous of a
virgin with no teeth and no money living
in a [ __ ] bedit? What the [ __ ] man? Jesus Rust.
Why the [ __ ] would I move to [ __ ] America?
You know what this guy on Reddit told me
to do? He said you should go to America,
right? And you will do damage with that
[ __ ] You want me to live in America?
You want me to move to America? Well,
mate, if I live in my mom's spare room,
at least I don't live in a bedsit. I'd
rather live in a spare good room than
live in a bedsit.
I'd rather have a nice life nice life experiences,
live in a lovely room, and not live in a
bedsit. That's better than living in a
bedsit. It's a It's a spare room. It's a
room. Yeah, it's better than a shitty
bedit with no bed in it. But uh yeah,
you could not uh pay me to um live in America.
Like I you couldn't even pay me to live
there. [ __ ] America.
Them stuck up westernized [ __ ]
[ __ ] that. I can't I can't stand
Americans. You could not pay me to [ __ ]
to to live there, mate.
And I don't think anyone's going to be
doing any damage with any accent, you know?
I would [ __ ] Oh, [ __ ] that. You're
going off them in London.
[ __ ] that, bro. Jesus Christ.
I've traveled more than you, Terry. I've
got more of a life experience than I've
got more life experiences than Terry.
Terry's never even been abroad.
Everybody. Yeah. Terry's not even been abroad.
Isn't that right, Terry?
Isn't that right? You've never been a brood.
Yeah. Terry's never been abroad. Oh, [ __ ]
No, no, no. Uh, how comes you've never
been abroad, Terry? Huh?
How come you've never been abroad?
I'm actually um going to go to Miami
next uh year,
but not if that [ __ ] is there. If that
[ __ ] is actually there living there, I'm
not going. I'll just pick another
destination. I'm not [ __ ] going where
that [ __ ] slaggers. [ __ ] that.
That [ __ ] stupid Syrian [ __ ] slag.
Get what I mean, Terry? [ __ ] Yeah.
[ __ ] that. If that [ __ ] is [ __ ]
there, I'm not [ __ ] going. [ __ ] that.
No, I'm not I'm not doing that. I'm
actually trying to actually go on holiday.
Yeah, I'm actually trying to go on holiday.
You you understand me? So, I'll just
pick somewhere else. [ __ ] the Syrian
slag. [ __ ] scat [ __ ] [ __ ] that, you know.
Yeah, I'm definitely definitely um
booking another holiday
next week for
go to Iceland.
Why would I go there?
That's so you silly goose.
You silly goose. Why am I going to go
there? You silly case.
skin in the bed [ __ ] with no bed and no
f money in it.
I'll wake up the whole [ __ ]
neighborhood. Me, mate. I don't give a [ __ ]
See, the thing is, Terry, I'm badass.
Who the [ __ ] is that? You're not coming
in, you skint virgin.
[ __ ] off you skint virgin. You shitty
little bedsick with your 13 g bum
change. [ __ ] off, you silly gun.
Go get a bed and go get some teeth, you
skin ugly bastard. You're not coming in.
Leave me alone. Go [ __ ] your fat ugly
disabled girlfriend. You horrible [ __ ]
Leave me alone. [ __ ] off.
Don't buy a bed, you skin bastard. You
skin [ __ ] you. [ __ ] off.
[ __ ] leave me alone.
You horrible skin bastard.
I'm upset now. Yeah. Funk.
Why does the mods keep banning me on
Reddit, Steven Howard?
They fear different opinions.
They're so power hungry.
They're power hungry.
No, I don't post like that anymore. I
just I just slide into people's DMs and
they just ban me. They ban you from uh your IP.
So what I do is the people I speak to, I
just ask them if they've got like
Instagram or something and then we just
talk on Insta because there's no point
being on a platform, Terry, where mods
need to have power.
Are you still talking about us? Izzy USA
is you [ __ ] virgin. [ __ ] off. Just
cuz you never had sex with Britney and
she rejected your ugly ass, you ugly
[ __ ] And that's why you had to make up
some suicide stories.
You think everyone's not had sex with
people just cuz Britney rejected your ugly ass? Ugly Sarah.
He's putting his ugly girlfriend up. Yuck. Yuck.
Two uglies together in a bedit skin.
E, turn the camera off. I don't want to
see that ugly the wolf. I know the
correction is you never had sex with
Britney cuz she rejected your ugly ass.
She didn't want to know. She didn't want
to know. You, you ugly bastard.
You know what I mean?
Uh, I've already had a girlfriend and
I've had sex more times and no, I think
he's a virgin because he is a big virgin.
I know him better than he knows. his [ __ ] self.
>> Listen, mate, he is a virgin. That
autistic broken dick has never been up
no [ __ ] woman, mate. Because if it
[ __ ] did, why do you think he
messages all of my ex hookups for sex
material? Because he's never had sex.
He's like a horny child. Cuz he's never
popped it. He's still a virgin. And I
don't care how many times he shows his
disabled girlfriend, that's no proof
that he's had sex. I have proven I've
I've actually proved I've had sex. I've
not just showed a disabled girl multiple
times. You're on the [ __ ] stand,
Harry. I've shown real evidence, mate.
I've shown real evidence, not a disabled
Dell and claimed I've had sex, you know,
proper hardcore evidence, you know, for saying
no, he he contacts them cuz he's a
jealous bastard. Cuz he's jealous of me
and I could pull them and he can't cuz he's ugly.
He he bullies me. I had him [ __ ]
scared to go to an event for 3 weeks.
Terry, I bullied him so bad. I had him
crying to the police. They weren't a
fire and I had him scared to leave his
house for three weeks. That's not
something that bullies me, son.
I literally had him crying to the police
screaming he weren't a fighter. No one's
had me running to the police, mate,
scared to go somewhere for three [ __ ] weeks.
No one has made me scared to go to my
events for three weeks crying to the
police. No one has ever done that to me.
Because no one's bullied me, Terry.
Just like when I've gone to your area
and you couldn't show up cuz I bullied
you in your own [ __ ] area.
Terry, I've been speaking about him for
[ __ ] whenever I want to. I made him
scared to go to an event for 3 weeks.
That person does not bully me, Terry.
Just like you don't [ __ ] bully me. I
went to your area. You didn't even come
out cuz you were too scared. Remember
that time, Terry? I went to your area.
your ends and made you scared to come
out. Same as I did with the virgin. But
like we say, like we know he would lie.
I'm saying he went to the police on me
cuz he couldn't handle me. He couldn't
handle me bullying him on YouTube like
you. He had nothing left in him.
No fight left. He was so much of a loser
that he had to get the police involved
cuz I owned his ass hard. I made him so
scared to leave his house you have to go
to the police on me. Imagine being that
much of a [ __ ] loser that you got
bullied so hard on YouTube that you got
no fight left in you.
You had to go to the police. What a
[ __ ] loser. I could never imagine
being that much of a loser. Just like you, Terry.
Just like you, bro. He had to do, bro.
He had to go to the police.
because I owned him. I bullied him so
badly he had to get the police involved.
I bullied him so bad that he had to get
law enforcement because he couldn't
handle the ass whooping. Think about it.
Two people are arguing on YouTube and
one's getting bullied so badly that they
had to go to the police cuz they can't
take it no more. They got bullied so
badly, so much of a loser, they had no
fight left in them. So they had to go to the police.
Imagine being that much of a loser. I
could never imagine being bullied that
badly, bro. Cuz YouTube has always been
YouTube to me, son. No one's ever had me
running to the police screaming I'm not
a fighter. No one's ever [ __ ] had me
being scared of going to events cuz I'm
so much of a scared loser. You know what
I'm saying, mate?
Exactly, mate. Exactly, mate. Yeah. Yeah,
that's it, man.
I love it, mate.
Yeah, I love it, mate. Love it.
I love it, bro. So, I literally
absolutely skin. Talking about yourself,
we don't have self injectors earlier.
Um, so you were saying about how uh I've
got um I I disabled the comments. No, I
Do you want me to answer your question?
Bro, I disable the comments because you
people repeat yourselves. You say the
same old [ __ ] You self-reflect. We
don't want your shitty self-p projecting
comments on our videos.
I mean, you're repeating and you're self-projecting.
Nobody wants that on the [ __ ]
channel. For [ __ ] sake. If you really
bullied me, you would have come on my
address and you would have done
something. You know, you know where I
[ __ ] lived enough times. We block the
comments because we don't want you
self-reflecting mongos on our [ __ ]
channel. For [ __ ] sake. We don't want
you self-rejecting fat ugly people that
can't get off of YouTube on our channel.
Just like now you're blocked. Bye-bye.
See you later. as a certain person would
say. You know what I'm saying? We block
you because you self-reflect and you
repeat yourselves. What do you want me
to do? Leave you on there? What? What do
you want me to do? Let you keep ruining
the channel. [ __ ] hell, mate. We have
to block you.
You know what makes me laugh? Yeah. Is
when you say that you you people block
you and they're blocking you because
you're bullying them, but yet you've
known where I've lived for god knows how
long and you ain't done nothing. I'm not
telling you to do something, but I'm
just saying it just it just seems a bit funny, right?
You people are obsessed with me. You
really, really are obsessed and jealous
of me, mate.
Can you have a normal conversation,
Terry? I'm saying that he's a
virgin because he is a [ __ ] virgin.
Not because I can get a girlfriend or I
can't get a [ __ ] girlfriend. Jesus
[ __ ] Christ, you know.
Jesus Christ, mate. [ __ ]
Hold on a minute.
Don't lie to me. I could never get the
number you do on here. No one would
watch him. Yeah, of course, man.
Cuz all he goes on about is [ __ ] me.
So, no one is going to go on the [ __ ]
channel, are they?
Ah, [ __ ] hell, mate. If you have to
go to [ __ ]
the police over YouTube, you know you've
been bullied, mate. When you have to go
to you you went to the police over me
cuz I owned you that badly. What a
loser. What a [ __ ] loser, mate.
And so what the [ __ ] So they say that
I can't say his name anymore. I don't
want to say his [ __ ] name, the
[ __ ] obsessed virgin. That bell
condition done me good because I don't
want to talk about the [ __ ] virgin.
That's good then, isn't it? If I can't
say their name, then that's good, isn't
it? Because I don't want to talk about
the virgin cuz I'm obsessed.
So that's that's that's a good thing
then, isn't it, mate?
Yeah, that's a good thing. So, yeah.
Oh, Timmy, you going to join? Are you? I like Timmy. Yeah.
It's Tibby time. I like Timmy. Yeah.
>> You argue with Natalie G. You called her
a slag, didn't you?
>> Yeah, she's a proper slag.
She's a prostitute. PJ, get it right.
>> Yeah. One second. Hold on. I can't believe
you know Mongol. Mongol was on the one.
PJ, he do knows the vi out for his
arrest for his [ __ ] um was it at the
riots? Yeah. So, Mongol is on the one.
The more he's on the one, the further
the sentence is. So, where is Mongol?
>> Yeah. Can you hear me? Yeah.
>> Yes. Where's Mongol?
>> I don't know.
>> He's on the one. We need him arrested.
>> Listen, you and Money Michael are pair of [ __ ]
>> No, no, no, no, no. The corn is
definitely on the one.
>> Oh, PJ, I'm gonna get this [ __ ]
autism out of you. I'm going to
>> We're going to put you in the [ __ ]
>> Listen, Mike. Listen to me.
>> Meet you in Blackpool.
>> Listen, Mike. I've got more money than
you will ever have. So, when you sit
there trying to talk about me being
scared, bro, you don't know what money PJ
>> Michael, you only know about your own
life. I will show you some money in the PJ.
>> What you saying flacker?
>> What you saying?
>> Listen, money Mike, you're skinned, bro.
You're the one that's skinned. I've seen your comments.
>> I'm skinn. Okay. If he's had about 15
points today and he's had a [ __ ]
luxury weekend on the house
>> and he's still got money.
>> You're both scared.
>> Come on, Flacker. Come on. I know you're like,
>> "You're skinny.
>> Stop being nasty, son.
>> You're skinned, Michael. You're right.
And I don't know what's going on. Flacker,
>> what's going on is your skin, Michael.
>> I'm skinn.
>> Yeah, man.
>> Bro, you're in the bed seat. Show me a grand then.
>> Bro, I've already showed over £1,000
multiple times, brother. Every single
time you get show money, you run away.
So, get out of here, man. I've got way
more than a grand. You don't know how
much money I have, bro. Yeah.
>> So, when you was with Monty in
Birmingham, right, let's let's get it right. >> Yeah.
>> Right. No, I'm talking to you on the
>> Yeah, I'm talking
like a boy cuz your mouth runs away with
you. I didn't say it again when I was in
my gave you a chance.
>> Hear me out. I gave you a chance when I
met you. I thought he's not that bad,
right? People Yeah, he says this and he says that.
>> Like a lot of people do it, but they
don't go on YouTube doing it or whatever
opinions they've got. They don't do
that. But what I'm saying to you is
right when you met Monty, right? Why did
you go and meet Monty? What's all that about?
>> What? Because you was crying over
Natalie G and I was and I was friends
with him at the time. So what?
>> They're laughable. Do you think them two
are ever going to last? He's a druggie
and a [ __ ] indust.
>> I know that. Well, I know that deep. He
probably gives her all his money, right? >> Yeah.
>> You've got a deep obsession, right, with
saying people are skink. You don't know
if people what what money
>> you don't. You're the one saying that I was skinn
you. That's your opinion, right? All
right, then. I'm skin. I'll own it. I've
done a lot,
>> bro. You You're the one that started it.
>> Yeah, well, I'm owning it like a man, right?
>> I'm seeing your comments and you don't
know how much money I have. So, what
you're saying doesn't make no sense.
>> See, see, hang on a minute. This is
where you're going with comments, right?
You you you could get someone comment
that could clone the account and you'll
think that's them,
>> right? It's your account
was on YouTube. way before.
>> But you, it was your channel cuz you was
making videos, you idiot.
>> Well, hang on. Hear me out. We know how
it works, right? All this [ __ ] women,
you know, I'm going to do this with
women and that needs to stop, right? I'm
trying to talk to you on a level cuz I
think there's something inside you on a
good day where you actually do [ __ ]
listen, right? And people hate me for
that, but I'll say how it is.
>> When I met you, I didn't think you was
that bad. The minute you got out of
[ __ ] Birmingham, you're saying, "Oh,
they met me buy cocaine. They made me
pay for everything."
>> I said Timmy did. I didn't switch on
you. I switched on Timmy. Right. No, no,
no. I switched on Timmy cuz he Cuz he
was I never said you. I said Timmy. So get
>> Okay. Okay. But you made a big thing of
Oh, we never forced anything on nothing.
I thought we had a good time.
>> Yeah, we did. But Timmy didn't
put his hand in his pocket.
>> Say that again.
>> Yeah, we did. But Timmy didn't put his
hand in his pocket. Yeah, but PJ PJ when
people are gamblers, mate, right? Real
gamblers. I'm not about these imbeciles
what they sit there and the flex of
mommy and daddy's money and go on about
all this, right? Real gamblers, right?
Where one minute you've got [ __ ] a
tin of beans and then the next minute
you're [ __ ] five grand up and you're
in the room, right? You you've got a lot
to learn. I don't think you're a bad
kid, but all this oh your sister's kids.
Oh, this this and that. Like you that is
a bit extreme from you and you wouldn't
ever say snaking me on his channel.
That's why I went for you. You seem to
forget what you've done as well.
>> Yeah, I've done my fair share back in
the day with you. I learned that
>> I started the war, man. You had a bit of
war and that's it. But from then, like
the last time I was speaking to you, I
thought [ __ ] hell. In all these
years, he's actually some has woke up
with him. He's actually trying, right? I
was being fair with you and cuz I
weren't getting back to you. Like you
was a bit like a woman to be honest.
You was because women are like that.
like non-stop. I can't get back to calls
and that you don't understand. I live a
very fast lifestyle. Okay? And that's
all I'm going to say to you, right? You
want to go on about all these stupid
YouTube games. Look, if you want to be a
man's man and meet us and we'll have a
drink with you. How's about that? That's
my offer to you. If you want to have a
we'll have a If you want to have a
drink, we'll have a drink. It's it's the
ball's in your court. Right. That ain't
me thinking I'm this and I'm that
because I'm not. I'm just a normal guy.
>> Right. There you go. Enjoy your
>> I accept.
>> All right, mate.
>> We got to go anyway. Anyway, PJ
>> PJ, YouTube is [ __ ] you up. You need
a break, lad. Just take it like a laugh
like us, dude. They keep saying we
finished and we keep taking the piss out the country.
>> I don't Yeah, but Timmy, I don't think
Monty Man's funny.
>> Monty man's a [ __ ] nunch, bro. You
know that. I know that. He had a
teenager that I can't I don't bully
people for no reason. He's a wrong gun,
PJ. And you're a wrong gun. And take it
like a man. and take some responsibility.
Anyway, we are see you in a bit. She's
still live. When we get back, we're
going to buy 18 cans of Stella. We'll join you. Michael Basset.
Michael Basset. A mad man. Oh, [Laughter]
I would have said disappear. Hold on. [Laughter]
I'm not tempted to go out, Bob. And do
you know why I'm not tempted to go out?
Because it's the same old [ __ ] every
time I go out.
That's why I'm not tempted.
Cuz it's always the same with [ __ ]
women here. Yep.
But yeah, go out, bro. If you're tempted
to go out, go out.
What's the [ __ ] time? 8:30.
Yeah, go go go out, bro. If you want to
go out, go out.
If you want to go out, go out, man.
What's the problem?
I beat uh Michael and Timmy and have
some beer with them.
Do you reckon I should go go beat them?
[ __ ] hell, man.
No, I wouldn't be seen dead anywhere
with Timmy, man. [ __ ] me.
I can't stop [ __ ] laughing. Timmy, [Laughter]
I can't stop laughing at Timmy. Yeah.
What is that?
Oh man, what are we going to do, lads?
What are we going to do?
Go to Birmingham and meet [ __ ]
And I never said anything about Michael.
I said stuff about [ __ ] Timmy because
he didn't put his hand in his pocket. Yeah,
I couldn't be seen with [ __ ] Timmy,
man. I can't. He is a [ __ ] He is a
[ __ ] but he's something to laugh at, you know. [Music] Mark.
I'm speaking to someone here.
What do you want to stand?
Um, the curry, the rice, and the chicken was £13
something. £13 something.
No, no, no, no. Yeah, it was nice, man.
No. No, no, no, no. Burden boy.
Do women ignore
Stephen Howard. Do women ignore?
Yes, they do.
They are [ __ ]
90% of other men. Yeah, man.
You like it when Peter Betty's out
drinking in the clubs, don't you, Steven Howard?
You like that, don't you?
I'm going to go in a bit anyways.
just speaking to someone.
No, not Monty, bro. Not Monty. [ __ ] him.
Oh, Monty wants the box.
He wants the box. [Laughter]
He's not even trying to join. What the [ __ ]
>> Sorry, P. Yeah, I don't
You know what I should do? I should just
go to Birmingham and go on Timmy's side. Yeah.
Go on Timmy's side and call him out in it.
Yeah. I might as well it Yeah. Yeah, Stephen Howard.
Skin the bed she with absolutely no bed
and no money in it. You drove me [ __ ] mad.
No bed and no money in it.
Absolutely no bed and absolutely no
money in it.
No, no money.
You're not coming. Timmy, join.
I might come to Birmingham. We can own um Mony.
What do you think of that, Timmy? He's
pissing me off.
I might come to Birmingham. [Music]
You know what I'm saying? Yeah. All
right, Timmy. I might come to
Birmingham. We can own that [ __ ]
What do we think? Next Saturday,
we can go home now. [ __ ]
Timmy Monty's like, "Oh, I know you live
at your mom's, bro. Even if I live at my
mom's, what the [ __ ] are you going to do about it?"
Okay, so I live at my mom's and what are
you going to do about it?
I live at my mom's. What are you going
to do about it? [ __ ] idiot. Yeah. Do Yep. [ __ ] no.
You must be
What is this? What's up?
One second. I'm speaking to someone. Dude, [Applause]
Well, I'm gone yet. I'll be back.