right?
Let Monty join a [ __ ]
Monty, you're a [ __ ] baldy bastard.
Come and join the [ __ ] panel.
All right, I'll [ __ ] meet you.
[ __ ] introduce me to that [ __ ]
Virgin Camp, that skin version.
You know why does everyone got to
[ __ ] go to you all the [ __ ] time?
You know enough, mate.
You're in the box. This guy.
There you go.
Well, let's see if this con joins.
So he look and he's scared.
>> Oh [ __ ]
All right. Is he Are you joining or what?
I really want to ask you some [ __ ] questions. Yeah,
I need to ask you some questions, Monty.
I'm trying to get Monty to join this bastard [ __ ]
hanger. I need to ask him some questions.
He's not um right Yeah.
know why he introduced me to that
[ __ ] virgin [ __ ]
You know what I mean? Grieves. I want to
know why he [ __ ] he introduced me to
the [ __ ] skin in a bed suit with no
bed, no [ __ ] money in it. You know
what I'm saying? I just had a delicious
um Indian by the way, Grezy. It cost me
£20. Chicken ticker. Tandoori chicken
curry. Now I was going to think about it
before doing it. Grezy, I was thinking,
should I? Shall I? Should I? Shall I?
Should I? Shall I? But then I was like,
I'm not some [ __ ] skimp cut in a
bedit living and out of London, so I can
probably afford it. You understand,
Grezy? I'm not a skimp cut in a bedit
with absolutely no money. like some people understand mate.
guy is an absolute s on Reddit
dismissing my struggles. [ __ ] hell.
Why do they [ __ ]
Why do these people dismiss my
struggles, Greavvesy? I don't know why
they do that. It's weird.
This guy is sing defending women again.
Why is there so many [ __ ] white
knights and simps on [ __ ] Reddit? I
think white knights is a better term for
them to be fair. White Knights. Madness. Absolute madness. Yeah.
So many white knights on Reddit. Grezy,
do you agree with me? There's so many
white knight simps on Reddit. So I'm
showing this guy, right? um
conversations that I've had with these
women and where like they've just led me
on and wasted my time. And I was like,
"Oh, well, you didn't even get to know
them." I was like, "Well, I did. I
approached them. I got to know them. I
got their number and I tried to arrange
a date. Am I supposed to be talking to
people for 10 years or
am I supposed to be talking to people
for 10, 15 years? I don't I don't I don't understand.
Can Can someone help me out here? I'm
trying to They just make excuses for
women. It's [ __ ] ridiculous. Like
even though I've shown their [ __ ]
some of them dead asses waste my [ __ ]
time, you know,
talk to people for talk to people for a
month. But why would you speak to
somebody for a month? If you've approached somebody
and someone's replying, why would you
speak to somebody for a month? That
doesn't make no sense. You've already
met in person. What? Talk for a month
until they find someone better than you
or talk for a month until they lose
interest. You don't need to speak to
someone for a month if you've approached them.
There's there's no reason to speak to
somebody for a month. A week absolute
maximum if you've approached them. I'm
talking about actually approaching. I'm
not talking about someone you've met online.
They always use excuses. It's [ __ ]
They really, all they do is look for excuses. Madness.
had so many [ __ ] white knights.
There's a lot of [ __ ] white knights.
Isn't it greasy?
Well, you don't need to. Okay. But you
don't need to speak to somebody for a
month. If you've already approached them
and you've got their number,
you don't need to speak to someone for a
month. And a month is a long time to be
speaking to someone every day. Yeah, it
kind of is. It is quite a while to be
speaking to someone every day only for
them not to meet you in the end.
You don't need to speak to someone every
day. You've already met them in person.
You you you want to be meeting them
within about four or five days.
So, it's just another excuse. It's just
Anyways, we're not going over this. It's
just another excuse. Oh, you need to
speak to them longer and then you speak
to them longer and then they just [ __ ]
you around anyway. So, it's like it's
just another excuse. I don't even know.
I don't even know why we're talking about this.
Okay, but what about most of them that
don't even reply to the first message? I
mean, most of them don't even reply to
the first message. So,
I mean, it doesn't really matter, does it?
Because I've had people agree to meet me
and they haven't. So, all of this is
this nonsense talking about it to be honest. So,
There you go. I mean, most of them don't even reply.
And then when they do reply, they agree
to [ __ ] meet you. And then on the
[ __ ] day they're supposed to [ __ ] meet you.
I'm sick of the whole dating thing, bro.
I'm sick of it. That's why I don't go out anymore.
That's why I don't go out anymore, Greezy.
Because of this problem, you know.
But I am thinking of going out every week again
just to annoy Bomb because he thinks I
can't go out every week and I can't afford it.
So I might just go out every week just
to annoy him in it. We'll do Saturday
next week Friday the week after
Thursday. So we just do it to annoy him.
You know what I mean?
You know what I mean, mate? I could
easily do it and annoy him, but can't be bothered.
Be funny. It would be funny. [Music]
It would be funny, man. We had a laugh.
You know what I'm saying? believes they
Grezy, what are we doing this year, man?
Come on. You need to go abroad. You need
to go to Scotland.
Come on, Grezy. You're getting a You're
getting old, man.
You're getting [ __ ] old, lad.
Come on. How about me, you go Scotland
New Year's Eve?
I'm going to Scotland uh New Year's Eve,
Gezy. I'm booking the thing um soon, the
trains or the plane cuz it's going to be
a trying to get out there New Year's
Eve. If I haven't already booked
anything, we should go together New Year's Eve.
Might as well.
Let's go. Go to Scotland.
No, I want you to come with me.
Yeah, [ __ ] might as well. It give it a whirl. I would.
You might as well, Graves. I would give
it a whirl. I would.
I would. Would you? Yeah, I would.
Give it a while.
Give it a little try. [Music]
No, I never do you greasy. Me and you go way back.
Where's the [ __ ] skin in the bed with
[ __ ] no bed, no [ __ ] money in it?
>> All right, Lim.
>> What's up, PJ Big Man?
>> I'm all good, man. How are you?
>> Oh, I'm fabulous, man. Good, good, good to hear.
>> Listen, how do you conquer the vinderoo without crying?
>> Oh, I'm used to it, man. I'm used to it.
L, you know me.
>> I've been doing it for years, you know.
>> Oh my god.
>> Well, you can't have a vindaloo.
>> I never tried a vindaloo. I'm scared.
>> Have you tried a mad address?
>> Yeah, I had a mad address, man. Had a
mad address. That was spicy. I had to
wait. I had to wait. It was cold. I had
to wait. It was cold and then I chewed
>> Oh Jesus.
LMS, you need to um you need to order a
vindaluya, eat it, and video your
reaction and put on YouTube.
>> No, I'm going to cry. I'm going to cry,
>> bro. Do you know the worst thing I had
yet? It was called a um a Carolina
Reaper burger, bro. I had to sign a
leaf. Yeah. Before eating it. Almost
killed me, bro. Oh, it almost killed me,
>> Yeah, it was bad, bro. I decided to
[ __ ] leave. Oh, that's what you call hot.
>> Yeah. Uh,
I just I've got to ask PJ.
>> Yeah, man.
>> Have you ever worked?
>> Yeah, I've worked. Have you?
>> My CV is two pages, boy. >> Really? >> Yep.
>> But you're not working at a You're not
working. You're not working at the
minute, are you?
>> I'm in a rut right now. Like, I'm on
pip. Uh I think I last worked in 2023,
>> man. Do you know what though? That
that's fine, though. Like, at least you
own it. At least you're honest. Like,
that's what I respect, you know, man. Like,
at least you you're honest.
>> What did you come to Milton Kes for?
Oh, I went [ __ ] last time I was there
a couple of years ago. I just went to
the shopping center just look around,
bro. Ain't been for a few years.
>> I kind of thought they was here to pick
up some roids. >> Nah. >> Yeah.
>> Are you Do you live near the You live
near the shopping center, would it?
Um, it's about a 25m minute walk, but
there's this really bad there's this
really bad uh hill where people die and I don't
>> like the hill the the death hill.
>> Me and you should go out for Guinness.
>> We could.
>> Yeah, why not?
>> In Temple Ball, you ready?
>> Come to London, isn't it?
>> Come to London.
>> Yeah, man.
How old are you, LMS?
>> I was 36 the other week.
>> Really? I'm 27 this [ __ ] month. 28.
Sorry. This month 28 this month.
>> You haven't lived, man.
>> I like you. I like you, PJ, but you're [ __ ] man.
>> Like, how school?
>> Did you go to school? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Why haven't you got any friends?
>> I do have friends. You [ __ ] plonker.
>> Okay. Okay.
Monty doesn't have friends.
>> I don't need to talk to my friends. They
need to talk to me. You know what I'm saying?
>> Have you ever been to Have you ever you
you've been to Birmingham? Is it?
>> Um I've been to Manchester. Not
>> Yeah. I love Manchester, man. I'd love
to go again. I've been so many times. to
I've been to York. I've been to Bristol.
I've been to Brighton. I've been to Hunt
Stanton. I've been to uh [ __ ] Leeds.
I've been to London, obviously. I've
been Shepherd's Bush. I've been Camden.
I've been [ __ ] Westminster. I've been >> Scotland.
What's the area where What's the area where um
I can't even remember. I'm brain
damaged, man. I got brain damage,
>> bro. At least you at least you [ __ ]
um at least you've been places. You've
been to quite a few places to be fair.
>> Yeah. All I can say is if you
>> Yeah. If you want to live, go see your
favorite bands. Go do something. Just do
something. And right now, I am just fermenting online.
>> Have you been to Scotland?
>> Nah, I've been to Wales though.
>> Yeah, I've been Wales a few times.
Scotland. Cardiff's good, isn't it?
>> I wasn't. No, I never been to Scotland.
>> No, Cardiff.
>> Cardiff. I went to Rexom. is really far
away from there.
>> Yeah, that's North Wales.
>> Yeah, you should come to London, man.
Come to London next Saturday. We'll go
for some beers. >> PJ,
I don't want to be seen with you in public. >> What? >> Yeah. >> Why?
>> Uh nah. Uh are you ready? Are you ready
for a London stream? Yeah.
>> Have you ever heard of Carrie B? >> No.
>> Well, if I if I if I go if I go to
London if I go to London and do a live
stream, Carrie B is going to be there.
And you can be there, too, dude. You can
be there, too.
>> Yeah. Have a good time. Have a good
>> I mean, you should meet Timmy Aldridge.
Nah, you should smoke some of my zoot.
That's what you should do.
>> What are you drinking, Lens?
>> Gay [ __ ] >> Huh?
I'm drinking gay [ __ ]
Hey, look. I got this left. I I got this
left. This is the last. This is the pro
th This is it. This is it, bro.
>> Okay. How about this, Lens? How about
this, Lens? Right. I I'll come to Milton
KE next week. If I come, will you meet me?
>> I don't have any money, so no.
>> It doesn't matter, man. I I'll buy us
drinks. I've got the money sorted, bro.
It's not a problem.
>> I don't have any money.
>> You don't need money.
>> I can't I can't get to the location.
>> Well, I'll send you some money when I'm there.
>> Okay. Okay. We can be friends, you know,
like you can replace you can replace
Monty, man, because at least you're
cool. You know, you're not a snake, you know?
>> I'm not a snake, but I'm >> Exactly.
>> You're a cool dude.
>> I'm leaving. You grew me too hard this month.
>> No, Lambs. I'm being serious. Lambs.
I was actually going to come to Milton
Kes and we could go for some beers.
Oh, what a lovely site.
I'll come to your house, man.
Send me the address. I'll come round. Yeah,
Monty's watching, by the way.
What do you think of that, Greaves? And
me going to Le's house.
I don't know how he can drink beer out
of a can. I can't drink beer out of a can, bro.
I can drink it out of a glass bottle,
but no [ __ ] can. It's rank. Nah.
Nah. Mil ain't that far. It's about half
hour on the train. 40 minutes. It's not that far.
Me and him can get some [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah, I remember when I done I
went to Milton Kees to um do some
approaches. Do you remember when I went
around the shopping center? You might
not remember it, but
yeah, I I [ __ ] remember it. Yeah, man.
Oh, I want to smash Monty's face in so badly. Greasy.
[ __ ] I want to smash his face in, man.
The little [ __ ] snake, you know.
Lem says that he's got no money.
I want to smash his face in, bro.
[ __ ] annoy him.
He's saying, "Oh, at least I can get,"
Bro, I don't want to get laid by a manta.
Natalie G is a [ __ ] ma.
Isn't that right, Grey? Yeah, man.
I had an Indian, bro.
Yeah, I had a nice Indian.
You had McDonald's yesterday, Grezy.
Well, early early. hours this morning
and it was not. Bro, the nuggets made me feel sick. [ __ ] burning.
Where's the [ __ ] skin virgin? He's
not been on YouTube, has he?
The skin [ __ ] Huh? Yeah.
Oh, it's skin virgin in the bedit.
Skid bird in the bed. No bed, no money. Virgin
that little saying
you [ __ ] skin. I'll throw you.
I'll throw you high skin bastard.
Yeah, I've got a big problem with Joseph
F. When he comes back on here, I'll tell him.
Joe F. We're going to call him Joseph F.
I can't believe he thinks that saving
£13,000 in three years is good.
That's [ __ ] skintlin. Grezy,
that's skint [ __ ] skint flint.
And you know it, Grezy as well. You know
it's skinting skin flint.
You [ __ ] sh P your little B with no
bed. No money in there. You know,
seriously, do you reckon Virgin boy is
ever going to finally get laid?
I I think he'll die me. What do you guys think?
You're the one that gets no women.
That's why you have to [ __ ] No, it's
not a lot of money, Bob.
£13,000 really isn't that much money,
mate. True ask me. Is it not to save for
3 years? Is it mate?
Really? It'd last you about 6, 7 months,
mate. It's not a lot of money, mate.
No, mate. Not a lot of money, mate. No,
it's not a lot of money.
That would go in like six, seven months.
I'm not even joking. I used to spend
about three four grand a month easy
gambling, drinking, designer clothes.
Trust me, bro.
It's not that much money. Not to say for
3 years. Think about it, right? If you
done nothing for 3 years. Yeah.
Say you done nothing for 3 years, bro.
just to get 13 grand.
Think about it.
It's really not a lot of money. It's not life changing, you know?
I mean, you've seen how quickly money
goes, right? I had
like seven grand. I think I had the
most. I think I've had is about seven
grand. And mate, when you're drinking,
gambling, escorts, buying a line of
clothes, it goes, it [ __ ] goes, mate. You know,
goes, goes and goes, you know,
13,000 is not a lot of money. You have
had no life experiences. And I don't
need to be jealous. I've got better
clothes than him. I'm better looking
You know, I've had more life
experiences. Nothing to be jealous of,
mate. Trust me. [ __ ] trust me. Life
is all about life experiences.
And having none for 3 years for the sake
of 13 grand. Nah. Nah, mate. M it Yeah. 13,000.
It wouldn't even last a year.
I don't know why people going on like
it's so much money when it really isn't madness.
But it's because who's showing the money?
It's because of who's showing the money.
It's not because of the actual money.
People like to have their favorites on this site.
I'm saying, Grevy, it's who's showing the money, you know?
It's not about what how much the money
is. It's about who's showing the money. Yeah, madness. No. No.
Oh, the lanky. The lanky virgin. Nons legs.
The one with the disabled girlfriend.
The virgin in the bedset with no teeth.
You know, lanky virgin boy. Yeah, man. Wow.
Yeah, these people on Reddit are [ __ ] idiots.
So many Simpsons and white knights. Yeah,
the more I think about this greasy, the
more I don't ever want to go out and try
again. You know what I mean?
I've already had [ __ ] and getting laid
in this country is impossible. So, I'm
not sure why you would say that to me
knowing the situation.
the fact that you can't even get a date,
let alone get laid. But yeah, I'm not
sure why you'd say something like that.
I smash her face.
Why would you say that, Bob? when you
know getting laid here is impossible.
Mhm. I don't really have much of a
[ __ ] sex drive anymore to be fair.
I think it's because I know it's
impossible. Getting laid impossible here. So
why would you crave something that's
impossible to get? It's [ __ ] stupid.
I don't really have a sex drive to be honest.
never grown up.
They never have. They never will.
So, I don't know. I don't really have a sex drive.
It's so mad how like you get so many
people on the internet talk [ __ ] like,
"Oh, go on Tinder to get sex. Go on
Tinder to get laid. Go out and speak to
women." And like it's so weird, Gregy,
how they say one thing on the internet,
but what you experience in real life is
completely different. It's mad in a way, isn't it? It is.
Even getting laid is [ __ ] impossible
to be honest. So mad, is it? They make
it seem like
you can just go and get sex and get a
relationship when you want. It's madness.
But meeting someone is just impossible. It's [ __ ]
That's why I stopped trying Grezy cuz
there's no one for me. So
tried a million times before.
Have to really stop talking about it. It's depressing.
Yeah, it's depressing, bro.
It really, really is depressing even
talking about it. I don't even know why
I bring it up. It's so depressing. Yeah.
Do you reckon if I go out next Saturday
it will change? Greasy
like honest opinion. I don't want you to
agree with me if you don't agree with
me. I I want your actual honest opinion.
Do you think if I go out try next week
it will be different?
Maybe maybe it'll be different. Do you think?
Yeah. What? Dressed up as Chucky.
No, but I'm saying if I go out on Chucky.
No, I'm saying if I go out next
Saturday, do you reckon I'll meet someone Grezy? Huh? Maybe.
Why? Why? What makes you say that?
Why? What makes you think I won't meet anyone?
No, but seriously, if I go out
seriously, do you reckon I'll meet
someone next week if I just try?
You You really think I won't meet
anyone? Grieves here?
No, I want your honest opinion. I I
don't want you to agree with me if you
don't agree with me. I want your honest opinion.
Adman said to me, "It will always be the
same there." You know this?
He's Well, it will never change, will
it? I told I remember I showed him.
Yeah. Like what happened, you know, from
like the the weeks I'm certain week I
went out. He said, "Well, it would never
change, would it?
That's what he said, Grezy. Well, it
would never change, would it?
Is he right?
Well, it will never change.
And he said, "You'll never change."
That's what he said to me. You'll never change.
Funny as [ __ ]
Do you reckon I might get lucky next week?
So you reckon I might get lucky? Really? [Music]
I'd rather stick pins in my eyes.
Yeah, I'd rather stick [ __ ] pins in
my eyes, mate. [ __ ] that. I ain't
trying. [ __ ] that. Tried enough.
But like, it will never change, will it?
You'll never change. He said Yeah.
after kicking the bollocks.
Well, I'm going to be back