Oh man.
[ __ ] thing needs [ __ ] charging.
>> What in the bed s man
should still be [ __ ] w. Oh [ __ ]
Lovely electric blanket. Oh, no. N
this person is on about me going to Wales and
giving them money.
Well, you know what? H
I could go to Wales on Saturday to be fair,
but only if this is guaranteed.
Otherwise, I'm not [ __ ] wasting my
time. I'm not wasting my money. Simple. Who knows? Madness.
This guy said he spent £400 last time he went out.
But he said he hadn't been out for 3
months. I said that's not bad then if
you've not been out for 3 months.
Yeah, that's not bad.
I haven't been out for 3 months. Good
to be fair. Yeah. Oh,
Just chilling, bro. One second.
I had a kebab. Yeah.
Did you watch my video?
It's always Reddit, bro. I'm always on Reddit.
Reddit's [ __ ] addicting.
I got [ __ ] [ __ ] Izzy [ __ ] messaging me.
And we got another one that says if I
give them £100, they'll [ __ ] me. So, I
might go to
I can even go to Wales or Manchester.
Don't really want to go Manchester. It's [ __ ] far.
I'll go out Saturday if it's guaranteed,
but if not,
not wasting my time.
Did you watch my video, Grezy? You can't
tell me that you don't agree with it.
Come on, mate. That video was a banger
that I done.
watch it and come back to me. Yeah,
I'm under my little electric blankie. Grievesy.
My little electric blankie. Oh, it's so nice.
Yeah, it's so nice. more skin.
I [ __ ] banging bing [ __ ] mad.
Oh, you're on YouTube again, Terry. No life.
You can't say that when you're on my live stream.
Anyways, get going your mug. Yeah, right.
So, I'll see what I'll see what they're saying.
See which one to pick from. [Music]
Yeah, she does. Cuz I used to speak
about having a baby with her. Yeah.
So, I might go to Wales on Saturday. I'm not sure.
I'm not sure what I'm up to yet.
I know she she likes Peter Belly.
He wants to have a baby with me.
This [ __ ] is there.
Yeah. He said that she needs an escort
cuz she needs to pay her debts.
She needs to pay her debts.
It's cute, isn't it?
She said before, Greavvesy, you
ejaculated in my mouth. No, just steps.
Can't believe she licks my ass.
I was like, "What the fuck?"
Imagine the next guy that goes to kiss
her. She's so lucky, Greg, that I had a
bath before meeting her. You know, I had
a really nice bath. Like, honestly,
I can't believe she done that. That's mad.
Cuz if I didn't have a bath or shower,
she'd be licking [ __ ] a load of [ __ ] you know? Yeah.
Yeah. I've got a lovely 2K.
I can do whatever I want. Easy, man.
Isn't that nice, Greasy?
No responsibilities. Oh, it's lush.
It's lush to have no responsibilities.
Absolutely [ __ ] lush it. Say
What? What happened to the Only Fans
one? Why she stopped wanting to come?
She was a coward as well. Yeah,
I think Greezy should play the roulette.
What do you think, Stephen Howard? I
think he should play the roulette. Me? Yeah,
skin [ __ ] virgin. I had a lovely kebab, Greavvesy.
I'm having macaroni cheese tomorrow. Yep. Yeah,
I love macaroni cheese.
Grezy wants to join the side men.
They're not that big, are they, Greasy?
The side men. They're not that big.
Monty's trying to um get back into my good books.
I can tell, man. I can tell it's not
happening. And he can [ __ ] off.
He can [ __ ] right off. I'll never be
friends with that snake again.
Just like I'll never be cool with my
sister again. I've got two sisters. what
I get on with
sh all the time and obviously I get on
with my mom as well. simple like some
people you just don't
it's just best to just never you know
what I mean ever um
speak to again you know
or get on with again you know what I mean Grezy
This is the way it is. Yeah.
Go on Tinder. Um,
why does the skint virgin keep calling
me big nose when I don't even have a big nose?
I mean, that's like he's so insecure,
isn't it? I don't know why he's talking
about my nose. No one has ever said that
I have a big nose ever. Crazy. That
That is some serious self projection.
That is, bro.
He's insecure because he knows that he's
the ugly one. It's obvious, bro. Why the
[ __ ] does he keep talking about my nose?
My nose ain't even [ __ ] big.
What the [ __ ]
[ __ ] idiot ears, man. He needs to get laid.
You need to lose your virginity before
it's too late.
By the way, Stephen, Howard, Joseph is
not one of the brothers anymore.
Joseph is is not one of the brothers
anymore. Only me, you and Grezy.
Yeah, because with these people Steven Howard. Yeah.
I've noticed it when I go out virgin boy like
[ __ ] say that he's a virgin and
stuff. Everyone sticks up for more. How
can he be a virgin? No, no, no, no, no.
But no one sticks up for me.
So [ __ ] them, bro. Same with [ __ ]
Joe. Same with like even that [ __ ]
ghosting has done it as well. Whoa. How
could he be a virgin? He's got a
girlfriend. How can I be a [ __ ]
virgin when I prove I had [ __ ] sex?
No one sticks up for me. So Yeah.
Yeah, they are. Because
think about it, Steven Howard, when I
say that he's a virgin, people always
say, "Oh, how can he be a virgin? He's
got a girlfriend." But when he calls me
a skin virgin, no one backs up. No one
backs me up.
No one backs me up. No one says, "Oh,
well, he's actually proved he's had sex
or oh, he's actually show thousands. I mean, nope."
You know what I'm saying? It's mad. No
one ever backs me up.
Who's the same two spastics?
See, you're saying that my life is uh
pathetic, but it's not because I'm
actually saving money and I'm leaving
the country in November. So, that sounds
like a smart move to me.
Yeah, sounds like a smart move to me, mate.
Yeah, no one backs me up,
you know. They back the [ __ ] skin
version of the bed set up, but they
don't [ __ ] back me up. [ __ ] you.
Backs Peter belly up. I'm sad. No,
it's weird that, isn't it? It is weird.
No, I don't ban anyone that's got an
opinion. I ban people that self project.
That's exactly why I disable the
comments because it's just the same repeating people.
Who? Who are you talking about?
No, I ban people that self project
and repeat. Big difference. Yep.
And if you've got so much of an opinion,
why don't why don't you join the
hangouts and we'll talk about it. If
you've got so much of a [ __ ] opinion, huh? Uh Sarah.
Yeah. This guy said he spent £400 last
time he went out, but he went to a
[ __ ] strip club. I didn't go to a
[ __ ] don't even know where that
[ __ ] money went.
won't be doing it in a hurry.
Definitely definitely won't be doing it
in a hurry again.
Sorry about that. I was just type something. No,
none. The truth doesn't come out of your
[ __ ] mouth. Well, bro, the truth about what?
What do you speak the truth about? You
call people skin? Your skin yourselves.
You call people ugly, you're ugly
yourselves. What do you say that's not self-projected?
There is no truth about it.
Everything you say is self-p projection.
There's no truth in it. And you spamming
ruins the channel.
Think about it. You don't know about
anyone's life but your own. So
everything you say is just self projecting.
There's no truth that comes from any of your mouths. You know,
mate, listen. You don't have a
girlfriend. So, everything that you're
trying to say about me, you don't have a girlfriend. Again, self-projecting.
Come at me with something that doesn't
apply to your own life
and then tell me about how you are
telling me the truth. Go on, tell me
something that doesn't apply to your own
life and then come back to me.
Simple. That's it.
Anyways, bye-bye now. Yeah, man.
Hey, hey, hey.
Look at that, man.
I don't know, man. Not sure.
Look at my face compared to the virgin's face.
I need to wash my hair by
the way. Look at my face compared to virgin's face. Uhhuh. Yeah. Um,
[ __ ] Reddit fears different opinions.
speak to someone on Reddit. I tried to
get them on Instagram quickly
or something because the Reddit mods
banned people for no reason. Yeah.
Nothing wrong with what?
No, not interested. She's ugly.
Nataly G is [ __ ] ugly. [ __ ] that.
I don't have the same nose as lamb.
You people call people ugly cuz you're ugly.
That's why none of you come on camera.
Oh, it's self projection.
Every time these people come and they
try to call me ugly, they're really just
talking about themselves.
They always talk about themselves.
No, I know. But you're you're trying to
say that I've got Lim's nose when my
nose ain't even [ __ ] big. You know
why those I've never I've never been
told. Nope. I'm not insecurities. Nope.
Show my face right here right now. I've
got absolutely no insecurities. None whatsoever.
None at all. Not scared to show my face.
Never have. Never will be. You're scared
to show your face. I'm not scared to
show my face.
So, never been insecure about any anything honestly.
How could you say your nose isn't big?
Why don't you come and show your face?
I'll pop the link in for you.
Strong facial features.
Why do you come in, bro?
Why don't you join the link? Show your
face, man. We should all show our faces together. Why not?
Why not, mate? Oh, [ __ ]
I need to send someone something.
One second, please.
I don't even know why any of you [ __ ]
talk about my [ __ ]
Nope. I don't have Instagram for people
on YouTube. I don't know why you talk
about my looks in a good way or a bad
way. I literally don't care. No matter
what you say, whether it's good or bad,
I literally don't give a [ __ ] Like,
you're never going to make me insecure.
You're never gonna
It doesn't matter what you say, whether
it's a good thing or a bad thing. It's
just pointless. I don't really care what
people on YouTube have got to say about the way
that I look. So, yeah.
You're not a woman.
was doing something, man, on Snapchat.
But yeah, man.
It's not my insecurities.
I'm not insecure about the way I look.
You need to ask me a question, Steven Howard.
Ask me why these people
call me ugly every day. You need to ask
me and I'll tell you.
You have to ask me. Just ask me like that
and I'll answer you. Cuz they're ugly.
It's because they're ugly. That's why
they call me ugly. Cuz they're ugly. Yeah.
No, no, no, no. Cuz they're ugly.
>> These people are actual muners.
Where's the [ __ ]
bro? Where is the skin version? H. Um,
yeah, I'll do it for a million pound
cuz then I could just try it with other
[ __ ] with a million pound. Of course,
I would do it for a million pound
with a skinned virgin in the bed sit
with no bed, no money in it. Do it.
That's the question, mate.
You reckon a skinned version in the bed
suit would do it?
Did I [ __ ] do that?
He is [ __ ] skimp, mate. Let's not
[ __ ] pretend. He is [ __ ] [ __ ]
He's really skinn.
He is really [ __ ] skin, mate. Oh, [ __ ]
You know I People on Reddit, Steven
Howard, they say um
they say that I need to go on Tinder
to get laid. Stephen Howard, they say
use Tinder. I'm on Tinder.
It doesn't work. I'm on Tinder. Yeah. Bam.
Have you ever been to a strip club? Steven Howard. No.
So, how much you betting on the football on Saturday?
I'm going to do
20 quid, I think.
Yeah. £50 on how many teams?
>> No, you should do £50 on four teams. I
think I'm going to do £50 on four teams.
Yeah, I might do four teams. Me, bro.
I think I could get good. I reckon I
could get four in. I
No, maybe I'll do three actually. No,
I'll do three.
I'm going to do Slow,
Kitty Minister, and Darlington.
That should win.
I wonder what that pays off a 50.
It should be a good return though.
Should be a good return.
Yeah. So like just do 60 on the football in it.
Yeah. Do £50 on three teams. I think I
will return about 350.
I think it will turn 350. Any
luck with the women? Um,
any luck with the women?
Uh, what country are we in?
Maybe I forgot what country we're in.
I mean, we're in England, so no, maybe no.
Why would you ask something when you
already know the answer to it?
Yeah. Six. Yeah.
You should put 50 on 16s.
That would be good.
They say go on Tinder.
It's a hookup culture.
It's hookup culture. They say,
"Yeah, it's hop culture." They say
hookup culture. Everyone wants sex, huh?
Do they now?
I must be missing something. [Music] Sorry, Mom. Yeah.
Why don't you put £50 on five teams?
That would be good, isn't it?
How easy do you reckon it will be to get
three teams? I reckon you could do it.
Three teams. I reckon you could.
Yeah, I reckon you could.
Three teams should be easy in the lower league.
What? Three teams?
Nah, you could do three free teams. You could get
what? You don't reckon you could do
free? You could get three teams.
No, I reckon you could get free teams, man.
Three games, I reckon.
What about four? Yeah.
Imagine a treble both score no draw. Oh,
that'd be lovely.
A treble. Both score no draw. Jesus.
That' be good. Yeah. Heat.
I'm going to do Slow Kitty Minister and Darlington.
I reckon that will come in me.
We should do an eight. Both teams to score.
What about that one? An 81. You know
that first football bet we won was so
nice. That 80 to 280. Oh, that was
lovely. That was
that was a lovely one.
Yeah. And imagine it comes in. You would
have wish you had 50 quid on it.
Yeah. Could you imagine a virgin [ __ ]
betting on the football?
No, I can't [ __ ] imagine it either
cuz he's too skint.
No, I can't imagine it, mate. No.
Izzy is still trying to get me to go Manchester.
[ __ ] that man.
She keeps saying, "Oh,
come to Manchester. Come to Manchester. [ __ ] Manchester. [ __ ] that.
So, I remember I used to go Manchester
all the time. It's crazy looking back at
the things I used to do.
It's actually crazy to think
How much do you think it would cost you
to go Manchester from the Friday
and then you come back on the Monday,
you go Friday, you come back on the
Sunday. So, train, hotel, drinking, food.
How much do you think it would cost?
I'm thinking like 600, 700.
What do you think?
>> Yeah, I say about 6, seven.
What are you saying?
What would your prediction be? Yeah. 500.
What do you reckon if I done it, I would meet someone?
Even reckon I would meet someone if I done that.
I could meet someone in it. Uh definitely no.
I feel like if I was to go to Manchester
again, I'll just go for two days.
I actually stayed there before for two
days when I was
when I met that guy in uh
from Germany. We just got on it together.
Yeah, I remember that.
It was fun.
Yeah, it cost about I'd say it's cost
about 500 to be fair
to get rejected by women.
Yeah, I remember when I stayed two days
in Manchester before it was sick.
We had a good old laugh, man. Manchester was good.
I remember kissing this woman in a club
and just sucking her tits. But in the actual club,
I think I fingered her as well. We had a
good old laugh.
I was a mad bastard. I swear I was a bad
bastard back then.
spending £500 just to get I've got a boyfriend.
That' be mad in it.
But you'd have to get on the G. You'd
have to stick to beer the first [ __ ]
night. The first night you go, you'd
have to stick to beer
because of um
you'd have to stick to beer because of [ __ ] um
what do you call it? Cuz obviously you
can't do rum two days in a row. So you'd
have to stick to beer on the Friday then
Saturday you can get on the rum. You'd
be [ __ ] bro. By the time you come
back to London, you'd be [ __ ] Nah,
you'd have to stay you'd have to stick
to the Guinness on a Friday, then on a
Saturday you could drink the rum.
Cuz I remember when I was in Manchester.
Yeah. And I I was planning to go
Blackpool and go home, but obviously the
train strike I had to stay in Manchester
and I was [ __ ] I still got on the
drink obviously cuz I had to, you know. So
yeah, I had to stay in another hotel.
It was good, man.
Them traveling days were good.
They were fun, man. Yeah, man.
You should do that every week, could it?
Go to a city, right, for two days. Go to
Leeds for Friday and Saturday, then
Manchester Friday, Saturday, then Newcastle,
Friday, Saturday. Could you imagine?
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Imagine you actually done that.
That would be sick of it.
Then Edinburgh Friday, Saturday,
Glasgow, Friday, Saturday. Nah.
I couldn't do that every week, but I
won't be able to afford it. What the
[ __ ] Every week? No way.
No, I won't be able to afford it.
And I wouldn't do it anyways.
It would be fun to think of,
but I just wouldn't do it.
That'd be expensive. [ __ ] That'd be
very expensive. That'd be about 7800
pound a week.
You're good though. Could
you imagine, bro?
That would be sick. Oh. Oh [ __ ] [Music]
Yeah, I'm good.
Nah, man. Just um had a [ __ ] I'm still
burnt out from last week.
[ __ ] spending 600 [ __ ] pound. Not
even get a date.
Why is it impossible to get a woman in
this country? Jim
Yeah, I went out uh last week
looking my best. Looks maximing.
I got 10 numbers.
Didn't even get a date.
Yeah, impossible here. Impossible
here in London to even get laid, mad.
But people go on like it's so easy. Yeah, right.
People say go on Tinder.
Women love confidence. No, they [ __ ]
don't. I was confident last week.
They They weren't interested.
I done some sick confident approaches.
They weren't interested.
Nah. No, they [ __ ] do not love
confidence, mate. No, they [ __ ] do not.
I'm always confident when I go out. Not interested.
I do approaches [ __ ] sober, too.
Clearly, I'm not confident enough. Oh, I
[ __ ] am, mate.
They don't care about confidence.
That's a myth.
Oh, I definitely am confident enough,
mate. Trust me.
[ __ ] trust me. They don't care about confidence.
That's cat, bro.
That is cap.
That confidence thing is is a myth.
No way did they care about confidence.
I used to be a lot more confident as
well. It never made a difference.
I used to be crazy confident. Now I've
just lost the energy for it. And yeah, not interested.
That's what it is. It's about them.
They're not interested.
about you, your confidence or this that
or the other. That's the mistake I was
thinking all of these years. I thought
it was me, but it's just they're not
interested in England, you know.
I always thought, yeah, maybe be less
confident, be more confident, you know,
different hairstyle. I used to think it was me.
Yeah, they really don't care about
confidence at all. >> Yeah.
One to him. Listen.
One second. What?
Yeah, man. I'm going to own this [ __ ]
I'm going to [ __ ] own this [ __ ]
[ __ ] bro. She just blocked me on [ __ ] Instagram.
I'm going to go [ __ ] tell her to get
raped. She sent me a load of [ __ ] and
[ __ ] blocked me, coward.
You stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] And I'm going
to block her. I'm going to get the last
word. Trust me.
So when someone blocks you on Instagram,
I've got another phone. So I'll do on that phone.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] bro. Sorry, bro.