[Laughter]
I can't stop laughing. It's so funny.
Oh, it is funny.
It's just I've been creasing literally
all day yesterday. Oh, it was really,
really funny. It made me laugh. So yeah,
people really need to learn to call it a
day on there, man. Honestly, they they [ __ ] do [Laughter]
[ __ ] YouTube, it causes so many
problems, you know.
So many so many problems.
Oh mate. Well, at least what I said was true.
No, I proved it. I knew I was right.
I knew I knew I was right all along. And
you see, I knew I was right all along
with these people here. Yeah.
Oh, man. I knew I was right. It's lush
to be right. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
I proved everything I said. They can't
take a day off of YouTube and I proved
it. And you know what, right? I'm not
going to start saying that people are
skin. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. I'm not going to start
saying that. But what I'm going to say
is I know for a fact, right, cuz I've
been watching some of this [ __ ] when it
popped up that they definitely ain't got
no life. Any single live stream that you
click on or you watch back on, it is the
same people. Smokey B, all of these
people, if they had stuff going on in
their life, bro, they wouldn't sit on
YouTube writing all day, bro. It's so
[ __ ] obvious. Like, they can't make
it any more obvious. It's so obvious,
isn't it? It is so obvious.
Like because if they if they truly had
[ __ ] going on in their life, they
wouldn't be on YouTube all day every day
typing. And I've seen it. Yeah. And I've
seen what's going on as well. So, bro,
they they can't talk about nobody, man.
They really can't talk about [ __ ] no
one, man. [ __ ] weird.
And yeah, I just don't have time for
this [ __ ] anymore. But I thought
Monty was the whole Monty thing was so
funny. So I had to just laugh at it
to be honest.
I don't know why this guy keeps going on
about Natalie G just [ __ ] I thought I
was [ __ ] bad without [ __ ] Morgan
for [ __ ] sake. He's He's worse than
me. I think he's worse than me.
He's worse than me, bro. What the [ __ ]
man? I swear to God.
Yeah. It's why I'm not watching these
live streams anymore. It's the [ __ ]
same [ __ ] every time.
Every time it's the same [ __ ]
It's a madness. It is actually a
I don't [ __ ] know, man. You know,
I don't understand why this guy still
keeps going on about Natalie G.
Bro, this guy, I thought I was bad with
the Morgan thing.
Just living life, chilling, bro. I don't
have time for this [ __ ] anymore. And I
proved what I said was right as well.
How these people got no life, like
Smokey B and stuff, cuz every live
stream I clicked on, they were there. So
it it shows at the very least that they
don't have anything going on in their
life even if they did have money because
bro you know when people I know from
experience and I know people that have
come off of here it's so obvious that
the people that do this uh they've got
no life. Like
let's talk about this whole Discord
thing as well cuz he was trying to get
me on this Discord. I told him I'm not
going on your stupid Discord with these
low lives. Yeah. that he thought I was
stupid. He was trying to get me on
Discord. I was like, "Bro, like look at
this. Even this Discord thing, you got a
guy, bro, that's [ __ ] 18 years of age
and he's wasting his life on Discord. I
mean, bro, the people there's some
people out there I'm very sure would
kill to be 18 again." And he's wasting
his life being a low life on [ __ ]
Discord. What the [ __ ] hell, man, is
wrong with these people in this [ __ ] community?
Something is seriously wrong with these people.
Something seriously wrong with these
people, man. I'm telling you. Um, so
it's been on other communities. Yeah, I
just can't be bothered with it. Um,
I'll be out drinking later. Haven't
drunk in a while. I was supposed to meet
someone last week, Joe.
Yeah, they kind of done the dirty on me.
I was looking forward to going out
drinking. I was actually very looking
forward to that. But
yeah, I had to recover from that um
spending that £600 and getting no dates.
But in a way, I'm kind of glad it did happen because
well, it was weird cuz somebody replied
back and they were supposed to meet me
last Saturday. They said, "Oh, where do
you want to meet?" I said, "Oh, let's
meet in Liverpool Street." And I was
actually looking forward to going out
for a drink because I hadn't drunk in a
while. And I was like, "If they want to
meet me, I'll go out. But if they don't,
I'm not going to go out because I'm just
not going to bother. But I'll be I'll be
going out today."
So, they kind of just trolled me and
[ __ ] me around. And yeah, I didn't end
up meeting them.
So, I'm good, man. I'm just chilling.
I'm going out later drinking. So, yeah.
So, they just wasted my time anyways. So
they didn't end up meeting [ __ ]
same old [ __ ] in it. Yep. So
that's how it is now. Is it? But
yeah, like I said, man, when I go out
today, I I know what to expect.
I literally know what I'm expecting. I
know what I'm in for.
But for the sake of 100,200 pound, what
else is there really to [ __ ] do?
Let's put it Let's put it this way. So, yeah.
Something to do in it. Why? Why the [ __ ] not, bro?
It's It's so weird cuz she messaged back
and I I I know what they're like, but I
I like to try to give everyone the
benefit of the doubt. And she's like,
"Oh, I was busy with uni, ret.
Let me know when you're next in the area
again." I was like, "Okay, well, I've
got some dry clean and designer clothes.
why not try and meet this person?
And then they said, "Oh," I said, "Oh
yeah, I'm going to come to your area
Saturday, which is Liverpool Street,
which is near where I used to live." So,
and then they agreed to it. And then
they said, "Oh, I'm sick. Oh, [ __ ] off,
man." You know what I'm saying? I was
like, "Just I can't be annoyed with all
of this [ __ ] because you know when they
me cuz you know when they messaged um
back it was like um a week later and I
was like, "Oh, well, do you know what?
Yeah, we might have spent £600. We might
have um you know went out drinking and
had to deal with a load of [ __ ] But
if it get if it's a date that's worth
it, then it was worth it. If you find
one person that's worth it, it was worth
it. And I thought this could this this
had potential and then they just do what
they always do. So I don't expect
anything different now.
So, it'd be stupid to think that
that I know I know everyone's got
different tolerance levels and obviously
mine should have I should have gave up a
long time ago like gave up hope but I
don't know just I'm more stubborn than
most people but like I said the fact
that you can go out looking your best
getting 10 numbers and not get a date it
doesn't look good so no I don't care
anyways I'm going out drinking because I
want to go out later so it is what it
is. Yeah, he's good.
He's good. Yeah, man. So,
it is what it is, isn't it?
Disgusting, isn't it? But it will never
change. I think we've said all we've had
to say about it. You know,
see what I don't understand is why they
why they have to play games. I can
understand if people don't want to meet
someone or they're not interested or
whatever, whatever the [ __ ] it is, but I
don't understand why they play games with people
because we're supposed to be the [ __ ]
immature ones, but all they do is literally
the only thing that's going to happen
today when I go out is going to hear
I've got a boyfriend. Typical. Going to
hear I'm not interested. Typical. and
I'm going to get some numbers and my ass
is going to get led on. That's literally
all that's going to happen. And you'd be
afford to expect anything else.
Yeah, they like to do that. Lead people on.
So, I don't know why they do it. It's
just silly, isn't it?
Yeah. So, I didn't I haven't been out
for like 3 weeks drinking cuz
Yeah, that was a bad one, bro. [ __ ] it now. £600.
Jesus. Even though I won the money back,
it's not the point.
But yeah, should be like 150 200 today.
Hopefully not 600 again. Nah,
I know. No, I haven't been gambling. Uh-uh.
I don't gamble, bro, much,
but I'm going to start doing a football
soon. I'm going to start trying to win a
football bet every week, like I was
saying before. Start with like 160 and
try to really study this football and
try and win a football bet every week.
Um, but I don't really do it, man. Nah,
can't be annoyed with it, mate. All of
the money I won, I just saved. That's
why I've got money. So,
nah, it's my birthday next week. Uh, is
it next week? Yeah. Or 27th, whatever,
man. Whatever it is. So, I was going to
go on my birthday, but I just going to
go out today. So, yeah.
Yeah. That's the only reason that I
didn't try for so long, Joe, is because
of the 10 numbers and that.
Like you might not think I can afford
it. I can afford it, bro. I can I can
afford to go out drinking every week.
Trust me, bro. I've got money, you know.
But I just lost even when I had the
house, I lost a love for it,
even for like a year. I can go out every
week if I want, bro.
No, cuz my birthday's on
my birthday's on um
my birthday's on a Monday, so I'm going
to go out the weekend before that. Nah,
I'm not going to Newcastle. Pointless, bro. Nah,
I've done all of that [ __ ] before, man.
Why am I going to go Newcastle?
Why the [ __ ] am I going to go to
Newcastle, man? For what [ __ ] reason, huh?
It's never going to change here with the
women. I've accepted it now, bro. It's
It is what it is. So, yeah.
Cuz the thing is why I had to lose hope is because,
think about it.
It's very likely that the same thing
would happen again. You know, if you
looked your best and you got 10 numbers
and you didn't even get a date, that's
definitely going to happen again
considering you're probably not going to
get 10 numbers for a very long time
again. So, it's very likely that the
same thing would happen again. You see,
but obviously I was I was hopeful that
person was going to meet me.
Oh, everything happens for a reason. But
again, just mind games as always.
So, I'm not No, I'm not going Newcastle.
I'm going somewhere New Year's Eve. I'm
definitely going somewhere New Year's Eve.
Definitely. Definitely going somewhere
New Year's Eve. H. So, yeah.
Yep. Some of your some of your sayings
are funny, Joe, when you say, "Oh,
Reddit sad." Like anything that they
have to anything where someone has to
control something is sad.
You think Reddit is sad. Oh, bro. Yeah.
See, I was going to say I've tried all
of that before until you mentioned the different countries,
but it's never it's not it's never going
to change unless you go to Asia.
That's always how it's going to be here.
Like, I don't care about it anymore,
man. I really really [ __ ] don't.
That 600 [ __ ] [ __ ] told me a lot,
bro. That is bad. Really, really bad.
Cuz say I was like a normal person
working or just like a normal person. I
didn't win the money back, I'd be
[ __ ] Just like a normal person would be [ __ ] So
yeah, it's [ __ ] up, bro.
No, I was to be fair I was thinking of
trying like France and that France and
Belgium and stuff but I don't I can't
imagine it working.
Obviously you can't knock it until
you've tried it obviously but I think as
far as England goes now it's time to
give up. Like I'm only going out later
cuz I want to go out drinking later. I
just want to go out. But I mean I was
actually thinking about it. You know, I
did actually do a cold approach in
Belgium when I went to Belgium and I got
her Snapchat and stuff and she was like,
"I can't really understand you. Your
London accent is a bit too thick and shit." So,
we're supposed to meet up. I can't
remember exactly what happened, but I
only done one approach.
But yeah, you know, you don't know, bro.
Anywhere that's out of this country, I'm optimistic. But
as far as this country goes, I mean,
there's nothing left, you know.
Yeah, they do sit in it. Yeah, they do.
They definitely do because
it's not real. They lie a lot as well on
Reddit as well. They lie a lot as well. So,
I wish I could get with a French woman,
but that is impossible. I think that is
Isn't it mad Joe how like Monty's lost
everything on the same website you can
watch Cal Freezy on.
But I didn't do any approaches when I
was in Belgium or the Netherlands cuz I
was just like on holiday. So I didn't
want to just I just wanted to enjoy myself. But yeah,
that's how it is.
There's some actual people on Reddit. I
was This guy's like a 27y old kissless virgin.
Good luck to him.
Yeah, just messaged me now. They've just
got the same
same attitude, bro.
They all have that they all have the
same attitude as well. But a lot of the
things that these people do, Joe, as
well. Um, and it's not just people on Reddit.
They dismiss people's struggles. I don't
know why they seem to do that. Like, I
don't know. Like
I was having this conversation with this
woman and she was like, "Oh, well, yeah,
you don't speak to them enough." And
then I say, "Oh, I have here, I have
there." And it's like, "No matter what
you what you show them, they just miss
everything that you show them. So
there's literally no point even having
an argument about it because
it you just go round and round in
circles. So there's there's literally
like no point even having an opinion on
it because you just go around in circles. So
they do dismiss a lot of um people's struggles.
Um this is an interesting one as well. I
was speaking to this white knight Joe.
Oh, I did I forgot to say this. I was
speaking to this guy on Reddit and he
was saying about how the country is dead
and no no no no no no I got the correct
word for it now and he was saying about
how oh like he was agreeing saying oh
it's dead that's why people leave the
country and then he was saying oh maybe
it's your vibe and I said my vibe what
the [ __ ] are you talking about this
woman was supposed to meet me on
Saturday she's all of a sudden
disappeared now she's claiming that
she's sick and he was making up I was
like bro you're a white knight like it's
so obvious you're a white knight and
then he was like oh right and then but
the funny thing is he was contradicting
himself throughout the whole argument
about our conversation about different
countries because he was saying about
how other people have left they've left
he is no longer in England at the minute
so he contradicted himself throughout
the whole argument and then he was like
oh um I'm a he was like I'm Um,
what did he say? Then he says, "Oh, I
got all of these women." And every
single woman he showed was a [ __ ]
Asian woman. Contradicted himself
throughout the whole argument. He's a [ __ ] idiot.
That's the word for them. White knights.
A s is what Monty is. But the people
that make excuses for women are white knights.
So that's where we're at basically.
It is [ __ ] It is [ __ ] bro. And I
say the same thing to my mom, Joe. Like,
I don't even have these arguments
anymore. When when you know when people
sit there and say, "Oh, women are
different." I just say, "I believe it
when I see it."
And to that, they they can't say nothing.
That's that's the way I see it, Joe. I
don't want to be told this. I don't want
to be told that.
I want to be [ __ ] shown. That's what
I want to be. And no one can show me. So
therefore, it doesn't exist.
So I believe it when I see it. And
that's how I end it. I don't get into no
debates. Debates. Why am I going to get
into [ __ ] debates, bro? For people to
to dismiss what they're shown. It's a
waste of [ __ ] time.
We're going out today. We're going We're
getting on the piss.
No, I don't like Natalie G. No.
>> No, I just been chilling, bro. Been out
for a few weeks, so I can't wait to go
out today drinking.
>> I know what you're doing, Joe. You think
you're tempting me with your gambling wins?
Nah, you're not tempting me, buddy.
I'm done with that. Oh, I did see the
Timmy meet up. That was funny, isn't it?
Uh, all on the same website you can
watch Mickey Mouse on. Oh, that's funny, man.
They're all the best of They're all the
best of friends.
Yeah. [ __ ] money. Mike was like, "If
you want trouble, come around the
corner." I would have went around the corner, me,
I would have I would have [ __ ] went
around the corner and said, "Come on
then, you [ __ ] cunt." He's about like
5 foot tall, bro.
And I'll challenge him to see what he's
really about, bro. Nothing.
Do you know what, bro? When I was
watching it, it was actually pissing me
off, you know, before they met. Yeah. It
was actually pissing me off because all
all they done for the past on one of the
days 8 n hours was talking about meeting
up yet they still couldn't manage to do
it. And it was annoying me, bro. It was
It gets to a point where, bro, you can't
even watch that [ __ ] you know, bro. Cuz
you just want to end up getting
involved. Like that's that that's why,
bro. I was thinking, bro, I might just
go Birmingham and slap them all up cuz
it was annoying me, bro. Like when you
watch when I was watching some of it.
Yeah. No, you're not banned.
But um the thing is, yeah, like it it
does annoy you. Like it does annoy you
like watching it. It used to be the same
with that [ __ ] um P [ __ ] Repair
Man and Pat Mustard. They're making it
impossible to meet each other when they
live in the same [ __ ] place.
But Timmy's a coward. He always gets
people to [ __ ] fight his battles and
[ __ ] See, with me, if I was in that
situation, I would have just stayed in
the city center and I would have just
stayed live and they wouldn't be able to
talk their way out of it. And it is
annoying, bro. It is annoying. Yeah.
And then [ __ ] Monty trying to get me
on the Discord with the five great pedos.
You want to know a fun fact? That sad
Joe, the fact that Jaden is 18 years of
age and he [ __ ] sits
and he sits on Discord at 18 wasting his
life away. Like, it's mad, isn't it? 18
[ __ ] He's 18, bro. He's younger than
us and he'd rather sit on Discord being
a [ __ ] low life, man.
Do you know what I'm saying, bro?
That is [ __ ] sad, bro. Come on. Like
you you you know that is sad.
You know, I don't like that Davey UK
either. I said if they've got anything
to say, Dave lives in London. I'll
happily meet him. He can say something.
We can sort it out to my face, bro. You
know there the [ __ ] Listen, I don't
like that Dave UK. Simple, bro. I don't
like him. Yeah. He's no better than the
rest of them. And at the end of the day,
if he's got something to say, he can say
to my face. That's it. So,
I ain't [ __ ] around, bro.
Not going on Discord.
Yeah, but do you agree with the fact
that Jaden's 18 and he's wasting his
life away on Discord? Yeah.
Yeah. It's like when Timmy says, "Oh,
show me money." I'm not showing you no
money, bro. If you don't think I've got
money, that's on you. I'm not playing
your stupid little games. Simple. That's it.
That is That is it, man.
It's sad as [ __ ] cuz he's 18 as well and
he said he's wast you know wasted his
life on you on Discord being a sad
[ __ ] bastard you know yeah man so YouTube
no but I was I I lived my life whilst I was on
to be honest. So,
yeah, bro, them little tactics don't
work, Joe. They're boring now, bro.
Everyone knows why.
Oh, [ __ ] That's another thing. You know
that James subscribed to um a lot of
channels that you don't think she would
be subscribed to.
You know, people like Jane just needs to
be ignored. like straight up need to be
People like Jay need to straight up be ignored, bro.
Yeah, she's subscribed to a lo load of
these um troll channels. But yeah,
no one cares about that virgin.
That's the oldest trick in the book,
bro. They used to do it with LT as well.
Let's make up stuff so people come
online and start um start um
start explaining themsel basically.
That's like old [ __ ] bro. They've been
[ __ ] doing that for years, mate. Honestly.
But these [ __ ] women playing games, huh?
Yeah, I haven't I'm not getting my
haircut. I haven't had my haircut for a
couple of weeks. Just going to brush my
beard, go out, send it, bro. Simple.
Well, like I said, I'm going out cuz I
want to have a drink anyways. But yeah,
I'm sure it will be the same old as it always is.
What else was I to say?
But yeah, he just needs to um he just
needs to [ __ ] that Natalie G off now.
He really really does.
Don't know how someone can
how someone can be obsessed with someone
like that. I really really don't know.
And I could have had her a long time ago.
[ __ ] hell, man.
Need to give it a break.
[ __ ] hell. The madness.
But you know the maddest thing about it,
Joe? It's all on the same website you
can watch Mickey Mouse on.
It's all on the same website you can
watch Spongebob on.
See, I do kind of feel bad that I
brought him on here. Like when he would
met Timmy the other day and Mike, I was
like, "Oh shit." I kind of put him on
it. But he didn't have to stay on it.
And I didn't know what they were going
to do cuz they hadn't done it to me.
So I didn't know it was going to get
that deep. Cuz a lot of these people,
they done [ __ ] to him before they done
stuff to me.
Um, they done stuff to him first and
then done stuff to me.
Do you understand? So, I didn't know
what he was in for. And I'm not even
chatting [ __ ] on that one.
So, I don't [ __ ] know, man.
I don't know, bro. I don't know.
But yeah, that Smokey B definitely don't
have a life cuz I've seen him on a few
live streams typing.
This man claims he's got all of this
money, this life, but yeah, he's out
selling YouTube typing away every day.
What does four and four add up to seven?
Cuz that doesn't add up. You know,
they ain't got no life on there, bro.
They really ain't got a life on there, man.
What is he going
for? Is it that riot [ __ ] that happened ages ago?
I got to do I got to go court in three
and a half years. But I'm not going to go prison
and it'll probably be dropped by then. But
yeah, it's kind of scary
if he is actually going prison.
So he actually got charged with it. Was
it that thing from ages ago?
It must have been that what happened?
Was it the thing from ages ago with the
riots and [ __ ]
Or what what what happened? Like what
happened? When did he get arrest
arrested and charged and [ __ ] The uh
So what was it? Was it the one from ages
ago when he was doing the riots and he got nicked?
See, one day you'll get [ __ ] You can
get away with it a million times, but a
millionth and one time you get done for
it. It's like me. I've not been to court
since I was 18.
So, and I'm 20 [ __ ] eight next week.
So, at the end of the day, I've got
caught in a couple of years, but he'll
probably be dropped by then. And even if
it doesn't, I'm not going to prison,
believe you me. Cuz there's certain
guidelines. Your solicitor should be
able to tell you there's guidelines they
go by. So,
That's mad. See, I I I've been nicked a
I've been nicked so many times. Racism, abuse,
misogynist [ __ ] And they always dropped
it. They always dropped it.
And I mean bad [ __ ] I've been licked
over and they always dropped it. Always
got away with it.
I don't know why, but
I've been nicked so many times over this website
and they'd always they'd always drop it
even if it took like six, seven months, but
he must have [ __ ] Yeah, it must have
been that thing from year. So, he was on
bail and then they've charged him. Yeah,
he probably thought he was going to get
away with it.
Hopefully he doesn't go to prison. He
might get community service or something.
Depends. I don't think he's going to go
prison for three [ __ ] years,
but he might get a fin or something.
That is [ __ ]
Yeah, but it doesn't matter though cuz
I've got evidence of him harassing me.
So if it does go to court in three and a
half years, I've got all of the
evidence. So it's not going to work even
if it did go to court cuz I've got all
of the harassing, the stalking,
everything. I have everything on my
phone. And trust me, it will matter in
front of a judge. So trust me.
Trust me, it [ __ ] will, bro.
Nope. Don't really gamble anymore. No. So,
and it's not winning as well. It's
cowardly. You know, going to the police
and crying because you got your ass
whipped on YouTube. It's cowardly. And
in the end, you're never going to win.
And you'll realize that as well. It's
cowardly. Like, it really, really,
really, really is cowardly.
you know, to start [ __ ] on YouTube and
then run to the police because you got
your ass whooped, crying to the police,
and then you act like you've won,
man, you really really haven't. And
you'll discover that if it goes to court
in 3 years, which it won't. So, it's not
it's not even funny. It's cowardly that
very very cowardly.
And also, it's like when Monty Man goes
live, right? these people. That's
another thing I need to say. He'll go
live, right? And madness is is about to
happen. The bomb is about to go off and
then somebody comes in putting nudes up.
And I'm thinking, doesn't that just
defeat the whole object because you're
going to shut down the [ __ ] you're
going to shut down the [ __ ] live. So, um
you know what I'm saying? Suppose it's a
bit different because you No, it doesn't
matter if I took it further. I told a
[ __ ] numerous times to leave me alone.
He wouldn't do it. He tried to get my
money stopped, my benefit money stopped,
and he caused me inconveniences. So, I
thought, "Fuck it. I'll put up posters."
Simple. You know, you started it. You
want to be an online little keyboard
warrior harasser every single day.
Don't cry when somebody does post of
you. And the fact they're never going to
meet you fairly as well. I mean, look,
[ __ ] even Timmy meets people. You
know, you you're being a coward by doing
what you're doing on YouTube every day
and not meeting someone. So, you can't
cry when somebody puts up posts of you,
especially when you're trying to get
people's money stopped as well. So, um
that's one of the reasons why I done it
as well, cuz you were trying to get
people's money stopped two years ago and
he kept harassing me. So, I thought, [ __ ] this. So, yeah. completely deserved.
So yeah, and then they put up nude and
then Molly has to end the whole live
stream. Defeats the whole object
really, doesn't it? Just defeats the whole object. Yeah,
cuz they want drama, but then they're
[ __ ] putting nudes up trying to get
the whole [ __ ] thing banned.
So yeah, I had these benefit people call
me like two times and I thought, "Fuck
that. I'm doing the posters. [ __ ] that,
bro." So yeah.
So you try to get other people's income stopped, right?
You try to get other people's income
stopped. You don't call the shots on
what people do to you
because that's not just YouTube. You're
trying to get people's money stopped
trying to so that you don't call the
shots. You don't have control on what
happens to you. You could easily catch
him off guard. He's been uh Joe, it's
not going to work, buddy. Stop it. We've
been over this a million times. I'm not
playing these silly little games. I'm
28, not 8 months.
Yeah, bro. Like, do you not do you not
understand the whole thing about going
around in circles?
I've been to his area two times and he
was nowhere to be seen. That tells me
that someone's not about much. I don't
play silly games at 28 nearly 28 years
of age. Been there, done it, worn the t-shirt. Boring,
boring, boring, boring.
I'm not playing them silly games. you
could easily catch him. And then uh but
I was live in his area two times for
several hours and he was nowhere to be
seen yet wants to be a YouTube keyboard warrior,
which is weird cuz I've met a I've met
loads of people on here.
I've met loads and loads and loads of
people on here.
Could get a breakfast, you know. And uh
I keep eating so much food, man. Cold
makes me hungry.
Makes me hungry as [ __ ]
I had Burger King. I had a [ __ ] I
need to sleep before going out later.
I might go live later in the pub, Joe. H
why the [ __ ] not
have some Guinnesses? E
might go for a meal tomorrow. load it on
like a nice Indian, you know, for ages.
Maybe we'll get a date someday.
I doubt it. I [ __ ] doubt it, bro.
I was thinking of that USA Izzy two days
ago, but I'm not obsessed like Monty. So,
it's okay to think of these romantic
moments sometimes, you know. Yeah.
I don't know, bro. [ __ ] knows. So I
don't know what white so
why is the way it is here guys know
it will never change will it just like
Antman says hey
I still have USA Izzy oh I had an escort
message me the other day she's like oh
you want to come around I'm in the area
I said Um, I kind of don't want to come
around because I had an issue with a guy.
Um, so I'd rather not like even if he's
okay with it, I don't want to be
anywhere near that building because it's
just bad vibes. And then she was like,
oh, I'll ask cuz I know I really don't
want to. And then she was like, oh, I
said, where you going to be after? Cuz I
go around. She says, oh, I'm going to be
Northampton. I said, I'd rather come to
and I'll go for a night out in Milton
Kes. It's not a problem. I'd rather
travel 60 70 miles and and you know and
keep my pride than go anywhere near
there ever again. [ __ ] that. Nah, bro.
It's it's principle. You know what I mean?
Nah, [ __ ] that. I'd rather travel like
to Northampton. See, to me, these places
don't seem far to me cuz I've been all
over the country. So, I don't see 60, 70
miles as particularly far, to be honest.
So I said, "I'll see you if you if you
go to Northampton. I'll come
Northampton. It's not a problem. I'm not
I'm not going to that place." And she's
like, "Oh, don't get confused." I said,
"Uh, darling, I never got confused. We
made a deal." Obviously, me and the
other person and they tried scamming me.
Trust me, I've been doing this for years
and never had a problem like this
before. I had people that didn't agree
to things and I just found another
escort. But that's I've never had it
like that ever.
So I said if you go Northampton, I'll
just come to Northampton. It's not a problem.
I was thinking of going somewhere I've
not been drinking before. Maybe like
Bristol. I bet you've not been to
Bristol, have you, Joe? You've not been
to Bristol. Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ] I meant to
ask you, how much did your motor holiday
cost? That was a cheap getaway, wasn't
it? That That was a cheap getaway. I was
thinking of going to like Bristol. I've
been to Bristol before, but not drinking. Bristol.
I went there during the co if you remember.
They all talk like right in front of me.
Yeah. When my right nightmare, that's
how they talk over there if you haven't
noticed. Yeah. What would you be doing
in Bristol? Huh?
When you live in Newcastle.
So, how much was your motor holiday? Go
on, tell us. Huh? So,
the total fights worth £80.
Yeah, I'm thinking I'm going to go
Florida next summer. Never.
I'm definitely going to I think I'm
going to go slower the next year. Um
like June or something.
Yeah, but I can answer your question,
Joe. It does seem that way. But let me
tell you something,
right? Let me tell you something. The
thing is is that oh [ __ ]
with um when you've been abroad for me
and a lot of other people once you've
done it you've kind of done it not for
the rest of your life obviously you know
I'm still young I'll do it again but
once you've done it you've sort of done
it and you know I've been out of London
multiple times and also the fact that
think about it bro everything you want
is in London
like and obviously I had the money to
enjoy it back then as well. I still do
it now, but you get what I mean. Why you
never left more? Because, bro, there's
everything in London. Restaurants, it's
just a money. It's just a place of
money. You know, London there's there's
not really any need to go anywhere else.
And I don't like the the hot weather.
And I had gone away as well. So, so
that's the way I you know, that's it, man. Like
the first thing I had done when I got
money, the first thing I done was go abroad.
Um when I was in the financial position
to it, the first thing I done was leave
and I was 23,
which makes me think that obviously
nonsex is skint because why is it took
you until 31 to go abroad
for somebody that's apparently got all
this money? It doesn't make sense. I
done it at 23.
Um, I' done it twice as well in the
space of a month. So, but
but yeah, I'm definitely going to go FL
the next I'm going to put a deposit on
it. I think
pay it off like most people do. That's
what most people do anyways for the
words like that. So,
but yeah, I don't know.
But you do realize the countries that
you're going to, there's no culture difference.
So the places that you're going to,
there's no culture difference because
you go in Maltto, it's full of English
people. You go Spain, it's full of
English people. You know, you're not
going Japan, you're not going [ __ ]
Thailand. You're not going to [ __ ]
you know, Dubai. So, I'd agree with you
if the places that you the places that
you're going it's the same as England
basically because it's all full of English people.
No, I'm being serious.
And you're only going m because of the casinos. Yeah.
London's a very expensive place.
Yeah, but the women are not westernized.
The women are Asian.
The women are nice.
They ain't got a bad attitude like they have here.
Why are they so [ __ ] Why are they so
stuck up in England?
I don't know why they are, bro.
So, what what's your closest city?
What's your what's your closest city,
Joe? Is it Newcastle?
Yeah, I know. But I'm saying a lot of
English people live in Moa. Yeah.
Nope. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
No. No. No. No. Even dating apps work over there.
The only ones that you need to pay are
the really really good-looking ones. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no. Okay, let me
tell you something over there. Okay, if
they're like 18, 21, 22, you have to pay
for them. Yeah. But if you want someone
that's like 27, 28 in their 30s, you
don't. They actually want relationships.
Like, it's like, okay, here, okay, say
for example, you wanted to get laid with
a with somebody in their 30s. I wouldn't
be able to do it. like you you can't get
anyone here. Whereas in Asia, you can,
you know, 27 28 and you don't have to
pay either, you know, like
and yeah, you could say that they're [ __ ] indirectly
using you for your [ __ ] money, but
they're not. And even if they were,
isn't that what women do here? Go for
rich people that will provide for them?
So, it's the same [ __ ] But no, in Asia,
um there are women that want
relationships when you don't have to
pay. No, there is. Trust me, there is.
There is. And the Philippines, it's not
all about paying. Yes, a lot of them you
have to pay.
I was thinking of going to Doncaster,
you know, Joe, cuz that's where Antman
always used to go out drinking.
Never been there. I said, "Oh, maybe
I'll go there Saturday." But it's a bit
of a trick, isn't it?
Yeah, that's this woman I went on a date
with. She was from York. Another time waster.
Yeah, leads. Leads is expensive.
[ __ ] Leads is expensive, man.
See, that's the thing here. You can't
get any woman here. Like there's there's
this woman. Oh, bro. Even even women
that have kids have got attitude. They
think they're better than you.
Um yeah, there's women that are like
there's this woman that I used I think
she's like 38 and she thinks she's the [ __ ]
They think they're better than everyone.
Even women with kids. Yeah.
So you can't get anyone here at all. But
you go to Asia, you can.
I've never been to Hal either. But
yeah, I've never been there.
No [ __ ] reason, eh?
No [ __ ] reason to go.
Need to go to bed soon. I' going out later.
I can't wait. Yay.
To hear I've got a boyfriend. Yay. I can't wait.
I don't know how I got them women I used
to get in the past
when people are sat there saying that
they they they haven't even kissed
anyone. It's bad.
We should all blame Laney for not having
me in the 1980s.
Huh? Wrong generation, mate.
Wrong [ __ ] gen fuckingeration.
I wish I was born in 1980, man.
I start know it.
I was born here.
I don't even feel like going out much
nowadays, man. I'm just like chilling and eating.
But we will get [ __ ] today. 100%.
See if we get a date for Sunday. Don't think so.
Good old Thursdays, eh? That's just old
school Peter Belly, is it? going out on a Thursday. Yep.
Definitely old school Peter Belly,
mate. I'm so tired.
You'll never quit gambling, Joe. You an addict, fella.
You an addict fella.
You an addict fell.
I need to try and win like [ __ ] 30k.
I really need to try and win like 30
grand, bro. But I don't think that's
ever going to happen.
What if I won 30 grand online and trying
to get that money? See, I don't I don't
care about the buzz no more. I don't
know why I've gone off it.
I'm bored of everything now. Drinking,
gambling. I'm bored of it all.
Serious. I really am bored of it all.
I don't even get urges for it.
Even though winning like 30 grand would be nice, but I
I don't really get the um I don't get
the urge for it.
And even the women thing now, I don't
really have much of a sex drive cuz I
like I'm like, "Okay, I know what it's
going to be like every time I go out now."
it's always going to be the same. So
that's why I said maybe what happened 3
weeks ago was a good thing
cuz now you've accepted that it probably
is always going to be like this now. So
that's a good it was a good thing in a
way and it was going to got the money
back as well. So
do you get me?
But no, I'm not like [ __ ]
nah, I don't I don't get the
I don't really get the B anymore.
Last time I gamble was 100 to 500
on the on the online r. I don't know why. Yeah.
No, you haven't pissed me off, bro. I'm just chilling.
But I'll probably never ever get laid in
this country again unless I use escorts.
How mad is that?
That is mad when you think about it, is it?
It is actually mad. It's very, very unlikely.
Very, very unlikely. Yeah.
So I was thinking of a mad thing. Yeah.
Imagine you went out like Friday, Saturday
every week to a different city. So for
example, Leeds Friday, Leadeds Saturday, Edinburgh Friday, Edinburgh Saturday
every single city do two days. Imagine
how long that would take you. Like just
getting on a drink.
That would be a [ __ ] That must that
would take you months.
Why would I do that, bro? How would I be
able to pull a bird when they're just
going to say they've got a boyfriend?
It is mad though, isn't it?
It is kind of mad how like you can't
meet anyone, in it,
do you know? I think it's strange though
that you can't meet anyone.
No, you would get a [ __ ] date.
You can't even get a [ __ ] date. Oh man.
It's mad, isn't it? It is [ __ ] madness.
But I know like I I've even said this
now, Joker, like you know when people
say, "Oh, you'll meet someone." I don't
even say you won't.
I don't even I won't even say you won't. I say
you've got more chance of winning the lottery.
Yeah, you you might do, but you probably
got more chance of winning the lottery
to be honest.
You probably got more chance of putting
500 pound on roulette and getting it to
a million pound
statistically speaking. So, I mean, you
could apply that logic to the [ __ ]
lottery. But yeah, anyways, imagine you
went to every city and you done Friday
and Saturday in every city, Joe. It
would take you months, isn't it?
Bristol Friday, Saturday.
Next week, Cardiff Friday, Saturday.
Plymouth, Birmingham leads, Newcastle, Glasgow.
[ __ ] hell. Imagine that. Could you imagine that?
Oh, [ __ ] me, man.
Nope. I don't get any matches on dating apps.
See, this is what Okay, so this is what
I'm saying to you now. Like remember I
was saying to you earlier about
dismissing my struggles. So that's
and I can hold a conversation. I'm a
good texter. I'm good at approaching. I
can hold a conversation at any time with anyone. So
any thoughts on the women leading me on?
See, this is what I'm saying. There's no
point because you're always going to
dismiss my struggles. So, there's no
point of any kind of debate. There's no
point talking about it because whatever
you you are shown, you will just make up
stuff anyways. So, there's little to no
point even wasting energy on it to be
honest with you. There's no point of any opinions.
I know what I've done. I know what I've
tried. I know what I done three weeks
ago. I know what I've texted. I know how
I text and that's it. You know,
there's no point talking about it really because
why wouldn't I be able to hold a
conversation? I mean, I've showed where
people have not replied back to the
first message. I've showed where people
have agreed to meet me and never.
So, you're not going to talk your way
out of everything?
you're not going to be able to talk your
way out of that. So, it's like you're
talking to someone like me, bro, that's
met thousands and thousands of women
and there's been different situations.
Cuz people say, "Oh, well, say for
example, someone says, "Oh, well, you
asked them to meet too quickly." Then I
say, "Oh, really? Okay. But then what
about the one that never replied in the
first place? What about the one that
agreed to meet me?" and inflict.
So, you know, it's like there's that you
at what at some point you you know,
you're going to run out of excuses.
You literally are going to run out of excuses.
And that's what it is, you know,
and that's it, bro. And that's it. So,
I never say about numbers that don't
reply because I already know the excuse.
Oh, well, they gave you their number cuz
they felt uncomfortable. So, it's just
no no point. But I would like somebody
to answer me why these people give their
numbers, lead you on, agree to meet just
to dump you in the end. that always
seems to get dismissed because there's
no excuse for it. So that's it.
What do you mean I've never showed them the successes?
What What am I supposed to show them?
What? I got a date in April.
I think the last time I got a date was April. So
that's my problem.
So that's that's why
it's the leading on and [ __ ] I can't
stand it, bro. Why? I can't be [ __ ]
What the [ __ ] am I supposed to show them, bro?
They're the ones that can't hold a [ __ ] combo.
They're the ones that can't.
So why why do you do that anyways? Why
do you dismiss people's struggles, you know?
Why do why do you dismiss people's struggles?
Cuz I have it where people have actually
agreed to meet and then they never just
like I was supposed to meet someone last Saturday.
Does it like I don't know, bro. Does it
not suit you or
what's the story?
Why don't you ever mention it?
Because you have there's no you can't
talk your way out of it.
It's because there's no way you can talk
your way out of that one.
You can talk your way you can talk your
way out of people not replying.
You can talk your way out of maybe
somebody stop replying, but you can't
talk your way out of somebody that leads
you on, agrees to meet you, then don't.
That you can't disagree with
because what what can you say?
No, but you're supposed to be No, no,
no, no, no, no. But you're supposed to
be throwing back about it. You're
supposed to think, "What the fuck?" So
when when you always say to me, "Oh,
what do you want?" that what what do you
want them to say? I want them to be
shocked by it. I don't want anyone to
feel sorry for me. I don't I don't
[ __ ] want sympathy. I just want
people to think to actually understand
how bad it is. Then if they understood
how bad it is, then that's it. But they
seem to go on and on and on
as if um
as if you haven't shown them anything.
give an example right here actually.
Where is she?
She said this was
she said all the things we talked about
previously. I think you should see
someone because you either like it or
not. And by the way, I can't blame you.
You have resentment against women. I
replied in quotation marks. You have
resentment against women.
Do you think I maybe I feel that way
because I've had bad experiences and
being led on and took the piss out,
flaked, and ghosted. I showed you my
experiences, but you seem to dismiss
them. I guess my experiences don't suit
you. It really feels like my experiences
don't suit you, hence why you dismiss
them. And throughout the whole thing I
showed, she didn't acknowledge any of
the things I showed. So,
it is weird, isn't it? Cuz she was
trying to say about how like um
she was saying [ __ ] like, "Oh, you you
you ask people to meet too soon." So
then I showed her like messages where
people would just randomly disappear. And
yeah, so then she could obviously talk
her way out of that one.
There's one here from New Zealand, France,
Ireland, England. There's loads so many
screenshots I've got. So, it comes to a
point where it's like, [ __ ] hell. How
many excuses are you are you really
going to keep making, you know?
Well, like I said, I believe all women
aren't the same when I'm proven
different, when I'm proven wrong. I
think that's meeting in the middle. That
is I think that is meeting in the middle. Cuz
why would you believe something that
you've never seen? That's so ridiculous.
Why would you think all women are
different when every single woman you meet
do exactly the same thing? And all of
the all of the women that you see other
people meet do exactly the same thing. So
I would not believe something that I've never seen.
My whole argument is I've gave them
several chances to prove me wrong and
none of them can. So what I say and what
you say is ridiculous. It doesn't make
sense. What I say and what you say, it's
up to them. And I've gave them chances.
Look, I gave someone last week. I was
supposed to meet someone. Was it last
week? Yeah, it was last Saturday. So I
gave somebody the chance and the benefit
of the doubt to prove me wrong. And what
did they do? Come up with a [ __ ] excuse.
So we are at we are sort of occasionally
you know trying to get them to prove us
wrong but none of them seem to can none
of them seem to be able to. So
they all really do seem to do exactly
the same thing.
They do really do similar stuff.
They they they lead people on and [ __ ]
You can't possibly
Yeah. There you go then.
Yep. It's always the same thing. Just
leading on and playing games. That's
literally all they ever do,
you know? That's literally all they ever do. Yeah.
So, like I say, I believe it when I see it.
And if they really are all different,
then it should be easy for them to prove you wrong. You know,
it's one of the reasons why I never
believe in God.
Well, what do you want me to do? Pretend
that they're not all the same. And
pretend I've not had bad experiences.
Like, like I told you, how would you
feel if you went out, you got 10
numbers, you spent £5,600, I don't know
what the [ __ ] I spent it on, and you
don't even have a date and the only
person that replied messed you around.
I mean, let's get better experiences and
then maybe the mindset will change
because that's how your mindset is.
Like, what do what do you want me to do?
Go out today and think that it's going
to change? No. Cuz it's not going to
change. Wouldn't it make more sense me
going out today knowing it's not going
to change and then be surprised if it
does than me think it's going to change,
it doesn't, and then get annoyed by it.
cuz I think to think the worst is
probably the best cuz then you're not
disappointed by it.
Let's use today for example when I
finally go sleep in a minute. What do
you think is going to happen, bro?
Come on. Let's hear it from the horse's
mouth. What do do you think that this
time round is going to be different than
all the other times?
Do you really really think that it's
like one of your parents doing the [ __ ] lottery?
It's not going to be different this time. So,
I didn't spend it on a day. I don't know
where the money went. I don't know where
the [ __ ] money went,
but I spent a good 500 600 pound. I
don't know why I sp Yeah. [ __ ] Basically,
well, I have moved on. I'm going out
today drinking anyways cuz I want to
drink and I'm going to try knowing that
I'm not going to get anywhere.
I mean, I have moved on. What the [ __ ]
It will never change with women. I know
that for a fact.
But what you're saying don't make sense
because you're you're saying that all
women are different. You want people to
believe that all women are different.
But how can someone believes something
that they've never been shown? See, you
might think I'm being difficult and I'm
being awkward, but I'm not. It's the
truth. Cuz every single time you give a
woman a chance to show different, it's
always the same [ __ ] So leading on mind games,
it's it's [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] Just like that one in Finland. Time waster.
Do you accept that you're going to
approach me with that? All right.
Yes, I'm very very aware of that. But
we're not again, we're not talking about
that. Okay. Well, let me let me answer
you this question. Well, dating apps
don't work. So, that's all we have. And
B, it's not about them
not trying to meet anybody or trying to
meet someone. It's that is a small part
of it. It's the whole them giving their
number, leading people on, you know,
there's no excuse for that and that's
mostly what they do, you know. Um, so yeah,
we're not talking about that, bro.
That's going to happen every time you go out.
But I know I'll get some numbers today
and I'll be led on like always.
Like [ __ ] always
cuz that's always what happens. They
just lead people on for their own sick entertainment.
So what and anyways about these
successes. So you want me to tell people
on Reddit that are what? I approached
8,000 women and I got laid four or five times.
It's not exactly good, is it?
It's not exactly [ __ ] good, is it? Come on. So,
do you know what's so weird, Joe, is
people on Reddit tell people to cold
approach as well, and then when you cold
approach, they tell you not to cold approach.
[ __ ] weird, isn't it?
So, we're talking about them leading people on.
That's the main part of it, you know. So,
and the negatives outweigh the positives. Um,
I know what happens. You get friend-zoned.
Yeah, I know what happens. You get friend-zoned.
So, back to the whole women.
So, if all women were different,
why do so many of them do the same stuff?
Lead on, mind [ __ ] same attitude.
They do a lot of the same stuff for
people that are different.
See, with me, I'd be very concerned if
somebody was the same as me. You know,
I'd be very, very concerned.
These women seem to do a lot of the same
stuff as one another for people that are
that are apparently different.
Do you not find that a bit strange, J?
Do you not find that very very very very strange?
I used to think I was m I used to think
I was [ __ ] immature to be honest. Yeah. So,
and there's been no successes recently.
There's been nothing for a long long
time. So there's nothing to really bring up.
Oh, I got a date last April. Who wasted
my time? I mean, what is there to exact
what is there to exactly bring up?
Do you know what, bro? I might not even
go out today to be honest with you. I'm
so cozy in bed
and I don't know, man. I just can't be [ __ ]
No, this is the problem. The thing is,
Joker, you know, the more you think
about this, bro, the more you just see
it as just a waste of time.
The more you think about it, bro, this
is the thing.
The more you think about this, bro, the
more you realize that, bro, there's like
there's just no point, you know? I I
I've kind of gone off um drinking now as
well to be fair.
I kind of have gone off drinking now.
I used to love drinking. Now I don't really drink.
I'm [ __ ] starving I am, man. All I do
is eat, eat, eat, eat, eat. So
nah, I don't think I'm going to,
brother. I'm definitely going to do it
next week, though. 100% because it's my
birthday. So, I think I'm really dumb, bro.
Think I really am, bro. Seriously,
I can't justify it.
This is what happens, man, when you've
had too many bad experiences.
I'd rather just get a nice takeaway,
bro. Just chill, man. [ __ ]
going out in the cold.
Yeah, I'd rather save myself for my
birthday to be fair.
Let's just smell a drink now. I don't
like the thought of drinking. I used to love drinking.
Don't know what happened.
I think where I've had so many bad experiences.
I just don't I just want to like your
priorities are supposed to change as you're older.
Like I was thinking of pissing the ball
off, you know, like going out every week
drinking to show I can afford it. But
that's just immature, is it? Cuz he
seems to think I can't afford to go out
every week when I literally can.
I could go out today and spend over
a,000 pound if I wanted to and I'd still
have money. But I mean, it's just like
I can't be [ __ ] bro. I don't know
what it is, man.
I don't know why I feel that way, man.
But I'll only drink Guinness now anyway
as well. [ __ ]
But I'd like to think the next time I go
out, it doesn't annoy me.
Hopefully it doesn't. I don't think it
will. I don't think it will cuz I expect
it now cuz the 10 numbers and no date. I'm hoping
I'm hoping it doesn't. It shouldn't do.
You know what it is now. You know, as
long as I don't get led on, then
I think the work the bad thing about it
was I looked my best as well. So, I
actually looked maxed. So, there was no reason why
I didn't get a date.
There's literally no reason. Like, you
should It's not like you got a date with
somebody and they wanted to take things
slow cuz So, that's better than nothing.
You literally got [ __ ] nothing.
I don't think you understand like how
severe that is.
That's really bad, bro. It's [ __ ] bad.
But it took me like two weeks to recover
from that, bro. It was depressing as [ __ ]
Not even a single day.
That is [ __ ] bad, bro. That is [ __ ] bad. Hey, babe.
Do not think that's bad, Joe. It's [ __ ] wild.
Nah. Why am I going to meet Monty again
for him to keep going on about [ __ ]
Natalie? [ __ ] that, man.
All he goes on about is that [ __ ] Natalie.
And he's doing it all wrong. He's
playing the game all wrong. You know, he
could have played it if he was with me
that he could have when he met me, when
I met him a few months ago, he could
have played it right. you know, he could
have easily played it right, like
made her jealous and like he plays the
whole thing so wrong and he should know
at his age, but he doesn't
like at least with me in the USA easy
thing. I was younger
so and that was with experience, you
know, I know what they're like. I know
what these women are like now.
And I don't think it was as bad as that.
Like, yeah, I might have been obsessed
or whatever, but I don't think it was.
He doesn't stop. like he doesn't stop like so
but he could have easily like if he had
like tried to meet other women and just
ignored her they always come back and
you know he doesn't understand
but he can't have had much experience
with women cuz I could never fall in
love now nah and even if I did I'd know
what they're like so I would just expect
somebody to just dump me. So, I don't
give a [ __ ]
So, it's strange, isn't it? It's
strange. It is weird.
Very weird, lad.
Yeah. I like that USA. Is he
cuz she lovebombed me.
So when I've been lovebombed,
I think it was a case of like I had
approached and approached and approached
and approached and approached and failed
and then I finally found somebody that
seemed right, you know.
So I was just happy for somebody to give
me a chance. So I didn't even know they
wanted sex. So that was what happened with me.
and no one's ever offered me their
number before that and no one's ever
offered me their number since.
So I just thought, you know, it was a
one in a life. Things like that is like
just one in a lifetime where you will
approach somebody and they will offer
you their number. There's and they just
want to [ __ ] you straight away. That
that was one in a lifetime.
So yeah. And
that's why it pissed me off.
And the way they went about it was nasty as well.
They went about it really nastily
and narcissistic, but people didn't
understand it even though when I'd
explain it and stuff.
So that's why it pissed me off
cuz we had made like
cuz we had made plans and stuff. So
that was a mad thing.
But even if like they the plans was
never going to happen, I didn't think
they was just going to [ __ ] disappear.
But they just disappeared.
What the [ __ ] So,
but yeah, but I didn't go on like him,
man. [ __ ] me, you know. Yeah.
[ __ ] [ __ ] man. [ __ ] [ __ ] Proper dick.
Indeed, Joker. Indeed.
What do you think of it all?
I was right with the USA thing, weren't I, Joe?
Somebody could have really ended up dead.
It was quite scary, bro. When that [ __ ]
used to It's quite scary.
That would never happen again. No, I'm
not obsessed at all. I'm not. No, I'm
just comparing it to Monty's thing. I'm
not obsessed at all, bro. I'm really
not. No, I'm [ __ ] not obsessed. I'm
just comparing it to Monty's thing. And
why I was like [ __ ] because of that?
I'm not obsessed at all, bro. You
[ __ ] mad. I was excited to go out on Saturday.
See, back then I could actually blame myself.
When I got these dates, I'd mess him up
by talking about her. But now I don't
even get dates. And then it's like when
you finally moved on, now you can't meet anyone.
So when you couldn't move on, you'd meet
all of these women that would give you a
chance. So now you have moved on. Well,
we moved on [ __ ] ages ago, but you
now you would ever find someone that's
that wants to give you a chance.
See, it's God [ __ ] with you about it. Yep. So,
yeah, those days are gone, bro. Those
days are gone.
It's gotten harder, isn't it?
It's definitely gotten harder. Yeah,
that Ricky Milling. Have you seen that
Ricky Milling account? Jo
[ __ ] white knight [ __ ] So
he's he's another white knight.
He's another white knight, lad.
Sticks up for women.
I feel bad, but these [ __ ]
So I don't think I'll go out today. I
was going to go out today, but I'm too [ __ ]
The more I think about it, bro, the more
it's just not worth it.
It's a [ __ ] thingy.
Money needs to get off YouTube in a
needs to get off YouTube.
what he really [ __ ] does to be fair.
I was arguing with this woman on this
police video. She's like, "Oh, all of
the people watching the police, it was
um some guy beating up the police." I
said, "I would have watched as well. I
[ __ ] hate the police. [ __ ] the
police. They're corrupt."
She was like,
"Well, let's hope you don't get stabbed
because you'll be begging for them to
help you find a big bad guy that done
it. The big bad nasty man that did that
to you." I said, "I have, you know, I've
actually had my phone snatched off me."
And I've never run to the police. I hate
I actually hate them, bro. Like, if I
saw one get beat up, I'd watch. I hate police, bro.
It's [ __ ] corrupt as [ __ ] Yep.
Yeah. He's got long-term effects as
well. He needs to [ __ ] just
He just needs to meet me again. We'll go
out again, man. I was thinking of going
to Birmingham. Do you know with when
that stuff was happening with Monty
and Money Mike? I was thinking of just
going there, bro.
I think like I was thinking of just
going there, bro,
and [ __ ] teaming up with Monty and
smashing them both in when I was
watching that [ __ ] bro. It was annoying
me. Even though Monty's a snake and
that, but Mike's worse than Monty, bro.
I can't stand that money m bro. And I
used I've met him a few times. He used
to be all right, but I've seen what he
does on YouTube.
I'd love for that [ __ ] [ __ ] to tell
me to [ __ ] come around the corner,
bro. I slap him in his face, bro. I met
him when he was in London. When he come
to London, he was [ __ ] himself, bro.
He ain't nothing. He ain't nothing, bro.
He ain't nothing, bro. Trust. He ain't
that. Mike ain't nothing.
He's worse than Monty. Even though Monty
might have snaked or whatever, bro.
Like, I've known Monty years. So, when
you compare him to [ __ ] Mike, he's
not even bad.
Timmy's not that bad either to be fair.
But he will always switch that mic. He's
got about 100 troll accounts. He's worse
than [ __ ] Timmy and [ __ ] Monty. You understand?
Trust me, bro. I'd love for him to tell
me to come around the corner, bro. [ __ ] [ __ ]
But there probably like three of them in it.
But yeah, I I was thinking of going to
meeting Monty again, but it's pointless,
bro. All he's going to do is talk about
Natalie and I'm going to get the blame,
so there's no point. He still blames me
for that Natalie thing, by the way.
Yeah, but to be fair, Tiger's not really done anything.
Tiger's strange, but he's all right, you
know? He keeps out of [ __ ] Tiger's
harmless, but he is strange. He's weird,
but he's harmless at the same time, you know?
But that mic is [ __ ] bro. Like, I've
seen him what he does on there.
I've seen him comment on nons legs his
thing and it's just annoying, bro. back. So,
but with Monty, the thing is is that like
if I bet him, he would just keep going
like that and that Yeah,
I went to [ __ ] Birmingham and spent £200.
Didn't seem to make much [ __ ]
difference, did it? [ __ ] Monty.
He just needs to go and [ __ ] focus on
these children, bro. To be fair, he
needs to just get off this [ __ ] and
focus on his children and just [ __ ] NG off
cuz you could have tried with other
women, bro. When he was with me, he had
a chance. He was buying [ __ ] drink, lads.
[ __ ] But he wouldn't do it when every
single woman was better than Natalie. So,
but then you could say the same thing
about USA is he isn't it Jo? Every
single other woman I had been with was
better than her.
So, and it still didn't feel the same
for like 2 years until it was over. So, but
and it was weird cuz it's not like I
couldn't get any other women cuz I cuz I
got other women back then as well.
That's the thing. That's the weird thing about it.
They must have thought I was [ __ ] crazy, bro.
mad. Some of these people
They must have really thought I was mad,
bro. I was younger then as well.
See what mine was weird cuz it's not
like I couldn't get any better because I
could get better and I did get better
and then and then I was going to say,
"Oh, well maybe I'm just comparing it to
Monty's. I don't like the [ __ ] bro."
Like I'm just saying I'm comparing it to
Monty's. I'm just saying that then we
can say, "Oh, well maybe they're
American." That's not an excuse cuz I
met loads of other Americans. So,
I don't know what it was, bro. [ __ ]
knows. So, you know when you say Monty,
that's the best Monty can get. That
weren't the best I could get cuz I had
better and could get better.
So, I don't know. I don't know what it was.
Who knows, bro? But I understand what it
is with him. Obviously,
it is [ __ ] He's He's [ __ ] bro.
Really really is [ __ ]
He is really bad, bro.
So, it did go away in the end. It didn't
go away in the end, bro.
Off the [ __ ] god knows how long.
That was annoying as [ __ ] that was, bro.
I used to hate that. I used to get drunk
and tell everyone about it.
Then it got less and less and less and
less and less.
[ __ ] that, bro.
That's what's going to happen to Monty, in it.
That's what's going to happen to Monty.
Yeah. I will never forget them dark
times, bro. Back in the old house.
And I actually bought a new phone as
well. I bought a new phone to Messenger. Remember, J. So yeah,
Marvel was a weird one
because I didn't even like them to begin
with when I when I saw them again. I
didn't like them.
I didn't like them. So like what I'm
basically saying is I didn't like them.
When I when I approached them,
obviously I might have had a few drinks.
I can't remember. But
when I when I saw them again, when I met
them, I didn't really I was like, "Oh, okay.
Just stick with it." And then after
that, I was like, "Whatever." So,
because the fact that they blocked me
and they disappeared
made Peter Belly's feelings stronger.
Whereas if they didn't block me and
never spoke to me again, then it would
have been like, "Oh, just whatever." You
probably would never spoke to them
again. So that's also how they can play
a game because if them if they distance
themsel from you and you like them even
a little bit, that could make you like them more.
So, do you remember that Australian
from a couple of months ago
in the nightclub? They messaged once,
they disappeared, and I was like, "Now I want more."
And then I was in love for like a total
of 5 days and then got over it. Yeah, man.
So you you understand for like 4 days
and then so yeah that's how people um
you can get stronger as well. So
it is [ __ ] though like because it's like
if you ever feel that
it's weird though cuz if you fall in
love with someone no one else will do
until you actually get over it and you
feel like you'll never meet somebody
ever again that you'll fall in love with
but then you will or like at least so
it's [ __ ] man. I hate that, bro.
That is horrible, man. Now Monty's
dealing with it.
Yeah, cuz she was being a prick.
Yeah, she was being a [ __ ] prick. That's why.
Yeah, she was a [ __ ] man.
It's like back when she landed into the United States,
Joe, she completely turned.
We would have been good, man. She was
She was a year and a bit older than me.
I think she was born in April 96. So,
she was a she was a couple of months
older than my sister. A my sister's
June. She's April. So,
it's kind of weird when you think about
it, is it? She was older than my sister, but [Music] no.
So what you're saying is
So what you're saying is Joe
So what you're saying is I can't let I
can't let things lie.
Is that what you're basically saying? I
couldn't let Yeah. Yeah. Back then I
couldn't. Now I could cuz I'm older now.
But yeah, back then I couldn't let it
lie. [ __ ] that. No. [ __ ] that.
Them [ __ ] were laughing at us. [ __ ]
that. No, no, no, no, no. Yeah.
Them [ __ ] were laughing at us.
Monty man's life has been ruined all on
the same website. You can watch Cal Freezy on.
I was watching some Cal Freezy videos.
Joe, do you know who that is?
He's a good YouTuber.
He's a [ __ ] weird looking fella. him.
You know the FIFA lads, Joe?
You know Cal Freezy and them the the FIFA lads?
You don't know about the FIFA lads?
How the [ __ ] do you not know who the
Sidemen are? I used to live by the side
men. They're very famous.
I don't know how you don't know the
Sidemen. They're KSI and stuff.
Nah, you must know who they are. Don't
be silly. Of course, you know they are.
I used to live near them.
I saw I saw one of them before. I spoke
to him. He didn't He didn't really want to talk.
Yeah, I see him. And I've I've seen him
twice. That one. They used to live by
me, but he he didn't talk.
Nah, I didn't want to talk.
You don't know. How do you not know
these big YouTubers, Joe?
But yeah, anyways, back to the subject.
USA Izzy was addicted as [ __ ] bro.
She was a
That was addicting. That was addicting.
Isn't that right, Joe?
And do you not remember out of all of
that time frame, I come out with these mad sayings
like taking a baby away from its mama? [Laughter]
Oh, well, I got Where the [ __ ] did I
come out with these things?
taking a baby away from its mama.
[ __ ] mad, bro.
The best is it? Yeah. [Music]
So, what's Monty going to do anyways?
What's he going to do?
[ __ ] trying to get me on Discord with
the [ __ ] five great pedos
trying to get me.
You should have just saw USA Izzy's
boobs. He had the best boobs, bro. Oh my god.
They're better than that. way better.
I missed the kisses and stuff for a
while, you know, the lovely kisses and
stuff. I like to feel loved, you know.
It's nice to feel loved.
I was thinking about them like a couple
of days ago, bro,
when I was pulling my plonker. Yep.
I think I have a wank bank.
I have a wank bank, bro.
I don't I do watch porn, but I don't
really like watching it.
I think about when I got a [ __ ] in the Attiway.
Sometimes Sig, sometimes the Nottingham
one, sometimes USA.
So I just I just have a wank bank.
I don't really like to watch pawn. Nah.
S had big boobs as well. Yeah.
No, we're talking about someone from America.
Yeah. Do you remember Izzy's boyfriend
that was messaging me? I'm going to come
to London. I said come to London then.
He's not even with her anymore.
Yeah. I don't know why me and me and I
should reunite in it.
Me and Izzy should reunite in it, Joe.
Me and the original Izzy. Nah.
Never, mate. That would never happen.
I'm surprised she never ever tried
getting back with me
considering I had more money than Kenji.
I have more money than Kenji. Is weird, isn't it? Little Isabella.
Isabelli was my first kiss. Joe,
how do you feel about that? She was my
first ever kiss. Oh,
do you remember them little videos, Joe?
The little roulette video.
A, that was lovely.
I used to call her My Little Pony.
Yeah, I used to call her My Little Pony show.
Yes. At times. At times. That times [Laughter] madness. Yeah.
I don't have the energy to go out, bro. Today,
I don't have the [ __ ] energy, mate.
I had burger last night as well.
I'm starving, man. I'm starving.
No, I'm not depressed at all. I'm just chilling, man.
See, look, Timmy's uploaded. It's never
going to stop this. Yeah, you know, we
used to make jokes about this [ __ ] bro.
And it's actually going to happen. Like,
someone is going to get hurt or sectioned.
Someone is definitely going to get hurt
or sectioned on here, bro.
We used to make jokes about it. We used
to take the piss out of it. But it will
happen. It will happen, bro. It will
happen. Trust me.
Yeah, it will happen. [Laughter]
[ __ ] madness, bro.
I'm not depressed at all, bro. I'm just
chilling, man. I'm just bit tired to be fair.
He's never going to get off YouTube, is he? Huh?
Never. I can't believe he was actually
living in the tent. That's mad. That is
See, I was like sleeping on the stairs
at one point, but mine weren't over YouTube.
Well, it was but like
I mean it was but kind of like
it was but it was more
No, it wasn't because I got kicked out.
No, I got kicked out before that.
It was before the YouTube thing.
See, I have no long-term effects from
YouTube. Whereas Monty does.
That's why he needs to get off of YouTube. You know,
he will never get off YouTube though.
This is what I mean. Is his birth Oh,
it's his birthday today as well.
[ __ ] I heard his dick picture got
sent around, Jo. [ __ ] Yeah,
I heard like Natalie sending his dick picture around.
What do you think of USA? Izzy, Joe,
would you would you go on a date with
her if you were single? Her
little accent was so cute.
I don't know. I haven't seen it
and I don't want to to be honest.
Would you go on a date with her?
Cute, isn't it?
Do you like her?
I ain't seen his dick, bro. I want to
[ __ ] see his dick.
You'll laugh though. But I like October.
I like I like it like this. A bit cold.
Don't like the Don't like the heat
to be fair.
I don't even think I'd let that give me
a [ __ ] to be honest.
Oh, I don't have a pick of her, bro. I
don't have a pick of her anymore.
Do you like her, Joe? He just
What about USA? Izzy. Would you [ __ ] USA? See,
you get with USA. No.
Yeah, but you'd still bang her in it.
Yeah, she isn't.
The Brazilian one was better, is it? Yeah.
My favorite was the Italian one.
She was sexy, but just another time waster
going on a date for the sake of it. That
was the best one. I think
I actually met her in a Weather Spoons.
I like her. I like Weather Spoons. I
like a nice central London Weather Spoons.
That's where I like doing my approaches. Yep.
I would have loved that Italian one
though. Oh my god, that would have been
perfect. The Portuguese one was good.
Yeah, that was years ago. That's when I
come back from [ __ ] Belgium, man. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, she was good.
We held hands and everything. Yeah,
that was [ __ ] years ago, bro.
No, she just kept making me wait for a kiss.
So, we met the second time. She didn't
want to kiss. She said she wants to take things slow.
But I don't know, bro. I don't know. I
just It's just all exhausting to be
honest with you.
No, I said I don't think I I found her that attractive
even though she looked completely fine.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't
She looked completely fine.
I don't know. What do you think?
I'll never forget the time I went in the
casino with 150, walked out with four
grand, joker cash,
get a nice multiplier. Uh yeah.
So what do you think would have happened
if I kept meeting her? Jo
I don't know, bro. I don't know.
What do you mean I couldn't be binary
relationship? What do you mean?
See, with the last one I went on with
that Italian, I don't think I done
anything wrong trying to kiss her cuz we
was holding hands and we was vibing in it. So,
we was holding hands and vibing. So, I
didn't think it was the wrong move to
um to go for the kiss.
What do you mean binary? Yep.
That was years ago though. But that
proves my point cuz there's been no recent ones.
Sig was a weird one. She was trying to
say that I was too old for her, too
young for her, yet she [ __ ] me, which
don't make sense.
She didn't even want to [ __ ] at first.
She's like, "Oh, I'll take you around,
but we're not going to have sex." And
stuff. I said, "Okay."
And then she was just wanking me off and that
I was just playing with her tits. And
then she just jumped on my dick.
Weird. It's very, very weird. But I said
I was going to take her to Nando. I never did. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, it's [ __ ] up, man.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] up. E,
you think this whole dating thing is funny?
I don't find any of it funny, me.
How can you find it funny, Joe? I don't
find it funny, me.
Oh, I had this disgusting bagel. I don't
think I told you.
I ordered a bagel, right? I don't think
I come back on YouTube since then. And,
bro, I'm sure the bagel was off.
It started smelling. It smelt like fish
and [ __ ] I think someone took a [ __ ] in
it or something. Bro, it was nasty. Oh
my god. It put me off eating for like 3
days, 4 days.
It was a salt beef bagel and it smelt like fish.
It was horrible, bro. I'm saw someone shattered it.
[ __ ] nasty, bro. It was disgusting,
man. It was [ __ ] vile. Oh, I got a
refund from Just Eat.
There was some place near the area, but
it was I ordered from it before and it was fine.
You could smell it as well, but I just
thought at first it was like it was it
was maybe because it was cold or
something. They done it on purpose. I
don't know what the [ __ ] it was.
Oh, it's disgusting. Vile.
Must have been off. Must have been.
They're lucky I didn't go back with it
and [ __ ] threw it in their face. Dirty [ __ ] Yeah.
Do you reckon Monty Man will be on
YouTube today, Joe?
Nah, he could [ __ ] he could still he
could still build his life back up again.
He could try to meet a woman, ditch Natalie,
you know, go see his kids, you know.
There's still things you could do, man.
It's not that deep.
Fairly is [ __ ]
Getting a haircut in this weather. No
thanks. That makes me feel cold. Oh, I
couldn't imagine having that. I'm
getting a haircut for my birthday, but
Oh, [ __ ] that, man.
I won't be going out later. I'm going to
It's too cold. Too cold. Can't be asked.
No, [ __ ] that, man.
Next week. Definitely my birthday.
Going off the drinking, Joe.
gets boring when you've done it so many times.
Yeah, it does get boring.
[ __ ] I'm tired as [ __ ] man.
I am so tired, man. I'm I'm hungry
again. I'm so Why am I so hungry?
I don't even live near spoons anymore.
No. Why would I be getting an escort?
I'm not using them escorts, bro.
Don't really want to after last time.
Why? I haven't been to an escort since.
Can't be bothered with them anymore,
bro. I can live without [ __ ] sex. I'm not asked.
I can live without it, bro. I'm not asked.
[ __ ] hungry. I am. All I do is eat in this weather.
I eat like four times a day.
It's bad, man.
I'm so Yeah.
I can live without sex, Joe. Something
that you can't do. Yep.
I've been eating loads of piggies
lately, Joe. I've been eat I went to the
calf, right? Um not yesterday, the day
before and I had four bacon,
two sausages, two egg, and mushrooms.
I'm a fat [ __ ] bastard.
I love my little piggies.
Oh, I'm a fat bastard, man.
Really fat [ __ ] I am.
I love bacon. I've always loved bacon.
But I got put off eating pork, you know,
for like a week. Seeing how ugly [ __ ]
the pigs are. Seeing how ugly the pigs are,
it put me off like eating it for a little bit.
But I love Biggies.
Yeah, I had Burger King last night.
I had a Chinese last night as well, but
I didn't pay for that one. Yeah, it's
not a joke, man.
Sick of you just eating this weather.
I want a vindaloo.
I want a vindaloo. A certain person
can't have a vindaloo. Isn't that right, Joe?
No, it's not for the white um
the white scrawny [ __ ]
[ __ ] no muscle [ __ ]
Had Domino's the other day.
I'm hungry, bro. I'm really hungry. Oh,
why am I hungry again?
Well, Monty man will be going live soon
talking about Natalie.
[ __ ] hell, it gives me a headache.
Yep. I love food.
I love onions as well.
I love food.
Yeah, he's going to talk about Natalie.
Maybe I should go to Birmingham today to
see the [ __ ] show. Nah. and
saying we don't have USA anymore to give
us some milk. Jo,
but I'm very sleepy.
Yeah, I was [ __ ] thinking of going
the other day, bro. They were pissing me
off watching this [ __ ] going around
in circle [ __ ] I was just going to go
there and be like, "Do you know what? I
have the [ __ ] all of you. I love you
all." No, they get you like that. You
know, when you watch the same repetitive
[ __ ] they're [ __ ] talking about
meeting and they never [ __ ] meet. I
say, "You know what? I love you all.
[ __ ] the lot of you. Come on.
[ __ ] the lot of you [ __ ] I love the
[ __ ] all of you, you know. Yeah, it's [ __ ] annoying.
No, it is annoying, don't it?
Uh, I went to Belgium years ago. Yeah.
Just something to do.
Yeah, just something to do.
You know, uh, Joe Monty man was
paranoid. I was talking to Natalie. You
know, there was somebody that I've got
on my WhatsApp that looked a bit like
her a little bit and he thought it was her.
when it [ __ ] wasn't. Yeah,
I am so hungry and cold. So cold and hungry.
Joker won't meet anyone.
Joker will not meet anyone.
Why do you go for a pint with nons legs, Joe?
You should go for a pint with nons legs.
This is why I hate the cold in the
mornings. It's so [ __ ] cold, man.
Oh, it's bad. It's bad. Bad. Bad. Bad.
Why they going for a P with nons? Uh
Yeah, I do.
Yeah, she had nice milky boobies. Joe,
I should have took a picture and showed everyone.
She's a little horse. She is.
She's a loose cannon.
Do you remember Joe?
You'll be my 25th.
What's up, bro? What the [ __ ]
I don't know what size they were, man.
All I know is they were [ __ ] big. Yeah,
I don't know. Boob sizes.
They weren't escorts.
And escorts do count.
They they they just don't count as a body count.
But they definitely count.
Just like you if you was in the porn
industry, that would count.
That reminds me, I still haven't heard
back. I applied to be a porn star. I
still haven't heard back.
Huh. I should do
it. Takes a while. Antman actually
recommended me. It took them a while to
get back to him.
Yeah, that porn star thing.
uh four or five,
which is bad to be honest, considering
the amount of women I've approached.
Escorts count. They just don't count as
a body count, but they definitely count as experience.
Yeah, I think about four or five.
So, not many.
I think that's like the average.
Nope. But that's the dating game in this country.
Oh, well, no, it's not the age of 18.
Cuz I didn't try until I was 23. So,
no. No, cuz I didn't try when I was 18.
I tried when I was 23, 22, 23,
which is still pretty bad to be honest.
But I didn't try when I was 18. Yeah.
Yeah. But I got No, I got two in a year
before. Three? No.
Three in a year before.
No, I think I got three in a year before.
Did I meet Sig the same year I met USA?
I think I did. I got three in a year before.
Oh, look who's live here.
Joe, did you get the notification as well? [Music]
Five is good. Four. Five is good.
But what's so mad, Joe, is that women
can get laid whenever they want.
It's not fair, is it? No, I do think
it's fair. I No, no, women should have it easier.
That's not But that's what I said. My
problem was never that. My problem was
that even when you put the effort in,
you still don't get anything.
That's the That's the thing about it.
That's the weird thing about it is even
if you look Max and you try, you still
won't get anything.
That's the weird That's the weird thing.
Not the fact that they've got it easier. Yeah.
Why is there loads of women that are
virgins, Joe, or haven't been with many people?
That's strange, isn't it?
That is [ __ ] strange. No, they're [ __ ]
These women are [ __ ] Joe.
But if I was just starting off fresh
now, I probably would never get laid. No, probably not.
I mean, I fingered and had [ __ ] with
people that I've not had sex with. I
think I fingered like three people that weren't escorts. Um, yeah,
but I didn't [ __ ] them. I just fingered Yeah,
it's fun fingering someone, Joe.
It's really fun fingering someone.
Have you ever done it? [ __ ] man.
Yeah, I like fingering.
What's money saying? Yeah.
Do you remember Joe? There's plenty of
room for me on the old plane.
[ __ ] guy with money. I can barely
keep my [ __ ] eyes open, you [ __ ]
I can barely keep my [ __ ] eyes open,
let alone travel to Birmingham.
He is in Birmingham, right?
Hey, don't call me a [ __ ]
You're the one that can't even come on
the hangouts and talk. Oh, [ __ ]
I'm tired as [ __ ] bro.
Okay, tell him tell him I'm I said that
I'm going to go to Birmingham.
Go on his chat and say that I'll go to Birmingham today.
I'm sure Birmingham is decent on a
Thursday. It's got to be. I'm sure it is.
Okay. Go on there and tell him to come
on here. We'll arrange it. [Music]
I can't even be bothered drinking it anymore, bro.
The [ __ ] thought of it, man.
I am so cold and hungry. [Laughter]
Yeah. Go on his thing.
Go on his thing and tell him I'm him.
Go on. Tell him to Yeah.
Tell them to come on the thing.
I kind of feel bad for money. [Music]
I think I got worms, you know.
Look, honey. Why did you put the link up?
I can't give you my number, lad. Sorry.
Yeah, it's a good day as well. Thursday,
tell him to come. Tell him I'll come and
hang out and meet up. Yeah.
Why do you want my number, bro? I'll
give you it. I'll give you I'll give you
it. Give you it. Um it is
my WhatsApp is 07 54 2 38 27 59
I want you to come and um move me up.
See how Mark said, "Monty, come b me if
I have a drink with you."
No, you have to go to Monty. It's
Monty's birthday. You can't do that. Oh,
you still John.
Yeah, he needs to come here and I'll go
to Birmingham. We need to arrange it.
I know when you're born, Joe. You're
born in August.
Are you a Scorpio like me? I'm a
Scorpio. What are you?
Wait, why don't you meet Mike and Timmy?
Yeah, that's a good point.
I don't know. I just guess you were born in August.
I gave you my number then. Message me. Joker.
I'm a Scorpio. You're a Scorpio.
Um, Lord J's a Scorpio. LT's a Scorpio.
Yeah. So, your birthday is November then, I'm guessing.
Bonnie said he's getting sent down. I
can't take him serious, bro. I swear
down. I can't take this guy serious. Yeah.
My mommy from America was born in April, Joe.
Yeah, she was born in April.
Yeah, my mom was born in April.
Good month for it.
No, you can join my panel, bro. [ __ ] off.
Is he actually going to get sent down? I
don't think he's going to get sent down
because they would have they wouldn't
have released him.
Is he actually getting sent down? And I
might go to the court to watch.
I remember I trolled one of the
streamers before, Joe. I said to him I'd
kill him. Do you know Chipmunks? And he
called the police on me and I got I had
to go for an involuntary interview
and they cautioned me. Basically, they
didn't even arrest me.
Yeah, I used to troll them gambling
streamers, bro. [ __ ] Elvin [ __ ]
Melvin, bro. He thought he was going to
get me in prison.
What the [ __ ]
Yo, you're a troll joker. [ __ ] off, man.
[ __ ] off, you [ __ ]
Yeah. Can you go on money? Tell them to
come on my live.
Baby Peter from America. Do you remember
that one Jo? Oh, bless.
I think I got worms. I'm not even
joking. I think there's something wrong
with me, bro. [ __ ] man.
Are you live? Yeah. Yeah, sure.
I want to meet my money for a piss up.
I only come on YouTube to watch Timmy Aldra's show.
Oh, he's not meeting me. Okay, he's lost
then. I'm watching him, by the way.
Oh, I just wanted to meet for a piss up, man. Yeah,
I need to go in a minute.
I need to go sleepy.
No, [ __ ] that, bro. He's just going to kick,
bro. I'm [ __ ] tired, man. I am
Now I'm thinking of USA Izzy.
Could you imagine, Joe? USA was next to
me now, snuggling me, like just hugging.
That would feel nice. I like hugs.
Could you imagine, Joe,
just hugging, you know?
I want to be hugged.
I want to be huggled.
What's your opinion on that, Joe? To be huggled. What's this?
I like to be huggled
by my mama.
Well, at least you're not going to know
about that, is he?
Are you watching it, John?
Right. Let me join. One second.
See, is this the thanks I get?
Is this the [ __ ] thanks I [ __ ] get?
[ __ ] pair of [ __ ] See,
I can't be [ __ ]
I'm not joining the box anymore. [ __ ] See,
I need to wipe my b my bottom. Oh, [ __ ] Oh [ __ ]
Yeah. [ __ ] that.
I'm not joining the buffers.
See, you see me? I joined.
I joined the box. He says no. So he's lost.
I almost I I got the blame even though
they weren't together. [ __ ] pair of
Right. Remember my little nesticles now. Joe Joseph.
I really want to snuggle that USA. Izzy, man.
She can keep me warm
with her big arms, Joe. [Laughter]
I would have paid for the night out as well. well, Joseph. But no.
Oh, you would say is he? I want to see
if I have a picture of her. No.
Going to show you a picture joke of my mama.
I'm so tired.
I don't know why Monty does this, bro. I really don't.
Nah, not decent. She just had big boobs, Joker.
And I like boobies. So,
yep. Left me all by myself.
She abandoned me. Joker.
No, to be fair, I'm only mentioning it
because of the [ __ ] Monty thing. [Laughter]
This community is sick. [Laughter]
No, this community is too sick, bro. Yeah. Sick.
[ __ ] hell, man. Yep.
That was my mama.
You can ask Joe. Joe will tell you all about it.
Taking a baby away from its mama.
Okay. taking a baby away. Peter Benny
can't get attached anymore because he's
already found his mama. Joker
cuz he's already found his mama.
Because he's already found his mama.
Oh, that's cute, isn't it?
Someone made that up for me. Joker.
Nah, she's my mama.
She has the same hair as me.
Monty needs to stop arguing on his
birthday, bro. What the [ __ ]
birthday. Just get off of YouTube and
meet me in Birmingham. Simple, man.
because he's already found his mama.
Joker, would you sleep with a woman that
slept with 25 other guys?
My friend Antman lives in Thailand now. Joker,
this is his third time and he's never coming back.
He's teaching English.
He said he will never come back to England. Never.
He loves it there.
Yeah. He says England is depressing. The
women aren't interested here.
He said the women just aren't interested
in this country. Joker.
So he goes to Thailand
Choker. They're just not interested in this country.
So you have to go to Asia.
Do you know the maddest thing is Joe is
that these people are
they're just taking a piss out of Monty.
Do you know that Joe?
That's a sad thing. A joker.
Joker, you know the sideman, don't you?
Do you know who the Sidemen are? Joker,
do you know who they are?
How do you know they are Joker?
How do you know these things? Joker.
Do you know what's so mad though is the
people in his chat are just taking the
piss out of him and he doesn't even realize it.
That's the mad thing. He doesn't they're
literally taking the piss out of him and
he doesn't even realize it.
That's the madest [ __ ]
That's so mad.
I want USA to cuddle me, Joe.
To give me a nice cuddle.
I just want a nice huggle, you know, to
be kept warm.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] minion. They are. Yep.
Just been chilling, bro. I don't really
come on here much anymore.
Why am I worse than Monty? Joe.
Hey, Gregy. Do you know what's so mad? I
was watching Star Wars the other day,
and it's so mad how Monty's life's been
ruined over the same website. You can
watch Star Wars on.
So innocent, huh? Yeah, right.
on the same website Monty and Timmy met on.
Why am I worse, Joe? I like boobies. He
has nice boobies.
Why am I worse, man?
I like Star Wars.
I like Star. Did you used to like Star Wars, Grezy?
I used to love Star Wars, man. Like when
I was a kid.
Yeah, it was good. Good story lines.
It wasn't that popular to be honest.
I was watching the Darth Maul fight and
I still remember to this day what
happened before I'd even watched it.
I was going to go out drinking today,
Grezy, but I ain't got energy.
I said to Monty, I'll come to Birmingham
today, have a drink with you, but he
doesn't want that. So, because it's his
birthday, so yeah.
Well, you know what? Somebody said to
me, Joe, that I see women as trophies
and that anyone will do.
That's funny, isn't it?
Yeah, they are trophies.
Anyone will do, Joe.
Do you get it?
Anyone will do. It's true though. They are trophies. Yeah. trophies though.
There something to use and abuse. Yeah.
Troph trophies anyone will do.
There was just one. They were like, "Oh,
you're just talking to me cuz I've got a
vagina. You just want to get with me
because I've got a vagina. That's what they said. Trophies. Well, yeah,
they are trophies, man. I don't even see
them as people.
I see them as [ __ ] scumbags.
Something to use, you know? Nah,
anyone will do.
Anyone will do. How do you How How will anyone do,
Joe? That's [ __ ] how. Huh?
That's silly to say anyone would do.
Yeah. It's funny, isn't it? Trophies. Yep.
Money needs to meet me. Yeah, I said
I'll come to Birmingham today, but he
doesn't want that.
We could have a good day. I'm sure
Thursdays are good in Birmingham.
Yeah. Did you see when they all met up,
Timmy was like, I'll [ __ ] knock him out. Jesus Christ.
Oh, you know Pluto had a baby Grezy
Pluto from Mickey Mouse's clubhouse
and all the same website Monty and
Timmy's meeting up on. You can watch
Baby Pluto. So innocent, isn't it?
Yeah, I had a baby.
But don't think YouTube's innocent
because look at what Mont happened to
Monty and stuff.
I think Joe's rich. Me? I think Joe F is
I think Joe F is rich. I think Joe's got
more money than Ed Sheeran.
Do you think you got more money than Ed Sheeran, Joe?
Of course you do, man. I've seen your
investments and stuff.
I think you're you you're richer than Ed
or the same.
Do you think
I think you've got more money than Ed
Sheer and me?
Yeah. You show them who's boss. You show
them you should work and stuff. Yeah. I
think you've got more money than than
than Ed Shean.
What do you think, Joe? Yeah,
you're rich, man. You're [ __ ] rich.
But your gambling is concerning me. You
don't want to end up like Timmy Eldridge.
I'm surprised you've not lost yet. You
keep winning, but you don't seem to be
losing. Not that I want you to lose, but just saying. Yep.
I'm just saving some money at the
minute. I do this like three times a
year and I'm bored of the drinking. I'm
so bored of drink going out drinking.
Dealing with women. [ __ ] It's boring,
bro. It gets old, man. I just want to
chill, you know. Greasy. I just want to chill.
I still remember USA is his boobs coming
out when she pulled her top up. Joe, it
was a lovely sight.
She was our little [ __ ] wasn't she, Joe? Huh?
What the [ __ ]
No, Joe, you're the goat.
Yeah, Timmy and one of your friends now.
I come here to laugh at Timmy to be
honest. Timmy makes me laugh.
Greasy. Timmy makes me laugh.
Anyone will do.
Anyone will do. That's funny, isn't it?
Some of these people on Reddit. Yeah,
there was this woman that commented.
They was like, "Oh, how much money do
you have left to last you?" This woman
commented saying, "Nothing, I'm fucked."
I was dead. Greasy.
The little avatar. You know the little
avatars on Reddit. She's like, "Nothing. I'm fucked."
That's funny, isn't it? Yeah.
No, that wasn't a one night stand. That
was my mama.
No, it was my mama.
You see women as trophies. That's funny as [ __ ]
They are trophies.
Yeah, we women are evil. Little rascals joker. Anyone would do.
What is it?
This woman says that I'm a very stubborn man.
I'm not stubborn, am I?
She says, she says this, "Yes, you sort
of do. You think about the reward of
sex, but you never express anything
else. You never told me about the type
of women you want to share a life with
or what values she should have. It seems
like anyone will do."
That's funny, is it, Grezy? It seems
like anyone would do.
No, she dismissed my struggles.
She was saying how she wanted to suck my dick.
She lives in France.
I showed her my dick. She says, "I want
to suck your dick and stuff."
She made me come and stuff.
No, she's not my match cuz she's obese.
She's an obese woman.
Yeah, it seems anyone will do what? D.
Well, they have to have big boobies, so
She hates men as well.
She hates men. I hate women. So Yeah. [Music]
Anyone will do.
How will anyone do, Joe? You know I'm quite picky.
Huh? Seems anyone will do.
She's French actually. Yeah, man.
She said, "I'm a perfectionist." She
said, "I'll suck your dick and make you come."
I said to her, "If I got a girlfriend,
would you still suck my dick?" She said,
"Would you like me to?" I said, "Yes,
that's hot. And I can tell you really
want to suck a dick as well, cuz you've
never before." She said, "I don't think
that's a good mindset, though. If you
want a girlfriend that bad, you should
at least be faithful."
I said, "Ah, it's just a blowjob."
Also, the way you was talking about your
perfectionist and would take your time
was really sexy. She said, "Probably."
Yeah, it's not nice. You should want to be faithful. No.
This is crazy.
Seems anyone would do
anyone will do. That's like you know it
greases. Anyone will do.
Yep. Anyone will do with you in it,
Greasy. It's so obvious. Anyone will do Uh,
that's my mama.
I need a woman with big boobies, Joe.
Otherwise, I can't get my nutrients. Do you understand?
I can't be with a woman that doesn't
have big boobies. No.
You know what made me laugh about Monty?
He said that he doesn't want a slag
misses. He said he doesn't want his MS
to be a slag. I was dead
showing her bits on YouTube and that
all on the same website. You can watch Pluto on [ __ ] madness.
That is a madness.
I was laughing at you all day yesterday.
You know, you I can't stop laughing.
I really can't.
Could you imagine
me? He said, "I don't want to slag misses."
That shows us it's that. And then it
made me think of the side men because
they're also on YouTube as well. But not
I don't see none of this stuff happen to them.
You know that is a madness. Monty just
can't get off it, can he?
Him and Timmy Aldridge will never get
off it till they're dead.
You know, they will never come off of it.
And what values do I want a woman to
have? Well, she has to believe in God.
A woman has to believe in God.
Otherwise, I can't be with her. Grieves. Yep.
How's that sound?
And she has to have big boobies as well,
like my mama did.
Are you the same greasy? Any woman that
you get with has to have big boobies.
Yeah, they have to.
They have to. Oh, I can't get with them
cuz how else am I going to get my milk and stuff? Huh?
Think about that, Grezy.
What about you, Grezy? What values you
look for in a woman?
No, seriously. A woman has to like
horror films. She has to like all kinds of foods.
She's got to have big boobies.
She has to get [ __ ] as well.
Quezy, did you say you could be with
someone that don't give [ __ ]
Cuz 80% of men would not go with a woman
who doesn't give anal.
So would you would you or not did you
say I think I I forgot your answer
before if you answered
I don't think I Good. No.
Imagine that. Just like straight going
like with no [ __ ] [ __ ] that. Nah,
that is weird.
That is weird. Very weird.
I was Did you know I was conceived on Valentine's Day? Yep.
Yeah. conceived Valentine's Day. Yep. No, seriously.
Crazy. I was
crazy. I was
If I had a baby, it would have to be
born April like my mama.
My mama was born in April.
I'm surprised most people are not born
in October. To be fair, the most common
month is September and then the least
common month is February. Yeah. So,
I'll go bed. I thought she