[ __ ] on Insta, bro. She is [ __ ] man.
Where he's making uh
excuses for these um Yeah. Yeah,
that thing on Reddit still pissed me off, bro. Yeah. Well, Any
chance of speaking to someone that's um impartial now
[ __ ] roll on November.
I can't wait.
I can't [ __ ] wait.
Oh, toxic [ __ ] November.
Why are you meeting him today?
Did you hear about the Reddit thing?
Would you like to
What do you mean him today? Man,
what do you think about the Reddit thing?
Yeah. Yeah. One second, bro. [ __ ]
I can't wait to leave, bubble, bro.
I seriously can't wait to leave, bro.
It's so toxic dating in this country,
bro. I can't wait to leave.
I'll put the link.
There you go.
It's [ __ ] there, bro.
Hello PJ. Can you hear me? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Listen up. Right. Don't say
nothing. What's his problem with this uh
[ __ ] um [ __ ] and he's calling people
out on the internet, right? I mean,
you're supposed to meet him today,
right, at 3:00 today, right? And the
fact is fact is, right, he actually
asked for backup, right? He needs P. He
needs [ __ ] um Money Mike on his side,
right? And also he needs basically
Timmy. Now tell me something, right? Why
is it fair for me to basically fight
three people against one?
He's a [ __ ] He even rung a police last
night, right? Because he was scared that
he was going to get beat up by me. Man's
a [ __ ] mate. I was going to meet him.
>> Where was you supposed to meet him?
>> Uh by Birmingham [ __ ] train station.
Do you know what? I'd rather meet up
with you, mate, than him.
Are you still going,
>> mate? Honestly, I'll come and meet you,
mate, because he seems like he's more a
[ __ ] than anything, mate.
>> Yeah, but I'm in London, but ain't it?
I'm far away from you.
>> Yeah, you know, you know what I'm saying? Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. The man's [ __ ] mate. He phoned
the police last night, right? Crying
like a little [ __ ] mate, because I was
going to meet him. Three against one. Do
you think that's fair, PJ?
>> No, obviously not. No.
>> Calling out all these people on the
internet, right, mate? Saying that he's
an odd little [ __ ] right? And when I
actually confront him, right, and be a
man. Yeah. Cuz he doesn't like to fight
me. See, he knows that he's going to get
totally [ __ ] up. Yeah. And he just bad
man and [ __ ] like that for months and
months, right? Real talk. He's been
talking his hard guy, right? And now he
went on the phone last night in front of
his mother crying to his own [ __ ]
mother, mate. It's madness. It's
madness. I haven't got a problem with
you, PJ. I kind of like I don't have a
problem with you, bro. You know,
>> but what the [ __ ] is Timmy getting
involved in Money Mike for?
>> [ __ ] those. Do you know what? You know
what I said to Mont? Hey, did you see
that when Monty met [ __ ] Mike and
Timmy and you heard
>> Did you hear Did you hear when Mike
said, "If you want trouble, come around
the corner." I would have went around
the [ __ ] corner. I would have [ __ ]
went around the corner. You [ __ ] mad,
bro. That [ __ ] He's He's He's He's a
[ __ ] He's a He's a snake, bro. That
money, Mike. He's a [ __ ] weasel. I
would have went around the corner, but
he didn't. He's a [ __ ] That's impossible.
>> Mongo's a narcissist, right? Because he
was saying to Kaye and all that, right,
the Kay, no, Kay still. No, Kay's over
him, mate. Kay's got a real man in her
life and she's confirmed, mate. He
thinks he thinks, right, this is what he
thought PJ, right? He thought he got
with Natie, right? [ __ ] Natie, right?
Then then he gets back with Kaye. Nah,
mate. Kaye moved on to bigger bigger fishing and
>> he's he's obsessed with Natalie, is it?
>> Yeah. and he's obsessed with [ __ ]
Kaye, mate. It's not normal.
>> And he goes, do you know what he said,
uh, PJ? He goes, "Oh, I don't want to
meet up with Kaye and Rise because they
will affect my kids because it shows
that I'm a violent person and I lose my
kids and I won't be able to see him."
Wait a minute. Didn't he meet up with
[ __ ] uh meet up with Kimmy and have a
fight with him when he had a chance of
losing his kids there? Really? He's
scared of me, mate. He's fighting me.
>> That's true. That's true.
I want to meet them and I want to sort
them out, but he doesn't want to. He
wants to basically be two free people against one.
>> Just go there and go live. They might
not show up.
>> Oh, he show up. All right. Because he I
can't, mate. He's phoned the police. >> Yeah.
>> Do the police.
>> Wait, wait, wait, wait. Do you know
where he lives?
>> Uh, no. I don't know where his new
location is. New location. He's got a
new Cuz then you could have just went on his door.
>> Even Even his dickpick is out there.
Have you seen it?
>> I am. No, I'm not really concerned.
>> I don't want to see it. [ __ ] Personally,
>> but what a personally like like he's
been calling me.
>> When's your birthday?
>> Uh, 1 to the 4th, 1987. >> April. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Mine's in uh two weeks.
>> Yesterday. He he thinks that he's still
in a relationship with uh [ __ ] what's
the what's her name? Um K and he really
thinks you know I sat there listening to
him right of his kids on you.
>> Oh yeah yeah yeah. He thinks it's not
going to happen mate but trust me it is
>> yeah K can over K can overrule [ __ ] S
what was it? SGO or something. She can
basically rule it and this is what he's
scared of. I swear on everything about
my life, Kaye can overrule it. And he is petrified.
>> He has he hasn't got a clue, PJ, about life, mate.
>> Bro, you got your window smashed in it.
[ __ ] hell, man.
>> Yeah, that was because of him, mate. [Laughter]
>> Yeah, it was to be fair, PJ. It's not
even funny, man.
>> No, I'm not laughing at that. It's just
the way he said it.
He honestly he he he is such an odd man
is he like calling people out and then
he has to run to mommy and he sat there
last night telling people what he's
going to do and he's going to get a
football and play in front of the in on
the football field and he's going to
call me over and beat me up. What do you
want me to be a [ __ ] goalkeeper for
him? Like I said to KK last night, the
man's a disgrace to society, mate. He
brings his kids into he brings his kids
into a conversation right when it suits him, mate.
>> Yeah, I know. I know what you mean.
>> Do you know many times he he has abused
his children on this internet?
>> Yeah, a lot.
>> [ __ ] disgusting, mate. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. For all for all the people in the
chat, right, listening to this
conversation, right? I swear I was going
to meet him today, right? But the only
part about it, right, I can't meet him,
right, when it's three against one.
That's just that's just out of order,
>> you know? I mean I mean to be fair
though Timmy doesn't count. He's just a [ __ ] mother.
>> Oh, do you know what? I I know what
truth will tell you. I leave Kaye sort
[ __ ] Timmy out. >> Yeah.
>> You know, but you know what the [ __ ]
this world coming to?
>> He said
>> he said that he was going to hide in a
corner and follow me and KK and I bo the
club up and I was like what? Really?
You're going to follow us? >> Yeah.
>> Uh how tall are you?
I'm tall, mate. K. And I've put loads of
weight on muscle, mate. Trust me. And
I'll [ __ ] flatten that [ __ ] in a
second. I don't drink anymore, CPJ.
>> But I don't think Money Mike's going to
like hit you for no reason, bro. To be honest,
>> I don't know, mate. It doesn't add up,
does it? Like two two one. I don't know
this Money Mike. And I don't know
nothing about him.
>> He's just a [ __ ] bro. He's He ain't
nothing, bro. Trust. I met him. Yeah.
>> Yeah. For all the people out there.
Right. I was going to meet him today
with KK, right? And KK's here to confirm
it, right? I'm not going to go to a
location, right, with three people
against one, right? That's totally
unfair. He's been calling people out on
the internet, right? Come on, meet me.
Meet me, right? Not actually meet me on
the [ __ ] app that you got, right? But
I would have met him today, right? But
no chance in earth and I'm meeting him,
right, with three [ __ ] people. That's
unfair on so many levels.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I thought you
>> He's a [ __ ] weasel, mate. And he goes
running to his mother. Like his mother
gives a [ __ ] His mother said he's not
fit enough to look after the dog. No one
not even allowed to. Do you know what?
His mother actually said he can't even
He's Do you know what? I don't know
who's worse, his mom or him. I really don't.
>> [ __ ] I'm getting to the point now,
PJ. Like his stuff comes out of his
mouth, right? It's just total [ __ ] mate. >> Yeah.
Yeah, KK can confirm it. We was going to
go today, weren't we?
>> No comment.
>> No com. No, we was going to go today to meet him.
>> What you saying?
>> No comment.
>> All right, I get what you're trying to
say. All right. >> Yeah,
>> I know why. I know. Yeah, but
>> just do what you feel is best in it,
bro. I'm not going to encourage you.
Just do what you want to do in it.
[ __ ] I'm not going to meet him in a
free gun. [ __ ] that.
Just suicidal [ __ ] That is
>> why Kayie, can you hear me?
>> You think it's all funny, is it? >> What?
>> I said you think it's all funny, isn't it?
>> Oh, yeah. It's such a laugh, isn't it?
>> No, it's [ __ ] it, huh?
>> Yeah. It's such funny that he's she's
had all her [ __ ] windows smashed. No,
>> not that. No, just I tell you what,
right? We should meet up.
>> How did you get it fixed? Did you get
the window fixed?
>> Well, I don't give a [ __ ] about the
windows. I'll smash them myself.
>> No, but what is it still like broken?
>> Well, no, they've been fixed now.
>> Okay. Yeah, [ __ ] hell. But
>> why do you think everything's funny, PJ?
People's lives are in danger.
Like, nothing do you think of, mate?
>> I don't think it's funny, bro. I don't
why I don't think it was funny, bro.
>> I'm not I'm not telling you what
happened, but trust me, you know, top
people are involved, bro.
>> What do you mean?
>> I'm not telling you much, mate, but it's
not a joking m a funny matter, mate.
It's just gone beyond a joke. This
>> you what? Like, you got attacked or
>> I'm not saying a word, mate. >> Okay.
>> Oh, [ __ ] hell. It's madness, bro. You
think a pizza is bad and hookers and
basically deliveries? Nah, no, no. What
happened to me and KK is beyond that,
mate. It's beyond that.
It's It's got to the point that
I'm not saying [ __ ] but trust me, it's
not funny. PJ,
>> you know, the thing is, Rash, do you
know what's so mad is like obviously I
know you've said stuff in the past, but
I've said stuff in the past and with a
lot of people, they seem to use it
against you forever. And I'm sick of it,
bro. I'm [ __ ] sick of it.
>> Well, he's on about me, right, last
night about this 13 and 14y old or
whatever, right? That's [ __ ] right?
Didn't he sit in an actual lobby and
actually say that he wanted to [ __ ] PJ's kids
and to watch it?
>> Yeah. Did everybody hear that? Did he
not forget that he said that live on stream?
>> Yeah. Do
>> you know what?
>> I don't think that man's going to there.
How's it going?
>> Oh my.
>> Oh, PJ. PJ this.
>> Anyway, anyway, PJ, turn the music down
a sec. Right there.
>> Just want to ask you a question about
today's events. Yeah, I get involved.
I'm not getting involved. I'm going to watch YouTube.
>> Oh, shut up you stupid
love. You stood there and let it happen
and go, "Oh, YouTube. Oh, it takes lives. Woohoo!
>> You know what? Give
>> me a tissue.
>> Anyway, voice. Anyway, why are you
asking for donations? I thought you had
£13 grand in the bank.
>> Oh, the donations for your funeral, mate.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Why are you
asking for donations? Are you lying
about this £13,000?
>> No. The the actual donations are begging
for money to come down today. Why are
you begging? You should be taking Kaye
to [ __ ] Cyprus,
>> not [ __ ] begging on YouTube. Oh yeah,
you can't get out the country, can you,
lad? You can't get out the country.
>> What's your problem?
>> You can't get out the country. What's your problem?
>> You can't You can't take Kaye to a nice
abroad holiday. If PJ had £13,000, at
least he'll take some prostitute. What's your problem?
>> He's not a prostitute.
>> Come on, PJ will give a prostitute. He
He's too [ __ ] desperate.
>> All right, Timmy. What's your problem, man?
>> What's your problem with me, Virgin?
>> You are the virgin. I don't know how you
even I've got to give it to Weiss. I've
got to give this to Weiss. At least
Weiss is now not a virgin. You still are.
>> I mean, I mean, I proved I've had sex,
but okay, whatever.
>> At least, you know, used his talle tal.
You know what, Timmy? Timmy, you know,
you know if I was Monty the other day, I
would have smashed you and M.
>> No, you wouldn't do nothing. You ran
away from me like I ran away from you. I
beat I already beat you when I'm live
with you running back.
>> I already beat you. I already beat you.
How's he beat me? We just beat [ __ ]
Okay, PJ. Come and meet me today, PJ.
I'm not meeting you anyway. I don't need to.
>> No, no, no. PJ, I'm around all day
today. Monty's you as well. You can even
put your donation link PJ to get your train
talk is cheap PJ and you done nothing.
You've been home by you probably had the
biggest on here. Let's be honest to you.
>> Monty smacked you when you done nothing.
It's like between us
Monty smacked you and you done nothing.
>> Don't go there PJ in between us. Don't hurt me.
>> He told you he told everyone
>> PJ. Okay then PJ meet today then. Shut
your mouth. Talk is cheap PJ. Put your
donation PJ all even I will donate you10
PJ to come to Birmingham.
Why won't you come to Birmingham virgin?
Why won't you protect his skin and talk she talk
>> every even [ __ ] Terry
put you on the floor.
Hope you watch my previous video later, girl.
>> Anyway, anyway, Birmingham today to get
a second ownage in the mattress or not.
>> I rise. Do you want to go to Birmingham
today? I'll meet you there. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Come on then. Dare you, PJ.
>> Oh my god. [ __ ] hell. I'm going to m own
PJ. You will be on the floor now. See
you later. Do you want a donation PJ to
your train? You skint. Would you like a
donation PJ for your train fair?
>> Timmy, are you asking?
>> Would you like a donation? But the paper
would donate to
>> Timmy was in the pub. Yeah. With £80. He is
>> any anyway virgin. How does it feel that
Weiss has lost his virginity and you're
still a virgin?
>> I mean, you're the only virgin. I mean,
>> pizza. You know, they call him a virgin.
I call virgin pizza.
>> I'm a virgin. Yeah. I've had sex.
There's a video of me getting There's a
video of me getting my dick sucked. So,
>> no PJ prostitutes.
>> There's a video of me getting my dick
don't count that has actually got a prostitute.
I've only had sex.
>> Let's go to Birmingham. Yeah,
>> let's go to Birmingham. Rice.
>> Yes, I'll see you later, PJ. Just let me
know when you're in. All right. I'm not
kidding. They all not the trolls like I
will see you. Just don't you worry. Get
make sure you get your
>> Birmingham New Street.
>> I'm not going to fight you in Birmingham
New Street, you [ __ ] clown. Are you
Are you a [ __ ] fo
obviously make out your talking about
turning up a train station for the
police and CTV? This is the worst
organized fight I've ever [ __ ] known.
He is honestly
why don't you meet a canel park right
Mongol and [ __ ] and Royce can have it out can't
park man there's no CV you can [ __ ]
go boom boom boom
>> oh go
>> I mean I mean organized a [ __ ] new
street station for [ __ ] sake
[ __ ] hell it's like watching [ __ ]
war and grommets and I Birmingham 3 p.m. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. There's no train stations, PJ, no [ __ ]
Anyway. Anyway, guys, Robin and Grommit.
Yeah, I'm going to call you Robin and
Gwit. Yeah, Robin and Gwit. Why are you
organizing a fight in a train station?
Why? Why you watch my previous video?
>> Why are you running? Why are you
running? Anyway, I'm off to go and get
my large breakfast, dads. Okay, we'll see you.
>> Yeah, see you soon. Not at the train
station, PJ. I don't do train stations.
You're going to take it like a man.
>> I'm going to take your virginity as
well. I'm going to take
>> You're going to be the backwards man
again. You're going to be I'm going to
take your virginity.
>> Don't hurt me.
>> I'm going to take your virginity. I'm
going to [ __ ] you hard
by nature. Girl, women are being [ __ ] again.
>> Do you know the funny part about it?
>> That's basically the video about Yeah.
when you when you think about it, he
goes I I lo He goes I lost my virginity
cuz I'm okay. I was in a relationship
for seven years. Not bad,
>> bro. He says that I'm I'm a virgin yet
I've proved I've had sex multiple
[ __ ] times. What the [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Why
didn't you just get a girlfriend and
settle down, PJ?
>> Because it's not as easy as that. >> Why?
>> But I'm not a virgin. That's the point.
He's He's the one. He's an actual
virgin. You understand?
>> Yeah. In Queen, right? I'd meet up with
[ __ ] uh uh [ __ ] right? But it's not
fair. Three against one, right?
>> Come to Birmingham today. I don't
[ __ ] mind, bro.
>> You [ __ ] please.
>> I thought you [ __ ]
>> I'm not. >> Why?
>> Because we fell out, isn't it?
>> Yeah. But
>> we You know why we fed out? cuz I called
Natalie ugly and [ __ ] and that's how we
fell out of it.
>> Well, you're not far wrong there. She's stinking,
>> you know, and that's
>> getting involved in that [ __ ]
>> No, I'm just saying it. I'm just saying. Yeah.
>> Is KK fighting Natalie? No.
>> Why would I fight Natalie?
>> Natalie is not with Natalie.
>> Natalie hasn't got a problem with KK
now. They sorted it out.
Hey, I would love to meet that [ __ ]
but he saw a [ __ ] house is just unbelievable. No jokes.
Yeah, PJ, you going to meet up with me? What?
>> Yeah. 3 p.m. I'm
>> January. You January, where are we going
to meet? McDonald's.
>> Birmingham. [ __ ] um
>> train station.
>> The Five Guys. I'm going to go to the
>> We haven't been to Five Guys.
>> The Five Guys is a restaurant.
>> Yes. I don't know where it is. I don't
know where I'm from.
>> Where is the Five Guys located?
>> It's out It's outside the station. Yeah.
>> I want to [ __ ]
>> PJ before years ago.
>> You never met PJ?
>> I have. >> Huh?
PJ, I've already met you, haven't I?
>> Yeah, a few years ago.
>> Raise is a non PJ. Oh, that's >> Yeah, probably me.
>> I want that money, Mike, because he's
been trolling me, you know, badly, man.
I've caught him. I I want him bad. So,
like, I don't mind coming today, you
know. I want that little [ __ ]
>> Are you actually genuinely going to go? Yeah.
>> Yeah. I went to Birmingham a couple of
month a few months ago just to meet
Monty. Remember? Yeah.
>> So, how long is it going to take? How
long is it going to take? Is there from
your location to Birmingham?
>> Probably like 2 hours and 20 minutes
from the exact house.
>> And you'd actually go.
>> Yeah, it's like an hour and 20 minutes
on the train, but obviously I need to
get to train station. So, yeah,
obviously I'll go. It's not too far.
>> Right. We I'll make a deal with you, PJ.
I know that's a long time to be on a
train or whatever, right? Or if you're
legit, right, and you're not [ __ ] me
about yet. Give me your number, right?
And I'll meet you.
>> You got my number, bro? What the [ __ ]
>> I haven't.
>> Yes, you do. On WhatsApp.
>> I've lost it. >> Okay.
>> Right. Well, give me your Right. Right.
Have you got a pen? You can write my number down. >> Uh,
yeah. Everyone could have cuz it's my
WhatsApp number so everyone knows it.
>> Wait a minute. Can you see this in the back chat?
>> Right. Can you see that in the back chat?
>> Yeah. Okay. That's your number. Yeah. Okay. Okay.
>> Yeah, that's my number. Text me if
you're legit. Right. I'm not going to
leave you go two hours in the chat.
That's a bit scummy. Like, you know what I mean?
I've got your number.
>> Rise can't afford a McDonald's. Nah, I
can't, mate. I'm on food parcels. I told you.
Look, I can't afford a tra I can't
afford the ticket to
>> Why did you Why did you say I was I was
laughing about um I wasn't
>> What was that?
>> You said that I was laughing about um
the windows. No, I wasn't, bro. No, if
you if you see what happened, mate, I
think like I can't say nothing online,
trust me. But it's bad, mate. It's not
even windows. It's not the windows or
the door is is a problem. It's what happened.
Like, I can't talk about it.
>> Yeah, I got you. I got you. I got you.
>> Yeah. So, you must have got hurt in it.
>> No, I don't. No, I didn't get hurt. None
of us got hurt. PJ, how long is it going
to be until your friend from [ __ ]
again? You always do this. You're on and
off like a light switch.
>> Nah, no. I want that money, Mike. Anyways, so
he's a [ __ ]
>> I tell you what, if you could show me
you're in Birmingham today, right?
>> Most just make the whole YouTube
everybodyelcome. You know what I mean? >> Yeah. Could you imagine
like that'd be [ __ ] up on there?
>> It would be.
But I think I wouldn't want to meet
[ __ ] [ __ ] because I would go bad, wouldn't I?
That would go bad.
>> I don't know why [ __ ] was saying last
night, "Oh, why don't Kaye go out with
Magic Mike?" And I was like, "Huh?"
Sorry to say and still you said
>> it looks like an albino is it
>> I don't know but if you could show me
and KK that you're in man uh in what
what Birmingham today. Yeah. Me and KK
will go straight away and we can meet
you. German flight.
>> I will. Okay. I will.
>> No broadcasting mine. No broadcasting. H
>> Yeah. Okay. I will.
>> We have a day out. >> Yeah.
>> You tell me. You tell me your time by
text message. Let me meet you.
>> Oh, I'm going to go out for 3, so I'll
show you. I'm there around like 2 then. Yeah. >> 2:00.
>> KK is obsessed with [ __ ] No, she's not.
No, she's not. It's history between KK
and [ __ ] [ __ ] What? They don't understand.
>> Are you right with now?
>> No, I don't talk about that. I can't. He's history.
I got bigger fish to fry. He's a [ __ ]
>> He's a n He is actually a nons to be fair.
>> He actually his neighbor His neighbor
said that he was basically [ __ ]
watching the kids next door while they
were in the back garden with bikinis on and really
>> Yeah, he's a wrong mate. He got finished
when his neighbors come on his internet.
Yeah, but if you can show me and KK
you're at that station, right? You'll
have to wait for a couple of I don't
know how long will it'll take Well, it
won't take that long anyway, but we'll
be there if you can show us. You can wait.
>> Swear to God, no lies, mate. We are
>> No fighting or be fair. >> Huh?
>> No fighting because I'm not into all that [ __ ]
>> No, we'll be fighting them though. It
>> Yeah, but trust me, you you you don't
understand. I'm quiet, mate. You find a
different me in real life.
>> Yeah, but we'll be f Yeah, but we're
fighting them though, is it,
>> mate? Are they worth it? He's already
>> Yeah, but
>> Yeah, but think about it, mate. He's
already phoned the police like like a [ __ ]
>> True, true.
>> Yeah, they're going to be swarming the
place, mate. Honestly, they are. What?
Like, man, it
>> Yeah, they're going to be everywhere.
He's already alerted, mate. [Laughter]
See, I'm quiet TP. I'm not like [ __ ]
mouthing off here. It's the quiet ones
you want to look out for, mate. And I'm
silently quiet. I've been Look what
happened to me when with
I was quiet, mate. I just know what he
needs, mate. But but [ __ ] oh, it's a
different cut of fish, mate. >> Yeah,
>> I'm not all mouth. I'm legit.
Mongo's going to prison soon anyways. Yeah, he's
>> a Ky. Do you think he's definitely going prison?
>> I he is
>> like properly.
>> Yeah, he is. He's gonna
>> It's not looking good.
>> Yeah, but is there Yeah, but what if he
gets like community service or something?
>> No, if he I don't know what his crime rate is.
>> Be lucky if he gets
>> to be honest. If he has a tag, he's
going to break her, right?
>> Because the thing is, right, he didn't
get remanded, did he?
Well, I don't know what his crime rate
is. Like if he's going to play on his
disability, Yeah. he's either going to
have a fine community service or he's
going to be on tag. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, yeah. That That's what I think he's
going to have because I don't know if
he's done it before. Is he You've been
with 10 years. Has he done anything bad, Blake? >> No.
>> Apart from the riots? >> No.
>> No. So he's got a good Yeah, he's got a good chance.
>> Yeah. So yeah, he's I don't know. They
might even teach him a lesson and just
chuck him in prison to back up his ideas
to be fair. >> Yeah,
>> cuz they did that to me. See, it does
seem good, you know.
>> Well, you you've been to prison.
>> Yeah, I've been in prison three times
for my ex-girlfriend, mate, for the
lies. She was telling
>> Well, you've actually really
>> Yeah, I've done prison, mate. It's a
piece of cake.
[ __ ] that. [ __ ]
>> You get locked up. Yeah. For you get
locked up for 23 hours of your life.
Yeah. You got three meals a day. You get
a gym. You get a [ __ ] um library. You
get a [ __ ] mate. It's It's hard work.
If it's his first time in jail, it'll fly by.
>> What is he What is he going on the 27th?
The 27th is my birthday. Is it? Is that
when he's going to court? >> Yeah.
>> Why don't you go and watch it?
>> Yeah, I was thinking of that to be fair.
I was actually
>> you can actually you can go in you're
public you can go off the roads and
>> we should go we should go together let's
go to the court together
>> yeah and see him basically down
we all shout in the background no [Laughter]
>> ris is a real G truth I am mate if PJ's
up for we will meet you PJ I'm going I'm
going cuz I want to I want to smash them [ __ ] in
>> yeah But they going to be on cork and aren they
>> Yeah. What are you are you nervous?
>> No. Why am I nervous? Well, it's [ __ ]
[ __ ] is the one that's nervous, mate. Not me.
>> Yeah. Yeah. True.
>> Think about it.
>> How long did How long did you do in prison?
>> Uh I My first sentence was 3 weeks. The
second sentence was uh four weeks. But
you are free. You don't do the full
sentence. So four weeks, two weeks I
done, three weeks I done a week and a half
>> and the last time is 14 days I done
>> a week and a half in vision. What's the
point of that?
>> Well, this is system of you mate. >> Yeah,
>> watch the video nature girl that I done.
>> No, I was just talking to him. Go on.
>> I was going to say it does you good, you
know, going in jail.
It makes you think about a lot of [ __ ] you know.
>> Yeah, it's true. I know people that's gone prison.
>> It's not as bad.
>> Have you got Have you got Have you got a
lot of convictions then?
>> No, I haven't got any convictions to
tell you the truth. It's just basically
my girlfriend lying about, you know,
abuse and [ __ ] and it's lies. We were
both alcoholics. I never That's the only
thing I've been to prison for is
domestics. That's it. There's nothing
anything on my records. It's just
domestics. Everything. KK seen my
record. She can tell you. She's seen it.
>> She's actually She's the only person on
YouTube who actually see my convictions in court. >> Yeah.
>> She's read them.
You know, I'm not even kidding. KK can
confirm it right now. She actually
generally she's the only person on
YouTube to actually see my convictions
in real life. Haven't you KK?
Well, they can't hear you over that shout. >> Yes.
>> There you go.
So, there we go.
Why am I How can I be Look, listen. How
can I be reounced? Yeah. In a different
country when I'm basically [ __ ]
meeting PJ today. Does that make sense? >> Yeah.
>> What a [ __ ] stupid comment that is.
Anyway, I'm going. Give me a shout when
you're at the location.
>> [ __ ] me about. Yeah,
>> I won't. I won't. I won't. I won't.
>> All right. Peace out.
>> All right. See you, man.
But yeah, man.
Did you uh watch my video bubble?
This woman on Reddit said she couldn't
get with me because I was 5 years older
than her and I'm not Muslim.
Yeah. When I went on her profile, it
says she's been with a 28-year-old before.
[ __ ] isn't it? These women are [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] isn't it?
Yeah. I give up, bro. The dating game is toxic.
They make excuses.
They're [ __ ] Their standards are unrealistic
bubble. These women, their standards are unrealistic.
And if you don't meet their unrealistic threshold,
um, then they're not even going to give
you a chance. That's all it is. you know,
it's impossible to meet their standards
nowadays pretty much. So yeah,
it's madness, isn't it? bubble. It's a madness.
It's [ __ ] mad.
Women are all the same.
All the [ __ ] same. Yeah.
No, I don't need to get ready yet.
Only takes a couple of hours to get there.
So yeah, I will, bro. No games.
So yeah, it's very toxic, in it, bubble
blower, the dating game.
It's depressing, bro. Very, very depressing.
Never changes either.
It's horrible, isn't it?
Very, very horrible.
No, about 2 hours.
About 2 hours.
We're going to [ __ ] these [ __ ] up, Rice.
All on the same website. You can watch
the side men on.
Yeah, this is a [ __ ] up community.
This is a [ __ ] up community, mate.
Yep. It's not that far. Ay lion.
All on the same website. You can watch
the sideman on Rice. Don't get nervous
now, Rice. We're going to [ __ ] these [ __ ] up. [Laughter]
Do you remember when Monty and Money
Mike and Timmy met the other day? Timmy
was like, "I'm going to knock him out.
Did you hear it? Oh, mate.
I'm going to knock him out.
Did you hear it on the Discord and that
uh Rice? I'm going to knock him out. [Laughter]
Oh, I love it. Love it, man. [Laughter]
What? Rice. You heard Timmy say that you you
No, it's not nice though. I've had my
windows done in Rice. I've had my
windows done in over YouTube. Ask Kaye.
Yeah, I'm going to knock him out.
Yeah, I'm going to knock him out. And he
done the [ __ ]
I can't lose my virginity. It's already
been lost a long ass time ago. So that's impossible. [Laughter]
Never. Here's Hey, Rice. I've actually
had my window smashed over YouTube, bro.
It ain't nice. I know what that's like.
That ain't nice at all.
It's not nice, mate. Really ain't nice. Nah.
Meeting up for fights over YouTube. Madness. [ __ ] madness. So yeah,
this car's autobanned, bro.
right? This person wrote,
"I doubt there is any difference in
America or Canada or England. Women's
standards are pretty much impossible to meet nowadays. Pretty
someone said, "Try living in London, my
friend. Three out of 10 thinking they
deserve a 10." Yep, pretty much.
They've got so many options.
It just makes dating impossible,
especially somewhere like London.
So that's the answer to your question,
Rice. Why I can't find anyone? Because
these women have got unrealistic expectations.
To be honest with you, I don't even
think I'd approach anymore. Like when I
go Birmingham later, I'm not even
approaching. I'm not even
I'm just going to [ __ ] knock these
[ __ ] out and come back.
It's a waste of time. It's toxic. It's
toxic. It's boring. It's depressing. I
can't be annoyed with it. I give up. I'm
[ __ ] off in [ __ ] November. So, that's that. Yeah.
I won't be doing no approaches, no nothing. Yeah,
I won't be doing any approaches in Birmingham. No, no, no.
Yeah, [ __ ] dating's [ __ ] in this
country. The dating game.
[ __ ] social media ruin it. [ __ ] simps.
Simps and white [ __ ] the game up.
[ __ ] any chance up of having a kids or
meeting anyone. It's mad. Yeah.
Nope. That's the only thing I've not tried.
I can't believe it's impossible to meet
someone. I just can't. It's so toxic.
That's why when I go Birmingham late,
I'm not even drinking approaching. It's too toxic. Yeah, man.
I don't know, bro.
It's really weird. Really weird.
I'm going to knock him out.
Well, it's impossible for me.
Yeah, it's mad, isn't it? Like her using
my age as an excuse.
I'm going Birmingham later. Yeah.
Using my age as an excuse.
Mad, is it? [ __ ] mad.
That was depressing earlier, bro.
Dealing with their [ __ ] again. [ __ ] depressing.
They will never change, will they? Smacking Stacy.
These women would always be the same here.
Yeah, they would always be the same. Yeah. Madness.
gave up on this dating thing [ __ ] um
earlier, bro. I wish I gave up earlier.
That's my biggest regret in life. But I
guess I thought it was going to change.
This is what I said to Antman. I wish I
gave up earlier
like a few years ago, but I was still
trying then. I wish I gave up sooner, man.
I wish I gave up sooner, man. I knew
there was no one for me. Even when I was
younger, but people kept telling me,
"Oh, you're going to meet someone."
Never ever ever changes. I wish I gave up sooner.
Really wish I did, bro. But I'm not that old.
No, I'm not getting an escort.
I should have to,
mate. You wouldn't even be able to get a
seven out of 10. You won't even be able
to get a four out of 10,
mate. They all play games. Even fours
out of 10.
Yeah, I'm going to Yeah, just get an
escort until I leave in November. That's
where that's where we're at now. Cuz
this is never going to stop. And I'm not
going to be made to feel ugly by these
women and I'm not going to be playing
their games anymore. So,
I'm not playing their silly games. And
you you think a seven out of 10
is loyal and play games? No, they're
not. Even an average to below average
woman, you can't get a seven out of 10.
I'm probably like a six or seven out of 10.
And trust me, mate, you won't even get a
five out of 10, let alone a seven out of
10. They're all the same. It don't
matter what they look like. They've all
got the same attitude, the same egos.
Even the fat and all even the fat and ugly ones.
So yeah, it has to be uh
No, it's women that play games and we're
not talking about men, so stick to the subject.
Yeah, well, whatever. 6.5, whatever. You
get the point. It's irrelevant. But that
woman on Reddit trying to use me not
being a Muslim as an excuse and me being
too old, even though she was 23 and 25.
Um, even though she was 23 and I'm 27,
which is five years,
that tells you all you need to know.
Just give up. It's never going to change
in this country
because of their unrealistic standards.
It's it's so obvious, isn't it? So,
um, no, because we're talking about
women. We're not talking about men. So,
please stick to the subject.
That's not me um creating a narrative.
The subject is about women.
Uh well, there definitely isn't somebody
out there 100%.
And if you've been following my journey
for the past four or five years,
there definitely definitely definitely not.
But it doesn't matter if men do the
same. We're talking about women.
So, and another thing is when women are
slagging off men, no one says women do
the same. So, you know, you're you're
talking about a narrative people are creating,
right? But when women are slagging off
men, no one's saying, "Oh, women do it
as well." So, you can't play two sides
of a coin. Stick to the subject.
We're talking about women. We're not
talking about men.
So, and people are certainly not talking
about women when women are slagging men off.
So, no, they're not the same. Both sexes
are not the same. So,
I don't have any disabilities. So,
but yeah, anyways, that's where we're
at. So, there's definitely not someone
out there. Definitely not. after that
[ __ ] them 10 numbers are not one day
I will never try here again.
So it might have to be the escort figure
until November to be honest. Um is that
what about when a woman does a shitty
thing and and and everyone says, "Oh,
she don't owe you anything." But when a
man does it, it's completely fine.
H what about when a man doesn't want to
lick a woman out and a woman and a man
is called gay? But then if a woman
doesn't want to suck a dick, oh that's
fine. I mean, we can go on all day about
double standards, mate. And that's only
one thing that they have.
And you're banned. Bye-bye. I mean, if
you want to go out if you want to go on
about double standards, bro,
that's the only thing that they have.
So, you're not going to win with that
one either. I can give you so many
double standards when it comes to women. Yeah. So, yeah. So yeah,
but I'll never try again here. I I I
don't think I will, bro. I generally
don't think I will. Like, I don't even
think I'm going to go out on my
birthday. I think I'm just going to go
for a meal
because there's no desire, there's no
motivation to want to ever try again. I
feel like I've met enough women.
Um I know they're all the same. They
have proven them to be all the same and
there's no point dealing with them.
Um, I know what they're like now and I
know what I need to do now. So that's
it. Sad way it had to end, but that is
the way it will end and has ended. So
yeah, I'm still going to Birmingham. So,
I wish I gave up um after the USA easy [ __ ]
There's just not someone for everyone.
It's It's that simple.
You're never going to stop meeting a
woman that plays games. It's never ever
It's always going to be the same here.
It's so [ __ ] obvious.
Oh, something stuck in my [ __ ] tooth, bro.
A long time ago.
Women are all the same.
They are all the [ __ ] same. It's so
obvious. I don't know how people can say
they're not. They They are literally NPCs. They literally
are all the [ __ ] same. Like, I don't
know how people say they're not. They've
got to be [ __ ] capping, bro. Like
they really have to not think that
they're all the same. They're [ __ ]
crazy. They are all exactly the same. Same attitude,
stuck upness, same games, same
mannerisms, same excuses.
Once you've met one, you've met all of them.
They're all the same.
And the thing is, everyone dismisses
your struggles either. So there's
there's no point even getting into a
debate about it.
They seem to think that women can't do
no wrong. Like when they play games and
lead people on, they they don't they
don't address it.
They always make up excuses for them. Oh
well, they might have changed their mind
or No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm [ __ ] too old for you.
Uh, what about the millions of people in
relationships? Well, there's millions of
people that aren't in relationships. I
mean, there's loads of people that are
virgins. That doesn't mean anything.
Just because other people in
relationships, it doesn't mean you're
going to be in one. You can't compare
yourself to others because then you achieve nothing.
Comparing yourself is never going to get you anywhere.
And there's also millions of people that
aren't in relationships. And there's
millions of people that's never been in
relationships. So, I love how you try to
say something to suit your narrative. I
mean, there's people that are virgins
out there. There's people that have
never held women's hands.
So just because there's people in
relationships, it doesn't mean you're
going to meet anyone.
That that's not the way that works.
That's why there's a whole point whether
you believe there's someone for everyone
and there's not someone for everyone. Yeah. So
just because other people have found
someone, it doesn't mean you're going to
find someone. There's plenty plenty
plenty of single people out there.
Plenty of single people out there. More
people are single than than in relationships.
Every most guy I know are single.
Tenants, people, [ __ ] people that are
not I all of the people that I know
mostly are single. Let me hold on. I'll
tell you actually. Let me go on my WhatsApp.
And I'll tell you about women I know as well.
Right. Single single
single single single single relationship.
Single single single relationship.
Single. Single. Single.
Single. Single. Single. Single. relationship, single.
Most of the people I know are single. Literally relationship,
single. I swear to God, bro, most of the
people that I I know are single.
There were some in relationships.
Single. Single. And obviously the women
that gave me their numbers were single as well.
And these are including women's numbers
that they gave me. Single.
Most of the people that I know are single.
I'm sure there's got to be people in
relationships. So that millions of
people in relationships,
um, it doesn't make any sense because
most of the people I know are single,
even women that I've come across,
but all of these people are single. I
don't know and I don't care. I don't
compare myself to other people. It's not
my problem. I'm going to Thailand in November.
I don't compare myself to strangers. I
don't care. I'm not interested.
It's not my problem. I'm leaving.
So, I tried my best here. It's never
going to change here.
That Reddit thing pissed me off trying
to say that I'm [ __ ] too old for her
and she wouldn't get with me because I'm
not Muslim. Yeah. Then I find out that
she's been with a 28-year-old. I'm not
dealing with this [ __ ] no more.
I'd have to be a real [ __ ] loser to
want to deal with their [ __ ] ever again.
You know, I I'm not I'm not degrading
myself. I'm not putting myself to their level anymore.
So, but for your record,
for the record, most people I know are single.
And these are all kinds of people I met.
So, what you're saying don't make no sense.
There's got to be more people single
than in relationships. There's got to be.
There has to be.
Yeah. And they're probably still [ __ ]
single as well.
This guy is in a relationship,
but not many people are.
So what you're saying don't even make
sense because if there's millions of
people in relationship, there's got to
be millions of people single as well. Yeah.
But yeah, it's not my problem anymore,
bro. I'm not going to be made to feel
ugly by these women ever again. I'm not
going to like there there's a certain
point where you say to yourself, "Enough is enough.
Could be a month, could be two months,
could be a year, could be 10 years.
Everyone's got different tolerance
levels." And mine was quite high to be
honest. I out with their [ __ ] for a very
[ __ ] long time. Um, and yeah.
Nah, I'm good, bro.
I can't believe that [ __ ] woman on
Reddit tried saying that I was too old
for her and she wouldn't get with me cuz
I'm not Muslim. Using that as an excuse.
So they'd rather lie to you than just
say, "Oh, I don't like the way you
look." Even though there's nothing wrong
with the way that I look. And they
somehow seem to think that lying that
just annoyed me. That even though they
didn't they don't live in my country and
I don't [ __ ] know what they look
like. Like who
who the [ __ ] do they think they are?
Like you know that that in itself. Who
the [ __ ] do they think they are? You know,
and that's what it is. They've got these
insane unrealistic standards. That's
what this problem is.
They, you know, all of this, oh, they go
for personality. No, no, no. It's
[ __ ] It is [ __ ]
Nope. It's not that. Because when I went
on her Reddit, she had been with a 28-year-old
and I I told her I was 28 cuz I'm 28 in
2 weeks. So, that's [ __ ] because
I've caught you out lying. you liar
because you've already been with a 28-y old.
It's the lies I can't deal with. You
generally think lying is better than
being honest, being a liar. That must be
part of your [ __ ] narcissism.
So, yeah. And and they all do that.
So, I caught her. I said, "Oh, I thought
you didn't go with 28-year-olds.
Liar." That's that's what I said to her.
You li I thought I was too old for you.
You liar. I'm never [ __ ] um
I'm never ever going to give them the
time of day ever again. I'm [ __ ] off
in November, bro. I'm out of here.
Yeah, man. And I'm and I'm making my
decision by leaving because I'm not
dealing with this anymore with these
women in this country. And I'm leaving,
bro. And I'm leaving. It's important.
And that's my choice to leave. I'm not
putting up with this [ __ ] anymore with them. So
there was one I was talking to, she
lives in Brighton. She thought, "Oh,
you're above average looking." "Oh, I'm
above average looking. Let's go on a
date then." She went quiet after that.
Yeah. I said, "Oh, you think I'm above
average looking? Let's meet up. Let's go
on a date." At some point
at some point she went quiet then. Stupid [ __ ]
Yeah. I [ __ ] hate them, bro. Literally. Yeah.
I'm not dealing with this [ __ ] anymore.
I'm not putting up with it anymore. Simple.
I'm putting my foot down, Charlie.
Putting my [ __ ] foot down. So yeah,
life's too short for this. It it's toxic
as well. It's very, very toxic.
Going to another country is going to
change things because Asian women are
you're going to get what you want.
You're actually going to get a
relationship. You're not going to deal
with these [ __ ] women that have got
unrealistic standards that think they're
better than you. It's toxic. is very
very very very toxic
trying to say, "Oh, you're too old or
you're too I'm not dealing with it no
more. I'm not dealing with their [ __ ]
period anymore. So that's it. I'm done, bro.
I'd rather save my pride,
you know, and that's the way I see it
now. Generally, I'm not doing it."
No, it's not wrong to have standards,
but they have got unrealistic standards.
There's a big difference between having
standards, high standards, and
unrealistic standards. Their standards
is, "Oh, well, you got a beard. I won't
date you." That's literally what they
do. Codine, I'll give you an example,
right? Say you're a guy that's got
green eyes. Mr. I don't know. Green eyes
and you're a nice person. No, no, no.
The fact that you've got green eyes,
this is how shallow and materialistic
they are. They won't get with you
because you don't have blue eyes. I
swear to God, bro, that that's literally
how they work. Or if you have a beard or
you don't have a beard or you have hair,
you don't have a hair. Like that's
that's generally how they move.
Um, so they've got unrealistic standards.
That's the difference. They have got
unrealistic standards. They don't have high standards.
Because if you had high standards, I
would fit in. I dress good. I smell
good. I've got money.
So, and Peter, you said you're seven out
of 10. And I haven't tried to chat nines
out of tens and 10 out of 10. You've
made it up. I'm a seven out of 10 and
I've tried to chat up five, six out of
tens. So, you might want to get your
facts right before saying stuff.
Like I mean I've never there is no nine
out of 10 in England. So I don't know
where I would have chatted up a nine or
a 10 because they don't exist in England.
So I'd love to know who these who these
nines and tens are. I mean these women
on my WhatsApp from the last time I went
out, they ranged from about 5 to seven.
Same as me. Pretty much the same as me.
But yeah, they've got unrealistic
standards. They ain't got high
standards. There's nothing wrong with
having high standards.
Just like that woman on Reddit. There
was nothing wrong with me. Looked good,
dressed good, not fat, not ugly, and
that wasn't good enough. And then they
use an excuse. Oh, you're too old for
me. Oh, you're not Muslim. Ah, [ __ ] Am
I dealing with that [ __ ] again? You
know, get the [ __ ] out of here, man.
Yeah, I'm doing bad today to be honest.
Really bad because of the women's situation.
It's really bad, man.
I just can't wait to leave now.
Really, really can't wait to leave. I'm
buzzing. [ __ ] buzzing, you know. So, yeah.
So that's the kind of standards that they have
and it's like what this American woman
was saying. I was speaking to her
and she was like, "Oh, like it's bad
because they would rather like reject
someone for like not having a beard or
having a beard and that person could
actually be a good person rather than
the other person that's not." That's
that's the truth of it. That's the
[ __ ] up thing about it.
See, I can't get with her cuz she's too
young for me. She's like 19. That is too
young for me. And no matter what the
woman look like, I generally wouldn't
get with her now if she was 19. I'm
older now. So, um,
so I it doesn't matter what they look
like, I wouldn't get with a 19year-old now.
So, the only people that are okay are
not suitable for me. And that generally
is like that's a valid point. You know,
28 19 that's weird. you know. So,
23 not weird. 22 not weird.
Yeah. Will happen when you least expect
it. Well, I've been hearing that for 15 years
and still nothing's happened. Every
woman you meet is exactly the same.
Every woman's exactly the same. might
come across, but apparently they're all different. Yeah, right.
None of them are different. They're all bad.
That's why I'm leaving, you know.
That's why I'm leaving.
I'm not dealing with their [ __ ] anymore.
I'm not being made to feel ugly cuz
that's what they do. Yeah, unrealistic
standards make you feel ugly when you
are not ugly or they make you think that
you are this person that you're not.
So it's toxic. Very very very very
You know there is nothing wrong with
you. You look normal. You look normal
enough for somebody to give you a
chance. You act normal enough for
somebody to give you a chance. Why aren't they
There's none the same. Literally all
women are the same. Every single woman
is the [ __ ] same. They all lead
people on. They all play games. They all
flake. They all use the same excuses.
Very, very concerning if they're not all
the same them because they do a lot of
the same stuff for people that not that
are not the same.
They do a lot of the same stuff for
people that are different.
So, it's very concerning if they're not
all the same, but they all seem to do
the same stuff. Lead people on, take the
piss out of people, same excuses,
same bollocks with them.
They do a lot of the same stuff for
people that are apparently different. Do
not think that's a bit weird
cuz I'm telling you, there's no one like
me. And if there was anyone like me, I'd
be very concerned. So
why do they have so many similarities if
they're all different?
Cuz they're all the same. It's obvious.
Women are all the same. Every single one of them.
Um yeah, I'm going on holiday in November. Yeah.
Nope. I've tried with average women,
ugly women. They're not interested either.
I was supposed to meet someone last Saturday.
Yeah. And the day before they said that
they um they were sick.
Same old. Same old. Same old. Same old.
Oh, I'm going to Thailand.
Yeah, it's always going to be the same
here. I was going to go out drinking
yesterday, but I never bothered.
No, it will never it will never change.
And the more you try, the more you lose
hope and the more you become depressed.
It's not worth it.
just leave. That's what I'm doing. Sorry.
All women are the same.
So obvious now.
It's so obvious. I mean, how many times for how
for how long
are you going to keep putting yourself
on the line for these women to prove
they're all the same? Like, how many
years are you going to do that? It's
[ __ ] insane. Like, how many years
were you willing to do that?
They're obviously all the same.
It's [ __ ] obvious, bro. They will
always be the same.
[ __ ] 10 numbers and not even a single date.
Yeah, that was my final straw, I think. Definitely. Yep.
Oh, they are all the same. All women are right. One second. So yeah,
you still there coding?
You don't need to bless me, mate. You know,
it's my own fault. I should have left years ago. [Music]
Um, do what you want to do, bro.
I'll probably stay in now until I till I
go in November.
To be honest, there's no reason for me
to go out and try or anything. I'll just
go for a meal on my birthday.
Yeah, I won't be trying again.
10 numbers are not a single day. Get [ __ ]
Get [ __ ] if you think I'm ever trying
to get here, mate. No. One sec. Yeah. D Yo,
>> PJ, are you sure you're coming? Yeah,
just making sure. >> Yeah,
>> right. I'll have your word on that then.
>> Okay, I'm coming. I'm leaving in a bit.
>> Yeah, we'll be there like just after midday.
>> Yeah, I will. I'll show you anyways on WhatsApp.
>> Yeah. Yeah. All right, that's all I need
to know. Bye-bye. All right. All right.
enlightened. Yeah, right. it's bad.
If these women aren't all the same
bubble, why do they all do and say the
same stuff and play the same game? It's concerning
for all of these women to do the same
stuff if they're not all the same.
Do you not find that a bit strange?
I find it very strange.
All women are the same, Tilly. All women
are the [ __ ] same.
Yeah, I went out three weeks ago, uh,
Tilly, and I got 10 numbers and I only
got one reply.
I looks maxed and I only got one reply.
That was it for me. I was like, nah, [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that. I'm not trying again. I'm not
dealing with that [ __ ] again. It's for
the best. Giving up was for the best to
be honest with you. You know, I
spent5600 and obviously when I won the money back,
I was like, nah, you really need to give
up now. Like, nah, seriously.
So, call it a day and move on. I think
that's what the best my best the best
idea was. That was [ __ ] disgusting.
And the the first number that the only
number that replied was supposed to meet
and they never. So
yeah, I'm not playing their games no
more. [ __ ] them. [ __ ] a lot of them.
If I have to go about sex for the rest
of my life, so be it.
I'm not low myself to their level anymore. Simple.
Yep. And they were supposed to meet me
as well, Bubble. They agreed to meet me.
Yep. They were they were they agreed to
meet me, too.
Nah, that's not the point. If I've had
it loads of times,
I tried millions of times. So yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, if I was still a virgin, I
think I'd still be trying, but
I'm not putting myself through that um
anymore with these women. I'd rather be
alone than degrade myself,
you know, dealing with their [ __ ] you know?
I'll just use escorts for the rest of my
life if it gets to that point. Sir, mad. Yeah,
I was on Hinge, but I didn't get any
matches on Hinge.
I didn't get any matches on Hinge. Yeah.
What do you think, Bubble? Yep.
Go on dating apps. They say get laid. It
will get you laid, they say. Huh?
Meet people through friends. Yeah,
it's not worth it. Yeah,
anyone would do
Women are bad people.
Bubble bad people in general. Anyone would do.
Anyone will do.
Seems anyone will do. Bubble.
Seems any wonderful will Yeah.
I was messaging Dmond earlier.
London is very westernized.
It seems anyone would Yeah. Okay. Heat. Heat.
Nice. I'm [ __ ] tired, but I need to
go Birmingham in a bit.
Going to go see Rice and Kaye. Yeah.
We're all going to go clubbing.
There's this woman I met in Birmingham.
We was talking. We had plans to meet and
then she said, "Oh, I don't feel the
spark. I'm not interested in dating
right now." That's what I'm saying. They
lead people on.
They They lead people on and play games.
That's literally all they [ __ ] do.
They will never change. They'll always
be the same.
Trolling, piss taken. [ __ ] all that, bro.
All right. I don't want to.
They will never change these women. Ever. Yeah,
even if we get on the drink, I'm still
not going to approach. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that, bro.
You know, I've only been on three dates
since having this phone. And I had this phone in
I've had this phone since December. So, go figure.
Loads of numbers.
I'm just not anyone's type in this country.
I think every country has a different
type. I don't [ __ ] know, bro. Belgium. Maybe
maybe I'll be maybe Belgium. Maybe the Netherlands
obvious in terms of like other countries
that are non the not western, but I'm
obviously not anyone's type in this
country. It's so obvious.
I'm going November.
I'm not dealing with these [ __ ]
But there's got to be another country.
But Thailand, I'm someone's type. And
it's got to be somewhere like Belgium
because I'm no one's type in London.
It's so obvious.
So they have a type that they go for.
And by type, I mean like, you know, you just nah.
There's people that are way better
looking than me and they still can't get nothing.
It's got to be this country. It's got to be. No,
no, it's not closer than Scotland. You
still got to go under the [ __ ] sea. So, so
or maybe Albania or somewhere, but
definitely not this country.
Definitely no one's type in this country.
Albania, Belgium, or something like that.
It's definitely not this country.
I know that for a fact they're not
interested in this country. Yeah, but
you still got to go under the sea and [ __ ]
I remember when I got the train to
Amsterdam, it was long.
I remember when I done that by myself.
I went all the way to Amsterdam by myself.
I was a crazy bastard. But yeah,
I don't know what you have to look like
here to get women.
Maybe blue eyes, 6'5, something.
I don't know. >> Yeah.
What do you think? Yep.
Belgium for Christmas. [Music]
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
Do you remember when Jaden said to
Monty, "It's got to be some deep rooted
issues that every single woman you get
with, they [ __ ] you off." It's got to be
some sort of deep rooted issue. I was
dead when they were saying that to Monty in it.
Yeah, that Discord thing is sad as [ __ ]
There's got to be some sort of
So what rice you actually saw when Timmy met Mike
and Monty? I'll knock him out. How did
you see it? Well, you are you on Discord, Rice?
I'll knock him out. I'm going to knock
him out. Timmy was screaming in it.
It's embarrassing. I'll be leaving. I'm
going to leave at 11:00.
Be leaving at 11:00.
Don't be nervous, R. You'll be with me, bro.
We'll show them [ __ ] who's boss.
You're with me, son.
Does anyone remember that M? Do you
remember? Anyone remember that Mike Cariggi?
Yeah. What happened to him?
Don't know if you remember
We're going to go on the drinks, right?
Me, you, and Kaye on the drinks. Yeah.
Do you like this YouTube?
Yeah. You don't have kids on Yeah. You
haven't been on there for ages, have you? Uh, Yeah. [Music]
Right, I'm going to stop reading.