[ __ ] went down the wrong hole. That dude
went down the wrong hole, man. [ __ ] Jo [Laughter]
Oh, that is funny.
That was funny as [ __ ]
All on the same website you can watch
Star Wars on.
That [ __ ] needs to be monitored.
It needs to be [ __ ] monied. [Laughter] Huh?
You've got both to pick with me. I was
sleeping, mate. King likes his little
five guys. Cost me 40 quid. That did
cost me 40 [ __ ] pound
40 [ __ ] quid. That cost me a couple
of burgers and a milkshake.
Yeah, I should have
all on the same website. You can watch
Obi-Wan Kenobi. Hey, did you see the
woman in the back? Did you see the woman
in the backy with the with the um orange high
on the second one with the orange high viz?
She almost got [ __ ] hit.
Yeah, she almost got [ __ ] hit. Yeah.
Yeah. I was supposed to go.
I was supposed to go and um
back uh Rice up, weren't I? Cuz I'm team Rice.
Yeah. Go with a lightsaber. [Laughter]
Oh, but they don't really want to fight
yet. I was thinking the same thing as LT
because why are they fighting in public?
They go to like a park or something.
You know what I'm saying, bro? They'd go
to like a park. Why are they going
somewhere where they know it's going to
get broken up? Know what I mean?
Like with mine and Timmy's Yeah. There
was no no one broke it up. They just
took the L. Why are they going where a
fight could get broken up
and obviously other people and stuff?
But if they really wanted to fight,
Yeah. they wouldn't go somewhere where,
you know, it could be broke up. Yeah.
King loved the little um King loved a
little burger. Greasy.
He's a lovely little whiffer.
I've got a bone to pick with you. That's
what I say to people on Reddit. I've got
a bone to pick with you. Why are you
telling people to go out and approach Go
out and approach women?
I've got a [ __ ] bone to pick with you.
[ __ ] telling people to [ __ ] go and
talk to women. [ __ ] off. And then when
we do, we have to deal with that
[ __ ] [ __ ] off. I got a bone to pick
with you. That's what I say to them. these people really
listen. Do you know why I don't so do
you know why I don't show my bad
experiences with women grievy on my
screenshots and WhatsApp messages?
Do you know why?
I'll tell you why I don't like
screenshots and stuff like unseen stuff.
I don't show anyone anything because
they it doesn't suit them. So why am I
going to waste my time trying to
convince people that are always going to
defend women? It's a waste of everyone's
time. I've just I just got this guy on
Reddit right here.
Um I said this is what I said. uh
greasy. Now, correct me if I'm wrong.
He said, "Yeah, if people are doing
that, you know, sometimes people are
just trying to be nice and ends up and
it ends up being cooler in the long run.
Like, they'll pretend to be interested
so they don't have to let you down, but
in the long run, they're going to let
you down a lot harder. You know what I
mean?" I said, "Uh, no. Being nice, they
are lying and leading people on on
purpose via text. Uh, there's nothing
nice about that. No one's putting a gun
to someone's head and making somebody
lead somebody on and tell a load of
lies. That's the whole point of these
people make excuses for women. Do you
understand? It's a bit different than
somebody giving you their number because
they want to get away from you. You
understand it? This is via text. So, I
don't think somebody leading somebody on
and lying is being nice.
You know, it's they always make excuses
for these women. That's why there's no
point getting into any kind of debate,
any kind of argument. Um because they're
always going to defend women. So
pointless. And Kings doing good.
I have three sugars. Yeah. So
there's no excuses for people leading
people on and playing games. They know
what they're doing. They're not
innocent. They're not doing it to be
nice. Um, if they were being nice, they
would literally just tell you that
they're not interested in dating and
then just block your number or
something. So, you somehow seem to think
that lying is better than telling the
truth. I mean, have you ever heard the
saying, "Honesty is the best policy."
Yeah, it's a true saying, "Honesty is
the best policy." Everyone knows that.
I don't know why people are going.
Yeah, I would have backed him up obviously, but
then I could have went for a drink, but
I I didn't want to go for a drink today
cuz I would have ended up approaching
and I'm done with these skanks in this
country. So, I'd rather just stay in and chill. Yeah. White.
would have [ __ ] him up. Yeah.
But why are they fighting in public? I
don't get that. That's madness.
No, you can't. He's downstairs.
You want the link, do you? One sec.
Yeah. Why do these people make
Why do they make excuses?
Grezy, can I ask you that since you're
an impartial party? Why do they make
excuses for women when they leave people
on and stuff?
Why do they make excuses for them?
He didn't reply to the last message.
>> Yeah, he didn't reply to the last message, mate.
>> Oh, virgin.
>> You are a virgin. Yes.
>> Why didn't you turn up to Birmingham?
You could have had the best.
>> You are a virgin. Yes. Stop calling
yourself a virgin.
>> Get in my cra right now as I speak cuz
I'm that tired to keep me. Stop calling
yourself a virgin. Make out. You're a
gangster. Gangster PJ,
>> stop calling yourself a virgin. It's not nice.
>> Nah. Is that we? >> Bye-bye.
You get kicked.
>> Yeah. I don't know why he keeps calling
himself a virgin. Can't be good for his
um mental health.
Yeah, he went quiet after that. Um, Grezy.
of course he [ __ ] would.
Why do these people make excuses for
women? Jamie took the W.
No, he's just downstairs. He'll come up later.
That five guys cost me 40 quid. Now, it
might seem a lot of money, but again,
obviously I'm not a skin virgin in a bed
suit with no bed, no money. So,
obviously can afford it. You know, I can
afford these things cuz I'm not a skint
virgin in a bed suit with no bed, no
money in it.
I'm not happy with any women. I think
they're all the same me.
I never ever ever ever want to deal with
them ever again as far as I'm living.
Because why would you want to deal with
people that are all the same? A, they're
all the same. B, they've all got
unrealistic standards and expectations.
So, it's like a mugs game. It's the same
thing as gambling. It's literally the
same thing as gambling. It's a mugs game.
Nah, all women are the [ __ ] same.
If I was in a country like Belgium or
Netherlands, then maybe I'd go out every
week. Maybe I would.
Maybe I probably would, to be honest.
But not here. I can say I'm done with
this country at the very at the very
least. So yeah,
>> they're all the [ __ ] same. They're
[ __ ] barefaced [ __ ] liars. They
try to make average looking people,
normall looking people feel [ __ ]
ugly. They're horrible, horrible,
horrible people. And they are. And I
mean it. And I've never been shown any
different. So I'll never think different
until I'm shown different. Actions speak
louder than words. So,
it's like a it's like having a bad child
and the child's telling you he's going
to change, but the child never changes.
We would want to see change. We would
want to see actions,
you know, a way of showing that the
child has [ __ ] changed. You know what I'm saying?
So, that's it.
Yeah, they even make excuses for women
leading people on. It's mad.
It's toxic. And man had um the right
word for it. It's very very toxic and
very very negative. Toxic was the right
word though. Defo trying to date women
going out approaching. It's very very
very very toxic. It is. It very It
really really really is. It's toxic.
It's negative. It's expensive.
The dating game, Grezy, I think he he
hit the nail on the head. Yeah, it is
toxic. Like getting numbers, being led
on, it is very, very toxic.
It is. It is very toxic. It's very
negative. It's [ __ ] discouraging as well.
Why do you think I've not been out since
3 weeks ago? I got no desire to want to
try ever again.
No desire. because we I know what they're like, you know,
and why am I going to try and speak to
someone that's got unrealistic standards
that's just going to lead your ass on? It's pointless, you know,
about they lead people on to try to make themsel
um not seem bad. They lead people on on purpose.
do it on purpose to [ __ ] with you
because they're [ __ ]
You remember that Muslim girl saying she
wouldn't date me cuz she's a Muslim. I
messaged her there. The one I met a
couple of time how many times I meet her
once, but I saw her again and um yeah,
she blocked me on WhatsApp. It's the
lies and the [ __ ] And I was like,
I'm not going to put up with that
anymore. You must have you must really really really
have to have no pride to want to put up
with that [ __ ] ever again. That's the
way I see it.
That is really the way I see it. You
have to be really, really down bad to
want to put up with their [ __ ] ever again.
The lies, the [ __ ] the leading on.
Are we [ __ ] eight or 28?
Are we eight or are we 28? I'm pretty
sure I'm 28 in 10 days.
I'm not a child. I don't deal with
people's games and their [ __ ] and their lies,
you I've got more respect for myself than that.
So, that's it.
It's annoying, bro. Really, really annoying.
So, yeah, I'm going to try and sleep
with King today. Yeah,
that woman in a high viz was [ __ ]
running for her [ __ ] life. She almost
got knocked down.
This site needs monitoring. There's no
way these fights can keep going on on
the same website you can watch
Scooby-Doo and Star Wars on.
There's no way. This needs to be monitored
cuz people watch the Sidemen. Me and
King watch the Sidemen and I know they don't fight.
Yeah. You reckon I would have beat Monty Greasy?
Yeah, I didn't look at them properly,
but yeah. Do you reckon I would have beat him?
I think I would in it. [Music]
Yeah, that guy's making excuses for
women. No one puts a gun to someone's
head and makes somebody lead someone on.
Like literally no one does that.
Nobody [ __ ] does that via text, you
know? So they seem to make a lot of
excuses for them.
And they always say about them changing
their mind. That is just an excuse,
Grezy. Because the amount of times I've
gone on a date with someone and I've
never changed my mind before the date.
It's like they're so scared to blame
women for anything. Do you know what I
mean, Grevy? So, they come out with
these things. Oh, women don't owe you
anything. Oh, no. It's like they're so
scared to offend
that they have to cover up the truth.
Like they try and say that women go for
personality. Yeah, they go for
personality once you've already passed
their unrealistic threshold.
Yeah. After that, if you can finally get
through that, then yeah, they do. You
know, personality is is second.
If you are not the exact type that they
are that you know that
that they after, they're not even going
to give you a chance. This is another
thing no one [ __ ] tells you. You know,
there was a woman I was speaking to in
Brighton. Yeah. And she said, "Oh, I'm
above average looking." I said, "Oh, I'm
above average looking." Really? Let's go
on a date then. Let's get to know each
other. You're single.
Oh, [ __ ] And she said she never had a
boyfriend as well. She said she never
had a boyfriend. So, this is what I'm
[ __ ] saying. The amount of times that
you go on Reddit and you see these women
that claim they can't get a man, it
infuriates me. They are mocking actual
men that struggle. They can find a man.
They can find a partner.
You know, it annoys me. Do you know
what? If I had one wish, Greasy, do you
know what I would do? Do you want to
know what my one wish would be?
Obviously, the most common thing would
be obviously be a millionaire.
Generally, do you know what? Do you
really want to know what my wish would be?
Generally, do you really really want to
know what my wish would be if I had one
wish? My wish would be
ban Instagram, Tik Tok, Snapchat, dating
apps, and only allow
YouTube's a bit dodged, ain't it?
YouTube, WhatsApp, and Facebook. Then
these women would be [ __ ] because then
they wouldn't be able to be picky. They
wouldn't be able to go around acting
[ __ ] And every man that they want,
they wouldn't be able to get them. Do
you know why, Grezy? Because they would
have to approach the man. Because don't
forget, most men are scared to approach,
right? So, if there was none of these
simps, right, online, they would have to
simp in real life. And obviously they
wouldn't be able to simp because they're
scared of women. I if I had one wish,
bro, I would ban them free apps. I'd
take it over the millions of pounds, you
know, and and you know, get society back
to normal, you know. I generally
generally would generally generally
generally would, bro, cuz then these
women would be [ __ ]
There'd be no being a [ __ ] There'd be
no mocking the average guy. They
wouldn't be able to get men they want.
Unless unless the men approached them,
they wouldn't be able to get them. You know,
now with all of these simps and these
white knights, they [ __ ] it for all of us.
>> They've completely [ __ ] it, you know. So, yeah,
10%. There's no 10%. They're all the same.
All women are the [ __ ] same. But
yeah, that's what my um that's what my
wish would be
to be honest. buying them apps
because that's what um that's what the problem is.
I hate when they try and say they can't
find anyone. Greavesy. It really really
annoys me. These women can find men.
They can get a boyfriend. They can get
sex. They can get anything
unless they're really really really um
ugly. And I mean they would have to be
really [ __ ] ugly for them to not be
able to find a man. They can get anyone
they want. Even an average woman.
I was born I was born in the wrong
[ __ ] generation. [ __ ] hell.
Just blame lady for that though. It
It's not like they say they don't want a
man. They moan that they can't find men
and then when they get the chance,
you're not good enough for them.
It's weird, isn't it? No one's good
enough for them, but they claim they
can't find anyone. One sec.
Wait, what the [ __ ] Hold on over there.
You never had sex with Izzy. Are you
still going on about that [ __ ]
You need to get laid. You need to lose
your virginity. You still going on about that?
God, man. You're obsessed with my sloppy
seconds. Give it a break. Oh, >> rice.
What's going on?
Oh no, that sounds bad to me.
>> What's going on?
>> What you doing tonight? Was really
smart. Yeah, you know what? [ __ ] I'm
coming for you.
What's going on?
>> Yeah. Yeah, you do realize that, right?
Don't worry about it. You set us up.
Don't worry. I'm coming for you. I know
where you live now, little boy. And
don't worry, I don't need no backup. I
will be coming for you, you little [ __ ]
>> What the [ __ ]
>> You want to make a bet? You wish you
kept your count your chickens, mate, cuz
what you did to me today where it was dirty.
>> I didn't do anything.
>> Oh, of course did. Oh, yeah. Of course
did. You asked me to come.
Do you know what?
>> I want to try. Shut the [ __ ] up. You
answered me. You basically set me up.
>> No. How did I set you up, you idiot? I
hate Monty. I just didn't go cuz I fell
asleep. How did I set you up?
>> Why didn't you set up?
>> How did I set you up?
>> Because you asked me to come to
Birmingham, right? And then beat that.
>> Yeah, but I didn't answer you when you
asked me to show where I was. So, I
didn't even show I was there.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. What was your
excuse? You fell asleep and you said you was leaving.
>> If I set you up, Listen, listen. If I
had set you up.
>> Yeah. I would have showed you me there
and you would have got jumped. So learn
the definition of being set up if you
are going to say I've set you up
>> cuz I [ __ ] didn't.
>> Come through. Shut up. You [ __ ]
>> Okay, fine. I'm not going to I'm not
going to tolerate your abuse.
I didn't set I didn't set him up.
I didn't set him up at all.
You know what I'm saying? Yep.
[ __ ] hell. I didn't set him up. How
the [ __ ] did I set him up? I didn't set
him up at all.
I didn't set him up at all, man. Yep.
Yeah. Now Vice is coming for me.
What the [ __ ]
Now he's coming for me. What the [ __ ]
B Rice Monty Timmy in it.
They're saying, "Oh, what does women get
from leading you on?"
Well, sick entertainment, obviously.
All right, Captain.
>> You're the ugly skinned bastard. PJ,
>> bye-bye, Virgin.
Obsess over my sloppy seconds.
Pretending to be Monty Man. I thought
that was Monty Man, bro. Yeah. Yeah, man.
It did look fun though. Like the
Birmingham like you you heard the music.
I bet a lot of people was getting drunk
today. I haven't drunk for ages.
Greavves are you proud of me?
No. I've come to realize I don't like
drinking that much. I think I only used
to go out and drink to try and meet people.
But part of it was I don't know.
But then I realized all women were the
same. So yeah,
don't really drink.
I think I could live without drinking.
I said to this guy, nothing changed for
them. They led me on on purpose.
to boost their own ego.
What do you think, Grezy? If these
people, if some of these people have um
agreed to meet you and then the day they
come up with some excuse, I mean, they
are [ __ ] with you.
You know what I'm saying? Like it's it's
obvious. No, like leading you on and
then dropping you. They are doing it on purpose.
There's nothing that's changed. They
knew from talking to you they were going
to lead you on. It's [ __ ] obvious,
you know. Why do they make excuses for
women? I would I would love some sort of
answer to that.
They they've done it on purpose just
like the same way as a man would do it on purpose,
you know? It's
I don't understand. Like it's
Why do they keep defending women?
Nah, they don't have anxiety. Nope. Stop
making excuses for the [ __ ] Now, this
annoys me, Greavves. I'm just reading
this thing on um Reddit. I turned 25 in
2 months, and the fact that I've never
been in a relationship has eaten
has been eating away at me a lot lately.
Oh, that triggers me, bro. This was
posted by a woman. It's
Let me Yeah. She's She's never been in a
relationship by choice. You've never
been in a relationship by choice. You know,
you've never you've never been in a relationship.
Why would it eat eat at you if it's by choice?
Why would something eat at you if if
you've chosen to to be that way? You
know, I I don't choose to be single and
sexist, but that's my life. So, and it
would always be my life. So, at the end
of the day, you are choosing to be
single. Why would choose and you are
choosing? Because women have options. If
you want to if you want to say that like
you know they're not why are they saying
that it's eating them away? You see you
see you understand how that kind of
feels like you're being mocked grievy
cuz I went out 3 weeks ago and I got 10
numbers and I didn't even get a date. So
how do you think we feel? You know, if
if if if a woman can get any man she
wants and she's complaining that she
can't get a relationship and it's eating
away at her, right? Wouldn't you maybe
think that what what would happen if you
actually had to go out and put effort in
and you still couldn't find anyone? You know,
do you know what I'm saying?
my reason for wanting a relationship in
the first place of your first paragraph.
I'd like I'd like to have a husband and
children someday. Brilliant. Nothing
stopping you from doing that. There is
literally nothing stopping you from
being in a relationship. There's nothing
stopping you from having a husband and
having a a child. There's nothing
stopping these women, Grezy. Unless
they're they look like [ __ ] Shar.
There's nothing stopping them.
Stop mocking the average guy. So, this
is my point on how picky they are.
They'd rather be 25, right? Ah, 25 and 2
months and have no one and have anything
less than their unrealistic standards.
This is my whole point in what I was
saying. Do you understand?
They're acting like they can't find
anyone. That's what annoys me. They're
really acting like they can't find someone.
Do you agree with me, Grezy?
Why can't you
Why can't you get a relationship?
But you understand what I'm saying,
Grezy, right? You understand what I'm saying?
You know, these people will say that
they can't find anyone, but they've got
multiple multiple multiple multiple options
just because they're a woman. Do you
understand? So, it's like, what the
actual [ __ ] I'm going to do a video on this.
I'm going to do a video on this and
screenshot this person's thing on
Reddit. And yes, I know 25 is
technically still young, but never have
been in a relationship. 25, but you've
chose to not be in a relationship.
That was your that was on you to not be
in a relationship. You know, no one's
forced you not to be in a relationship. So, it's like
say what you think sometimes. You know
what I'm saying? You know,
it's like they're actually mocking. They
habitly mock people that can't actually
find someone. Somebody that actually
wants a wife and somebody that actually
wants a [ __ ] kid.
I don't want kids. I don't want a wife.
But you get my point, you know. And
you're saying you're 25 and you've never
been in a relationship. I'm 28 and I've
tried more than anyone in the world and
I can't even get a [ __ ] date. So it
feels like you're mocking people.
Please God, I beg you ban these free
apps, three, four apps just to make
society a little bit more normal again.
Do you know what I'm saying? I'm I'm
doing a video on this. I am doing a
video on this. There's some tasty views
to be had on this. I'm telling you, bro.
Why can't you find a boyfriend? Have you
got crippling anxiety? Do you look like
Shrek? Cuz they're the only two reasons
why you can't find someone.
Because we all know now that if somebody
wanted to meet this person, Greavvesy,
they would reject them.
you know this if you're a feminist and
you don't want someone then that's fine.
You know you you're saying that you
don't want someone but you're trying to
act like you can't find someone.
That's the thing that's annoying me cuz
it feels like they are mocking you. Do
you understand Grezy? Not obviously on
purpose, but like
they are they are mocking you really.
25 and 2 months and you've never had a
relationship, but it's your choice to
not have had a relationship.
So they have these unrealistic standards
and then they wonder why they can't find anyone.
maybe have less unrealistic standards
and then maybe you'd find someone
and she said at minimum 6 to 8 months I
have another 40ish pounds to lose and I
don't think more self and with the south
the weather people more nicer I live in
a big city so there's lots to do in Massachusetts
there's no reason why this woman can't find someone
and Yeah, you're on a weight loss
journey. Okay. But I'm pretty sure you
could still find someone,
you know, especially since you're in America, just mocking.
And then this and then this woman says,
"At least you're not 39 and never been
in a relationship since I am very shy
and anxious." I mean, okay, at least
this one this person admits it. You
know, they're shy and they're anxious.
That's why they've never been in a relationship.
See, with me, there's not really a
there's not really a reason why I'm not
in a relationship now. Put the effort
in, put the money in, put the time in,
and I still can't find anyone. So,
there's not really a reason why I can't find anyone.
It's It's weird. It is weird. So,
you think I'm right, Grezy?
Do you think I'm right, lad?
You think I'm right, don't you, Grezy? Come on.
Don't you greasy? Yep.
Yeah, of course I'm right about this.
It's lame. They can't find someone.
They can't find anyone cuz no one's good
enough for them.
You know what I mean? That's why they
can't find someone. They're too picky.
They're too picky. That's what it is.
Tell me I'm wrong, Grezy. Tell me I'm
[ __ ] wrong. H.
So, if it's eating away at you being
almost 25 and never been in a
relationship, how would you think I feel
when I'm 28 in 10 days and I can't even
get a date no matter what I try? That's
why it's it's a mug's game. It's toxic.
This is what I'm saying. Yeah.
You know, I'm not shy. I'm not anxious.
I can't find anyone cuz I'm not Muslim
or because I'm [ __ ]
5 years older than someone. So, yeah. So, yeah,
I'm so glad I gave up, Grezy. Once I won
that £500, I just like, nah, that's my
ticket now to to give up forever here. Um,
and it's been good since. I felt right
since, you know, I don't even feel
bored. I feel like I'm on holiday giving
up with this whole dating thing
cuz it's just a complete and utter toxic
Mugs game. That's literally all it is.
That is all it is. You know,
it's a Mugs game, is it, Grezy? Mugs
game. When I won my the money back from
what I spent, I swear I'd never try again.
I got a lucky escape.
Yep. A lucky escape.
What's your opinion on it, Grezy? Why
don't you tell us what you think?
Tell us what you think. Greasy. Huh?
They need to ban Tik Tok. They need to
ban Instagram. And they need to ban dating apps.
It should be illegal for them to mock
actual guys that struggle.
It should be illegal. [ __ ] mocking
the [ __ ] man. They can get any man they want.
Stop saying you can't find somebody and
that you want to [ __ ] you know,
bro. I just I'm just sick of these women
mocking the average guy that struggles, Jamie.
You know, these women saying that they
can't find somebody when they've got
literally millions of options. Stop
mocking. Stop habitally mocking other
people. Stop doing that.
Why are they mocking people? It's mad,
bro. They can find someone, anyone they
want. As long as they're a four out of
10, they have they can get anyone.
Stop mocking men.
It's [ __ ] annoying, bro. You know.
Yeah. Well, there's this Okay, so
there's this woman. Okay, I'll tell you
what I'm saying. There's this woman
that's saying that she's 25 in 2 months
and it's eating away at her that she's
never been in a relationship, but she
can be in a relationship. Women have got
options. Women can get any man they
[ __ ] want. As long as there were four
out of 10, they can get any man they
want. Me, on the other hand, I can go
out, get 10 numbers, and not even get a
date. I could go out spending hundreds
just to hear I have a boyfriend, I'm not
interested, and I will never ever get
anywhere. This is why I gave up. These
women can get any man they want. It's
because of their unrealistic standards
that they don't meet anyone. That's what it is.
Stop [ __ ] mocking people. You can
find someone. You're just too [ __ ]
picky. Just like all of you. You know
what I'm saying? It's [ __ ] madness,
bro. really is.
When I got 10 numbers three weeks ago
from approaching, I swear I'd never try
again. And I haven't. That was my clue to leave.
I won the money back and I swear I'd
never ever try again cuz yeah, it's it's
clear as day. All women are the same
now. And that's it. It doesn't matter
what anyone says, they will show
something completely different. So
yeah, that's it.
Why are they saying that they can't
[ __ ] find someone when they [ __ ] can? Huh?
You know, it's [ __ ] mad.
Uh, firstly, I'm not your mate. And most
people I know that are single. So,
you're 30 and you've got a partner. Good
for you, bro. Firstly, I'm not your
mate. So, don't ever call me mate cuz I
don't know you. And I was going through
my um I don't know if you was on here
earlier, Grezy. I was going through my
WhatsApp and my Instagram
cuz somebody said millions of people in relationships.
Yeah, but there's also got to be
millions of people that aren't in relationships.
Greasy. Do you know why? Because all of
the people that I know, most of them are single.
Women, men, most people are single or
the same. It's either got to be them.
Most of them are single or they're the same.
Like there's millions of people in
relationships. If there's millions of
people in relationships, there's got to
be millions of people that are single.
Cuz most of the people that I know that
have no correlation or relation to each
other, even women, are single.
And there's people obviously I know that
in relationships, but most most of them are single. So yeah.
Yeah. And not all men are you white knights.
And not men are all white knights like you.
Single. Single. It's crazy, isn't it? So
many people are single. No,
you are doomed.
You are doomed.
Like, you think sticking up for women is
going to get you laid. I'm just not
scared to say what I think. You know, if
somebody calls me an incel, I don't give
a [ __ ] You know, that's that has no
substance to it anymore. I I'm just not
going to sit there and defend women when
I know what they're like. I'm not scared
to say what I think. So, yeah.
Yeah. You're in a happy, loving
relationship. Good for you.
I will never deal with them ever again.
I've gave them countless of chances to
prove me wrong and they're always the same.
So yeah, like I said, I got a lucky escape.
I'll never try here again. I'm out in
I'm out next month anyways. So I'm out
of here. I can't [ __ ] wait. Oh, I'm
rubbing my hands. Oh, it's going to be
exciting. No more [ __ ] from these
[ __ ] women in this country. Oh, it's
going to be lush. It's going to be lush.
No more makebelieve boyfriends. No more
mind games. No more you're too old for
me, you're too young for me. [ __ ] all that. Yeah.
I can't wait.
I can't [ __ ] wait. I really, really
can't wait to get out of here. Yeah,
I don't know why these women say they
can't get relationships when they can.
I think the police need to make that a
law for women to stop complaining.
Um, they need to really really make it
illegal for women to complain about not
being able to find anyone cuz it's quite
offensive, you know. It is. It really
really is quite offensive because these
problem these women would have no
problems getting into relationships.
They'd have no problems
um you know getting sex or whatever it
is they want.
Injured gone. Bye-bye. So yeah, that's it.
I think that's the skint virgin in the
bedsit in it.
I think that's the skint virgin in the bedsit. Yeah.
So, I prove that they're the ones that
are jealous and obsessed with me. By me
not reacting to these people, Steven
Howard, it shows that they're the ones
that are obsessed with me. Told you.
Even if it took two weeks to prove it, I
proved it. They're the ones that are
obsessed and jealous with me because
when you stop, they gravitate toward
you, which means that they're the ones
that are jealous of you. And I also
discovered as well that these people
have got no life on here. Um because
they'd be on YouTube every day, like
every day. And every single live stream
I'd click on, they'd be there. Uh so
that's how I discovered that these are
the ones that are jealous of me and and
they ain't got no life. So, it was good
to be off YouTube, to be honest, to know
like what they're like.
They're the ones that are jealous of me
and they ain't got no life. Have you
seen that account, Smokey Be Grezy? This
guy says that he's got a misses. This
guy says that he's got money. Yet, he
comes on YouTube all day, every day. He
Now, I was off of YouTube for over a
week and I didn't go out drinking. I
didn't really have much going on in my
life. So, if these people actually had a
life and stuff going on in their life,
they wouldn't be on here the way they
are on here. Does that make sense? So, yeah. Yeah.
They're the ones that are obsessed with me, lad.
But yeah, they can't seem to see see the
wrong in women,
you know. They just defend them.
They can't do no wrong in their eyes.
Oh man, I wish I gave up years ago.
I wish I really gave up years ago.
I wish I did.
The police need to make it illegal for
women to complain.
It's very, very, very, very horrible.
It's very degrading.
Um, you know, they shouldn't be able to
complain about not being able to find
someone. They can complain about
somebody that they're with and ask for
advice what to do. But don't say that
you can't find someone because everybody
knows that if a woman goes on Tinder or
if a woman goes on a dating app, she can
pick any man, which is [ __ ] it up for us.
So, stop moaning and complaining you
can't find someone, you know.
about it's eating away at you. That
really hit a nerve. That did. That
really, really, really hit a nerve. You know,
society is [ __ ] bro. Society really you know.
Nah, stop boring. It's the truth,
though. Why do these women keep
complaining they can't find somebody
when they easily can?
It's not boring. It's the truth.
Nah, nah, nah. It's not boring, bro.
It's not boring. I've had enough of it.
You know, I've had enough of it.
Complaining they can't find someone.
I'm going to reply to that if it lets
me. Hopefully I don't get banned.
Right. Stop mocking.
Stop mocking the average man. Any woman
who is even average
can get any man they want. Right.
Stop mocking the average man. Any woman
who is even average who can get can get
any man they want without even trying.
Three weeks ago.
Three weeks ago. I
Yeah, I'll reply back. Yep.
So, what do you say you think of Reddit mody?
What did you say you think of uh Reddit mods? Crazy.
They ban people to feel powerful. >> Yeah,
they need that power. Greasy,
Without that power, they'd go mad. Greasy.
Without that power, abandoning people,
they go [ __ ] mad. You know, they need that power.
Just depressed, bro.
Depressed. Thinking about my bad
experiences with women.
Just the same old.
How are you doing?
That guy on Reddit went quiet
trying to make excuses for women leading
people on. [ __ ] off.
Someone was supposed to meet me Saturday.
I wish I got excuses made for me.
If I was to lead people on and stuff,
they' probably call me a [ __ ] prick. Yeah.
Why is the [ __ ] skint virgin in the
bedsit so obsessed with me?
Monty spent £200 on trainers, didn't he? £200.
No, I've got an Xbox.
Yeah, Jensen. I went out three weeks
ago. I got 10 women's numbers and I
didn't even get a date. I was supposed
to meet a woman last week, but she flaked.
All women are the same.
All women are the same. There's no good ones.
Yeah, I look maxed. I looks maxed, bro.
Uh I think I approached about 30 people.
I got 10 numbers. I only got one reply
and I was supposed to meet them last
Saturday. Took them two weeks to reply
and then they said that they were sick
and they couldn't meet me.
Yeah, I don't think I'm ever going to
meet anyone, Jensen. That's why I gave up.
Yeah, that's why I gave up, bro. Because
it's like you go out, they say they've
got a boyfriend or they're not interested or
um they give you their um number and
lead you on.
So, don't get disheartened.
So me going out getting 10 numbers and
not a single date even though I looked
my best is not supposed to dishearten me.
H I don't think you understand the
severity of that. I went out, I
approached, I got 10 numbers and I
didn't even get a date.
I don't think I I can't be disheartening, bro.
I think that's enough to to to
discourage anyone. I mean, they put me
off women for life.
I just realized they're all the same,
you know? Like, the more women you meet,
the more you just realize they're all
the same and they're not good people.
That's why I haven't been out in 3
weeks. It's my birthday in 10 days. And
I said I was going to go out on my
birthday, but to be honest with you, I probably won't. So, yeah,
I'd probably just go for a meal. Yeah,
I'm just going to go for a meal. I think
I just don't want to ever try again with
women. I just they're just all the same.
There's no good ones out there. I know that now.
I can't find um motivation or courage to
ever want to try again. Not courage, the
desire to ever want to talk to a woman again, Jensen,
cuz you got 10 numbers and you didn't
even get a date. I don't think you're
going to meet someone somehow, you know?
Let's be real about this, bro. Let's be
Let's be so real about this.
>> Yeah. And I spent about £600 as well,
Jensen. I spent about £600.
Oh, Reddit's banned me again.
It's a [ __ ] Mugs game. I'm on dating
apps. I can't get any matches.
Nope. It won't out every week. I tried
the bars, the clubs, the street, the train station. Um,
nope. Don't get any matches on dating apps.
Well, there was one big fat single mom
who was about three out of 10. So,
I approached on the street, the train
station, the pubs, the bars, the clubs,
shopping center. I've approached everywhere.
Not interested in this country.
So, I prefer not to humiliate myself anymore.
Yeah, it's not worth it.
All women are the same. Yeah.
Uh I just accepted I'm going to be sexist forever.
Bit of a shame though. Wasting your
youth, not even being able to get laid
or anything. It's a waste of life, isn't it?
And then the last time I went out,
Jensen, I spent about £600,5600,
but then I won the money back on
roulette. And then after that I was
like, "Nah, I'm not I'm not going out
again. I'm not trying.
I'm not trying now, bro."
Yeah. Do you know what I don't Do you
know what I hate about these women? Uh LG, right? Um
this woman uh was she wrote about she
said I am 25 in two months and the fact
I've never been in a relationship has
been eating away a lot eating away at me
a lot lately. That was kind of that kind
of hit a nerve.
That really really kind of hit a nerve
that did cuz it's like they're habitedly
seeking men uh sorry habitatly um
mocking men that actually struggle
because there's no women that can't find someone.
No, they're they're filled with options.
So stop saying that you can't find
someone. I replied on the post, "Stop
mocking the average man." Dot dot dot.
Any woman who is even average looking
can get any man they want without even
trying. How have you not managed to find
someone? I'm 28, tried dating apps,
approaching women, and I can't even get
a date. Three weeks ago, I got 10
numbers and not a single date. How do
you think I feel?
So, I'll be looking forward to my
response. [ __ ] mocking men. That is
that is mocking men. That should be a
crime, you know, for them to even
complain about not being able to find
someone that they need to put a law on
that, bro. Just like they put a law on
incelss or any misogynist
um things against women, they need to
stop women being able to complain about
not being able to find anyone cuz that
is offensive. That is very very very
offensive especially to someone like me.
You know it is very offensive bro. I
take offense to that
because there's no re reason why this
woman cannot find someone,
you know. So, she said she wants kids
and a husband. Yeah. Why can't you why
can't you find someone? What's the problem?
I don't know. I was supposed to go there
today and back rice up, but I just I was
just sleeping all day.
Yeah, I was just I was just sleeping all
day, man. Sleeping all day. Yep.
Oh, you know, uh, bro, you know, [ __ ]
Money Mike, uh, Timmy and Monty met and
then they're all the best defense now.
money. Mike was like, "If you want
trouble, come around the corner." I
would have went around the corner, mate.
I would have said, "Come on then, you
little cunt." That's what I would have
said. But obviously, I've got history
with Mike. Monty doesn't have that much
history. Yeah, they they're best of
friends now. They're best of friends. Uh-huh. Yeah.
Best of friends.
Let Timmy come up. One sec. Yeah,
they're best of friends.
Yeah. Do you remember when [ __ ] Timmy
was like, "I'm going to knock him out.
I'm going to knock him out." Yeah.
I was actually tempted to go to
Birmingham today, but I was sleeping all day.
>> All right, Timmy, I'm going to knock you out.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] all, lad.
>> I'm going to knock you out.
>> Why do you kick people out your hangouts
when you get owned, lad?
>> You don't own anyone. You got owned by money.
>> But you didn't come to Birmingham today.
Even the [ __ ] Royce owned you for
[ __ ] sake. Yeah, I was supposed to go
meet Rice today and it was supposed to
be me and Rice versus Timmy and Monty.
>> Bro, I waited all day, dude. I stayed
out all [ __ ] day hoping you was going
to turn up and you [ __ ]
>> really to me.
>> Why were you afraid of the Mongol?
>> No, you're afraid already,
>> bro. He got owned by the voice of all
people. That's shocking. How did he get
owned by Rice?
>> Cuz Rice throw the [ __ ] rail in him
or some [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Did you see the second part,
>> brother? Like the [ __ ] he said about his
family, he should have knocked out the voice,
>> you know,
>> like bas all the [ __ ] you say about
people's folks. You should have been
knocked out and you was afraid to come to Prime.
>> Why did you say you were scared of Prime?
>> the prime?
>> Why did you say I'm going to knock him out? Huh? >> PJ,
>> you were afraid to come and stay cuz you
knew what you were going to get, lad.
>> No, I didn't.
>> Listen, listen. If that was Listen, I
would slap you at my cup. I've already
put Listen, Timmy. I've already beat you now.
>> Timmy, I've already beat you. I would
have slapped you at my cup. I've already
beat you. I beat you a tiger. I've
already defeated you two. You know
>> you don't get it. If you would have come
up today, you wouldn't be mouthing off
now. You'd be in the back of an ambulance, lad.
>> What about by you really? Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's [ __ ] true, lad.
>> All right. Listen, LT, you want to make
sure your kids are not going
>> There's no LT [ __ ] mate. There's no
>> LT. You need to make sure like your
children don't go on YouTube cuz this is really bad.
>> You're afraid LT, mate. You should be
worse than LT today, lad.
>> I'm going to knock him out. You remember
when Timmy said that?
>> Yes. You stop listening to that Py LT
and start [ __ ] living in the real world. Lad,
>> I'm going to knock him. Remember when
you said that to me?
>> I don't think you understand, PJ. You
would have come up today. The
consequences what would have happened.
>> Stop listening to the [ __ ] wheel.
>> What do you mean? It's not funny. PJ,
you would have been hurt.
>> Hey, listen. Timmy,
>> you're calling you.
>> PJ, if you think I'm full of [ __ ] come
up tomorrow, lad.
>> Timmy, I don't want to beat you again.
Well, you're not going to beat no one,
son. You don't understand, lad. I had
someone ready to scar you open in the pub, lad.
>> I'll bring King with me.
>> You weren't me. I'm not saying who he is.
>> I'm going to bring King Grezy to Birmingham.
>> All right, come to Birmingham tomorrow,
lad, and see how tough you are, dude.
>> Not like I beat you last time in London.
>> I like, but he's leading up the [ __ ]
goddamn path. That one.
Timmy, I'm going to get Timmy. Okay, you
>> I'm not going to argue someone's got
autism an absolute imbecile, right?
>> You really are this gangster for what
you say you are, lad. Then come to Birmingham tomorrow.
>> Should I go there tomorrow? I'll just go
there tomorrow. [ __ ] it.
>> Okay, come tomorrow, mate. Like, mate,
this will be another level.
Should I just go there tomorrow?
>> Why is this bast
a lot coming from don't like you? >> Yeah.
Listen to me.
>> All right. My lad and we'll go from there.
This guy's actually that [ __ ] he
thinks messing up.
>> This community is so sick.
>> Well, stop laughing then. Come up then.
Stop listening to that northeast monkey. That's
>> okay. I'm bringing people with me. I'm
>> You don't understand, bro. You've got
out of a lot of things lightly. You come
back to this city, lad. You will not get
out of this one. So, lightly. I'm
bringing people with me.
>> There's no London Tyler [ __ ] where a
glass where your window goes through.
That you will literally be the back of a [ __ ] ambulance.
>> Oh, listen.
>> What come
the [ __ ] point you'll be [ __ ]
more than you [ __ ] ever been.
>> You can laugh if you want. Let's see if
you got minerals, mate. Tomorrow
you see that woman in the orange like
the west. Did you see the woman riding
the other drivers?
>> All these little [ __ ] like BJ
carry on [ __ ] being a coward. You
autistic. You think this is real life?
>> All right, fell.
smart. You are a [ __ ]
>> Um, you are [ __ ] >> Yeah.
All on the same website. You can watch
the side bend on.
It's now my house moving. He almost got
knocked over. Listen.
I'm going to knock him out.
I should have went today though, Elsie.
I should have went. Now wife is angry with me.
Rice has been defeated. You know, cuz
Rice got defeated.
Yeah, I should have went today in it. I
should have went. Yeah,
but to be fair, I don't really comment
here much anymore. LT
the skin virgin still does videos on me
but he's just a keyboard warrior so he
doesn't bother me [Music] you know.
Yeah. All over YouTube. Yeah. All on the
same website you can watch Pluto ony. Yeah.
I'm going to knock him out. I should
have went today so me, Rice, and Kayie
could all be a happy family.
We would have all end up on the drink in it, Grey. Yeah, man. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. That's why I don't bother
with the [ __ ] skinned virgin in the
bedet anymore. You see, bro, is it? I
just wanted to show you that fight
because I thought you would have found it funny.
I don't really bother with this anymore,
bro. I was off here for a little while.
Come back. I can't be asked.
You know what's the day tomorrow? Saturday.
Well, today I'm going to go Birmingham
today. [ __ ] it.
I'm going to go to Birmingham today, I think.
Yeah, I'm going to go to Birmingham. I'm
going to knock him out.
I'll go Birmingham tomorrow, LT. Yeah.
But will you watch? I want you to watch
on your little mobile.
On your little mobile. [Laughter]
I'm dead. I'll go tomorrow. [ __ ] it.
I'll go tomorrow. [ __ ] it. Yeah.
Go tomorrow. Yeah,
[ __ ] it. I'll go tomorrow.
I'll do Pluto and Star Wars proud.
Grezy, King will be watching as well
with his little paws.
King will be watching. Only Grezy with
his little paws
smiling. Yeah. Yeah. I'm going tomorrow.
[ __ ] it. I'm going tomorrow. I'm going
I'm going to teach these [ __ ] a lesson. Yeah.
But Rice is angry with me. It was
supposed to be me and Rice versus
uh Monty and Michael.
Yeah. I want that money, Mike, bro. I
want that money, Mike.
[ __ ] tell me to come around the
corner. I would have went around the
[ __ ] corner. [ __ ] Mong.
No, I can't bring King with me. He might get hurt.
He might get hurt. Bless him. No, I get
We don't want Little King getting hurt.
He'll be watching. He'll probably be
watching on the TV. Greasy.
He'll be watching on the telly. Yeah.
No, Rice is not my friend now. I didn't
go. He said I set him up, but I didn't
set him up. I didn't set him up. Really? I didn't.
Well, Rice is my friend. No. Yeah.
I didn't tell
Ela. I didn't tell you about that bagel
I got, did I?
Bro, it was [ __ ] stinking, bro. I got
a bagel. Yeah, [ __ ] two weeks ago. I
ordered it. There's a place I ordered
that once before. It was all right.
Yeah. Ordered it again. It started
smelling like fish. Some [ __ ] fishy
smell. And I thought maybe it was cold
or something. Just needed to warm it up.
And it But even thinking about it now,
I've just had chocolate.
Oh, what was wrong with it, bro? It
started smelling like
fish. I think someone wiped their ass
with it or something, bro. And I was
picking out the bits that looked all
right. I don't know. I kind of been put
off bagels now. Yep. I've kind of been
put off bagels now, bro.
It was [ __ ] vile, bro. It was [ __ ] vile. Absolutely. Absolutely
about to be sick. I want to be sick,
bro. I don't want to stick up that five, guys.
[ __ ] that, bro. It was [ __ ] vile,
man. I don't know what was wrong with
it. I don't know if it was off or
someone had shuten it or something. I
don't [ __ ] know, bro. It was nah. No,
no, no, no, no. It was nasty. Nasty, bro.
the but yeah I'll be going tomorrow anyways. Yeah,
I'm sick of that. I just want to shut
the whole community down now. Know what
I mean? LT, this has been going on for
[ __ ] years and years and years and
years and years. I just want to shut the
whole community down,
you know? Just shut them all up once and
for all. I want to be the king of it and
I don't want anyone else coming back on
here, you know.
Yep. Well, I I'll be going to a park.
Well, my phone's blocked, so I'll have
to meet them in like the pub and then
walk to the park and then we'll do it or
walk away from the public cuz obviously
my phone's blocked, so can get a new
one. So, I can only go off Wi-Fi.
Yeah, I can get on the drink tomorrow as
well. It's Saturday. Yeah,
I'm going to knock him out.
I'm going to knock him out. Greasy. Yeah.
How you been though? How's a little Bubshion?
I bet he's growing up rather rapidly. Yeah.
Is he growing up rather rapidly?
How's the little bub shed? Huh? Yeah.
Oh, bless. Bless him if he's drawing on
walls. Oh, bless you.
Oh, that's so cute.
That's so sweet.
So, if I go tomorrow, you're going to
give me a w. Yeah.
Have we make it 150?
Make it 150. Yeah. So when I turn there,
you're going to give me the 150. All right.
150. Yeah. Why not
give me 150?
Yeah, give me 150.
I'm I'll be going tomorrow anyways 100%.
I don't need a cash. I've got my own
money, but I'm not going to turn down 100 pound, you know. Yeah.
I want to shut this whole community
down, Grezy, cuz it's not safe for kids
to go on,
you know? It's really, really not safe. Yeah.
It's not [ __ ] safe, bro, for kids to
go on. So, I want to shut this whole thing down.
I want to shut it down, bro.
Once and [ __ ] fall. Yeah,
I want to own just [ __ ] I want to own
the community, bro, you know.
Well, we'll see who meets me tomorrow,
won't we, lad? Huh? We'll see who meets
me tomorrow, won't we?
Won't we, lads?
I'm going to [ __ ] knock him out.
I'm going to knock him out. All I'm
Did you Did you hear that bit when said it, Grezy?
That poor woman almost got hit. Yeah.
All right. Let me tell you something as well. Um
LG, you know that Smokeoky B ain't got a
life? You know when you were saying that
you're not on here if you got stuff
going on in your life? Well, I was off
here for 8 days. Yeah. And periodically
I'd go on the live stream. Yeah. Like
click on it and I'd read for like 2
minutes and it was the same people. So
that's how you know that these people
ain't got a life
cuz they wouldn't be on here typing
every day, bro. If they've got [ __ ]
going on, it's so obvious that they
ain't got a life. Um, I'm probably going
to get the train about
probably 1:00 p.m. Yeah,
about 1:00 p.m. to be honest. I want to
get there nice and early. Lovely.
Oh, by the way, LT
Monty's going to be getting sent down.
He's got caught on the 27th.
So, he's So, he's going to be getting sent down.
Yeah, he's going to be getting sent down
cuz of riot [ __ ] Do you remember the
stuff that happened with the riots?
I can't stop giggling, Boozy.
I can't stop giggling.
He's still crying over Natalie
LT. It's like when [ __ ] nonslegs used
to cry over [ __ ] Britney.
She don't want to know you. She rejected
you. She don't want to know.
Now he's going to be getting sent down.
He's going to be getting sent downtown. LT Yeah,
we're going to take you downtown. Yeah,
you still need to go to Belfast and sort
that law J out. LT,
come on. I'm going Birmingham tomorrow
and I am definitely going.
And I I am definitely going. So yeah,
I'm sick of these [ __ ] I'm [ __ ]
sick of them. [Laughter]
I swear to God, I'm sick of them. Yeah. [Laughter]
I'm so bubbly. Yeah, you need to go to
Belfast. No, LT,
you still need to go to Belfast. [ __ ]
it. What have you got to lose? Nothing.
I'm going Birmingham tomorrow. So, yeah. you know.
So, who won the fight? Rice or Monty LT? Who won? Mhm.
He dodged his punch in it. That was a
nice dodge though.
Yeah, he dodged his punch, didn't he?
There we go.
What's the first bit? Um, LT,
I reckon Monty might be able to take LT.
All women are the bloody same.
Yeah, still depressed about women and
[ __ ] Slim, but I'm used to it now,
to be honest.
I give up. I'm I'm gone next month anyway. So,
I'll give you that opportunity if you want. Yeah,
the women's situation is still [ __ ] though, Slim.
Really, really [ __ ]
But it will it will never change, will it? So,
Give you that chance if you want.
Slim. Why are women all the same?
When women say they can't find someone,
that should be illegal. They can get any
man they want.
[ __ ] mocking the average guy you know.
Well, can't you come to Birmingham
tomorrow then LT? You can come as well
if you want.
Bing and me off.
All women are the same slim.
All women are the same lad.
You know, all women are the same, man.
I think to Birmingham tomorrow as well.
The Skint Virgin
I think the skin virgin should come to Birmingham tomorrow. really really
the skin virgin.
And the reason I took a break off of
YouTube is because whenever I go for the
[ __ ] skin virgin, people say, "Oh,
well, he can't be a virgin. He's got a
girlfriend and he can't be skint because
he's shown this. And I was like, well,
what about when I showed thousands? What
about when I've proved I've had sex,
you know? What about then? No one ever
says anything about that. That's another
reason why I come off a little bit
because no one ever backs me up. So,
[ __ ] the lottery. You know,
it is weird to be honest. Yeah.
Yeah. He's definitely still a virgin,
mate. Definitely. He tried to come in
earlier talking about Is he? He's
obsessed with my sloppy seconds. Obsessed.
Well, I guess I would be too as well if
I was still if I was a 31y old virgin.
Nah. All women are evil.
All women are evil. And all women are
the same, man.
They're all the same evil.
All of them. Yep.
I just can't find the motivation to want
to try after getting 10 numbers and not
even getting a date. Like I lost the
motivation. I lost the desire after that
to be honest.
And the fact I spent 600 pound as well.
So I can't find the motivation or the
desire after that to ever want to
entertain it again to be fair.
Cuz it will always be the same here. Is
it? It's obvious now. Yeah,
I've been put off women. There's no
point if they're all the same.
They say the same stuff. They do the
same stuff. They have the same
matterisms. They have the same excuses.
They lead people on the same way. But
they're not all the same. We crossed the
line there. They're not all the same.
They just have all the same similarities, same mannerisms,
same mind games, same sayings, but
they're not all the same. That's just by
choice. Huh? Yeah, right. Only a [ __ ]
white knight would [ __ ] believe that
they're not all the same. They're the
same. They're all the same in every [ __ ] way. Like literally,
there's nothing different about any of
them, bro. Trust me,
they don't even turn me on anymore.
They're evil. And I don't want anything
to do with [ __ ] evil. Evil [ __ ]
Horrible, evil, nasty, nasty bastards. They are. So,
but I'm gone next month anyways. So
yeah, I'm not even going out drinking on
my birthday to be fair, bro. I'll
probably just go for a meal.
Yeah, there's no going back after that,
I don't think.
And you need to take pride in yourself
as well. Like, bro, do you not have any
respect for yourself?
What What are you going to do? Go out
and be made to feel ugly by women that
you're better than dealing with their
[ __ ] their lies, their excuses? Do you
not have any pride for yourself?
Like, bro, you're worth more than that
dealing with these stuck up women that
are all the same,
that think they're better than you, that
have the same attitude. Like, bro, I'd
rather live without sex for the rest of
my life than ever have to deal with that again,
you know? Cuz pride is a um pride is a
big thing. Just like I won't accept
money from anyone
ever again. So, I'll just go about sex
for the rest of my life. Don't bother
me, bro. It is what it is. So,
oh wait, when I got a 10 number and I
didn't get a date, when I got the 10
numbers and I didn't get a date, it
depressed me for like over a week. But
then after that, I was like, "Okay,
well, now we've learned our lesson. We
know it's never going to change here. We
know all women are the same
t so there's no point trying again."
So, in a way, it's a good thing it
happened because I learned that like
it's never ever going to change her.
So, there's been no point in me ever
even going out ever again. You know, got
the money, can afford to do it, can go
out every week if I want to. Not a problem.
But it's like it's mad. I was supposed
to meet someone on Saturday. Slim. I was
supposed to meet somebody in Liverpool
Street last Saturday. Oh, I can't meet
you. I'm sick. [ __ ] off.
final straw. Get [ __ ] So yeah.
Yeah. So I'll never entertain him again,
bro. I don't think if I was in Belgium
right now or the Netherlands right now,
I'd go out every week cuz I feel like
there'd be more chance of me meeting
someone. But here,
they're obviously not interested here.
So, it's like I'm wasting my time. I'm
wasting their time and it's they're
never going to be interested in this country.
So, it's what it is. I tried my best and
that's all you can do. So,
Now when I went out I spent5600
and then I put £100 in a roulette and
then I won500 and something took it that
was it bro I was like that's my lesson
learned. So, lesson learned. So, yeah.
So, toxic. Antman like he he that's the
right word for it. What Ant-Man said. It's toxic.
It really really really is toxic. That's
the right word. Negative and toxic.
That's what it is. You know,
and and what makes me laugh is the the
people that try to make excuses for
them. Oh, they done it to be nice.
What? They've led somebody on and agreed
to meet somebody to be nice. I don't
think that's being nice. I think you're
you're you're being sarcastic. So then
they always make excuses for them as
well. So there's no point you even
saying anything or proving anything. So that's that. Yeah,
I can say the past four or five years.
I've never really had a good experience.
Not really. No, it wasn't worth the
time. It wasn't worth the money. No, I
didn't. Didn't at all.
I wish I left years ago to be honest. But yeah,
but I always thought I was going to meet
someone here because that's what people
tell you, you know,
they've got unrealistic standards.
That's the problem. That's the [ __ ] You know,
that is the problem. They've got
unrealistic expectations and unrealistic
standards that are just impossible to
meet. So you're just a mug even trying.
You're best off just paying for sex.
Like if you want sex, obviously I don't
care about sex, so I'm not going to pay
for it. So but you know,
cuz no one should have to go out and
deal with their [ __ ]
their lies, their [ __ ] their games.
Not I'm not dealing with that ever again.
I'm not sure. I'm not sure.
Yeah. I was texting at Damon yesterday.
I said he's a little nick.
I said he's a little nick and his
girlfriend and his ex has got saggy ass tits. Yeah.
And you need to obviously think what's
best for you as well. Like all of these
bad experiences I've had and the stuff
that keeps happening as well. You need
to really think about what's best for you.
You won the money back that you spent.
You've tried recently. Just give up now.
That's it. Just give up.
So that's what I'm doing. Yeah.
Cuz I was expecting that person to meet
me last week.
I trying to be positive about it. I was
like, "Oh yeah, okay. Well, I might have
spent £600, but I got the money back and
I've got some nice gums to wear from the dry cleaners. Um, and
I should go out and try, you know, uh,
sorry. Um, let me just go out and meet
this person cuz I've got nothing to
lose. And if if I met them and the date
went bad, I would have I would have done
some approaches, but I would have only
have went out cuz she wanted to meet me.
But I'm not going out to approach or
meet anyone. I'm not doing that. But I
would have met her cuz we agreed to go
on a date. So I wouldn't mind going out,
spending a couple hundred pound, not a
problem. And then obviously if whatever
happened, I would have just tried to
meet other people whilst I was out. But
I'm not going to go out and do the whole
thing all over again, you know.
I'm not doing that.
And they met in Birmingham. So yeah,
they met in Birmingham. So I'm not going to Yeah,
you can understand my point, can't you, LT?
You know, where would somebody find the
desire or encouragement? I don't even
drink anymore. And bro, I can afford it.
Trust me, I can go out every week. I've
been saving money. Every bit of money
that I spent the past two months, I want
it back. I done good on the football. I
done good on the roulette, but I just
don't see the point in it.
It's not even about the money. Like,
it's it's just I can't be asked with it.
Drinking. Like, I nah, bro. I'm just I'm
over it now, bro. Really over it.
Really, really, really over it.
My dry cleaning cost me £30
and then I won30 on a football bet, won
150, 200, 500. So all of the money I
spent I got back.
So I'm all right, bro. Good with money. Yeah, man. [Music]
And then the lies. Oh, I'm not going to
get with you cuz you're Muslim.
Or I'm not going to get with you cuz
you're too old for me. Or you're too
young for me. like you're not ugly. We
are not ugly. We do not need to be
dealing with their [ __ ] and them trying
to make us feel like we are not good
enough. You know what I'm saying? Are we
perfect? No. No one's perfect. But
you're good enough to [ __ ] be able to
go on a [ __ ] date with someone. I'm
pretty sure. So, [ __ ] them and [ __ ] their standards.
You know, they're not even worth it
anyways, bro. What? For like [ __ ]
dead sex. No, I'm good, bro. [ __ ] that.
you know. So, yeah.
Toxic. Proper toxic.
They're so shallow. Like they some of
these women um LT would would would get
would not get with somebody because
they've got a beard. And they would not
get with somebody because they don't
have a beard.
Do you know what I'm saying, bro? Like,
that's how shallow they are. So, they
would rather like miss out on a good person
um because someone's got a beard or they
don't have a beard or they have hair or
they don't have hair. That's how they
are, bro. They're [ __ ] They're
proper proper [ __ ] And I was
saying earlier before you joined that um
uh basically that if I could if I had a
wish, I'd ban Tik Tok, Snapchat,
Instagram, and dating apps. Bam. And
then these women would be [ __ ] because
all of the men that they'd want, they
wouldn't be able to get them unless them
men approach them. And most men are
scared to approach. And they're
obviously not going to approach men. So
they would have to get what they're [ __ ] given,
you know? I'd love it to be that way,
bro. I would I'd choose that over a
million pound, I think. I would.
And then they'd have to And then they
could And then obviously they wouldn't
be picky because I mean,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. But but no,
no. You're missing the point. You're
missing the point. There's a difference
between a fat [ __ ] and a fat person
that doesn't take care of themsel and
then there's a difference between
somebody that's a six, seven out of 10
who they're not even going to give a
chance. I mean, there's a bit different
that that that's the difference. There's
a big difference between somebody not
getting with somebody who hasn't worked
on themsel and somebody using all of the
excuses in the world to not get with
somebody when there's nothing wrong with
them. like this video that I showed,
nice beard, nice hair, nice eyebrows,
suited and booted. There was nothing
wrong with my appearance and that was an
example and that is just an example with
somebody that lives in a different
country. So, I mean, I don't think
anyone's got preferences for fat people.
That's not the point. The point is is if
you look good enough
um and we all have preferences. Yes,
every single person has preferences but
they don't exclude themsel to them
preferences whereas women do
you know that's the difference. They
exclude themsel to a preference.
So you kind of miss the point in what
I'm trying to say. The point I'm trying
to make is somebody that's above average
looking is still not good enough for
them. That's what the problem is. So yeah,
if that makes sense. So they've got
unrealistic standards. They don't even
got high standards. They've got
unrealistic standards. You know,
cuz let's just say, right, that somebody
wouldn't even give me a chance. Yeah. I
looks maxed. Why would you give me a
chance? If I look maxed, I'm above
average looking. I'm average to above
average looking. So, wouldn't you
wouldn't you want to know my
personality? Let's just use it as an
example. But nope, they wouldn't want to
get to know your personality because you
don't um you don't get past their
unrealistic standard threshold.
So, that's it's it's just insane to be
honest. Thinking about it, it's mad.
Then you get these women saying, "Oh, I
can't find somebody. I can't find a man."
I'm going to I'm going to email the I'm
going to email the um the MP about this
and basically say that you need to make
this illegal where these women are
complaining about not being able to find anyone
cuz it's causing me distress every time
I see it cuz they can find somebody,
they can find a boyfriend, they can have
kids. They are mocking men that can't, you know. So yeah, man. That's it.
So So there's nothing wrong with me.
There's nothing wrong with the way that
I look when I look Max. But yet how yet
it seems so impossible for me to even be
given a chance. You not see that as [ __ ] up?
It's very very very [ __ ] up. It's
depressing as well.
Very very very depressing
and it will never change. So that's that.
It will never change with these women ever. Yep.
Depressing, isn't it?
To be honest. All right, bro. To be honest,
that's [ __ ] for so long. I just feel
like normal now. I'm not going out. I
just feel like I'm I'm on holiday, you know?
But you can't compare a fat [ __ ] to
somebody that's that's a man that's six,
seven out of 10.
There's a big difference. That means you
are being picky. That means you've got
unrealistic standards. That's the difference.
That is definitely the difference.
There's a fine line between having a
realistic preference and being um being
too picky. There's a big difference. So,
and it shouldn't be a deal breaker as well. Like
you never had it before where like
Yeah. Well, the simps [ __ ] the game up
in it. That's
sad, isn't it? Nope.
These women are all the same, bro. All the same.
How they stay a lot is [ __ ] beyond me. Yeah.
No, they're not ever.
I don't even get a sex drive anymore,
bro. I don't even have a sex drive
to be honest.
Cuz how can you want to be have anything
to do with people that are evil? People
that are not growing up in their head, you know?
Don't know how much I weigh, bro.
Yeah, it's depressing, bro. It's depressing.
I just spend all day on Reddit, to be
honest, bro. I get to chill, save money,
so it's all good, man.
Yeah. Yeah. Like I said, I was going to
go out drinking on my birthday, but nah,
I can't be [ __ ] bro.
That was it for me, I think. Bro. Yeah. [ __ ] madness.
Yeah, football's on tomorrow. I'm not
doing a football bet.
Nope. Don't even gamble anymore. So,
yeah. I'm surprised I've not played
roulette since like three weeks ago
since I won.
Nah, bro. I don't need money problems in
my life. Don't need My life is [ __ ] hard enough
with these [ __ ] women.
Yeah. So, I don't want to gamble.
You [ __ ] get mood swings and [ __ ]
would be um on a place where they didn't ban people.
I should have found someone by now, bro.
[ __ ] hell. I'm 28 in [ __ ] 10 days.
Been on this community six years. Still
haven't found anyone.
Haven't found anyone in six.
Oh, the escort thing put me off as well. Yeah,
sometimes I have thoughts of like
killing myself and [ __ ] bro. But like I just
cuz of my experiences with women and [ __ ]
and the fact it never changes as well.
I mean, there's nothing you can do about
it, but then it kind of just goes away. Yeah, man.
It is [ __ ] depressing, you know.
Very, very depressing.
Never changes either.
I don't do anything anyways. I just
sleep all day now. I don't even go out every day.
I got really put off by them
experiences. I swear to God, bro. Been
put off doing anything
as it would anyone, you know, as it would anyone. So, yeah.
Yeah, man. I've had faults and [ __ ] but
it's pointless, bro. Cuz like, what's
the point of being alive to suffer?
I don't see the point.
You're never going to meet anyone.
You're never going to have a sex life.
You can't meet a normal woman. It just
seems to defeat the whole object of life.
You know what I'm saying?
So yeah, nothing gets better. Nothing changes.
People on the Reddit, People on Reddit's
been saying the same [ __ ] for years.
Nothing changes. Never has, never will.
I'm surprised I didn't go back to
Gamblin to be honest
cuz people do that when they're like
depressed and [ __ ]
But no, bro.
I'm pretty much just here waiting to die, you know.
Yeah, he will. Cuz he's not even my dog anyways.
He's not my dog anyways, but I just look
after him sometimes. Yeah.
Yeah. It doesn't matter if he loves me,
bro. This life is [ __ ] I'll never get
over 3 weeks ago. Never.
Never. There's no going back after that,
bro. There's no going back after that.
There's literally no going back. There's
nothing anyone can say, anyone can do.
There's nothing. I should have I should
have been with I should have had a date
by now with them 10 numbers. One of them
And I didn't. So Did I? That's it. Yeah. Nobody. Yep.
What was a wild night when I got the 10 numbers?
Oh, that night. Yeah. Never again. life, bro.
Yeah, of course they do. They've all got
boyfriends, don't they? Yeah.
Yeah, of course they do.
I only started brushing my teeth recently, but Yeah.
stocks in it. Another change. Never mind
Will never change.
I will never go out and try anything ever again.
These experiences. [ __ ] that. Yep.
I don't even message that account.
I just message another account.
I literally got [ __ ] all in them years
of trying really.
People on Reddit still tell you that you
don't know what the future holds.
What they say on Reddit that you're
going to meet someone Yeah. Anyways, I'm gone.