Oh man,
can't go to stop thinking about my bad
experiences with women. [ __ ] depressing
and [ __ ] what happened three weeks
ago as well. I can't get out my head, man.
Super super super depressing. Bre.
Yeah. [ __ ] hell. Oh dear. [Music] Yep.
[ __ ] none of those.
Reddit can do is [ __ ] ban people.
That's all they can do.
Yo, how are we doing, man? I'm just
[ __ ] depressed, bro. Really depressed.
Yeah, it's depressing, bro.
That's just sat here thinking about my bad experiences
and how I'm completely [ __ ]
It's bad, isn't it?
Really, really, really bad.
Uh, easy. I got three I went out three
weeks ago. I got 10 numbers and I got no
date. That is depressing as [ __ ] If
that isn't not enough to give up
forever, then I seriously don't know
what will. That is [ __ ] depressing.
This was that was three weeks ago as
well. That goes to show you'll never
meet anyone. So, I'm not sure why people
keep telling me that I will. You know,
that is [ __ ] depressing to be honest.
It makes you want to kill yourself.
Like, no [ __ ] bro. It has
then you go on Reddit and then they ban you.
Yeah, it's depressing, bro. Yeah.
Very, very depressing. Depressing life.
Yeah, it's depressing that
I have a lot of messaging to do on Reddit. Wow.
Depressing in it, bro.
I'm thinking the suicide, bro. I'm not
even joking. This is depressing as [ __ ]
I swear to God, man. I'm not even
joking. It is depressing. It'll never
change. [ __ ] depressing as [ __ ] It is.
It's [ __ ] depressing. Yep.
If I got 10 numbers and I didn't get one date on
didn't get one date, bro.
Well, people on Reddit will say that
I'll meet someone.
So they say, well,
they say a lot of things, don't they? on
Reddit. They say a lot of things.
They say a lot of things, bro.
A lot of things.
And year after year after year, it's the
same old [ __ ] No matter what you do,
what you try, it is so depressing. Oh my
god. If I could explain it into words,
how depressing it actually is.
And do you know the thing is you go on
Reddit, right, and you read what like
someone else has posted and then they're
telling them, "Oh, you need to go out
and approach women." Well,
funny you should say that. Um cuz I've
done that already. Then I then send them
my videos about the Makebelie boyfriends
and then the leading on and the [ __ ]
and the [ __ ] and the [ __ ] and
then they don't say much to that. So
they tell people to go and approach
people and then when people approach
people, oh you can't do that, you need
to go on the dating apps that don't work. [ __ ] idiots. Yep.
It's a load of [ __ ] mate. Yeah,
they say you're going to meet someone.
They say you're going to meet someone on
there a lot of things.
any more bad experiences.
I think that's a small thing, isn't it? You know,
it is so [ __ ] depressing, bro.
I hope I die in my [ __ ] sleep. This
is depressing to think about this [ __ ]
Really is so [ __ ] depressing. Yeah.
The person negative, toxic.
Same mode. Same mode. Same mode. Yeah.
Reddit bans people. Yeah.
I've got a bone to pick with you. Why
are you telling people to go out and approach women?
Then I show them my approaching videos
and the dating apps and stuff. Yeah,
that's what I show them.
will be me killing myself before long, mate.
To be honest, it's depressing.
It is [ __ ] depressing. It is. Really, really is. as [ __ ]
I still don't think you're going to meet someone.
Talk about delusional Okay. Yep. [ __ ] depressive. Sorry, bro.
There you go.