Okay.
My sleep in is absolute [ __ ]
Get that later.
Yeah, baby boys. Should
I leave my t-shirt on?
Yeah, might as well. It's a bit cold. Get down. Oh [ __ ]
There we go.
Yeah. Well, I would have won I would
have lost the football bet if I had done
it. So, good thing I didn't do it.
Yeah. Good thing I didn't do it. [ __ ]
So, let me resolve this microphone issue.
This ant man really needs to stop trying
to troll me, bro.
You know, I'm not [ __ ] naughty, man.
I'm not [ __ ] Timmy Alders. I know
what you're [ __ ] doing. What the [ __ ]
you sending me [ __ ] JMX for? Like
the guy's rich and he's got millions of
[ __ ] followers. I mean, good for him.
Like, I don't know why this guy's I see
what he's trying to do, bro. I need to
put him up about this. Like, you need to
really really stop cuz I'm not stupid. I
see what you're trying to do. You know,
stop trying to mock people.
That's what you're trying to do. Why you
sending me [ __ ] JMX?
What the [ __ ] man?
No, I was going to do a bet earlier, but
I didn't bother. I went to get
breakfast. I was supposed to do a
football bet, but I didn't bother.
I was going to do a treble boat score
draw, but yeah, I just didn't end up
doing it to August
and I would have lost anyways
again at some point.
Yeah, I'm next. Come anytime.
Bring your friends. Rice has was sending
me abuse earlier
to say that I'm a womanizer.
I said, "Stop it, Rice. Me and you are friends.
I'm Rice's friend. I'm not going to I'm
not going to say anything to Rice. He's my mate." So yeah,
Bryce is my friend.
You can you can have a timeout anyways, buddy. Yeah,
I was depressed [ __ ] earlier, man.
Just thinking of the women's situation, potato head.
It is [ __ ] depressing, isn't it?
Oh man, to use escorts all your life.
That is depressing.
That is [ __ ] depressing.
You'd have to use an eth school every
month for like eight months minimum.
At least 6 to 8 months before you even try again.
You can't try for like 6 to 8 months
minimum. If you are even thinking of trying again
seriously that long if not longer.
That's [ __ ] That is literally [ __ ] up, bro.
They're [ __ ] evil as well. They're
evil what they do.
That is So yeah, you'd have to get like
an escort twice a month or once a month
for like 6 months.
Like you I I don't think I'd ever try
here again, bro.
I feel like I've done what I've had to
do. I've tried enough times. I shouldn't
have to try again. I've tried and tried
and tried and tried and tried. I can't
deal with that lies. I can't deal with that [ __ ]
because me putting up with that is is is
lowering yourself worse than using an
escort. Putting up with their [ __ ] is is
somehow degrading yourself.
The mind games, the [ __ ] the lies,
their attitude. Who's dealing with all
of that, bro? No one wants to deal with
that [ __ ] Nah. You know what I mean? So,
and I'm still and I'm still meaning what
I'm saying that these they need to make
a law. The police need to make a law on
women complaining that they can't find
anyone. You know how they like have a
law against incelss and incelss and
people that hate women and
they need to make a law on women that
act like they can't find someone when
they can cuz that is causing me distress
when I'm reading that [ __ ] cuz only
women can find someone. They're just too picky. So yeah,
this school's all come and see me today. But
no, boss, but that's what it's going to be anyways.
That's what it's going to be forever.
That's the way it looks, isn't it?
Bad, is it? Really, really bad.
Really, really, really bad.
I was going to watch this incel thing
yesterday, but I fell asleep. Like I
said, even though I'm not a virgin and
I've been with people, I can relate to
them because of obviously the struggles. So,
it's really, really bad. Really, really
And that's why I don't gamble anymore,
bro. cuz I don't need that added stress
and the mood swings and stuff. My life's
hard enough, bro. I don't need
gambling in my life, you know.
So, it's why I probably to be honest with you. Yeah.
That personality thing is such [ __ ]
anything is such [ __ ]
But I was thinking at the same time give
something has really really really got to give.
You can't keep going around in circles
forever, bro. You know,
it's not good, man. It's not good.
Not good, bro.
Yeah, you have to get an escort every
month for 6 months.
8 months. 6 months. 8 months.
Cuz I could even try if I wanted to. And yeah,
because obviously for my my own mental
well-being, it wouldn't be a good idea
to go out and try. So yeah,
it's bad, bro. Really, really bad.
Like I said, maybe I'll try Belgium or
somewhere like that, some other country, Asia, cuz Yeah,
it's bad, isn't it?
I mean, let's just say that it is one
of, you know, the simple fact that
you've got a beard. That tells you all
you need to know about them that
somebody would reject somebody for
having a beard
or not having a beard. You know, it's
[ __ ] They're [ __ ] They really are You know,
they are, man. Hey,
I don't understand the point of this hole.
Reddit thing when they just ban people.
I just don't understand
if they just ban people and delete their accounts.
I don't know. Yeah.
But every time I've gone out and stuff
um every single time I've gone out going out
which makes it pointless going out again. You know,
yeah, I see what that um I see what that
Ant-Man's trying to do.
[ __ ] Why are you sending me JMX?
some guy that's got [ __ ] millions of followers
and good for him if he gets women, bro.
That's not I don't compare myself to
other people. I don't get jealous of
other people. I'm not like you. I don't
compare myself to other people because
I'm really going to lie on this guy when
I when I fix this microphone issue. It
doesn't it's not let me send voicemail
for some reason. I don't know why, but
I'm really going to lie down fix like I
don't compare myself to other people.
Somebody could have millions of pounds
and I wouldn't care. I don't get jealous of anybody.
Like I don't compare myself to other
people because it's a complete and utter
waste of time.
You know what I mean? I'm not I'm not like you.
Really? Really? I'm not like you.
When I used to go cinema and that, it
used to annoy me very rarely. But bro, I
don't compare myself to other people
because it's a complete and utter waste
of time. Who cares what Jim, Jack, and
how he's [ __ ] doing? You know,
there's going to be people that are
better than you, people that are worse
than you. Who gives a flying [ __ ]
Don't know why you're showing me [ __ ] JMX.
What the [ __ ] I don't know if you know
who that is. [ __ ] J, you know.
And you call me obsessed.
You differ, bro. I don't compare myself
to other people.
I can wonder why I'm not skin. I can
wonder why I'm not a millionaire. You
know, it's not going to [ __ ] change
my life. So,
it's it's so silly.
So, I don't know why he's trying to mock
people and it's so [ __ ] obvious cuz
he knows the situation.
He knows about getting the 10 numbers.
So, why are you like trying to mock
people? I don't understand.
You're obsessed with Morgan.
You need to get laid then my sloppy
seconds wouldn't matter to you. That's
not me reacting to you. out to me just
telling you straight that you're
obsessed with my sloppy seconds,
which is how we know you're a virgin
because the way you go on about sex, my
sloppy seconds. It's so clear you're a
virgin. You've never had it.
So obvious. So so obvious. And that's
not me reacting to you. That's me
telling you it's me stating fact.
You're obsessed with Morgan.
Somebody in a happy relationship that
has a sex life wouldn't care about women
that I've been with, you know,
I can't wait till my birthday about Fortnite's meal.
That would be lush.
I wish I done that slow and kitty
minister today though. I would have won.
I reckon I could win a football every
week for a month. I'm going to try at
some point. Start with 160 win. 160 win
and just keep doing it till I lose.
They very different opinions on Reddit.
in America that said they'd meet me if I
paid for them to come here. I go there,
but I'm not getting with a [ __ ] 19y
old. [ __ ] that.
I wouldn't even I don't think I'd even
[ __ ] a 19y old now, to be fair.
I don't know the average well
maybe 21 22
but yeah Virgin boy you're obsessed with
Morgan you're obsessed with Izzy
This is what makes me think. Well, it's
not what makes me think. It what makes
me know that you're a virgin is the way
you convince yourself that people
haven't slept with people and stuff
because in reality you haven't
slept with anyone.
No matter how many time you show the
wall, it doesn't prove you've had sex.
So that's a fun fact for you.
Well, I was going to do a football bet,
but I didn't. I was going to do a treble both scar
30 pound on it, but didn't bother to be honest.
Can't be bothered. Yeah.
Reddit would be so good, bro.
Yeah. Did Swindon come in? We see that.
Oh, no they didn't. They would have
lost. No, I'm just going to do this is
the team that you want to do every week.
Yeah. You want to do SL and you want to
do Kitty Minister?
That's the ones that you want to do.
Thank me later. Thank me later.
Literally next week do Kitty Minister
and do SL. It will win cuz I was going
to do a double today and I never I was
going to do a treble. I was going to add
Darlington, but they lost. But trust me,
it will win.
Yeah, bro. You need to do um
darling. You need to do um slow and um
FL and Kitty Minister.
Yeah, both teams to score. When I do it
again, I'm going to put 160 on it and
I'm going to do it every week until I lose.
The [ __ ] Reddit mods are power hungry.
Them Reddit mods are power hungry. Yeah.
But yeah, I don't know why this Ant-Man
is showing me damn X.
Stop trying to mock me, kid. I wasn't
born yesterday. I know what you're
trying to do. [ __ ] JMX.
Oh my [ __ ] god. This guy is obsessed
with comparing himself to other people.
I've never known anything like it. Like
you want to talk about people being
obsessed, right, with these videos where
people pretend they've got boyfriends.
Okay, I'll take my hat off to Okay, I'll
own it up. You
You [ __ ] keep comparing yourself and
me to other people.
It's [ __ ] annoying as [ __ ]
I don't get jealous of other people. It
doesn't bother me what other people do.
You are obsessed. You was the same when
you was back in England. Let's start
talking about what you're obsessed about
now. Nope. Even when you even when you
don't post anything, they still ban you.
They autoban you. They fear different
opinions. They need that power. Without
that power, they go [ __ ] mad
because no other website bans you.
YouTube don't really for for them
reasons. Instagram don't. Um, Snapchat
don't. It's only Reddit.
They're literally power hungry mods.
I don't know. They just autoban me. If I
If I make an account right now, which I
have and I message people, eventually
I'll get banned within like 3 hours.
They just autob me. Yeah, they do. Even
if I use a VPN.
No, he hasn't fell out with me, bro. He
just sent me some thing earlier of JMX.
He said, "Oh, do you remember JMX?" I
said, "Yeah, what about him?" And he
showed me him with his girlfriend. I
said, "I mean, the guy's got a million.
He's got millions of followers. The
guy's rich. The guy's not ugly. I mean,
what about him?" Yeah, I know who he is
from back in the day. Okay. And your
point is why are you show me?
I see what he's trying to do. He's
trying to mock me. And it's not it's not
going to work because I don't get
jealous of other people. I don't care. I
don't compare myself to other people.
He does. When he was back here, he does.
So, could you imagine he was actually
me? He would have ended up killing
himself. If he was actually me, bro.
Bear in mind, I've tried with Emily more
times than him, right?
And what used to annoy me, what used to
like annoy me about him yet is he
wouldn't try a lot of the time, yet it
would piss him off. I was like, how does
that even make sense? Like 3 weeks ago,
I got 10 numbers. I didn't even get a
date. I'm in my rights to be pissed off
and give up, you know? Like, I'm in my
rights to do that. There's nothing
anyone can say to me. What can someone
say to me? go out and try. Been there,
done it, worn a t-shirt, tried.
There's nothing anyone can say to me.
Whereas I can say to you, but when you
used to come out, when you used to go
out in England, you didn't even used to try,
you know, most of the time. So, you
don't really have
any room to complain. I [ __ ] do,
though. I got 10 numbers. I didn't even
get a date. I was supposed to meet
someone last Saturday. They're wasting my time.
That along with the fact I've been
trying for years and I've wasted enough
time and money on it, I'm in my rights to complain. So,
and as I was saying before you just
joined, I need to give up for like six
months minimum before even considering
trying again. I have to. I have to.
You literally have to, bro. But there's
Yeah, there's nothing else you can do now.
Yeah, bro. That is that Yeah.
So, when I was on my way to get
breakfast um earlier, I was thinking
that you either need to just use escorts
for the rest of your life or leave.
There's nothing else now. Like, we're
we're beyond everything else
because the same thing is going to keep
happening. And I know what you're
saying, oh, escorts are not the way. No,
no, no, no. But the thing is, going out
and getting led on is not the way. Here
and I've got a boyfriend a million times
is not the way. And it's just going to
keep happening and happening and
happening and happening and happening
and it's never ending.
It's never [ __ ] ending. It's the [ __ ]
they do as well, you know, even when
they give their number. It's literally
never ending, bro. Never ending. So
it comes to a point where like
something's got to give.
Something's really really really got to give, you know,
and then they say they go for
personality when they don't go for
personality unless you [ __ ] pass
their unrealistic threshold standards first.
It could be simple as you having a beard
as why somebody wouldn't go with you or
you not having a beard or one of your
eyebrows were bigger than the other.
That's how shallow they are. They try to
make it seem like they
they don't go for um No, it's not even
looks cuz even if you're good-looking,
they still won't even give you a chance.
They make it seem like
appearance isn't a thing for them. Yeah.
Even when you look matt and you can look
your best and do your best, they still
won't even give you a chance. But they
think that they they make it seem like,
oh no, appearance that don't matter.
I mean, that's what goes with everyone, you know.
Appearance is the first thing.
That's the very very first thing,
you know. So,
like I said, that woman trying to say
that she wouldn't get with me because
I'm not Muslim and I'm too old for her,
even though 23 and 28. I'm not dealing
with that [ __ ] no more. I'm not dealing
with their [ __ ] no more.
And the only time you're not going to
deal with this is probably when you're like 50.
Probably about 50 to be fair.
I think that's the only time potentially
the games would stop is when you're 50
years old. I'm not even joking. It's [ __ ] So,
I don't know, bro. What can you do?
But yeah, they need that power anyways.
Sleep state. They need that power. Them
mods need that power. It's like oxygen to them.
Without oxygen, you die. They need that
power. If they don't have that power,
mate, they go I I'm convinced these
Reddit mods are a bunch of um just like 40year-old virgins
that sit on Reddit all day,
you know, to feel powerful because
that's the only thing they have in their
life. Honestly, I I I I feel like that was
and I feel like a lot of people that
give advice don't have no life because
if you would actually go out and
approach women, you'd actually know what they're like.
Evil stuck up, play mind games, and
they're not any different. As much as
these people sleep state that these
women are different, every woman you
will come across will do the same thing.
But they're all different.
So, but yeah, they're not all the same.
They just managed to do and stay and act
the same way, every single one of them. So,
yeah. Well, if they didn't ban for
stupid reasons, people wouldn't [ __ ]
keep making accounts, man.
You know what I'm saying?
So yeah, if they didn't ban, sorry bro,
if they didn't ban for stupid reasons,
you wouldn't keep making [ __ ]
um so they are very very power hungry
because no other um
no other site bans for silly reasons
like that. No Instagram, no YouTube, no
nothing. They ban when you do something
really [ __ ] up. whereas Reddit will
just ban you for having a different opinion. So yeah,
but yeah, like I said, they need to make
a law on women complaining about men.
They are in no position
or and they have no right to complain about men.
I mean, not being able to find a man.
Yeah, I've seen it.
So, yeah, they're in no right to complain.
Hate it when you see women complain
about men. I hate it. I hate it, bro. If
only they knew the struggle.
Like, there was this one woman on Reddit
sleep state, right? And she was like,
"Oh, it's it's eating me alive that I'm 25
and I've never been in a relationship."
And and you're thinking to yourself,
"This is by choice. You're single by
choice. Why would something that you choose
be eating you alive?
So, you're choosing to be single, but
yet it's eating you alive. So, they're
habitatly seek out to mock people. This
is what I'm saying. Did you go out
approaching getting 10 numbers and not
even getting a date? I mean,
no, he wasn't. So, it's like they they
they it's that needs to be illegal. That
generally needs to be illegal. As
ridiculous as it sounds, you know, it does because
they are mocking. Trust me, there there
are people out there that are still
virgins that are my age. You know, they
can't. And it's not a choice.
You know, they can easily find a man.
They can easily get into a relationship.
They can easily get sex. um
for you to even be able to get just a
date, you need to go out looking your
best, doing your doing your best, spending hundreds,
and you wouldn't get a date for a very long time. So,
it's mad. And then you get these women that complain
Yeah. How they can complain about not
meeting someone when they've got all them options.
It's bad, is it?
There's women out there now that are
28-year-old virgins and they own it cuz
no one's good enough for them.
It's [ __ ] isn't it?
It really, really, really is [ __ ] up. Yeah,
I wouldn't even mind if they And it's
like women that say I don't owe you
anything. It's so ick. It's so eh like I
was speaking to this woman on Reddit
earlier before I fell asleep and I was
showing her like my WhatsApp combos
and bear in mind she was talking to me
and then she's like I said, "Oh, you
didn't read anything I sent you." She's
like, "I I don't owe it to you to read
them." I was like, "Huh? You're
messaging me. We're talking. I'm showing
you my struggles and you're telling me
that you don't owe me." It's like it's
such a lame attempt to cover up when
women do wrong that I don't owe you
[ __ ] It It's like literally trying to
sugarcoat every single time a woman does
wrong. Has anyone else noticed that?
Like you don't owe me anything, yet
you're sat there typing away to me over
and over and over and over and over
again. Why are you still here? But yet
when I send you messages, you don't want
to read them, [ __ ] [ __ ]
Same old boring e.
That is so ick.
Oh, I had a chicken biryani.
I got some left, so I'll heat up in the
microwave when I'm um when I'm uh ready
to eat some more.
But that I don't owe you anything is so
ick. It's so ick.
It's just so It's just like used to
cover up their shitty behavior and it's
so used in the wrong context. Like
it's like they they they say it every
single time they do wrong. It's madness.
We live in such a sexist
world, bro. Such a um
double standard [ __ ] world. E
cuz they use it in the wrong context.
When a woman does bad, they cover it up
saying that they don't owe anyone
anything. But that's not how that works.
That's not used in the right context. Cuz
could you imagine you going around,
right, being a [ __ ] to people being like,
"Don't know you nothing. Don't know you
anything. Let's see how many people
would agree with you. It's [ __ ] ridiculous, bro.
And they only use it for women as well.
They only use it um when a woman does wrong.
You know, double standards. Double
I was supposed to be
like sleep state. I don't mind. show my
um WhatsApp messages
and showing the [ __ ] I've been through,
but it'd be a waste of time because it
won't suit anyone.
They just resort to making stuff up and
dismissing it anyways. There's no point me. I mean,
I've got some messages here.
I messaged nine numbers.
Hi, it was nice meeting you last night.
How's the hangover? How's your day
going? I switched up between 10 numbers
and only one number replied. Imagine that.
Oh, that's bad. it.
But somehow people still think that
you're going to meet someone.
Wow. They're very optimistic.
I mean, how many more bad experiences do
you need to keep having
before people say, "Yeah, I don't think
you're going to meet anyone." I mean,
like, how many more bad experiences
really do you need to keep having?
Obviously just throwing that out there, you know. So yeah,
they say go on dating apps on Reddit. Steven Howard,
they call it a hookup culture.
You know, when you get into any kind of
debates about this, right,
you're just going to be like the boy who
cried wolf. That's all you're going to
do. You're just going to end up feeling
like the boy who cried wolf.
I don't know if you ever known the
riddle, the boy who cried wolf.
Look, no matter what you do, no matter
what you say, it gets ignored or
dismissed because it doesn't suit anyone.
So, you've already lost before you even
open your mouth because whatever you say
um or show them, they will just dismiss it
and carry on as if you didn't show them anything.
It's [ __ ] up, is it? Yeah, we
had a nice breakfast this morning.
No, [ __ ] off.
[ __ ] off, Rice. I had your [ __ ] abuse this morning. No link. No,
we're speaking to this transgender in
Glasgow. Stephen Howard, we've been
speaking for ages. She says, "Oh, you
should come and move in with me."
Yeah, it's funny though. woman abuser.
I'm a woman abuser. Why? Because I state
facts and I don't lick their ass. I
mean, I've got backup to to show what
they've done to me over the years.
So, if you are going to call somebody a
woman abuser, right, you might want to
actually have evidence to back it up
like what I've got. I've got [ __ ] what
they've done to me over the years.
It's never ending, you know? So
yeah, I can't keep a woman. Whatever you
say, white knight,
are you the one that had to date a 50
year old woman or was she 60?
Rice, come on now. You're the one that
had to get with a 50y old woman. So you
should actually be telling yourself that, you know.
and Kaylee. Well, she's um well,
yeah, we won't get into that. But
Rice, you was with a woman in her 60s.
She was probably older than my [ __ ] mother.
Like, imagine that in a in her 60s for
[ __ ] sake. And you want to talk about people like
you had to get with a woman in her 60s, bro.
I wouldn't even get with a woman in her
[ __ ] 50s. Are you [ __ ] My mom's
[ __ ] in her 60s.
That is [ __ ] vile, bro. Vile.
So why am I a woman abuser? Why? Cuz I
state facts and I defend myself.
Come on, Rice. Why? Why? Because I defend myself.
And I show all the bad things they do.
Sorry it don't st you, bro.
Sorry it don't st you.
You can't even keep relation for two
seconds and cry on social media how
women are treating you. Well, no. I'm
just stating how they're [ __ ] I'm in
my right to complain. I have every right
to complain cuz I'm not I I'm not a
white man. I say it how I see it.
They're evil. They're stuck up. They
lead people on and I've got evidence to
prove what they've done. Is that right, Candy Man? You know,
you know what I'm saying, Russ?
I'm not even going to insult you. I
can't be bothered.
Rice, you're saying that I'm not attractive.
I mean, whether I'm attractive or not. I
mean, bro, have you seen yourself? Come on.
I'm not even going to start insulting
you, but you're you're going to try and
tell me I'm not attractive.
Oh, Jesus Christ, bro. You got run out
of three areas. You let your windows get
smashed and you done absolutely nothing.
What kind of man are you?
You know, you you got beat up by [ __ ] Monty.
Yeah, you've literally, bro, you've took
more L's than me, and that's saying
something. But I've actually took some
W's as well.
Like you've got run out of Okay, listen.
Listen. What was you about in Scotland,
right? And these people are going at
you. Do you think that could ever happen
to me? Do you think that could ever ever
ever happen to me, bro? Come on, Bryce.
It's ridiculous. You had to get escorted
by the police.
Do you know what I'm saying? You you had
to get escorted by police.
You didn't even stand your ground. You know,
I stood my ground before. There was this guy.
There was this guy, right? And he uh
approached one of the tenants. He
thought it was me, some gay guy with a
kid. He had a couple of kids. Must have
been from a woman he had been with. And
I was living there at the And then when
I went back there, I said, "Who the [ __ ]
do you think you're [ __ ] recording?
You've been here." Even though he didn't
record before me, I said, "You've been
here 2 seconds. We've been here years.
Don't think you're going to start trying
to [ __ ] record people." Yeah. He was
a big [ __ ] as well. And I told him,
"Come on." And I said, "Try and record
me." And I slapped that camera out your [ __ ] hand.
And ever since then, he was all right
with me. He moved out, but that was And
it wasn't even me. He was recording. It
was one of the tenants, but the guy
looked like me, so he's stupid. So when
I see him, I said, "What the [ __ ] do you
think you're doing?"
I wasn't in drunk mode to be fair. But
right, you're a laughing stock. You got
[ __ ] run out of three areas, bro.
And you're going to come on here and try
and criticize me.
And if I [ __ ] met you that day,
Kay would have been leaving you for me.
Katie would pick me over you any day. So yeah, yeah.
I know lick women's ass is rice. I say
it how I see it.
You know what I mean? Handy man,
what am I supposed to think?
What am I supposed to really think? H Andy man,
after getting 10 numbers and only one
replying and leading you on and being
led on in the past, what is someone
supposed to think?
Do you understand that all women aren't
the same? Well, I mean, that's just
illusional at this point. See what I'm
saying? What what what do they expect
someone to think?
Go on, Candy. Man, tell me what is
someone supposed to think?
I'm all for constructive criticism.
People don't get banned.
Only haters get banned.
What am I supposed to think? What kind
man? Just just think of it for my
for my uh position, right?
What am I supposed to do? Go out every
week, spend hundreds, getting nowhere,
getting [ __ ] getting made to feel
ugly when I'm not? Even though Charles
say I'm not. It's not a solution. It's
not a solution anymore.
It's not the answer. So what am I
supposed to do?
Listen to a bunch of white knights
saying that all women aren't the same.
Yet them keep proving that they are the same.
Do you understand what I'm saying? Like
we we get anyone to say anything, bro.
All of these white knights saying, "Oh,
you don't know women. They're not all
the same." Yeah. Every single one you
will come across will be exactly the same.
So what? You know what I'm saying?
Leading on people for their own entertainment.
I said something as a joke um
earlier to this transgender on Reddit
and I said, "Oh, I want to go out and
beat a woman up for all of the bad
experiences I've had." She told me that
I was sick and I'm well. I said, "Okay,
but what about all of these women that
have led me on for their entertainment
and all the bad experiences I've had?
You don't see that as kind of sick? It
might not be as sick, but it is still
very much sick what they've done because
I mean it's sick. Obviously, I didn't
mean it. I just said it, but just punch
someone. But so that's not thick what they do. So yeah, they literally
It's not even like they you approach
someone and they say, "Oh, I've got a
boyfriend or I'm not interested." They
literally lead people on. They literally
lead people on and and do stuff to make
people feel like [ __ ] Cuz think of it,
Candy, man, what's the problem? I would
say, right, I'm conventionally above
average looking when I try. Can we agree
on that? Let's say 6.57. Let's just say
for argument sake 6.57,
right? So, shouldn't I be passing the physical attraction threshold?
No. To even be given a chance. I'm not
perfect. I'm not a model by any means,
but you would say that you you look
pretty good. No.
Whatever. You know,
so what's the problem?
You understand? What's the [ __ ] problem, bro?
You You understand what I'm saying?
Oh, this Rice was giving me abuse trying
to say that how I can't hold a woman. I
can't keep a woman. And I then said to
him, "Mate, you have to get with a 60
odd year old. Don't try and tell me
about people that keep women that can't
keep women." Because, mate, my mom is in
her 60s. And I don't think I'd ever get
with a woman in her 60s, mate. If that
even if that was my only option in the
[ __ ] world, that is [ __ ] insane, bro.
Uh just sick of women. I was going to do
a football m earlier, but I didn't
bother. I was going to do a treble uh
both scar no draw,
but only one boat, no draw. So
these women are so full of [ __ ] Joe, I
was speaking to this woman on Reddit,
right? and she was saying, "Oh, I can't
get with you cuz you're 28 and I'm 23
and you're not a Muslim." All the
excuses in the world. And then I went on
her post, obviously a hypothetical
example, right? Cuz I don't know what
they look like. They don't even live in
England. Then I go on their profile and
they said they've been with a
28-year-old before. And I'm thinking,
"What the fuck?" Like anybody would
actually think that you're some fat ugly bastard
and you're not like a six, seven out of 10. Like it's
nah. This is this is crazy, bro.
These women's standards are completely
completely unrealistic. And Joe, I was
on Reddit uh yesterday
and obviously I'm on Reddit every
[ __ ] day and this woman said that
it's eating her alive that she's 25 and
she's never been in a relationship.
I said, "Huh? It it's eating you alive.
It's eating you alive. The fact that
you've not chose to be in a relationship
for 25 years of your life." Yes. By
choice. That's eating you alive. Really?
How about going up and down the country
approaching [ __ ] thousands of [ __ ]
men and getting the same old [ __ ] for
years? Let's see how you think then. Huh? [ __ ] bullshitters.
They're [ __ ] absolute liars, bro. You
know, they they need to make a law, Joe,
on women complaining that they can't
find men. They need to make that illegal
just like they make hating women
illegal, hate crimes, where they need to
put a stop to that because it is
mocking. That is mocking someone. There
is not one woman out there, unless she's
completely fat and stinking that can't
find a man. I mean, even then, they
probably could still find a man. So, do
you not understand how that is offensive
when I'm reading that? You know,
stop moaning. If you don't want a
relationship, say you don't want a
relationship. Don't say you can't find
someone, right? Because you can
you can find someone. Any woman can find
someone. Stop mocking people. It's
mocking any it is it is generally [ __ ] mocking, you know.
No, they are lying to me, you know. And
then they're trying to say about they
wouldn't get with me cuz I'm not Muslim.
It's all [ __ ] and it's all lies.
You know, I can understand if somebody
gives you a chance and they didn't like
your personality, but bro, I should be
very much meeting these people's
standards lookswise threshold.
I should very much be meeting it, you
know, but that's it.
Well, they must be able to find someone
worth it. Surely to God out of all of
them options they have and they can't
find someone that's worth it. There's no
way. There's no way. Yeah, they might
have they might have to deal with like a
bunch of they might have to deal with a
bunch of creeps and you know, but there
are surely men that are worth it that
they could get with. I'm sure they're
[ __ ] well with the amount of options
they have. Use me as an example, right?
They somebody wouldn't give me a chance
for maybe because I've got a beard or
maybe because one eyebrow is bigger than
the other, maybe because my ear was
lighter than the other ear, something so
shallow and materialistic. They they
seem to think that appearance doesn't
matter to these women. But the fact of
the matter is is even if somebody is
good-look or they look good enough or
they just look normal, that is not
enough for them. They wouldn't even give
that person a chance. Yeah. They're the
one they are more shallow than men.
Yeah. They try to make it seem like we
don't go for looks. We don't go
appearance doesn't matter. It it's more
than appearance because even if you look
good, they will find you wouldn't you
will not meet their standard threshold.
Simple. So they wouldn't even entertain
you. That's how it is. They they they
seem to like to lie and say, "Oh, now
I'm hearing that's that doesn't mean
anything." But it does,
you know, cuz I I can be a six out of
10, a seven out of 10 when I try. I
dress good. I smell good.
No, not at all. Because I wouldn't
reject No, no, no. Okay. I wouldn't
reject somebody because they don't have
big boobs. That's the difference.
And No, no, no. But that's where you're
wrong though because I have I have
bothered with women that are flatchested.
I am bob I have bothered with women that
are flat chested. I don't exclude myself
to that preference. That's the
difference. They exclude their self to
that to that preference. So no, not not
even not even. So yeah,
I have been with a woman that's got smaller boobs.
There's a woman in America. She said,
"Oh, she'd meet me if I pay for her to
come here or I go there." I'm not
getting with her cuz she's 19. That's
not an excuse. I wouldn't get with
anyone that's 19.
To be honest,
I mean, they can still have sex with
you. They could still [ __ ] you. You know
what I'm saying? Like, so it doesn't
make sense. It doesn't make any sense.
You know, you are I am above average
looking when I try. I shouldn't be struggling.
This obviously there are people that are
not going to like you.
Okay. And and and and you know, like I
said in my video, as an exception, there
could be like a woman that only likes
goth men that looks like a goth or you
know, there is times when that happens,
but you shouldn't be struggling the way
that you're struggling. There's nothing
wrong with the way that you look. That's
just put it as that way. like, you know, so
I mean, I've been with women that
haven't haven't had big tits.
And even if that's the case, Joe, we're
not denying it. Women are denying it.
Women are denying it. How can someone
look good, dress good, smell good, and
someone not even give them a chance?
So women are the ones that are more
picky and more shallow, but they're
being made to feel like ah appearance,
you know, go for appearance. So yeah,
and I was trying to think like
something's got to give here when I come
back though. So I feel like I'm just
going to have to I just have to use
escorts for like 6 months.
six to eight months I reckon
cuz I can't go out and try anymore
because of my whole because of my mental
wellbe I won't be able to do it and
that's the thing we haven't even lost
confidence we've lost hope we've lost
hope and we've been discouraged so yeah
we've lost hope and um
and we're discourage
That's it. I don't think we've lost
confidence. And you know, it's not about
that. Even though they do make they do
try to make people feel like they're ugly,
you know, when there's nothing wrong
with the way that you look, they're just
they've just got unrealistic [ __ ] expectations.
It is bad. It is really really bad.
Really, really bad.
cuz you should be finding some people
that are giving you a chance.
But even out of 10 of the numbers, if
even two people gave you a chance, then uh whatever. But
I don't know, bro. What what what
the solution is to be honest with you.
I don't know. Very odd.
Today this woman on Reddit, she said,
"Oh, oh, you're above average looking.
You look good." She's 19. She said she
never had a boyfriend. I I said to her
as an example, "Oh, even though I
wouldn't get her, I was like, "Oh, why
don't we go on a date?" She lives in
Brighton, by the way. Why not? Even
though I wouldn't actually do it because
you're 19, but I like you're 19. You
says that I'm You said that I'm above
average looking. You said you've never
had a boyfriend, so let's meet. Why not?
Not not straight away. They weren't
interested in that. But then then they will
sit there and say how they can't find a boyfriend.
So do you not understand the problem with that? So, that, bro?
No, I mean, when I come back,
you need to give up for at least 6
months. At least 6 months. See, the
thing is, you don't understand, bro.
I've got money. I've got money. I can
afford to go out every week if I want
to, you know, and even if I want money,
I still wouldn't go out.
Yeah. They don't give you a chance to
get to know them if if you're not their
type, Bob. If you're not their type,
they don't even give you a chance.
And I don't think I'm anyone's type in this country.
So, like I was saying before, I think I
need to go somewhere like Belgium or
maybe the Netherlands or some sort of
other country cuz I'm obviously no one's
type in this country even though I'm not
[ __ ] ugly. But who knows, you know?
Yeah, cuz I'm not living there.
I reckon if I lived in another country
for as long as I have here, I don't
think I would have I think I would have met someone.
Even like Belgium or something. I don't
know. I don't know.
Am I off out tonight? Um
well, considering the last time I went
out was three weeks ago and I got 10
numbers, I only got one reply and I spent £600. Probably not.
No. Probably not. No.
I won't be out for a very very very long
time after that. That is depressing as [ __ ]
I don't even drink anymore. I've come to
realize I don't even like drinking that
much. So, I can live without alcohol. It
doesn't it doesn't bother me, you know? Whatever.
You go out, you hear I've got a
boyfriend, you hear I'm not interested,
you get numbers, you get led on. The end.
The end. That's literally all that ever
happens. Literally all that ever
There's literally no point.
And Ant-Man's trying to mock me as well.
I need to pull him up about that when I
um fix this mic um phone issue out. I
see what he's trying to do. And he needs
to understand that I'm not like Monty.
I'm not like Timmy. I know what you're
trying to do.
You are obsessed with other people. You
are obsessed with comparing yourself to
other people. I'm not. I don't care if
someone's richer than me, poorer than
me, gets more women than me. Um, at the
end of the day, he was showing me this
JMX guy. I said, "Yeah, the guy's got a
girlfriend. He's got over a million
followers. The guy's rich. Okay. I'm not
jealous of anyone. I don't compare
myself to other people. So, you're not
going to be able to troll somebody
that's got a higher IQ than you. And
it's so obvious what he's doing. Cuz me,
I don't compare myself to other people.
I don't care what other people do.
I don't compare myself to strangers cuz
it's a waste of my time
cuz they're not me, I'm not them, and my
experiences will never be theirs. So, I
just see it as when he used to compare himself Um,
I I never used to get it. And the fact
that he never tried anywhere nowhere
near as me, but then he would still
complain, which doesn't make any sense.
Reckon you should try again?
Okay, you tell me why I should try again.
You need to really sell this to me. So,
I got 10 numbers. I only got one reply.
They were supposed to meet me. They
never. I spent £600.
You really have to tell me why I should
go out and try again.
And the last week before that was the
same. The week before that was the same.
You really need to sell me and convince
me how the next time going to be
different. If you can do that, I'll go out.
Nope. You're not. Nope. You're not
selling. I'm not buying it. Nope.
I will never go out again. I don't think
after that. That is that is [ __ ]
depressing. If I got a date, if I got a
if I got [ __ ] a date,
no, no, no, no, no, no. But it's not
possible because everyone's got
different experiences. So you comparing
yourself to another person doesn't mean
it's possible. Everyone's got different experiences.
And that guy's got millions of followers
and he's rich, which is probably not
possible to I mean, it's not even
possible to make money on YouTube anymore.
So, it's very much not possible for me.
I think we've established that. So, and
you can't even make money from YouTube
nowadays. Trust me. I had when I had
that main channel, I was nowhere near um
eligible to make any kind of money from YouTube.
So comparing yourself to people that got
lucky, it's not going to change your
situation. It's a waste of time. It's a
complete and utter waste of time. And
you're saying about how you know you're
sick of the boyfriend [ __ ] hearing me
sending the videos. I'm sick of you
comparing me to other people. I'm sick
of being compared to other people. It's
a complete and utter waste of my time. So,
I'm Bro, I've not been out for almost a
month. I'm not going out on my birthday.
Why am I being so extreme? Because I got
10 numbers and I didn't even get a date
and I spent £600.
I don't think I'm going to be going out
for a very, very, very, very long time.
I mean, it's been almost a month. I've
had the money. I have money. You understand?
So, yeah. compare me to other people,
it's a weak argument because just
because other people met someone, it
doesn't mean you are. Everyone is
different. You are not them. You've had
bad experiences with women and you will
keep having bad experiences with them.
No one else is going to change that.
Someone that's in a worse position than
you or or a better position than you.
Maybe not. I mean, I've not been out for
a month almost and I've got plenty of money.
I can go out anytime I want. So,
yeah. No, I won't be going out. I I I I
can't justify going out.
I can't justify it. But yeah,
I can't find the motivation, the desire
to want to go out and try again after
getting 10 numbers and not even getting
a date. There's no one there's nothing
anyone can say.
There's literally nothing anybody can
say to that, you know.
So, no, I don't think I will be. I
really don't think I will be
already tried internet dating doesn't work.
Yeah, but the reason why I don't want to
go out again is because of the numbers.
Because if you can look your best, do
your best and get their numbers and not
get and not even be given a chance, it's not exactly
motivating, is it? I mean, come on. It's
not exactly motivating, you know,
and I'm not torture I'm not torturing
myself. It's the truth. So, nah,
I have no reason to go out. No one's
interested in this country. So why would
I want to go out and torture myself?
So I mean, how are you going to try and
tell me the next time I go is go out is
going to be different? Okay, let's let's
okay, let's let's think about this,
right? You've been trying for four or
five years and it has been the same [ __ ]
for four or five years. Your past has
been predicting the future for four or
five years. Can you meet someone? Yeah,
but you got more chance of winning the
lottery twice in a row. And I've never
done the lottery because if it was
anything short of lottery odds, you
would have already met someone. I mean,
we've tried more than anyone in the
world. We've been up and down the
country. We've been to Scotland. We've
been to Wales. Yet, we're still we're
still in this situation. We're still
having this problem. So it's it seems to
me that it will continuously keep happening
and it has been for four or five years.
So that's that.
No one's type. You don't need to go out.
You You know the answer. So,
you know what? It's You know, it's
always going to be the same here. You know?
>> Yeah. I mean, you say that the past don't u
predict the future, but it's been
predicting it for 5 years.
It's been predicting it for 5 years. Yeah.
I haven't had sex with somebody for 2
years that wasn't in ES school. Well,
without paying about 2 years. How many
times have have I gone out in two years? So
go out looking for a one night sand. Oh bro,
you guys really don't have a brain, do you?
So it's not wrong.
So I haven't had sex for like 2 years
with someone that weren't um an escort.
I mean that's Somalian but that was you
know that doesn't really count.
I I haven't had Okay. Right. Let me let
me give you a summary. Right. I've been
up and down the country
for years and I've been with about four
women and I've approached about 8,000 women.
Does that seem worth it to you?
I mean, could you imagine a woman,
right? Okay. Okay. Let's just say a
woman has been with three, four
different people. She's not had to
travel up and down the country. She's
not approached 8,000 men.
So, you really see that as worth it.
going out, approaching 8,000 people,
spending all that money, dealing with
their [ __ ] I mean, there was times
I never got anything. I remember when I
went to leads before and I didn't get
even a kiss.
Look, and there's and there's been a few
times I mean, I've been to Manchester 10
times and I've only been laid once. So,
you know, but there there's no leadup to
anything. I haven't had a date since
April. So, what you're saying doesn't
even make any sense. It's not being an
It's not being extreme. I have not had a
date since April and I have been trying
lots since April. So, there's been no
lead up to anything. So, what you're
saying don't make sense. What you're
saying does not make no sense.
What you're saying doesn't make any sense.
It really does not make no sense because
I mean I should have a date.
I should have had a date out of them 10 numbers,
you know. No, I thought I'm using it as
an example. No, I'm using it as an
I'm using it as an example. So,
so you think it's worth it then? Yeah,
it's not facts. It's Okay. Okay. So, why
don't Okay. So, why have I not get got a
date out of any of them 10 numbers? I
was supposed to meet somebody last week.
They come out with a [ __ ] excuse.
Okay. Okay. So, why have I not had a
date since April? Go on.
Why have I not had um you know,
why have I not had a date since April? Go on.
Go on. Then
why haven't I got a date out of any of
them 10 numbers?
I mean, one replied, one agreed to meet me.
So, what you want me to go out every
week spending $400
just to be in with a chance of meeting someone? Really?
Really, bro? Come on. Um, well,
the fact that I looked my best, I tried
my best, I was confident. I mean,
surely you would have got a date out of
all of them women that I approached. If
I didn't even get a date, why would I
bother trying again? I looked my best,
done my best, was confident as well, got
10 numbers, approached about 30 women.
So, you want me to keep going out every
week? it and dealing with their [ __ ]
until I find someone. I'm not doing it.
I'm 28, bro, not 18. I'm not dealing
with their [ __ ] anymore. I'm an adult.
I'm not dealing with their silly little
shitty games, you know, just
spending3400 every [ __ ] week, you know?
It's some [ __ ] madness. I'm not doing that.
I am not [ __ ] doing that.
Yeah, I must have said something wrong.
I mean, I can show you the screenshots
if you want.
I mean, I can set I can literally show
every single one of my messages, you know?
I mean, I mean, I've explained to you
how it's not me, but you you keep
dismissing everything I show you and
tell you. So,
I mean, I I I can show you combos and
make you go smacked, but it won't suit
you. Okay, I'll give you an example.
I'll give you the last woman that I spoke to, right?
No hidden gems here.
There's no hidden gems here. So, you
need to point out exactly what I done wrong.
Okay, here we go. This was the last one,
so it was September. Okay. Hey, was
lovely meeting you last night. How's
your day going?
Hey, nice meeting you, too. Day is going
okay. How's your weekend? Glad to hear
my weekend is going good. Just had a
roast dinner and now chilling. Waited a
couple of days.
Hey, I'm going to Liverpool Street on
Saturday. Let's meet up. Question mark.
Didn't reply. Put a question mark. 3 days. Um,
right. Listen, hear me out. Hear me out.
One second. One second. One second. Question mark.
Then they were like, "Hey, sorry. Been
tied up with uni. Let me know next time
you're around the area. Smiley face.
I'm going to come back on Saturday at
7:00 p.m. Let's meet then. Because at
this point, J's like, "Okay, I might
have got 10 numbers and you know, I
didn't get a date and I spent £600, but
I want the money back and this is a new
week and surely to god this woman's
going to be different, eh?" Right. Yeah.
So, I said, "Oh, there's a Weather
Spoons pub next to Liverpool Street
Station. Let's meet there."
didn't reply. I said, "Is that fine?"
Didn't reply. Messaged them a day
before. "Hi, are we still good for
meeting tomorrow at 7:00 p.m.?"
They replied back saying, "Hey, sorry.
I've been sick the past few days. Need a
rain check on tomorrow."
Now, from what I'm reading here,
this person has agreed to meet.
I mean, they've agreed to meet.
I mean, they've agreed to meet me.
So, what have I done wrong? What? So, it
was a boring chat. I mean, I can show
you loads and loads and loads and loads
of different messages throughout my
whole phone book, and you're going to
run out of excuses cuz an excuse you
have for one, you're not going to have
for the other.
And this is where your argument will
come to an end. That's if you don't
dismiss my struggles, which you probably
will do because it won't suit you. So, I
mean, I've got loads of different examples.
So many different ones. I can Let me get
some up here actually.
What? That was a message, right? And
there's no hidden gems.
So, I can I can get some more up,
right? Here we go.
This was an American. Funny enough, I
approached Oh, [ __ ] Um,
I approached this woman and she uh
she um, this is when Charles messaged
me. So, I remember this one. Hi.
Hi. It was lovely meeting you earlier.
Did you get to where you need to go? Fine.
Hey, I'm going around Lester Square
later. I'd love to show you around. I'm
sorry. I'm not interested. Thanks for the opera.
Strange. Here's another one. Hi, it was
nice meeting you yesterday. How's your
day going? Hey, Peter. Yes, really.
Thank you for your approach. You h Did
you have a great evening? It is good.
And I went to Notting Hill and now I am
walking. And yours? No problem at all. I
just thought you look nice, so I had to
come over and talk to you. I've just
come back from a walk and to get some
food. Where did you end up going in the
in the last in the last night? Anywhere
nice? And um
I didn't hear from her again.
Here's another example.
I said, "Oh yeah, this is another one."
"Oh yeah, I thought you look nice, so
it's a win-win." Haha, cute. It's hard
work out there in the world, ain't it? I
said, "Yeah, what kind of guy do you
usually go for then? I'm guessing I'm
not your usual type." Um
uh she said, "Haha, tall, dark, and
handsome. I don't really have a type.
Just someone funny and has their [ __ ]
together. What about you? I said, "Haha,
would you cast me as dark and handsome
and same? I don't really have a type.
Just someone who has a nice personality,
looks nice, someone who's loyal and up
for trying all sorts of different
things." Then they wrote, "Haha, I
would. Yeah, personality first, right?
What's next on your new things to your
things to try list?" And I said, "Oh,
thanks. Well, there's a few countries I
want to visit and foods I need to try.
What's your favorite food
and never heard from them again?
Here's another one. Hey, it was lovely
meeting you last night. How's the hangover?
This is where you say they go for
personality. Hey, hangover is not good.
Was nice meeting you, too. But I just want to
I just want to be honest and say that
I'm not looking to date or anything
right now. Hope you had a good night.
So you can see where your argument is
coming to an end here, right? Because
these are all different examples. Um yeah.
Hey, it was lovely talking to you last
night. Shame I had to jump on the bus
and we couldn't finish our chat. Did you
get home? Okay.
She She said, "I did, thanks.
I mean, you're calling me boring
and I need to come on more interesting
yet they've got no enthusiasm in them."
I said, "That's good. Any plans for
today?" Never replied.
uh another one that I arranged to meet um and
she said we arranged to meet she said
Snowy let's cancel I don't I don't have
the capacity for drinks dating right now
let's explore this in the new year ID
then wrote laughing emoji
so you can see where
you can see where your argument is
coming to an here with all of these different examples.
You're going to laugh at this one, right?
Oh, they're such piss takers. I said, we
could get a coffee or something to eat. Um,
we could get coffee or something to eat.
What do you think? I said, yeah, that
sounds nice. Or if you drink, we could
get some cocktails. She said, yeah,
that's okay. Where were you thinking? I
said, "Yeah, let's go for some drinks."
Look at the next thing she writes. I
just wanted to mention this in case it's
not what you're looking for. I would be
only in London until September, so I'm
not looking for a long-term thing, but
I'm not really interested in anything physical.
And I'm thinking, huh?
What are you talking about? It took me
like 5 minutes to to think. So, you're
not interested in a relationship and
you're not interested in anything physical.
So, what the [ __ ] would you [ __ ]
want? [ __ ] sake. It's it's one of the
[ __ ] other. So, I've been dealing
with their [ __ ] and their trolling and
their piss taken for many, many years,
you know? I I don't mind putting the
combos out there and showing everything.
No, no hidden gems, no nothing.
It very much is them by what these
conversations are showing
because they don't even give people a
chance. This is what these messages are showing.
Pure leading on is taken. Um it is them.
It really really is them, you know. And
and I'll say it until I'm blue in the
face and I'll prove it as well, you
know. It's it is them. It is these
women. 1 million fucking%. Even if I was
wrong in some of them, whatever.
But I'm not wrong in all of them. And
I'm I'm more than happy to put the
combos up. I'll do a whole folder on it.
So, this is the [ __ ] that I've been
dealing with for many, many, many years
with these women. Many, many, many
years. And I'm not repeating it.
So, that's it.
They are obviously
they are obviously taking a piss, Joe.
Of course it's them. Of course it's
[ __ ] them, bro. Why Why do they agree
to meet someone and then suddenly back out?
Um PJ, do you say you say you've been in relation? [Music]
I've been in a relationship once. I mean,
did you not take into account anything
that I have just said?
Cuz again, you seem to dismiss everything.
I know they're taking a piss. I know it's them. Um,
no. Never. I have never agreed to go on
a date with a woman and then backed out.
Never in my life of 28 years. No, I
haven't. No, I haven't.
Because how can you change your mind
that quickly? It's not an excuse, you
know? It's it's it's not an excuse.
You've agreed to go on a date with
someone and you've suddenly backed out.
There's no excuse for it, you know? So,
it doesn't matter who I've been in a relationship with.
I mean, what about the easy jet flight? So,
these women all agree to go on a date,
yet they suddenly back out. Okay, I've
got one. Okay, I've got one. Hi, it was
lovely meeting and chatting to you last
night. Sorry I couldn't stay longer. I
had to go back to the tenants. Um,
let's meet Saturday 5:00 p.m. Hey,
sounds good. So, they've agreed to it.
So, I was like, "Oh, we're still good
for today 5:00 p.m. Hey, I'm so sorry.
Something came up." I said, "What's up?
So, where can we meet?"
Honestly, I had a great time with you
the other night, but I want to be
upfront with you. After some thinking,
I've decided to give things another try
with my ex, and I don't think it would
be fair for us to see each other while
I'm figuring this out. I think you're a
very kind person. I hope you understand.
Sorry for any confusion.
So, on the day you was just about to
meet me again,
you're going to give your ex another
try. Yet, you in England Um,
I mean, what's the chances that you're
you haven't done that on purpose?
I mean, it's obviously done on purpose
because if you really felt that way
about your ex, you would have gave your
number and agreed to meet.
So, all of this stuff is done on purpose.
This is the worst one as well. um with
this Australian one as well. Uh
hey uh sorry today's been hectic. This
was the teacher by the way. Hectic.
Unfortunately I've got plans this
Thursday. My mom's arriving from Australia
and I said I sent her a voicemail. I
said hello. She's like hey uh I know it
might seem like I'm making excuses but
I've got plans with my fan for the next
few days again leading me on. This is
the point of what I was saying. I said,
"No, it's fine. Do you honestly want to
meet It's fine. Honestly, do you want to
do a day next week?" I thought it'd be
cool to get to to know each other
better. No, she lives here. This
Australian lives here better so we could
do next week, but if you don't want to,
it's fine. She then replied, "Hey, I
thought you were really genuine on
Thursday night, but I just wanted to be
upfront. I've recently started seeing
someone. I didn't want to leave you
guessing, and I really do wish you all the best.
that's leading somebody on. I don't know
how many times you can keep [ __ ] you
know, making excuses for these [ __ ]
women because I'll put all of these chat
logs out there. I I'm I don't care.
And here was one. Um, hi, it was nice
meeting you last day. Yesterday, how's
your day going? Why can't you accept
that? Any thoughts on the part of her
leading me on whilst claiming that she's
seeing someone even though she's not?
you seem to keep dismissing a lot of
what they're doing and the reasons
behind it, which is why I don't put these
logs out there because anything I pull
up, you I pull up, you're just going to dismiss.
So leading people on, I mean, they're
they're evidently leading you on.
No. Right. Okay.
She was saying that she was seeing
someone yet was talking to me at the same time.
Are you a [ __ ] I mean, the only ones
that they're writing is when they didn't
reply to the first message or when they
say they weren't interested in dating to
begin with. They are the only ones that
are in the right. Whereas, when you've
when you've wrote a message and they've
ignored it or where they've straight up
said, "I'm not looking for anything
straight away." They're the only times
they're in the right. all of these other
ones where they're leading you on,
agreeing to meet, um they are leading
you on. The only ones that are not are
the ones that Yeah, like I said, if they ignore you
or um or they say straight away they're
not looking to date, then obviously
that's that. But the other one, they are
leading you on. I've got another one
here. Hi, it was lovely meeting you last
night. How's your day going? Hi, I'm
very tired today. Been at work since 7:30.
How are you? Oh, yeah. I'm good, thanks.
I didn't get the hangover as I stick to beer.
Then I asked her to meet up.
Never heard from her again.
Oh, here's another one as well. I was
talking to this Romanian woman who I met
when I was with Monty. I met her and we
was talking for like two weeks saying,
"Oh," she was saying, "Oh, yeah, well, me um d
um you know."
Yeah, but Yeah, but they're leading you on.
Yeah, but they're leading you on,
right? So, there was this woman I was
speaking to and she was like, "Oh, I
turned around and said I said her voice
note, right?" And then I'll show be this
is the one I met when I was with Monty
and they all replied by the way I was
like I really like you out of curiosity
do you like me and if so what do you
like about me trying to like flirt here
she said hi I'm sorry I can't say
anything as we only seen each other once
to be honest I don't know how this is
going to work as we have distance
between us yet this woman have no
problem leading me on for two [ __ ]
weeks saying oh yeah we're going to meet
again keeping me on that string like she
would have said this within the first
second or third message but again
leading me on saying oh we we'll agree
to something next week and just leading
you on and then she's like oh to be
honest I don't feel spark between us but
good luck with the dating knowing damn
well she's led me on for two weeks and
we had plans to meet and then she says
there was no problem at all I'm not
ready to date anyone yet so if you was
so if you was not interested in dating
anyone. You should have said stated that
to begin with. You should have said,
"Oh, I'm not interested in in dating." Or
they have literally led you on to then
drop you. They are not right in what
they're doing. So, they lead you on.
They should have said within the second,
third, or fourth message, "I'm not
interested in dating Retatater." But
they didn't. They've kept talking to
you. They've led you on.
Um and then they've dropped it when when
when you know when crunch comes to
crunch. So it's they're not right.
None of these women are right at all
these ones here.
Some last said last year you always
lived in I said yeah I've always lived
in East London. She said I'm on holiday
that weekend. Sorry.
They say a lot of the same stuff of
women that aren't all the same. So sorry
man. I have I have to have to put out
there. Then I wrote I wrote um no
problem. Where are you going on holiday?
Anywhere nice. Didn't reply.
So I mean
I mean if you really didn't think it was
going to work, you wouldn't have kept
messaging me back and forth, back and
forth, back and forth. I mean, there's
one thing giving your number and being
nice and then a second thing is leading
someone on is another. So, yeah,
you always you're always going to make
excuses for these women. I wonder if I
was gay if people would be making
excuses for these men. The one from Finland, right?
Okay, bro. Whatever you say. Yeah. Okay.
I mean, I know they're leading me on. I
know they're taking a piss. You know,
I've been dealing with them for years. I
know what they're doing. Let's see any
of them. Let Let's see where any of
these women have been in the right.
Oh, there's that one I met that Sunday,
the one that tried to tell me. Um,
so yeah, they lead people on to drop
them. That's what they do.
You want me to put this You want me to
put the messages up, Joe? I don't mind
putting the messages up, Joe. If you
really want me to put these messages up,
I don't mind, bro. But I know you're
just going to dismiss everything. I've
got nothing to hide.
I really really have nothing to hide, you know?
I know they're stringing my ass along. I
know they're [ __ ] with me, you know.
I I'm the one that's been in these
convos. I know this [ __ ]
you know. So,
I know for a fact it is these women. The
only time they've been in the right is
when they've not replied to your first
message or they've been up front yet.
90% of these women haven't.
They do a lot of the same stuff for
women that are apparently all different.
I'm very very concerned.
I am very very very very concerned
that these women act exactly the same
way for people that are apparently different.
I'm I'm I'm I'm I I think I'm going to
have to call the white coats, mate. To
be honest with you,
if you want me to put these screenshots
up, I have no problem doing it. Um
but then I feel like you're just you're
just going to dismiss my struggles anyways.
But they're clearly stringing you on.
They're giving you their number. They
know you live in London. They're still,
you know, talking to you and keeping you
on that stream. They are leading you on. It's obvious. So,
but women aren't all the same.
They just do the same thing and act the
same way and have the same mannerisms.
Yeah, I'd say I've got more money than
that Joe to be honest.
See, there's not really an excuse they
can use. You know, I'm decent looking.
I'm a good approacher. I'm good at
texting. There's not an excuse in any of
these screenshots they can use.
The only ones they can say is the ones
that didn't reply or the one that's been
up front. But most of them, it's very
the same leading on.
We're leading people on cuz if they
didn't feel a connection, they wouldn't
be leading you on for two weeks. You understand?
But you think Joe's right or me? Who's
right? Me or Joe?
I'm trying to find some other ones.
See, look. Right, this woman, I'll give
you an example. Right,
she was like, "Hey, what are you up?" I
was like, "Hey, what are you up to next
week and fancy meeting?" She said, "Hey,
so I'm going to be moving a house, so
not a good time of year. I'm also going
to be away at a wedding in Spain weekend
after that. Where were you thinking
anyways? Again, sort of leading somebody
on because they're not talking about
distance here. They're not talking about
anything how it won't work. Then I was
like I was like, "Oh, where are you moving to?"
And I was going to come to Liverpool.
I've only been once it seemed like a
good house, so why not? So they they
literally lead you on and then drop you.
They lead your ass on, play you, and
drop you. That's all that ever happens.
I don't mind putting these messages up,
bro. There's a lot of them. But you're just
going to dismiss them.
Cuz I know you can't critique them.
You can't critique any of my messages.
You can't critique any of my approaches.
That's why you can't do it.
But I know I'm right about these women
bubble. I know I'm 100% right.
And I'll back it up and I'll swear to
blue in the face. It's these women that
are the problem.
Yep. No, not interested.
I got 10 numbers three weeks ago and um
I didn't even get one date.
So yeah, I don't mind putting these
messages up even though they're
depressing, but I don't mind to be
honest with you.
And then you can kind of understand why
people feel the way that they do.
Put it all in.
So yeah, it's the same old Beetle Juice.
I haven't been out for 3 weeks. Yep. Yeah,
I know. I've been dealing with it for
years with these women, but they're not
all the [ __ ] same. You see, they're
not all the [ __ ] same. They just do
the same stuff, say the same stuff, and
act the same way. But they're not all
the same. That's where I draw the
[ __ ] line. You know,
remember, they're not all the same.
Yeah, they act the same way,
do the same stuff, have the same
mannerisms, but no woman is the same,
you know? Any
thoughts on the me getting the 10
numbers and not getting an eight?
Beetlejuice, you seem to just dismiss that.
Maybe didn't suit you.
No, it probably didn't suit you, did it?
I even leave the comments open since
people want to try and tell me that I'm
a coward and I don't I don't let anyone
have their opinion. I'm very much going
to leave myself open for constructive
criticism cuz I know no one can critique
it and I'm going to leave the comments
open and I'm not going to ban no one.
Why would it not suit you? Because
you didn't really mention it. You didn't
acknowledge it when I told you.
So, it seemed that it didn't suit you.
So, if you I'll do this. I'll leave the comments open,
you know. I I I'll enable the comments
and I I'll take any constructive
criticism because I know I am [ __ ]
right. 100% I know I am right.
I don't mind doing this video, bro. It's
not a problem.
And then you try and tell me after this
how I've still got hope. Yeah.
Yeah. I got 10 numbers.
It might be me, not the women.
Okay. I'm going to put these screenshots
out there. Yeah. Of these messages.
Um, okay. And I'm I'm going to enable
the comments so everyone can have their
say and whatever because I'm always
being called a coward. So, it's it's
it's me and not the women. Yeah. Okay.
I'm going to put these messages out there then.
there. Not a problem. And I'm going to
I'm not going to disable the comments
either. So, you can anyone can have
their say. You can tell me exactly
what I have done wrong. No, I got one
reply. I got one reply
and she led me on.
No. One replied and we agreed to meet
and then for some reason she uh he was
sick. So it's not it's me and not the
women. Okay then. So you can tell me
exactly what I've done wrong when you've
seen all of these messages.
Yeah. Cuz Yeah. You're going to be
you're going to be gobsmacked. So be
prepared for it. Yeah.
We we'll let you decide when you see the
messages. Again, there's no hidden gems. Yeah. Oh, yeah.
might help. Speak nice to them. Might
Uh well, when you try to speak to a
woman, she pretends she's got a
boyfriend, funny enough. Yeah. When you
try to speak to them, they they pretend
they've got a boyfriend. It never
helped. Speaking to them nicely never
helped. Anyways, I'm going to do this
video. Yeah, because this needs to be addressed.
But don't dismiss the struggles. Um
because I'm going to I'm going to leave
the comments open as well. So, I want to
be I want to be critiqued.
And if you're not going to critique me,
then I'm right. Simple. That's that's
how it is, you know.
And I've got so many messages, even
though they're they're from like, you
know, the past couple of months.
You're going to find yourself in a dead
end with with these excuses
cuz I'm actually a very good texter as
well, even though you've never seen me type. So yeah,
cuz I said to my mom when I had this
conversation the other day, I said,
"Don't start something you can't finish.
I'm prepared to give you my phone and
show you what I've been dealing with
with these women for years. And I have
no problem. I have no problem you going
have my phone." And she weren't
interested. So I was like, "Well, then
don't start an argument if what my what
I show you don't suit you." Simple.
So that's that's where we're at.
So I don't know if I should start with
the 10 numbers or I'll start with the 10
numbers and probably go from there
maybe. It is [ __ ] bad though to be
honest with you. But
and like I said, I'll leave it
I'll leave the comments open as well.
I'm a big boy. I can take constructive quizzes, mate.
And I know I'm [ __ ] right as well.
That's the thing. I know I am right.
They say all women are different, Steven
Howard. But all women prove they're all the same.
White Knights say one thing and they show another.
So, you know, that's it. That's where we're at.
Probably have to get some like full
combos as well, to be honest, so you can
actually see the whole thing. sort of
there's no sort of um I mean white
knights say they're not all the same,
but they all show that they are. I mean,
where were these where were these women
that are apparently not all the same? I
can't find them anywhere. They all do
the same stuff, say the same stuff. I'm
going to put this video out there cuz
I'm sick of this [ __ ] Joe trying to
sit there and say, "Oh, well, it's not
you. It's not them. It's you." I'll put
everything out there. I'm not asked, bro.
They're the only ones that are right or
the ones that never replied or was up
front. They're the only ones that that
were was not in the wrong, you know,
generally, but most of these people are
in the wrong. and I'll show it as well.
Think of it. If you meet a woman from
Birmingham, right, and she gives you a
number and she's messaging you, right?
Yeah. You are they are leading you on
like they are, as soon as you try to
flirt, they are leading you on.
Cuz if they really felt that way, why
are they messaging you?
You know, if you're not ready to date
anyone, you shouldn't have been
messaging people. It's as simple as that.
You're not going to win, bro. I'll eat
you alive with these experiences.
which is mad because I'm also going to
add in the fact that they say that these
women are not different, right? And we
have put our ourself on the line
multiple times for them to prove that
they are different, but yet none of them
[ __ ] can. So, are we just going to
keep hearing you say something that's
not been proven a million times? You
know, look, here's another one.
I've got so many messages, bro. I don't
want to I feel like I'm going to make a
lot of you people lose hope by putting
this out there, bro. Yeah, that's it.
Even said to this person, let's go to a
restaurant. Not interested.
Where are these different women? E,
where are these women that aren't the
same? I was saying just stuff the [ __ ] lane. Yeah.
None of these women are different.
None of these women are different. It
doesn't matter what any of these white
and and and I'll even send a [ __ ]
video to [ __ ] Laney.
I'll even send a video to [ __ ] Laney
if I [ __ ] have to
cuz don't start something you can't
finish, you know? I will finish it. I
will back up everything I say.
And it will also prove that they don't
go for personality as well because
you know like [ __ ] I'm
you know I'm [ __ ] average looking.
I'm [ __ ] I'm normal [ __ ] looking
if not above average looking.
A lot of they say a lot of the same
stuff for people that are apparently different.
They say a lot of the same stuff for
women that are apparently not all the
[ __ ] same. I'm very concerned. Are
you not concerned, bro?
How they all do and say exactly the same
stuff, but yet all of these women aren't
the same, says nods legs. So, I'll be
I'll be rubbing it in his face as well.
cuz he always says that all women are
are all different and I don't know all women and
I mean can it get any clearer that
they're all the [ __ ] Hey,
why do they do and say the same stuff if
they're all different, you know?
They do a lot of the same stuff for
people that aren't all the [ __ ] same.
people that are not all the same.
And I think I'm going to leave the video
up. If I decide to do this video, I'm
going to leave it up. Might delete my
last one. But
yeah, I'll leave it all up, mate. I I've
got nothing to hide. Sir
to know me, my personality,
but they go for personality and they're
not all the same.
So they say a lot of these women do a
lot of a lot of similar things for
people that aren't all the same. I'm
calling the white coats out, mate, cuz
that is very [ __ ] concerning.
And I'm going to pull up the ones where Um
well obviously they weren't wrong as
well. I'll give you an example where
ones that generally word wrong are ones
that don't reply which is still a bit [ __ ]
to be honest. It is still a bit [ __ ]
because they say they go for personality
and if they really did, you know, they
they would give you a chance to get to
know your personality,
you know, but it's [ __ ] cuz they
don't go for personality.
You want me to do this video? Uh,
Stephen Hen, I don't mind, bro. I really don't mind.
I don't mind doing it. I need to compile a folder. Yeah.
leading you on because look,
we'll just arrange closer to time
anyway. She said yes, kiss,
but then she's saying that that it's not
going to work because of the distance.
So, it doesn't really make a lot of
sense, you know.
Yeah, when I'm sick of people keep
[ __ ] blaming me. Simple.
I mean, I could just disable the
comments and wait for Joe to come back.
So, yeah. Again, she's very much
leading me on with this one here again.
Yeah, I'll just disable Should I just
disable the comment?
Yeah, look, here's the one with Here's
the Birmingham one. Any
thoughts on the getting the 10 numbers
and not getting a date? Bob, you seem to dismiss that. Um,
it just seems you people are just full
of excuses, aren't you?
It seems you people are just full of
excuses when it comes to women. It's madness. So
these women are not all the same, but
they do and say a lot of the same stuff.
I'm going to throw that joke up there,
you know, a few times as well.
They won't be able to find them. They
won't be able to find them, bro. Don't worry.
I think I I'm going to do this video
dedicated to Jo.
They say a lot of the same stuff for
people that aren't all the same.
Yeah. They're going to really really um
they're really going to come to an end
with their excuses
cuz there's so many excuses they have for women.
Who do you think's going to win this
argument? Me or Joe?
They're not going to find them, mate. Trust me.
they're not going to find them.
But then I feel like it's a waste of
time because my experiences will just get dismissed.
But then it's just they're just going to get dismissed.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
What do you think of the messages? The
messages seem fine.
And we're going to put an end to this
Ricky Millan [ __ ] as well cuz he always
seems to say, "Oh, well, people talk
about babies and no no and put women off
and no and like I've just had enough of the excuses,
you know? I've heard enough of them to
last me a whole entire [ __ ] lifetime. Like literally. Yeah.
Any response on the women leading me on,
Bob? No. That that got dismissed. So,
I'm very aware that these experiences
are not going to suit anyone, but I'm
just going to put the video out there anyways because
it doesn't seem to suit anyone. There's
no point of me being a candidate to any argument.
There's literally no point even me being
a candidate to any argument because
they're just going to make stuff up and
dismiss everything I show them what
women do. So, but I'll do it nonetheless
because he doesn't have money obviously. Yeah,
exactly, bro. Exactly. It's the same as
that Smokeoky B. You remember when I
come off of here, right? Um,
you know, when I'd go on some live
streams, I would see Smokey B
and he would be on every day, but yet
he's got a family, he's got a life, and
he's got money. I know. It doesn't make
sense, does it? Yeah.
What do you think of this women thing? BDK.
All they do is lead people on. I have a
boyfriend. I'm not interested. Or you
get led on.
That's literally all that ever happens.
And to be honest with you, I'm not I'm
on here cuz I mean I'm not really doing
much nowadays. I kind of lost hope after
all the bad experience experiences with
women. I'm selfaware.
You understand, bro? I'm self-aware. I'm
not pretending that I've got a life and
money like Smokey Be yet he's sat on
YouTube every day. And these people, it
tells you what they're about because
they'll be on it all day every day. And
if people had money and a life, they
wouldn't. I mean, I've got money, but I
don't have a life anymore because of the
the women [ __ ] put me off. But I admit
that I'm not calling other people. You
understand? They call other people yet
they spend every day on YouTube.
Stop being s about it and go out and try
again. Well, I'm going to put these
messages up soon and I want you to tell
me if I should try again after you see
all of the [ __ ] that I've been dealing
with for years. Maybe you'll have more sympathy.
Yeah. Let's see what you're saying after
you watch this video. It's going to be a
long one and you need to tell me how I'm
the problem. Yeah,
I've heard loads of different excuses.
Oh, you're talking about babies. The
baby talk about women. This is why they
do what they do. No, no, no, no, no.
Every [ __ ] excuse in the book I've
heard, you know.
There's no going back after this, bro. I
don't think there is.
But they think that you're going to meet
someone. They think you're going to meet someone, BDK, you know.
So now it's very
you're going to get your
you're you're going to get your ass led
on. So even if you get a number, you're
going to get led on. That's all that
ever happens. So I mean me if me sat
there now saying women are all the same
is very very warranted. And to be fair,
the question will always be, why has
none of these women proven to be any
different for people that are apparently all different.
You know, that's what it is. You know,
we got King tonight as well. He's
staying around another night.
It's very very much condescending. Very
very much leading people on.
Keep trying doesn't work BDK because I
got 10 numbers
uh three uh three weeks ago, bro. And I
didn't even get a date. Like there is no
keep trying, bro. There was no keep trying. Um
I I I I don't want to humiliate myself
or put myself through it ever again.
So I mean the only the only other thing
you can do is give up because there is no hope.
That's that's where we're at. I just I
don't I know not I know keep trying is
not the not the um answer since that day
when I got them 10 numbers and I spent
600 pound that's why never try again
never there's there's no reason to I
looks maxed I look my best there's
literally not one reason why I do not
have a date
there's not one reason why I do do not
have a date out of any of their numbers
but I don't So,
so, and this is going to be to this
stupid little Ricky Milling [ __ ] as well
that likes to white women and tell
people that they talk about [ __ ]
kids. You know what I'm saying? It's [ __ ]
They're they're unrealistic standards
and then they're impossible to meet and
then people talk about [ __ ]
Yeah, bro. I I I got the money back. I
got the money back, bro. Um but it's not
the point. And I've got money. I can go
out. It's not the point. But bro, I
don't want to I don't want to repeat.
I never want to do it again. It's like
being scared of flying and going on a
plane and being [ __ ] scared and you just
would never do it again if it was that
bad because there is no hope. There is
generally no hope.
There's no need to give up. There's no
need to keep trying. There is no hope. I
don't know how many times you're going
to keep trying until you get the
methods. They're not interested in this
country. It's as simple as that. Like I
said, if I was in Belgium, if I was in
the Netherlands, yeah, I probably would
try. I try every week.
Definitely would. I I try, bro. But not
in this country. They're clearly not interested
or the simple fact I've got a beard or I
don't have blue eyes. I don't know what
it is, but it ain't [ __ ] normal.
I spent £600, bro. And I don't even know
what I spent it on cuz I don't even
gamble anymore. I won the money back and
then after that I was like, "Okay, we
won some money back from the times we've
gone out. Try and give up now." Like
that's, you know, something's got to
give at some point.
You know, it's been going on for years
as well. It's been going on for [ __ ]
years, bro. You know, I don't fancy my
odds of going out, trying again, and
somehow it's going to be different the
next time I go out. I'm not fancying them odds.
Oh yeah, bro. That's where we're at, lad.
try again in maybe like six to eight months
maybe BDK you could go out in like six
to eight months minimum six minimum you
know like but before then no you can't
you generally generally you generally
can't go like there's no herbs there's
no there's no nothing you know I gave
them my all and that's it and I'd say
six eight months six to eight months cuz Um, yeah,
you'd have to use an ethical a month for
like 6 months or something, but you
can't you can't try again. You can't try
again for a long time, bro. It's not healthy.
There's no reason why you haven't found anyone. You've tried.
You tried your best. You looked your
Um, and I'm going to mention that stupid
Ricky Millan in that account as well
since she likes the white night woman.
um he's more than welcome to make
another account and try to critique any
of these messages because he won't be
able to. You know, talking about kids,
the the most the ridiculous [ __ ] that
these people make up for these women is insane, bro.
I feel bad for them, bro. I feel bad how
so many people can be so different but
have exactly the same similarities.
They act the same. They do the same stuff.
I feel bad for them. They're so alike.
Anyone would think that they're the
same. Anybody would think these women
are the same.
It's not If you didn't know any better,
you would think that these women are all the same.
You know, you know I'm a big boy. I can
take it, mate. I can take these stupid
trolls cuz I already know I'm never
going to meet anyone. So, nothing anyone
says is going to And should I throw the
dating apps? Um,
should I um throw the dating apps in
there as well?
I could do that as well. Maybe I'll
leave that for another video. But
I'm not deleting the video as well.
Keeping it up there forever
cuz it's [ __ ] disgusting. Vile it is.
Get to know me. Didn't get to know my
personality. No weirdness. No pit talk.
They make they have a lot of excuses for
these people's unrealistic standards. I find, you know.
Yeah, that's like D, bro.
Yeah, good for you, bro. But I'm not the
one pretending I've got this, that, and
the other yet spending all day every day on YouTube.
So that's it. I've seen what you people do.
I have seen what you people do
um on here, but yet you talk about
others. I don't care. You can say what
you want. Nothing you people say bother
anyone. You know, you're just names
behind the screen.
Like that 8, nine days I was off of
YouTube. It was like, whoa, hold on a
minute. These people are saying they've
got all this money, this, that, and the
other. They're typing away constantly on YouTube.
Something's not right here, bro. Smokey
B. Something is not right here. You're
saying that you've got a better life
than everyone else, but you're on
YouTube typing away every day. Cuz
people that have actually got [ __ ] going
on in their life, they leave, you know? Yeah.
>> I ban people because you repeat the same
old [ __ ] and you're a hater.
So, bye-bye now. So yeah,
that made me give up. I don't even have
a really bad sex drive anymore.
>> You don't really know where to go cuz
it's like you approach, you get led on.
Where does where does someone really go from here?
I want to show that Mickey Million [ __ ]
as well. Tries to say that the problem
is you. No, no, no, no, no, no. And
nothing to do with their standards. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. And like
I said, I'll point out where they've
been right, even though it's still
wrong, you know, because obviously women
go for personality. It's all about the
Um, but yeah, when they don't even give
someone a chance, I mean, otherwise, I
mean, it's like you hear all of these
things on the internet, but your
experiences show completely different.
So, I'm very concerned. I'm going to
call the white coats on them to be fair,
man. They're all different, but all act the same.
very very very very concerning.
I'm calling the white coat. I'm calling
the right I'm calling the white coat
to be honest with you
cuz the skinned version of the bedit
with a absolutely no money in it.
Says that they're not the same. But then
when you look at this they do all the same stuff.
And he says that, "Oh, you haven't met
all women, but I've met more women than
you. I've met a hundred times more women than you." So,
yeah. Oh, people are going to be
gobsmacked, bro, by this. They're going
to be so gobsmacked
by this video.
And I think it will open a lot of
people's eyes as well,
cuz they always seem to make it about
personality. No, no, no, no, no, no. and
desire or the motive to ever want to try again.
And I know it seems like I haven't got
the money, but I do have the money, bro.
I've got the money.
I've got a couple,000 spare. I could
easily go out. Not a problem. Not a
problem at all. But I just know what I'm
going to get, you know, and that's the
and that's what happens in the end. Um,
they still tell you you're going to meet
someone, Steven Howard.
They still tell you that you're going to meet someone.
Talking about kids.
Oh yeah, let's have babies. Let's have
babies. Again, there's no babies
mentioned in any of these messages. So,
I'm not sure where you're coming coming
where you're getting that from. You know,
I do remember Steven Howard
Timmy was saying, "I'm going to knock you out."
So yeah, it's uh it's very much about
personality. Once you've already
pass their unrealistic standard
threshold, then it very much is about personality,
you know, like we're not expecting every
single person to like us. But to get
that many numbers and not even a date, I
mean, that's the bit that's a bit [ __ ]
is it? You know, let's let's not, you
know, let's not pretend.
But they still tell you that you're
going to meet someone.
Isn't that funny, Stephen Howard? Yeah.
I'm going to knock you out. But you know
what? You know what was funny about it?
That it was the same website you can
watch Yoda on from Star Wars. Bless him.
I'm going to sleep with King tonight, I think. Yeah.
Titled the video, There's Someone Out
There for Everyone. in quotation marks.
I don't know what the title of the video.
Maybe dating in 2025, you know.
Yeah. If I do this video, Bob Bills, are
you going to watch it, please?
Are you please going to watch it? Thank you. um
10 numbers or nine numbers where they've ignored
and then I finally got one
and then [ __ ] before they were going
to meet and lo and behold
well they they didn't. So,
and I'll show lady the video as well.
You know, not to try to bully an old
woman, but I want to try to make her
understand. You know, I could have won a
million pounds, but it's not the point.
It's the fact that you went out, you
spent £600, and you didn't even get
given a damn chance. So, you know,
and that's it.
It's so obvious that it's their standards,
you know? It's it even though it all
points to that these people still like
excuses for these women, you know, time
and time and time and time and time and time again.
But yeah, I'm going to um put a folder up of Yeah.
And I'm I'm all for like not giving up
and trying and and and and and and you
know whatever, but I can't find
um the desire or the motivation to want
to entertain it again
after, you know, spending5 600, 10
numbers, not even getting a date. Um you
know what I'm saying? So that's it. So yeah.
Or should I write or should I put it as
but remember women aren't all the same.
Yeah, that's what they say.
I mean, I'm 28. I should already be
settled with someone. You know, my life
is pretty [ __ ] to be honest. Not [ __ ]
but like my life isn't [ __ ] but it's
not as good as it as it as it as it should be.
You know, like in my um
you know, at my age, my life should be a
lot better than it is. And I feel like a
lot of other people should as well, but
my life should be a lot better. You
know, I should be living with some, you
know, I should be living with a woman. I
should be settled down. Do you understand?
I should have to be keep trying. You
know, I've tried and tried and tried and
tried and tried again. Simple.
They don't see me do it with other
girls, bro. Why do you keep dismissing my struggles?
So, yeah. So, I'm going to have to do
like the the 10 numbers and the one that
replied and the other ones and I'll show
like the whole conversation.
and shows what I've been dealing with
for years with these women.
So yeah, go out, spend a load of money,
get led on, lose my hope.
Same old [ __ ]
every time you go out and try.
Or maybe I'll I will list it as dating
in 2025 is nothing but a toxic waste of time. So yeah,
I really want to rub it in that Ricky Mill's face.
But I should be I should be [ __ ] to
be honest with you, I should be settled
down with someone now.
Be honest. I should be with someone
cuz I'm kind of like old now to like
not uh to be going to like bars and
clubs and stuff like that. You know what I mean?
And every single genuine person is going
to say there was nothing wrong with your
messages cuz there's nothing wrong with
my messages with these women. You know,
there's nothing wrong with them at all at all. So yeah,
and just because I might have won500 or
600 back, it's not the point. It really
really is not the point. That is insane
to have not even got a date. Um
I don't think there's any there's no
going back after that cuz even even when
I had the house yet, I never ever spent
£6700. Never. The only time I spent £700
is when I was gambling casino. So, I
kind of knew where the money went. So,
that was kind of my own fault, but
obviously I had the money. But,
and then the cycle never ever ever ends.
So, I'm I reckon about 6 to 8 months.
So yeah, I think I'll need to give up
for a minimum of 6 to 8 months. I reckon death.
No, bro. No one's going to get their
numbers. They'll get their names, but
they won't know what they look like.
Trust me, bro. And I'll show you the
[ __ ] that I've been dealing with with
these [ __ ] for years. It's
a very very very very long one.
But like I said,
and it's kind of like what I'm saying is
it's like what I say. It's not about
what anyone says anymore. It's about
what these women keep showing themselves
to be all the same. Do you know what I'm saying?
It's not about what you say. It's not
about what I say. It's about being shown
different. and no one can show you that
they're not not the same. So,
it's gonna rattle about Ricky Milling as well.
Um, trying to sit there and say I'm the
problem and I talk about [ __ ] babies.
Is this guy for [ __ ] real and he's
white [ __ ] head? You know,
go back to [ __ ] Nex's channel, you
[ __ ] little weasel.
No, they would only know their first
name, bro. They'd only get their first
name. They're not going to get their
[ __ ] last name and that [ __ ]
little weasel. Go back to the [ __ ]
nonsense channel, you [ __ ] little weasel.
We say that I caught that. Yeah.
They're not going to find them from
their first name, bro. Don't worry.
Don't you worry. They're not going to find them.
So, yeah. And like I said, I'm not deleting it. People Oh boy.
Me and a skint virgin going to
Birmingham. Even I would me and Virgin
boy skin in the bed seat with no bed, no
[ __ ] money in it.
Virgin boy skin in the bed with no bed,
no money in it.
No bed, no money in it. Can you imagine
him in Birmingham? That's why I was kind
of tempted to go to Birmingham today.
[ __ ] bring the virgin along with me.
Bring the [ __ ] skin virgin along.
Might get blade.
What do you think, bro? Yeah.
murder boys in the ship with no money.
It's like what that Ricky Millon says.
He says, "Oh, I'm jealous of him because
he's got money." Bro, I've got my own
If only you knew. Uhhuh. If only you [ __ ] knew.
But yeah, I think that's bomb behind
that account. Defer. >> Yeah,
that's definitely bomb behind that account. Yeah.
Yeah. That account, bro. Cuz he would
lick my ass on here, then I'd see him
like slag me off on someone else's
channel, and I was like, "If you've got
anything to say, say it here." And then
he stopped coming on here, little
[ __ ] you little [ __ ] [ __ ]
This video is going to be dedicated to
him as well. So, yeah,
you like my messages, don't you? Um, Steven Howard Here's
the problem. Well, you'll see that I'm
the problem, won't you then? When I when
I show these when I show these conversations.
You're in work. You're in work and
you're sat on YouTube.
Pretty sad, isn't it? So, you're at
work, but you're sat on YouTube
being a keyboard warrior.
I mean, being on benefits at home
doesn't mean you're at work.
I mean, yeah.
Yeah. Anyways, I'm going to show these messages. Anyways, bye-bye now.
I am the problem. So, I want people to
tell me exactly
how I am the problem when I put these
messages out there. So they're all going
to be me um WhatsApp messages that I
have got. So I want people to tell me
how I am the problem and what I have
said and what I have done wrong. It's
going to be interesting, isn't it? I'm
going to leave the comment section open.
Um and everyone's titled to their opinion.
So yeah, we'll see exactly how I'm the
problem and not them.
So yeah, that's uh that's how we're
going to go with this one.
I think I'm going to win this argument,
aren't I, Stephen Howard?
Women aren't the problems,
but let's say we'll see, won't we?
And I will say that they don't have to
reply to you and they're not leading you
on by not replying to you. But it goes
the whole thing goes as okay. Well, if
they're not even giving you a chance to
even get to know your personality,
it it's got to be them. Like I am going
to put all of these messages out there
and show the [ __ ] that I've been
dealing with with these women for many,
many, many years. Hey Mr. G, long time no see.
Have you been catching up with the Monty stuff?
So yeah, I mean they weren't leading you
on. They didn't do anything wrong
technically, but it goes against what
everyone says when they're trying to say
that they go for personality, which what
you will see in these messages.
Um, be prepared. You're probably going
to have to take anti-depressants after
this cuz it it is [ __ ] depressing to
be honest with you. It is depressing.
Um, but yeah.
So, yeah, I'm going to put these
messages out there.
Cuz I don't compare myself to other people.
It's a waste of time. I don't compare.
Yeah. I don't compare myself to
strangers. Waste of time.
You either find someone or you don't.
And I will never find someone. So, it's that simple.
Last time I went out was 3 weeks ago.
Got 10 numbers.
Um, didn't get a date. Spent £600. I was
like, "Yep, that's me. I'm throwing in
the towel. I'm done. [ __ ] that." Like I
said, even though I won the money back,
it's uh it's not the point. That's
ridiculous. I could be a millionaire and
it would still be [ __ ] like nah.
That is it. That is generally generally
generally it. That's the end I reckon, bro. So yeah,
it's time to try in another country
or use their schools for the rest of your life.
whatever the [ __ ] it is. P2. So yeah,
it's [ __ ] Ant-Man as well. So yeah.
Uh, am I gay? No.
Why would you think I'm possibly gay?
Cuz I don't lick women's asses. But all
of these messages will like show
everyone like all you need to know. You
know, they'll probably still get
dismissed. But, you know, as long as one
person acknowledges it, then I feel like
my job is done to be honest with you.
Even if one person just acknowledges it.
Yeah, Monty's a liar.
Cuz it shows where they've messaged back
that they've agreed to meet you as well
and then they've and then they've backed
out for no reason. So what these people
are saying can't be true.
I don't approach them. I don't approach
them. And for many years I just thought
they were going to be different. But
they're all exactly the same. Time
wasters. Leave people on. See, the thing
is, Mr. G, people can say that they're
not all the same. But they will always
show you they're all the same. I was
having the same conversation with my mom
the other day, and I was saying, I've
had bad experiences. They do this, they
do that, they do this, they do that. And
whatever I was saying wasn't getting
through to her brain. So, at the end of
the day, you can say something, but they
will always show them all the same. So,
at the end of the day, it's it's
pathetic, really, isn't it?
You know, people say they're not all the
same, but they are showing you every
time that they are all the same. I mean,
how old am I, mate? I'm 28. I've been on
this [ __ ] since I was I've been on
YouTube since I was 22. And they are not
grown up in their head. And I don't
approach them. I don't I've literally
not tried for almost a month.
I don't even use escorts anymore. The
whole thing just put me off, you know.
To be honest with you, they'll never
change. They're all the same, obvious.
Uh there's millions of people that are
not in relationships.
I mean, I don't know. I don't compare
myself to other people, but fun fact,
Mr. G, most of the people that I know are single.
Whether it's tenants, whether it's
friends, whether it's people I've just
met. Most people I know, including
women, are single. So, there's got to be
a lot of single people out there as
well, even though that does not suit
your narrative. I mean, at the end of
the day, you know, there there's a lot
of single people out there. You know,
maybe I'll do another video on this
sometime. I've I've gone through my
WhatsApp thing, right? And I've met
people drinking online, like all
different sorts of people.
And most of these people are single.
There is some some of them are in
relationships but most of them are single.
So I would say now more people are
single than in relationships. Why is
there so many people that are single?
Why are there so many men that are struggling?
I mean I'm going through the list again.
I'm trying to
Most of them are most of these people I
most of the people I know are single.
So, and that doesn't compare to my
experiences. My experiences is whenever
I try to speak to somebody, they pretend
they've got a boyfriend. Or if I have a
if I get a number, they lead me on. So,
whatever other people do, it's got
nothing to do with me. I'm not them and
they're not me. And I will never compare
myself to someone because it's not going
to change my situation.
Whether it's for the best or for the
worst, comparing is irrelevant.
It's as simple as that. I'm going to put
my experiences out there and show what
I've been dealing with. And there's not
going to be a lot you can say to that.
And I'm going to leave the comments open
as well. I'm going to show where I've
been led on, where I've been took the
piss out of. And all of these married
men, millions and millions. It's not
going to even come into any kind of
argument because what you see is what
you get. And I'm going to show you what
I've been getting.
So that's it.
So that's that's that. And you're going
to be so [ __ ] because there's no way
you can blame me either because all of
my messages are going to be out there as well. So
comparing is absolutely ridiculous.
It's ridiculous. It's not a valid
argument. It will never ever change one
situation even if they were trying to
even get better. So mean most of the
people I know were single.
Not even joking, bro. Women I've come across
that have a normal life. Most people I
know are single.
I mean one in three, four men are in a relationship. So
if there's millions of people married,
there's got to be millions of people
single. There's got to be there's so
many single people out there. So, yeah.
And you say the population is rising.
You don't really see that many uh
pregnant women nowadays to be fair. So,
It's just depressing. That's why I gave
up. Like, I know there's no one for me.
There will never be anyone for me. And
that's it. And if I can put these
messages out there and help people understand,
then that's it. Like I said, I know it
will get dismissed, most of it will, but
cuz they dismiss what women do, bad
things women do. It's what it is, isn't it?
So, yeah, maybe there's just not someone for everyone, you know. Well,
that's not going to change my bad
experiences. Whether it's going up,
whether it's going down, I know my
experiences. I know what I experienced
when I go on dating apps. I know what I
experienced when I tried with women in the past.
So whether it's going up, whether it's
going down, I know for sure it's not
going to change my experiences.
So it's nothing to me
cuz I don't compare myself to strangers.
I used to say the same thing to Pat
Musk. Um, you know, I don't compare.
It's a complete and utter waste of time.
Me comparing myself to another person is
a waste of time.
Well, it applies to me and that's all
that matters. Whether it applies to
other people, whether it doesn't apply
to other people, I'm not interested. It
applies to me and that's why I'm going
to put my messages um
out there. So, it it it applies to me
and that's good enough cuz I'm the one
that's going to be affected by it. So,
and I am affected by it. So, like I
said, I don't compare myself to strangers.
Just cuz someone else does it doesn't
mean I'm going to do it.
You know, I can go abroad by myself
doesn't mean anyone else can. They might
be scared. I can gain muscle in two
weeks, doesn't mean every anyone else
can. Comparing is so so different
because to do with meeting someone, a
lot of it is, hate to break it to you,
is luck, you know? I mean, somebody
might have got lucky at work. They might
have got lucky on a dating app. You
know, a lot of it is to do with with
luck. That's why there is a lot of
people that are single. There are a lot
of people that never got lucky, you
know. And that's what a lot of it is to
do with meeting someone is is about
luck. And just because other people have
got lucky, that does not mean you are
going to get lucky. That does not mean
you are going to meet someone.
You know there's there's nothing in any
kind of Bible that says you will meet
somebody because other people have met someone.
Some of these people might have got
lucky at work. These people might have
got lucky on a dating app. These people
might have been together for like 10
[ __ ] 15 years before Tik Tok, before
Instagram. There's loads of different
reasons why people are in relationships.
But you are not going to be in a
relationship. And that's what you need
to focus on. You you are not going to be
in a relationship. You're not going to
meet anyone. Doesn't matter what Tom
Dick and Abby [ __ ] does. You are not going to
which I'm lacking in. Well, I mean, okay. So,
I mean, I approach women and they
pretend they've got boyfriends. I mean,
I get numbers, they arrange to meet and
then they back out. I mean, what am I
exactly lacking in?
I mean, I I can approach. I'm confident.
I mean, when I try to speak to people,
they're not interested. I mean, what
more am I supposed to do? I mean, you
try to speak to someone, I've got a
boyfriend, I'm not interested. You get a
number, they lead you on. Is there
anything I'm missing? Cuz no one's
getting blocked here. No, I get I said
the same thing to my mom. Let's do it
right here, right now. You know, if you
want to have a debate, you want to start
a debate, let's finish it.
You know, I mean, I've got loads of
friends, I've made friends.
You blaming women's ridiculously high
standards, unrealist, sorry, unrealistic
standards, cuz there's nothing wrong
with high standards on me,
you know, I quote, lacking in social
situations. Let me give you a fun fact.
I have met more women than anybody in the world.
Yeah. Yeah. And you're right, Mr. G.
You're right. Thank you. I agree with
you. I agree with you 100 fucking%.
But what about bars and clubs? What
dating apps? What about messages where
these women have agreed to meet you and
then backed out?
What about all of those ones? Because
it's not it's not one thing, Mr. [ __ ]
G. It's not that you're going out on the
[ __ ] street and someone's pretending
that they've got a boyfriend because
that's not the main [ __ ] issue. For
my sake, you every time you go out,
you're going to get numbers. You're
going to you're going to get in a
conversation with somebody and you're
going to get a number. The main issue is
not about approaching on the [ __ ]
street. It's about the whole fact them
leading you on, giving you false [ __ ]
hope. And even if you approach somebody
in a bar in a club, they don't even give
you the chance. It's not
it's not one thing, mate. It's not it's
a load of different things. So,
it's it's it's it's mad. You're not
intelligent enough for me, Mr. G. Now,
we've known each other for many many
years now. It's not the point of
a woman not being like being approached
in the street. It's several different
things. Most of the issues is not that.
My problems is getting the numbers and
being led the [ __ ] on.
Being led on time and time and time and
time and time and time again.
Well, I'm not a predator and I'm not a pervert. So,
which makes me laugh as well, Mr. G,
because these women claim that they
can't find a boyfriend. That should that
that should just be completely illegal
at this point. Them saying that they
can't find a boyfriend and they can't
find someone. It's like it's mocking
people that actually can't find a woman.
Do you understand? Cuz these women can
find can get with any guy they want.
They can get with any guy they want. You
know that. I know that. But yet they complain.
It's it's [ __ ] up, isn't it?
But I'll put these messages out there,
man. I don't mind.
Um I I No, no, no. I fully do. No, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Here's
here's where you're wrong. I fully fully
do. I fully fully understand that a lot
of people um you know, don't like being
approached um for various different
reasons. They might not be looking for someone.
I do. But you don't see it from my point
of view that dating apps don't to work.
So there's no other alternative than
going out and [ __ ] approaching. You
do not see it from my point of view. I
see it from their point of view, but
you know, they're just [ __ ]
anyways. So it's it's that simple, you know,
and you dismiss the fact that they need
people on and play games and all of that [ __ ] So
they are [ __ ] They are proper proper [ __ ]
And I' I've put myself on the line a
million times for them to prove me wrong
and none can.
So if you are trying to say they're not
all the same, it's a weak argument
because they prove they're all the same.
They literally prove they're all the
same time and time and time and time and
time again. So what's the whole I don't
get these people that sit there and say
women aren't all the same. What what's
different about them? their hair color
cuz what what's what's different about
them? The color of their fingernails
cuz they seem all the same to me, Mr. G.
I'm very very concerned that all of
these women that are apparently different, right?
Uh do all the same stuff that that have
very that have a lot of similarities for
women that are not apparently all the
same. Do you understand, bro? Huh?
So, yeah. Well, I don't want anything
anymore. I've given up. So,
find the motive or the desire to ever
want to try again after 3 weeks ago.
I just generally can't. I just generally
generally generally can't you can look
to max get 10 numbers and not even get a single day.
I don't want to meet a woman back before
I thought they were when when I thought
they were different. I don't know man.
Maybe sex having you know having someone
before I knew they were all the same and
it was never going to happen.
Maybe that was the reason.
I mean my life is pretty [ __ ] right now.
You know, I'm 28 in [ __ ]
you know, 9 days. I should be settled
down with someone. It's not exactly
good, is it? You know, I put more than
enough [ __ ] effort into this [ __ ]
but I just have to accept it for what it is,
you know? I can't What do you want me to
do? Go out every week and spend £500
to to hope that the next woman is not
the same, you know? It's not. I can't do
it, bro. I can't do it. I'm not doing
it. Simple. So, that's it. Yeah.
But I don't want to meet a woman. I'm
done with them, bro.
So, it's clear they're all the same. So, Yeah.
So, that's where we're at
because it's I just can't get over how
someone can't even get a date.
how like you can't
and how people on Reddit try and tell
you that you're going to meet someone
when you're clearly never going to meet
anyone. It's clear as day.
How many times you have to keep going
out and dealing with this [ __ ]
before you realize that there's no one
for you? Cuz that's what it could just
be, which it is. You know, there could
just be no one out there for you, Mr. G.
By you, I mean me. Uh,
okay. Uh, good for them. There's loads
and loads of people that are virgins.
There's loads and loads of people that
have not kissed a woman. Am I supposed
to feel better? I mean, I I definitely
don't. Again, comparing yourself to
strangers is never going to get you
anywhere in life. And these messages are
going to show that I am not the problem
in these in these WhatsApp messages. So
no matter what you're saying, it won't
ring right. You know,
women have got unrealistic standards.
Think about this right now. If I had
blue eyes and I was blonde, we wouldn't
be having this conversation.
And that's that is what it is. you know,
appearance is a big big big big thing.
And unless you meet their,
you know, standard threshold, they're
not even going to give you a chance, you
know, cuz think about it right now.
Yeah, you could blame me all you want.
You can sit here and blame me all you
want. This is a this is quite a a true
thing as well. You can sit there and
say, "Oh, I'm the problem. other guys
doing. No, no, no. But we all know that
if I looked fully white, didn't have a
beard, had blue eyes, I could be the
same person, but women would would would
get with me.
So, it is very much their standards,
you know, and that and that says it all,
you know, not even so much of a as a
look thing, but you know what they're
going for. Like say he was like 6'2,
looks fully white. You I mean Mr. G,
somebody done an experiment on this
before. I swear to God, bro, they done
an above average looking guy on Tinder and
they were they they done this thing
where they were saying that he has been
with kids. I swear to God, bro, women
didn't mind. I swear to God that they
were like, "Oh, um yeah, I've I've I've
been a child predator before." and the
women were still um you know giving him
the chance because they like the way
that he looked and then somebody else
that was act to normal that was average
they weren't interested. So, I think
appearance wise, whether that's like uh
you know uh if you're ethnic or
whatever, it it pro it plays a big
[ __ ] part, bro. Trust me.
And and that's it.
Because I've done a I've done social
experiments before where I've been like
a white guy with blue eyes and I've had
women keep messaging me, messaging me,
messaging me, messaging me, messaging
me. same person
uh different looks
so to speak. So that's another thing you
also need to consider as well. Like it
is women are more shallow than men.
No, not not even Brad Pit. Not even No,
bro. Not even Brad Pitt. Like just a
good looking fully looking white person
like me. But if I looked fully white and
not [ __ ] what people say I look like.
No, not Brad Pit. You could just be a
normal looking white above average white
guy. Seven 7.5.
But you'd have to be white as well cuz
you know your uh heritage is a big part
of dating as well. It's not even just
your looks. Obviously, I've got the
beard. I've got the
So, I don't look like I'm I'm white, but
it's not it's not just Brad Pit.
So, yeah. And then you could be like a
pedophile and women would still go for
you. It's not even a joke, bro. So,
yeah, that's it.
Same. Like I said, I've done it with a
white guy before, blue eyes, and I had
women trying to get with me and [ __ ]
Obviously, I didn't meet them because I
um not going to catfish someone, but I
don't experiment. I've also done a a
profile of that USA Izzy who was like a
four out of 10 and she has
she got 5,000 likes in a day. So I don't
ever want to hear about women
complaining they can't find someone.
Do you understand? Um that's it.
Yeah. They sense the threat. Like I told
you, I done a social experiment.
Well, if that's the case then, right?
Okay. If I make a dating profile right
now of a white guy with blue eyes,
are you telling me no woman will want to
meet me? Same person, same personal, same personality,
somebody looking different. So, you're
telling me that none of these women? You
really want to test that theory?
So it is their unrealistic expectations.
That's the only thing it can be. All of
this personality thing is a cover up. Do
they go for personality? Yes. Once
you've already met their unrealistic standards,
you know, I mean, yeah, sure. Okay.
There are people with people that are
not the best looking, but it's not just
about looks. It's about people's
heritage as well, which is what I found, you know?
So, we need to stop coping, bro. We need
to stop making stuff up at this point.
Personality is like
the last thing that they go for. I'm not
going to make make it seem like they
don't go for personality, but you need
to pass their their standard threshold.
You need to be white. You need to be
6'2. You need to have [ __ ] blue eyes.
If you are not that then or black cuz if
you're anything in the middle like what
I am, you got no chance. So people will
say, "Oh, it's people's personality."
And it's just an excuse cuz I've got
friends. Believe it or not, Mr. G, I've
got friends. I've got loads of friends.
Me going out all over the country for
these years, I made a lot of friends.
you know, this personality thing seems
to be a big cop. Um, is uh
Yeah. So, yeah.
No, but I'm saying if you're like me,
right, even a black guy will find it
harder than a white guy. But if you're
somewhere in the middle like me, you got
no chance in this country.
like a generic looking normal white guy.
Like a normal guy, you ain't got no chance.
Um, so that's it.
Cuz white is the most desired um thing.
So you need to meet their unrealistic standards first.
So this whole personality thing is
caught. Women are more shallow than men,
but people try to make it seem like
they're not shallow and oh, they only go
for personality when it isn't. They are
liars, bro. They are [ __ ] liars.
You know, they're shallow than [ __ ] men.
No, I'll give you an example. Um, Mr. G,
since you want to talk about people
being Muslim, and this is why you need
to stop for your own sanity.
cuz it's not healthy.
I was speaking to this woman on Reddit
right now. Bear in mind, I showed her
like a video of me looking like a 6.57
out of 10. Beard done, hair done, nice
clothes. Well, you ain't seen me for a
while. And I used as an example. I said,
"Would you go on a date with me?" Even
though I don't know her, I don't know
what she looks like. I just said, "Let's
see. Let's use this as an experiment."
She says, "Oh, uh, you're too old for
me." She's 23. I'm 28. Perfectly fine.
and she said she wouldn't date me
because I'm not a Muslim.
So, um, then she said she wouldn't date
me because I'm I'm not a Muslim. Then I
went on her page and it seems that she's
been with another guy before that was
28. Then I made another account being a
white guy slightly better looking than
me and none of these excuses were to be
heard. So, this is why for your own
sanity, you need to give up because
you're going to be this guy that's not
ugly, looks normal, you can even be
good-looking, whatever [ __ ] and
you're going to hear every single excuse
in the book why somebody will not give
you a chance. And do you really want to
put yourself through that [ __ ] It's not
healthy. You know, there's there there's
more to life than that. Um, and
like I I could understand if you was fat
and ugly and you don't look after
yourself. I could get it. But that in
itself it's it shows their standards, you know,
so they're unrealistic. They're not
high. They're unrealistic cuz there's
nothing wrong with having high
standards, but theirs are are [ __ ]
unrealistic. You wouldn't go on a date
with somebody cuz they have a beard or
they don't have a beard.
So it doesn't matter. It doesn't matter.
She purely would not give me
a chance to go on a date just cuz how I
looked, even though I look completely fine.
So you not see the problem with their standards.
Not even a little bit, you know? And I
looked good as well. I looked dapper. So if personality
really mattered to them more than the
way somebody [ __ ] looked, they would
they would give somebody the chance to
go on a date with them, but they don't.
The more than this personality thing is
crap. It is. It is. It [ __ ] well is.
It's to It's like when people say women
don't owe you anything. It's to cover up
their shitty behavior. It's to cover up
all the bad things they've done. For example, Mr.
Right? Say you were lying in bed.
Oh, I want some money. I want this. I
want that. But you're not doing
anything. Then we could say, "Oh, no one
owes you anything. No one owes you
anything." Well, it seems this word is
used when it comes to women doing shitty
things like ghosting, leading people on.
It seems like a lame attempt to cover up
the [ __ ] that they do. And fun fact,
Mr. here. You've never ever ever
um you've never ever ever heard about a
man not owing a woman anything. So, you
see the double standards. It's literally
used to cover up their shitty behavior.
Well, I'm never going to meet anyone, so
that's not going to be a problem, is it?
Yeah. You need to pass their unrealistic
standards first before they even give
you a chance to even get to know you. So,
cuz if you're not perfect, they're going
to say, "You're too old, you're too young." And
I wouldn't mind dealing with it if you
was actually ugly. If you was actually
ugly, then I'd be like, "Okay, well, we
know." But when you're not and you know
that there's nothing wrong with you and
you're going to have to keep putting up
with the [ __ ] it's not really good at
it, you know? So that's how it is. So I
put it down to the fact I don't look fully white.
That it's got to be that. There's
nothing else it can [ __ ] be.
Why you would not pass their unrealistic standards.
So, you know, you going out trying that
now is just insane cuz you already know
that you don't meet their standards. You
already know that,
you know, if if someone if someone uh I
was doing a delivery job. I was doing
Uber Eats, Mr. G. Man, I was doing this
I was doing Uber Eats around central
London for a little while. You might
have missed that, but it's like, you
know, it's clear as day you're not going
to meet these women's standards. So,
it's toxic. Are you even trying? Um, so yeah.
No, wasn't for one night. I done it a
couple of months ago.
No, I done it a couple of months ago.
I done it a couple of months ago because
obviously I don't submit the house
anymore, Mr. G. So, I had to find ways
to make find other ways to make money. I
got some money now, though. I'm all
good, bro. But I uh uh [ __ ] bro. I lost
the house. So, but
I was winning a lot. So, I've got money.
I'm good with money, bro.
But I was [ __ ] bro. And I lost that
lost the house for a little bit.
Took me a while to build up. Not getting
that sublet money anymore. Uh, but it's
all good now. Anyways,
still [ __ ] but it's got money in it. So,
um, yeah, I done it for I done it a few
times, bro. It's exhausting. I made £88
on a Friday and £88 on a Saturday.
So, it's [ __ ] hard though. It was
hard, bro. I around central London as well. So,
It made me realize there's a lot of
[ __ ] in this country.
Well, I'll be going Thailand next month anyways. So,
yeah, I'm going Thailand next month.
Don't know if you heard the news.
Be joining Ant-Man.
Yeah, I'll be joining Ant-Man. So, yeah.
Yeah, bro. Be fun, isn't it?
Say that's getting a lot westernized now.
I can't believe I came to you, Mr. G,
before you came to London. That's mad.
Still ain't been London.
you won't like the pipe prices, let me
tell you that much. So, yeah.
Really? How much did you spend? Did you like it?
That's mad. how someone's done like a a
Tinder profile of somebody being like a
child predator and women would still go
for him just cuz of his looks.
It's mad at
[ __ ] crazy, bro.
So, I don't know what I'm going to title
this video. I'm just going to be like
dating in 2025 is toxic.
I mean that's that's that's the that is
the word for it is it toxic.
It's toxic. It's negative but toxic is
banger for it to be fair.
Yeah. How did you like London?
You know, I hate Valentine's Day. It's
coming up. It's just a shitty day, ain't
it, Mr. G? Just a day to make fun out of
the people that ain't wanted by no one. You know,
let's poke fun out of the Let's poke fun
out of the people that ain't wanted by nobody.
Whoever made that [ __ ] day, bro, is is cruel.
Make fun out. Make fun out.
make fun out of. Um,
yeah, loads of fit birds that aren't interested.
Yeah, very fun.
Yeah, loads of fit birds that aren't interested.
Mad, is it?
Women with unrealistic expectations.
But I'm sure women aren't all the same. Nah,
women aren't all the same, Mr. G. They
just all have the same mannerisms. They
act the same. They do the same stuff.
They lead people on the same way. They
have the same excuses,
but they're not all the same. Like, no,
of course not. They just have the same similarities
for people that are so different. I
know. Like, they're not all the same. I
know women aren't all the same. No, they
don't say the same stuff, do the same
stuff, make the same excuses, lead
people on the same way. I mean, I've had
conversations where I've had the same
conversation with another woman, but
they're not all the same. No, they're just similar.
Oh, maybe it's just by chance, but
they're not all the same.
That's [ __ ] concerning, is it? For
people to act the same way and do the
same stuff for people that are
apparently not all the same.
That's very strange. you know,
cuz obviously they're not all the same.
I'm agreeing with you. They're not all
the same, but they do a lot of the same
stuff, same excuses. They come across as
NPCs most of the time. I know I don't
know how to talk to women. Uh, nah, I've
not approached and they've said they
have a boyfriend straight away. Nah,
I've not got numbers and had people
agree to meet them. Never. Nah, not me,
bro. Nah, must have been someone else.
I didn't come to your country two times
approaching women, did I? Nah, that was
that was another PJ.
>> Yeah. I don't know how to talk to women.
>> Yeah. You're right, bro. Yeah. It's
nothing to do with their unrealistic
standards, is it?
Yeah. It's nothing to do with their unrealistic standards.
Like I said, if I was white and had blue
eyes, we wouldn't be having this conversation.
So, um, that's it. They've just got
unrealistic expectations and standards. Simple.
That's how it is.
Simple as that. So, yeah,
we're about being nice. I'm going to do
this video in a bit, right? I'm going to
do a video in a bit and I really want
you to watch it. just stay on here for a
couple of days and I'm gonna I'm not
going to disable the comments because in
order for somebody to critique me, I
can't disable the comments. I'm going to
blow your [ __ ] mind. I really am
going to blow your [ __ ] mind. Um,
so it's just about being nice. You sure?
I mean, the video is going to go up
anyways when I make it. I need to
compile a load of messages and albums
and I want you to critique every single
one of them.
I want you to tell me exactly what I am
doing wrong. And you're not going to be
blocked. No one's going to be blocked.
Right. Let's hear it right here and
right now. Yeah. No excuses. I'm not a [ __ ]
you know, and you're going to struggle.
And I will and I will give my opinion
where I think they have not done
anything wrong as well. Still [ __ ]
ignoring but you know they haven't led
anyone on. Um but it is still [ __ ] you
know. So I want you to tell me exactly
what I've done wrong. I'm going to go
through every single one of my messages
starting from the last time I've tried.
Um and you're going to come to a dead
end because you don't know how I type.
See you don't think I've got any kind of
way of typing and stuff. So, your mind
is going to be blown. So, I'm going to
I'm going to um I'm going to put them
up. I'm going to put them up where
they've not reply to the first message,
which is why I gave up. The one that did
reply that agreed to meet me
and all of this stuff that you are the
problem and this that and the other.
This is all to cover up their standards,
their unrealistic standards. So,
even though I feel like I'd be wasting my time,
but I mean that's it. So, yeah.
So, yeah. I mean, it is depressing cuz
I'm I'm reliving it, but I'm a big boy.
I can take it. You know, I've already
lost hope. So, yeah, man. So yeah, that's it.
But that is that is the the the facts is
they have got unrealistic standards cuz
yeah it's personality they don't really
care that much about
you know they only they they want
somebody with a they would go with a guy
that is nice.
Oh I can't wait to put this video out
there but I really can't.
Oh, it's reliving it cuz it is [ __ ]
depressing. But like I said, whatever.
So be it. Here where
they said they're not interested
straight away before getting to know my
personality. So I guess I wasn't there. Unrealistic standard.
Even though they didn't lead anyone one
on, it still shows that they've got unrealistic standards.
I need to try and get all of these
messages together as well.
Doesn't matter if they don't owe me
anything. If they don't owe me anything,
why they leading my ass on?
If they don't owe me anything, why are
they leading me on?
Hey Jane, I'm going to um I'm going to
well, why don't I go around and start
being [ __ ] to women and then come out
with I don't owe you anything.
How would that wash, Jane? I'm going to
be doing a video in a bit and you're
more than welcome to um critique me.
you're more than welcome to say where
I've what I've done wrong and ret
um you know um and yeah like I said I'm
not going to be disabling the comments
so it's going to be like a
roast me thing basically cuz I I I know
I'm [ __ ] right mate with these women.
I know I [ __ ] am. I'm going to put
all the messages up where they've led me
on wasting my time basically explaining
why I've given up with this now. So
start with them numbers that one and
then we'll go into like more recent ones
and I'm going to show every bit of the
conversation as well. So and you can
tell me where I've done wrong.
You I want you to tell me exactly what I
have done wrong, you know. I mean,
they are unre they do have unrealistic
standards because if you do not pass
their unrealistic standard threshold,
they're not even going to go on a date
with you, which going on a date with
somebody is getting to know their
personality and det. So,
so it's just basically going to be a
summary of the [ __ ] I've been dealing
with for years with these women and why
I gave up. So yeah, that's it.
>> Yeah, man. I've always said women have a
vendetta against me. I've I've been
saying it for years.
I've been saying it for [ __ ] years, bro.
Like at the start I was saying it just
like to take a piss of that but I
generally think it is that way.
These messages are going to blow your
[ __ ] mind out the park as well.
Well, I mean if I'm white and got blue
eyes, they've got no problem with it.
So, but all of these excuses, oh, you're
too old for me, you're too young for me
because you don't fit their unrealistic
physical standard type.
Maybe you've got a beard, something as
shallow as that. So, so yeah,
that's it, though.
Yeah, I'm going to say um
I'm just going to say dating in 2025 is
toxic. That's [ __ ] that's it.
I'll do an odd joke here and there about
how women aren't all the same.
Cuz it takes a while to get to know someone's personality.
It really, really, really does take a
while to get to know someone's
personality. And it shows that even
though some of them weren't doing
anything wrong, they haven't even given
you the chart. So, this whole
personality thing is cop even though
these people, you know, need to stop.
Obviously, we can't blame them. We can
blame the ones that have led you on.
So, we can blame the ones that have led
you on and stuff, but it will just show
that like obviously
um you know, all of these people that
are saying, "Oh, they go for personality
and that it can't ring right because it
takes a while to get to know what
someone is like." And like I said, it
could be simple as you not having a
beard or you having a beard or you
having black eyebrows. So,
anyways, we've done enough rambling on.
I need to I need to still compile all of
the the photos and stuff cuz I want to
do it bit by bit by bit by bit by bit. Yeah.
And I won't block any kind of
constructive criticism, but any kind of
hate will be blocked.
Any kind of hate or stuff like that will
be blocked. So yeah,
I don't think it's a conspiracy. I think
it's because I look like I'm Turkish,
bro. Even though a lot of people say I
look like I'm white. I don't look fully
white. Look, I don't look I don't think
I look fully white, bro.
And that's another thing. You would have
thought I was [ __ ] Muslim by looking
at me. But yeah, we hear these excuses.
No, we won't date you because
you're not. I'm just saying.
Well, I don't look [ __ ] white, do I? So, yeah,
I'm just peeing right now.
I'm peeing, bro. So
there's not going to be no hidden combos
and not going to be no hidden nothing. Yeah.
And anyone's welcome to comment. No
one's getting blocked, you know. That's
how confident I am that I'm right.
That's how confident I am.
Right. Let me um compile these things uh
these uh photos now, lad.
Um and do this video.
I'm not doing that. I don't need to
change myself. What? Just for somebody
to maybe like me. Get [ __ ] bro.
Yeah. And I'm going to show these people
on Reddit as well, but I'm going to show
them on another channel. Um, so
I know I'm not going to probably get
much with this because people are just
going to dismiss my struggles and defend women. Um, so yeah,
I will show you all of the bad
experiences I've had.
Yeah, cuz I've not had a shave for a little while. So yeah,
I got a lucky escape winning that money back.
Yeah, I got a lucky escape.
Why would I go out and waste time again?
Why would I go out and waste money again
to hope that a woman's different? You
know, it doesn't make sense.
And we'll point out, like I said, the
fact that even though
Well, I will show you, Jane. I will show
you. Well, I was supposed to meet
somebody last um I was supposed to meet
someone last Saturday. I don't need to
build my intelligence. I'm more
intelligent than most of these women
will ever be.
Far more intelligent than they will ever be.
Um, anyways, I'll show you. Yeah, the
messages. These Yeah,
I'm far more intelligent than most of
these women. It's like that USA Izzy.
She thought she was intelligent. She
thought she was smart. And then when I
gave it back to her, she shut her mouth. You know,
you know what I'm saying? So, yeah.
Do they still think you're going to meet someone, Mr. G?
Yeah. They still think that you're going
to meet someone.
I don't know. I don't know when it
happened, but I know where it happened.
But that doesn't mean someone's not
intelligent because they can't answer
one thing. Let me ask you a question.
Okay. I don't know. Let me ask you a
question. You want me to ask you a question?
Huh? What's the capital of Canada?
Cuz I know all my capitals.
Go on. Don't look up. You got 5 seconds.
1 2 3 4 5
Bro, you're not going to beat me. I know
all of my capitals. So, does that mean
that you're not intelligent?
Huh? You've just you've just looked it up. Okay.
What's the capital of Australia?
No, it won't Montreal. It was Ottawa.
What's the king's name? King Charles.
Yeah, but you're just looking it up.
You're just looking it up. It's obvious. So
>> yeah, I knew I I know about the capitals.
You ask me a capital and I and I'll tell
you I will know it. You ask me a capital right now,
I should be able to get most of them. I
know my geography,
but you might ask me what I don't know.
But go on and I'll answer it straight away,
whereas you probably just looked it up. Donald Trump.
Oh, I don't know that one. Argentina.
No, I don't know. Uh, Russia is Moscow.
No, I don't know. Argentina.
Russia. I'm sorry. It's Moscow. No.
Yeah. Ask me another one.
Ask me a capital. Ask me a capital, bro.
Ask me about America as well. My
geography is really good with America.
I thought it was Moscow though. Okay,
let me ask you one then. What's the capital of Denmark?
Capital of Spain is Oh,
it's Madrid, isn't it?
It's got to be Madrid. Hopefully, it's not Barcelona.
Yeah, it is
was right. Okay, try again. Yeah,
go on. You're not You're not talking to
a [ __ ] mate. Washington, easy.
That one's Washington. I don't know. The
first person on the moon.
That one's easy, bro. Washington. [ __ ]
sake. Come on.
I know a lot about America.
I'm not sure.
Ask me some more capitals. I specialize in that.
Yeah, I said Washington,
which is the same thing.
Washington, Washington DC. That's what I meant. So, so anyways,
capital of South America. [Music] Um, Colombia.
Is it Colombia?
Yeah, but that's what I meant.
So, well, I said Washington, so yeah.
Why is it Colombia?
I don't act dumb.
Okay, ask me another one.
Yeah, it's a continent. But I just said
it. Yeah, it's a continent.
Yeah. I don't know. I thought that might
have been, but yeah, it's a continent. Yeah.
Anyways, ask me another one.
We never said Washington DC is in
Colombia. No one said that. Anyways, ask
me another one. Yeah.
Oh, that's easy. Cape Town.
Yeah, that's Cape Town. Easy.
he was talking about capitals.
Oh, I didn't see the first one. Yeah,
it's Cape Town.
First capital of America. H, New York.
Oh, is it? I thought it was Cape Town.
I thought it was Cape Town. M.
Yeah, it had to be in New York. It's
obvious, isn't it? Wasn't that like the
That was like the first state.
that was made. No,
I thought it was tapes out here. [ __ ]
Can ask another one.
What does sublet mean, Mr. G? What does
subletting a house mean?
I'm not interested in you, Jane. You're
an attention seeker. Get [ __ ] Yeah.
What does sublet mean, Mr. G? when you
sublet a house.
I was illegally subleting for 3 years,
Mr. G. I was getting three grand a
month. Bet you was jealous of that, wasn't you? Mhm.
But you was jealous of that, wasn't you,
Mr. G? And I got off scot-free as well. Ah,
would you illegally sublet if you could,
Mr. G? Even though you, you know, you
wouldn't go prison. I'm lucky they
didn't come. I'm lucky they didn't come
after me, is it, Mr. G? Yeah.
>> Yeah. I was lucky they didn't [ __ ]
come after me, bro.
>> I hate women, Jane. They're all the [ __ ] same.
He start showing his messages certainly
are distracting me. Yeah. Yeah.
I can't believe Monty had a fight with
somebody on the same website.
You can watch um
You can watch um Yoda on.
It's weird, isn't it, Jane? The same
website you can watch Yoda on
Star Wars is the same um
website you can um
not unless one of these numbers go on a
date with me. Um that that's me down in
this country, bro, for at least
I'm going to say a year, bro.
I'm going to have to say, yeah, there's
there's nothing that would tempt me.
There's nothing that will change my mind
because it's the severity of it, you
know, spending £600, not even getting a
single day, not being given a chance,
there's no going back from that.
And even though I won the money and I
had the money to spend, it's not the
point, bro. I didn't stay in any good
hotels. I didn't gamble. So, I don't
even know where the money went. Cuz if I
gambled or I stayed in the hotel, I'd
know where the money went. Yeah.
But no, there's there's nothing, bro. I
think that's that's the end.
That is the end, bro.
Do you do football bets, Mr. G?
Do you still do football bets?
I've got a biryani I'm going to eat. I'm
going to reheat in a bit in the microwave.
So now there's there's no going back after that.
But I f
Mr. G, do you still watch the Sideman?
No. It is very very serious and it's
very very personal
to be not given a sex life, to be mocked
by women. It's I I find it very very
personal. Very very very personal
and that's why I don't try anymore.
So we need to create a folder for this
YouTube video once it
is. It's very very personal to me.
You know I don't gamble anymore. Mr. G
um he was on a couple of weeks ago.
Yeah, he ran off when he got docked.
Yeah, he ran off and he got uh doxed.
Well, his face, you know, he's he's what
said got doxed. So, I don't I don't find
it a hobby. I think it's depressing
getting rejected by women when you're
not even ugly. You think that's a hobby?
That's not a hobby at all. That's [ __ ] depressing.
Good's not been on here for years. Yeah.
Yeah. Well, I'm going to do this video,
Grezy. I'm not going to disable the
comments. Anyone's welcome to their uh
opinion on what what I've done wrong
and whatever. And that's it. any kind of
hate though or spamming or like insults
like troll that will get blocked but
anyone can agree disagree
so there's no hold bars because I I I'm
so confident that I am right I think you
still want to hear yeah
so there's there's going to be no no
hold bars say what you want just don't troll Right. Um,
yeah. I'm not scared to approach it. I
still can't even get sex. I still can't
even get a relationship. I know. It
makes it even worse, isn't it? It makes
it even worse because there's literally
no excuse for it.
Um, yeah, he did come back for a little bit like
was it like a year ago?
Yeah, you can tell me what my problem
is. Yeah, you're more than once you've
seen their messages, you can tell me
what I've done wrong.
Yeah, you can tell me what I've done wrong.
But yeah, um
that's what makes it even worse because
there's no excuse for it.
No, Jame, listen. Listen. Just wait
until I put these messages up.
Okay? Just wait until I put these
messages up and then you're more than
welcome to say what you got to say.
That's it. No one's going to get blocked.
I'm sick of people saying that women
aren't the problem and people talk about
having babies and all of these excuses
that they use because women's got
unrealistic standards, you know,
expectations and so
going to compile a lot of messages.
I know it all contradicts itself.
Yeah, I'm going to put these messages up of um
my conversation with these women
starting with the last time I went out
the 10 numbers and yeah,
it's going to be a long video. [ __ ] hell. Yeah.
Yeah. Nothing's going to tempt me into
trying again. No, I don't think so.
Unless, like I said, one of these
numbers randomly meet me that I've
already got, I'm not going out and
trying again. I should have to.
They've made it clear that they're not
interested in this country.
Maybe I should title the video they're
just not interested in this country.
Nah, I want a I want a better title.
That is a funny title, but I want to put
as um dating in 2025 is toxic and [ __ ]
you Ricky Millen as well. You [ __ ] s.
I'm going to start I'm going to start it
with that as well. Yeah.
And I want that Ricky Billing to make
another account and
I'm going to find I'm going to find his uh
his account. I'm going to unblock him. I
don't think he is blocked. Is he? I'm
going to unblock you if you're blocked.
Let's let's let's let let's let's get
into this. You know what I'm saying?
music. You said that people talk about
babies and having babies with people and
that's why people can't get a woman. So,
what are you seeing in front of your
[ __ ] What the [ __ ] are you seeing in
front of your eyes?
You know what I'm saying, Grezy?
It's going to really come to a dead end,
isn't it? These excuses.
The same website you can watch Pluto on Grezy.
and Mickey Mouse. I'm going to knock him out.
This [ __ ] needs to be monitored. Yoda's on here.
Grieves. Yoda's on here. Yeah.
No, no. Link. If you got anything to
say, Jane, you can say it to my face.
You say it to my face. Yeah.
Right. I'm going to make this video
anyways. Yeah. So, give me some time.
Get your popcorn ready. I'm going to
title it, they're just not interested in this country.
They're just not interested in this country.
No, I'm not going to talk about it. Yeah.
Right. I'll be back with this video.
No cold bars. Say what you want. Just no
trolling and projection. Just you can
give any kind of criticism.