Right. Come on, Ricky. Nice and early.
I wrote you a little poem. I'll rip you
a new [ __ ] in this live stream if you
want me to.
I'll read it out to you if you if you
don't want to read it, mate. I don't
mind reading. I'm not Monty I can read
cuz I had to say everything I had to
say. So, you you've been completely
[ __ ] Like there's there there's no
coming out of that.
Um, so yeah,
come on, Ricky. You're not blocked.
Everyone knows you're not blocked.
You're up nice and early. So,
I've replied to your message and yeah,
I'll read it out to you if you want
that. Do about 3 minutes, 5 minutes.
Let's see what you've got to say back to
me. Yeah, your four thumbs up doesn't
bother me at all, mate. I I generally
don't care about thumbs up. No one's
getting blocked. I don't care. Stays
behind the screen.
We know you up nice and early. Come on.
Sorry to be so long, but I had to do I
had to do this, you know.
Yeah. Come on, Ricky. I don't mind
reading this out to you, man. and let's
see what you've got to say back. I was
going to bring up someone else, but I
want to stick to the subject that we're
that we're talking about cuz I guarantee
you, you're not going to win against me,
mate. Trust me, I've been doing this for
[ __ ] years, you know? I I Yeah,
that's it, man. No one's blocked. No
You should read it all, man. It's It's
highlighted everything that you've said.
you know, it's highlighting everything
that you've said and how you've also
contradicted yourself at the end. So, I
[ __ ] with you up there, didn't I?
Really, mate. The last bit is kind of
like um a big [ __ ] you, you know? But
yeah, that's it, man. I'm all good, bro.
I just want Ricky to come on. I need to
read this out to him
cuz when more people join, I'm going to
read it out, you know, when more people
join. Anyways, I understand it's long. I
appreciate that, but I had to say everything, man.
Um, so I had to highlight everything
that you was dismissing. Yeah.
I know I'm [ __ ] right. I don't care
about names behind the screen, bro. It
doesn't bother me. I don't give a [ __ ]
I don't need to block people. I know I'm
right. One million%. 100%.
H just chilling, bro. All
I read out to everyone.
And uh yeah, you need to learn the the
definition of facts. I've also quoted um
some words that you've said to me which
then actually makes it not fact what
you're saying. See you you I'm too smart
for you, mate. You understand these
things? You know what changed in the
last two [ __ ] years, bro? Like what
actually changed in the last two years?
Did they ban Tik Tok? Did they ban Instagram? No.
That's it, man.
They didn't ban any of these things. So,
your four thumbs up, I don't give a
[ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] about your
four thumbs up. You know, all of these
people don't even leave their house.
Like, I've probably met more women than
they have. I'm all right. I'm a big boy.
I can take it. You know, I can I can
defend myself. You know, it's it's fine. you know,
Monty is smarter than me, but you don't
get no women. You're a virgin. So, and
that's what it is. I very much
understand it. These people like Ricky
and these people, they don't get women.
This is why they white night. This is
why they do what they do. They don't
deal with women. They don't understand
anything. Even when they're shown
things. Now, I went on a message uh the
messages and Tiger Tiger said, "Uh, I
see what you mean now. They should have
told you first that they didn't want to
take things further to you in advance
instead of them prolonging it and your
texts are very polite." That I respected
him for because this guy doesn't know
me. He doesn't know anything about me.
We don't like each other. Um, and um,
yeah, we don't like each other. And for
him to write that, that says a lot,
mate. And then you got Ricky talking a
load of [ __ ] Um then where he
contradicted himself and half of the the
stuff that he said, but and then I
replied to him saying, "Yeah, it's crazy
yet people still find excuses to put the
blame on me. I give up." That's what I
said to That's what I said to this tiger.
No, it was a different tiger. No, no,
no, no. It's a different tiger. This guy
does not like me, bro. He doesn't go on
any of my [ __ ] So for him to have
commented what he what he's commented
Yeah. I want him to come. I I'll read
the message out to him.
I will read the messages out to him if
he if he wants. I don't mind, bro. I'm
all for it. I completely [ __ ] you up
in my response. There's no getting back.
Do you want me to read it? I can read it
if you want. I can read what I wrote. I
love [ __ ] reading, bro. I can read it.
You know, you want me to read it? I can read it.
I can read it if you want, bro.
Yeah. Okay, let me read this. Right.
This is what I've said. Right.
Right. He said, "Just read through some
messages and you weak of desperation,
loving their messages, asking what they
like about you, saying you'll go their
city, sending voice notes all after
meeting once. You are way too full on.
It's massively off-putting to some um to
women. That partly why they won't meet
you. It's it's way you're acting. Also,
non-stop asking to meet them when you
don't know them. You have no game, PJ.
That's your problem. This is not a dig.
It's just facts.
I replied to your message. This is me
now. I replied to your message on a
video, but in case you can't be bothered
to watch it, I'll be nice and reply
here. I think that I've read in
quotation mark some messages. Pretty
much sums up my argument. You seem to
dismiss the ones that didn't reply to
the first message. You also dismissed
the ones where they replied back once. I
asked them a question. I never heard
from them ever again. How about the one
who admitted to having a great time with
me and was still up for meeting, then
hit me 3 hours before meeting with, "I'm
sorry. I'm going to give it another go
with my ex." What was the excuse there,
Ricky? So, yeah, the some was you
picking out a few that you thought you
was right on and the others you
dismissed because it didn't suit your
narrative. Yeah, loving their messages
as I mentioned in my previous video in
in um brackets in case you haven't seen
it. I would strongly advise you getting
your eyes tested if you haven't done so
already because how did you manage to
dismiss the fact that they were loving
my messages more than I was loving
theirs? Going by your logic, if loving
messages on WhatsApp is a big problem,
would that not make the women who loved
my messages also the problem with me
since they are doing the same? Even
loved my messages and I never loved
theirs. So, by by your logic, it's okay
for women to love messages, but if I do
it back, it justifies them being toxic
and leading me on and it being a me
problem. You've never addressed the
women that loved my first message.
First, do tell us what you thought about
it. I'm curious. Explanation mark
asking what they like about you saying
you go to their city and sending voice
notes all after meeting once and you
were too full on and that's partly why
they won't meet you. It's the way you're
acting. So I wrote now as I stated
previously this goes back to I quote
some messages but to be honest it's less
than 10%. I said that to one two three
people maximum. What about the rest you
dismissed that involved none of the
things that you're mentioning. Also you
might want to retake geography lessons
because Finland is a country not a city.
So last time I checked last time I
checked. So what so what I met a woman
from Finland we was talking for a month
so I suggested going to see her. Big deal.
You know, question. Why are you not
allowed to send someone voice notes
because you've only met them once? Is
this some kind of new rule you've made
up? Pretty sure you've you pretty sure
people send messages all the time to
people that they haven't met. That's
partly why they won't meet you because
of how you're acting. I said, now I'm
not sure if you remember, but I approach
women in public bars, clubs. I've never
been one for online dating. So, if I'm
approaching them and they reply and
agreed to me and love my messages in
brackets, the thing you call me out for,
I would have guessed I came across
normal since why give me their number,
reply, love my message, and agree to
meet you. I'm sure if I was acting
desperate and being off-putting, they
wouldn't even bother replying in the
first place. That ruins your whole
argument. Um, also, none
meet when you don't know them. Also,
non-stop asking them to meet when you
don't know them. I would advise you to
learn the concept of non-stop. Asking a
woman out twice is hardly non-stop. I
don't need to know the ins and out about
someone because I asked them out on a
date twice. It's like when people have a
problem with you trying to meet a woman
after a week of because you're speaking
to her too soon. Yet have no problem
with women wanting to meet someone
straight away without knowing anything
about them. Personal experience. Um
you have no gay PJ and this is not a
dig, just facts. I've replied, "Well,
considering I don't have to rely on
dating apps and can approach women and
get them to reply, I would bet that's
more than what most can do, including
yourself, am I lying? If not, please do
please do show me how it's done. I'd
love to learn from the best." Um, then I
replied, "Also after uh also before I
finish this, I just wanted to say,
please learn the definition of facts.
Facts is something that is set in
stone." In fact, let me pull let me pull
a quote from you from yours a while
back. Quotation mark. You're
good-looking, PJ. Women are too picky.
That's why you can't pull. Which very
much sums up of everything you saying
anything but facts. You can't play two
sides of a coin. Hold that. You know, you know.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. Come on. We We'll start an argument.
You know, I'm not insulting you. You
know, I'm writing something. Yeah. So,
at the end of the day, mate, you know,
let's have it here and now. You're not
getting deleted. No, it would mean it's
not that serious. You've been [ __ ]
with people for God knows how long on
other people's channel. Let's Let's get
to the ins and outs. I've I've quoted
everything that you've said and I've got
an answer for it.
Starting with the lover hearts. Okay.
Come. Okay. Hey, if you don't want to
read it, come on here then. Come on
here. So, you got bodied. You got
shattered. There's nothing you can say.
You know, there is literally nothing you
can say. The some messages sums up my
argument very well. The some that you
pick to suit your narrative. You understand? It is Yeah.
Just pointing out where. Okay.
Bro, I'm not angry. I'm not angry at
all. I I love a debate. What am I angry
about, bro? I'm chill. You wanted to
have a debate. You wanted to write
something. I replied back to you. So,
what? You just going to wind people up
and not say anything?
I said, took it serious. Not all just
pointing out where you're wrong. Aren't
you the one non-stop talking about me on
your boyfriend's channel? which is one
of the reasons why I unblocked you. So you're
I don't control everything. I'm
everyone's unblocked. I'm not going to block him.
So you want to start [ __ ] right? So you're
I actually thought this guy was being
serious. So what, bro? You I mean, I've
caught you on your boyfriend's channel talking [ __ ]
Yeah, he's more than welcome to air my
views air his views about me. I'm not
I'm not bothered, bro. He's more than
welcome to do that. That's all good,
man. That's all good in the hood.
Yeah, I'm a bit creepy. I don't think so.
It's not about it being deep. I'm not
angry, bro. I don't mind these debates.
What the [ __ ] It's because you you what
you're saying don't make sense and you
also what you're saying isn't fact as well.
because you contradicted yourself. Hold
that out. You know, people like [ __ ]
nons legs, right? Can say what they want
because they Oh, another thing is Yeah,
bro. Like, honestly, oi bubble, bro.
Listen to me. Yeah, this I'm actually
being serious right now. I don't know
why this popped up, bro. That guy is so
jealous of me talking to women, bro.
He is so jealous of me talking. Not not
Ricky. [ __ ] Virgin boy, bro. Have you
seen it, bro? He gets mad when people
talk about women, bro. Uh talk to women.
He hates it, bro. Have you seen it? He
hates anyone speaking to women,
stalking women on WhatsApp
on the street.
Bit of a weird thing to say. Do you not
think that a Do you not think that's
weird, bro? This guy hates me talking to
women. This is how I know he's a virgin.
Like, honestly, bro, like hear me out
here. We're not talking about Vakia.
This is how you know this guy is a big
virgin. You know, you always ask me.
Yeah, listen to me, bro. Just please
listen to me. You're always asking me
about how, you know, um how I know uh
he's uh how he's a virgin and stuff,
bro. He gets mad anytime I talk to a
woman. Have you Have you not noticed
this? I don't know how it popped up. I'm
not even subscribed to the [ __ ] and I
don't care about anything he says, but
this is this is weird. And I can't help
but but tell you how weird it is. Like,
he's so jealous of of anyone speaking to
women. That's how you know he's insecure
and he's not happy with himself. Like,
bro, this is not even me being reacting.
This is me telling you how [ __ ] weird
it is what he does. Like, I don't care
about anything else. This is weird and
you can't help but acknowledge how
[ __ ] weird it is.
How do I It popped up. It popped up. I
think No, no, no. I saw a comment and I
clicked on it. Bro, he is jealous of
anyone speaking to women, bro. No,
seriously. Like the first few times I
thought, "Ah, he's just [ __ ] with you
in it." But no, no, no. He definitely
definitely definitely hates anyone
meeting women, bro. I'm telling you. No,
no, no. He does. He does. Cuz think
about it, bro. Listen, listen. You know,
the messages that I put out there, I
would have had to physically went out
and met them women cuz everyone knows I
don't I don't get people off date apps
and you know, whatever. So, the fact
he's probably thinking in his head, the
fact that you've gone out and you've met
them women, he's jealous. He is jealous,
bro. He is. He [ __ ] well is. Like,
even though they didn't meet you, yeah,
you're having good conversations with
people that you've approached. He could
never do that.
He hates the fact that you're not a
virgin like him. Like, call me, bro. Say
whatever you want. No one's going to get blocked.
Seriously, he hates anyone meeting new
women. That's how I know he's a virgin.
Like, you can say what you want. I don't
care. Disabled girl. Bro, listen. No
person acts like that. They don't, bro.
Seriously, they don't. Seriously, Bob,
listen. Bubby Bubbly. He doesn't.
No one acts like that. Seriously, nobody
acts like that, bro. Not even Red Star.
Not Red Star. Not H. Not anyone that
[ __ ] with me. I swear to God, bro. I
promise you. No one acts like that but him.
He's a jealous virgin,
you know. And I'll be proven to be [ __ ] right.
So, it's not that serious.
How can he be jealous when he's got someone?
Uh because the girl that he is with is
very ugly and very disabled.
I mean, I'm the wrong person to be
asking. If he is not jealous, he's got a
funny way of showing that he's not
jealous by getting mad every single time
I meet new women. And he is the only one
that does it. So for somebody that's not
jealous, they sure [ __ ] act it, mate.
You know, they sure act it. He hate He's
been this way forever. Even when he was
single. Even when he was single, he this
virgin has always been like this. Why do
you think he's got the nickname virgin
boy? He hates anyone
meeting. Do you know what I think it is
with him? Let me Let me Let me Bro,
okay. Let me tell you what I personally
think this is. You want me to, bro? I I
would rather have nobody than be with a
disabled girl. And he would rather have
somebody else other than who he's with,
which is why he stalks all of my sloppy
seconds. So, I would rather have no one
than have a disabled girl. I mean, I'd
rather have no one. I don't know how
many times I I I have to explain this.
This is what I think it is, right, with
this little virgin, you know, um is
where he's met you, right? This is what
I personally think it is. Where he's met
you, right? Let me just give my 50
cents. Agree, disagree, I don't give a
[ __ ] Where he's met you, right? Cuz
this is entertaining to me. Where he's
met you when you was younger. Um,
you know, when you know when um Where's
your girlfriend, Eldridge?
Where's your girlfriend? Why are you not
getting any action? So, when Okay, let
me just run by this. Right. So when I
was on Monty's earlier, I had these
people trying to flame me. And do you
know how I shut them up? Do you know how
I shut every and each one of these
people up? There was about three of
them. I said, "Oh yeah, I'm all of these
things, am I?" Well, guess what? You
can't take a day off of YouTube. And
that's been proven. So I'm all of these
things that you are not and you have all
of these things, right? Yet you can't
take a day off YouTube. And they
couldn't say anything, bro. They
generally couldn't say nothing. They got
ruined. That's all I had to say was I've
seen you on YouTube. So, anyways, let me
tell you what I think it is with um this
this this guy, right? So, he's met me at
a young age
and he's he's clinging on to you because
of his condition, right? Just hear me
out, right? So he thought that he was
going to be friends with you forever and
t and d and obviously where you're
younger than him and you have more money
than him, you're better looking than
him, you've done more things in your
life than he has, he hates it. And the
fact that you're better looking than him
and you've had more women than him, it
doesn't matter about now. You've been
with more women than him, you've got
more life experience than him. He hates
it. He hates the fact that that that is
what it is. Doesn't matter what trolls
say, bro. Because if he if he was in a
happy loving relationship and his life
was all hunky dory, he wouldn't spend
all day [ __ ] with someone because
that is trying to [ __ ] with someone.
Because at the end of the day, that is
worse than sitting on YouTube moaning
and complaining. We can go live, we can
sit there, we can moan, and we can
complain and whatever. But to actively
try to [ __ ] with someone all day, every
day, bro, your life ain't good. I can't
I can't lie, bro. Your life ain't good.
It can't be good for someone to do that
every day. It screams to me someone's an
insecure, unhappy virgin. That's the
only alarm bells that is ringing.
Reaction, no reaction. What the [ __ ]
ever, bro? Get on with your life. But
somebody reacting to you. Do you
understand what I'm saying? You know,
nobody that's happy with their life sits
on YouTube and tries to [ __ ] with
someone all day, every day. It doesn't
take Einstein to work this [ __ ] out.
Why do you think I don't reply to them?
Um, most of the time cuz I can't be
bothered, bro. It's just same keyboard
warrior [ __ ] I gain nothing and you
know, I'm not in a relationship. So, for
somebody to be in a relationship and
claim they've got all this and claim
they've got all that, there's got to be
some deep rooted jealousy somewhere or
you just want to waste your life away on
somebody that you're apparently better
than every day. So, let's really think
about which one is the more logical. Is
it the fact that he's jealous of
something or he's not jealous of
something and would agree with you and
the fact that he just wants to spend all
day every day [ __ ] with somebody
whilst apparently he's got all this
money and his life is perfect but he
wastes all day [ __ ] with me.
See, it doesn't make sense, does it?
Come on. We're all adults here, you
know? We can all have our opinion here.
Cuz at least if you admit you're
jealous, it won't make you seem like a
[ __ ] [ __ ] Because the alternative
doesn't make sense. The alternative does
not make no sense whatsoever.
You understand, bro? It doesn't. It It doesn't. Cuz
cuz my life's not perfect. I don't I
don't claim that my life's perfect, but
I don't do half the [ __ ] these people do on it, you know?
So they're not even like moaning or
complaining. They're actually [ __ ]
with people on here. That's the thing,
bro. That's the thing. So,
and I've and I've come off and No, I'm
not mentioning, bro. I'm just using as
an example, bro. I mention him very
rarely, but I'm using it as an example.
We're having a renewal here. It shows
that he is definitely jealous of
something. Oh, his life is [ __ ] you know.
you know. Yeah, he'll never stop. That's
what Yeah, I know he'll never stop.
That's fine, bro. I don't I don't mind.
He's jealous of something. It's obvious.
No, no, no, no, no. He will never stop.
He will never ever ever stop. No, no,
no, no, no. He will never stop. Listen,
this whole these people, if you Let me
talk. This whole these people do this
for reaction, it it doesn't wash
anymore. They don't do it for reaction.
And how I know this is because even if
you don't react to these people, they
would still do it. It's not about a
reaction. That is far long gone. That
excuse. It's not about reactions
because, you know, it's it's not about a reaction.
Um, it really really isn't because even
if you don't react to them, they will
still do it. Like, and I'm I'm prepared
to prove that to you if you want.
No, I'm not giving him everything he
wants. I'm telling everyone how much of
a sad [ __ ] he is. What? So that's
everything you want. Okay. And then
after I stop doing that, then what?
Okay. So I'm telling everyone that
you're jealous that I can approach women
and I can speak to women on WhatsApp.
Okay. And then then what? So you got
what you want. Okay. And
and then what? Okay.
I don't understand. And and what?
See, it doesn't make any sense. So,
so you so you will [ __ ] with somebody
every day just to get a five minute
reaction every 6 months.
Do you not see that as a bit strange?
Cuz I don't message USA. I don't [ __ ]
with anyone she knows. I don't do
anything like that. That's like me
[ __ ] with her until
[ __ ] until she reacts with me every day.
Why Why would I want that? You know what
I'm saying? I'm not sure. I'm going to
cook some bacon in a bit though. I'm a
bit hungry now.
So, if you're obsessed with somebody,
you would do it. Reaction or no
reaction? So, these people are obsessed.
It is weird.
It is weird. It is very weird.
It is strange.
So when that Ricky Mill apparently it's
not that serious, but it is that serious
because you write [ __ ] every day on your boyfriend's channel. Right. And
yeah, you write [ __ ] on your [ __ ]
on your boyfriend's channel and then
it's very serious to you to to be doing
this. You know,
it's a madness, isn't it? It's a [ __ ] madness, man.
I did find it funny, bro. Like some of this [ __ ]
They got some nice smoked piggies.
I ain't had smoke bacon in ages to be fair, man.
You know, even this guy is replying to um
Tiger Tiger. Yeah, I think the ones that
are thumbs up in Ricky are trolls and
then the ones that's So, he's got five thumbs up,
right? He's got um
So, he's got No, he's got three thumbs
up cuz one of them is me and Ricky's got
five. So, a lot of people agree with
this guy. I see what you mean. They
should have told you first. They didn't
want to take things further to you in to
you in advance instead of them
prolonging it. And your texts are very
polite, too. That is good. There's no
making excuses. There's it's just that
that is that is the truth. Yeah. It's
that's where we're at. So, that is that
is genuine. That's why I got three
thumbs up for if you include me. I had
to thumbs that up. So,
Um, no. There go. Oh, Yeah,
Ricky got bodied. So, yeah, the fact
that this guy got three thumbs up, I
think there is people that do agree with me.
I see what you mean now. I mean, you've
only just seen what I mean now, Tiger. I
mean, this has been going on [ __ ]
years, bro. you know, like at the end of the day. Um,
I don't know.
Yeah, I don't even give a [ __ ] about sex
anymore, to be honest, bro. That's why I
don't use escorts. I can't be annoyed with it.
I thought I'd be bothered
fixing this part for that.
But yeah, it seems that Tiger still goes
on my channel, but he doesn't go my live stream. Strange.
I might go out on my birthday, but can't see it.
I can't see it to be fair.
I don't even I don't even have a sex
drive anymore, bro. I just I can't be
bothered. I can't be [ __ ]
I really can't be bothered with it, man. [ __ ]
You think I'll ever drink again? I don't
know. You know,
I don't drink anymore. No.
Don't know why.
Dude, you just get used to being by yourself, man.
So, I don't really care anymore.
What did you think of the messages
trying to [ __ ] w me up?
Yeah, pretty much. I could go on my birthday, but
there's just no point. You're never
going to meet anyone.
I need to change at this age now. I need
to leave, bro. I need to really um
get out of here, bro. You know what I'm saying? Yeah,
like I said, I got I got off from the
last time I went out and I spent
that5600 pound, but put me off. Then I
won the money back and I was like, I
don't want to do it again. But [ __ ] that.
Yeah, this Ricky's a troll, man. I
thought he was actually being serious,
but he's just a [ __ ] troll.
Three people liked Tiger's message,
so they must have been agreeing with me. So yeah.
Yeah, but I don't understand how he can
believe that when he's he's an idiot, bro.
cuz it's like half people agreeing with
me then half people agreeing with him.
But I don't understand how they can
agree with him when these women have
actually agreed to meet me. That's what
where his argument [ __ ] up because he's
saying that I'm coming on. Okay. So if
I'm coming off as weird and desperate,
right? Why are these women giving you
their number, loving your messages, and
then agreeing to meet you? Does that not
make sense to you? It doesn't make
sense. if you was coming across weird,
they wouldn't even reply back, let alone
agree to meet you. So that's why that's where he's
um arguing seems to fall flat on his
ass. You know what I'm saying? So that's it.
And also this is the bit that says also
none stop asking them to meet you when
you don't know them.
Yeah, you can. Yeah, but okay. Okay. Okay. But
I don't understand how he's saying that
I of desperation. So why did these women
agree to meet me?
And he says that I'm loving their
messages, but they were loving my messages.
So it's it that's not even an opinion.
And then he says sending voice notes
after all meeting once. I mean, you
don't need to meet someone 26 times
before sending somebody a voicemail.
It that doesn't make sense.
And why is it okay?
Um, no. The reason I'm calling him a
troll is cuz he's not reading what I wrote.
No, I'm not saying that he's a troll for
that. I'm I'm saying that he's a troll
because he's not reading my response.
That's why if you agree, you agree. If
you disagree, you disagree. I mean, I've
only got three people that agree with me.
They don't even like me. So [ __ ] at
the end of the day, right,
you're having your opinion, but you're
also dismissing a lot of the other
messages what they've done.
Why are you dismissing what they've done?
So that's it. Like,
so you're coming across as weird and
desperate, yet they're messaging you
back, loving your messages, and agreeing
to meet you. So, what happened within
the last couple of hours then?
What what what happened?
Cuz if if they don't message you,
they've got an argument. They can say,
"Oh, yeah, you come across as weird or
they gave you their number to get away."
And they could very much use that
argument and to that you wouldn't have
any sort of defense or, you know, even
if they say, "Oh, I don't want to take
things further straight away." They
could argue you've done something wrong,
but when they constantly keep messaging
you back, loving your messages, agreeing
to meet you, you've got no argument with
them ones. You generally generally
generally [ __ ] don't,
you know, like he was he would have been
better off saying the ones that didn't
reply to you, you acted weird and that's
why they didn't reply to you because
we wouldn't be able to argue with that, you know.
So then by your own admission, you would
be admitting that they're leading me on
then. So if I'm acting weird and they're
messaging me, agreeing to meet me, you
would then say that what they're leading me on.
You're not you won't win, bro. You
really won't win.
Because if you're wrong, if you're if
you're right on something, I'll say that
you're right on something. It's not a problem.
And I said to him about that woman in California, right?
We met, we agreed to meet,
right? I [ __ ] owned him in it. He got
[ __ ] bro. I Okay, so then, right, so
that woman in California, right, said
she was going to meet me,
you know, said she was going to meet me,
right? Listen, listen.
Said that he was going to said she was
going to meet me. Yeah. And she said she
had a great time with me. Yet on when we
were supposed to be meeting, she said
that she's getting back with her ex.
Ricky didn't say anything about this
one. You understand? So, he's he's
dismissed a lot of the ones where he
knew he was wrong on. You understand?
Maybe, bro. Maybe if they were genuine.
But he's he's if he's given his opinion,
why has he dismissed 90% of the messages?
Because it doesn't suit his narrative
and he knew he would have lost. That's
why you understand. He knew that,
you know, why didn't we hear about the
other ones? Why did these women agree to
meet if I'm so weird? Why do they love
my message? Why can't I love their
message when they can love my message?
There's a lot of unanswered questions here.
If he's definitely not a troll, he
should be able to answer these ones then
because he says that I'm loving their
messages. Uh they loved my messages
before I love their messages. So
he is strange. He is strange.
I mean, who do you think won the
argument? me or him. I don't care if
people disagree with me.
No one get they just just don't dismiss
dismiss things that don't suit you. you know,
he had some points. Okay. So,
okay then. So, why is it okay for them
to love my messages and they I can't
love their messages? Why is it that
these women have agreed to meet me if
I'm so weird?
I mean, answer the questions. You know,
you you know, we're all up for a debate.
You know, I'm going over some of the
things he says off my heart, right?
Like, at the end of the day,
uh he's saying that I'm loving their
messages and that's a problem, but they
they were loving my messages.
So, what what's wrong with loving
someone's messages? I don't understand. Um,
he doesn't he doesn't have a valid
point. He doesn't have a valid point.
Because if he had a valid point, they
wouldn't agree to meet you.
That's why he doesn't have a valid
point. Because why are these women
agreeing to meet you if you're weird?
Do you not get me? Think about it,
right? You approach a woman, right? And
she thinks you're weird. You message
her, she's not going to reply. She's not
going to reply and agree to meet you.
Why has she agreed to meet you?
And you're gone. So, he doesn't he
doesn't have any fights. Also,
I was going to bring up cold approaches,
but that's that's changing the subject.
would I'd rather stick to the subject
cuz I'm proving him to be wrong.
That's the thing. Like I am proving him
to be wrong. That's the thing.
Okay. So, what I'm asking is why are
they allowed to love my messages but I'm
not allowed to love their messages? If
I'm so weird, why have they agreed to
meet me then? I'm I'm I'm I'm curious as
to why why does it happen? You know,
he doesn't have valid points. He doesn't
have no valid points.
I don't need to ask them because I
already know the answer. You know, I'm
asking you. You know, it's
what he's saying don't make sense. You
know, there's been approaches where I've
approached a woman and she's not even
given me the chance. What's wrong with
this society, right, is
they hate to admit that women have got
unrealistic standards. This is what the
problem is. This is where this problem
comes into it, you know, because I I bro
because I want to know if you know the
answer. This is what the problem is.
This is very much the problem. And yes,
men men do as well. Men do the same.
Well, they don't do the same thing
because their standards are just high.
They're not unrealistic. People don't
want to admit that women have got unrealistic standards.
You know, that's that's what the problem
very much is. And they try to sugarcoat
it by saying, "Oh, uh, well, you got a
bad personality and t this is what
happens, bro." You know, Paley, but I
mean, does Paley have standards?
Um, well, you're talking about [ __ ]
stinking slags that nobody would get with.
So, I mean,
and I'm pretty sure there's people that
Natalie G haven't got with, but I mean,
you're talking about slaggy, dreggy,
ugly women. I mean, that's a bit
different, you know? That's a bit
different. Okay. Okay. Sorry, let me
rephrase that. Okay. Average women,
right? Someone that's like a five out of
10. Yeah. And to be honest with you, I
would say Katie does have standards. She
only went with Rice to piss Monty off. I
mean, she would never get with me even
though I don't like her. I mean, I think
she only done that because, you know,
to piss Monty off. I mean, she would
never get with me even though I don't like her. Um,
average is like uh
I don't know.
Not USA, is he? She's below average. Uh,
maybe that Brazilian one that I kissed. Justin, okay,
let me ask this to Ricky, right?
So, you know how you say that about
women? Um, it's weird and stuff, right?
Uh, now I've got a video on this channel
that's unlisted where I have gone to try
to meet a woman, speak to a woman, and
she's like, "I'm not interested in
getting to know anyone or meeting
anyone." That was lit. She didn't even
let me finish my sentence. I mean, I can
put it up if you want. It was when I was
in the cinema. I put it up. I was like,
"Oh, let me go and approach this woman.
I'm not interested in getting to know
anybody or knowing anyone."
What was the excuse that time? I mean,
I've literally got it where I've tried
to approach a woman on a train station
and her first word was, "I'm not interested."
You see what we're trying to say here
when you're trying to say about how it's
people u people's personality and stuff
and it's just it seems like it's very
very very much a cover up uh because
they've got unrealistic standards and
they don't want to they don't want women
being um made to seem like they're wrong.
And I have got videos where I've
approached women and they've said
straight away they're not interested. So
would that kind of contradict everything
that you're saying since we're having a debate?
I've already given up, bro. I'm done.
Like I'm leaving.
So would that not kind of contradict
everything that you're saying?
Cuz they didn't get to know me, my personality, nothing.
I mean, it's not a zero success rate, is
it? I wouldn't say it's a zero success rate,
you know, and Yeah, that's it.
No, I I don't want you to agree with me.
If you want to disagree, you can
disagree. I'm just asking him, bro. If
you want to disagree, disagree with me.
I don't mind. You're not going to get
blocked. I'm a big boy. I can take it.
>> No, I've been with women. I've been on
dates with women. I've been with women,
but come on. I've had one that stands.
But yeah, I just wanted to say that to Ricky.
I've got some approaches where Yeah,
I've where they've not even given me the chance.
So, what what was that time then, Ricky? Like, yeah.
Maybe I should put them up for Ricky.
There's a lot of women that you will
just go and speak to them and they'll
say straight away, you're not
interested. They'll just dismiss you
straight away without even looking at you. So,
I think we need to stop lying to people
at this point, you know? Um,
one I can tell you how many one night
stands I've had. I mean, I've got a
[ __ ] in an alleyway as well. I can
tell you actually. One, two, three. One second. USA, Izzy, Manchester again.
Five one night stands.
Five. Got blowj. No, no, no, no. More
than that. Six. Just a 19y old. 1 2 3 4 5 six.
Yeah, I've been with six people that
weren't escorts. That's not bad. That is
still pretty like
it's higher than a normal woman's body
count I'd say
blow job anyway and obviously I fingered
people and stuff.
Yeah, six I've been with six people.
Sorry I had to calculate that. That's
gone over my head. Yeah.
Yeah. six on 28. Yeah,
that's how it is, right it?
I just try to see the positives. I just
try to see it as like
I try to see it as I've been with women,
you know, like so
I just try and see the positives even
though it's hard to, you know, but yeah.
Nope. I'm not going to any of them
places. It's full of English people. But
what I think the problem is honestly,
yeah, I don't think I'm ugly, you know?
I think everyone that's not a troll can
agree with that. I think it's cuz I
don't look like I'm fully white. I think
that is the problem, bro. Like, I
generally generally generally do.
That's what I think it is. Um,
that's what I think it is. Well,
personality doesn't matter unless they
already accept you or give you the
chance. Until they do that, personality
doesn't come into it.
Again, you need to get through their
looks. You need to get through that unrealistic threshold.
No, no, no, no, no. Being not ugly is
not good enough. Being decent looking is
not good enough for them. It might seem
good enough for you. It might seem good
enough for me, but that's not good
enough to them. A woman would reject you
basically because you don't have a beard
or because you have a beard.
So, it's it's not good looking might be
enough for you and good looking might be
enough on me, but it's not how I'm
talking to them.
So, it's it's not even just looks. It's
not even just looks. It's their it's
their preference. If you're not their
preference, they won't they won't get with you.
So, it's not it's not even just that.
It's it's it's ethnicity and their
preference as well. It's not even just
that. Like, okay, let me give you an example. Yeah.
Yes, it's looks. But what I'm saying is
even if you're good-looking, they're
still not going to give you a chance. I
can make myself good-look and I try and
speak to someone and they say straight
away, I'm not interested. Okay, I'll
give you an example, right? Say there's
a woman, let me give you an example. Let
me give you this analogy. And she likes
a guy with brown hair, blue eyes,
um, and a bit of stubble. And I try my
best to look the best I possibly can.
She won't get with me. She won't even
give me the chance. That's what I mean
by their unrealistic standards.
So that's what I'm saying. So you could
be good-looking and and and still, you
know what I'm saying?
And that's what the problem generally
generally generally is. Don't Don't get
me wrong, I [ __ ] up a few times. I'm
not saying I'm perfect. I I [ __ ] up a
few times, you know. I could have been
in relationships and stuff. Don't get me
wrong, but I'm saying that most of the
time that is what it is.
Cuz if you go on a dating app, right, and you
you use a white guy, Yeah. he will get
more success than me. Somebody else
fully white. You know what I'm saying?
But me, I I'll get [ __ ] off. It's
strange. It is strange. Yeah. Nope. 510.
Oh, that's another thing. Height as well.
So, it is their standards. Definitely
definitely is their unrealistic standards
thanks to Simpsons and White Knights. Well,
it's not really them. It's social media,
isn't it? That's allow them to be able
to do that. But really, we we need to
blame the people that made [ __ ] Tik
Tok and dating apps and [ __ ] Yeah. So yeah.
So that's how it is. Yeah.
Yeah, they got unrealistic standards.
Simple. And the last time I went out
approaching, I was super confident as
well. Super confident.
Yes, men have standards, but they don't
have unrealistic standards. And do you
want me to know? Do you want me to prove
how I'm Do you want me to tell you how I
know? cuz I put a dating profile up as
an average woman and she's got 5,000
likes. I put pictures up of me and I
don't get any matches.
Um, read into what you will. Did you see
my response to Ricky Millington?
Millington. Um, Joe, if you haven't,
I'll read it out to you. I done a little
message to him. I'm very good at reading
and I want you to give your um opinion
on it. I'm into this [ __ ] you know,
like writing and and stuff. Yeah. I've
done a fake profile of a woman and she
got 5,000 likes and I can't even get a likes.
Yeah. It says it all. So, Joe, can I can
I can cuz you're an impartial party.
Okay. I'm going to read it to you. Yeah. No distractions, right? So,
Let me read this to you. It will take a
minute and you can tell me what Oh,
[ __ ] You can tell me what you think,
bro. I'm good at reading unlike Monty.
Right. Let me ban this guy for a sec cuz
he's going to put us up. So, here's the
thing. Yeah. Right. You still there
before I read this?
Even then he says in the end when he
lost that it's not that serious.
So you still there before I read this?
Yeah. I really want to read it out to
you because I've I've done this myself.
So he said
he said just read through some messages
and you of desperation. loving the
messages asking what they like about
you, saying you'll go to their city,
sending voice notes all after meeting
once. You are too full on. It's
massively offputting to women. That's
partly why you won't meet why they won't
meet you. It's the way you're acting.
Also, non-stop asking to meet them when
you don't know them. You have no game,
PJ. That's your problem. And this is not
a dig, just facts. I replied saying, "I
replied to your message on a video, but
in case you can't be bothered to watch
it all, I'll be nice and reply here." I
think that I've read in quotation mark
some messages pretty much sums up my
argument. You seem to dismiss the ones
that didn't reply to the first message.
You also dismiss the ones where they
replied back once. I asked them a
question and I never heard from them
ever again. How about the one who
admitted to having a great time with me
and was still up for meeting then hit me
3 hours before meeting with I'm sorry
I'm going to give it another go with my
ex. What was the excuse there Ricky? So
the I quote some was you picking out the
few that you thought you were right on
and the others you dismissed because
they didn't suit your narrative in
quotation mark loving their messages. I
wrote as I mentioned in my previous
video in brackets in case you haven't
seen it. I would strongly advise you
getting your eyes tested if you haven't
done so already because how did you
manage to dismiss the fact they were
loving my messages more than I was
loving theirs? Going by your logic if in
quotation mark loving someone's message
on WhatsApp is a big problem would that
not make the women who love my messages
the problem since they're doing the same
if some even love my messages and I
never love theirs. So, by your logic,
it's okay for women to love my messages,
but if I do it back, it justifies them
being toxic, leading me on and it being
a me problem. You never address the
women that loved my first message first.
Do tell us all about it. So, do tell us
all about what you thought about it. I'm curious
in quotation asking what they like about
you saying you'll go to their city and
sending voice notes all after meeting
once. You are too full on and that's
partly why they won't meet you. It's the
way you're acting. Then my reply to that
what I quoted. Now, as I stated
previously, this goes back to the I
quotation mark some messages. But to be
honest, it's less than 10%. I said that
to one to two women maximum. What about
the rest that dismissed
domest the rest you dismissed that
involved none of the things you're
mentioning? Also, you might want to
retake ge geography lessons because
Finland is a country, not a a I
quotation mark city. Last time I
checked, so what? I met a woman from
Finland. We was talking for a month, so
I suggested going to see her. Big deal.
Question. Why are you not allowed to
send someone voice notes? Because you've
only met them once. Is this some kind of
new rule you've made up? Pretty sure
people send voice notes all the time to
people they haven't even met.
That's partly why they won't meet you
because of how you're acting. Then I replied,
"Now, I'm not sure if you remember, but
I approach women in public, bars, clubs.
I've never been one for online dating.
So, if I'm approaching them and they
reply and agree to meet me and love my
messages in brackets the the thing you
called me out for, I would have guessed
I came across as normal since why give
me their number, reply, loved my
message, and then agreed to meet me. I'm
sure if I was acting desperate and being
off-putting, they wouldn't bother even
replying in the first place, which ruins
your whole argument. Then also then I
was like also non-stop asking to meet
them when you don't know them. I would
advise you to learn the concept of
non-stop. Asking a woman out twice is
hardly non-stop. I don't need to know
the ins and out about someone because I
asked them on a date twice. It's like
when people have a problem with you
trying to meet a woman after a week of
speaking to her and claiming it's too
soon yet have no problem with a woman
wanting to meet someone straight away
without even knowing anything about
them. Brackets personal experience. USA
is other people t and you have no game
PJ this is not a dig just facts and then
I wrote hm well considering I don't have
to rely on dating apps and can approach
women and get them to reply I would bet
that's more than most men can do in
brackets including yourself am I lying
if not please do sure show me how it's
done I'd love to learn from the best
then the last bit was also before I
finish this I just wanted to say,
"Please learn the definition of facts."
Facts is something that is set in stone.
In fact, let me pull up a quote from
yours a while back. You're good-looking,
PJ. Women are too picky. That's why you
can't pull, which very much sums of sums
up everything you saying as being
anything but facts. You can't play two
sides of a coin. Hold that L. They got
[ __ ] ruined. I mean, what what the
[ __ ] can you say to that? Seriously,
what can you say to that?
What the [ __ ] can you say to that?
Nothing. You got ruined, mate. [ __ ] ruined.
Which is something them seven [ __ ]
thumbs up won't [ __ ] tell you
cuz that's that's that in it, you know,
that is that
you're [ __ ] you got bodied, mate. What
the [ __ ] can you say to that? I don't
need to I don't need to delete nothing.
You got ruined, mate. Absolutely ruined.
Absolutely [ __ ] ruined, mate. So,
yeah. Who's going to who's going to pay
for this guy's funeral, mate? Cuz he got wrecked.
So, the thing is, Joe, right, if he
turned around and said, "Oh, the ones
that didn't reply to you, you made them
feel uncomfortable. They gave their
number to get away from you. He'd have
an argument and you wouldn't really be
able to convince him that you're right.
I mean, yeah, they gave your number, but
they could have they could have done it
to get away from you. You understand? So
that that then he would win. But
obviously where they're replying back to
you, they're loving your messages, doing
the very thing that they're saying not
to do, and they're agreeing to meet you.
It's going to be hard to get out of that
one by saying, "Oh, you're acting
weird." So, because you're acting weird,
they're leading you on and agreeing to
meet you yet not meeting you. So, at the
very least, they're leading you on, right,
mate? It doesn't make sense. Really,
really does not make sense. And trust
me, if I thought I was wrong, I would
say I'm wrong.
Like, you're not going to, you know, he
he he could have he could have easily
had me by the balls if he said about,
you know, the ones that didn't reply
back. I mean, think of this, Joe.
There's this guy, right? He's called
Tiger Tiger. Not the tiger that I
fighted. And he said to me, "Uh, I see
what you mean now. They should have told
you first that they didn't want to take
things further to you in advance instead
of prolonging it. And your texts are
very polite, too." That got three thumbs
up, four if you include me. So, these
are people that don't even like me that
are saying this.
So, it's I don't care about thumbs up. I
don't care who's against me. I don't
need to block anyone. I'll stand my
ground. Simple. So, yeah, that's it. Cuz
you got [ __ ] wrecked. There's nothing
you can say. You're not coming back from
that, bro. Unless you want to pick out
other [ __ ] messages.
Um, so yeah, you you got [ __ ] in the ass.
No, but do you get my point? Do you get
my point? Okay, Joe, if you're if you're
acting weird and you're coming across as
weird, right? Why have these women gave
you their number? replied to you, loved
your message, and agreed to meet you.
That is not the acts of somebody that is
weirded out. Do you understand?
So, and also for a fun fun fact, right?
Would you class USA Izzy as working out
or not working out? Would you class that
as a success? There's a reason why I'm
asking you this. I mean, would you class
that as something that worked out better
than um the other ones? You know,
and also I could have showed him other
things, but that's kind of changing the
subject and I wanted to stick on the
subject. I can show him messages, right?
No, not messages. I can show him
approaches where I've tried to approach
a woman and she's not even let me finish my sentence.
That would [ __ ] up your argument as
well. You know, I I've had it I've got a
video on this channel right now that's
unlisted where I have tried to speak to
a woman and she said straight away, "I'm
not interested in meeting anyone or
getting to know anyone before I'd even
finish my sentence." So,
and I'd love to see you talk your way
out of that one.
And also, you're saying about how asking
somebody if they like you is weird. I
asked USA Izzy, "What do you like about
me?" and I got sex. Would that not ruin
your argument? Okay. Yeah. They went
back to their country and they [ __ ]
off, but I got them. I got their body.
Let's just say if you done that every
week, we could class that as some sort
of success. So, I can ask one woman
something that would work. But I can't
ask. It doesn't Your argument doesn't
Your argument don't make sense. The only
argument you have is they gave you the
number to get away from you and that's
why they didn't reply to you cuz you
found you know what I'm saying? That's
the only that's the only thing that they
could say with their messages. I'm
giving them suggestions.
You know what I'm saying? It's it's mad. You know,
I can show you the approach if you want
me to. It was from a few years ago, but
it's an example. It's happened a few
times. You know, you tried to speak to
someone and they said straight away,
"I'm not interested. I don't want to
know. Uh, I'm not interested in knowing anyone."
Now, if you put on Reddit, they'd call
you an incel, you know,
which is um which obviously contradicts
what they're saying because they're
saying that women go for personality.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. But that
doesn't really make a lot of sense, you know?
So, that's it.
And also, why have you dismissed 90% of
the other messages as well? That's another thing, you know. So, yeah.
And he and he took a big L in the end
because he also contradicted what he
said. So, is it women are too picky or
is it the way that I'm acting? Because
you can't play two sides of a coin.
That's the point of heads or tails, you know,
and that's it. So, yeah,
I put some good messages out there.
I put some really good messages out
there as well.
See, the thing is these people don't
know anything. If they they wouldn't
last a day approaching women. They
wouldn't last a day. Uh
to him as well. I said quotation mark
took it I said took it serious. Not at
all. just pointing out where you're
wrong. Aren't you the one non-stop
talking about me on your boyfriend's
channel? Yeah, when someone puts you in
your place, they're taking it too
serious. I I loved writing that
paragraph. I was I was I I was almost
having a wank whilst [ __ ] writing it.
It's [ __ ] lush cuz it's the truth,
you know? It is the [ __ ] truth.
You can you can ask a woman to meet you
a couple of times if you don't know her.
Okay. What? So what if you don't know
them? You know what the [ __ ] Don't tell
a woman to stop meeting men for casual
sex cuz they don't know them. You know
what's your opinion on a woman going to
a club and [ __ ] somebody within 5
minutes that they don't know?
No. But do you see my points though? No.
There is more to life. But do you not
understand my point?
You know, if you readed if you if you if
you [ __ ] if if you weirded a woman
out, just stop making excuses for them.
You know, it's not like I couldn't have
been wrong in every single one of them
messages. There's no way I could have
been wrong in every single one of them. So
if if I was given an unbiased opinion on myself
reading them messages, I would say that
the ones that replied back were in the
wrong because they've led you on bit
like what Tiger Tiger said. And the ones
that didn't reply, you could have
possibly done something wrong, said
something wrong, acted weird.
That's what I would have said. I would
have targeted the ones that didn't reply
more because they would have a valid
argument with that one. They can't say
that you're weirding women out that are
agreeing to meet you. That doesn't make
any sense. And saying that I've loved
their messages when they've loved mine.
That's weird. That is [ __ ] weird,
bro. And then you're saying I'm taking
things serious cuz I've literally ripped
you apart in my last message. Come on,
bro. It's not serious to me. I'm I'm I'm
calm, man. I don't mind. I'm going to
make some piggies in a bit because um
cuz if you come across in a bad way,
people wouldn't reply and they certainly
wouldn't agree to meet you.
We need to stop acting like women don't
have unrealistic standards the same way
men do. We need to really really really
stop sugar coating this [ __ ]
No, bro. Um just replying to some guy,
about he was trying to critique some of
the things I done and I replied to him.
Completely wrecked him, bro. Completely wrecked him.
I'm not deleting any
I don't care about your thumbs up. I'm
not blocking anyone, bro.
What I find mad is why you'd get eight
thumbs up even though I've shown where
they've led me on. That's the That's the
bit. But again, I don't give a [ __ ] to
be honest with you because I know them
three people that agreed with me on some
other person's thing is genuine. I mean,
not to be weird or rude, but when was
the last time these people have probably
left their house,
you know? It's like
It's strange, man. Like, it is weird. It's weird.
I mean, at this point, Joe, there's no
point even really getting into any kind
of debate, is it? Because I've shown
what I can. You know, I've tried more
than anyone in the world, and they still
they still sit there and they will
always sit there and take the blame off
of women. This is something that we need
to accept and just don't get into any debates
with anyone. I think that's that's it.
in the future, in the near future.
Cuz if I'm wrong and they want to say
that I'm wrong, but you can't have been
wrong every time. Just like I'm sure
they could have been wrong any time.
Every time. You understand what I'm
saying? It's it's
it's strange. You've met someone,
they've agreed to meet you, they backed out.
What the [ __ ] I don't get it. I
seriously don't get these people, man.
But that tiger tiger, that guy was genuine.
Uh, no, bro. I don't have him today.
He's not actually my dog.
It's like USA is, you know, I'm not I'm
not saying every single thing that she
was saying about me was wrong. She
exaggerated it, but exaggerated it. Um,
but at the end of the day, the way she
went about it was the wrong way.
You know what I'm trying to say? Now,
I'll give you an example, right? Um,
there's this woman from Italy, right? I
tell you, and and this woman, I actually
thought she was a narcissist cuz, um,
I tell you what happened, right,
quickly. Um, cuz I was on this message.
I didn't put the message up.
Um, so this is an example, right? So I
approached her and I was her tour I was
her tour guide for like an hour, two
hours. Nothing sexual, not trying to
kiss, didn't drink. We just walked
around and spoke about things and ret
um showed her around the Eminem shop.
Um, and then she gave me a number. Now I
I didn't think anything was going to
happen. I didn't want anything to
happen. Then I've messaged her the next
day and then she's not replied, which I
thought was a bit a bit tunty really.
You know, when you when you spend that
amount of time with someone and they
can't even reply back, especially when
you're not expecting anything. And then
as soon as I wrote a negative message,
she was like, "Oh, sorry I didn't reply
back to your message sooner." And I'm
thinking, you was never going to reply
back to my message. It's been 3 months.
It was a bit rude into when nobody was
expecting anything. And then she was
like, "Oh, um, I didn't want to lead you one." Ret.
I mean, if you replied that you wasn't
looking for anybody, considering you
lived in another country, and granted
you didn't lead anyone on, I'm pretty
sure people would have been okay with
it. And then throughout the whole
paragraph, she was just trying to
victimize herself. Um, it's weird. It's
very, very weird. She was just trying to
victimize herself throughout the whole
and I'm thinking, yeah, I mean, when I
approached you first, you you probably
did feel uncomfortable cuz I would feel
uncomfortable. But then as time went on,
you surely understood that nobody was
going to take your phone. They got your
number and they they had good intentions
in the end. So, I just don't She was a
proper narcissist. She was. You could
tell by what she was writing. You know,
it's like they always have to try to
victimize themsel. It's like, you know,
you just replied like a normal person. I
mean, yeah, you might have not, you
know, you might have not owed anyone
anything, but it would have took 5 seconds.
I mean, I'm just using examples like
[ __ ] that people have to go through with
these women. You know, you was never
going to reply back ever. Don't say
about you replying back sooner. You was
never going to reply. Why are you trying
to victimize yourself? It's ridiculous.
Um, and then she's saying, "Oh, I didn't
feel the connection." I'm thinking,
"Huh? I just I wrote one message to you.
You lived in a different [ __ ]
country. I don't think anything was
going to I don't think I was expecting
to [ __ ] go to Italy." You know what
I'm saying? So, it's kind of like it's
it's if you are honest with somebody,
then that's fine. That's people would
rather somebody I don't know about
everyone but I'd rather someone be
honest than tell a load of [ __ ] tell
a load of lies and it's just that that
example was really [ __ ] because if if
you meet somebody in a bar in a club and
they don't reply I mean that's it's not
as bad cuz we just pull it down to like
they're they're drunk and they just
can't be bothered whatever. Um, and
obviously they're drunk. But when
someone's not drunk and you spent time
with them and they can't even reply,
it's a bit rude, isn't it? I mean, let's
let's be fair, Joe.
So, I don't have a type of woman,
whatever I like. But you know what?
Yeah. And there is more to life than
women. And and and and having these
debates is [ __ ] pointless because Yeah. It's Yeah. So,
but like USA is the way she went the way
she went about things
was weird. Very very weird. since we
want to bring up examples. I mean, you
didn't you didn't contact me or address
me personally stating that you had an
issue, you know, and you know what I
find so weird about women, Joe? Yeah. Is
you know when you go on a date, right,
and they they claim that it's like they
give up on the first sight of
disappointment instead of just like
giving things a little bit more time to
see if things will work. They give up at
like any kind of disappointment, they're
like, "Nope, that's that's done." Like
that's that is another thing that I find
is is [ __ ] up. Like they
like if they go on a date with you and
then within 10 20 seconds they claim
they don't feel the vibe. I mean,
feelings grow. People change. People can
go from not liking people to liking
someone. So they don't really even give
stuff a chance.
They give up on the first sign of
disappointment. It's weird. It is weird.
That That's another thing I noticed. No,
it's weird. It is weird.
But yeah, I'm at that stage now anyways,
Joe. I don't give a [ __ ] like
if I meet someone or not. I don't even
have a sex drive anymore. So [ __ ]
maybe I've just had so many [ __ ] up
experiences and this is why I can't
relate, you know?
But do you not understand that that
Italian woman, she was [ __ ] That was
that was just country because it's like
you you've done everything to victimize yourself
when you knew in the end that someone
had good intentions. I mean that that
was that was [ __ ] up. So
they're just um
um yeah, they give up at the same
they they they give up at the first sign of disappointment. Um
like like one of the dates I went on,
she was like 32 and I acted normal. We
we had similar interest and then she was
like, "Oh." And I said, "When when are
we meeting again?" and say, "I don't
really feel the vibe." And I'm thinking,
"So, what you're going to give up at the
first sign of disappointment? I don't I
don't know what what more they want you
to do other than what you're already
doing." So, it just it just I don't I
don't get it. I don't get it at all. Um,
but yeah, I've had so many [ __ ] up
experiences. This is why I can't I can't
be one of these people that lick women's asses.
You know, maybe if I did meet so many
women, maybe I'd agree. But I can't
agree with somebody that's had my
experiences. You can't agree with with
with with these with these people. Um,
and I'm pretty sure you wouldn't either,
even if you didn't care, cuz I know what
they're like. I've met so many women.
Like, how many women do you think I've met
in my life? How many do you think I've
met? I've probably met more than
probably more than anybody my my age. I
mean, I don't know. I don't know. I've
met a lot I've met a lot of people, bro. So,
I can't see the good in them. I really, really can't.
But what I will say, Joe, is Non Legs is
still very jealous of me speaking to
other women. Have you clocked on that on
his channel? Um, he's very, very
obsessed with me speaking to other women.
This is weird. I clicked on it cuz one
of the comments popped up. So, I clicked
on the channel just to well, let me see.
And yeah, he's very, very jealous of
people speaking to other women. No one
else does this. No. Red Star, Pat
Mustard never used to do it. He's very,
very jealous of anyone being able to
meet new women. Like even though
somebody like they they said they were
going to meet and they never, I think
it's more the fact that you are capable
of going out and meeting women and
actually getting their numbers.
Something that he can't do cuz believe
it or not, it's a normal thing to me,
but most men can't do it. Most men
wouldn't be able to go out and get
women's numbers and get them to reply
back. That is a it is even though it
seems nothing to me, it is that is a big
thing. You know, most people wouldn't be
able to do that.
um especially by themsel. So he he
doesn't like the fact that you can go
out and meet women. He doesn't like I
don't know what it is. It it is weird
though. Like really really it is. It is.
And and it ain't for reaction cuz no one
else it generally you can see that bro
it's not just been with a couple of
people. He's done it with a he's done it
with a lot of people.
I don't know why he he he he
why he does that.
I think he's not happy in his
relationship and he definitely doesn't get sex,
Joe. Like I'm trying to think what it
could be why somebody would be jealous
of someone else meeting other women.
It's so weird.
Very very very very strange individual.
No one, no one else acts like that.
Nobody else acts like that, bro. I'm
telling you. No one does. No one else
does. No Red Star, no Pat. No,
nobody, bro. No one cares. If I meet
women, no one cares.
No, it's not a reaction. No, it's not a
reaction. Cuz even if you don't give
them a reaction, they still do it. So,
you can't even use that as an excuse.
And he is the only one that does it.
No. No. No. No, no, no, no, no. He is
the owner with that. That is that is
something wrong, bro. Like all of the
other things he's trying to do to piss
you off, but that that is genu that is
genuine. He used to do it with Izzy as
well. No, no, no. He used to do it with
Izzy as well. No one else does it but him. So,
No, no, no, no, no. He does it. He does it because
he's weird. He's weird. He's very weird.
But you need to stop this whole reaction
thing, Joe, because he doesn't watch
anymore. Because listen, right? He's the
one coming on YouTube every single day
[ __ ] with someone for a reaction.
Okay, let's go by your logic. So, let's
say he's doing it for a reaction, right?
So, let's just say
he's going to get a reaction every
month. So, let's just say that it is
promised that I'm going to react to him
every month. So, I'm on YouTube every
day for a month. He [ __ ] with me every
day. And then after the month, I react
for 5 minutes. Okay. And then what? So,
you've wasted all of that time, all of
that energy to get what? 5 minutes of reaction.
Strange. For somebody that's got a
girlfriend, for somebody that claims
they've got all of this and they're not
skin, it it it it makes you wonder why
they would sit on YouTube every single
day [ __ ] with somebody for a
reaction. I mean, would it get boring
after a while? I mean, what? Someone
reacted every month. Okay, so you react
and then what? Okay, then and I reacted
for 5 minutes and then what?
Doesn't it doesn't wash. It really really doesn't.
You know, we're not talking about
somebody that's coming on for 5 seconds
writing [ __ ] and you're going mad for
hours every time. Meaning what? A
reaction every month. That's like me, right?
[ __ ] with somebody every day for a month.
I don't know, bro.
What did you think of my messages? I
thought they're pretty good, man.
Um, I don't delete their numbers. I
delete their convos. I don't know why. I
just leave it up there, bro. It's just a habit.
So, anyways, he [ __ ] with me every day
and I reply to him every month. Then
what? Then what, Joe? You know,
you can't be all of these things that
people are telling you that you are.
I'll give you an example. I was on Monty Man's um
live stream uh yesterday and these
people are saying that I don't have
this. I don't have that. I don't have
this. Oh, I'll reply to you, J. One
second. I don't have this. I don't have that. Um
uh I don't have this. I don't have that.
Um, and then I I simply replied, "Okay,
well, you're the ones that sit on
YouTube all day every day. You can't
take a day off of YouTube. I've proven
that many times. So, what's your life?"
They couldn't reply. They just shut up.
That old account because what what what
can you say? Yeah, I'm this, I'm skinn,
I'm this, I'm that, and you don't even
know how much money I have. You don't
know anything about me. Okay. So, if
your life is so good, why you sat on
YouTube all day typing from the time you
go to bed to the time you wake up to the
time you go to bed? and Jay Willow. The
reason I I message again, uh, okay, so
if I message somebody and they don't reply,
I will message them again two weeks
later and because sometimes it's worked
where they've not replied to the first
message and if I message them again one
more time in two weeks, they've met me.
So it has it has actually happened
before and then if they don't reply to
that one then I just delete it because you know
it has worked in the past where someone
has actually met um
believe it or not. So then if they don't
reply to that one I just need [ __ ] them with it.
But it has worked that's why cuz yeah
[ __ ] them anyways bro. But that's the
point I'm trying to make.
And then they can't argue like you're
saying that I'm skin, I'm this, I'm
that. And here's another thing I wanted
to say. Oh yeah, this comment kind of
was like he was like, oh um nurseries
are going um you see nurseries going
bust. You say the west is dead, but
there's there's kids and t I mean, yeah,
there's people having children because
there's different ways people have met.
They might have met through work. They
might have got lucky on a dating app.
They might be someone's type. They might
have met [ __ ] years ago. You know,
there's different reasons how people
have met. None of them are none of them
have have got any
any relation to you
because at the end of the day like I can
tell you a fun fact. Most of the people
I know that are single and I can tell
you that for a fact.
Yeah, there's there's n people have but
at the end of the day, bro, I don't know
the statistics, but there's got to be
millions of people that are single.
And I have used up and I have used
pickup lines. Yeah. Last time I went out
I I used pickup lines. The last time I
tried I was confident I used pickup
lines and they just weren't interested.
But I don't know what the statistics
are, but most of the people that I know
are single. Like even people that I know
in real life, and I'm not even chatting
[ __ ] I swear to God.
I swear to [ __ ] God.
Um, so obviously
it's not rare for people to be single.
This is another thing. I don't, like I
said, I don't know what the statistics are, but
it doesn't mean Yeah.
No, I'm not watching. No, this guy was
basically saying that you he was trying
to be funny. He was said he was saying
that I say the west is dead but there's
still nurseries you know as as to say
that people are still having kids. Okay.
But how many single people are there?
How many single people are there in the world?
And like I said there's different
reasons and and different ways people
have met. You know what I'm saying? So, it's like,
but yeah, most of the people I know are
single and they ain't found no one.
Most of the women I know are single as well,
funny enough. There's a lot of single
people out there.
Maybe not virgins, but
no, there's there's a lot of single
people out there.
So, I don't understand his point
cuz there's no elephant in the room, mate.
Nons. I'm not a nons. Bye-bye.
So, there's obviously people that are
single out there. No. But yeah,
you still there, Joseph? >> Yeah,
you know, I'd get an escort every month,
but I don't have a sex drive anymore.
I mean, there's a few things you can do.
You can either leave the country, which
is what I'm doing.
You can use an escort every month and
give up for like 6 months, or you can
approach every single day until you meet
someone and hope you get lucky. But
personally, I wouldn't go I wouldn't go
down that option. So, there's a few
things, but I I would say personally if
you're if you're staying here,
just use an escort for like 6 months and then maybe
try again if you want after 6 months,
but I personally would just leave or you
know, but I have a sex drive. So,
yeah, they're a temporary fix. Yeah.
They get addicting as well. That's
another thing. When you use them, they get addicting.
So, we worked out that over the years,
I've been with six women, Joe.
Yeah. I've been with six. I mean, ones
that weren't escorts, ones I like slept
with was six,
which is just normal, I think. But it's
not normal for the amount of effort I put in.
I mean, that just shows how hard it is
to be honest.
I don't [ __ ] know, bro. I don't
What do you What do you do? E, what do
you say? Huh?
Yeah. I don't know about going out for
my birthday, man. That's I don't know.
I don't think it's good though for your mental health. So,
I don't think it's good for your mental
health, you know.
What do you mean they won't give you
what you really want? What do you really
See, with that 19y old, I didn't mind
giving her £50.
Low job. She swallows. That's cheap for
[ __ ] 50 quid. both schools to charge
you a lot. >> Yeah.
But I get what you mean though. Then
it's like the whole USA is thing that
was different. Even though it was very
transactional, it was the fact that, you
know, I approached her,
you know, I made her like me and um yeah.
Um, and like she gave me her body even
though it was no real different to an
escort and it was just love bobbing. You
you you understand what I mean? Is it?
You understand what I mean?
Even though it was just the same as an
at school, you know.
You got me. Yeah.
No, I don't want a relationship.
I generally think Yeah.
What will sort my problem out? Yeah. To
end this once and for all is join the porn industry.
Generally think like that. I I said I
applied for it. I didn't really. Um
Antman was recommended it. But I
generally think that would sort out all
of your problems
because you get paid, you you get to
have sex. Um
and I think generally that would be the end.
You know, that would be the end of all
of this madness. I think
I want to be able to seduce somebody and get sex.
You know what I mean?
Seduce someone and get sex. You know,
I want like well what I wanted before
was like sex, but like not a relationship.
So being able to like seduce someone or chase,
but saying that it's not even just that
because I don't know cuz I I I would pay
a woman to [ __ ] her and I I and it to me
it would be the same even if I had to
pay her. I don't know. I don't know.
It's weird cuz like say I could pay a
woman to [ __ ] her and if I paid I would
still feel the same as if I didn't pay
cuz I got what I wanted. I don't [ __ ]
know, bro. It's just weird.
It is just so I don't know. It's hard to explain, you know.
I don't know. It's weird. It is weird.
It is very weird cuz I was happy with
the OD fans one, you know,
cuz most women are not worth being in a relationship with,
you know. I would have liked to see that
one from Finland. I would have liked to
see, you know, that French woman
because you got to understand when
you're saying that you want a
relationship, you need a you need a
relationship with the right person.
That's another thing that you don't
mention. You know, you need a
relationship. You can't just say, "Oh, I
want a relationship." Because you need
to find someone that you would want to
be in a relationship with. You can't
just pick anyone. You know what I'm saying?
But yeah, there's like people I would
have been in relationship with
like that French one and that [ __ ]
Finnish one, but don't know what happened.
I don't know, bro.
I think friends with benefits is is what
what I'd want, you know.
I don't know. I've never been on a date
to a cinema. I hate going to the cinema,
seeing couples, man. I hate it.
It really really does like grind my
gears. And you know what's so mad is
it's so weird when you go to the cinema
because you will see the kind of women
that these men go for
nowadays. Like [ __ ] they are really
low in their standards
because they can't get anything else.
So it's weird cuz you'll see some ugly
guy with some woman that look and and
yeah cuz I just don't like seeing couples.
So I need to go to the cinema on Mondays
now like first showings
cuz I should have met someone by now, you know. So yeah, I haven't.
Oh no, man.
I would have been in a relationship with
that Italian one. She was sexy. But
yeah, I would have I would have um
I would have got a relationship with her. defer
if I could have
cuz I know them people are getting sex you know
I should have stayed with little Isabelle it
tell you what would have been Perfect.
That Italian one would have been perfect, but
Oh, some woman on WhatsApp. Ah, [ __ ]
Yo, I messaged some woman on WhatsApp,
right? No, Messenger. Sorry.
I said, "Why did you block me on
WhatsApp?" just to see what the response
will be that hey Pete I'm going to
change my number and purchase OTU SIM
that's why removing everyone from WhatsApp oh
yeah right and I said why she didn't reply
you know why I I I can't be bothered
with these even if I wanted to get in a
relationship Joe because I'm sick of
these games I'm sick of the [ __ ]
all it is with these women on my His
mind games are [ __ ]
you know. It's not worth going through
that to get a relationship.
It's not worth going through any of that
[ __ ] mind games. It there there's no
point of it. There's really no point of
But honestly, I think my problem is cuz
I don't look fully white.
I generally think it's because like
Yeah. the way like my what my ethnicity
looks like. Look,
my beard and stuff [ __ ] trim,
you know. I I generally think it's that, you know,
it's just a mind games.
I can't be dealing with it, bro. It's
not worth it.
You should have to deal with that just
to get into a relationship with someone.
I don't know.
is what it is.
L can't approach can he Joe? His anxiety
won't allow it. No. Yeah.
Like I said, the last time I went out
was like a month ago. I got 10 numbers,
one reply, one agreed to meet me, spent
£600 and didn't want to repeat the
process ever again.
I think that's fair enough.
I think that's fair enough. Is it Joseph?
I got a football tip for next week. By
the way, you want to do um slow and kitty minister?
You want to do slam and kitty minister?
They always both score. They do, man. I
wish I done it [ __ ] I wish I done
that on Saturday, man. [ __ ] Sleep.
They've done They've won. I need to win
a football bet every month. I need every
week for a month.
I can't be motivated after spending all
of that money and not even getting a
date. I'm not motivated, bro. Can't try again.
It's not worth it. Even getting sex is
is not worth it.
That's just [ __ ] going. Yeah.
So, why what why do you think I can't
get dates, Joe?
Do you think it's my ethnicity? I think
it is. It's not my looks, bro. It can't
be. I've shown you what I look like when
I look Max. I don't know what it is. It
is It is weird. It is weird.
It's got to be either your
I don't know, ethnicity or [ __ ]
the fact that like you're just average looking
or even if you're decent looking, it's
not good enough or whatever. I don't
know. It's weird. It is generally weird.
Well, I would say it's ethnicity to be honest.
I don't know cuz it doesn't it doesn't
seem normal, does it?
It doesn't seem normal.
And it's not good for your mental health either.
It's like you saying about the beard.
Even if it's true about the beard, why
should someone have to get rid of their beard?
I mean, what happens when you go out mangled?
This is how it goes, right? You go out,
right? I do approaches on the street
sober before I start drinking. Not all
the time, but most of the time. And what
will happen is you approach someone,
they say they've got a boyfriend
or they're not interested or they don't
say much or maybe you'll get a number.
Then you go to bars and clubs deal with
the same [ __ ] I've got a boyfriend.
Then you probably get about three, four
numbers or whatever. Then you message
them the next day. Probably what
normally happens is half of them reply,
half of them don't reply. And then you
talk, you agree to meet, they agree to
meet you, and then on the day that
you're supposed to meet, you never hear
from them again. So, they just lead you
on. That's literally all that ever
happens. And you get to a and you get to
a certain age where you're just sick of
it, bro. you know,
you know, you get sick of it.
There's nothing different ever happens.
You know, you don't even get regular
dates. I could understand if you got
regular dates, but now
yeah, I can show you what I go out
looking like. I look good when I go out.
Well, the last time I went out, I look
[ __ ] sick. That's what made it worse
cuz I looked I look smacked and I got
their numbers and I still didn't get an
A. What the [ __ ]
I look smack. I looked good.
and I still didn't even get a date. What the [ __ ]
So, could you imagine how many times
that will happen?
That is weird, man.
Why Monty and Rice had a fight? Uh or
have you seen it? So
Ricky Millington bodied
star and boss. I'm going to make some
piggies in a minute. I'm [ __ ] starving. So yeah.
Yeah. Monty met up with Rice and they
had a fight. Richie all on the same
website you can watch Yoda.
Same website you can watch Yoda. Um Joe
I mean I can show you my approaches if
you want if you got Snapchat.
Um, I can I can show you some examples.
I don't mind if you got Snapchat or um Instagram.
I don't mind sending them.
I don't put on this channel because of
um trolls and [ __ ]
which it should have anyways. I should
just put up on this channel. But
back when I used to put the gambling
lockers up, I had to put the gambling
lockers up because if anyone was
thinking of gambling, they'd have to see
that you lose money as well.
They have to see that you lose money as well. So
then obviously that game trolls ammo.
Who are you man? I don't know who you are.
I can show you some of my approaches if
you want. I can do it. I can put an
approach up right now if you want. Mangled.
I've got one on here as unlisted. Do you
want me to put it up?
You found Jaw Pro? Really?
Oh, I didn't even know to be honest.
What did you do wrong in your approach?
I mean, I used pickup lines last time. Uh,
okay. I'll put it up. One sec.
I want to sec.
So I put as public.
It's an old one.
It's titled 23rd of September.
It's only I mean you get the gist basically. So
going to make some piggies. Like I said,
I put the approach on my channel, bro.
Going it. 23rd of set.
What the [ __ ]
Yeah. Go on it, bro.
I think it's a short. It's a short, bro.
It's a short.
There you go.
Nah, I can't. I can't join your [ __ ] I
I I can't let you up. You're part of
Discord. You're part of Discord, lad.
You're part of [ __ ] Discord. Yeah.
I thought I just called son. I thought
you up here.
Yeah. Did you watch it? Um, Yeah,
I want to join Discord.
Me and Joe's going to join Discord with
with you and Jaden. Yeah,
you can't I can't believe you ruined Monty's life.
You You ruined his life.
I'm going to make some piggies, bro. [ __ ]
You ruined B's life. You're mad.
Oh, look at this beard, Davey. Jeez.
You're trying to say that you're better
looking than Peter By, bro. You [ __ ] mad.
Nah, bro. You ain't better looking than me, boss.
You're not better looking than me, boss.
Of course they weren't bad. Of course
they weren't bad, bro. One second. I'm
just peeing. Of course they weren't [ __ ] bad.
Obviously they wasn't bad.
It's just the women are just piss takers
in this country. That's why I gave up. I
really give a [ __ ] bro. You know,
you know what I mean?
Cuz they're [ __ ] piss takers.
Yeah, I got a long beard.
Look at that.
I don't have anxiety, bro.
Trust me, I don't have anxiety. I've
been approaching for years, mate. I
don't have anxiety.
Trust me. When I approached, you know,
let me let me tell you something, right?
You want me to give you a fun fact?
You're going to think I'm taking a piss
when I say this. I had more luck when I
was nervous. Okay. So, what I mean by
that is there were some times where I
used to be really, really, really
confident. Like last time I went out and
I was super confident and I still and I
still got nothing.
Didn't care. They weren't interested.
But when I've done it before when I was
nervous, shut myself. um
um I I I got better results.
So that's why I never believed that
because when you know when I when I
approached USA job I was [ __ ] myself
[ __ ] myself. It must have been a
period where I weren't I weren't I
weren't confident and I was absolutely
[ __ ] my pants
and she couldn't tell.
So if they could really pick up anxiety,
how could she [ __ ] myself?
I was I was So I don't I don't believe
that is true. Even though confidence is
good to have nonetheless, you want to
feel comfortable doing it. Oh, it's
freezing, babe. [ __ ] freezing. It is.
Anyways, I'm going to make some piggies now.
I said, "Don't worry, mate. I'll leave
all the [ __ ] bacon. You know how much
I love bacon." But seriously, like
that's it, man. So,
why are you going Thailand? Some bacon. [Music]
>> You think I'm intelligent? Nurious. >> Yeah.
My life is [ __ ] I should have a lot
more. Almost 28, bro. I'd never pretend
that my life is perfect.
I should be like with a dog in a relationship,
but you know, it is what it is, though.
I mean, rice don't work. Look at what
look at rice. I just compare myself to
people that are worse than me and make
make me uh
helps me feel better, lad.
But I don't have anxiety.
Yeah, I want Discord.
I've already tried all of that. Did you
not watch my approach? Um, mang mangled.
I showed you I showed you an approach. I
just put it up.
>> I'll link it to you if you want. I'm captain.
>> I'm sure you sure you know.
One second, bro.
I hate having to close this [ __ ] bastard phone.
I just think you'll approach, bro.
Oh, it has to be dark [ __ ]
be, man. I can't have [ __ ] light
theme on [ __ ]
But you know what I don't understand?
People on Reddit say go on dating apps
to get laid, but they don't bloody work
for me. I can't even get a bastard match.
I can't even get a bastard [ __ ] match.
Oh, trying to do this [ __ ] bottom half. Right. [Music] Let me
like mushrooms as well. Just
they tell me to go on dating apps to get
laid on Reddit.
God don't [ __ ] know, man. Oh, [ __ ] I'm so
I have to grill my bacon. I have to
grill my bacon, man. really
bear with me to multit
The bread softened up. Use some bread and butter. Yeah. Virgin
Ricky got ruined. Oh,
>> Ricky got [ __ ] ruined.
Do you know what I don't understand?
No, I'm not putting myself out there,
bro. After after um a month ago when I
got them 10 numbers.
Why have I got these pills in my pocket?
I didn't take them. I must stop talking.
After I got them 10 numbers, bro, and I
spent £600. Never again. [ __ ] that, bro.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Cuz I looked
my best. So, I got 10 numbers and I
didn't even get a date. And I got I got
one reply that said they were going to
meet me, but they never. So, I mean,
never, bro. It's going to be very hard
to try and convince me to go out again
after that. That is [ __ ] bad. That's
the last time I tried Notorious.
And I swear I'd never go back after that
cuz it was it was depressing, bro. I was
depressed for like over a week after
that, man. And then I won the money
back, but it's not the point. That's not
the point. That is insane.
So, I showed you my approach anyway. So,
I don't think it's your approach. It's
they've got they've got a physical type.
If you're not their physical type, they
will not get with you. It's if you go on
a dating app and you're a white guy,
blue eyes, you're tall, a woman will go
with you regardless what it is very much
about uh appearance.
It really really is. People try to make
it seem like it's not that and you know
it's about personality, but it's
bollocks. It really and truly is [ __ ]
No, personality is secondary what they
go for. The first thing they go for is I
mean I'll give you an example. Mongled Mongol, right?
I was on Reddit and this woman was
saying to me, um,
uh, I can't get with you cuz you're not
Muslim and you're 28 and I'm 2. I told
her I was 28. Uh, and and you're, uh,
she's 23 and I'm 28.
Um, and she was saying, "Oh, I can't get
with you cuz you're too old. You're not
Muslim." Using all of these excuses in
the book. Yeah. I found out that she had
been with a 28-y old before. And I'm
thinking, "What the [ __ ] I mean, I'm
decent looking. I'm not ugly. This woman
wouldn't even hypothetically give me a
chance because I'm not her type. She
wouldn't even give me a chance. So
that's it's [ __ ] bro. It very much.
It is materialistic things, physical
stuff like that. It is, bro. Trust me, it is.
Trust me, it is, bro. And because I
wasn't [ __ ] white, like I didn't look
like fully white. Um
that's obviously why she didn't
give me a chance. So it is very much to do with
you know people's um you know physical
type and that
even though they try to say that it's not
personality is not as important as
people make out. Bro it's [ __ ] It's
cop. It's like when people try and say,
"Oh, women uh women um
they won't uh women doesn't owe you
anything." It's it's to try to justify
their shitty behavior when they ghost or
they lead people on and stuff. It's all
they're very much afraid of putting any
kind of blame on women
in this society. You know what I mean? Notorious.
It's just strange. It is strange.
It is very very strange.
They even got high standards. They've
got unrealistic standards. Yeah.
Well, I've not got through it and that's
why I'm going Thailand, bro. That's what I'm leaving.
So, I didn't think it was by looks. I I
until that woman was making all of these excuses
saying, "Oh, you know, you're not
Muslim. No, no, no, no, no. I can't get
with you cuz you're Muslim." You know? Um, yeah.
Yeah, I've got money though. Yo, I've got money.
I'm all good for money now, bro.
But yeah, I mean,
it's never it's never, you know, we're
just born the wrong generation generation.
I'm going to have piggies, so bear with me. But yeah,
I need to sort my [ __ ] out, bro. Honestly,
you're getting old now, man. I'm not 25 anymore.
>> You know how it be.
But no, it is definitely um they
definitely got a title.
Right, let me try and do this egg
without [ __ ] it up.
So, I'm just going to do bread and
butter with the bread, I think. Yeah,
let me try and do this without [ __ ]
this egg up here. Lovely.
Uh, why are you talking?
What are you talking about?
Look at this egg. I done it perfect. One sec.
Look at that. Perfect. There go. Yeah, man.
Have to grill my bacon. I don't grill my
It's [ __ ] weird. I don't actually
smoke maker. That's weird. Bacon.
Never did say that.
That's an actual egg in it.
>> Oh, [ __ ]
One second. Did I tell you sleep?
Smoke bacon's all right, but one's
better, but she picked up the wrong one
for some reason.
Can't get over. He's [ __ ] isn't he?
He is [ __ ]
He's on YouTube, isn't it?
video, Joe. When Timmyy's like, I'm
going to knock him out.
Did you see that?
You saw that, didn't you?
I'm going to knock him out.
This bacon's almost ready.
Did you see that?
I like my bacon nice and crispy.
Nice and crispy, baby.
Don't know about you [ __ ]
Like my nice and crystal bush ready.
Don't worry. I'll eat I'll eat the [ __ ] bacon.
little bed [ __ ] with no bed. No money in it.
That's so touchy, bro.
Oh, you can't.
Why is it?
Wish you would have told me, mate. body. [Music]
>> How are you going to lose it?
Oh, is that the bar? Oh, that is the
bar. Is it [ __ ] cheese mine? Why not?
Want to burn the bacon's done.
>> Oh, yeah. That is, isn't it? It looks like [ __ ] Jesus.
That was why weird boy. Find out.
Look at that.
Some lovely smoked piggies.
Some lovely smoked [ __ ] piggies, mate. Red and
that's what you call it. [Music]
One second, bro.
You watched it? Yeah.
That's an old one, but few years ago. Yeah, I know
they're rude, aren't they?
But people don't think they're the problem.
The madness, huh? Yeah, madness.
There we go.
Hopefully this egg comes up.
There you go. Love this.
Yeah, they don't care, bro. They're [ __ ] hospital.
I've already made food. Bread, bacon,
red, bacon, eggs, red, bacon, bread. Mhm.
You never lose it.
No, you won't lose it.
Like I said, both okay, but
I prefer the normal B. [Music]
I know, mate. I must be gay.
You can't deny she's attractive. What's my phone?
She's half the night. She's attractive.
Yeah, he's copying with that one. She's
not attractive at all. And I've had more
women than him.
He's definitely definitely copying.
He's definitely definitely copying. It's
the name. Yeah. Not looking around the
se so hot. No, she's not. I think she's [ __ ] ugly.
No, she's [ __ ] ugly.
I have more women than him
before he tried to call me gay.
I would say that to be a [ __ ] I have
actually been with more women than him.
Yeah. They themselves. Exactly. It's a
trend. It's a trend.
It's a trend, isn't it, Joe?
Wait, you actually like her? I don't
think she I don't think she's that good.
I mean, she's not as good as people make
out. Nowhere near as good as people make
Yeah, that was he he was saying that to fy people.
No, she ain't nothing.
Why would someone be that self? They're
not even that good looking.
Why do people say that? Why they copy each other?
Are they that insecure about their sexuality? It's mad.
Nothing secure about their sexuality. Jo.
I mean, and I've been with more women
than he has. But I do know that fact I
have been with more women than that [ __ ] virgin. Um,
but apparently I'm gay.
That's interesting, isn't it? I've been
gay for so many years, but I've never
been with a man.
Why is she not your property? What's your type?
>> Yeah, we're both gay. It must be
I like if I had to fancy a celebrity I would pick um do
about half a bit. I would say
celebrity. Oh, so many of them.
Um, I'd say Selena Gomez if that would
be one of them.
I'd say Death by one of them.
There's this blog I like.
He used to be on a Nickelodeon channel.
I say about
and that belongs from the Nickelodeon channel. Yeah. Um,
see, people used to like Beyonce. I
didn't really see the height of her.
I'm getting retain Swift just cuz she's a billionaire.
I'd love some of her money, but nah. Um,
who was that other judge?
Don't know. I don't know.
No, not that one. I'm talking about one
that was on a program called Italy. You
might not know it. Um, years ago,
it was blonde.
It's a statement that Jennifer Anderson,
she's not even that good. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, I remember that. Jennifer
Anderson, people used to say something about her.
Yeah, I used to love that.
obvious as well. But
yeah, obviously I was a kid. I liked her
and she's old now. So that's what I mean
by life. But I like the blonde.
I like I used to like the blonde.
And to be honest with you, I used to
like that as well even though she's
Asian. I used to like both of them.
Obviously I was a kid. They were older
than me. I used to like that guy.
Yeah, I can very much fall in love with
an Asian in the right circumstances, I guess. Yeah,
that base was lovely. Yeah, she's
perfect as well.
I used to like to adjusted as well. I
still do be fat. Yeah,
I like USA is
I'm only joking. But no. Yeah, nice.
No one is virgin. No, nobody was as nice
as Virgin boy trying to make out. You can't [ __ ]
even though you probably got [ __ ]
Even though you probably got kids,
they'll still refer to you [ __ ] find
someone [ __ ] attractive.
You know what I'm saying, mate?
There's a trend for puppy
by Joe. Could you see the similarities
before between me and USA? Is it
be honest? Could you
could you see the similarity now?
You can see the similarities, couldn't you? Oh,
how we doing, bro?
>> That bacon wasn't nice.
Wash it down with some nice cola. Thank you, mama. Oh [ __ ]
Taking a baby away from its mama.
Taking a bobshin away from its mama.
What do you think of that?
Taking a baby away from it. Mama
[ __ ] madness, isn't it?
Don't let these [ __ ] women win.
Where's that [ __ ] troll gone, bro?
in the USA. Izzy was more of a mom to
me, you know.
This is my mama.
My nice, nice mama. Oh,
back in the nesticles.
Oh, that was yummy.
Oh, don't talk about my mama like that.
Talk about my mommy like that.
Why are you talking about my mama like that, Candy?
She might have been stinking, but she
had nice boobies. Candy man.
How was about that one?
Joe, do you remember that account that
used to come on saying, "Don't let these
hunting women women win." Like trying to
egg me on to go out and try. Do you
remember that account?
Yeah. I think it was Joker me.
It could be LT though, is it? It's like
LT could have come back. Yeah. for a
night out with his little baits.
And um and uh and um
and he could just be like writing to try
and wind me up to like get me going. And
that imagine it's LT and these little
goons like they'll come out for a night.
I was like, "Let me go. Let's egg this
[ __ ] on." And it
Yeah. Let these [ __ ] women win. They
know what they're doing, is it? They
know what they're [ __ ] doing.
Yeah, it was a nice meal though to be
fair. That's what life's about. Going to
nice restaurants, Joe. I've been to a
lot of nice restaurants.
A lot of nice restaurants.
I've been to a lot of nice restaurants,
man. And you know the thing is Joe like
you know that's one of the things that's
good with London is there's so many nice
restaurants that you don't get that with
other places like yeah you know up north
you get the nice multicultural buffets
but you don't get it like you do in London you know
you just don't get them nice restaurants
like you do in London like in London
You're spoiled for choice. Really spoiled.
You know, steak houses. Yeah.
No, never told him that.
Yeah. What do you think of what Ant-Man
said to me, Joe? He said, "When you was
traveling up and down the country, them
women were laughing at you, mocking you.
They were mocking you, laughing at you.
Nah, bro. I'm tired, man.
Can't I can't talk.
Yeah, I paid for a meal and I got sex.
It worked out cheaper than an escort. So,
why does she want why does she want um
why does she want casual sex with people?
I don't get that, Joe. Why would she
want casual sex with people?
Bit boring in it.
Why do you want one night stands? Nah.
Do you want my number? I'm never
deleting that approach. I've still got
it on my phone.
How can I delete the moment I met my mama? Joe,
taking a baby away from its mama. You
want me to delete a You want me to
delete a video where I met my mama?
Nah, it's my mama.
We have the same hair, same eyes.
No, I'm just, you know, I'm just
sometimes I like to reminisce about good
the good times, you know, foods, things,
places I've been, people I've met.
She is my mama.
Well, why does she look like me then?
Nah, I I pulled my ploner over like when
I got a [ __ ] in the alleyway
by this American.
She was nasty. She was,
"I really want you, but I don't think
you want me."
I was like, "What the [ __ ]
I said I do. This was in the O'Neals.
Good old O'Neal's e. No,
that's what she said.
She like, I really want you, but I don't
think you want me.
You think that's weird that that woman
gave me a [ __ ] in the alleyway?
And I remember that day the bouncer
tried cop blocking me, but it never worked.
He really tried.
Why didn't I [ __ ] her? Because as I was
walking to the hotel to try and book the
hotel, bear in mind it was going to cost
about £300. Her friends caught up with us.
So I just took the [ __ ]
Yeah, her friend just caught up with
with us. So, she was on it though. She
She actually was coming on to me. I was
drunk as well. I was like, "Oh, okay.
I'll just go along with it."
Well, no. I approached her. And then
she was like, "Um, she was coming on to
me saying, "Oh, I really want you." And
[ __ ] I was like, "Let me just get a
drink and we'll go somewhere else."
Oh my god. It was the best blow job I've
ever had in my life. She was from
America as well.
Oh my god. It was the best one I ever
had in my life, matey.
It was mental.
She must have knew she was doing that.
There's no way she could have been that
drunk to not know she was [ __ ]
sucking someone's dick.
But that's another rare thing. It's very
Yeah, it doesn't matter though. I got a [ __ ] so
and I got to finger her and touch her. So,
it's fine, isn't it?
Yeah, I had some good times in that O'Neals.
I done a lot of fingering in there, Joe.
A lot of fingering.
I remember this time, I'll never forget,
bro, where like I was fingering this woman and
I swear to God, bro, she was like her
eyes was rolling out of her head and
then she was she was crying over her ex
whilst I was doing it.
I was like, "What? You're not supposed
to be crying over your ex." Um,
and then she was and then she literally
pulled her top off and she was coming on
to me, kissing me, jumping on me
like in front of everyone. I was like,
"Uh, you can't be doing this here."
Every everyone was looking. I swear to
God, it was like at the bench trying to secrete secrete.
Um, and she kept doing it and everyone
was looking. I was like, "You can't do that.
Um, I carried on
and then she put her boobies in my face,
Joe. And then I was sucking her boobies.
Then we got kicked out.
I was like, "Bro, this is like the wrong
[ __ ] place. What the fuck?"
And then other ones. Yeah, I fingered.
I used to rinse that place, bro. That's
why I met all the army lads.
Uh, I done a lot of kissing there.
I had a lot of dates there as well, but
I never ever like pulled pulled where I
got sex except from that [ __ ]
Them Americans used to be [ __ ] hard
to get. That's when I used to be
obsessed with Americans. I used to go on
a Thursday. I was full of Americans. So,
yeah. But it's not enough success for
the amount I've tried, Joe. I've been
all over the country. I've been up and
down the country.
I've done a lot of traveling. I've done
a lot of approaching. I should have had
a lot more success,
but I've been with a few Americans.
But no, Americans are not hard to pull.
I tell you, the ones that are hard to
pull them [ __ ] French ones, you got
no chance. Generally, if you ever get
with a French woman, consider yourself
lucky cuz that is impossible.
Americans were like stuck up. I mean,
they're not easy, but
French, they're the ones that are hard
or Italian or anything like that, mate. Americans are
I'm trying to think how many
trying to think.
Obviously, USA is the the one that
sucked my dick.
Depends if you're talking about kissing.
One I figured was American, but she was
Mexican. If you're talking about like
kissing and that uh
I'm sure there's been other ones.
Oh, I think the Canadian.
I don't know, you know.
No, there was one
I've kissed a couple of Americans
as well, but they're harder. They're not
They're not easy.
They're not They're not Well, they're
not They're not hard compared to French.
They're impossible. They're impossible.
They are. You never get with a French woman.
I don't know how you could ever get with
one, to be honest. I would have loved to
have got with some of them cuz they
always seemed good over text, but they
just troll you, Joe. There was one that
was like, "Oh, um, yeah, I'm going to
see my my It's like they are trolling
you." She's like, "Oh, when do you want
to come to France then and and see me
and then they're just leading you on and
then it's just they just play a game
with you the whole time." Funny in a way.
They do it in such a funny way that you
can't even get mad at it. And they're
just trolling the [ __ ] out of you all
along. It's mad.
But that's what they always do. They
always they always troll you. French Uh
but back to the Americans. Uh
Yeah, I have. Um,
but don't you think I should have had
more success than I did, Joe? You know,
I messaged someone on Reddit and they
like, "Not you again."
Yo, they were like, "Not you again.
I thought that would make you laugh, it hard Americans. Ah,
yeah. But it doesn't matter if you're
not owed anything. If you put effort in,
you deserve something out of it.
So, there was this woman I was speaking
to on Reddit. I was like, "Oh, have you
read the conversation I sent you?" She
said, "I don't owe you anything to read
it." I was like, "Uh, I mean, you're
messaging me back. You're typing me.
You're typing to me, but then when
I'm showing you messages, you don't owe
me to read them. I mean, is this the
entitled women that we're dealing with
nowadays? Get [ __ ]
Really get [ __ ] you know. But
like I said, Joe,
I think I've been to more cities than
you in England. Would you agree?
The only places I've not been is Glasgow, Blackpool, Plymouth.
I think that's about it. I think I've
been everywhere in terms of main cities.
I've been literally everywhere, bro.
Been to Bristol. I've been to Wales.
Yeah. Done all that. So, they're the only few
They're the only few places I ain't been.
So, I say I've traveled more the around
the country than you have. And I've been
to Manchester 10 times as well.
done a lot of um traveling.
And it's so obvious that you live in a
it's so obvious that you live in um
Newcastle. It's obvious, isn't it?
You obviously live in Newcastle. So obvious.
Imagine going Imagine having a camper
van and going all around.
Imagine going all around. Imagine having
a camper van and going all around
England. Yeah. from drinking every day
in in a different city. Not every day,
but say you done every day for a week in Leeds,
every day for a week. That's what I was
thinking of doing like going to
Edinburgh doing Friday, Saturday,
Glasgow, Friday, Saturday, leads,
Friday, Saturday. Could you imagine you
done that? That would be mad, isn't it?
Like you're on Friday, Saturday in different cities.
So, you need to have a lot of money for that.
Could you imagine that though? Jesus.
Could you imagine that? That'd be mad.
Yeah, that would be mad. Yeah.
Yeah. I went on Izzy's photo on
Instagram earlier. She She's grown up to
be quite pretty, you know.
Yeah. She's grown up to be quite pretty.
Little Isabelle. Isabelli.
Isabelli will never meet me again. She hates me.
Well, I'm surprised you never tried to
come running back, little Isabelle.
>> Was you around them times with the
Weather Spoons and the holding hands, Joe?
Not sure. I think so, cuz the guy that
she was with before broke up with her.
They broke up.
He was giving me some [ __ ] on Facebook.
I'm surprised she never ever tried
coming back cuz obviously me having
money and [ __ ]
No, I didn't hear.
And she's like, I'm surprised she never ever tried.
He died. Yeah, right.
Yeah, but I'm surprised he didn't come
running back when I had all that money.
I mean, I still have money now, but
still, you know,
you didn't die, you idiot. Being stupid.
How did he die?
Yeah. Yeah. But if I kept meeting her,
she would have friend zoned me.
How would you know that he died?
She might have not gave a [ __ ]
before, Joe. You never know. She might
have never gave one.
I'd be the first
doggy. How do you know he's died?
Maybe she's never gave him no job before, Joe.
So he died. How did he die?
So, listen, Joe. Uh,
so do you reckon she'd ever meet me again?
I think if USA was here, she'd meet me again.
See, USA uh sorry, normal Izzy liked me
when she was like 18
and she um never was she wasn't getting attention.
Are you actually chatting [ __ ]
Yeah, I actually fought for USA Easy as
well and she never come back. I fought
for her, Joe. I was going to take on
that as I was about I was I was going to
take on that Arsenal Mark [ __ ] You
saw that, didn't you, Joe? I went to his
area two times.
I was going to fight that [ __ ]
you know, trying to steal my little Isabelle,
you know. Don't you remember, Joe?
I was like, "Right, I've had enough of
this little cunt." I was a lot younger.
I was a lot younger then, too. You
remember when I went to the park,
I was trying to impress Isabelle? Ah,
can't believe she'd never come back. So,
what if I if I um, you know, went to
your where you lived and stuff?
Do you think she'd ever meet me again, Joe? Nah.
I'm surprised she didn't come back, though.
Do you reckon she'll ever meet me again? Imagine
me and her meet again
and then we go on camera. That' get a
certain person jealous, wouldn't it, Jo?
Like a reunion
seven years later, eh?
What do you think?
>> Why not? Do you remember when she met
me? I remember she I won like £300 on
roulette. I didn't have a I didn't have
as much money back then. She completely
rinsed me, man.
She rinsed me, matey.
Yeah, I won like £300.
didn't have as much money back then,
bro. She saw me win on the roulette and
she's like, "Oh, let's meet up. Let's meet up." Yeah.
You come on to me, you know, kissing me.
The only two people that's ever come on
to me was her and USA. Is he? They're
the only two people. Yeah.
Yeah. Not the first time.
That's what makes me think I should go
out and approach women again to get the
virgin jealous. What do you think, Joe?
We know what we know what trigger We
know We know what triggers him, don't we?
Going out and approaching women. It
triggers it, but it
that's how you can trigger the virgin.
You don't even need to get with them.
You can just go to a club
and then trigger that virgin really hard.
That's the only thing that tempts me
back to doing it sometimes because it
triggers it. It triggers diversion.
It is. It does, doesn't it? It generally does.
I wonder what the Somalian's up to nowadays.
I wonder what that's up to nowadays.
Joe, what do you think she's doing? H
can't blow my nose. [ __ ]
Never tried it.
Yeah, she sucked my dick, but she wasn't
that good at it. She kept [ __ ] me
like three times. I said, "Fuck sake,
running out of [ __ ] come here." M
Yeah, she shot my dick a few times. Yeah.
Yeah. She doesn't try and mess me anymore.
I think it was around this time
was was it been two years already?
It was last year. Yeah. SW
was like W in Thailand. We love you.
You know what made me laugh though when
you was like, "What do you want them to say?
What do you want people to say in it?"
Yeah. I remember saying to this guy, he
said, "Have you tried Thailand?" He
says, he says, "Have you tried dating
apps?" What do you want them to say in it? Yeah.
They were thinking of things in it. Yeah.
Do you do you reckon Izzy still likes Peter Belly?
I remember was holding hands playing the roulette. Wow. Yeah.
Do you like Little Wizzy?
She was a little game player.
I don't entertain that Jane. She just
wants attention. She's never going to
meet anyone. That Jane
I can see through the games.
I'm not playing your silly games.
Do you remember USA is Joe? I know this is you.
I know this is you messaging me. Yeah. [Laughter]
They meet you for a good time and they
get the neverending nightmare.
Joe, they get the never ending nightmare. Huh? >> Yeah.
Is that cute? No.
I think it's very cute.
This woman said it's going to be hard
being your friend because if I disagree
with something that you say, you won't like it.
Yeah, we can still be friends.
Do you remember Joe? It seems anyone
will do. She said, "Seems anyone will do."
I was dead.
"Seems anyone will do," she said to me.
"Seems anyone would do."
And what does she mean that it seems
anyone would do? H. No.
She said, "You're so annoying and
frustrating." And I said I couldn't
blame you because of these
circumstances, but these excuses will
only go so far. No,
I might play some fishing frenzy and do
a video. Nah.
I said, "Would you look out for me if we
was friends?" She said, "Yes, that's
exactly what I have been doing. Even
though you don't think I do because you
don't like what I said.
It will not be easy to be your friend
because when I say things to help you,
you won't listen." Yeah, I've got a French friend. Nah, mate.
Can't afford it.
Can't afford it, mate.
We're not all rich like you. We can't
all gamble like you, Joseph. Do you not
um get bored of the gambling? I don't
gamble anymore. Really, bro? I would
have thought you get bored. You got
bored of it.
I mean, the buzz don't even do it for me anymore.
I don't know why. I just I don't know.
Do not think that it's like added stress
that you don't need in your life.
That's why I don't do it.
Well, I am going to do the football. I
want to try and win a double. I want to
try and win a both teams to score every
week for a month.
I really want to try, bro. But
I don't I don't know. Why do you think I
stopped the gambling really? I don't I
have money. I can do it. But
I think I just outgrew it to be fair.
Everyone's different in it.
I don't know.
I just kind of got bored of it.
The [ __ ] the mood swings.
I ain't gambled since I won that £500.
I need to win a both teams to score
every week for a month though. So, can
you help me?
I was going to do uh treble both score
no draw on Saturday, but I never
bothered. But I was thinking about doing
it. I'm going to get one in one day. Trust me.
Both score no draw.
Could you imagine that, Joe?
Could you imagine doing the correct
score for three games?
You'd be [ __ ] loaded.
You would be loaded.
Nil nil three games.
You would be [ __ ] loaded.
[ __ ] loaded, mate.
Yeah. Have you ever done a correct
score? They're [ __ ] hard they are.
They are hard, aren't they?
Yeah, they're hard. Quick score is hard. Huh?
I would say you gamble every day, don't you, Joe?
Oh, can you record like a full session
so I can watch H?
You're addicted to gambling.
You are addicted, isn't it? It's obvious
you're addicted in it.
Really? So, you haven't lost at all lately
on your 200B phone. Huh?
Monty really needs to get off of
YouTube. There's nothing wrong with a
200 pound phone, mate. I'm going to be
getting a £300 phone soon. I'd love to
get the new fold, but I can't afford it.
Like £1,700. And even if I could afford it,
I still wouldn't do it because I can't
justify it. I'm on a fold right now,
but I can't justify. Even if I could
afford it, I don't think I'd pay that
anyways. Not 1,700 prof.
Do you want my opinion, Daryl? [ __ ]
That's what I thought of it.
I think Do you really want to know what I think?
I think they're not trying to fight
because why are they fighting in a
public place knowing that it's going to get stopped?
It doesn't make any sense. Like you
would fight [ __ ] in a field or
somewhere you know it ain't going to get
stopped. They're fighting in public when
they know it's going to get stopped.
So it doesn't make any sense. Would you
agree on that?
So like when Timmy come on like on my road,
they weren't stopped.
Yeah. They still confronted each other.
But what's the point of doing it when
you know it's going to get stopped?
It just doesn't make sense. You know
that eventually it's going to get broke up.
Do you think Rice has got more balls
than me? Yo,
I reckon I could beat Monty. I
definitely reckon I could. Bro, he
wouldn't beat me.
You think Rice has got more balls than me? Yeah. Nah,
but even if they have a rematch, I don't
think Rice is going to win.
Yeah, but think about the time when I
went to meet Bomb and he didn't show up.
What about when I went to meet Terry?
What about when I went to meet Mark two
times? What about when I went to Virgin
Boy's area twice?
You know what about when I confronted
Timmy and Tiger?
See, you like to forget things on here, don't you?
Okay. So, what about when Tiger and
Timmy come on my door and I confronted
them? What about when I tried to meet
Arsenal Mike and Mark Twice?
What about when I met Terry Terry and I
didn't know what he looked like? What
about when I went to meet twice.
What do you mean? Nothing happened. I
still [ __ ] showed up. I was in Mark's
area for [ __ ] hours trying to meet him. So,
you know, I could beat Monty though in
it. I should have went to Birmingham
though that Saturday, man, and met Rice and K.
Yeah. Somebody would have got seriously
hurt in it. I'm going to knock him out.
Do you remember we said that about Monty?
Do you remember Joe?
I should have went though, man. Now, now
he's not my friend anymore.
Um, Rice is not my friend anymore.
No, he's not my friend anymore.
because of that.
I liked Rice. He thought I'll set him
up. I said I didn't set you up.
I could have probably got into KK's
knickknacks, Joe. If I showed up,
I probably could have. I think Kaye was
excited to see me, wasn't she?
Yeah, I've met Kaye before.
Yeah, he But I didn't set him up. How
did I set him up? you know.
So, how did he go? He says that he's
agrophobic and he's scared to leave the
house. So, how was he able to go to Birmingham
if he's agriobic? Yo. Nah. Nope.
How did he go to Birmingham then if he's got anxiety? Huh?
Do you reckon Monty could beat me though?
I don't think he honestly could. No, really.
A good blow job. [Music] Really? Jo,
why don't you get with nons legs as Mrs.
Joe? Would you bang nunch legs as misses?
Huh? Would you would you do nonsex with Mrs. Jo?
So, why do you only get a £200 phone anyways?
Why don't you get the new Samsung Galaxy Fold?
I couldn't afford that, mate. [ __ ] that.
I couldn't pay that money out on the phone.
And I wouldn't pay that money out on the
phone. That's ridiculous.
Even though the fold phones are really good.
They're class Samsung folds.
Why wouldn't you get a better phone if
you've got all this money, Joe? I don't get it. Maybe like
Yeah, you could you could you could book a holiday
with that. You can go to America with 1,700 pound.
I'd still get like a 400 pound one
though, like I'd still want a decent phone.
Yeah, exactly. That's why I wouldn't do it.
That's why I wouldn't do it even if I
had it. I mean, I technically could do
it, but I wouldn't do it.
rather go on um
go on a holiday with that money.
You know what I mean?
You can only really justify if you would
do it if he was a millionaire though, is it?
If he was a millionaire then it's
different, isn't it? Yeah. Would
you say that you're close to a millionaire?
Would you say you're almost a millionaire, Joe?
Yeah, I reckon you're a millionaire. Almost.
You have to be Joseph. Huh? Joseph,
are you almost a millionaire, Joseph?
Yeah, you are. You must be to be able to
do all this gambling then.
What are you familiar? Yeah,
you're almost a millionaire. Really?
Why would you say if you have over
£1,000, you're laughing?
Why would you say that?
Yeah, but you're going to be an old man.
Why are you laughing if you've got over £1,000?
You said before that if you have over
£1,000, you're laughing.
Like generally, how how do you work that one out?
Yeah, that's what you said. Yeah.
I've got like one point something. I
don't know. I don't really do much
nowadays, so I just save money.
But I need to get a new phone as well.
That's the thing. I'm getting some
birthday money as well. Yeah,
I don't really do much anymore.
Nothing to do. disease boobies.
Nah, you're not going to you're not
going to get me gambling. If I'm going
to gamble, bro, I'm going to do it on the football.
I think the phone will cost like300 pound.
You know, this phone. Yeah. I don't know
what's wrong with it. It's not letting
me do voice notes on Instagram,
Facebook, or anything like that. It's
not letting me do any any voice notes,
which is weird because the microphone's
not broken obviously because I'm talking
and it lets me do videos. But when I'm
trying to do on like Messenger and
stuff, it doesn't work. And I've looked
up every tutorial. I've tried everything
and it doesn't work.
It doesn't work on apps. I don't know why.
And obviously it can't be the microphone
because I'm talking.
I've done everything. Permissions all
stopped it, reset it. I've done
everything and it still doesn't work. I
don't know why.
Yeah, I really don't know why, man. Weird it
don't know why that is.
Maybe you can buy me the phone, Joe.
You can buy me the phone now. I'm poor. Huh?
I'm joking. But I am poor.
I just seen Selena Gomez on Instagram.
I'd love to have sex with I'd love to
have sex with Selena Gomez.
She's got some nice boobies. Um,
nothing. I'm about to go to sleep, bro.
My sleeping pattern's [ __ ] up,
you know. My sleeping pattern's [ __ ]
I sleep all day, bro, and then wake up. Yeah,
I don't do much these days, man.
Need to start doing stuff soon.
Just chilling, man.
It's win. You hibernate in the winter, don't you? Oh, mommy.
Yeah, I'm just chilling at the moment.
I've done a lot over the years. It's
only for now,
you know. I've done a lot over the
[ __ ] years. So,
you know, I'm just chilling out to be honest.
Yeah. Sometimes I think my life isn't
good, but then I compare myself to Monty
and Rice and then I feel fine again.
That's so weird to think that if Monty
didn't come on here yet, he might still
like have what he lost.
You know what I mean, Joe?
He might still have what he lost if he
didn't come on here.
I shouldn't have got him on here. I
You know, remember, you shouldn't
compare yourself to others.
Yeah, but that's different because you
compare myself to people that are in relationships
and just because other people in
relationships, that doesn't mean I'm
going to be in relationships cuz part of
meeting someone is luck.
So, I think that is different.
I think that is different when people
are comparing you to people in relationships
cuz maybe them people just got lucky,
you know? So
that's the difference. You know,
you know how it is.
Maybe I should try and find someone
to have a baby Peter with.
What do you think of that, Joe? Find
someone to have a baby Peter with. >> Oh,
that' be cute, wouldn't it?
But seriously, Monty needs to get off of YouTube.
Why don't he just get off YouTube? I
don't understand. It's going to end
really badly for him.
Will he just get off now?
I wouldn't like to be dealing with all that [ __ ]
No. Why would it be put into care? Why?
Why would it be put together?
No, it be cute.
Well, maybe the mommy can be the parent, huh?
Why do women want to use condoms during sex, Joe?
Some women will only [ __ ] you if you use
condoms. That's a bit boring, isn't it?
He must have pointed out.
Why do they want people to use condoms?
Yeah, but why do they want you to use
condoms? Why would they want that?
Why? Why? Why do I want people
to use condoms? Huh?
You'll need Viagra at your age, won't you guy?
I had a one night stand on my birthday.
She didn't make me wear a condom.
No, I'm not talking crap.
I'm being honest. Why do they want you
to wear a condom?
Yeah, I had a one night sound on my birthday
and she didn't make me wear condom.
Yeah, it was good.
So, if you overdose on Viagua,
do you die hard?
That's a joke by the way, Joe. I nicked
it from somewhere. Do you do you die hard
if you overdose on Viagra?
That's a good one, isn't it? [Laughter]
That's a good one, isn't it? Yeah. Oh,
that French woman's online. I'm going to
call her my mama. Hi, mama.
She's the one that said anyone will do.
That's my mama.
Nah, I've only took it once to try it. No.
Do you know what I hate is whenever you
get a one night stand, it's always when
you've masturbated three times that same day.
You'd always think, "Oh, you're going to
go out and get nowhere." And then when
you do finally get somewhere, you ain't
even got no come in you.
That's the mad thing. Always happens.
Sure you've noticed that as well.
Yeah, that French woman's my name, mama.
Yeah, she's my name, mama.
Anyone will do
what? I'm getting [ __ ] old. What the
[ __ ] do they want me to do, Joseph? Huh?
Do you remember when you said there's
plenty of room for me?
I can I can go and go and go. Me
sometimes I think of USA Izzy like the
um one night stand and not like just
pictures. Sometimes I think of Stig.
um the [ __ ] in the alleyway,
sometimes the one in Nottingham. I just
think of all of the experiences that I've had.
That's what I do over.
Yeah. It's fun.
Sometimes Joe, you can masturbate and
masturbate and masturbate
and still want sex. Then once you've had
sex, it relieves it.
No, you can't ask me something. Sorry,
I'm about to go sleep. Yeah. My mama.
What happened to my mama? Yeah,
sometimes I just masturbate over like
her boobs and stuff
in the time we spent together.
I don't know. Yeah. Really?
So you're saying Joe, you can live without women.
You reckon you could live without women?
I think I could.
Yeah, they're [ __ ]
Yeah, I think I could. Yeah,
maybe six, seven.
Yeah, six, seven. Baby.
Yeah, but could you could you could you
live without a woman?
Could be worse. I could have never
kissed any There's There's a guy I know.
He's 27. He's never had sex. Never kissed anyone.
saying that nonsense is 31 and he's
never had sex. So [ __ ] you know,
I think he's tried to have sex, but he
he hasn't managed to do it.
Something's wrong with his Pekka. Obviously wanks.
Yeah, but how would you have sex?
I wish I could have sex with Selena Gomez.
She's got a big curvy body. Joe,
I'm a strong person as well. I was
homeless at one point.
No, he's a virgin cuz we can't get a woman.
But nonslegs is a virgin.
Definitely a virgin.
Yeah, he's definitely a virgin. He is
a [ __ ] d virgin as well by the looks of it.
I've banged about 200 escorts, Joe.
Got to be about 200. Uh,
I would say Selena Gomez.
She has big boobs and she's got a curvy
body as well.
Keeps me warm in the winter. Yo, she
could keep me warm in the winter,
couldn't she? She could snuggle up in
the old nesticles and keep me warm. He uh
he could snuggle up next to me and give me huggles.
I bet she would look good pregnant as well. Yeah,
that'd be cute.
But yeah, that icon, that blonde one,
she she was nice, man. Especially when
she was like 22, 23.
She's older than me.
Now she just looks too old.
You know how you know um nonslegs is a uh
is is a non because he always says oh
16's legal 16 is legal and he tries to justify it. Um,
why would you try and justify it if you
if you didn't like that people that age
when you know that it's morally wrong,
you know? That is that is [ __ ] weird, is it?
Cuz I had this woman on Reddit say, "Oh,
you're speaking to a 19year-old." I
can't even remember. It was somebody I
approached. It was someone else. I
didn't even realize that person was 19.
And then I was and then she's like, "Oh,
you you 25 and above?" I said, "No, I
mean, I can get with a 22 23 year old if
I want to. That's perfectly fine. I
don't need to get with a woman that's 25
and above. 22 and 23 is completely fine.
I could get with a woman that's that
age. What the [ __ ]
Cuz that's weird." Um,
and I think I did say about how 19's not
a child, but the way he tries to justify
16 as being okay, you can just tell he's a nons because
why why would you argue with that?
It's so morally wrong. A 16y old
What do you think, Joe? Do you think
he's a nons?
Yeah, it's not me.
Yeah, there's a woman. There's some girl
in America. She said that she would suck
my dick at that and she's 19. And to be
honest with you,
I would get with a 19year-old
in terms of sex if they were really
good-looking. Now I'm older. If they
were really good-looking,
then I would. But I would never date
one. I would never ever date one. But if
they were that good-look and they'd have
to be really good-looking, then maybe I would.
But they'd have to be really [ __ ]
good-looking for me to get with a 19y old.
But I wouldn't
I really I think the minimum is like 22 23.
I'd say it's about 23 now. I'm almost
28. I'd get with a 23 year old.
Yeah. And the way he justifies it as
well. Why does why is he justifying it
if if he doesn't like a 16y old? That's
like me. I don't have anything in common
with a 19year-old.
I used to just get around to suck my
dick and that.
But why is that woman on Reddit saying
don't go for a woman if she's 25 and
younger? Um I was like I can get with a
23y old. What the [ __ ]
I wonder what she's up to now. That 19y
old. She's actually 20 now.
She doesn't message me anymore.
used to suck my dick. Yeah.
Yeah. I used to always say it's 18 and
above and he said it ain't state. He
said this isn't states in America.
He says this is not and he'd always get
he'd always get offended by it.
So he is definitely a non
just cuz he's with a woman that's older
than him now. That's probably because
that's all he can get. There's not
younger people. I reckon if he could
cold approach like me and he didn't have
anxiety, I reckon he would go for kids.
What do you think, Joe? It's only
because these disabled groups have
adults in them. I generally think he would
uh I reckon if he could approach like
me, I think he would have gone for kids.
What do you think? Uh,
what ones that [ __ ] up or didn't [ __ ]
up or either.
Oh, that boy was worth meeting me.
Well, none of them cuz they [ __ ] me
over in the end. episode.
Well, none because
Yeah, but that USA Izzy deserved
everything she got.
She was a [ __ ] No, she actually was a Um,
she was She was a [ __ ] though. She
She was a nasty [ __ ]
She was a nasty horrible [ __ ] Go Um,
I don't think USA is regretted meeting
me, but clearly she did,
but she was two-faced, so
I don't know.
No, that's what she should have done.
She should have said
she should have said, "That's fine. Move
on and stay in contact." She She went, "Ott,
what do you mean? I'm always starting from scratch.
No. What do you mean?
No. What are you talking about? Huh?
What are you all about? Oh.