Right, this [ __ ] has got me on the Billy
Bear [ __ ] sandwiches.
Now that ain't a good thing.
I just nipped out, got some tea bags,
made a tea, and I'm having some [ __ ]
Billy Bear sandwiches. This [ __ ] lied to
us. He said we was talking about babies. The liar.
You [ __ ] liar, Rickster.
I'm nothing but a liar. You are.
I see you for what you are.
You're nothing but a horrible little liar.
You said I'm decent looking. Shout out
to the women that keep pretending they
got [ __ ] boyfriends. You [ __ ] tank. Lovely sandwiches. [Music]
Can't be nice. Very bad sandwiches.
Yep. Eating some belly bear sandwiches. M.
This is what you call Ricky. Me to sandwiches. [ __ ] B.
You need to [ __ ] read a book on how
to stop contradicting your [ __ ] self, you [ __ ]
I'm going to come to Holland. I'm going
to do you, mate.
Right. You're pissing me off. If I need
to put any more of these approaching
videos up, I've reached my daily limit.
But if I need to put any more up, mate,
I'm [ __ ] coming to hunt and I'm going
to [ __ ] do you.
Yeah. I'm not going to go burn with him,
mate. I going to [ __ ] hunt. Yeah.
Yeah. We have out face to face. You
liar. You said people was talking about
babies. That's why they can't let women.
You [ __ ] lying.
You're a [ __ ] liar. Bad savages.
They are lush.
Where are you?
You're just jealous. [ __ ] off. You're
just jealous cuz you can't go be you little virgin.
You better little virgin. Shut the [ __ ] up.
Roll up my beard and your ugly face.
[ __ ] [ __ ] You're jealous of me.
That's what you are. Jealous.
You're jealous of me, mate. You can't
grow a beard cuz you ain't got the genetics.
I'm not not taking a piss. Not taking a
piss at all, mate. I just went to the
local supermarket, just spent [ __ ]
How much was it? [ __ ] eight quid. Jesus Christ
on the sal bags. This living is getting
too too dear.
Bring it down and burn Huh? Heat.
That doesn't make any sense.
Super bus bar.
too much bother.
You're not again. Why?
I'm having some belly bear sandwiches at the minute. Look.
What do you mean grow up? I've been
eating it since I was a a ba rice.
I've been eating it since I was a bubin.
I'm not going to stop now. Even though
the the bottle was quite thick. So
no, I'm never stopping you. What?
It's a [ __ ] hookup culture, is it, man?
So, R, what's your problem? Huh?
If we have a fight and I beat you, K has
to give me a [ __ ]
Only joking. Oh, Franklin got it all gun.
Franklin is shooting them copies. Aha.
Oh, I died abortion.
Oh, this person called me cute. It
reminds me of the good old USA times
when I got called cute. Really does.
I can't finish that rice because the
butter is too thick. I couldn't spread
the butter because there was something
wrong with it.
But that's all right.
Just have some of it.
might be going to Hull soon. Um, Rice.
Yeah. To confront that Ricky. He's been
doing my [ __ ] heading as of late.
So, I might go and give him a little visit.
If I have to post one more video, mate,
I'm [ __ ] coming to do you in. And I'm
not playing around anymore,
you know? What's up? S
Can't believe he's got me on a He's got
me on the [ __ ] Billy Bear sandwiches.
Rise. Come to Hull. I'm going to Hull to
[ __ ] that Ricky Millington up. He's got
me on the Billy Bear sandwiches. He's a
nasty bast rude.
Nice cup of tea.
I've took my little cucados. Yeah. What's
Why have you gone back to white theme?
You silly goose.
Right on a minute.
Oh gosh, I'm stuck
to them Billy Bear sandwiches.
I had some Billy Bear sandwiches, man.
>> My experiences don't suit them. They No, that's
Why do I keep getting matches from
people from Thailand?
My struggles don't suit you.
They don't suit you.
I'm going to Hal.
I got a friend in the hull, by the way.
I met him in Leeds.
I need to catch up with him. It's been a
long time, man. Poor guy. He lives in the hull. Oh, man. Mama Why we doing
that's not true?
Yeah, it doesn't. I show these people
clear as day proof and they just shake
their head like no
don't suit them.
Don't shoot them.
Yeah. Why is nobody joining my little live stream?
What are you doing?
I'm not replying to you anymore, Ricky.
You're a troll.
Right. What's going on here then?
I can't meet anyone on day me.
Oh, is that a match?
I don't have any matches. Rice.
I'm not sure why, you know.
really not sure why. Let's see.
See, the reason why Monty never tried
with me is
I'm just watching the video of Rice and
Monty fighting is cuz Monty has known me
for many years.
He's known me for many, many, many years.
So, you know, he wouldn't like
he wouldn't fight me because we've known
each other for years, you know.
since I was [ __ ] 16.
So I mean that's 12 years.
Me and Monty go way back.
So that's why
I could defeat him though if I wanted to.
I'm surprised he didn't try to hit me
though to be honest.
I'm really surprised
to, you know,
I miss Best. Oh gosh. Ow.
We need your remote.
He's coming out in a couple of days.
Luckily, I've got some money for you,
Franklin, too, to keep you to keep you
going for the month.
We're not making it, lads. Yeah.
I guess mommy's tired. So
come all knows her zero life experiences
has never known more women than me.
Well, considering I've been up and down
the country for multiple years meeting
women, I definitely know more women than
you, mate. I've been with more women
than you have. Just because they weren't
relationships, it doesn't mean I
haven't. Of course, I've been with Of
course I've known more women than you,
you silly [ __ ]
What the [ __ ]
I've been on more dates than you as
well. Been on more dates, been with more
women. Just because I haven't been in
more relationship, it doesn't mean anything.
You've only been in like three relationships.
You definitely I I definitely know more
women than you. Been on more dates.
You've only been in three relationships
and you've slept with none of them.
That's why he's still a virgin. But you
you get what I'm saying. N
he's jealous of USA, is he?
How can he say that I don't know more
women than him when I've literally been
with more women than him and I've been
on more dates than him and I've met more
women than him?
How do I not know more? Of course I know
more women than you. I've met more women
Okay. Yeah, they're strangers on the
street, right? Everyone's a stranger to
begin with. And whether I got rejected
or I didn't get rejected, I've met more
women than you.
What does it matter if I didn't get
rejected or I got rejected? Yes, I've
met more women than you, which is how I
know they're all the same. What the [ __ ]
Wait, wait, wait. So, you can't have an
opinion on a woman that you've met
because you don't know them.
So you you can't have an opinion on what
they've done because you don't know
them. That does it doesn't count as an
experience because you don't know them.
The [ __ ] That's stupid.
Every single one of them has rejected
them. Not entirely true. I've been with
multiple women. I've been on multiple
dates. Not entirely true. Um but yeah, a
lot of them have. Just like they would
reject you. That's why you rely on paid dating apps, you know.
So just because you don't know them for
100 years, that doesn't count as an
experience because they're a stranger on the street.
What the [ __ ] The guy's a [ __ ] idiot.
And you would also get rejected if you
went out cold approaching. You would
have never been with anyone.
You would never. That's why you
resort to [ __ ] disabled girls,
right? You're in a relationship with one
woman. Yeah, that that's one woman, a
disabled woman, that's not women, that's
a woman, [ __ ]
Oh, yeah. And by and by the way, just because
you don't know someone for a very long
time, you can't have an opinion on what
they've done because you don't know them.
Does it make sense? Doesn't make any
sense. So if I if I if I if I meet a
woman and and she leads me on, let's
just say argument sake, I can't have an
opinion because I don't know her.
What is this bl knowing [ __ ] got to do
with anything? I don't understand.
Yes, I have had a girlfriend. And even
if I didn't have a girlfriend, that
doesn't mean anything. I have more life
experience than you. I have encountered
more women than you. I have been on more
dates than you. I know more women than
then and [ __ ] now. Yes, I do, dumb nuts.
You've been in three relationships which
neither of them have slept with you.
Congratulations. You're older than me.
You've been in three relationships and literally
I mean what the [ __ ]
Sorry about that, bro.
And man was like, "My mom agreed with
me." I said, "Well, my mom don't agree
with me, and I've had way more bad
experiences than you."
Well, and he's telling me about his nan and [ __ ]
He's an idiot.
He's an absolute idiot.
I don't know why he's going on like he's
never been rejected. Another that's
another thing. If you went around
approaching as much I did, you would
never even have got a date. You're that
ugly. So, I don't know why you you going
on about cold approaches and why you
need to know somebody to have an opinion
on them. That doesn't make any sense. It
doesn't matter if they're strangers.
They're doing the same [ __ ] They're
saying the same [ __ ]
You don't need to [ __ ] know them
to know that they're all the same. [ __ ]
Uh, no. I would not sleep in a bed with
another woman because I like my own bed.
Unless the bed was actually really,
really big. No, I like my own space. You
know, you're supposed to sleep by
yourself. You do realize scientists tell
you that you're supposed to sleep by
yourself. Like, no. I've been next to
somebody in bed before and I've kicked
them out again. Another idiot.
Oh, no one cares about the Morgan stuff.
You're just you're just you're just an
insecure virgin. That's boring. Now I'm
but I want to get on to the bit where
you know you say about um
I have been with more women than you and
I know more women than you will ever
know. Not that you know that you will
ever know. You're an idiot. You're an
absolute [ __ ] idiot.
And you know, the fact that you're still
going on about my sloppy seconds, it
just shows how much of an insecure
virgin you really are. No, no one cares
about it. It just goes to show that
you're obsessed. Very, very, very
Really, really. It just goes to show how
obsessed you are. Cuz think of how many
women I've been with since this person
that he's mentioning, yet he's still
obsessed and convincing himself that
I've not slept with this person.
It shows you the virgin. Really just
shows everything I say is right. You know,
he's still obsessed with the same person
from years ago.
Yeah, it's just repeating, man. Your
channel was boring.
Your channel was very, very boring, mate.
I don't understand how this virgin is
trying to say that I don't know more
women than him.
I mean, that is ridiculous.
Very, very ridiculous. I absolutely know
way more women than you will ever know. Been
you're obsessed. Very obsessed. The
whole world is is is
convincing yourself that people ain't
slept with people. It's [ __ ] sad,
man. It's really really sad.
Really, really. Like, it doesn't even
bother me. It's just sad.
It just shows how much of a virgin you
are, you know, the more you do it.
Like, it it don't even matter why you do
it. I mean, your whole world, your whole
life is obsessing and convincing
yourself things to make yourself feel
better about the fact that you got
rejected by Britney. It's so sad.
You would have thought like in years
time people would have moved on.
It's all You compare a lot of my
situations to the Britney situation.
Really, really sad.
I wish I could do a video, man, but I can't. You spent
two hours and
Yeah, you spent almost two hours doing
live streams talking about me and some
random one night stand from years ago. I
mean, you really really are.
You need some serious help.
that Britney for you. You seem to think
everyone's the same as you and Britney.
I don't know why you seem to think just
because Britney rejected you.
I mean, it's it's weird. Why are you so obsessed?
So, we're really really wondering that as well
cuz you are literally convincing
yourself that I've not had sex with
people. No one's saying that you should
believe me or you shouldn't believe me,
but you keep going on about it. So the
more you go on about it, the more you
must believe I actually have really
cuz why are you why do you keep
validating yourself? Why do you keep
convincing yourself things?
That's what I'd love to know.
So cuz you know that I have slept with them.
You know you are so so boring.
And if I lied about sleeping with someone,
I've slept with about three women since
this person that obviously weren't
escorts, maybe four women. I mean, why
are you so do you do you seem to find it um
a uh relatable you do you seem to think
it's relatable to you and Britney?
That's the only thing I can think of
that it must be. Yeah.
You I explained the [ __ ] story about
a million times. I don't know why you
keep going on about it. It's
very all all your channel comes across
as as an insecure virgin. That's the
only thing that your channel comes
across as. I can't lie.
I mean, that is mad. It's
Everyone needs to be like Kim and
Britney. Everyone needs to be a virgin like him.
or or if not then he's he's not happy.
It's strange. He is a very strange
individual isn't it? I must say Brian
the more you convince yourself the more
it more likely it is that you believe it
to be honest with you. You know
we got Sig, we got that one from
Nottingham. We got a one my birthday. We
got a 19year-old.
It's very weird to cling on to somebody
from a couple of years ago still
convincing yourself that I've not slept with them.
It's so weird. You are obsessed.
Oh my god. If you if if I lied about
sleeping with someone, I mean, the
difference is not me being a virgin and
not me and me not being a virgin because
I've already slept with people before
and after them. So why that's really you
convincing yourself things at this point really is.
I mean we're almost in a new year so
it'll basically be 3 years. Okay.
It didn't happen with him. I didn't meet
her. What the [ __ ]
No, you didn't. [ __ ] Aisha Bouty.
No, you did not. It's because you said
that you had sex on a park bench. It's
not believable. Not because I didn't
have sex with her. You [ __ ] idiot.
And I assure you that if you went around [ __ ] approaching,
you would get rejected by every single
woman. There wouldn't there wouldn't
have been [ __ ] you know what I'm saying? Yeah,
more rejections. You've paid for five
dating apps and you've never put
yourself out there and you think that's
a win because you haven't given your ch
yourself a chance to get rejected. The
guy's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's a madness.
Is actually a madness, bro.
You're the one convincing yourself
people ain't slept with people,
you know. It's [ __ ] wild.
He thinks everything is a Britney and him situation.
He's so insecure. He really, really,
really is insecure, bro. It's actually
It's actually quite sad to see. You know,
I have absolutely met more women than
you, just like I have been to more
places than you where I've met these
women more than you.
I've had more life experience than you
because I've had more money than you.
How have I not met more women than you?
You literally convince yourself people
haven't slept with anyone. You're that
sad. when it ain't even the difference
between people being a virgin and not
being a virgin. You're that sad? What?
Because the one night stand
lie that she didn't sleep with me to say
face. How many times has that happened?
I bet that's happened a million times.
You know, it's it's crazy. No one's
going to admit to some little skint
virgin that they don't know that they
[ __ ] someone that they've met once. Use
your sense. and and you are still pretty
not sure about it to be honest. That's
why you keep convincing yourself things
when no one cares about it, you know, cuz
you're the only one that goes on about
it. No one else.
So, it must mean you there's some sort of
you're not sure kind of. See, I don't
lie about things, you know?
You know what I'm saying?
The guy is an absolute [ __ ]
I feel bad for him.
How can he say that I've not met more
women than him when I mean rejected by
women? Bro, you have never put yourself
out there cuz you ain't got the balls
cuz you of anxiety. That's the only
reason your ugly ass has never been
rejected by somebody in [ __ ] public.
The guy is a [ __ ] [ __ ] man.
You go out and, you know, cuz you're so
you're so scared of rejection. That's
why you used to [ __ ] sit there and
say, "Oh, I've never been rejecting me."
When you'd think at 31 years of age, I'm
pretty sure everyone's been rejected.
Unless they've been in a relationship
their whole life. Obviously, then that's
different. But how have you not been
rejected at 31 years of age?
Don't you think that's a bit strange?
No, your your girlfriend is literally a
dwarf and she's disabled.
Okay. What the [ __ ] this person.
And it's not even like me reacting.
You're the only one
that that spends all your life convincing yourself
people ain't had sex with people.
You know, I think it's getting a bit sad now.
uh you know it's it's almost 20 it's almost 2026
and you're still convincing yourself
things to make yourself feel better you know
I think it needs to kind of stop now
it's getting a bit old I would have Oh, okay. So
just uh you contradicting yourself cuz
you were saying that I was calling
yourself your girlfriend this that and
the other and
then you're saying that I've got a big
nose and I'm ugly. So would that also
make you a bully? These low IQ people
really do make it too easy for me. Swear
down but I feel like I'm pretending to
be sometimes. So, it's okay for you to
call people names,
call people ugly, but when somebody
tells you a few hundred about your
girlfriend, it's bullying. Oh, [ __ ]
hell. You really are a [ __ ] aren't
you? I mean, some of these some of these
[ __ ] people, bro, I swear to God. Ah,
didn't you call Monty's girlfriend fat
and ugly before?
So, is it only bullying when someone
says something about your girlfriend?
What a [ __ ] bro.
Okay. Women would every single woman in
the world would reject you if you
approached them literately.
Which is why you get bitter. The only
reason you get bitter that other people
can meet women and speak to women
because you can't do that. And that's
why you had to resort to a [ __ ]
disabled girl. Everybody knows that, you know.
What a [ __ ] absolute [ __ ] you know.
What is that?
no evidence to go with that you're a
nons other than you continuously argue
the fact that it's morally right to go
with a 16year-old. I think that would
that would be that would class as you
being a nod. I mean that that that is
that is pretty good evidence is it
really you know
there's no evidence to suggest that
you're a n other than when somebody says
it's wrong to get with a 16y old oh uh
it's legal with America generally I
reckon if you had a balls to approach
which you would never do cuz you got
anxiety which is why you bother disabled
girls you would have probably got with a
kid by now I genuinely think you would of Um, so
there is evidence that you were an aunt
and the whole Britney thing as well. I mean,
if you said to me, "Get with us. Would I
get with a 16y old?" I tell you the [ __ ]
right off. She could be an 11 out of 10.
I go 16y old. Him, on the other hand,
would say, "Oh, uh, I'm Oh, it's legal
in certain states." parts of America and
then you would justify how it's somehow
morally right. Yeah, I think that means
you're you're a nons, mate.
It really really [ __ ] does, you know,
especially someone in their 20s.
>> Yeah, I've got the same baby, bro. to to
to give it to another baby who joins the
family. It's nothing to do with nons
even though in your nons head you would
think that you know it's oh sh should I
do a video and rip this [ __ ] to shreds like
yeah I've got a baby bro you don't enter
to chuck memories it's nothing to do
with nonsery as you're making out mate
we're not all a nons like your dad
so the fact that your dad's a nons the
fact that [ __ ] you know what I
Wanking material. That's definitely
definitely a nons. That is that is
definitely definitely definitely a [ __ ] nons.
Use it saying that's wanking material.
Definitely definitely a nons. You are
only a nons would think that. Definitely
definitely only a nod would think that.
That is disgusting, bro.
Who even would come out with something
like that unless they're thinking it. Oh my god,
that is vile, bro.
I'm not the one always sat there trying
to justify how it's being with a
16-year-old is legal and it's a [ __ ] child. You know,
I understand if it's like like I I
example. This person was trying to say
you can't go with anyone younger than 25.
And I was like, well, yes, I can cuz
they're in their 20s and they're an
adult. 16 is not an adult. Why are you
trying to justify why somebody can't go an adult?
>> Yeah. It's cuz you're a [ __ ] non yourself.
Y we all [ __ ] ns. Yeah,
you're still going on about USA, is he?
I don't understand. I really really
really don't understand this. It's 2026,
mate. You need to you need to really stop that.
Really [ __ ] madness, man.
How can he sit there and say that I've
not met more than him?
So that's how you are a nons.
Why would you why why do you want to be
with why do you want to go near a 16-year-old?
And again, nothing says you have to know
somebody for years
to judge someone's actions.
That That's not the way it works,
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying? He's
he's a he's a he's a he is an actually
he's low IQ this guy but I swear to God
he really is yeah
also you went with a 17y old when you was 21 knots Uh,
no. That's not a box. See, take him
back. No, what what I want to know is why
do you want to be with a 16year-old so
mad? And yeah, okay, you you might have
a girlfriend, but that's just your cover up.
Why you was you so desperate about 16
year olds? I I want to know that when
you're in your 20s,
didn't you just go along with it because
you wouldn't want to go with a
16-year-old? I don't understand it. Really don't. Yeah.
Hopefully you take it down for YouTube today.
That is not a human. No human.
He's an idiot, man.
Oh, here we go. Morgan again. He's obsessed.
He is so
determined to convince himself that it's
a Hill and Britney situation. I'm
actually like, this is crazy, bro. The
girl told you something that you wanted
to hear because she had some random skin
[ __ ] [ __ ] messaging her. It's it
she's not going to tell you the truth
when somebody knows her name. And better
yet, I don't understand why you would
care if you believe what you're saying
because you know that it's [ __ ] Simple.
Yes, of course you believe what she says
because you're so determined that it's
you and Britney situation and how you
are a virgin. So, of course you would
believe something a stranger who I've
met once said cuz how many years have
you been convincing people that they're
a virgin like you? You know, this is not
this is not the [ __ ] first time. You
know, not the first time. Not the last
time. It won't be the last time.
You know, you
you know what I'm saying?
It's You're so desperate to want to
think people are virgin just cuz you're
a virgin. I mean, like the whole escort
thing. Why did you really need
confirmation from someone's [ __ ]
mother? All cuz you can't get laid. All
cuz you are still a virgin. Why the [ __ ]
did my mom have to [ __ ] tell you? You
know, if I knew you was convincing other
people stuff cuz you were a virgin
yourself, I would have told her not to bother.
How many times have people lied about
being raped? And that's a pretty that's
a pretty [ __ ] um that's a pretty
severe accusation. How many times have
people lied about people that they've
met once? many many times. You're so
desperate to cling on to any kind of
hope that I got rejected like Britney
rejected you. You know what? I'm I'm
[ __ ] really going to going to [ __ ]
do a video on this [ __ ] bro.
Like I said, it is almost 2026, mate.
And it's getting boring now. Really [ __ ] boring. Yeah.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Yeah, this is this is very very very
very strange. Very
very very very very strange. This guy
is really weird though.
I found that beard. So
the irony of someone talking about
someone's beard when they've got no
teeth. Oh, the irony. Huh?
And I understand how someone can have no
teeth and then judge someone else's appearance.
That's always seemed weird to me to be honest.
You have a YouTube channel
calling someone ugly all day cuz you're
the ugly one. Even when I when I don't
see you doing it, I know you're doing
it. No, no. You are the one that's
insecure. You're not pick not [ __ ]
copy my [ __ ] words.
I'm the biggest reject into society. You
can't even go to normal events.
You can't even function in normal
events. I mean, your mom starved you.
I mean, let's let's not talk about society
like it's ridiculous. And I love how
he's saying as if if he went out, he
would It's mad, isn't it?
Lives my bloody mother. You live in a in
a cancelled bedsit, so you might want to
actually get your own place before
talking about people and who people live
with. And I've explained this about a
million times, but every time somebody
explains this to you, right,
you live in a cancelled bedsit with no
bed. That is worse than living with your
mother. And you don't even live in
London. So again, before trying to talk
about other people, you might want to
get your own place and actually get a
bed. Just like you you should get some
teeth before trying to talk about other
people's [ __ ] beards. I mean, are we
really having a conversation about [ __ ] beards?
You know, why do you care who people's
live with? You live in a in outer London
in a bedsit. I mean, what what why do
you care about who people live with? You
live in a shitty bedsit
with no bed.
I don't understand.
You live in a [ __ ] cancel bedsit. I
don't know how many times I have to
repeat this. your living circumstances
ain't that great. And also in London,
people live either in a box room or they
live with their parents,
which is obviously you didn't because
your mom starved you and she kicked you out.
Obviously, that's a bit [ __ ]
different. You would have learned these
things growing up. You know,
you live in a council bedsit with no bed in it.
That is literal facts.
Want to take the piss out of my mom? Yet
your mom stared you.
You live in a
So he's taking the piss out of basically
most people my age that live in London basically. Oh,
why does this virgin in a council bed
sit care about who people live with?
I really really really don't understand it
when he's living circumstances is
[ __ ] He's got no teeth. He's got no
bed. He's got no money. He's got no life
experiences. And then he seems to think
he can he can judge other people's lives.
I I don't I I I I don't understand.
I really really really really don't
understand how someone like him can try
to judge other people's lives. I really don't.
I mean, it's strange, bro, isn't it?
I don't know how you can keep giving it
the big in your little shitty out of
London council bedsit trying to tell
people who they live with. I really really don't, you know.
It's strange. Very, very, very strange.
There's people in their 30s that live
with their parents in London. Your mom
kicked you out and starved you. So, you
you didn't know about that stuff. You
know, you was abused as a child. So, you
it's like if you actually lived in
London, you'd be living with your daddy.
Exactly. You live in a council bedsit
with no bed, not even a house. So,
please again stop telling me who I live
with. Thank you.
Oh my god. This is what I'm saying,
Ricky. I've gone over this and a lot of
it is just the same old [ __ ] It is the
same old [ __ ] over and over and over
again. Yet, you're saying that my
content is repeating and boring. So why
do I keep catching you on this virgin
channel over and over and over and over
and over again? A lot of it is repeated,
mate, you know.
Okay. Okay. One sec.
I need to talk about that rejection
thing. I don't know why he keeps telling
people that he's not been rejected when
he [ __ ] well has.
Britney being one of them, other women
being one of them that's broke up with
him. I don't know what is this ego with
him. It's part of his insecurity where
he thinks he's never been rejected when
he [ __ ] well has because someone that
has not been rejected will not be with a disabled girl.
I mean, can you at least do one of these
things? Like, I don't I I Bro, I
seriously don't get it. You know, why do
you keep telling people you've never been rejected?
There's literally not one person on
earth who's 31 that's not been rejected
unless they've never tried or they've
been in a relationship all their life.
You have been rejected. You [ __ ] well
have. What would you What would you
class Britney as if that wasn't a
rejection? that you're crying over some
girl who don't want you. Okay. What if
that's not rejection?
You know what is? I mean, I've seen you
get rejected in my face by somebody in
an Eminem shop, but you will try to
brush it off because, you know, you
don't want to say that you've been
rejected. You would have been rejected
by every single woman if you dated normal women.
You know what the [ __ ] The guy is an idiot. It's
you've never been rejected at 31 years
of age. I mean, women have been rejected
for [ __ ] sake. How have you somehow
made it to the age of 31 and not been rejected?
You literally have been rejected. You
had to go on five dating apps and get
with disabled women. And you know it
deep down. That's why you spend half
your life convincing yourself, I've not
slept with people who I've met once.
Yeah, that that's that's part of the [ __ ] reason. Know
been on more dates than him, met more
women than him, had have more women
friends than him, but I don't know more
women than you.
How do you How does that one make sense, bro?
But I don't know more women than you. Okay.
So, out your own living circumstances
and get your teeth fixed before trying
to judge other people's lives. You know,
you live in a shitty council bedsit.
You've never had a job. You don't have a
job. You don't have no money. And yes,
13 grand is no [ __ ] money. And you're
trying to judge other people's lives. I
mean, people in that position shouldn't
be judging other people's lives. You
know what I'm saying? You got no life
experience. I can sit here on my wands
and say I've got more life experience
than you and I'm younger than you.
But you're trying to talk about my life.
What the [ __ ] would you? It's weird,
bro. Really weird. Look at
that. This is pretty boring to be fair. Okay.
Yeah. When someone talks about your ugly
girlfriend, they're a bully. They're a
Oh, [ __ ] hell. Yes, sir.
Why are we talking about down syndromes
that are together?
You say that people's insecure, yet your
whole life is trying to convince
yourself that people ain't had sex with
random ass people that you don't even [ __ ] know.
But I'm the insecure one. Yeah, I'm on
YouTube doing my own [ __ ] thing. [ __ ]
out of here, virgin boy.
To grow up.
You have got erectile dysfunction.
You're a virgin. Yes.
How many hours of your day do you spend
convincing yourself these things? It
can't be it can't be helping, you know.
But my life is better than yours, you know.
I don't know what insecure vibes I I
give out. I mean, you I go on your
channel, you're sat on YouTube every day
calling me ugly when I'm better looking
than you. You convince yourself I'm not
had sex with people. I mean, I don't
know what I do that makes me insecure. I
know what you do.
He's older than me and his life is
[ __ ] worse than mine and he's and
he's trying to talk about my life. How
can someone older than you with a worse
life than you try and talk and try and
talk about other people's lives? I have no idea.
What the [ __ ] would you would you do?
Eh, you know,
you've been saying the same [ __ ] with
19. I I I know like
your mom I know your mom starved you and
stuff and whatever, but you know there's
nothing wrong with with people living
with a parent. We understand that your
mom abused you and you know whatever and
and she kicked you out, but you know
it's you're getting a bit salty now, man. Really,
you you go on like you're independent.
You've never had a job. You've got
absolutely no money. You don't even have
a bed. I don't understand why you're
trying to compare your life to [ __ ]
mine. It's weird. It honestly is.
You got no assets. You've It took you
till 30 to go abroad cuz you couldn't
afford it. You Your life is worse than
mine. And you're 31.
Your life is is is is worse than mine,
kid. So don't don't try and talk about
other people's [ __ ] lives.
You know, it's weird. What would you
actually do if you was in London and you
didn't get a council house cuz you
wouldn't be able to afford to live by
yourself. So, what would you do?
You know, it's very very strange. He's
got really deep rooted mummy issues. I
swear to God, man. He really does. You
live in a council shitty bedsit with no
bed. I don't know how many times someone
has to explain that you are not living
in good living circumstances.
You live in a cancel bed.
I mean I don't know how many times
someone has to keep [ __ ] repeating
the same [ __ ] You have got no car. You
have got no money. At the end of the
day, people like that I would think,
yeah, they could try and tell me about my life.
I mean, you haven't even [ __ ] worked.
Like, I can actually sit there and say, "Yeah,
I've had a I've had a couple of jobs,
right, and and and whatever, you know,
and I've and I've worked before and I've
had responsibilities and stuff." You
know what I'm saying? You've never even
worked. You've got no [ __ ] money. You
know, it's took you [ __ ] years to
show a little tiny bit amount of money
and you think that you are in a position
to judge other people's [ __ ] lives.
What the [ __ ] am I [ __ ] hearing?
You're probably the biggest loser at 31
to be honest with you. Like, I'm not
even joking, bro. 31.
Like, your priorities are are supposed
to change when you're like 27, 28. Um,
yet you're 31 and you have nothing.
Literally, [ __ ] all. You haven't even
been on a [ __ ] plane. I mean, what
the [ __ ] Like I can I can name a couple
of [ __ ] examples.
So could you live in a bed sit with no
bed with a disabled girlfriend? All of a
sudden you can start judging people's lives.
Please. Good. It's embarrassing. Very
very very very embarrassing. And I don't
even think that you're in it you're in a
happy relationship because of how much
you go on about my droppy seconds.
I absolutely know more women than you
then and now. That's what I'm going to
title the video. Uh, yes, I [ __ ] well
do. You know,
you haven't been on a plane. You don't
have a bed. You got [ __ ] all money. You
got no life experience.
And you talk about me. How was How was that? Uh,
you don't need to keep putting on the
disabled voice. You already sound
disabled. So, I don't know. You know,
every time you're switching, you sound
better. You sound better when you switch
or you don't switch because you sound
like a [ __ ] [ __ ] So, just just
putting it out there.
How are you going to sit there in your
shitty little council bedset and um
try and judge other people's lives
rather than your own life? I I I [ __ ]
don't understand that one >> really. Yeah. Okay.
I don't know why he he keeps talking
about who people live with. I know I've
answered this. I've said this before,
but it's never been answered.
I'm insecure. Why? Why am I insecure?
You're the one convincing yourself that
every situation that I've been in has
been the same as you and Britney when
she [ __ ] rejected you. But there's no
evidence that I'm insecure about
anything. You are the one that wastes
every day of your life on YouTube
calling people ugly, but the only one
that's ugly is you and your girlfriend,
but you you you still covered YouTube
and [ __ ] do it. That's the acts of an
insecure person. There's no there's nothing
that is insecure about me.
There's literally [ __ ] all. Show my
face. Don't talk about anyone else because
Yeah. I I mean,
back up what you [ __ ] say. You can't
do idiot. [ __ ] absolute buffoon.
as [ __ ] This guy [ __ ]
He says that with his disabled girlfriend. one sec.
But why you would get rejected just like
you have been rejected which is why you
had to pay for dating apps.
You know what I'm saying? You would
never you don't have the balls to do it.
Look how you react when [ __ ] people
[ __ ] talk to people.
He's an absolute bro. He is so insecure.
You would have thought somebody at his
age would have would have called it a
day. You know what I'm saying?
Sat there in these shitty little pencil
benefit beds sit trying to judge other
people's [ __ ] lives. Do you know what
I'm saying? It's it to be honest with
you, it is [ __ ] crazy.
Who knows? Again, I'm insecure
apparently. He is the one that keeps
talking about my looks, but I'm the one
that's insecure. You waste a lot of time
talking about my looks, but me, the one
being insecure apparently, right?
You're better looking, I'm insecure, yet
you waste all your life.
I'm not so sure, mate. You know, you can
only you can only fool people on here
really, if you think about it.
I mean, all you do is come online every
day talking about people's looks because
the fact is you and your girlfriend are
the ugly ones.
Ugly fat [ __ ] and you're a scrawny ugly
skinny little [ __ ] with ugly clothes.
That's that that's that's that's the thing, bro.
You know what I'm saying?
See, this is really strange, bro. This
is really, really, really, really,
really, really strange.
I just don't understand how a 31year-old
loser can critique somebody that's
younger than him.
I shot someone, bro. It's [ __ ] weird.
It's so [ __ ] strange. You would to
get off YouTube and live your life. You
know what I'm saying? Any normal person,
but you? Nah, not you, mate.
Can't do that.
You've been rejected by Britney. You've
been rejected by other women. Don't sit
there in your virgin shitty cancel
medset and try and [ __ ] tell people
that you ain't been rejected cuz you're
[ __ ] well off, mate. Because to end
up with somebody as disabled as that,
he's a he's a [ __ ] idiot.
But I'm insecure.
Look at my channel, bro. My channel's
normal. There's no more stuff in my channel. You know,
you got rejected by every single woman
except the one that you're obsessed
with. That one. That one. That one. just
living, you know,
convincing himself every single day that
people ain't slept with people. So at at
the [ __ ] at the first part, bro,
yeah, I was like I used to think, what
the actual [ __ ] But now I just actually
just just see it as just weird.
Obviously have to mention that.
Also, I've got I've also got to mention
that it's I've been on a channel and
most of it is just repeating, but you
said you didn't like boring repeats,
but that channel is repeating and boring
cuz we've heard all of this for years.
All of this same old [ __ ] same old
little virgin convincing himself that
people ain't slept with people cuz
Britney never slept with him. I mean,
you would think at our age people would
have grown up now. You know,
weirdo, you have to question, you know,
what someone's life is about when
they're sat on YouTube doing this day in
day out, day in day out. You know, you
really really need to think that this c
person can't be happy with their life, man.
You know, it's it's it's it's [ __ ] weird. Obsessed.
Nah, someone like that can't be happy
with their life, man. Constantly waking
up every day trying to [ __ ] with
someone. Nah, there's no way.
There's no way a happy person does that.
Reaction or no reaction. So, you might
want to sort your shitty skinned virgin
life out before trying to judge other people's
at all because they're a stranger. We
can't judge them. We can't judge the
things that they do because we haven't
known them for hundred years. New rule,
by the way.
That is just that's the badest thing
I've ever heard. You know, you know,
if you literally approached and you
didn't target disabled women, you would
get rejected by literally every single
[ __ ] woman. You you you're so ugly
you wouldn't even get a number.
That's how bad it is. A number doesn't
even [ __ ] mean anything.
That is strange, bro.
He is he is [ __ ] Why does he care so
much about who people live with when he
lives in a bedset owned by the council,
not even a house? I I I really want a
response. I actually want like a whole
like video dedicated to why somebody in
a bedset with no job thinks that they
can judge other people's lives.
I I just I just want to know that. It'd
be interesting. It'd be really really
interesting to hear that cuz you're not
you're not [ __ ] you know high status.
You know the only reason you you you
know you you you've got a tiny amount of
money is because you sat in for 3 years
and saved it. [ __ ] anyone can do it. So weird.
Nobody is insecure but you
day in day out convincing yourself that
people ain't had sex with people.
[ __ ] what a sad life.
And it's not for reaction either because
uh I'm not explaining it but you're not
going to get out of the way by just
saying it's for reaction. You've been
doing it for [ __ ] years.
You think everyone's a virgin like you?
I mean, how many years are you going to
keep [ __ ] doing this,
you know? It's mad. It's It's You would
get rejected by every single woman if
you did not resort to a disabled girl.
You would get rejected by every single [ __ ] woman.
Like every single woman and I and I mean
no no every single [ __ ] woman. Like
I'm not even joking.
Really? You ain't got no job. You barely
got any money.
But you talk about other people other
people's lives. Why don't you sort your
life out? Get off of YouTube. Stop
harassing people every [ __ ] day cuz
you're an insecure little virgin. You
know, you might want to take your own
advice. Get off YouTube. Go get yourself
a [ __ ] job, but you've never worked.
Go sort your own ugly [ __ ] shitty
life out. You're [ __ ] in your virgin
with shitty meds before trying to preach to others.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
You need to [ __ ] grow up.
You've never ever ever had a job. Not
even a job in your life. Imagine that.
You've never had a job in your life. Ever. You know
guys are tall.
USA is you're a sad bastard.
It shows how much of a virgin you are
the more you do it.
Not everyone not everyone is not every
situation is the same as you and
Britney's. I think that honestly is
going to be is going to be titled uh video.
Honest to God
like you need to stop thinking that
everyone is the same as as when Britney
rejected you. You know, I know that
you're obsessed and stuff, but that
still seems to be [ __ ] with your head
massively. You know,
strange as [ __ ] Anyways,
I'm gone anyways. See you.