Sorry, I was going to um do a video
about this but [ __ ] can't cuz my
upload limit. But let a few people join.
Let me get into this little [ __ ] rat
face [ __ ] little shitty little live
stream that he spent two hours
um [ __ ] obsessing over me. And yeah,
let a few people join.
Right. Okay. One second. Let me rip this
country into threads. I was going to do
a video, but I thought, "Fuck it. Yeah,
we'll talk we'll look we'll also talk
about the definition of insecure as well
since you want to throw that word out there. Yeah,
since you want to throw the word
insecure out there. I'll uh I'll tell
you the concept of that as well, which
is what you are and what you're doing
every day on YouTube because you ain't
got a life. you're low life. So yeah, um
yeah, let a few more people join and
I'll explain how I absolututely do know
more women than you and I have
absolutely been with more women than you
and I'll also address like some of the
things that you have said cuz obviously
I'm not going to miss anything out. So,
uh, yes, I have been with more women
than you will ever be, um, through cold
approaching and one that you literally
still talk about to this day because
you're jealous. So, I don't know why you
keep [ __ ] talking about this person.
Um, but you do because deep down you
know that it's someone you could never
get because you're in fact an ugly
bastard. All part of your insecurities.
I don't know why you keep [ __ ]
projecting your insecurities onto me.
It's [ __ ] pathetic. Really is.
Really, really is. I mean, for [ __ ]
sake, mate. You had to resort to a
disabled girl because no other woman
would have you. You would never be able
to cold approach in the first place
because you ain't got the balls to.
Yeah. You've been rejected by [ __ ]
Britney. I absolutely do know more women
than you and I absolutely have been with
more [ __ ] women than you. Yeah. You
said that I've got no life experiences,
bro. I can name you things that I've
done that you haven't even done. I've
been on a plane. I've been [ __ ] to
more places than you. I've been with
more [ __ ] women than you. I can name
you things that I've done. I've had a
job unlike [ __ ] you. But how the [ __ ]
I do I have zero life experience, you
know? Like I know absolutely more women
than you will ever know. And I've been
with more women than you. And I don't
know why you keep telling people on
YouTube that you've not been rejected
when you [ __ ] well have. You've been
rejected by Britney. That's why you keep
going on about USA is because you
compare it to a you and Britney
situation. You seem to think that
everyone's got the same life as you
because only you can get a disabled
woman. No one else can get somebody
that's not disabled. That's your life.
You think everyone's got the same life
as you. That's why you tell people that
they haven't slept with people because
you haven't slept with Britney. And so
what? The [ __ ] made up a story about
me. She only met me [ __ ] once. At the
end of the day, she only said that
because it was a random person messaging
her. Like, people lie about people
[ __ ] raping people all the [ __ ]
time. It's 202 [ __ ] five. You know,
the fact that you still go on about it.
How the [ __ ] am I insecure? I'd love to
know how I'm insecure. You know, people
talk [ __ ] about me all the time. They
talk [ __ ] about my looks. And I've never
stopped showing my face. I mean, I will
show my face right here, right now,
mate. And I'm a million times better
looking than you. There's nothing wrong
with my nose. There's nothing wrong with
anything. Why am I insecure about
anything? How am I insecure?
You know, I don't understand how I'm
insecure about [ __ ] what? You know,
you look like a [ __ ] drenched [ __ ]
rat. This is teeth. Something that you
don't have. Yeah. And another thing, why
do you have no [ __ ] teeth?
Dental care is free for everyone on
benefits. You know, that's the perks of
what um you know, you have when you're
um when you're on benefits, you know.
That's the perks of what you have. Why
do you have no [ __ ] teeth?
So, I have absolutely met more women
than you and I've absolutely been with
more women than you. And I can also
prove it as well. So, stop [ __ ]
talking [ __ ] And and and another thing
is you got proof that you're insecure.
You sit on YouTube every day talking
about the way that I look because you
know I'm better looking than you. That's
you being insecure. No one's in in No
one's insecure. You know why am I
insecure over some stupid little
ratfaced little skint virgin? I'm not
the one going on about you every day.
You're the one going on about me cuz you
are the one that's obsessed. Go look at
your last two live streams. Yeah. And
you're saying that I'm because I said
that your girlfriend's fat and ugly, I'm
a bully. Oh, what did that make you
then? Keep going on about me every day,
you [ __ ] stupid little skin bastard.
You know what I'm saying? Like, what the [ __ ] Cory?
You know, it's almost 2026 and you're
still going on about somebody that I met
years ago and I'm the one that's jealous
of your girlfriend. How How does that
make sense? Because I don't sit on here
talking about your girlfriend. You are
talking about my sloppy seconds, but no
one else does. Why? Why am I jealous of
your girlfriend, mate?
You know, why really would I be jealous
of your girlfriend when there's no
evidence to back up that, you know?
You're you're an absolute [ __ ] fool.
You know, absolute fool, mate. And then
you're going to sit there in your
[ __ ] skint little shitty out of
London council beds sit and try and tell
me to sort my life out.
You're going to tell me I need to sort
my life out. You got no teeth. You got
no money. You got no bed. You got no
job. You've never had a [ __ ] job. You
got less life experience than me. And
you're older than me. And you're trying
trying to tell me how I need to sort my
life out because apparently I live with a parent.
You have no job. You have no teeth. You
have no money. And you're trying to talk
about someone else.
Cory, these people are like kick out of
the head, bro. I'm telling you, there's
something wrong with them.
They really really need to get a life.
Honestly, I I I don't understand these
people, bro. I seriously don't. You know,
they seem he seems to think everyone is
a virgin like him. Like genuinely, bro,
he seems to think right because Britney
never slept with him. That goes for all
of the women that I have been with
because Britney never slept with him.
Is he [ __ ] mad? She told you that she
threw me out because she had some random
person messaging her and she [ __ ]
wanted to victimize herself
because I put her details out there. You
[ __ ] I mean, people [ __ ] lie about
getting [ __ ] raped a lot. Like,
okay, I have been with about five more
than five more women since being with
her. Why do you keep mentioning this
person? It's not a you and Britney
situation. You know, because you seem to
like to say, oh, how people remember
little bits of things. Yeah. But you are
the one that's comparing everything to
you and Britney. You think everyone is
the same as you and Britney. And listen,
and stop telling people on YouTube
you've never been rejected. You [ __ ]
well have been rejected. Yes, you
[ __ ] well have. You've been rejected
by [ __ ] Brit um you've been rejected
by Britney. You can't get anyone normal,
which is why you resorted to disabled in
the first place about I'm [ __ ] you're
an absolute [ __ ] idiot. And then
you're saying about how I've met women
that rejected me. Yes, I've met women
that's rejected me and I've met women
that slept with me. something that you
will never have. You understand? Skinned
virgin in your beds. I'm going to
mention that a few times cuz we need to
also talk about your living
circumstances. Yeah. A little bit
[ __ ] more. You [ __ ] What was the
other thing as well? Yeah. Um uh yeah.
Look at you, bro. Look at your face and
look at my face. and you're telling a
man like me I'm insecure, you know. And
yeah, also another thing is you're
saying about um
you're saying about I'm um
what was it? Uh um
yeah. No, I'm not wasting my time. I'm
just putting it straight, bro. doing it.
Like I'm just I'm just putting it
straight. I'm not wasting my time. I'm
just putting it straight, bro. Like
you're a [ __ ] idiot, bro.
You're an idiot. You're an absol And it
is a waste of time, Cory. I'll say
something to you in a minute as well,
bro. Yeah, but like you live in a
council bed with no bed and no money and
you're trying to talk about people
living with their [ __ ] mother. What's
the actual [ __ ] Don't you need to sort
your life out before trying to talk
about other people?
still going on about USA is he in almost
2026. You're a sad bastard. No one on
YouTube gives a [ __ ] Even people that
hate me, you go on about the same thing
because you never slept with Britney.
This is this is exactly what this is, bro. Yeah,
that's it. All because he has never
slept with Britney. This is where this
comes from. Okay,
let's just say that I'm lying about
sleeping with this person, which I don't
know why I would lie about sleeping with
someone and I don't know why anyone
would care. I've been with multiple
women before and since.
So, uh, you don't like the fact that
people can get with people that aren't disabled.
Yeah, that's what it is. You don't like
it that everyone's not a virgin like
you. That's what it is.
But yeah, they are um Yeah, I'm not
wasting my time. I Cory, yeah, listen.
I show these people. You are wasting my
time. I waste my time, bro. Do you know
another thing that you're wasting your
time on? They uh I show their messages.
Yeah, but this goes for a lot of people,
not just people on YouTube. I show their
messages where women was like leading me
on and stuff. And this guy got 14 thumbs
up even though I proved the women to be
in the wrong. I mean, that's just like
typical, isn't it? Like, they will
always like dismiss your struggles and [ __ ]
But that's weird. Like, they're proper
proper white knights. That's why there's
no point with these people, bro. But
there's people outside as well that do
it as well. It doesn't matter. It's like
what Adman said, it doesn't matter what
you show them, how you show them, how
many times you do, they're just going to
dismiss it. [ __ ] them. Yeah. You can
show them as clear as day what they've
done and they'll still dismiss it. It's
It is true to be honest. It is true.
Yeah, of course it's true, bro.
They just would never think women are in
the wrong. It's It's not a big deal,
bro. Like, you just just We won't talk
about it anymore.
That's it. We won't talk about it anymore, bro.
I mean, I've got videos where what I put
up on my channel and you can be the
judge, but they'll always defend women
and let them, bro. It doesn't matter, does it?
At least they show what they're about.
I did have one guy say, "Oh, I see what
you mean now, cuz that is a genuine
person. They got shown something, now
they believe it." But a lot of people, I
don't know why, I almost had an argument
with my mom about this yesterday as well. Um,
and it is generally just the same
argument over and over and over and over
and over again. They just miss everything.
Um, I don't know.
Can I ask you why you do it? Like
obviously you can do what you want. I'm
not going to like stop you, but why do
you dismiss people's struggles when it
comes to women? Can I like ask you like
I'm not trying to argue anything cuz I
tried asking my mom this and it it's in
one ear and out the other. And that man
was telling me that his mom
agreed with him. I said, "You lucky
bastard. Your mom agreed with you. My
mom, she doesn't think women do anything
wrong. She she just dismisses everything.
Like you can't get through to her.
There's no point even even saying
anything. My my [ __ ] my and I've been
through more [ __ ] than he has.
I was like, "No, not my mom. No, no, no.
You You wouldn't get food to my mom.
No way. No way, bro. You could show a
woman killing someone wouldn't suit
her." So, I'm not saying I'm not saying
it's people just just people on YouTube.
It's it's a thing a lot of people do.
I'd love to know why they do it. Like,
I'm I'm completely unbiased. I'm I'm
unbiased, bro. And I I want to know why
they do it.
It's strange cuz you can't say I'm a
virgin. I'm not a virgin. I've been with
women. I'm not unbiased.
I'm not a biased. I have no reason to
hate for no reason. I just think they're
wrong. A lot a lot a lot a lot of the
time. And I think the things they do is [ __ ] up.
Yeah. And he keeps going on about this
USA, is he? He's obsessed.
He all his life is convincing himself
that I ain't had sex with people. What a
freak. He really really is a a bitter,
nasty, jealous little virgin. He really is, bro.
Sat on YouTube convincing himself I
ain't had sex with people. Oh my god,
he's embarrassing at that age. Then he
then he lives in a bed suit with no job,
no money, no bed, and he tries to tell
people they need to sort their life out
whilst he's in his little skint shitty
out of London bedsuit.
What the [ __ ] He's he's he's he's
an idiot, man. An absolute idiot. He ain't
he he got no teeth yet is free for
people on benefits.
You got no life experience at all. You
haven't met more women than me. You
haven't been with more women than me.
And just because a woman is a stranger,
it doesn't mean I can't judge the [ __ ]
up things that she's done just because
she's a [ __ ] stranger. What does that
even mean? What what what does it mean
if somebody's a stranger or not a stranger?
I'm putting the woman in a c in the same
category is is not fair. Uh, okay.
That's a fair point. I'll answer you. If
you've had nothing but bad experiences
like I've had all my life, you would
also put them in the same category.
I mean, they
are all the same.
No, they they do the same thing. They
say the same stuff. They act the same
way. They're not the same. No.
I mean, they they are the same. Like,
we're not we're not talking about
the same category. Anyways, we're
talking about this guy's comment got 14
thumbs up, yet I showed evidence of what they've done.
So, was there a point in me even showing
anything? Is there a point in me? And
and it got to a point where yesterday
when I was arguing with my mom, I was
about to like really start losing it,
but I just I just didn't because there's
no point because it's annoying. It's
frustrating when you're trying to get
through to someone and they're not
listening to you. It get very very very
exhausting. You know
it's it's just it's it is just it is annoying.
And then I just said to her in the
future, don't bring anything up to me.
It's not about women being okay. This is
my exact point. Did you not learn
anything from the messages where they
led me on? See, this is what I'm saying.
You're you you want answers, but when
somebody is telling you and showing you
something, you're dismissing it.
So, what's the whole point? Because
anything I show you, you're just going
to dismiss any bad thing that they do.
Which is the same thing as basically
what I said to my mom. I said, "There's
no point you bringing it up anymore.
Don't bring up any kind of argument
because you're just going to dismiss it.
So, there's no point. It's a waste of
everyone's time. No one gets anywhere.
It's not about being into or not into.
I've shown you what they've done. Why do
you keep dismissing it? I've answered
your questions. Answer mine.
Why are you dismissing people leading me
on? Why are you dismissing people
wasting my time? It's not a hard
question. I don't know why you keep dismissing it.
If it doesn't suit you, just admit it
don't suit you. I I I don't know what to
say to you, you know.
And I said to my mom, I think I might
need to see a doctor because I don't
think my voice is
being heard. Maybe I'm on mute because
you're not listening listening to what I
am saying. You know,
why is it so hard to comprehend? I've
shown you what they've done in black and
white and you're still shaking your head.
[ __ ] hell, bro. You know,
why do you keep defending women? Can you
just answer me? I I just want to know
why you keep doing it. Why? And this is
me being unbiased. Why do you keep doing
it yet you've been shown evidence?
And this is where we never get anywhere.
So, it's just a point. This is a pointless argument
and it's [ __ ] annoying as well. Like
not being listened to, it's [ __ ]
annoying. You know,
you get shown all the evidence in the
world, then you shake your head and then
you got 14 people thumbs up and someone
that's contradicted themselves.
What the [ __ ] I I give up. Well, I
generally We need to stop talking about this anyways.
We really need to stop
again. Nothing about the women leading me on.
Nothing about the women. Okay, we're
going to stop talking about this now
because we're just dismissing my
struggles and we're going round and
round in circles. I've asked you the
same thing about five times and you've
completely ignored it. You have a brain.
Is there any kind of brain in your head?
I've literally showed you and told you
what women have done and you are ignoring it.
Why are you ignoring it? You've come on
here. You You've said something. I've
shown you where people have led me on
and wasted my time. Why do you keep dismissing it? You know
what? What is it with these people def I
need to get myself a sex change because
mate I if if this is what life is really
like as a woman I need to get a sex change.
Why do you keep dismissing it? I've
asked you the same thing about a million [ __ ] times.
Why do you keep dismissing the shitty
things that they keep doing?
It's it's [ __ ] mad,
you know. Well, anyways, bro, all I can
say is good luck to you in the future.
Um, you'll learn the hard way. So,
keep defending women. Keep dismissing
things. Good luck to you, man. That's
all I can say.
Don't know why I generally don't know
why people do it.
Why do people keep dismissing my struggles, Cory?
Why do people keep dismiss I'm generally
wanting to know. Can can anyone hear me?
Because I don't feel like people can
hear me when it's me to do with
explaining my experiences with women. It
seems like I I have no sort of voice.
Cuz no matter how many times you would
Well, what do you mean? Because they
don't care. Well, then stop thumbs uping
a message. Stop bringing it up then. If
you don't care. Well, if you don't care,
stop bringing it up. You know
what do you mean you don't care? You
must care to be right and stuff. No, you
don't care because you got proven wrong.
That's why. It's cuz you got proven
wrong. Not because you don't care.
I'll give you an example, Krie. I woke
up last night. I went upstairs. I was
speaking to I was talking to my mom and
we was having a normal conversation,
right? And she was like, "Oh, this is
the thing that makes me really want to
leave a lot faster, bro, because when
you're not listened to, it's it's
[ __ ] annoying, bro. And trust me, it
takes a lot to annoy me." Yeah. Yeah.
She was like, "Do you remember that person?" Right.
You remember that person um that uh
Yeah, but these people defend women.
This is what I don't understand. They
white night women. It doesn't matter
who's having problems, who's not having
problems. Anyways, my mom was like, "Oh,
yeah, you there was this young lady that
you had going around Will's mother." I
said, "Ah, young lady." She was
literally being passive aggressive. She
was being a [ __ ] which is the reason
why I done it in the first place. No
matter how many times I explained it, it
was falling on deaf ears. Like I
explained why I done it multiple
multiple multiple times and it just
didn't suit her.
Like I I literally tried explaining it
over and over and over again and it just
weren't suiting her, you know?
It's like, so you you you bring up
something to get me in a bad mood. I've
explained to you why I have done it over
and over and over and over and over and
over and over and over and over again,
but you just keep dismissing it. So,
it's like they can do whatever they want
and get away with it and then as soon as
you do something, this is why I'm
leaving. This is one of the reasons why
I'm leaving, bro.
Like, I don't I don't speak I don't even
speak to my other sister anymore. Not
not that I can't, but I just don't. Cuz
when I block someone, I don't talk to
them again. Bro, you don't know what I'm
like nowadays. Once I'm done with
someone, I am done. There's no going back. Simple.
But I had a good I was doing a voicemail
yesterday. I said, "You're telling mom
stuff and whatever, but can you tell the
full story why I've done it?" And it
just gets annoying and it makes you
miserable when you feel like you're not
being listened to. It's [ __ ]
horrible, bro. Trust me, it is really,
really horrible why people are
dismissing [ __ ] that you keep saying, you know,
it's [ __ ] It's not that they don't
It's not about them not caring. Why are
they dismissing your struggles? It's
weird as [ __ ]
I'm sick of them dismissing my
struggles. And all of them 14 people
that like that guy's um comment, they're
all [ __ ] idiots.
I'm not speaking my mind. I'm speaking my experiences.
It's not about mind. It's experiences,
you know, and no matter how many times
you explain this that it doesn't seem to
go through anyone's brain
and it just becomes exhausting and it's
the same old conversation. It's [ __ ]
boring like yesterday, bro. You know
why they defend women? I don't know why.
It's got to be some sort of condition
that they've got. I've been with women.
I've had sex and I hate them. I I
[ __ ] hate them. So, at the end of the
day, what are you going to say about me
that I've that I've not had sex with
people, you know? What are you going to
do? I've I I've not had sex with people
when I [ __ ] obviously have. I hate
them. They're nothing to defend. They're
scum of the earth. It's how I I I know,
bro. I can prove my experiences with
them over and over and over again. We're
going to have to stop talking about it, bro.
What is the point in talking about it
anymore? It's boring now. It's the same
[ __ ] Everything you say gets dismissed.
So, we just stop talking about it. And I
say to my mom, "Stop bringing it up. I
don't want to hear about it." Cuz every
time I tell you why I've done something
or shown you why I've done something,
you dismiss it.
You dismiss it. Which is strange
considering what I've been through with
these [ __ ] When you got someone
like Ant-Man's mom that understood his
mom said to him, "Oh, just leave the
country. [ __ ] off." He was like, "Oh
yeah, if you if you're not happy here, leave."
I don't want a [ __ ] woman.
I don't want a [ __ ] woman. Those were
messages from ages ago, bro. I haven't
approached in a month. And anyways,
she was like, "Oh yeah, if you're not
happy here, leave." My mom don't act
like that. even though she knew what I
[ __ ] been through. And no one just
dismisses my [ __ ] I hate it. I'm sick
of people dismissing my struggles. It's
[ __ ] annoying, bro. I'm not talking
about this no more.
Um because of the past and that is it. You know,
why do you keep dismissing people's
struggles? No, I'm not obsessed with it.
I just find it weird how
people can put up messages of what
they've done and yet you'll dismiss it.
Like it it like you pretend it never
happened. Like it's it's just mad how in
denial people actually are.
It just I just find it I I just to be
honest, I'm not obsessed. I just find it
strange how you dismiss what you're shown.
But anyways, good luck to these white
knights. You know, that's that's their
life, is it? So,
okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Really?
Are you sure? Okay. Now, I will love to
hear it because I won't say something
and dismiss someone's struggles. Okay.
So, giving you a few examples. I
approached somebody and they said
straight away they weren't interested. I
approached them because dating apps
don't work. Answer me that one. Um I've
messaged somebody and they didn't reply
to the first message. I want to hear
that. Um I had a woman agree to meet me
on the same day a couple of hours after
she said all of a sudden she's getting
back with her ex. Oh, believe you me. I
would One second. I tell you how much
I'd love to hear it. One second.
Got my tea ready. I would love to hear it.
Knock yourself out, my good son. I I've
got all day. I would love to hear every
single excuse for one of them things
that I've just mentioned. Please do. I'd
even put my camera up because the
reaction's quite good. Um, but we all
know that you're going to make stuff up. So, yeah,
I turn my camera off. But anyways, you
can say it.
And there's not reasons for my
struggles. There's literally women that
have agreed to meet me then backed out.
Um, have you Okay. Have you ever seen
those cherry people on the street? They
try and get you to stop. Oh, no, no, no,
no. I understand. No, I get it. It's not
it's not the done thing nowadays. I know
that. Okay. Yes, I have. But dating apps
don't work. So, that's the only
solution. So, that's the answer to that one.
Uh, it's not about getting rejected
again. You're just dismissing my
struggles again. What about the women
that Okay, knock that apart. Okay. Now,
one second. Also, I'll give you another
one. Um, the woman that said that she
was going to meet me and she said that
it sounds good and she had a great night
with me. Then three hours before we were
supposed to meet, she's all of a sudden
getting back with her ex. What was the
excuse for that one?
What was the excuse for the ones that
agreed to meet me then on the day come
out with an excuse?
I'm listening. Come on.
Come on now. I want to hear it. I'm
waiting all day. Doesn't matter how I
got the woman's number. She said she had
a great time with me. She was still up
for meeting him. And apparently she's
getting back with her ex.
Come on. Come on. Come on. You know,
come on. Come on, son. No.
I've literally told you what the women
have said to me, so it doesn't matter.
I've literally read the conversation out to you.
So you tell me why a woman is loving my
messages and agreeing to meet me.
Okay. Okay. Let me repeat.
Okay. I would
say I'll explain myself again. The woman
was sober. She said she had a great
night with me. We agreed to meet on the
exact day she was sober. And then three
hours before, oh, I'm getting back with my ex.
Okay, I give up. Right, I give up.
Okay, see, this is what I'm saying,
Cory. They're they're dismissing my
struggles. You understand what I'm
saying to you, bro? They're constantly
fishing for things to um to for my
struggles and stuff.
You're never ever ever going to get
through to these white knights. There's
no point. Like, you can show them what
these women do in black and white and
they will never ever admit it. You're
wasting your your time, mate. They will
they will always keep defending women.
This is why I'm never I'm not bringing
this up anymore. There's no point
bringing this up anymore. You know, I've literally
explained something to you and you keep
dismissing it. When you don't have the
answer, you keep dismissing it.
You know, they're never going to stop
defending women. So, this is why I, bro,
I'd rather not have this conversation
anymore because they're never going to
stop defending women, mate. So, there's
no point. There's no point in it. I've
just told you. I've literally just told
you, right? And listen, okay, Jimmy, I
don't need to be I don't need to be an
insult. I've been with women. I've been
with women, but I'm not going to defend
them when they're being [ __ ] I'm not
going to do it. And you at the end of
the day, you said um and at the end of
the day, yeah, like I I've just told you
where women have agreed to meet me and
they backed out, yet you're still making
excuses. That's the whole point of me
dis That's the whole point of you dismissing stuff.
If you're not being a white knight, why
are you dismissing things that don't
suit you? That's what I'm saying. Like
you're saying that you're not a white
knight, but you're acting like a white
knight because there's messages where
women have agreed to meet and then back
out on exactly the same day. You know,
it's like I don't know what more you
want. Do you need to see a woman kill
someone? I don't I don't know what more
you're supposed to show them, you know?
You know, it's like they No wonder they
do this, bro. Like, it's mad. It's mad.
Yeah. And that's what I'm saying. Okay.
Okay. So, if you went on if you went on
that video of the messages, I was not
wrong in every single message. There's
no way I was wrong in every single
message because them women was agreeing
to meet me.
Yeah, you're a M. But guess what, bro?
You will never show your face cuz you
are the M.
You are the big M. I could put the link
up right now and you won't show your
face. No, it's seriously that you're the
M and you will never show your face cuz
you're an ugly bastard. Bro, don't
self-reflect on another channel. We're
actually talking serious [ __ ] here.
No, seriously, you are the M.
That serious. Anyways, so that what I'm
saying anyways, bro, is that like um
there's no way you was wrong in every
single one of their messages.
No, I wouldn't even call them simps.
They're not I don't like using that
word. I wouldn't say they're simps. I
would say they're white knights.
I would say they're white knights.
No, I wouldn't say they're simps. Like I
said, I say they're white knights.
There's a there's a difference, bro. Cuz
I don't understand how
I don't understand what more like you
you need to show them.
That didn't work. Okay, let's hear it.
fair enough. Okay, let's hear it. Let's
hear why these women loved my messages
and agreed to meet and ended at me.
Okay, let's hear it. Let's hear you
contradict yourself. It'll be it'll be
it'll be it'll be it'll be good, man.
Uh we didn't break down two cuz I was
right about two. We didn't break down
two cuz I told you a woman agreeing to
meet me on the first and then she all of
a sudden didn't meet me. So we didn't
break down two. We didn't break down two
at all. Huh? You barely broke down one,
mate. Not two. You didn't break down
No. One said they were going to meet me
and agreed to meet me on message via
message when they were sober and then 3
hours before saying that they were
getting back with their ex.
How are you possibly going to justify that?
Like, I'd like to see you try. So, a
sober person has agreed to meet you.
They said, "Sounds good."
Okay. Okay. Jay Willow, I've put the
messages out there. Okay. Okay. Okay. I
like to listen to both sides, the
stories, Peter. All these women can't be
wrong with me in the past years and no
one wants to meet. Okay. Now, and I'm
Let me reply back to you. I have showed
where women have agreed to meet me.
What's your opinion on that one, Jay Willow?
You know, okay, you're just going to
keep making excuses for women. I'm
wasting my time here. You know, Jay
Willow, I have shown you where they have
agreed to meet me and they've backed
out. You're not talking your way out of
that one, lad. Again, I'm wasting my
time with the I'm I'm generally just
wasting my time with these people. You
are making up stuff that spooks yourself
and you're dismissing everything that I
am showing you. I listen listen listen
Jay Willow they have agreed to meet me
stop making excuses for them you know
what I'm saying you know what I'm saying
bro they can message or meet no it's not
about who they can message and they can
meet they have said they're going to
meet so yes it is these women you this
is what I'm saying they're just
dismissing everything that you're going
to show them there's no point there's no
point in any of this I don't need to
look closer to home. I know my home and
I know my messages. Okay. Jay Willow,
did you read? Okay. Did you go on the
video that I show the messages?
Right. Okay. Did you go on the video
that I show the messages?
They can change their mind.
What a s. They can change their mind.
Oh, is that the excuse you're really
going to use? Okay, Jay Willow. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Because on Because a woman
says to me three hours before meeting
me, she's going to meet me and then all
of a sudden she's getting back with her ex.
Oh yeah, change your mind. Okay, bro.
Yeah, whatever. You're full of [ __ ]
[ __ ] about changing your [ __ ] mind.
Yeah, I go around and start [ __ ] with
people and then saying, "Change my mind.
Don't owe you anything." Say what you
[ __ ] think sometimes, bro. you know.
So, yeah, Jay Willow, no, I don't need
to look closer to home. I know my home
and I know what these women have done.
So, so hold on. So, your logic is that
they can agree to meet you and then
change their mind. But that doesn't make
any sense because why would someone
change their mind? If someone's agreed
to meet you, right, and they're still up
for it on the day, why would they agree?
Why would they change their mind? That
doesn't make sense. I I I've never
honestly yet before going on a date
changed my mind. I've changed my mind
when I've met someone. Yes.
Yes. I've changed my mind when I've met
someone. Yeah. But not when I've not met
someone. Why would someone change their
mind if they've agreed to meet on the
day? That doesn't make sense.
But what bro? Come on, man. That don't
make sense. JJ,
all men are players and will cheat on
women and mess them around. Is this
correct? Stick to the subject. We're not
talking about men. We're talking about women.
So, what you're saying then, it's okay
for a woman to lead you on if she
changes her mind. You know,
alls I'm saying is they can meet. All
I'm saying is there can be or not anyone.
Yes, bro. I what I keep the messages for
a reason, bro.
You know, but you you clearly you
clearly dismiss my struggles. I know
these women are doing it on purpose. I
know these women are [ __ ] I how
you don't agree, I don't know, but
everyone everyone has their own opinion on it.
It's clear as day these women are
trolling you on their messages.
There's no debate about that. We all
know that if I was gay, these men would
be being called a [ __ ] It's only
because it's women, Cory. People are
using these excuses for them. You do realize that?
You know what I'm saying? Like it it's
clearly obvious that they are leading you on.
Just like a man would get sick for
leading someone on. I don't understand
it. It's just weird.
Okay. It's only me that It's only me
that has these experiences. Okay, bro.
Well, let me tell you something, J
Willow. I know loads and loads and loads
of single people.
Yep. Loads of single people. Let me tell
you something. Most people I know and I
know a lot a lot a lot a lot of people
are single. Not 95 other men can get
women. No, they can't. No, they cannot.
There are people that are worse than me.
There are people that are virgins. No,
they [ __ ] well can'ts. That maths
does not add up, mate. Because how could
95% of people get women when they only
go for 10% of men? Literally, most of
people I know are single. I swear to
God, bro. Like people people that I've
met, people I've not met. So 95% men can
get women. Say what you think. Sometimes
I don't think 95% of men can get women.
That is literally something that you
have just made up.
And again, whether I experience or I
don't experience, I've showed you what
they've done. Again, you've dismissed
it. Again, if I was gay and and these
people were men, you wouldn't dismiss it.
Yeah. And I get ridiculed for it. Like,
bro, 95% of other men don't get women.
Not even in Liverpool. Where's 95% of
men come from? Well, 95% of men in their
20ies get women, bro. Really? Are you
[ __ ] Are you being serious? And all
of the people that I know, bro, I'm
telling you, most people I know are
single. Yeah, there's people that I know
in relationship. There's a few people I
know that are in relationships. Yes, but
I know people that are single. No one No
one goes on about these single people.
Yeah. Other Firebirds shagging birds
weekly. Well, let me tell you what.
They're not shagging birds. They're
lying to you. You know, they're telling
you they're shagging birds, but they're
[ __ ] well not, mate. You know,
they're [ __ ] well not.
They're [ __ ] well not, mate. Shagging
birds weekly. I don't think they are
somehow, mate. I think they're lying to you.
How can that lanky virgin try and take
the piss out of me in his shitty little
bedsuit? How can he in his little
cancelled shitty out of London bedsit
try and tell people that they need to
get their life together?
Sat in a bedit with no job and [ __ ]
no money, no teeth, trying to talk about
other [ __ ] people. Bro, that's that
was that was the the first thing I said.
95% of men can't get women, bro. And
what would I have to gain? I've had sex.
I've been with women. Why would I need
to lie? Why would I slag off women if I
didn't think it? I've been with women.
I've had women. I just know what they're
like. Maybe I'm the only one to that
that's not scared to say what they
think. Why would I Why would I lie?
But Joe, but but why would I lie? I've
been I've had sex. I've been with
people. So why would I lie? Because a
lot of people that are defending these
women probably are the same as me. And I
don't give a [ __ ] about sex anymore.
I mean, bro, I don't even get an escort.
I don't give a [ __ ] about that [ __ ]
I don't need to lie, bro.
Because it's not like I'm a virgin.
Like, cuz then it would be like, "Oh,
you're a virgin." But I'm not. I don't
even really have a sex drive anymore.
But I I I don't know. I wouldn't need to
lie, bro. I wouldn't need to lie. I just
don't understand how people can defend
them. Maybe these people haven't had
these bad experiences, but I have. So, I
mean, that's it. So,
I ain't tried for a month. J Willow,
these are I I I I use these messages. I
put these messages up because of um I
thought people would learn, but some people did,
but some people never.
No, they're not. No, they're not. Trust
me, mate. I know a lot of people and
most men aren't getting women. No, they
are not. No, they are not. And a lot of
the men that are getting women have to
lower their standards, you know. No,
they are not. I know loads and loads and
loads of people and they are not in relationships.
No, they're not. If a if millions of
people are in relationships, millions of
people are single. Cuz why is it that a
lot of people I know are single? No
[ __ ] way. Oh, as they No, I am not
drunk. No, I'm not. No one will learn
anything from you putting these messages
up. Um, well, you would learn because
I'm showing you my experiences.
I mean, I'm showing you my experiences
and what they're doing. So, wouldn't you
then would it make you kind of
understand? Okay. So, you say you don't
have these experiences, right? Say you
don't have these experiences, right?
Well, some someone don't have these
experiences. Okay. But I'm showing you
what these women are doing to me. So
that would at very least help you understand.
No, cuz I'm not explaining it. I'm showing it.
But it somehow still seems to be dismissed.
I'm not I don't want pity. Pity for I
don't want pity, bro. I don't want I
don't want pity.
I don't want pity. And also another
thing, Jay Willow, right? You want to
say that I'm a problem, right? And no,
no, no, no, no, no, no. You nobody has
asked about the person. Look at I don't
want sympathy. I don't want sympathy. You know,
you know what I'm saying? I I don't want
sympathy. I didn't say I want sympathy.
I just wanted to put the [ __ ] up.
You have worked yourself in a massive
rut. No, I've had a negative experiences
with women, which is why I feel the way I do.
I I never said no no no no no no Jay
Willow I've never said all women can can
be wrong but all women in their 20ies
have unrealistic standards which is why
somebody would struggle. It's not about
being wrong or being right. It's about
the fact that they've got unrealistic
standards which would explain the struggles.
I mean, I could even like prove that if
you want me to do, if you want me to,
you know. Okay. So, when you're sat
there, right? Okay. Okay. Let's let
between me and you now, right? Okay.
[ __ ] the messages. Yeah. Let's talk
about this for example, right? Say you
go on the street, say you go on a bar,
say you go on a club, you go to a club,
right? And you try to speak to a woman
normally and they're not interested.
Does that not make me somewhat right
about what I'm saying? Forget all the
people you know for a minute. Forget all
the people I know. Just me and you,
right? You say you go and try to speak
to a woman and she says straight away
that you're not in she's not interested.
What would have you done that was wrong?
but tried to speak to someone
by saying hi or using a pickup line like
what what would have you actually said
that was wrong?
Do you know? So it's it's it's literally they've got
um No, no, no, no. Jay Willow, listen.
Okay, let me let me Right. So, you
didn't answer my question about the
approaching, did you? Um, so you won't
like yourself. I'm going to tell you
something now. You won't like you.
Um, okay. You want me to answer you? Okay. So,
the the problem with that is is men have
high standards. Women have got
unrealistic standards. And the problem
with it is is people admit that men have
high standards. People don't admit that
women have unrealistic standards. They
want to make it seem like, oh, it's
about personality and your appearance
don't matter and ret when literally,
bro, I could get a woman right now and
reject me because I've got black hair
and not brown hair. But no one ever
talks about this. They really really
think that like I could be good-looking.
I can make myself good-look and that
wouldn't even be good enough for a woman
to give me a chance. That's when it's a
problem, you know? And at the end of the
day, And at the end of the day, right,
and at the end of the day,
so what I'm saying to you is, bro, we
men have men are the ones that are
lowering their standards, not women.
You know, women are the ones that date
up. Men are the ones that date down.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. I mean I
mean I've got I've got because cuz that
was the one of that's the reasons why I
put the approaching videos up because
you were saying about it's how I'm
acting. How am I acting bro? What trying
to start a conversation with a woman and
her saying straight away I'm not
interested. What do you want me to act
like? You know, you need to like
Yeah. And and and Yeah. But that's them
having unrealistic standards. Yeah,
that's the problem. They've got
unrealistic standards even though
they're average looking themselves.
So at the end of the day, they've got
unrealistic standards. It's not you being wrong. So
yeah, and it shouldn't be their choice
when they're average looking.
And what you know what I they need to
put this Jay Widow where men where women
need to stop moaning about men. They
really really really need to stop
moaning about men. They need to stop
complaining about men. They are in no
rights to complain about men. They've
got no rights to complain about men, you know. So
or we have our own quirks that we want.
No, but the difference is Jay Willow is
they will reject you for the most
pitiest, pettiest things. That's the
difference. I think that is the
difference. You not getting with a woman
that hasn't got white teeth is more of
something that she can change. They will
reject you for things that you can't change.
You know, that's also a big difference.
Yeah. You want somebody that's hygienic.
Okay. And your point is that is like
brush your [ __ ] teeth. You know how
you compare that to someone that
wouldn't get with somebody because you
know what I'm saying?
But the thing is Jay Willow, it's not
about you said it was about how I was
acting. Now I put approaching videos up
where I wasn't even given a chance.
How was I acting?
You know, how was I acting?
But when men when women moan about men,
I hate it, bro. I hate it. I I hate when
they complain about men.
It's it it's it's like [ __ ] you know.
Okay, PJ, you can't deny this. If I
messaged a bird and she rejected me, you
know what I do? I'd move on and forget
about her instantly. Yeah. What about if
you met her and she led you on and she
gave you false hope and she didn't meet
you? What about then?
Would you would you not be pissed off? You know,
like they owe you a date. Don't women go
on dates thinking men owe them
to pay for the date? I mean, that's
that's a two-way thing. I mean, they
think men owe them stuff. So, I mean,
you know, they they they go on date. I mean,
they go on dates thinking that men owe them something.
So, isn't that just like a a thing?
And if you don't owe people a date, why
are you saying that you're going to meet them?
Nah, I wouldn't be pissed off for 30.
Okay, I I'll tell you. Okay, I'll tell
you the last time I went out, Jay Willow. Yeah,
you know, right? I'll tell you. No, it's
not about a job. Even if you have a job,
you still won't meet a woman. Again, if
you're not her unrealistic type
physically, she's not even going to give
you a chance. It doesn't matter about a
job or not a job. Listen,
last time I went out, Jay Willow,
was about a month ago. It's my birthday
next week, next Monday to be uh precise.
I went out last
month. Well, obviously was last month
was a month ago. I approached [ __ ] I
got 10 numbers
and one replied and agreed to meet me. I
spent £500. I won the money back. I
swear I'd never try again, bro. [ __ ]
that. [ __ ] that. I look Max as well. So yeah. So,
and then like Jay Willow, like I know
now, like I know now like I I had to I
had to book this Thailand thing for my
own like mental health. I I couldn't go
out and try again. So,
you know, nights out with mates.
I've never been on a night out with mates,
drinking, escorts, food. And then I was
like, I can never try again, bro.
No, no, no. Having a job doesn't matter
because I've had a job. Okay, so if
having a job matters, why are all of
these women rejecting me before even
getting to know whether I have a job or
not? Then none of these women ask me
what I do.
None of these women ask me what I do
when I approach them. They say straight
away they're not interested. So, does
that not [ __ ] the argument up? [ __ ] the
messages for a second. Just forget the
messages, right? So, you're saying
having a job matters, right? Yeah. You
go and you try to speak to a woman and
she will say straight away that she's
not interested or she'll give you the
runaround. Very rarely does a woman ask
me what I do.
Women never ask me what I do.
Um because I claim to be a landlord
while I was a landlord for 3 4 years.
Whether it was illegally or legally, I
wasn't lying by saying I was a I was a landlord.
I mean, Daft, I wasn't lying.
There was no lying about it.
So, why why is it what what what Okay,
so when I approached them women on the street,
why didn't they give me a chance then?
They didn't ask me. We're just going
around in circles. We're going round and
round and round in circles, bro. And
we're not getting anywhere here. It's
It's just a waste of everyone's time. You know,
at the end of the day, it's not up for
you people. It's not up for me. It's up
for these women to prove they were
different. And they couldn't. So, at the
end of the day, it's like it's it's not
you or me. We've gave them enough
chances to prove that they're different
and they can't. So, at the end of the
day, that's where we're at. So, you
know, I don't I don't know that actual
because it's not up for you or me. It's
up for them. And they can't prove
they're different. They prove they're
all the same.
Um, I also love how Nons thinks that
just because someone's a stranger, you
can't have an opinion on them because
they're a stranger, you know? So, yeah. Yeah.
And I'm also I can't be told wrong.
You can't be shown wrong. You're saying
that I can't be told wrong and you can't
be shown different. I've shown you women
that have shut me down before I finished
my sentence. You can't even be shown
wrong. So, we're both as bad as each
other, aren't we?
Yeah, I know, man. Even when I approach
a woman normally and she pretends she
got a boyfriend and she's not
interested. Yeah. You dismiss that. So,
we're all We're all bad We're all as bad
as each other.
I mean, you dismiss what I dismiss what
you tell me. You dismiss what I show
you. So, it's like, yeah.
And and like I said, if if I was gay,
there wouldn't be any of this.
If I was gay, right, no one would be
here making excuses. So, what did that
tell you? So, I don't I don't know, man.
Yeah, but none of these women asked if I
had a job. They said they weren't interested.
It's like women can have unrealistic
standards, but people will just make
excuses for their shitty actions.
It must be fun being a woman, you know?
Like I get like, yeah, they get periods
and they have to give birth and [ __ ]
but they really really do have it easy.
They get all of these white knights
defend them even though they're they're
the ones in the wrong. They've got all
of these options.
Might just not like being approached on
the street, but they weren't all
approached on the street. And there's
nothing wrong with my looks. I'm not
saying I'm very good-looking, but I
mean, why wouldn't you like my looks? I
mean, I look okay.
Okay, but it's not just the street,
though. Oh my god. It's the same
argument. [ __ ] sake. It's not about
the street, bro. It's not just about the
street. It's about bars. It's about
clubs. It's about them giving their
numbers and leading you on. It's not
just about [ __ ] them saying that
they've got a boyfriend.
It's not one [ __ ] thing. Oh my [ __ ] god. You know.
Yeah. Okay. Whatever. See, you're just
making excuses for them. You're just
But what I'm saying is it's not about
it's not about the street. Why do you
keep going back on the street?
And yeah, it is weird for a woman to not
like my looks when I can look above
average looking. So yeah, that is a bit
weird because what you're saying Okay.
Okay. I'll explain it to you. Let me
explain it to you. Cuz you're saying
right that women don't go for looks and
women don't go for physical appearance
and you're trying to blame my
personality and I'm acting this way and
I'm acting that way. Then surely to God
if that's true then if I can look
average looking to like a little above
average looking, right? Yeah.
Then a woman would get to know my
personality by your logic and not just
say, "Oh, well he's not perfect
looking." Do you not understand how we
don't make sense what you're saying?
You said he's a fat [ __ ] and he pulls
nine out of 10. Good for him, bro. Good for him.
I don't think we're getting anywhere
here. We're going over and over and
we're having the same argument over and
over and over again.
Um, and we're never getting anywhere.
I've got my experiences.
Um, and you're just going to keep
dismissing them. And I think we everyone
said what they've had to say.
Um so yeah. Yeah.
They're just going round and round and
round and round and round in circles.
And the thing is I I don't contradict
myself cuz I'm not going out trying to
meet them. I've got money. I can go out
and try and meet them. But I don't want
anything to ever do with any of them
again. Especially after last time.
There's no there's no I'm happy now, bro.
I'm happy. There's There's P in the
dating pool, bro. Like, I'm so happy
that I gave up. I really really am. I'm so glad,
you know, not having to deal with that
[ __ ] that it's toxic,
you know? So,
yeah, I don't think I'd ever go back to it, bro.
No, I'm going to Thailand anyway. So that
there's nothing new with that.
Nah, I'll never approach again. I'll
Men are exactly the same. Men are not
exactly the same. Women are the same.
Um, men are not exactly the same.
Because let me Okay, let me give you an
example, J. Yeah, let me give you a
little example. Tell me if you agree
with this or you don't agree with this.
Now, you know, now please just just hear
me out, right? I know we won't come out
the best of friends after this, but do
you know what annoys me? Now, I don't
know if you agree with this. Yeah. You
will get men that generally can't find
anyone and they'll moan into
complaining, "Oh, they can't find
anyone. They can't find anyone. They
can't find anyone." and they literally
can't find anyone. Yet women when they
complain they can't find anyone, they
can get any man they want. They just got
unrealistic standards. Do you would you
agree with that one?
Would you agree? Cuz like there's women
that are 27, 28, claim they've never
been in a relationship, claim they've
never had sex, and no one wants them.
When we all know that a woman can get
any man she wants. And I've proven that
a million times.
Wait, men have it a lot easier than women.
Wait, hold on. Let me read that again.
Men have it a lot easier than women.
Huh? Men have it a lot easier than women.
Are you sure about that? Cuz I don't
think anyone could agree with that one,
mate. I'm pretty sure. Right.
You know what I'm saying? Uh,
I don't think men have it easier than
women, bro. I really, really, really
don't think anyone would agree with you
on that one. No, men does not have it.
Men don't have it easier than women. How
would men have it easier than women? All
a woman has to do is jump on a [ __ ]
date, right? Even a four out of 10 would
get 5,000 likes, bro. There's no way
[ __ ] men have it easier than women.
That doesn't even make sense. Like, no
one could no one could even agree with
that. What the [ __ ] How could they have
it easier than women
with all of these [ __ ] simps, white
knights, and [ __ ]
I never said no men can pull. When did I
say no men can pull? you know. Yeah. Obviously.
So, when did we say no men can port,
but I will never go back into dating. I
will never ever ever go back into dating.
Ebike. Never will I ever go back into it ever again.
because I knew if I was going to find
someone, I would have found someone by
now. There's no there's no
cuz when I went out last time, I looked
smack and I got their numbers and I
didn't even get a date. So that's why I
was like it's a mug's game. There's no point.
So there's there's no there's literally no point.
Yeah, men have it easier. Well, we all
know men don't have it easier stuff.
You're just trying to get reaction.
you're not going to get a reaction better. So,
I will never get back into dating.
I will never I don't think I will ever
get back into dating, bro.
I don't I don't know what I'm doing.
I've already done so much, but I won't
be ever going back into dating. Um
because it's always the same old. Every
time you go out, it's the same old. I'm
not interested. I have a boyfriend. You
get numbers. They lead you on. I'm not
asked with it, bro. I'm really really not.
Doesn't interest me, you know. Yeah.
You know, so I don't need to work. I've got money.
I've got unrealistic expectations.
That's true. Well, that doesn't make any
sense considering I've tried to meet
multiple women that agreed to meet me
but led me on. So if I had unrealistic expectations,
I wouldn't be approaching loads of women
when I go out. So that doesn't make any
sense. If I had unrealistic
expectations, why am I approaching loads
of women when I used to go out
when that would not make any sense.
Yeah, I'm a weird M. You need to stop
that M [ __ ] It's getting boring now,
bro. Really, really boring,
you know. You really, really need to
stop that. It's getting really boring
now. It's like nonslegs. You need to
stop talking about that USA, is it? It's
getting really old now. It's 2026
and you're talking about someone I met
[ __ ] how many years ago? It's making
you look really, really weird now. It's
boring, bro. It's just like that month
to think it's boring now. Should we like
come out with some new sayings?
Come on, man. It's boring now.
You know, I'm bored of this women [ __ ]
Why do you think I gave up? So,
see, with like babies and children and
stuff, I understand like if people say
mad stuff about babies and children, you
have to like admit you're wrong cuz
they're cuz they're innocent. But with
the with the women thing, they're not
innocent. They're [ __ ] Like I know
my experiences with them. So that's what
[ __ ] this whole thing up.
There's no such thing as leagues.
There's no such thing as leagues. And
this isn't a conversation about my
looks. Yeah. There's no such thing as leagues.
They're not in my league. They're not
out of my league. That's exactly
something that a white knight would say.
I mean, I can make myself above average
looking. And we're not talking about my
looks, mate, when you're probably uglier
than me. At the end of the day, mate,
you're probably uglier than me. Do not
talk about my looks and women that are
in my league. Um, and there's no such
thing as leagues anyways.
A league. There's no such thing as leagues.
At at the end of the day, lives with my
mom. Plenty of people in London live
with their mom, mate. It's nowhere near
as bad as you're making it out. There's
nothing wrong with living with your mom
in London. There's plenty of people that
live with their mom where they live in a
box room. And yes, 27 lives with their
mom and they know more than you. At
least I don't live in a cancel shitty
bedsit like nonslegs. I'd rather live
with my mom than live in a cancel shitty
bedsit broke. You know, you might want
to actually think about your own lives
before talking about other people. I've
literally stated a million times, I'd
rather live with my mom than live in a
council, shitty bedsit. And I don't know
how many times I've explained it. You
still don't get it. I'd rather that than
live in a bedsit with no bed and no
[ __ ] money skint like him. Yeah. And
I don't mind getting money out again if
you want me to. Leagues. Well, actually,
no. To be honest with you, there are
leagues. No. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
They are there are leagues, but not what
you're trying to make it out. You're
trying to make it a look thing and and a
physical thing. There is there is
leagues. I'll give you a league.
Taylor Swift is out of my league. She's
a billionaire. I mean, but women in this
country is not out of my league and I'm
not out of their league. You understand?
There's no such thing as leagues with
normal [ __ ] people,
you know? doesn't wash look homeless.
Work says he's bed with his mother. Bro,
you're just talking [ __ ] now. Just just
You're talking absolute [ __ ] I don't
wash looks homeless. Bro, you're talking
[ __ ] now. You know, as soon as you was
talking about leagues, yeah, there's
leagues with celebrities and rich
people, not women in this country that
probably have less money than me.
You're not lying.
Stop it. You're talking [ __ ]
You know, stop talking [ __ ] Stop making
excuses for women. Stop being a white knight.
Stop being a white knight. Stop being a
It makes me think, have you people ever
been with women? Have you ever met a
woman? Because you you seem to know
nothing. Like, you seem to absolutely
know nothing trying to talk about women
being out of my league. I'm not out of a
woman's league and a woman's not out of
my league. That's just such a
narcissistic thing to say. Well, like I
said, unless they're like Taylor Swift,
then yeah, obviously that's different.
But not in this country, mate, with
[ __ ] people, normal people that work.
They're not out of your league,
you know? That is so stupid. You know
what? I've never believed in leagues,
you know? Not like that anyway. It's not, you know,
you're because you're talking about leagues.
You're talking about leagues, bro. Really?
Sorry, I didn't.
I look homeless and I share a bed with
my mom. Stop talking [ __ ] But
anyways, good luck to you, bro. I hope
you do meet some women in the future and
you actually realize what they're like. Um,
okay, bro. Whatever you are for women.
Yeah, we've heard it all before, bro. At
the end of the day, I don't need to
argue. Do I know my experiences? I know
what they're like. I've shown my
experiences. If you want to dismiss
them, you dismiss them. That's up to
you, bro. I'm not interested. You know,
I've met more than I've met more women
than everybody on this chat combined.
Now, you think that's delusional, bro?
Do you know what I got up to in 4 years?
I don't understand the point of this conversation.
Yeah, my my Okay, so what about the
women? Okay, we're going around and
around in circles now. Let's move on.
We're having the same argument over and
over and over again. Like I said, bro,
good luck. Um, and I hope you meet uh
women in the future and you actually get some experience.
Um because you're you're going round and
round and round and round and round in
circles and it's just annoying, you
know. Yes. All women are perfect. I'm a
bum. I don't know anything. I've never
met any woman. Poor me. Didn't Yeah.
Damn. You got me. Does that make you happy?
Yeah. Okay. Yeah. We're moving on now. Anyways,
we're moving on now. So, I think we've
all made good points. Um, so anyways, I
hope you meet women in the future. Um,
and yeah, because no matter what I'm
saying, you're dismissing. So, we we're
going round and round in circles. And
I've asked my mom as well like, "Stop
bringing it up to me. It's annoying.
We're going round and round and round in
circles over and over and over and over
and over again." Okay.
You want me to answer your question?
What about all of the women that are
with people on benefits that ain't got
no money? What about women that are
dating guys that are in prison?
What about them people? H
What about women that are with guys that
have got no money, no job, [ __ ] all, in
and out of prison, don't have anything.
What about and people
what about what about what about them
people? So I answered your question if
you wanted me to. So
why are you talking about moving out my
mother's house? Why are you so concerned
about where I live?
Oh, [ __ ] hell. It's madness.
If a woman can't have you at your worst,
she shouldn't have you at her best.
That's the way I see it. Yeah.
So, it's so mad because you're talking
about people being this and people being
on benefits. Yeah. When you try and
start a conversation with a woman, she
says she's not interested.
Um, well, Cory, I lived by myself for 9
months. I lived by myself for 3 years
and it never made a difference. So, I
This is how I know. Okay. Do you want me
to know how your advice is [ __ ] Cuz
I've lived by myself and I've earned
money and it never made a difference.
Yes, I did. I lived by myself for 3
years. I used to go to the gym by myself
every day. I used to make money and it
never made a difference. Am I lying?
Are you going to tell me I'm lying since
you want to talk about life experiences?
No, I can tell you everything.
Sorry. I can tell you everything. I've
lived by myself.
Um, I've worked. I've made money. I went
to the gym. I was traveling. I still
never met anyone.
Am I lying?
So, it seems like everything I say, you
seem to think I'm lying.
I mean, I've lived many different lives,
bro, and it never changed with women
ever. I've had loads and loads of money.
I've had no money. I've lived by myself.
I've lived with my mom. I've And it
never made a difference.
No, I've given up, bro. I'm going
Thailand. No one cares about the past.
Well, I care about the past because I've
lived by myself and I'm telling you what it's like.
So, I care about the past. So, what do
you do? You think that if you move out,
all of a sudden you're going to meet a
woman? Do you hear yourself?
You seem to think that if you what if
you move out, you're all of a sudden
going to meet a woman.
Bro, have a word with yourself. You'd
realize that doesn't even make sense.
No, I don't I don't let anything
happens. The past dictates the future.
Yeah, exactly. It's not women. No, no,
no, no, no. It's not women. Even though
I've shown you where they've led me on,
played games, where they've said they're
not interested without even letting me
finish my sentence. You're so right,
bro. It's not women, it's me. Damn, you
got me. Yeah, man. I definitely haven't
sent you messages where they've led me
on and played games. Not Not where I've
approached them and they've um said
they're not interested straight away.
Oh, it was me, wasn't it? Damn. At least
I We learn something new every day, don't we?
Oh, yeah. You're right. Yeah.
Yeah. See, you learn something new every
day. Thank you for that, bro. This is
why I can't block these comments. Thank
you. I know, man. It's definitely me.
It's all me. You're right.
Um, it's not like I've approached women
and they've said they're not interested
straight away. No, that must have been
another PJ. It's not like I've looked
maxed and smell good and tried and then
they've said they're not interested. Oh,
damn. You're right, man. Yeah.
I I mean I don't know. I mean, again,
you keep dismissing my struggles,
you know. Yeah. Peter knows best. Yeah.
Peter, the same Peter that's met more
women than you, that's been up and down
the country. Yeah. I would say Peter
knows more than you. Yeah. Peter, the
one that's backed up my state, backed up
my claims and met more women than you, I
would say he knows best. Yeah. Laughing
back up. Laughing back at you. Yeah.
But yeah, I would say somebody that's
met more women than you will ever meet
and has put the evidence up there knows
more than you. Yeah. Without saying
socks, without being sarcastic, you know,
giving a woman a a round
a run. What? Huh? What are you talking about?
giving it. What are you talking about, bro?
That seems like bomb to me.
Oh, so it's it's down to it's down to me
and the way I look.
Oh, it's the way that I look. Oh, make
make it make sense then because firstly
you were saying that it's because of
this that and the other and then you're
saying it's because of the way that I
look. Make it make sense. Are you head
or you tails?
I giving the woman a runaround.
What? The one that What is it? The one
that was being passive aggressive and
being a [ __ ] I gave her a run around
because she was being a [ __ ] Again,
something that you dismissed. You always
seem to dismiss the things they do.
I mean, did I explain what they've done?
Why is [ __ ] the skinned virgin in a
bedsit trying to tell people that they
live with their mom when he lives in a council bedsit
with no bed?
I don't understand how somebody in a in
a cancel bedsit with no job can tell
people where they should or shouldn't be
living. The day I'm with a disabled girl
and I've got no teeth and I've got no
bed is not the day I try to tell other
people who they should and who they
should be living with. Just because your
mom starved you and you got mummy
issues, you're not independent, you
don't have a job, you don't have money,
so you might want to get your [ __ ] um
you might want to get your [ __ ] together um before
saying anything to me.
You live in a cancelled bedsit and you
don't even have a job and you're talking about me.
So anyways, Mike.
Uh anyways, Mike, um
any thoughts on what that woman done?
We're going round and round in circles.
We need to stop this, bro. Yeah. I don't
care if I'm obsessed with him. He's got
a channel dedicated to me. I am not
obsessed with that scruffy little virgin
living in a bed sit. He is the one
that's obsessed with me. He's got a
channel dedicated to me. He goes live
talking about me. No one's obsessed with
that skinned virgin with his disabled
girlfriend. Don't sit in your cel
[ __ ] shitty bedsit and try and tell
me who I should and who I shouldn't live
with. Mate, you haven't even been on a
plane. You haven't even [ __ ] been to
half the places that I've been. Don't
sit in that shitty pit bedsit and try
and tell me who I should and should be living with.
Don't you dare sit in that skin bedsit
and try and tell me who I shouldn't
should be living with.
So yeah, I keep bringing him up. He also
keeps talking about me. Have you gone to
his channel lately? Funny enough, he
keeps talking about me, mate, multiple times.
sat there in his skin bedsit telling
people that they live with their mom.
I have met more women than he would have
ever meet. Don't you dare sit in that
virgin bedsit and try and tell me that
you've met [ __ ] more women than me.
You [ __ ] skin [ __ ]
And if you and if you want me to [ __ ]
show buddy again, I will.
No one's obsessed with that skin little virgin.
But anyways, we need to stop this whole
talk now, bro, because we are going
around in circles. We've made our
points. You're never going to stop
defending women. I'm not going to waste
my time showing you anything. So, we're
just going round and round and round and
round and round in circles. And all I
can say is good luck to you.
Um, that's all I can say.
You want to keep thinking women are
innocent, good on you, bro. That's your life.
It's never going to get you laid. Uh
it's never going to make women like you. Um
so why you do it, we never know, but you
do it. So
it makes you think, Cory, if these
people have actually ever been with a woman, you know,
and like I said, it's not you. It's the
fact that it's women that you're you're
saying this stuff. If you were saying
about men, people would agree with you.
So that just proves itself that like
they're just simps because
Yeah. Why they defend women, how they
defend women, I can never know. But they do, you know.
It's bad, isn't it?
It's annoying though. It is annoying
though when you you you show stuff to
people and they still dismiss it, you know.
But I don't understand how a skinned
virgin can try and tell you that you
live with your mom and he lives in a can
of shitty beds. That's even that's worse
than living with your mom.
That's worse than [ __ ] living with your mom.
I've got the mentality of mentality of a
15y old. Oh, do I? That's nice.
I'll never approach again or anything like that. Yeah.
So, I just put them approaching videos
up to show thingy and that's it.
I don't know why they do it. I don't
know why they defend women.
Why do you defend women?
I think they're all [ __ ] idiots on here.
Cuz there's no reason why I don't I'm
not doing it. I'm not a virgin. I've had sex.
So why would I lie? Do you understand,
Cory? Why would I lie about it?
The same reason why would they defend
women when women don't even like these
people. I don't get it. You know,
uh you've dismissed literally things
I've shown you.
You've literally dismissed messages.
You've dismissed where they've not let
me finish my sentence.
So, that is kind of defending them
in a way. Well, it is defending them.
But why would I need to lie if I've had
sex and I've been with women? Why would
I agree with you when my experiences say
different? That doesn't make any sense. Oh,
so seaside mark. And again, you're
dismissing my struggles
because I'm nothing to do with suicide
mark. I've thrown you messages. I've
thrown you approaches,
which I don't understand how you can
just agree with them, but you somehow
do. But what's that got to do with CSI Mark?
No, no, no, no. I'm not asking you to
agree with me, but I'm I'm asking you if
you can uh you could understand why I
feel the way I do.
So that's it's like there was this guy,
he commented saying, "Oh, I get what you
mean now. Yeah, they should have told
you that before prolonging it." So I
I've done a video showing what they've
done and he saw it and now he understands
that is legit.
Yeah, but you don't understand it
because you're making excuses for them.
So you don't understand it. But you No,
but you don't understand it though.
No, you don't understand it though
because you're dismissing it. So So yeah.
So So it's crazy.
But yeah, we're just going to keep going
around in circles, you know,
cuz when I used to say to the skinned
virgin, "All women are the same." I
didn't really know many women. I I just
said the [ __ ] But now I actually do.
And I know more [ __ ] women than that
ugly rat face ugly bastard will ever
know. I don't know why he's going live, you know. Okay.
That's what I'm saying. Like you're
you're not um you know. Okay. Let me
give you an example, ebike. Right. Okay.
Do you want do you want do you want to
give Okay. Can I give you an example? Do
you want me to give you an example, bro?
So, you know when somebody commented,
"Right, I I'm going to I'm going to show
you how you've dismissed my how this guy
dismissed my struggles.
Right. So, you know that guy that
commented stating out some of the
reasons, right, why this is happening?
He says, "Oh, you're too forward. You're
you love their messages." Even though
they loved my messages completely got
dismissed. Um, you're sending women
voice notes. There's many women I didn't
send voice notes. You're being too full
on. There's a lot of women that I didn't
even act full on to. So it it's like
you've kicked out things that suited
yourself that you thought you could
argue with and then you dismissed all
these other things. So
So it's like what I was saying in the
video. So I can't love their messages
but they can love my messages. You're
not seeing how it seems very very like
you're full of excuses.
Do you not understand that? You know,
it's you're always it's like people are
always looking for excuses for women.
That's just the way it comes across.
So, but you're always going to defend women. So, okay.
Okay. It's completely objective. Okay. Yeah.
But yeah, don't sit in your [ __ ]
shitty little [ __ ] skint bedset with
no [ __ ] money with it on benefits
trying to tell me you've met more women
than me, you [ __ ] ski barted.
Yeah, but then Yeah, but it Yeah. Okay,
but Okay. Right. So, I'll explain myself
again. So, you said that's why some
people are given different reasonings.
Okay. So, what about the women that
loved my messages?
If I love their messages and that's the
problem, why are they allowed to love my
messages? That's not a reason. That's an excuse.
We're going round and round and round in circles.
That's not anything because they're using excuses.
We're going around in circles. My my
brain is going is acting fried, bro. No,
you're not giving reasons. Excuses.
Also, there was loads and loads and
loads of other messages. You know,
you're always going to defend women.
It's [ __ ] obvious now. I don't know
the point in all of this, bro.
Okay, but they Okay, let's agree to
disagree. Now, we're going around in
circles and we're not getting anywhere,
bro. Thank you for commenting. Um, I'm
not part of this anymore because you're
just going to keep dismissing
everything. So there's no point.
You're right. I'm wrong. I don't have no
life experience. I think I know
everything. I've never met a woman. I've
never been with a woman. All women don't
do anything wrong. I'm the problem.
Happy. So I don't, you know, I'll just
agree just to shut everyone up because
it's just we're going around in circles
at this point. It really really is.
We're just going around in circles
and it's [ __ ] boring now, bro. Really.
You're never going to admit they do
wrong. Like people are never going to
admit they've got unrealistic standards.
Fine, whatever. You know, there it's I'm
not I'm not doing this, you know.
Yep. Okay, bro. Whatever.
There's no point, bro.
And that very same guy said women are
too picky. So he contradicted himself as
well. But yeah, whatever.
You dismiss people's struggles. That's
all you do. So
So it's okay for a woman to love my
message, but I can't love her message. Okay?
See, I know I'm right. I know I'm right
because if I went in public and I showed
these messages to people that weren't on
this community, they would agree with me.
I'm sure to God they would agree with
me. And I wouldn't give them any any
like rundown or anything. I think they would.
Yeah. You just keep dismissing my struggles.
I've already I have been in a
relationship. You're in your 40s, mate,
and you've never had sex.
You need to make it make sense, bro. You
You're in your 40s and you've never had sex.
Yeah, that don't make sense. And you're
trying to talk about someone half your
age. [ __ ] off, mate.
You know, yeah, you're 29. Of course you
are, bro. Whatever. And why are you
asked if I've been in a relationship or
not? Bit weird. You You're not even in a relationship yourself.
Why don't you people focus on your own
lives instead of trying to put other
people down? Why don't you focus on your
own miserable lives, you know, than
trying to put other people down?
Yeah, of course you have, mate. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. You're all married on here,
aren't you? Believable. Eh,
I mean, we got somebody in a skint
shitty council estate bedsit trying to
tell people that they're living with
their mom, yet they've got no teeth.
That is what you call a [ __ ] life at 31.
You know what other people have at [ __ ] 31?
And you're sat there in a skint shitty
Kent out of date bedset trying to tell
other people what they [ __ ] what they
have what they don't have. Get on my
level, bro. Please.
You live in a [ __ ] cancel [ __ ] hole.
Do not try and tell people that they
they have not got their [ __ ] life together.
You know, you're in a shitty cancel bed.
Do not [ __ ] try and tell other people
who live in a house, you know, who they
[ __ ] live with. I live in a house
with a [ __ ] bed. You know, you know
what I'm saying?
Yeah, I've shown money as well, funny
enough, but you ignore that. Yeah, he
showed 13 grand, which is nothing. That
took him 3 years. Yeah, I showed money
on him, remember?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, he lives in a Yeah, he
he's in a relationship with a disabled
girl and he lives in a bedsit. I'm not
jealous of any of that stuff. I don't
want a relationship with a disabled
girl. Again, I've repeated this about a
million times. You know, I'm single. I
live with my mom. I've got more money
than him. I've got more life experiences
than him. And I've got a mom that didn't
starve me. You know, I'm I'm [ __ ]
well ahead, bro. Yeah. I'm single. I've
got teeth. I've got a mom that don't
starve me. I'm not with a disabled
woman. Yeah. So what I'd say out of me,
you know, I I wouldn't want to be
somebody that's got no teeth, no money,
disabled girl, bedsit. Like, [ __ ] that, bro.
He gets everything you want. I don't
want a disabled girl. Poor again. I've
got more money than all of you people.
I've proved that I've got more money.
Unemployed, better looking than you.
More money. Again, you're talking about
yourselves again. You people are all of these things.
He doesn't Somebody in a bedsit with a
disabled girl has not got a better life
than me. And £13,000 is not a lot of
money. So, I don't know why you keep
going on about how he's shown money.
That is not money. At 31, you should be
having a car, teeth, more life
experience, your own house. He doesn't
have any of them things. A disabled
girlfriend in a bedsit is no flex.
Okay. Okay. I shown £6,000. Okay. Did he
show restaurants? Did he show better
women? Did he show better clothes? Did
he go abroad before he was 30? No, he
didn't. Because he couldn't afford it.
Because he couldn't afford it, mate.
Mate, you think in your 30, right? You
think at 31 having 13 grand, no life
experience, no car, no assets is
anything to flex about. When have I ever
come here and said my life is perfect?
I'm not 31 with no teeth and no money
and a disabled girl. It's not a flex. Do
you not understand, bro? And I never
once said, "My life is perfect."
His mom starved him. He could never go
back with his mom cuz his mom starved
him. You know how many times he's been
saying this about people living with
their mom? I'd rather live with my mom
than live in a council bedsit at 31. I
don't want to live in a bedsit,
you know. Okay. Yeah. Okay. Fair enough.
Okay. Fair enough. Right. He he might
not. He might not. But why has he got no
assets? Why has he got no travel
experience? If he's got all of this
money and a better life than me, why is
he still obsessing over my sloppy
seconds? Why has he got no teeth? Why
has he got a disabled girl?
You know what I'm saying? Anyways,
you're banned. Anyways, why at 31 is he
all of these things? Yeah, some people
not into designer clothes. You got no
assets. You got no designer clothes
though. You've been nowhere in your
life, but you've got all of this money
and so it's a better life than me and
you live in a bedsit, but you but you've
got a better life than me, bro. Make it
make sense. make it at 31 years old make
a little bit more sense. Bro, I have got
more life experience than him. I've got
more money than him. Think about it,
bro. Listen, I showed Okay. Okay. If
he's got all of this money, why is it
when I showed £6,000, he ran away for
two years and couldn't even pull together £1,000?
Go. Answer it. Answer it. Answer it.
Answer it, bro. Okay, you've got this
better life than me. Whatever. You got
shown thousands pounds multiple times
and you couldn't even string again. Yes,
I do have it now. And I'm not going to
show you nothing. Yep. And I'm not
showing you not even £10 because you
people have been shown money multiple
times before. So yeah. >> Yeah.
>> You don't know how much money I've got.
And I'm never showing you money ever
ever ever again.
So I'm saying yeah, simple.
There we go. I I live at I live listen
Jay Willow, bro. Most people in London
live with their mom or they live Okay.
No, I tell you what people do in London,
bro. Yeah, you are a loser. Yeah, it's
not just a life experience, bro. You're
a [ __ ] loser. Anyways, your life is a
loser. Jay Willow, you do realize that
most people in London live with their parents.
But listen, bro, they they live with
their parents or
are they live in a box room like single
people live in a box room or they live
with their parents in London, bro? Yeah,
you are disabled. Stop talking about yourself.
Yeah, I know it's not utter nonsense.
How would you know? You're not from
London. You don't have no life
experience, mate. You live in a [ __ ]
bed [ __ ] that you don't leave. You don't
know about my city. You don't know about
London. You wouldn't even be able to
afford to [ __ ] go out in London.
Utter nonsense. You've never been to
London. You can't afford London. How are
you going to tell a Londoner about
what's utter nonsense in your bed up
north? Come on, bro. You don't know
anything about London,
you know? Are you [ __ ] mad?
You don't know about London. You
wouldn't even be able to afford to eat
in London, mate. How the [ __ ] are you
telling people what's nonsense and
what's not nonsense? You've You wouldn't
have be able to afford here. How do I
know? Most because I have friends. You
idiot. I know a lot of people in the
city that I'm from. You [ __ ] It
doesn't take Einstein to know. You live
up north and you're trying to tell me
about my city.
Yeah. Well, your your family will tell
you, won't they? Your family will tell
you about [ __ ] London, won't they,
bro? Your family will tell you about
London, won't they, Jay Willow?
Obviously, if you live up north, then
obviously it's a bit different. You
know, a lot of people are moving to
Manchester now, Jay Willow, from London.
A lot of people are moving to Manchester.
Prices and [ __ ] I know a few people
that's moved to Manchester, but
I don't need to name you 30 people,
mate. You're a stupid little Northerner
that's probably never been to London.
Don't try and tell me what is utter
nonsense and what's not utter nonsense. You know, bye-bye.
You live up north and you're trying to
tell me, bro, are you mad?
Uh, fruit king, you're fatter than me,
bro. Don't tell me to go to the gym,
bro. Your life is already over. Like,
you don't need to give me advice, bro.
Your life is already over, bro. You're
way more fatter than me. I'm not even
fat to begin with, bro. You You needed
to give yourself that advice before it
was already over for you.
Please, bro. Like, look at your own body
before talking about other people.
Truing. Ding. Stop it.
Yeah, but a lot of people are moving to
Manchester because the prices, but
I don't know if I could live in
Manchester, bro. I don't know about that.
Well, what are we going to say, bro?
There's nothing left to say about women.
I will never speak to any of them ever again.
I don't think so, bro. [ __ ] it. Is it?
See, if I was a virgin, yeah,
if I was like a virgin, then maybe I
would, but I'm like 28 next month and I
don't give a [ __ ] if I have no one or
not. And I'm not going to disrespect
myself to be able to find someone. I'm
not going to put up with their [ __ ] any
longer. You know, you get to a point
where you're like, "Enough is enough.
I'm not dealing with that [ __ ] anymore."
That's it, bro. Like I don't mind, you
know, I don't give a [ __ ] about sex, but
you know that's everyone's different.
300 maximum to my name. If only you
knew, mate. See, see Winchester, let me
let me give you some advice here. Yeah.
Stop talking about people that you don't
know. Where do these things come from?
You know, you people in your 40s and you
don't have anything. Look at your own
lives. You're telling people you don't
they Okay, one second. I'm not talking
about you here, Jay Willow. Yeah.
Listen. Um, no. I'll never start fresh.
I don't want anything to do with any
woman ever again. One second,
Winchester, right? Why are you saying
that people have got 300 backs to my
name? You don't know what I have. You
don't know how much I have. Again, this
is what makes me think they willow.
These people talk about their own lives
cuz it's so random the [ __ ] that they
come out with and you say that other
people have got nothing in their life.
Bro, you people on YouTube from the time
you wake up to the time you go to bed
and I've proved it many times. So, what
have you got, bro? Tell us. Not you, J.
I know you don't come on here all day,
every day. But I've seen you people on
here from the time you wake up to the
time you go you go to bed. Tell us
what's exciting about your life. Do a
video, bro. show us some of the things
you've got because I guarantee you now a
lot of your lives are a lot worse than
mine. I guarantee you that. Again, I
don't have a perfect life, but I agree
with that one. But you people are old
age pensioners and you're sat on YouTube
every [ __ ] day from the time you wake
up to the time you go bed. And when I
was when I was off of YouTube for nine
days, I clicked on the live streams and
I was on there and I saw it myself.
you know, you want to make maybe look a
bit closer to home. And you know what?
It's not about money. It's not about
whether you've got money or you don't
have money. You clearly ain't got
anything going on in your life, right?
To to do this, to do this every day.
Doesn't matter whether you work or you
got money. You ain't got a life. You
ain't got a [ __ ] life, son, to be
doing this, you know?
I mean, yeah.
Really? Okay, think about it. I'm better
looking than you people. I'm younger
than you people. I probably got a lot
more money than a lot of you people. And
I live in a better city than you people.
Think about it, bro. What do you people
have? You ain't got no money. Yeah.
Yeah. You got no money. Probably a lot
of you people. You're fat. You're old.
You're ugly. You probably can't even
leave your house due to anxiety. Bro,
your heart your lives are not hard to
beat. Trust me, your lives are not hard
to be at all by any stretch, you know.
And again, I'm not saying I am
goodlooking. I'm not saying that. I'm
saying that I'm better looking than you.
You're old. You're [ __ ] riddled with
[ __ ] anxiety, bro. Your lives ain't
hard to beat.
I'm not say I'm not moaning about
pulling. I'm just saying that women are
[ __ ] Women are [ __ ] I don't want
to pull a woman.
Well, when have I said recently that I
want to pull a woman? I have been
showing you what they've been doing for
the past couple of days, which again
you've been ignoring. So, whatever.
If I'm not sub to them, cuz I was I was
sub to Monty Man and I saw people commenting,
you know, make it make sense. Haven't I
shown that I've been with more women than you?
Um, when do I hound them on the street?
Uh, these videos were ages ago.
These videos were ages ago.
They were ages ago. These videos,
they were a The videos that I put up
were ages ago. They're not recent ones.
Um, and that's when I thought women were
different, but they're clearly all the
same. And haven't I shown you me with women, Winchester?
I mean, I've shown you me with me multiple women. Strange. Yeah. So, yeah.
What I don't understand is why does
nonslegs not have any teeth? I mean,
dental care was free on the to people on
benefits. I don't understand why he he
don't get his teeth sorted out.
It's free. You don't have to pay. Like
literally, if you're on benefits, Jay
Willow, you get this stuff for free.
Um, zero success. I've had one night
stands, I've had dates, I've had chances
of being relationships. Try again.
Again, not everyone has your life. I
don't know what it is with you people
seeming to think um seeming to think
that Winchester, no one cares about you.
You're an old man sat on YouTube every day, bro.
You know, no one gives a [ __ ]
Six one night stands at six one night
stands more than you. That six one night
If you think about that more dates than
you, I've met more women than you, but
I've also met more women than you. So I
know what women are like. So
I've probably met more women than
anybody on this community.
You know the [ __ ] I've got up to in four years, bro.
I probably have to be fair.
But he um
you never been in a relationship. You don't know.
Yeah, I have been in a relationship and
you're still a virgin. So yeah, I
definitely know how they tick. I think
somebody that's met as more women than
you, I would know exactly what they're like.
See, when people used to say, "Oh, I
don't like the stuff you're saying about
kids." I always used to agree with them.
Yeah, you can't really disagree. But
it's when they say stuff about women,
that's what annoys me because it's like,
you know what they've done to you. You
know what they've done in the past. And
that's what always used to make me fall
out with people.
See, when I fall out with people, I
don't speak to them again. They widow. I
don't speak to people. So, my sister, I
was supposed to go out on my with my
sister on my birthday. We had like a
little argument and I blocked her. We
could probably talk again. It's my other
sister I was speaking to her. I won't
talk to her ever again. That's my ego
now. Like, once someone's blocked,
they're done. They're done. Done. I
won't speak to them ever again. That's
what I'm like, bro. Like I'm even like
we just had like an argument, but I
won't talk to her again. Nah,
when I'm done with someone, I'm done.
That's the kind of person I'm like, bro.
Like I'm I'm like Yeah.
So that's what I'm like, bro.
Bro, no one's jealous of a skinned
virgin with no teeth that lives in a bedsit.
Why would I be jealous of somebody
that's got no life experience? Okay,
let's let's let's Okay, let's put up no
savings. I've got savings. I've got
money. You don't know anything about me
again. Stop thinking everyone's got the
same life as you. Why would I be jealous
of somebody? Okay, let's let's go by the
facts. I'm younger than him. I'm better
looking than him. I've got teeth unlike
him. I've got a mom that loves me. I've
got more life experiences than him. And
I've never had to be with a disabled girl. You know,
why would I be jealous of some lanky
skinned little virgin that's got no life
experience? Like, we're not just talking about money,
right? We're talking about actual life
experiences. The kid's ugly. The kid's
got no teeth. The kids with a girl that
I would never ever ever get with even if
you paid me. That's the God's honest
truth. Why would I be jealous of someone like that?
Bro, give your head a wobble. You
seriously need to give your head a
wobble. Um, Mo, how many second days
have you had?
Not answering your questions.
But do you know what I find strange is
that he's got a better life than me,
but he wastes every second of every day
trying to [ __ ] with me online. Now, give
give your honest opinion on this one, J.
Yeah, this guy's apparently got
everything that I'm jealous of.
What? No teeth and a disabled
girlfriend. But he's the one that
continuously will not leave me alone. Strange.
But I'm the one that's jealous of him of
all people. Bear in mind, I've never
been jealous, but yeah, he's the one
going live, doing videos, will not leave
people alone. I mean, the evidence is
there that he's clearly the jealous one. you know.
Yeah. You know, so yeah, that's it.
I mean, the evidence is there, Jay. Willow,
that's what makes me think you like
nonsense. Oh, this is another thing he
brought up. Oh, how do I know uh he's a
nons? Okay. Okay. No, no, I'm not I'm
I'm not saying Okay, I'm not going to
name you things that he's jealous of. I
don't have an ego. But for somebody
that's better than someone, they [ __ ]
waste a lot of time on somebody that
they're not jealous of. Because I
wouldn't [ __ ] with somebody that I
wasn't jealous of. I'd get on with my
own life. Okay, think about it, right?
He's got a lovely girlfriend. He's got
all this money apparently. Would he just
get off of YouTube and live his life or
create his own content?
I'm not I think of it. Think think of
it, bro. He doesn't bully anyone. I went
to his area and made him go running to
the police and made him scared to go to
events for over a month. I assure you he
doesn't bully me, mate. Somebody that
runs to the police screaming that
they're not a fighter. Um, so yeah, for
somebody to sit on YouTube and do But
this is what I mean. You people like
nons, you know, when me and Monty was
talking, you people like nons. This is
why you're so obsessed with this guy.
This is why you love him because he's a
nons and you people love nons. It's
obvious. It's so obvious. You love
pedos. That's why you defend him. I know
it now because I I had this conversation
with Monty man before as well. You love
nonsers. You stick up for nonsers. You
used to do the same thing with Pat
Muffin. You love nonsers.
And he and he says, "What what makes me
a nod? What makes me a nod? What makes
me a nod?" Um and then he says that I'm
a nod because I've got a baby grow that
makes someone a nod. I'll explain to you
how you're a nons. Because when somebody
says to you, "Oh, you want to get with a
16y old?" You sit there and say, "Oh,
well, it's legal. It's legal." Like, you
try to justify
how it's morally right. You're a nons
kid. You're a [ __ ] pedo. You know,
you've done it like a few times. And
that's why you people like him cuz he's a pedophile,
you know? And that's what you people are
in this community, pedos. So obviously
you like pedophiles. You love pedos,
man. That's what it is. You love pedos.
Everyone's heard him say it as well.
I noticed that as well. You love pedos.
Why do you love pedos so much?
Why you be huh?
Why do you people love pedos? Huh?
I do feel sorry for you though, bro.
Defending women. And you know, the
madest thing about it is I've probably
been with more women than a lot of
people in this community.
Don't believe everything you hear, you know.
You know, but you people do like
pedophiles. That's why you like nonslegs
because he's a pedo. Yeah, he's a pedo.
That's why you like him, is it? Yeah.
Trying to say has he how many times have
I shown that virgin money? But yeah, you
like pedophiles. That's why you defend
him. It's obvious you like pedos.
Yeah. And that's why none of them has
ever got with you bubble.
Yeah. You love pedophiles. That's why
you defend this [ __ ] creep. You know,
that's why you defend this creep. Cuz
you love pedos. I know. And that's why
they've never been with you. Yeah.
I feel sorry for you simps.
I really feel sorry for you little white knights
really thinking that defending a woman
will make women like you. See, like I
said, I'm not I'm just someone not
scared to say what they think. I'm not
an incel. I'm not a misogynist. I don't
have no reason to be. I've had more
women than you people, as immature as
that sounds. So why would I possibly disagree?
Yeah, man. You know, you're laughing at
your own life. You don't have a life.
Well, to be honest, you don't have a
life. That's why you're sat on YouTube every day, huh?
Yeah. Good for him. Good for him. I'd
rather be single than have a disabled
girlfriend. I've said that a million
times. I'd rather be single than have a disabled wolf.
So, don't know how many times I have to say that.
I would never get with a disabled the
wolf. I've got standards. So, yeah.
But guess what? I've got teeth. He
doesn't. I've got more life experiences.
He doesn't. I've got a mom that doesn't
hate me. He doesn't.
Sip of the tongue there, is it? Yeah. I
feel sorry for you people defending women. You know,
you're single. You're on YouTube single right now
cuz you ain't got a life. But aren't you single? bubble.
Aren't you single? Uh,
nah. I I I assure you, you're laughing
at your own life. Middle age [ __ ] sat
on YouTube ain't got a life. Yeah, you
ain't got a girlfriend though, do you, Bubble?
Do you have a girlfriend? Where's your
That's nice, man. Where's your girlfriend?
Yeah, I never had a second date. Where's
your girlfriend? Thank you. You don't
have a girlfriend. Mice has a
Money has a girlfriend. Where's your girlfriend?
You can't answer that one, can you? Uh, anyways, bias bastic. So, yeah.
Yeah, I know, bro. He has everything I
want I want in life. No teeth, no money,
sat in a bed sit, ugly looks, disabled
girl. I know, bro. I'm dying every single day.
I know, bro. Damn, you got me.
I mean, there's there's I'm pretty sure,
Jay Widow, there's people that you
idolize in your life. And there's people
that I there's always someone
that I've been jealous of, someone
that's got no teeth, no money, no bed,
cancel home, never been on a plane, no
life experience, never been to a nice
restaurant, been with less women than
me. Damn. See, people are just jealous
of different people. I happen to be
jealous of of that person. Oh, and let's
not forget the mom hating him is really
something to be jealous of as well.
Damn, you learn something new every day,
you know. Yeah.
Yeah, you do learn something new every day. 100%.
I'm never showing you money ever, ever, ever again.
I will never ever ever ever ever
show you money ever again.
Um, I would bet any money that she are
in better shape. He doesn't have any
teeth. He's got missing teeth, so that's
not possible. He's got missing teeth. So, yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm jealous of somebody that's got
mitten teeth, no money, living in a
bedsit, no life experience, and a mom
who hates him. Yeah, bro.
I've never Yeah. If I've got money, you
don't know how much money I have. You
don't know anything. You don't know
anything about what I have.
When have I told you that I've got £300?
Again, we don't all have your life.
You come out with the most random thing
that I've got £300 maximum. You don't
know how much money I have. You do not
Try again. I'm not showing you no money,
bro. I'm not showing you money again.
I'm not showing you money again because
every single time people show you money,
you run away. Why am I going to show you money? Huh?
Yeah. Well, my mom doesn't starve me. I
can I can certainly tell you my mom does
not starve me mate like a certain
persons did. So yeah. Um
why I don't show you money cuz every
time you get show money you run away.
You're just you're just little self projectors.
You're self projectors.
Uh take it back from YouTube. Well I
don't gamble anymore. You seem to think
people have got the same lives as you.
You know what it is with these people on
here, J Willow? They seem to think
everyone's got the same life as them.
This is their problem on here, bro. It's
like Timmy, right? When he says, "Oh,
you're skinned. Show me money." I said a
million times, "I'm not showing you no
money." If you want to keep show saying
I'm skinn, good for you, bro. I'm not
showing you no money.
Good for you. I'm never showing you
nothing. So, that's it, bro. Like,
that's the thing. That's the thing with
a lot of people. They think everyone's
got their life
skin. It's like it's [ __ ] bro.
They generally think everyone's got I I
don't gamble, J. I haven't. The last
time I gambled was when I put 100 on
roulette was a month ago and I won £500.
Then I won the money back that I
basically spent and I thought I swear
I'd never go out again after that.
That's the last time I tried.
I swear I'd never try again.
And people think it's cuz I ain't got
money. I've got money, bro. I can go out
every week if I wanted to.
I could go every week if I wanted to.
But yeah, I'm not going to do that, bro.
I was going to go on my birthday, but no,
no, I ain't doing that.
So, I'll never try again. But like I said,
you know, it's so weird, J.
I don't go out now. Yeah. I feel good,
man. I don't even feel bored.
You know what I'm saying? And I don't
even feel bored, lad.
Why? I said to my mom, "Let's go to
Florida." But she won't do it.
The thing is, Jay Willow, I'm so like relieved.
As soon as I gave up with the whole
dating thing, I was like, "Nah, never
again. Never ever ever again."
It took like two weeks to stop feeling
depressed about it.
So I swear I'd never try again after that, bro.
I can't afford that. Yes, I can. You
don't know how much money I have. You
don't know what I have. Again, we don't
all have your life, Winchester. We don't
all have your life, bro.
This is something that you're getting
confused. You don't know what people
have and what people don't have.
This is something that you should have
learned years ago. Just because you
can't afford something, it doesn't mean
we can't afford something.
This is people's problem on here, Jay
Willow. This is people's problem. This
really is people's problem on here.
They think everyone's got their life.
Yeah. I couldn't afford a flight. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I don't need to. I'm
not proving you wrong. I'm not I've
proved you wrong millions of times. I've
proved I've had more women than you
people. I've proved I've had more money
than you people. And you always dismiss
it. I don't need to prove myself to vi people.
Although I should have went to
Birmingham last week cuz it was just
going to be fun. I mean, that was just
going to be fun because I was going to
see Rice and that. I should have went,
but I don't even meet people now because
how biased you people are.
Like, [ __ ] that.
I'm not proving you. I'm not proving nothing. So yeah,
you think you think everyone's got the
same life as you. That's on you, bro. I
don't give a [ __ ]
So I don't need to show no money. I've
already showed you, baby, bro.
Never mind. I have well over £1,000.
If only you knew.
Ah, if only you knew. Yeah.
No, I've got well over £1,000. You don't
know how much money I have.
Why are you so interested in what people
have as well?
Why are you so interested in how much
money people have and what people don't
have? Okay. Okay. Okay. Let's Okay.
Let's go by your logic, right? You're
trying to say that I'm skin even though
I've won four football bets and I've won
on roulette. How could I be skinn? What
have I spent my money on? Did I?
You really really don't know about people's lives.
Jay Willow. Yeah. If you want me to show
you, I can show you. I can show you a
couple of thousand pound if you want off
of here. Like just to let just to let me
let let me just to show you, bro. just
to show you Jay Willow that these people
they don't um because obviously you're
like a genuine person on it. If you ever
think these people are telling the
truth, I'll show you a couple of
thousand pound, bro. I don't give a
[ __ ] I'm just not showing these people anything.
You know, I'll show you my bank account
if you want, bro. I don't give a [ __ ]
I'm just not showing these people anything.
I don't Bro, no. I'm just saying I just
don't want you to believe these people.
But I just don't want to show them nothing, you know,
now with the whole 13 grand that thing
he showed. If you won 13 grand or you
are or you you know you get four grand a
month on top of it, then yeah, it's
good. But why I said it was [ __ ] Jay
Widow is because he showed 13 grand,
right? He's never had designer clothes.
He's never been to a nice restaurant.
He's never traveled. He hasn't he hasn't
done anything with his life at 30
for for the sake of that 13 grand. You
don't understand, bro. I've lived life.
I've I've gambled. I've drunk. I've gone
to nice restaurants. I've been to nice
places. I've trapped. You know what I mean, bro?
No. I proven nothing. I've proved I've
had more money multiple times.
Yeah, it's not worth it. It's not worth
it for the sake of 13 grand, bro. It's
not worth it.
Is it Is it worth no life experiences
for 13 grand?
I saved three grand in a month before.
Yeah, three grand in a month.
If I really wanted to, I could get 13
grand in about 4 months.
I mean, like, not including the money
that I've got. I I reckon I could. Yeah. Antman
said the same thing. He said, "If people
just miss your struggle, you just [ __ ]
off and leave in it." [ __ ] them.
I feel a bit [ __ ] though. Like he his
mom understands him more than my mom
understands me when I've been through
more more with it.
No, no, no, no, no. It's not no. Not the
fact of traveling, but if you don't like
traveling and you don't like designer
clothes and you don't nice and you don't
like nice restaurants, what have you
done with your life?
What have you done with your [ __ ]
life? If you've got all of this money,
wouldn't you want to like improve?
Think about it, bro. Like, isn't there
anything that you wanted to do? Like, it's
me. It's mental, bro. was mental.
Obviously, I don't do much. I don't get
as much money now. But
I've done a lot of stuff, though. It's
that's why I don't really go out.
Yeah. But don't you have goals in life
that you you want to do?
Is a [ __ ] I don't Yeah, but you know So yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] me.
And he says about how the only women
that I've met is women that I've got
reject uh rejected on the street. If he
went and he approached women, he would
never even get a date. And he knows
this. That's why he That's why he um
That's why he um sticks with disabled
women cuz he's never been with anything
normal and he can't get anything normal.
That's why he goes on about this
American [ __ ] chick cuz he's jealous.
He would get rejected by every woman and
not even ever get a date. That ugly
[ __ ] could never get a normal woman.
That's why he goes with disabled.
That's why he because he could never
ever get with a normal woman, bro.
What do you mean by the bulldog? I don't get you,
bro. If I had my life, I I would live by
myself with a dog.
And he said, "Oh, another thing he said
is like, oh yeah, you've never been with
a had a chance to sleep in a bed with a
woman. I've been in bed with a woman
multiple times, and I like to sleep by
myself." Yes, I do. I like my own space.
You know, you're not supposed to sleep
next to another person.
Yes, I have. And I've kicked people out.
When I was in Nottingham, when I was
done with the woman, I kicked her out.
Yes, I did, [ __ ]
But bro, I've been with more women than
you have. Why would have I been in a bed
with a [ __ ] woman?
He's very very very insecure.
I don't know. I I I don't know why he
goes on about this USA, is he? He's
really really obsessed.
He hates the fact that anyone can get a
normal woman that's not disabled because
he can't. That's it's it's very
unhealthy, isn't it?
So weird, isn't it, bro? You not find
that weird, Jay. Willow, that like say
you had a woman and you was you was
convincing yourself every day that
someone hasn't had sex with someone.
It's so weird.
Do not find that [ __ ] cringe, bro.
That is strange, bro.
Oh, this guy is on.
>> Yeah. He would never be able to get with
someone like USA, is he? That's what you
call killing someone.
That's what you call killing someone,
bro. That killed him, bro. When I got with her.
Oh, that guy is legit then, bro.
Why do I watch him, bro? I go on the channel occasionally,
but I don't understand if he's happy.
Why is he on YouTube obsessing over me every day?
Obviously, no one's going to say
anything because they don't like me, but
he's not happy. He spends all his life
trying to say that I'm ugly when I'm
better looking than him.
It's very weird, isn't it? He can't be
happy. He's in I don't even think he's
happy in that relationship cuz I don't
know, man. Like, wouldn't people just
live their life, make their own content?
He wastes every second of every day
stalking me, but he's in a happy
relationship. I don't know, man. I don't
think he's that happy, to be honest.
He goes on about one night stands I've
had. He's so weird. Very, very weird virgin.
He's so weird. He He hates the fact of
anyone getting sex with a normal woman.
I thought he was in a happy relationship. So weird.
I don't [ __ ] know, bro. Why are these
people? He's a weirdo, though.
I don't make videos about him. Yeah, but
it doesn't matter though because he's
doing videos on me. He's going live about me,
so he's reacting to me. So that doesn't
make any sense, you know?
It doesn't matter, bro. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no. He's doing
videos and he's reacting to me.
So you wouldn't do that if you had a life.
So I've spoke about him for hours. He's
been going on about me for the past 2 weeks.
So he's reacting to me.
He's doing videos to me.
He's reacting more to me. So that
doesn't make any sense. So what? He's
wasting more time on me. So I waste some
time on him. He is the one that's
obsessed. It doesn't matter why he's
doing it or why he's not doing it. He is obsessed.
He is obsessed. It doesn't matter why
he's doing it, you know. So,
yeah, you need to go to the gym, bro.
He is the one that's obsessed.
Cuz the thing is, Jay Willow, they don't
do it for reaction. This is what I've
tried explaining a million times. They
don't do it for reaction. Cuz even if
you didn't react to them, they would
still do it.
They would never they'll never stop
whether you react or you don't react.
So, and then okay. So, then what happens
after you react? I don't get it. It's
not. And it's good because even if you
don't react, they still do it. So,
whether you react or you don't react,
they will still do it.
They will never ever ever ever ever ever stop.
So that's it.
I could right never go live again and
just do videos. Yeah. So videos, no live streams.
Videos and no live streams, right? And I
could come back in four years on them
same channels and they would still be
doing it every day. So
what what would they be doing it for? Then what?
For you to react four years later.
They don't do it for reacting, bro.
That's ridiculous. That is stupid
because it's not a reaction. They're obsessed.
They're [ __ ] obsessed.
And I was talking about him because I
was putting him straight on a couple of things.
Get your life sorted first before trying
to talk about other people.
Obsessed, bro. He is obsessed. Why is
that skinned virgin so obsessed with me anyways, bro?
Did you see the date in that video?
Oh, this guy is fiery. Yeah.
Yeah, this guy's an idiot, bro.
Sorry for these people defending women.
Yeah, they're proper proper simps.
Proper proper simps. Proper
Can't deny she's attractive.
You can't deny she's attractive, bro. [ __ ] virgin.