Sorry. Quarter Turkish. My mom's half
Turkish, so it makes me quarter. And the
rest of me is English, but my family's
western guy, so it's very hard to to
explain it to him. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
That's like my granddad. He's like 100%
um uh Turkish. He told me when he was
16. Yeah. Yeah. So, what is he is she
Muslim? Is she Muslim? No.
Yeah. Like he's supposed to be Muslim,
but I mean he would still do things that
Muslims are not supposed to do. You know
what I mean? Yeah.
Yeah. So Cyprus, you got the Greek side
and you've got the Turkish side. So
you're probably the Greek side and I'm
the Turkish side. Yeah. If you're from
Oh, you're from Is it Is it
um Is there an island you're from? Yeah.
So you're the Greek side and I'm the
other side. There we go. Yeah, I'm
atheist. Atheist. Yeah. What about you? Atheist. Atheist.
Jewish. You get a lot of Jewish people
in America, don't you? Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, you're pretty much the same as me
to be fair, but I look probably more
perfect like than I am. I don't I don't
think I look fully white.
I look Turkish. I know. And I look
forward. I'm only
like the beard. Is it the bean? Yeah.
But the maddest thing is I don't look
like my mom or my dad. I definitely
don't look like my dad. I take my mom's
side, but I don't look like my mom.
You look like a dad. Yeah. You got you
got any siblings? One one
brother? I got two sisters. Older
annoyingly. Yeah, it's annoying. But um yeah, it
happens. Yeah, I've always been atheist.
I've never just seen a reason to
believe. I got movement bend and stuff,
but I just just never believed in any
religion, you know. Yeah,
you definitely don't look green. [Music] What heritage?
I don't know. Like maybe it's fully
white to be fair. Fully American. Yeah.
No, you didn't. To be fair. No, that's
why whenever I want to spoke to you, I
thought, "Oh, she's from America." Okay.
Yeah, you looked um like
Oh, I didn't think you looked American at all. More like
maybe I don't know. Maybe like Polish.
Maybe like Spanish. Yeah. [Music]
Um, let's go a bit there. As soon as
there's a speech,
does your mom or dad speak any Greek? No. No.
My family died. Um, that's
So, how long have you been single? Um,
how long have I been single? A while. Oh, wow.