Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, man. Oh, I got late.
I want a bone to pick with you.
Why did you dismiss my approaches?
I said I put up some approaches. Why
didn't he say anything about them? madness.
Wait, Ricky, why didn't you um comment
on the approaching videos?
You said that I should have a girlfriend
and I'm the problem and t. So, that's
why I put the approaching videos up
to prove your argument wrong.
You didn't comment on any of them or anything.
You said I was the problem.
Then I put some approaching videos up to
prove that it's not true what you're saying.
And I also put up the ones about dating app
cuz you said that I was the problem.
That's strange, isn't it? Cuz you didn't
comment on any of the stuff that I put up.
That's strange, isn't it, Bob?
You say that to you, but I literally put
videos up of dating apps.
I put videos up of what happens when you
try to speak to a woman. Strange.
That is definitely strange.
Wh why why did you like the videos, bro?
Did you like them? Yeah.
Or did you like the approaches?
I was just showing basically, bro,
dating in 2025.
That's what happens when you try to
speak to someone,
but people say it's you. Yeah, he didn't
comment on any of my videos.
Yeah, we know he's been on YouTube.
I can't believe the [ __ ] skinned
virgin in the bedsit yesterday
trying to [ __ ] tell me trying to tell
me about my life when he's in a bedsit
with no [ __ ] bed and no money in it.
the council bed sit and he ain't even
got no teeth and he's trying to talk
about my life
being like I need to sort my life out
coming from you.
Somebody that can't get over my sloppy
seconds. Someone that ain't got no
teeth. Someone got that got starved by their mom.
I couldn't believe what I was [ __ ] hearing.
It's coming from you. Jesus Christ.
some skin b.
[ __ ] hell, mate.
But yeah, anyways, I hope you like the content, bro.
But people But Bob, you can understand
why people would think they won't meet
anyone now, don't you?
You could understand, can't you? Why you
would you would you you'd think that you
would meet someone, right? Because
obviously the dating apps and they call
it hookup culture.
I haven't seen Ricky today. He's gone
quiet, is he?
Where are you, Rickster? Don't go quiet on us.
You said that we should be having a
girlfriend because we're decent looking.
Well, I've shown you videos of me
talking to people normally.
I shown you
approaching people normally and I have
shown you dating apps. So where have you
gone, bro? I don't always think I'm
right. I'm showing you what I'm what I'm experiencing.
Why Why have you run away again?
Cuz I haven't heard from you. No
comments, no nothing. You know,
but Bob, there's he's saying about me
being the problem and I'm showing him me
talking to people.
So, how can I be the problem?
Well, the guy got annihilated, bro.
So yeah, but it doesn't matter anyways,
bro. You know, it's also talking about
it soon because
people are just going to keep dismissing
my struggles anyways. So it's pointless
to keep going on about it.
They're always going to dismiss my struggles.
They're always always going to keep
dismissing my struggles. So, it's like
what Antman said. He's like, "Just
leave." Simple. I told him about my mom
dismissing my struggles.
And he says, "Your mom's just this is
your he says, yeah, it's like no matter
how much you tell them or no matter how
much you show them, they just shake
their head." And we're like, "Nah."
Yeah, [ __ ] him then. That's what Antman
said. He said, "Fuck them."
Um, I don't know. I don't know what I'm
going to eat.
Probably nothing to be fair. Woke up at this time.
[ __ ] nose, bro. [ __ ] no.
But yeah, Bob, you can you can see why
now you'd think it's un
you because people on here were giving
me [ __ ] but no one replied to any of
the videos I put up about the dating
apps and stuff.
No one commented.
Did it suit anyone? No,
it didn't suit them, did it?
They tell me to go on dating apps, Bob.
They tell me to go on dating apps.
Oh, yeah. 100%. 1 million%. I'm
determined even more now to save to leave.
So hopefully the messages that's gave
you an insight of some of the [ __ ] that
I've been dealing with over the years
with these women,
even though people still blame me,
whatever. But hopefully that gives you
more insight, more of an insight.
What did you like the approaching videos?
Yeah, I think they were pretty good to be honest.
Yeah, Grievy. So,
Ricky said about it was me being a
problem and I'm decent looking and how I
should have no problem finding um a
girlfriend and it's the way that I'm acting.
And um well, since I've put the videos
up of the dating apps and since I've put
the videos up of me approaching women,
I haven't heard from him. I'm start I'm
starting to call the I'm going to have
to start I might have to call the ambulance.
I'm starting to get a bit worried again.
Haven't heard from him since the videos
have been put up. He seems to have vanished.
So, I'm getting I'm getting a bit worried.
I might I might have to call the
ambulance, you know. Why have you run
away again? I'll chase you. I'll chase
you, Ricky. I'll chase you. I'll chase
you. I'll chase you. I'll [ __ ] chase You know,
I don't understand how some skint virgin
in a bed suit could try and tell me
about my life. No teeth, no money, no
bed, no assets, no life experiences. Yet
you're trying to tell me about who I
live with and I need to sort my [ __ ] life out.
You I was listening to this cunt's live stream.
You It is almost 2026
and you're still convincing yourself
every day that I haven't slept with USA.
You sad sad insecure bastard. Everything
that you say on your channel is self
projected. You're the one that sits on
YouTube every day trying to con trying
to convince [ __ ] people that they're
as ugly as you. Trying to [ __ ]
convince people yourself that people
ain't had sex with people cuz you're
still a virgin yourself. It's almost 20 [ __ ] six.
Do you understand? You're still doing this [ __ ]
[ __ ] hell, Virgin boy. Never ever
going to get laid, are you? Never going
So many low IQ people on here, bro.
I love Ricky to come on my live stream.
Remember Ricky's quote from a year and a
half ago. Grezy, you're good looking,
PJ. It's the women that are picky.
Hold that L, [ __ ] Hold that L.
Cold that L
right and and he says I'm a N because
I've kept a baby girl. I kept a baby
girl for the next baby because it was an
unusual baby go. What's h keeping a baby
go having to deal with being a n.
What the [ __ ] is that how your mind works? You know,
like you are the one that says it's okay
to get with a 16y old because it's not
certain states of America. You are a
nod. You dirty nods. You should have
joined us earlier. Grezy, I was making I
made Bear sandwiches.
I made Bear sandwiches.
Yeah, I made Billy Bear sandwiches. I
nipped to the supermarket. Yeah,
Ricky was driving me mad. He got me on
the Billy Bear sandwiches.
Why is he run away? Ricky, come back,
Lucy. Can you get him back? He He seems
to run away when he gets proven wrong.
Now, what I don't understand is he says
that I'm I'm repeating and I'm boring,
but doesn't he go on Nonsex's channel,
which is boring and repeating?
It's literally the same [ __ ] Like, no
one goes on that channel except the
people that are obsessed with me. I
mean, that's a boring repeating channel,
but you don't mind going to that one. That bastard.
I'm going to do Monty in on Friday.
He thinks he's going to beat me. You
can't beat me.
Why? Why is he gone quiet? Why is this
Ricky gone quiet?
He said it was me that was a problem.
Why is Monty trying to get me on
Discord? [ __ ] off.
Not [ __ ] I'm not going on your stupid
Discord. Hey Big Bus Bonanza, how you
doing? Are you okay? I haven't heard
from Ricky since I put the approaches up
and since I put my dating profile up, so
I'm not sure what what what's going on
there. I hope he's okay.
[ __ ] done the runner
cuz you said I was talking about kids
and it was the way I was acting. So, I
thought I' I'd put a couple of
approaches up and the women didn't even
give me the chance.
How long are we going to keep these lies
up for, bro? Seriously, how long are we
going to really keep these lies up for?
I had a shower before I went to bed
cuz I was stinking. So yeah, I watch my
little body greasy.
But Big Bass Bonanza, they say it's
about personality, but none of these
women gave me a chance to get to know my personality.
And then they say dating apps is a hookup culture. Strange.
I'm not so sure.
I'm not so sure. I don't know about you,
but I'm I'm not so sure.
What about you, Greasy? They say that
it's a hookup culture.
I mean, Hugh, since I put them
approaching videos up, I haven't heard
from Ricky. I'm getting a bit worried.
I might have to go to Hull to see if
he's all right. You can only keep this
these excuses and this [ __ ] up for so long.
You know, you've been proven wrong
multiple times. You said that it was
about how people are acting
um and and whatever. It's how people's
acting and stuff, but that
um that proves what you're saying is wrong.
cuz I put up at least two of them videos
where these people said they weren't
interested straight away. It doesn't
matter what the reason was, you know? It
wasn't because of my [ __ ]
personality. So, these people need to
stop capping you. You know what I mean?
It's not about personality at first.
It's about their physical type. If
you're not their physical type, you're
not they're not going to give you a chance. Simple.
I don't know why it almost we're almost
in 2026 and it still capped.
Yeah, that's only that's only that's
only 1% of it, mate. I was going to put
more up, but I reached my daily upload limit.
Yeah. So, what was the excuses for these ones?
I mean, I told you I tried more than
anyone in the world. You didn't believe me.
I' been dealing with this [ __ ] for
years, bro, with with women. So yeah, [ __ ]
I've been dealing with it for years.
[ __ ] years, mate. It's not even a joke.
So them them 14 people that thumbs up
your comment must be like must must must
be wrong then
they must be wrong with what these
videos are showing
14 people or however much is it must be
wrong now then isn't it if you took that
to a courtroom
Ah, long story, bro. Long story.
So, them 14 people must be wrong then by
what these videos are showing
cuz we're not talking about who's right
and who's wrong. We're showing you
evidence of what they're doing, which I
don't know how anyone could argue with
that to be honest. But they still How
can they thumbs up something when
they've been shown differently?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I I know what you're
saying, but but his comment is not right
because the videos and the and the
messages show that he's wrong. It's it's
it's not up for debate. The videos are
showing that he is wrong. So, the only
people that fumbed up the comment are
the people that didn't watch the videos.
Cuz if they watched the videos, they
would know that he was wrong.
Yeah. Yeah. But what I'm trying to say
is if they had watched the video, they
would know that that is wrong. So, 14
people didn't watch the video. There's
no way because if they did, they would
see that that's wrong.
So, but that's what they do. They
dismiss people's struggles and make up
stuff. That's what they they always do
that when it comes to women, which is
why I'll never have this argument with
anyone ever again because it doesn't
matter what you show them. You can show
them clear as day evidence and they will
still say, "Nah, never happened." That's
literally what they do. You've seen it
yourself. You've seen the videos, bro.
So, how how can I think that I'm always
right when I'm showing you the videos?
This is this is the thing. This is the
thing that I'm actually
This is the thing that we keep dismissing
is there's video evidence of what they've done.
What how can you disagree with it? Clear
as day. So that's it's strange. It is
strange. Very strange.
Just think of it right. He's comment got
14 thumbs up. Well, maybe wrong now.
He's saying that I sent love hearts.
They sent me love hearts. He's saying
that I sent them voice notes. There's
some that I didn't send voice notes.
He's saying it's the way that I'm
acting. I've had women agree to meet me.
I've had women that didn't even give me
the chance to get to know how I'm
acting. So, how could they be right?
How could they possibly be right?
Yeah. I used a pickup line, but my
friend kept saying, "Use that pickup
line." So, I thought, "Fuck it. Try it
for the content in it." But yeah, so
there's no way then people can be right. You know,
it's not like they said Hugh, oh, you're
wrong on this one, you're right on this
one. There's So what you're saying is I
was wrong in every single one of them conversations.
Doesn't make sense. And if we was
talking about a man, no one would be be saying that. So,
so I don't know how he got bummed up
when he got proven wrong, but God knows.
But I also got people agree with me as
well. I got six people agree with me.
So, six genuine people is is better than
14 15 biased people that didn't watch the video.
I had uh yeah, I had a few people grieve
me, even people that's got no um
but yeah, it's annoying. I had this
conversation with with my mom yesterday
as yesterday as well and I said, "Can
you please stop bringing it up cuz it's
starting to annoy me cuz every single
time you're shown different or told
different, you you you just shake your
head. So, is there a point of this whole
argument? You're always going to clearly
keep defending women, which is weird cuz
Ant-Man's mom understood. But my mom
don't. But I've been through more [ __ ]
than he has.
This is what I don't understand. I've
been through more [ __ ] than he has. He
will ever go through it. Yet, my mom
doesn't understand. How does that make any sense?
They just dismiss it. And it gets very
very annoying. You know,
dumb can people actually be?
Like if you're having an argument and
you don't believe something,
that's very very very very rare. That's
very very thing. But if you're being
shown differently, I don't understand
how you can argue with what you're being
shown. This is what I'm not
understanding. I'm I'm You're dismissing
things that you are being shown. Whereas
in a in a courtroom, you that's what
gets people convicted of [ __ ] This is
this is what I'm I'm I'm struggling to understand.
Why are people dismissing things when
they're being shown different? So, just
[ __ ] them in it. Let them keep doing that.
No, she brought up something yesterday.
Oh, didn't you have a woman going on a
wild goose chase? I said, yes, I did.
because she was being passive
aggressive. She was being a [ __ ] and
there was a reason for it. And no matter
how many times I would explain this to
her, it's in one ear and out the other.
And I'm raising my voice now and it's
starting to annoy me, you know? So, it's
no matter what you show them, they're
just going to keep defending women. So,
is is there a point in any of it?
It's like Ricky Millington's comment.
How can that got thumbs up when the
videos are showing that he is wrong?
It's not up for debate.
There was clear as day women that have
have as has as has has agreed to mate
that agreed to meet. There was people
that didn't reply to the first message.
So what? I was wrong on every single
message. Really, bro. See, they're
[ __ ] idiots, man. They're idiots.
There's no getting through to these
people, bro. You could show them a woman
killing a baby, bro, and they'd be like,
"Well, the baby deserved it. he had a bad personality.
That's literally what they would say.
Like honestly, that is literally what
they would [ __ ] say. You You can't
get through to these people. I mean, I
put approaching videos up there. I've
got a channel putting my approaching
videos up there, another channel, but I
thought, let me put it on this channel
um to see
to see what Ricky's response would be.
Okay, let me show you the approaching
videos. I haven't heard from him. I
haven't heard from him all day.
Even though I've just woke up. I mean,
where was he gone?
He He says that I'm my I'm boring and
I'm repeating and I'm talking rubbish.
Yeah, he will go on a boring repeating
channel talking rubbish.
So what, bro?
Yeah. Yeah. But what? Yeah. Basically,
but don't forget a year and a half ago,
I quote, "TJ, you are good-looking. It's
the women that are picky.
So what changes in two years? So you
said that you get women. So what two
years ago you didn't get women and now
now you get women. Is that what you're
saying? Cuz I don't understand. A year
and a half, two years ago, you were
saying about women being too picky and
that was the problem. Which is the
problem. Let's face it. But then now
you're saying that
now you're saying that it's me. So is it
me or is it the women? Which one is it?
Right. stick heads or tails which side
of the coin are you?
What has changed in two years?
Like how I mean and then he was saying
that me loving the messages was
was uh was cringe. So he was but they
were loving my messages. Contradicted yourself.
And I don't think I'm right on every
single one. Like I said, if I was to
give an unbiased opinion and I watched
that video, right, completely unbiased,
I would have said that the ones that
didn't reply to you, you might have said
something wrong. You might have acted
weird, whatever. The ones that didn't
reply to you and maybe don't ask, don't
double text, but there's no way you
could have been miss dismissed the
amount of women that was leading me on,
which is what everyone seems to have
done. that thumbs up that commented. The
the comment that contradicted itself,
the very same comment that contradicted
itself got thumbs up. But we know that
they're all biased because somebody
that commented doesn't know me, haven't
seen him for years, doesn't like me. And
he even agreed and he got three thumbs
up for including me. So three that
wasn't me and himself. That's four
people. So, the fact that you even got
anyone, you know, saying, "Oh, yeah,
okay, this is [ __ ] up." It goes to
show, bro. It goes to show. Um,
I I I promise you if I went out on the
street and I showed these conversations,
it would be a very very different
opinion, you know?
And then I say, "Okay, we'll give you a
W and it's the way I'm acting." Okay,
what about these approaches then?
And I and I had to put the dating app
[ __ ] there as well because she's going
to say go on dating apps.
I was speaking to a woman on Reddit
today and uh listen to this grievy. She
said go on dating apps. Showed her my
dating app experience and never heard
from her again.
Bit rude is it? She seemed to have run away.
She seemed to have run away never to be
seen again. start to get a bit worried, you know,
I need to go to and make this day.
Yeah, but you you must be um new to the channel.
You must be new to your channel, lads.
I don't know why they do. They say it's
a hookup culture.
>> Do they say?
So they say you I don't know where
you've come from. I thought you was
fake, but you are from London like me.
Yeah. I don't know. Yeah. I've been
trying for years, bro. I don't know how
you come across me, but Yeah. I've been
trying for [ __ ] years, bro. And it's
it's just been
[ __ ] There's [ __ ] pee in the [ __ ] d.
I told you you didn't believe me.
These are just like I said, these are
about 1% of my coaches. I've only you know
trying to say that it's the way I'm
acting. What about the ones that said
they weren't interested straight away?
What about the ones that pretend they
had a boyfriend?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I put the link up,
bro. Watch it. One sec. Hold on. Hold
on. Hold on.
Yeah, they just did it.
And then we're going to [ __ ] get text
in the [ __ ] dick. Madness.
I was live. I was one second before I
put the link up, bro. I was live earlier
when he was on Bonnies
and these people and they continuously
kept making up excuses
even though they got shown black and
white [ __ ] evidence. It's it's it's
One second. I'll put the link out there. us. Oh [ __ ] [Music] Oh.
Got loads of people here.
I got a te.
I left you alone if I'm quiet.
I'm starting to get [ __ ] worried
about you, mate. Hello. >> Yo,
>> how you doing, man? You good?
>> Yes. Yeah, man. It's easier. It's easier
just to talk on here, is it? You didn't
want to put the link out yesterday, did you?
>> Yeah. Thought he was some I didn't know
he was real, was it? I didn't know he was legit.
>> Yeah. No, all I was going to say was
Yeah. This long typing it. You know this
Ricky guy? Yeah. He [ __ ] He's saying
that um he's saying that you've done
this this you know that Ricky guy. Yeah.
>> Yeah. He's saying that you've done this
wrong, you've done that wrong about the
love arts and the comments and that. So,
okay then. Yeah. What I don't get is
what about the other [ __ ] what about
the other 30 videos of you trying
different approaches then? What are you
doing it wrong in every single one of them?
>> That's what I'm saying, bro. That's what
I'm saying. That's exactly
>> he's contradicting himself, bro. It
ain't making sense.
>> He's also contradicting himself when
he's saying about me loving their
messages when they've loved my messages.
Yet, he got 14 thumbs up.
>> Is that how many got now? 14.
>> Maybe more than that. But how can that
be right when there's different
messages? That's what I don't get.
>> Yeah, that's it's [ __ ] It's so people
if people are liking that, they
obviously haven't watched the videos.
>> That's what I said. They they clearly
haven't watched the videos. They could
cuz bro, there's an account, right?
Yeah. You know that Tiger account, he's
been on here years and he doesn't like
me. He's got a yes, man. And bro, he
even he agreed to it. Even Oh, I see
what you mean. Like, what the [ __ ] And
he got three thumbs up. So that's four
people minimum agreeing. So I'll take
four people over 40 people that ain't
watch the video, bro.
>> Who even is he? Who is he, Ricky? So
I've never heard of him.
>> Oh, he's been on here for ages. But the
the funniest thing is, yeah, a year and
a half ago, he was saying to me about
how women are too picky and I'm
good-looking. So which one is it? I
don't understand. Are you Is it them or
is it me? Make Make it make sense, you know?
And you know like what I was saying to
you yesterday. Yeah. You know like when
you come out of the you know when you
come out London Bridge station you know
like where the McDonald's is. Yeah.
You've gone there have you looking fresh
and that like approaching.
>> Bro I've been everywhere. I've been I've
been all over the country. I've been all
over London. Like I'm from London like you.
>> Yeah. And you said you've started in the
morning and done it like till late.
>> I've done it all. Yeah. Bro I used to
literally Bro, you're not going to
believe this. Like I used to go out from
like 9. Yeah. and come back alive at 11
at night, bro. God,
>> one still get the same thing. I've got a boyfriend.
>> It was similar stuff. Yeah, it was it's
always this, right? You either you try
to speak to someone and it's either I
have a boyfriend, I'm not interested,
they don't reply, they don't they ignore
you or like they'll give you their
number and then they'll just start
playing games and [ __ ] It's always
>> Did they ever say they got you?
>> Yeah, but not really. But it doesn't
happen yet. It's not that.
>> But I have got it. Yeah, I have got that before
>> obviously. But I would put that in it.
>> [ __ ] [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> What did you say in New York?
>> I said uh what part of London are you from? >> Louis.
Oh, I've never I've never been there,
you know, but heard about I think you're Ronford. >> Huh?
>> Are you in Romford? I think I see it
somewhere that you're in Romford. >> No.
>> So, I thought I see that on a [ __ ] on
a video. I've seen you on it for years.
I've just never found you. Never ever
found your channel.
>> I used to even I used to even shut it, didn't I?
>> I don't know. I've seen you on it for
years, but I've only like found your
channel the other day. I've seen you on
it loads of times like on Vinnie's on
Vinnies and that and Griff.
>> Yeah, man. So, what did you gamble on?
>> I did.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> I'm staying off. I'm staying off. I say
I did. I still do. I'm [ __ ] gambling.
That's how I first got involved in this
community. Is it?
>> Yeah. You must have seen me gamble then
it in the past.
>> Yeah. I've seen I've seen your I
remember seeing a video of you years ago
and you're like in the casino you got
[ __ ] bare money and that on you. I
remember that. Yeah, I used to dabble a
lot in it. Yeah.
>> I can't I can't this um you know like I
play roulette. I don't I hate slugs. I
play roulette. Yeah.
>> And I really miss I really miss like the
[ __ ] I hate this two pound you know
that [ __ ] spin bar thing.
>> I used to I used to love roulette bro.
>> Yeah. At least before at least like if
you lose you lose quick. Now doing that
spin back [ __ ] thing that makes me
just want to [ __ ] mental. I got
arrested for smashing the [ __ ] out of
the machine. I actually got nicked for that. Yeah.
I had to go with everything. I had to go
I had to go court with everything. I got
a fine and [ __ ] community uh community service.
>> I can't remember.
>> Yeah. One of my um someone I know,
right? They lost this was a few years
ago, right? They lost um I think it was
a thousand maybe a bit over a thousand,
bro. And um they they had a split and
they went back with a hammer and smashed
the [ __ ] machine and Yeah. They had
to go caught.
Yeah, I've only ever smashed the I've
only ever smashed the machine up in the boogie once.
>> I've I've done it. I've done it once,
but they they did catch me. How did they
catch you? Did they come to your house?
>> Uh, no. They knew I was It was my local one. >> Yeah.
>> And uh I got arrested. I got arrested
for about two weeks later or something.
They come and got me from my place and
then uh they went to court and I got a fine.
>> Yeah. Is it? Yeah.
>> Madness, bro. Madness.
>> I bet they probably got my address cuz
um like one of my old self exclusion
letters from that book. They probably
got it from that.
>> Yeah, I've smashed one before. I
remember before, bro. I swear to God. Um
it was when I was younger, like I was
like 20. I lost um
I lost 50 pound, bro. Bear in mind like
I didn't have as much money back then. I
went back. Yeah. You know, I had like a
weight dumbbell bar and I put I put the
window in, didn't it? Like, you know,
the big like the big window. It didn't
go through, but it cracked it. >> Yeah.
>> But what's so weird is that I I went to
that bookies like a year later and they
didn't say anything.
>> I don't know why I even [ __ ] bother
PJ. Yeah. I don't know why I bother
because no matter how much I win, Yeah.
I'm still going to lose because even if
it takes a [ __ ] everyday betting for
seven days, at some point that money is
going to go back. I'm a gambler. So,
what's the point? There's no point.
>> The last time, bro, the last time I
gambled was um a month ago. I put £100
in and I got it to five something and I
just stopped cuz I used to gamble a lot,
bro. But with me, yeah, I didn't used to
I used to hate the mood swings. I used
to go mad, bro. And it just wasn't
wasn't worth it. Even if I lost the
money and I could afford it, I didn't
like losing, bro. So, just stopped doing it. >> Yeah.
>> I hate losing, bro. Hate it. Losing mood
swings. I just can't be dealing with all that.
>> The last the last few big losses I've
had has been in the Admiral Casino [ __ ] place. >> Yeah.
>> You know the one I mean it's open right?
>> Of course, bro. Of course.
>> South the one in South Bury. You know Bernie?
>> Yeah, I know Burmany. Yeah. Souththeast
it. Yeah. Yeah. That's where I lost last time.
>> You ever been sorry Keys?
>> Yeah. Loads of times.
>> Yeah. There's a little Weather Spoon in
the corner in it. Yeah, right next to Tesco.
>> Yeah, you know it.
>> I was in there. I was in that weather
stone about [ __ ] my mate just next to
me football stadium. I was in there
about 3 weeks ago.
>> Yeah, it's not it's not expensive, is it?
>> No, it's cheap bit of [ __ ]
>> When you go central and that's another
thing, bro, when when I when you go
central Yeah. Try with these women, bro.
It's like seven eight seven eight pound
a pint, bro.
>> Bro, have you been in somewhere called
Burger Lobster? That's so expensive.
>> Yeah, I've been there once. Yep. Yeah. I
used to go to different restaurants.
I've been Steak and Co. And this T-Bone
Burger Lobster. Oh, yeah. Bro. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> It's nice. It is nice. But it's [ __ ] well.
>> Yeah. I used to try different um I used
to go out approaching bro and then at
the end I just get a T-Bone steak in it. >> Yeah.
>> But it's [ __ ] isn't it? It's [ __ ]
up this whole women thing though, isn't it?
>> That is [ __ ] up. When I watched your
video, all them all them screenshots,
bro. You've got the worst luck in the
world. I swear. Like [ __ ] What is the
odds on that?
>> But they're leading you on as well
though. That's the thing, isn't it?
That's the like obviously in it.
>> I read one of them. Yeah, I read it. But
I was like I was so stunned. Yeah.
Falling asleep. I still read it. And
then like the bird she's like on it and
that and then she just then she you say
to her, "All right, what time then?"
then then nothing. Then you put a
question mark nothing. And then she just
blows you out. You know the one you
going to meet at Tottenham called Road
Station. Oh, she's a [ __ ] doing that to you both.
>> Yeah. And there was one as well, maybe I
didn't put that one up there, she was
supposed to meet me and then a couple of
hours before she says, "Oh, I'm going to
try with my ex." I mean, somebody was
coming on here, right, saying about how
they change their mind. How can you
change your mind that quickly?
>> No, she just chatting [ __ ] bro.
>> That's what I'm saying, bro. But you'll
get people that make excuses like, "Oh,
they're ch What?" So, all of these
people that have agreed to me have
changed their mind.
>> That doesn't even make sense, is it?
>> They just change [ __ ]
>> Yeah, of course, bro. Of course.
See the one see like I said to you the
ones that don't reply people can say oh
like you acted weird or you might have
they didn't like that that leaves
excuses that leaves room for excuses but
when they reply and they agree to meet
you there's no getting out of that you
know what I mean
>> see with me with that approaching I
don't do that personally but
>> [ __ ] know the amount of time money
effort and dedication you've put into
that and then it's just gone dead I can
see why you're so frustrated like
>> now if I was you if I went out now
approaching first two or people that
said no. I'll end up just saying I'll
[ __ ] off and going home when you get drunk.
>> Yeah, I know, bro. I know. Like I think
I generally think I've tried more than
anyone in the world as well, bro. I
generally like I know that sounds
delusional, bro, but I have, bro. Seriously. >> Yeah.
>> Obviously, there's people that approach
a lot as well, but it' be hard to
because I've been I don't know about
you. Have you traveled the country? I've
been like all over, bro. All over.
Actually, I've not even been that many places.
>> You been abroad though, is it?
Yeah. I said to you yesterday, why don't
you try some trampy shitto area? You
said you tried that in it.
>> Which one?
>> I said to you yesterday, try some like
disgusting trampy [ __ ] area. And you
said you've done that.
>> I've been to like Newcastle and stuff
like that. I've been like different
places and stuff, but it was amazing.
>> It's a [ __ ] [ __ ] hole. You still get
some nice birds there, but you tried
that already. You
>> Well, yeah. I've been New I've been
Yeah. Yeah. I've been Maiden Head. I've
been like places and [ __ ] like that. You
ever been Manchester? No, I've never
been there. You've been there yet?
>> 10 times, bro?
>> Actually, yeah. Know, I see some of the
numbers in brackets next to it.
Manchester in it.
>> Yeah, bro. Yeah, from Yeah, that's
that's they're old ones, bro. Yeah. So,
you must have Yeah, you have been
watching a long time then, is it?
>> Yeah, I've seen I've seen you on it for
years, but I haven't just subbed to you
the other day.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
I see some I told you yesterday I see
some videos some [ __ ] like [ __ ]
fat guy with a glasses saying like
better [ __ ] about you, bro. >> Yeah,
>> it's some brazer. I tell you yesterday
it's called fruit. Yeah. Yeah, I know
him, bro. He's been on here years. He's
a [ __ ] idiot.
>> Yeah, I see him for years. Just
yesterday I searched PJ watching like
your old videos approaching and that and
then I see come up with an old video of
him from three years ago and he's like
calling you a nonstop.
>> Yeah, he's a [ __ ] bro. He's a
[ __ ] How old are you?
>> He's the Dy one. He keeps going. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, I know what you mean. I'm 30.
>> Oh, okay then. Not much older than me
>> And that other one. Yeah. We was talking
about yesterday. That one you put the
picture up of. 32. Yeah.
>> [ __ ] hell. She's um what? She got her
head up on her ass or something. She's
like when it comes to like going to poor
bird. I don't know about you, but 32.
That's when old for a girl in it. You
know what I mean?
>> Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. She must. But
no. No. But the thing is the thing is
she didn't have a stuck up vibe cuz she
was from like the north in it. >> Um
>> she was from like um Newcastle. So she
didn't have that stuck up vibe. So I met
her right and then like yeah like within
20 minutes I like we had like a few
drinks and stuff and I was like oh like
let's meet again in it and then she oh I
don't feel the vibe. I was like what do
you mean you don't feel the vibe? Like
you're 32 you've got a lower SMB than me
and you're trying to act like you're
better than me bro. Like you they
they've hit the wall at that age. You
know what I mean?
It's just I can't. And the picture of
her as well, like she's not even like
she's not even a weapon. Like she's
[ __ ] she's about three, four, five at
best out of 10.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And then at the end of the day,
>> PJ, she just hit you like that. Like,
I'm not feeling this. Bang. That was it.
>> Say again, bro.
>> She literally just hit you with it like
that. She just said, "I'm not feeling
it." That's it. Done.
>> Within like 30 minutes. Yeah. But what's
so weird is she approached me. She was
trying to tell me how I'm good-looking.
And I'm thinking, but that's another
thing. They give up at the first sign of
disappointment. Like, you don't know
whether you like someone or not that
quickly, bro. Come on.
>> You know,
it's [ __ ] up.
>> It is [ __ ] up. It [ __ ] is [ __ ] up
to be honest. >> Yeah.
What What other choice do I have, bro?
>> I know someone I know someone who went
there. Yeah. And he had two ts. Yeah.
proper proper bit at all. Yeah. He had
them all week. Yeah. Seven days
massaging him, cooking for him, sucking
his dick, [ __ ] whatever he wanted.
And when he paid him like when he when
he worked out the equivalent what it be
now, money like it was [ __ ] cheap, man.
>> Yeah, that's true.
>> As you know, have you have you have you
ever done an escort?
>> Yeah, loads of them.
>> Yeah, I've done them so many times.
>> I always end up doing them when I'm like
[ __ ] packing out my head and I end up
in a hotel.
>> What I do What I do, bro, is I I get
drunk. Yeah. Nobody. And then at the end
of the night, let's go. That's cool.
>> When they come and they try and kill 20
minutes by talking, I always just say,
"Come on, let's crack on." You pay 160
and that like you could tell they don't
want to be there. Some of them are
disgusting. Like just they just wait.
>> But some sometimes you will get ones
that are really nice. It's It's
>> rare. Loads and loads of them. >> Huh?
>> I had loads of arguments with them and
the driver sitting outside as well. Bro,
you heard about the last time I went and
she said she was going to swallow in it?
>> No, just just come in her mouth, bro.
Like that's I don't need them to
swallow. I'm just a lot of these will
say, "Yeah, we'll give you a [ __ ]
right?" But you can't finish like in her
mouth. So, what are you going to do?
Finish yourself off?
>> Yeah, you paid extra for that, didn't you?
>> Yeah, I paid her extra and he agreed and
I said, "Like, if you don't give off the
money, I'm going to do the windows in,
bro." Simple. Like, don't take the piss
out of me. You know what I Was that an
Was that an incor one then?
>> No, it's basically, you know, um in
Stratford like where I used to live,
there's like a house I know that I just
go to. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So that's an in one. You go
there, they don't come after you. You go there. >> Yeah.
>> They they normally they normally have a
fella there like looking after him. The girls.
>> Yeah, they do. Yeah. And he and he and
he coming. I said I said to the guy,
"Get out of my [ __ ] face." That's
what I said to him as well.
>> Get out of my face. If you're not going
to give half the money back, I'm going
to do your windows in. like we agreed to
it because think of it bro okay if you
get a [ __ ] yeah and you don't come in
their mouth it's like £70 right whereas
if you pay 100 it's like it's always 30
extra if they agreed to it so that was
what the £100 was for we that's what we agreed on
>> well I bet she was making out I bet she
was making out she couldn't speak English afterwards
>> no I don't think so she was just trying
to say that [ __ ] that that that
wasn't agreement what it Yeah,
>> but I had this I had this um Chinese
school and she was licking my ass in
that, bro. She always texts me to this
day. She still texts me.
>> Well, she was tonging your ass in that.
>> Yeah, she's lucky I had a bath, bro,
before going there. You know that.
>> Imagine imagine if you just been in
McDonald's for a [ __ ] or something.
>> That's what I'm saying. Yeah, that's
what I'm saying. She got lucky, mate.
>> So, you ever been Amsterdam?
>> I haven't. I do want to go.
>> Yeah, I went there. Did you do you
remember when I went there?
>> I don't I didn't see none of that. Did
you do any brasses there?
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah, I was there for three days.
>> Expensive there. Expensive there.
>> Yeah, it is to be fair. >> Yeah.
>> Do you reckon if I've been to Belgium?
Yeah. But do you reckon if I was in
Belgium and I tried the dating game
there, do you reckon I would have had more success? Like guess
Look, he's gone.
Taking a baby away from its mama.
taking aboption away from its mama
away from its mama. Hey, bro.
>> Sorry, bro. I didn't mean to do that.
>> Yeah, I was saying that if I was in
Belgium um trying to date, do you reckon
I'd have more success?
>> I don't know. I don't really know
anything about Belgium. Why do you want
to go Belgium?
>> I've already been to Belgium. No, but
I'm just No, no, I'm just saying because
it's like I feel like Yeah, because I
don't look fully white. Yeah, cuz I'm
not like I'm Turkish. That might be the
reason I'm no one's type in this
country. So if I went somewhere else,
I'm not saying it would be easy, but I'm
saying if I if I was like if I tried as
much as I did here in another country, I
think I would like I don't know more
success. [ __ ] knows.
>> Yeah, it seems like here for you is just
[ __ ] [ __ ] But do you know what?
Yeah. Like you know when you're out and
about approaching, do you never look at
like do you ever see a couple walking
towards you? Yeah. And you look and the
birds are right and you look at him and
he's like a fat ugly disgusting [ __ ]
And you think
and and the worst thing is And the worst
thing is there then you will see a
decent looking guy with a [ __ ] ugly
woman. Bro, that's the worst. I went I went cinema.
>> It was a second um it was the second
last time I went to cinema cuz I I love
going cinema is it when a horror film
comes out, right? And I see this bit um
woman with this guy. He wasn't fat and
ugly but he was like he had like
glasses. But then you see all the decent
looking guys with these fat ugly women, bro.
>> I know. That's so [ __ ] up.
>> It's madness.
It is a madness, bro. It is. Do you know
the worst is when the person looks
similar to you as well? That's the
worst. But bro, PJ, you need to try try
Have you tried things like this? Like,
have you tried and sound stupid? Have
you tried other approaching all day, but
every time every time you go, try
different targets? Like, have a day of
doing women that are older. Have a day
of milks and then the next day go for
the fatties. Have you tried that?
>> No. I I mean I have I've approached all
different kinds of people. I mean one
one one thing I haven't tried there is
like approaching people with like only
darker skin like me like not black but
like you know Mediterranean.
>> Have you not tried it? Have you tried any milks?
>> Yeah, bro. Bro, listen listen. If you
approach a woman, this is you're going
to laugh at this, bro. Whenever you
approach a woman that's older than you,
the excuse is always going to be that
you're too young for me, bro. That that
happens all the time, bro.
But then when you when they say that
Yeah. Don't get angry if you ever just
laughed it off and said, "Trust me, I'm
very mature with my age if you're trying."
>> Of course. Of course I have. Yeah,
obviously, bro. Of of course. Yeah.
>> You said like age is a number. Don't
bother me if you're older than me and
all stuff like that.
>> Yeah, obviously.
I thought you I thought you was taking I
thought you was taking the piss
yesterday. Is it because you hadn't come
to the live stream when you were saying
that it was being serious cuz uh I don't
>> How many How many people have you approached?
Oh, I don't I don't really I don't really approach.
>> Oh, you've done it when you were
drinking, didn't it?
>> Yeah. When I'm when I'm when I'm so When
I'm pissed up, I do.
>> What? Um, what did what did they say?
>> I'm I'm a dirty. I'll [ __ ] I'll do anything.
>> What did they say?
>> I don't like it. Obviously, obviously of
legal age, but I mean I' do anything. I don't care.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> So, what do you think of the whole Monty
thing? His life got ruined, didn't it?
>> Say again when we broke up.
>> What What do you think of the whole
Monty man situation? His life got
ruined, didn't it?
>> He's not He's not with um He's not with
the net no more, is he? >> No,
>> they split up, isn't it?
>> Yeah. So, have you seen like some of the
women that I've been with and been on
dates with? And you obviously have it.
>> I see um I see one of them on the video
sitting in like the garden live
restaurant. She's talking and she looks
quite fit. I see there was another one.
She was [ __ ] disgusting though. You
got a video of kissing her. That made me laugh. Funny.
>> Do you remember the American one? She was like
>> Do you know Do you want know what the
funniest thing is? You know that ugly one? Yeah.
>> When you put the video up Yeah. There
was like 30 I think it was riffrats
posted it and you someone said she's
disgusting ugly [ __ ] and you you
commented to that comment. All you wrote
was lol. That made me laugh.
Yeah. But do you remember the American?
>> I heard that American girl was a weapon. >> Huh?
>> I heard that this American girl was fit.
>> No, she she Bro, she was like a four out
of 10. She was a proper [ __ ] bro. Prop.
>> Someone said she was whose chat was in.
>> Oh, she's like average, but bro, she was
a proper [ __ ] bro. You remember? What
did you think of that situation? It was
[ __ ] isn't it? >> Yeah.
What one are you on about?
>> The one the the American one that [ __ ]
me over. Is it?
>> Oh, I don't know what happened with I'm
on about one. What happened with the American?
>> You don't know what happened?
>> No, tell me.
>> You really, bro? So, the one I met
outside Eminem shop.
>> Can I just say one thing quickly? >> Yeah.
>> You want to know? Do you want to know
what made me sub to you? You funny [ __ ] >> What?
>> I knew I'd like you. Yeah. As soon as I
found a video of you about it, it's only
about a week ago. I can't I don't I know
you don't want to talk about it. I was
trying to get you to say you know the
[ __ ] the Brixton thing. You're funny
counting that video.
>> Oh yeah. Yeah. Oh. Oh yeah. Bro,
>> I'll explain. I'll explain it. Yeah,
I'll explain that one. Yeah.
>> Do you know how many times I Do you know
how many times I rewound that? It's the
way you say it so casually. You funny,
>> bro. It's what happened as well. It was
a guy like when he when he tried like
beating me up in April. I was trying to
steal his bike.
>> When he when he actually caught you was trousers now. Um
I was getting up. I think I might have
been getting up. No, no,
>> you should have said he was having a
[ __ ] or something.
>> Yeah. And he and his and his friend was
like pulling him away from me. I was
like, I'm not trying to I'm trying to
steal his bike, bro. I swear to God.
>> Did you say to him, "I don't give a [ __ ]
about your bike."
>> Yeah. I just said, "Yeah, I wasn't
trying to steal your bike." And that is
it. That's what I just said. But no,
this No, this American, she was a [ __ ] bro.
>> That made me laugh. Another funny video
I'll see of you is the one where you're
walking. It's not funny. It's sad. It's
the way it's the way you react when
you're walking along and someone that
ger gets hit by the car. Your reaction
is so funny.
>> Oh, but I still remember that the smell
of that blood to this day, bro. It smell
like raw beer.
>> You casually you just so casually go,
"Fuck, he's [ __ ] dead, bro."
>> I I was in shock, man. What the [ __ ]
I'm live streaming. I see this get
[ __ ] hit and he's gone flying.
>> I can't see him in the video get hit,
but you hear it in it. Yeah, bro. It's horrible. Horrible.
>> I wonder if he died
>> probably. I know. I know. He went into a coma
>> and I thought, "No, this is sad. I
shouldn't be laughing." And then at the
end of the video, at the end of the
video, you say to the guy, "What do you
mean, bro? He's over there dead. You
just [ __ ] killed him, bro." And I
burst out laughing again.
>> He must have been drunk and he's tried
crossing the road and just got hit.
>> Yeah. Where else was that? I was trying
to work out where he was.
>> You know, you know, Rockford Road. >> Yeah.
>> Um Yeah. There
>> is that is that where it was?
>> Yeah, like behind the Morrison sort of thing.
>> Yeah, [ __ ]
>> Oh, do you know about Rompin Road?
>> I do loads of times. Oh, yeah. Go ahead.
Sorry to interrupt you. What was you
saying? The Eminem shop. What one you on
about? The one near um Chinatown.
>> Yeah, the one that that that America I approached.
>> Yeah, you on about the Eminem shop near
Chinatown, is it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. What happened with her then?
>> No, I was just I've got a video as well.
Yeah. Okay. So all right. So I was chat
I was chatting to her. Yeah. Bear in
mind this is the first this is the first
time I bought a Stone Island. First time
wearing it. Yeah. So I've got my fresh
gums in it. So I started talking to her
and she said to me, "Yeah, do you do you
want my number?" She offered me her
number. And bear in mind I've approached
so many people before that. Yeah. And
after and no one's ever ever said it
again. So I was like, "Okay, yeah, okay,
whatever." So then they then they've
text me, this was Thursday. Then they
they've text me the next day saying um
oh let's meet up on Tuesday which was
the first message which is also double
standards because if you try and meet a
woman they say use as excuse but anyway
she wanted to meet Tuesday but before
the Tuesday she was proper love bombing
me saying oh yeah come see me um in
America you're cute like proper like
love bombing bro I still got like the
messages if you want to see them. So
then I've met her on a Tuesday, right?
We've gone for a meal. I paid for it.
We've we've hooked up. Yeah. Then she's
gone back to America and then she
blocked me. I got I said to my friend,
"Oh, can you message me? I see why she
blocked me." Started making up stories
saying I grabbed her and all. It was
like a different person, bro. And I was
like, "Fuck this." I tried messaging
her. I said, "What's what's your
problem? Why are you lying in it?" And
then she was being a [ __ ] I started
messaging her family and that, bro. She
was pissing me off. I swear to God, bro. Huh?
>> She went back to
>> She did, bro. She lived there.
>> Well, she actually did.
>> Yes. Yes, she did 100%.
>> So, I'm confused. Say that again. She
approached you outside the M&M.
>> I approached her. Okay. No, I approached
her, right? And we was talking approach
with her. She offered me her number. So,
she was a tourist. This was the first
day. So, I got her number and we was
talking. He said, "Oh, do you want to?"
She She text me the next day, said, "Do
you want to meet up Tuesday next week?"
I said, "Okay." So, we was texting till
then. We was texting till then and she
was like, "Oh, you're cute. Come and see
me like love bombing me and stuff in
it." like trying to make out that I'm
her exact type. And then when we met on
the Tuesday, we went for a meal. I paid
for it. Like we hooked up and then when
she went back to America, she blocked me
and I said to my friend, I like, "Can
you messaged her to see what's going
on?" You making up stories. I grabbed
her this, that, and the other. And I
messaged her saying, "What's your
[ __ ] problem? Why are you lying?" And
then Yeah. She started being a [ __ ] and
started messaging her family and that,
bro. Literally. Yeah.
>> You got [ __ ] over there.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And I was, bro, literally,
you know, I I actually booked to to go
to America the first time. I was going
to I was going to stick it on her, bro.
I swear to God, bro. It was only because
I was like meeting someone at the time
that's like, "Don't go. Don't go." They
were like begging me not to go, bro. I
was I was going to go, bro. I swear to
God, I was going to go.
>> What made her turn on you?
>> I don't know. I don't know. Because if
if there was a problem, you could have,
bro, you had my number. You could have
said something. What the [ __ ]
>> Why did you How did you leave it with
her when you went on a date? Like at the
end of the date, was everything all right?
>> Yeah. Well, we hooked up in her
apartment and then we I just we just
hugged and kissed. I just said, "Oh, get
home safe. Text me when you get back."
And it like,
>> "Did you smack it or not?"
>> She said, "Yeah." And she she said,
"Text me when you get back home." I text
her when I got back home and she said,
"I had a great night. Love." That that's
that was it.
>> Did you? >> Yeah.
>> You say you did better. So why what I'm so confused?
>> That's what I don't understand. That's
why I You know what? If there's a
problem, people should communicate. You
know what I mean? Yeah,
it put me off, bro, for like two years.
Like, proper. Like, it was bad. It was
so bad, bro, that like when I'd get
drunk and I'd get dates, like this was
before like it got a lot harder. I'd end
up talking about it, bro. Like, to be I
swear to God when I was drunk. Yeah,
>> it was [ __ ] up, bro. It was horrible.
It was horrible. It was horrible.
>> Who is that in the background?
>> Oh, this this stupid weirdo, bro.
[ __ ] But yeah, just some idiot, bro. But yeah.
Um, yeah. So that it was [ __ ] up for
like two years, bro. Is it?
>> Yeah. That's like I don't know.
>> She She was like average. Like a little
below average. You know what I'm saying?
And And her ego, bro. Her ego is mad.
>> I don't I don't What? What made her turn
on you like that?
>> I don't know. I don't know. We we we we
we assume that maybe she was like
cheating or something and she wanted to
or she just wanted to forget that she
had the one night stand and just like
just go back home and just live her
life. You know what I'm saying? I don't know.
>> I was just going to say I got a feeling
like maybe when she was back home I bet
it might have been her boyfriend
messaging her from her phone or something.
>> It was just weird, isn't it? It was just
weird. Have you got a picture? I put put
your profile picture as on
>> obviously it's highly um
filtered but yeah there
obviously she uses
>> put yourself on big screen.
>> I I can't do that anymore bro on this
phone. I don't know why it doesn't let
me. What do you mean? She's a three out
of 10, bro. She's [ __ ] hot.
>> Yeah, but she's with filters, isn't it?
>> Is it one of them ones and you meet her
and she's [ __ ] disgusting.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Obviously, I didn't have anything else,
so I was like, "Fuck it in it." Like,
what am I going to do?
>> People I know personally, the pictures
that they've got online compared to who
they are in real life looks like two
different people. I swear.
>> Yeah. 100, bro. 100.
>> But um do you reckon you can approach Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> I just uh obviously when I'm pissed I
have more confidence doing London [ __ ] though.
>> You like Guinness?
>> Yeah. I love it.
>> I love Guinness, bro. I ain't drunk for
like a month.
>> That was in Chinatown. I'm just talking
about yesterday. I go there all the time,
>> bro. I used to go there twice a week,
bro. I r that place.
>> Stop going to Chinatown because I just
end up losing loads of money there.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Happens. Oh, bro. Listen.
Yeah. You know when I um when I um went
to that China uh the O'Neals, I went
there about 40 times before I realized
there was a third floor.
>> I swear to God, bro, I didn't know that until ages.
>> I didn't know there was a third floor anymore. >> Huh?
>> I didn't know there was a third floor.
>> Yeah, there's Yeah, there's a bottom one
and the first one and there's a third
one. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Have you seen that bird who works on the bar downstairs?
>> Bro, there's so many. The staff change
all the time.
>> Lovely. Yeah.
>> When was you last there?
>> Probably about four or five months ago.
>> A while ago then. Yeah.
>> Well, bro, if you ever want to meet up,
you know, just we'll go to like waxies or something. >> Yeah.
>> You know?
>> Yeah. We'll go for a Guinness. I don't
mind, bro. Like, we both live in London
in it. And meet like in the middle. I
don't mind. We'll just get on it, bro.
And why not? It's my birthday. Um on the 27th.
>> Yeah. When are you going to F? Are you
actually going or was that joke?
>> No, I'm actually going, bro. Yeah,
>> next month.
>> Yeah, but we'll go for a drink in it.
You know what I love though, bro? Like,
I love like a nice central London
Weather Spoons. You just can't beat it,
bro, for like a nice spoons. You know
what I mean?
>> They're cheap as well, on it.
>> Yeah. And it's I don't know. It's just I
prefer that vibe, but
He sounds a bit like He reminds me of
Rocky Roid. This guy reminds me of Rocky
a little bit.
What the [ __ ] is them fireworks about, man?
Yeah, I love that O'Neals. I love that
[ __ ] O'Neals, bro.
Is that you trying to join, bro? Yep.
Is that you? I don't think that is him.
That guy seems cool, man.
I don't mind, bro. I'll meet him for a
beer, but drink anymore.
Yeah, I love that [ __ ] O'Neal's
only his class. I'm surprised you've
never bloody seen me in there, bro.
I used to go there every no.
Yeah. Do you like my little approaches, Bob?
I'm [ __ ] badass, isn't it?
>> Thank you, boss.
>> Yeah, man. I'm surprised you've never
seen me in the [ __ ] O'Neal then.
>> Yeah, I've been there probably 10 times.
I think you've been there more times.
No, that weren't me a minute ago trying
to join. Who was it?
>> Hey, bro. What What days did you used to go?
>> Oh, I don't know. No days in particular.
>> You know, Thursdays are good. Thursdays
used to be good there. first. See, the
thing is with London, bro, if you've
ever been out on a like I prefer like a
Wednesday and a Thursday. I know it's
like people go out Saturday, but them
them days are are good.
>> I [ __ ] um I've eaten in the oatmeals as well.
>> Yeah, I've had like a burger to be fair.
>> The food's quite [ __ ] in there to be honest.
>> I find you get a lot
>> I norally get lunch at like a Weather
Spoons and just go on the Guinness to be fair.
>> Yeah, I find you get a lot of American
girls in O'Neals in China. Yeah,
especially on a Especially on a
Thursday, bro. If you got Bro, if you go
there on a Thursday, it's nothing but Americans, bro. >> Why?
>> Well, you won't like it because too many
of them, they give you a headache, bro.
You know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> Have you tried approaching any of the
Chinese girls or is that not your thing?
>> I don't really like Chinese, but to be
fair, they're nice people. You know,
Chinese, they are
>> nothing against them. I'm just not
attracted to them. You know what I mean?
>> But to be honest, but you know what's so
weird though? I'm not attracted to them,
but there has been ones that I have, if
that makes sense. Like, there's been
like a couple, even though I don't, but
there has been a couple.
>> That makes sense.
>> Um, but yeah. No, no, but they're nice
people though. Um, Chinese people, they
are nice to be fair. >> Yeah.
>> Our Chinese escort, she still messages
me. She's in Manchester. I met her in
like London, but she was um she was
nice. Really nice, bro.
>> Was she Manchester? Yeah, she's she's
working in Manchester now. >> Yeah.
>> Um but yeah.
>> What ended up happening with that one
where you had the [ __ ] drama with the Glo.
>> Oh, they just gave half the money back
in the end.
>> The money.
>> Yeah. Half the money in it because I I
just didn't she just I just didn't come
in her mouth in it. So I thought I could
give half my money back in it.
>> Yeah. Normally they'll try anything not
to give you the money back. I said, "If
you don't give it, I'm doing the windows
in." But and bro, I didn't give a [ __ ]
I didn't give a [ __ ] because you're not
going to take the piss out of me.
>> And after that, bro, I just didn't go
out again. I just couldn't be [ __ ]
Waste of money, waste of time. And only
one only one of them numbers reply back
out of them 10 numbers. And she said she
was going to meet me in Liverpool
Street. And she disappeared. >> Yeah.
>> I was thinking, "Okay, [ __ ] it. Okay. I
might have spent £500." Yeah. But I've
won, you know, the money back. We got
somebody that wants to meet. It is what
it is. But then they [ __ ] around
anyway, so [ __ ] that.
And the other time you went out, how the
[ __ ] did you spend 600 quid? I thought you meant
>> I don't know, bro. Cuz the thing is,
yeah, I don't gamble anymore. Like when
I say that, I mean I might gamble every
couple of months, but it's rare. Yeah.
It's like I stayed in a nice hotel and I
gambled because then I could see where
the money went.
>> Yeah, that's what I thought. I thought
you lost in the booking.
>> No, not at all at all. It was like It
might have been like 400 and then with
the gam like with the£100 gambling 500.
No, don't forget, bro. Cuz I got a
haircut. I got food. I drunk. So from
like month I think it's like from the
Friday cuz I went out the Friday to the
Monday I spent Yeah. like £500. Bro,
>> how many? You had two braes, didn't you?
>> No, one.
>> Oh, one. >> Yeah.
Well, the most I've ever spent on a
night out before was £700, but I was
staying I I paid for like a hotel and um
I was gambling, but obviously I won
money gambling, but it includes on the
night out. It's when I used to [ __ ] it.
>> How the [ __ ] did you spend How the [ __ ]
did you spend £600 on the other one?
>> [ __ ] knows, bro. Maybe it was500, but I
know it was hundreds. I knew it was hundreds, bro.
>> Where did you stay?
>> It just adds up. The [ __ ] just adds up
cuz don't forget when you get a haircut
and like when I go out because I don't
go out every week that once you get it
adds up, you know what I mean? Whereas
like say if I got my haircut like and I
went out the next week, maybe I'd spend
maybe 80 to 100. You know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> How much do you spend on a night out?
Hope he's gone again.
Yeah, that guy's cool, man. Oh,
you need to get [ __ ] laid. Steven
Howard, you like my approaches, Steven
Howard? I'm the approach king.
I was meant to ask this guy. Has he been to Fabrics?
I know. He needs to get laid.
That's what he needs to do. Get laid.
People are going mad, bro.
He's saying that I'm 30 and not a single
not been in a single relationship yet.
He can only get disabled women.
Madness, isn't it? He can only get
disabled and I've had chances to be in
relationships, more relationships than
you. And he's trying to say, "Oh, I
haven't known more women than him."
Well, yes, I have known more women than
you. I've met more women than you and
I've been with more women than you. So,
how have I not know more women than you?
Uh, yes I do.
Yes, I [ __ ] do know more women than
you, you skin virgin. Yes, I [ __ ] do Yeah.
It's my birthday soon. Yay.
What's a better number? the 16th or the 27th.
>> Who do you think's going to win on
Friday? Me or Monty? I will. I'm going
to beat him, bro. I'm going to 100% beat
him. I had to have a shower before I go
in bed, bro. I [ __ ] stunk, man. It was horrible. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I'll meet you, bro. Why not? Yeah, man.
I mean, at least he understands what I'm
saying about the [ __ ] women and stuff.
I mean, that's it.
Yeah. So, who do you agree with, Steven
Howard? Me or Ricky Millington? That guy
is a [ __ ] buffoon. He is.
He He's gone quiet since I've put the
[ __ ] messages up, is it?
We got really quiet. Yeah.
He is a mug, mate. He's a mug. But
apparently women's got unrealistic
standards. So he says,
he says they've got unrealistic standards.
These words, not mine.
Yeah, this virgin's obsessed with me.
This is what I mean, bro,
with this community. It's so weird.
Did you see my response to him?
Yeah, you can see my response to him.
I [ __ ] completely ko him. Yeah.
Oh, just someone I had a one night stand with.
Yeah, man. Yeah, that Hugh is a cool guy, man.
He reminds me of um Rocky. I don't know why.
Me, him, and Rocky riding all meet up.
But no, that skin virgin is definitely
obsessed with me.
He's definitely definitely obsessed with me.
Definitely definitely obsessed with me
and my sloppy seconds.
I can't believe he still goes on about
USA, is he? Obviously, I just said that
to that guy because I've said
experiences I've had.
He all his life is convincing himself
that everyone's a virgin like him.
That's pretty sad at 31, isn't it?
Having to convince yourself that
someone's a virgin like you.
Everything has to be a you and Britney situation.
He seems to think everything's a him and
Britney situation where he got rejected
and he got [ __ ] rejected.
It's mad, isn't it?
People are proper proper low lives.
And he's telling me about people who I
live with. Yeah. He's the one that lives
in a bedsuit with no bed and they ain't
got no teeth. I'd love to know why he's
got no teeth cuz it is it dental care is
free. So there's really no excuse for
it. You're going to sit there in your
[ __ ] shitty beds [ __ ] and try and
tell me that I need to sort my life out, mate.
Yeah, man. Sorry. I can't gamble
anymore, bro. It's for the best.
No, I can't do that [ __ ] no more, bro.
Yeah, he's a [ __ ] idiot.
Birding B skin in your little bed [ __ ]
with no bed, no money in it.
Why don't you do it anymore? Should I
have McDonald's again? Gre Yeah.
I don't know what I'm going to eat, bro.
What am I going to eat?
Yeah, I've got a couple of thousand.
I don't know what to eat.
Should I get a binderoo? Maybe
does go fast. Yeah, it does go fast.
It goes faster than the virgin boy.
Virgin boy getting in your bed [ __ ] with
old bed. No money in it.
I think the skin virgin needs to get laid.
I don't think he'll ever lose it. Me I I
generally don't think he's ever going to
pop that virginity, mate. What do you
think, Greer? You think he's going to pop it?
Huh? He ain't popping that, mate.
How you going to lose it? Huh?
in your little skin bed. Try and tell
people who they can and can't live with.
A [ __ ] 31 still on YouTube acting
like a keyboard warrior with no light.
Bro, should I rip into this [ __ ]
You want me to rip into this? You want
me to rip into this virgin [ __ ] on a video?
rip into this [ __ ]
Right, I'm going to order some food. One sec.
Going to have a What should I A vindaloo.
So have a vindaloo, mate.
That skin virgin can't handle a vindaloo, mate.
Is he skink?
He's a skint [ __ ] Yeah.
Keeping it. Yes.
When's my birthday, Grezy?
Taking a baby away from it mother.
Taking a baby away from it month.
This is a problem with a [ __ ] up
sleeping pattern. You eat at stupid times.
Taking a bait. Nope.
Taking a baby away from it. Mama
£17 vindaloo pillow rice chicken starter. Um
should I should I not? Um
yeah, why not? We're not skid virgin
like some people.
Yeah, we're not we're not skinned like
some people. So,
I know I'm not I'm not I'm not um
talking about you at all.
Yeah. Binderoo pillow rice chicken start.
Is £1,200 a good amount of money to have? Greasy. £1,200.
It is, isn't it?
Yeah. Grievy. I was I was trying to
sleep earlier. And my ass was [ __ ] stinking, son.
I was [ __ ] stinking.
So I was like, "No, mate.
I've got to have a [ __ ] I've got to
have a [ __ ] shower.
What about 1500?
How about 1500? How about 1600?
How about that? We've
Yeah, I've got a couple of grand.
I was very smart with the money in it.
You That's mad. I had that house for 4
years, is it? Grievy,
I had that house for four years.
That's mad, isn't it?
Yeah, for four years
didn't have to work or anything. We
got that paid for me going trotting
around the country speaking to women
loves King, don't you?
You love king.
So what's happening when I go um to
Birmingham on Friday? Grezy, huh?
I got to Birmingham on um Friday.
It's not going to be the same website
you can watch [ __ ] Dobby on, is it?
Or Harry Potter? Nah,
it's not, is it? Oh.
no. I'm going to slap him up. Monty
won't beat me, bro. Trust me, Monty will
not beat me.
Trust me, he won't beat me, bro.
I took Timmy and Tiger on. You know,
Steven Coward, you need stop being a narcissist.
You need to give the virgin boy advice
on how to get laid.
I don't know how you can be 31 acting
like this on YouTube every day. What a
sad low life.
You want me to rip into this [ __ ] really
badly, bro? Like I did Ricky Millington.
You know what's so addicting is they're
so thick and so low IQ
that it just it just gets addicting,
bro. You know what I mean?
some little skint virgin on YouTube
every day talking about people living
with their mommy when you don't even own
a house. You don't even own a bed.
You don't own nothing. You're a loser.
How can you talk about anyone else? My
life's not perfect. I'm not saying my
life's perfect, bro. [ __ ] me.
You know you you got nothing at 31. Yeah.
Says I'm a n because I've kept a baby go for memories.
Yet you're the one that would get with a
16y old and you tried to justify how
it's morally right.
But I'm the dots. Which one sounds more
nonsy? What's a baby grow got to do with wanking?
wanking? Bro, that's how you know he's a
nons. Cuz only a nons would think that.
And I've been having Billy Best
sandwiches since I was the age of about
seven. Again, not a nons, you know?
Not a [ __ ] nons. You know what the
[ __ ] is naughty about having Billy Bear
sandwiches? I've been having it since I was seven.
What the [ __ ] Where's Ricky?
You ran away, didn't you, Ricky?
I can't I can't believe his whole life here
is dedicated to convincing himself I'm
not had sex with people. Why does
anybody care? Why does anybody give a [ __ ]
So you are the insecure one, not me.
You're the one that goes on YouTube
every day calling people that are better
looking than you ugly and you've been
doing it for years now. You know, when
are you going to get laid and get off of
YouTube? I think that's that's that
that's the real question.
And that's and then he says, "Oh, I
haven't met more women than him. I've
absolutely met more women than you then
and now. Absolutely. I've known more
women than you have." And just because
someone's a stranger, it doesn't mean
you can't have an opinion on them. Am I
not right in what I'm saying, Greavesy?
That constantly talking about some
[ __ ] deadbeat in America, you just
make yourself look so obsessed.
Cuz it's not the only person I've been with.
So it's not like you can say, "Well, if
you don't believe you, you're a virgin."
Why? Why are you
You're starting to look more and more
insecure by the day here.
I think he fancies USA. Is he? I can
give you her number if you want.
I might. But she probably wouldn't go
with Skinn Virgins. But I mean, I'll
give you I'll give you a number if you want.
She's still under the same number. I'm
really really getting concerned now about you.
No, I didn't put too much butter on it.
I had to lump the butter on because it
wasn't spreading properly.
There was a reason cuz it wasn't
spreading properly. I had to lump it on.
It was uh I had to do that.
So, do you want USA is his number? uh grinding by
cuz all you seem to do is convince
yourself that everyone is the same as
you and Britney.
You're obsessed. Again, shows
insecurity. There's nothing on my
channel that shows I'm insecure. I show
my face. I don't let people get me down.
You know, there's nothing that shows
that I'm insecure. There's everything
that shows that you're insecure.
And it doesn't matter why you do it, you
do it. So that's it. You know, sat on
YouTube every day reacting, going live
about people for an hour cuz you ain't
got no life. You're an insecure little
skint virgin. Simple.
And please stop dismissing everything I say.
You live in a I mean the guy's got less
life experiences than me.
Literally less life experiences than me.
And he's talking about my life being
[ __ ] when my life I've got more life
experiences than him.
Would you agree with that, Grezy? I've
got more life experiences than him.
What the [ __ ] US. Uh,
[ __ ] Izzy keeps telling me to go to Manchester.
Why does she want my dick so bad? [ __ ] hell.
She begging me to come Manchester.
Why am I insecure? Why have I said
that's insecure? You're the one saying
that I'm ugly every day. You're the one
convincing yourself people haven't had
sex with people every day.
I mean, women lie all the time. I'm
pretty sure it's not uncommon now for
women to lie that someone has raped them.
So, I mean, what did you expect someone
to say? Why are you so obsessed with
whose people been with? You didn't get
with Britney. Britney rejected you. None
of these things happen with you. And
this is where this stems from. You can't
keep going round and round and round in circles, you know.
See, at least with Rice and Monty, they
actually met. This has been going on for
years. This this keyboard warrior [ __ ]
When When are you going to stop?
When are you really really going to
stop? You get what I'm saying, Grezy?
When are you going to [ __ ] stop this [ __ ]
I should get £50 for my birthday which
I'm saving. My mom's taking me for a meal.
I just don't feel like drinking. Don't
you know? But like I get into this habit
of saving and just I just can't be asked.
They must be busy today. Y.
But what I don't understand, Stephen
Howard, yet is they're saying that
they're doing it for reaction, but
they're reacting to me more than I'm
reacting to them, which would then mean
that you've got no life. Which will
surely to me that that surely means if
you're wasting more of your life to get
a small reaction from me, that must mean
you're insecure and you've got a [ __ ] life. Huh?
Isn't that what that must mean? You know,
isn't that what that must mean? Or am I lying?
I don't know.
It's addicting, bro, making videos on
this [ __ ] because he's so low IQ and so
thick that, you know, it becomes um it
becomes like a drug.
bike. What do you like, Grey? The winter
or the summer?
I like the winter.
I'm a weird [ __ ] I'm a [ __ ] weird
[ __ ] aren't I? I don't know. There's
something about I don't know. I like,
like I said, I like October.
There's just something about just
snuggling up warm
just nice. I don't know. Yeah.
Well, I'm glad Q understands me,
understands what I've gone through.
He always wins the argument. Me or me or Virgin boy?
Cuz they say they're doing it for a
reaction, but then they're spending
hours talking about you. So you spend
hours every day talking about someone to
get a five minute reaction.
It just I don't understand what what's
the satisfaction in that. Is that just something to
to blame because you got no life? Oh,
just say we do it for a reaction.
What? So you spend every day of your life
trying to get a 5 minute reaction?
I'm not following. I don't really think
I'll understand to be honest.
I just think I don't think a lot of the
this stuff on this community makes sense.
You know, how much time do you think
you've wasted in 3 years stalking me?
Did uh didn't I show six grand expensive restaurants?
Um designer clothes, better life
experiences. Um, he's got a disabled
girlfriend and also he doesn't have a bed.
So, and 13,000 is nothing. You have
saved for 3 years.
He has no bed and he has no money. 13
grand is no money. You have saved for 3
years is not a lot of money. Okay. 13
grand, bro. 13 grand would not last 6 months.
Am I lying?
Am I lying? I mean, it's the context. It
took you three years to save 13 grand.
It took 3 years to save 13 grand and you
got no life experience.
Yeah, this creep was going like it's
going live obsessing over me again.
Obsessing over my sloppy seconds. Oh,
it's so cringe.
I don't know how someone could do this every day, you know.
Anyways, you're gone.
You're gone. I don't know how someone
could do this every day, bro. Candy,
man. I seriously don't know how someone
could do this what they do every day.
And they don't do it for reaction.
Again, I feel like I'm people are brain
dead when I'm trying to explain this. I
don't know how someone could do this all
day, every [ __ ] day.
I don't understand what the end goal is here. You know,
[ __ ] is really really jealous to me,
bro. I don't understand why.
You're supposed to have this loving
girlfriend and all of this stuff, but
you're sat on YouTube stalking me every day.
I don't I don't understand it. Why don't
you just live your life? You're [ __ ] obsessed, kid.
What are you What are you doing, bro?
What are you going to meet someone or I
don't understand the whole point of this YouTube thing.
You've been convincing yourself people
are virgin like you now for like the
better part of how many [ __ ] years? I
don't know how long you going to keep doing this.
Why am I insecure? I'm not the one
calling people ugly every day. Oh, by
the way, if you call his girlfriend
ugly, you're bullied. Yeah, it's okay
for him to sit and try and call me ugly
every day. But if you call his
girlfriend ugly, bullying.
What a [ __ ] [ __ ] He really really
is low IQ.
I I don't understand this, bro. I really really don't.
Cuz you know when you compare it to
people like Trevor now and other people
they eventually stopped. This weirdo
doesn't stop. I don't understand.
Reactions get boring. You've more than reacted
you know. And then when I say okay well
you get a reaction then you don't really
say anything after that. So
they say they do it for reaction but
then they're reacting more to you
putting energy towards you.
And then Sean's got a reaction with I
just I don't understand it. I just it
doesn't make sense. The whole reaction
thing doesn't really make sense.
This just seems like an excuse to be
obsessed to be honest.
Well, obviously he looks worse than me,
bro. We've established that.
Why? And why are you telling people to
sort their life out? You've got
literally no excuse for having bad oral hygiene.
Dental care is on the [ __ ] NHS.
The day somebody with no teeth and no
money and no bed tries to tell me to
sort my life out, mate, is the day I
ain't got a hole in my ass. Seriously,
what the actual [ __ ]
He's an absolute idiot.
I just can't I just can't get over how
obsessed someone can be.
I just, you know, when you think about
this, bro, it really, really is a disabled community.
And Joe's definitely definitely not one
of the brothers.
Really? Really? I I say that. So, you're
reacting every day for reaction.
Does anyone understand how that doesn't
make sense? But no one really really
says anything. So, you're reacting all
day every day
to to get half a reaction.
Am I Am I missing something? I I I don't know.
I mean, surely that would mean that
you've got a [ __ ] life, right?
Would it would it not?
And it's so weird and obsessive. You You
kind of have to react to it, you know? I
mean, it's weird. You don't know about
some USA is he?
Yeah, I've seen that. I think I've seen
that, bro. To be fair,
I don't understand. When is this When is
this Skint virgin going to stop?
When is this Skint virgin going to leave me alone?
Steven Howard, leave me alone. I don't
want to know you.
Why won't you just leave me alone? Yeah. [Music]
I just don't understand how somebody can
can spend all their all their life
convincing themselves elves that they
someone's never had sex with someone.
I mean, why does no one ever point out
this weirdo's behavior? Steven Howard,
why are you so obsessed with whether
someone slept with somebody or not?
Grezy, do you not find it a bit strange?
I've It's already been established that
I've had more with her than you have with Britney.
Do you think it's a bit of jealousy cuz
it's me and not you? I mean, it's
already been established that you you
you was obsessed with someone for three years and
you didn't do anything with them. And I
think what you're doing and that is the
truth and that's why you talk about
people not sleeping with other people
because you didn't sleep with Britney.
You know, how did how did I even get so [ __ ]
far in the [ __ ] first place to be
honest with you.
I don't understand it, Greavves. I
really really don't, you know. I really really don't.
But people said that you've got a happy life.
You don't seem happy to be on YouTube
every day stalking.
Am I lying, Grezy?
Am I lying?
You don't see You don't seem happy on
YouTube every day stalking people.
You are you insecure little virgin
obsess obsessed with who people live with.
But you live in a bed suit. You ain't
got no money. So
He said zero life experience. I can I
can literally tell you things I've done
that he hasn't done. Been to more
countries, been to more places, been on
a plane, been to nice restaurants, been
with more women, got more friends. Like,
I can go on and on and on and on and on
and on. I've also got teeth in my mouth as well.
Again, it's on the NHS. I I don't know
what the excuse possibly could be why
you don't have no teeth, you stinking bastard.
You know, I I don't I don't think we'll ever know,
you know, cuz whenever I had a problem
with my teeth, I always used to go to
the dentist. Rezy,
did you like my comeback to Ricky
Millington? He says that it's the same
old boring and repeating, but I said,
"Don't you go on a boring repeating
channel talking rubbish."
My comebacks are just so good. I'm too
intelligent for this community,
honestly. That's why it it it can [ __ ]
my brain up sometimes
cuz you're just arguing with [ __ ]
retards, you know?
Right. The food's coming in 15.
Is that okay with you, boss?
I don't really
got my basketball shorts on.
>> Yeah, I'm [ __ ] starving, man. No money.
No money in it. >> Yeah.
Right. It's come. The dinner's come.
The dinner's come, lads.
He was outside knocking a bro. It said
he was 15 minutes away.
You [ __ ] cheeky [ __ ]
All right, [ __ ]
What's your name? I have a boyfriend. [ __ ] that.
Right. I got the dindons here. Grim D.
Do you prefer
Do you prefer winter summer?
I got the ticker. Hey, don't
now. These people say that I've got no
money, right? So, how about I just pull this,
right? One second.
Yeah, winter 100. Well, October too cold
though. I'd say October is the best.
They're not saying I'm born there with a
boy. I'm not I'm learning a [ __ ] bed
and I bend no money in it.
Even though it's depression in the
winter, but I don't know. It's nice. Right.
You want to see my dings?
You want to see how quickly I could eat this? tickle
that virgin Wi-Fi
It's been burning the I should know.
Now, do you want to see the difference
between me and virgin boy? What?
Now you want to see the difference Man
by Elizabeth C. [Applause]
No, that's not that's not logic.
He's too intelligent to be logic.
But this is me.
So this is me
with a bit right.
This is me. Right. Watch this. Yeah.
This is me with the vindaloo.
Not much problem.
As you can see, right,
they don't have nothing to do here in
Kent. [ __ ] out of London. [ __ ] out of
I have [ __ ] probably like this in
shitty Kent. Sh city virgin man Kent Virgin
don't need a drink now.
Now this is virgin boy when he had it.
Are you watching music?
We covered it with rice which is a bit
too hot for him in virgin rice.
It covers up with rice. that again.
That's the difference between me and a
skin [ __ ] [ __ ] virgin in his council
bed [ __ ] Don't sit there with your
little pants little [ __ ] bed sit by
the council and try and tell me who I
should be living with. Now [ __ ] up and
go and suck your disable gas dick.
That's the only bit of action you're
going to get.
[ __ ] skinny version.
They gave me [ __ ] uh they gave me proper dumbs.
I like I'm a good actor. Back to Peter Benny.
To me, Spice has never bothered me.
Never bothered me at all. Never.
Just never ever bothered me. Spice. I
guess we're all made different, you
know. It's lovely in the winter, you
know. Nice winter in the winter.
No, I don't have that where he lives in Kent because
you know he's a [ __ ] skin.
A [ __ ] skin bastard.
A man like a you skin bastard.
See, they call me I'm having a takeway.
They don't know about other people's
lives on here. That's the problem with these people.
Everyone's got the same life as them.
Would you agree?
But no, Grimsy is one of the brothers
because whenever I slag off Virgin Boy,
he doesn't back him up. Even though he
doesn't back me up, you don't ever back
me up, Grimsy. That's fine. But you
never back him up, which is good.
Sick of people saying, "Oh, he's got a
partner. He's got a partner. He's got a
What about all the women I [ __ ] been with? You know,
I don't know what I'd rather have a tone
shake or a coffee. I don't know. I don't
know. That's a hard one.
I do like I don't know. I don't know.
boy in his little bed shitty
little council website
by the council Yeah.
Where is he? Do you do you live with
your parents or do you do you live
alone? I forgot.
So, how did how do you live alone?
How did you manage to pay? How do you
manage to pay for rent?
I don't know why he's talking about
people living with people like he's
independent. He literally lives in a bed.
You know, every most people in London,
they live with their parents.
I mean, most people in London, well, if
they're single, they live with their parents.
>> Most of them. And if they don't, they
live out of London.
You know what I mean? [Music]
Why are these people on YouTube so
concerned with who people live with? They never
talk. They never talk They never talk
about their own life, do they?
Huh? They never talk about their own life.
So if Monty goes to prison, right,
that's not going to be over YouTube, is it?
Nah, that's not over YouTube, is it? [Applause]
Who's my new best friend?
What's Monty's not going to miss over YouTube?
Listen, Gregy. You know I've woke up to
a load of old Bill before when I used to
say mad stuff. Gregy, please come on my
door. What was that old?
What was that? Huh?
He said to me, he said to me, "How could
you, how could that Ricky guy, he
contradicted himself?" That's exactly
the same [ __ ] as I was saying.
Who's more intelligent, me or Virgin boy? Huh?
I don't know why he talks about people
living with his mom and he lives in his
in his [ __ ] little bed [ __ ] and he had
got a job. You would have thought people
would have sorted their lives out first
before talking about others, you know?
Who's more intelligent, me or Virgin boy?
I think Peter B is way more intelligent than it. >> Huh? [ __ ]
Where is he? Listen,
people need to start giving that non like [ __ ] Yeah.
You got this.
Oh, someone sent me a little message on Tinder.
Is that cute?
I need to go out and find a new mama.
Oh, I'm stuck. Mama.
Oh, I'm stuffed.
You believe me, Grezy? I'm stuffed.
I'm stuffed. Mama, sit down, mama.
Remember that Tom and Joey,
you sit down right now and give me that
spoon. You are my nice mama. Oh,
Grey, do you remember that one?
Sit down and give me that spoon. You are nice, mama.
You remember the USA? I know this is
you. Stop pretending to be one of your
viewers. A How is that?
How good was that? Ah, yummy.
Right, I'm finished my food now.
What do you think of King having a five beauty?
You can't deny she's attractive.
You don't find Cole attractive. You're
[ __ ] gay. You can't deny she's attractive. [ __ ] you.
You can't deny his attractive music.
You can't deny attractive.
You know Monty man. Yeah. He's not going
prison over YouTube, is he?
It's not over YouTube though it
wouldn't say it's over YouTube. Would you? No.
No. Seriously, is it over YouTube? Oh, [ __ ]
That was lovely, mate.
You reckon you'll never lose it?
What's what's what's he going to what's
money going to prison? Why is What's he
going to prison for? Huh?
Why does this [ __ ] Izzy want me?
Yeah, but it wasn't over YouTube though, was it?
Yeah, but that weren't YouTube, was it?
I was, like I said, I was watching some
Harry Potter the other day on YouTube
and I was like, "Nah, this can't be
right. This [ __ ] ain't monitored."
Little Harry at like [ __ ] 9 years
old. Nah, that it can't be the same website.
It should be monitored cuz Timmy is on this website.
I think that skin virgin needs to go
prison. I think he needs to get laid.
So why does no one call him obsessed
when he's going at me? But if I was to
go at him every day, they called me obsessed.
I don't get it.
Yep. You remember when I messaged that
person on Reddit the other day,
Greavvesy, and they were like, "Oh, not you again."
They're like, "Not you again, Grezy."
That's what they said to me. I said,
"I'm struggling with women and stuff."
They're like, "Oh, not you again."
Look, these are my favorite t-shirts. Greasy,
I'll show you them.
Uh, all saints. It's got a bug on it. Look.
Do you see it? The bug.
I've always loved all sades. Yeah.
Yeah, Hugh said, "How long did it take
you to write that reply to um Ricky in
the comments?" And I said, "Um, yeah, it
took about 30 minutes."
But he got completely destroyed. Could
you imagine Monty typing something like that? Nah,
he was trying to blame me for everything
earlier when I was on his live. Grezy
said, "You got me on into this shitty community. Yeah. Do
>> you know what? I might do a video of
where they only respond to negativity.