Doctor is the
Where's my over gun?
What is where? Oh man. Oh sh. Oh, lovely.
Yeah, sleeping pattern's a bit better
now, which is good.
Yippee. Yippee. Yippee. Wow.
Franklin, you come out.
I need to verify my age for Xbox. Why?
No. [ __ ] that.
No. No. No. No. No. [clears throat]
You had to do a couple of things today.
I had to get the microphone fixed.
There was a fault with it. So,
yeah, I had to get it fixed.
I didn't realize there was three [ __ ]
microphone in the [ __ ] phone.
Nah, I can't be asked, man.
Not worth my time. Nope.
I was only joking, bro. And I said I was
going to go there. My [ __ ] going to go there? No.
I hate this cold weather. [ __ ] [ __ ] Sh.
Yeah, I can't be bothered, bro. There's
nothing in it for me.
So, what's the [ __ ] point? One second. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro. [ __ ] sake.
Yeah, it's going to be a sick day
tomorrow, bro. We got King as well, by
the way. So, it's going to be a sick day tomorrow.
Yep. Going for a nice meal. Going to get
smashed. I got my football on, by the way.
Make sure I uh
make sure I don't show the thing.
Yeah, I got a I got a double boat. I got
a uh double both score, no draw,
which is good.
Yeah, man. Double both score, no draw. And
yeah, sick, man. It's going to be good.
Nah, I can't be asked. There's nothing
in it for me.
Nothing in it. I done a few things today.
Yeah, I had to do some things.
I'm not meeting people for fights over YouTube.
I gain nothing. No, you didn't thought
as much because if I wanted to go there,
I would go there. Tell him to come to London.
Okay, tell him to come to London and
I'll meet him. I'm not wasting my time
and money to fight losers on YouTube.
Been there, done it, worn a t-shirt. I
don't go around in circles. It's called
having an IQ.
It's called having an IQ. Yeah. If you
really, really want to see this fight
100% 1 million%, tell them to come to London. Simple.
Yeah, I'm done wasting money, time,
[ __ ] traveling to [ __ ] people. I'm
I'm over it, bro. Done it a million
times before. I'm not doing it again.
So, tell him to come to London. And if
he ain't got the money, why don't you go
give him the money? I'm I'm not wasting
my time and money. Simple.
Simple, bro. Rice went to him. I went to
him last time. We met up. He can come to
London now. Simple.
about you thought as much. [ __ ] out of
there, bro. Tell him to come to London then simple
and I've got stuff to do tomorrow. I'm
going to be out all day tomorrow.
Going for a meal. Got this football bet
on as well.
Yeah, I've got stuff to do about you
bloody thought as much. Tell him to come
to London then.
Huh? Tell him to come to London and stop
making excuses. It's only an hour and
[ __ ] 20 minutes away. Yeah.
It's not about [ __ ] winning and
losing, bro. The guy is not going to
beat me. I'm not no [ __ ] Rice.
Yeah, he couldn't even beat Timmy
Eldridge. I beat Timmy and Tiger,
you know. But anyway, tell him to come
to London anyways and 100% or a million% meet him. Yeah,
I could go out today if I wanted to to
be honest, but
I'm going out tomorrow for a few drinks,
so might as well just save it till
tomorrow. Go out tomorrow. Yeah.
Yeah. Anyway, tell him to come to London. Simple. [snorts]
Right. What time should we have this
meal? Cuz I want to do Yep.
changing back to the other one. That's
[ __ ] weird, isn't it?
So, yeah, you can come to London, man.
Come to London. Like, yeah.
Oh. But no, I wouldn't accept anyone's
money either. Oh, I could say like you
can send me [ __ ] £500
and then I'll go if you really really
want to see it cuz I'm not wasting my
time and my money. I'm not doing it. I
am not [ __ ] doing it anymore.
I've done it for too many years. Yeah.
You want the link? Yeah. Too many years.
in one second. Hold on. Let me put the
link out. Hold on.
Tell him to come to London. We've got
all day. We've literally got all day.
Yeah. One sec.
Okay, I need to close the link. One sec. Yeah,
tell him to come. One second.
Right. Okay. Let me put a link up. I was
trying to do a different way. Tell him
to come to London, bro. He hasn't got
any excuse not to come to London. He's
got an excuse. I'm not going to
Birmingham. I can't be bothered. Been
there, done it, won the t-shirt.
Yeah, you can come to London. Simple.
Nah, I'm not going around in circles.
Dark theme. There we go.
Nope. Didn't hear anything, bro.
One second. It's not letting me add him.
Oh, there we go.
>> Are you Are you bag. You complete [ __ ]
bag. No, no, no, no. All last night you
were saying, "I'm coming to Birmingham.
I'm coming to come to London."
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. [ __ ]
>> Okay. Can you No, no, no. The
arrangement is for you to come to
Birmingham like you said last night to
every [ __ ] Yeah.
>> Still meet you. But I'm willing to still
meet you then.
>> Well, get get your ass to Birmingham.
>> I'm willing to still meet you.
>> Oh my god. What?
>> It's an hour and 30 minutes. Oh, listen listen listen.
Why does this guy not want to leave?
He's where where he lives. He's [ __ ] scared.
>> It's an hour and 30 [ __ ] minutes.
Yeah. Simple. It's an hour and 30 minutes.
And also, if you really want me to go,
send me £500 and I'll go.
Send me £500 and I'll go. Simple. How
about that one? You send me £500 and I
will go. Simple.
No, I didn't see it, bro. I don't really
care, man, about them two. They're
boring as [ __ ]
bro. I know he's like work, bro. I could
smash him up anytime. It ain't about
that. It's about I've done this a
million [ __ ] times.
A million times, bro. [ __ ] this. I'm not
doing it. And to be honest, I wouldn't
accept anyone's money. I've got my own
money, but I don't want to [ __ ] waste
money, bro. Waste time my money. [ __ ] that.
You know what I mean? So yeah.
Why would he get on the train to London?
It's not like I've disappeared. I'm
saying I will still meet him.
I'm saying I will still meet him, bro.
I'm literally saying I will still meet
you. It's not like I've disappeared. I'm
not [ __ ] doing that, bro.
Yeah. Fake Q's trying to come in.
You're [ __ ] [ __ ] like you. You're a
[ __ ] teacher. I'm [ __ ] London. And
that's how he's done. I'm going to London.
>> You were supposed to come to Birmingham
today. I know that
I meet in London. But I will meet you in
>> PJ, you will get dropped in London. You
get dropped in Birmingham.
>> You couldn't even beat Timmy. Listen,
listen, listen, listen.
>> Listen, listen. Timmy,
what did you say? Mike said, "Do you
want trouble? Come around the corner."
You shut yourself. Shut it.
>> I didn't [ __ ] myself. I was right in his
[ __ ] face. I mean, money now it
wished your listen.
>> He wished he wished your girlfriend
Yeah. to get cancer and you done
absolutely [ __ ] nothing. And there
was only two of them and he's a little
[ __ ] as well.
I would have told him, "Yeah, let's go
around the corner then." I would have
said, "Yeah, come on." That's what I
would have said. And you done nothing
but yet you're talking all of this [ __ ]
Yeah. Now you don't want to meet him
again. You done nothing, bro. You done
nothing. No, you don't need to pay for
my trainer. If you want me to go, you
need to make it worth my while. Yeah.
Simple, bro. I want [ __ ]
Yeah. I want [ __ ] £500 if I'm willing
to waste my time
and waste my money. And I've got money.
I don't need your But for it to be worth
it, no less than that, bro. Simple. Or
come to London. I'll meet you. That's it.
But why are you saying all this stuff
about money Mike? When he was in your
face, you didn't do anything. So what the [ __ ]
You know, he ain't about it, bro. Rice
is a [ __ ] [ __ ] And even then, he
had to kick him when he was on the
[ __ ] floor. Do you know what I'm saying?
He ain't about it, bro. He really ain't
about it. He really ain't about [ __ ]
You think someone Yeah. like him could
beat me? No. He couldn't even beat Timmy.
He couldn't even beat [ __ ] Timmy.
He's not about that life, bro. Trust me.
And think of all of the time he's met
me. Yeah. And he's never done nothing to
me. Think of the times he's met me and
he's never done nothing to me cuz it's
always an excuse.
It's always a [ __ ] excuse.
Look at all of the things he says that
I've I've said about his kids and stuff
and he's never done nothing to me
because he's he ain't about it, bro. He
really is not about it.
Yeah, you might have squeezed my [ __ ]
hand and it might have hurt cuz you're
bony, but you wouldn't beat me in a
fight. Come today. I haven't disappeared. You know,
I'm going out tomorrow. I won some money
today. I got a football bet, got my
haircut, got my microphone fixed. I'm
not wasting my time and money on you. Simple.
If I reach 500 pound in donations, then
I'll go 100%. But if not, then I'm not
doing it. Simple. Not worth my time. Not
worth my time, my effort, my buddy. Nah.
So that's that. Yeah, man.
Where the [ __ ] has Ricky gone? I'm
starting to get worried now. Grievy,
since I put the approaching videos up,
you seem to have seemed to have gone quiet.
Wow. I wonder what happened to him, bro.
Strange, isn't it?
He seems to have gone very quiet. Yeah,
this football bet looks good.
Yeah. Hasn't he gone quiet though? Um, Grezy.
He's gone [ __ ] quiet since I put them
approaching videos up.
Would you not agree that he's gone
quiet? He's gone very quiet, hasn't he?
Yeah. I went on the roulette today. I
put 50 pound in. I got it to uh 150
and I put 20 on the football.
This is a good bet though. This is So I
had to pay [ __ ] £35 to get my
microphone fixed on my phone. Oh [ __ ]
What a load of bollocks. Eload
Yeah. It's [ __ ] I hate the winter, bro.
Yeah. Ricky said, "It's how I'm acting
around women, but then I put approaching
videos up where they didn't even give me a chance."
That's mad, isn't it, Tanny? Mad. But
like I said, it doesn't bother me, bro,
what people say cuz simps are always
going to simp. Let them keep defending
women. Let them be virgins their whole
life. Some people are happy with that, you know.
Some people are happy.
Who are we to say what they're doing is
right or wrong? You know,
if they want to sit there and defend
women all day and remain virgins, that's on them. Yeah, man.
My steakhouse tomorrow. And I've got
another meal on Sunday as well.
I can't wait. Can't wait.
Got a nice trim ready for tomorrow. Yeah.
Nope. Changed my mind. Waste of time.
Waste of time. Waste of effort. waste of
money. I told him he can come to London
though and I meet him at a train station,
but he won't do that for some reason. Or
if you give me £500, I'll go, you know,
I don't mind going £500.
So yeah, I said I was going to go
tomorrow yesterday at 3:00 p.m.
where we didn't even arrange the actual
location. So I'm not doing this [ __ ] If
you want to give me £500, then I will go.
Other than that, come to London. Simple.
I don't I don't mind smashing someone up
for [ __ ] £500.
You know what I mean?
You all claim that you got money on
here. Yeah. So, send me £500 and I'll
I'll do it.
Absolutely. I'll do it for £500.
other than that. Nah,
not at all.
Not at all at all.
Not at all at all. Grezy, do remember
I'm going to knock him out.
Do you hear what
Did you hear what Mike said to him, Grezy? >> [laughter]
>> He said, "Do you want to drink with us
or do you want to do it bad?" Huh? [laughter]
I was dead, bro. He was like, "Do do you
want to drink with us or do you want to
do it bad?" [laughter]
And I was just thinking, "What? Did you
hear it? Did you hear it, Grezy?
What do you want to do?"
Meaning like what? The same website you
can watch Harry Potter on. [laughter]
I'm sorry. That just makes me laugh, bro.
Yeah. If I got steakhouse tomorrow
and then get drunk and then
got some got some got to go go to
another restaurant on Sunday.
Yeah. I can't wait, bro.
I can't wait.
He hasn't won. I told him if he comes to
London I'll meet him anywhere, bro. If
he comes to London, I'll meet him anywhere.
Yeah. I put 50 on the roulette. I got it
to 150 and another 20 pound football bet.
Yeah. Pays for the grooming and [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] expensive, bro.
Tomorrow will be my last time going out
until I [ __ ] off. So, yeah. Bad.
Yeah. Do you want to do it bad? I can't
get over Mike. Do you want to have a
drink with us or do you want to do it bad? Huh?
Should I go Should I go [clears throat]
to Birmingham, Grezy, and do it bad? [laughter]
Should I actually go and do it bad? Easy.
Should I go to Birmingham and do it bad?
I was reading this thing on Reddit.
Yeah. And these women are still trying
to deny that the dating game is easier for them. [laughter]
They're still denying it. They're
saying, right, that this is their logic,
Grezy, that um all of the matches that
they get are creepy men and men that
just want to [ __ ] them. And I mean,
yeah, okay, a lot of that might be true,
but at the end of the day, right, you've
got more matches. So, surely if you've
got more matches, right,
um you you've got more chance of meeting
someone that's decent. No, to a man that
doesn't get any matches.
You know what I'm saying? It's like,
what the [ __ ] Like, stop trying to be a
victim. That's what these women do. They
try to be a victim. You're not a [ __ ]
victim. Stop trying to be a [ __ ]
victim. Of course, women have it easier than men.
And don't give me that, oh, they risk
getting raped and [ __ ] murdered. No,
they have it easier than men. End of simple.
They have it easier than men. End of
story. So stop trying to say that you
don't cuz the thing is right uh Greasy
somebody was saying like oh like for a
man if he doesn't approach a woman he's
probably going to end up alone which is
true isn't it? You you won't even get a
date unless you approach like 200 people like it's
that is the truth. That generally is the
Like look how I'm going out tomorrow and
I'm trying. Do you know how much I spent
today on this haircut and getting my
skin cleared and [ __ ] um you know I
have to go and fix my phone and [ __ ] Do
you know how much money I spent bro
today? Over [ __ ] £100 just walking up
the [ __ ] road and I'll be spending
more money tomorrow. And that's just to
be with a chance of getting a date with
someone. It's [ __ ] rigged against men, bro.
It's [ __ ] It's mad. Of course it's
rigged against [ __ ] men.
Do you want to drink or do you want to
do it bad? [laughter]
That's mad, bro. This This site needs to
be monitored. I've I've said this a
million times before, but it does.
But yeah, it is rigged.
[snorts] But like I said, I plan to go
out my sister. It's my birthday a couple
of days, so that's the only reason I'm going out.
But the same thing will happen again. No doubt.
That's why you should just live your
life without worrying about it. Cuz it
is if you think about it. Yeah. If you
actually think about it, it the more you
actually think about it, Grezy, the more
depressing it actually is. And this is
where like the the problems,
you know, come into it. But they
definitely definitely do have it easier 100%.
Because men always have to f make the
first move. Men have to approach. Women
don't have to do any of that stuff. What
they got to do worry that they're not
going to get raped or murdered. Is that it?
[ __ ] hell, bro. Come on.
Well, it will never change, will it? So,
that's that, isn't it?
Or do you [snorts] want to do it bad? [laughter] Yeah. [laughter]
But but he was a big dad, was he? He
wasn't big then. Nah, he wasn't a big
man then, was he? Oh yeah,
but double both score no draw.
This will be lovely if this comes in.
140 from 20. Swindon, Colchester, North
County, and Cambridge. I was going to
put 150 on two teams, but then when I
won that money, I was like, there's
there's no point,
you know, but I was. And then I found
out that Northern the National Northern
League and the National South League
isn't playing. So,
yeah, they're not playing. So, I just
went with that.
It's going to be hard to win. Both got
no jaw, but yeah.
Do you want a pilot or do you want to do it bad? [snorts]
He'll be paying for it. Yeah. Yeah.
We need to take King for Walkie soon.
Yeah. I went to the barbers, spent a lot of money.
But this is this is what I'm saying. Yeah,
I got the haircut today cuz um I didn't
want to [ __ ] around tomorrow. So,
because it's going to take too long, but
you I tell you how many dates I'll get
for next week.
Yeah, this is going to be an example of
the dating game for men. Yeah.
Yeah. I want to do it bad. [snorts]
And how many h and how many
and how many fights have you showed up for?
Yeah, I say it, but then it's funny to
say, do you know what it is? It's funny
to say these things and arrange these
things, but then you realize there's no
point in it. Waste of time, waste of
money, you know.
Yeah, I could easily go to Birmingham
today and smack money up.
But what's the point?
Monty's not strong, bro. He only beat
Rice cuz Rice is a [ __ ] and yeah, he
isn't strong. He really isn't. You know,
why are people denying that the dating
gab is easier?
And then they say, "Oh, well, the same
amount of women are in relationships
with men." But no, that's not true,
though, because some people could get
lucky or whatever. There's loads of
people that are struggling to even get a date.
We're not even talking about just
relationships. We're talking about just
a [ __ ] date. So,
it doesn't make sense saying other
people or cuz Yeah,
whatever. Anyways, bro, they're always
going to deny that they've got the upper hand,
which is strange cuz I don't know how
they can deny they have the upper hand
with dating, but
they do. Strange.
I might have went to Manchester tomorrow
if was my sister. Maybe
Can't wait for that steak tomorrow. I'm
having steak today as well.
No, no, no.
Or do you want to do it bad?
That's jokes, bro.
That is jokes. [snorts] I'm so
I can't believe it. It's 2025 and
[clears throat] virgin boy still a virgin. Madness.
Wow. I can't believe he's never going to
lose it. Never going to pop it.
Can't believe he's never going to
[ __ ] pop that cherry.
[sighs and gasps]
Some madness, isn't it?
How you going to lose it?
How you going to pop it?
You know, you're never going to lose it,
are you? You're never going to pop it.
You want to do it bad or do you want to
have a drink
or do you want to do it bad?
That is jokes, bro. Anyways,
I'll be back later. Yeah.