Oh, [ __ ] hell, man.
I'm too tired about to do anything. I'm
[ __ ] going to sleep soon.
What happens when your [ __ ] sleeping pattern's [ __ ]
That's literally what happens.
My sleeping p is [ __ ] bro.
The [ __ ] Oh, it's there. Yeah,
I can't. I'm too tired.
I had to cancel it due to [ __ ] tiredness.
That's what happens when you got [ __ ]
up sleeping pattern.
Like mine is [ __ ]
Just going to get some food I think later, man. Jeez.
I was going to go out. Yeah, I've put it
on my community post. I was going to go
out today for a meal and some drinks,
but there's no way, bro.
There's no way. I'm too tired.
Yep. Too too too tired.
Yeah, I'm [ __ ]
Well, I need to go out tomorrow. I have
to go out cuz I got my haircut and [ __ ]
You go look at my community post.
I'm so tired, bro.
Cuz I I've been up since 11.
So, and I normally wake up at like 8 9.
So, yeah, my sleeping pattern's [ __ ]
So, I basically got my haircut for no reason.
Nah, not really.
It's always going to be the same [ __ ]
here in it in this country. So,
not really, man.
I mean, if you win £140, it's not
pointless, is it? From 20.
How's that pointless? Right. Yeah.
This is not supposed to change my life.
He said, "I'm willing to try and change my life."
Huh. Strange strange comment to make.
Very strange comment indeed.
Yeah. I can't go out, bro. I'm too tired. [ __ ]
If I'll even go out.
Yeah, I know. This is what a strange
comment to make. Huh? And to be honest,
if I went out today, it would have just
been the same [ __ ] with women anyways. So,
like it will always be.
Yeah, cuz I don't need a few grand.
I don't know when I'll be out next.
Well, no, I do have to go for a meal. My
mom's taking me for a meal.
Oh, it's just all [ __ ] up cuz I can't
go out today. It's just [ __ ]
everything up, basically.
Oh yeah. Okay. It's bum change. Okay. Millionaire.
£120 bum change. Okay. Millionaire.
We're not all millionaires like you.
Guy is such an idiot.
£120 bum change. All you people are millionaires.
These people have got to be Cristiano
Ronaldo on here, man. I'm telling you.
What do you think about me not going out
today? I just said to my sister, "Oh,
[ __ ] God can't pass it." You know,
bro, I'm going to block you. Yeah. Bye-bye, bastard.
Dude, dude, dude. [ __ ] bongo. Can we
actually get some normal people on here? Yeah,
bro. What the [ __ ]
like a let down now, but I just I just
can't go, bro.
I mean, that's six weeks.
Someone's like, "Oh, you can't stay in
for two months." I can I can stay in for
2 months. I've already stayed in for 2 months before.
Well, 6 weeks. Yeah.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
I just come out the shower.
Yep. Just come out of the shower, boss.
I don't know if any of you people still drink, but
I'm over it, me, bro. I swear that I'm
just over it.
It's the same [ __ ] in it. Like, yeah, man.
I'm tired, boss.
I'm watching these good cool GTA videos as well.
I don't know, bro.
I don't know.
There's no way I would have lost it. I don't think there are [Music]
Yeah, I was going to go out to the I was
supposed to go out to my sister, but I'm
too tired. I had to cancel.
I know. I've been up since 11:00 p.m.
How embarrassing, eh?
But it's all right, man.
I could go out tomorrow drinking, but
Sunday, I went out Sunday like two months ago.
I probably won't bother. I know I got my
haircut and stuff, but
this cost a lot of money. Nah.
Uh, I think I'm over it, bro. I think
I'm I really think I'm actually over it
now in this country. I really really do.
I got my haircut as well. It's
expensive, but I think I'm fully fully over it.
100% over it.
No, I think I'm really over it.
Trust me, I actually think I am.
Time to move on now. Call it a day here,
bro. 100%. One million%. Yeah.
No. Yeah. But it's cuz of what happened
last time, is it? The 10 numbers of no
date and the fact it's been going on for
years as well.
It has been going on for years.
So, it's not going to be any different
next time you go out. That's the That's
the whole thing, you know.
I'm fully over it, bro. I just feel like
a [ __ ] cuz I let my sister down.
Yeah. And the weather's [ __ ] as well.
That's another thing. If the weather
wasn't [ __ ] then I just Yeah, I'm over
it though. I think I am over it. Like
the women are in this country. I think
I'm over it, bro.
Really, really am.
Like I said, I've got money. I've got my
haircut as well. Um,
bro, go [ __ ] self-reflect your
insecurities on another channel.
Yeah, go self-reflect on another
channel. No one cares.
You know what I mean? Shire. Uh,
I don't know.
I don't know what to do, bro. I don't know.
It's clearly never going to work in this
country, is it? So,
yeah, that's what I'm going to do. I'm
going to get some food.
That's exactly what I was thinking.
Cuz all that's going to happen is you're
going to go out,
you're going to approach
and then and then you're going to get
numbers and then they're just going to
[ __ ] you over. It feels weird thinking I
could get numbers now. I haven't done
this in over a month, but I'm sure I
could still approach. But uh I think
giving up is just better, bro, to be honest. really is.
I definitely give up.
I don't know what food to get though.
I'm going to get some nice food.
Talking about yourself,
but my mom still needs to take me for a
meal as well. So,
I don't know how the [ __ ] I used to go
out in this weather.
I used to go out like two years ago. I
used to [ __ ] go out Thursday. I don't
know how I used to do it. I was [ __ ]
mad. But I think when you still have
hope then it's it's different cuz I
still had hope. But obviously there's no
hope in this country. So
that's that in it. Not really.
Not really, man.
Even if the if the football bet wins.
But no, I still won't go out cuz that
makes it seem like I need the money, but
I don't cuz I got money. So,
I don't know what will motivate me to I
think the only thing that will motivate
me to go out again here, bro, is really
one of them numbers meeting me. I think
that's the only thing and that's never
going to happen. So,
I want just take an L here and, you
know, take the experiences I've already
had and then just [ __ ] just call it a day.
Yeah, it's bad, isn't it? It really is bad.
And obviously I could have met my sister
locally, but I wouldn't I would I would
never go out locally. So that wouldn't
be an option
cuz there's not enough people. So
there's a lot of white knights on this
community, Shanghai. A lot a lot of white knights.
Weird, isn't it?
Yeah. Proper white knights defending
women. [ __ ] pathetic. But people uh
uh you're boring. Bye-bye.
I'm coming off this community stream by
the way. Um 100% I'm coming off this community soon.
You heard? Yeah,
proper proper amber.
Nah, you people don't hit. You people
don't talk the truth. You people are
just haters that talk about yourselves.
You don't speak the truth about anyone.
The only thing you do is self project
and bring hate. You don't tell the truth.
You talk about yourselves. You're
boring. I'm coming off. Who the [ __ ]
would put 200 pound on three teams? Who
the [ __ ] would do that? Stupidness, isn't it? Same atmosphere.
It's always the same atmosphere in here. Yeah.
And it ain't even about money. We could
go out today. We could spend £500,600
if we really wanted to. Not that we would.
Uh, boring. Talking about my looks again. Insecure. Boring.
Insecurities coming at you. Go away. You're boring.
Come up with something different. Come
up with something new.
Stop being insecure
about your looks. Stop talking about
other men's looks.
You need to grow up, you sad bastard.
Talking about other men's looks, you
[ __ ] [ __ ] I know that uh you know,
you can't say that on YouTube and
someone reports you get banned.
You're an absolute [ __ ]
talking about my looks. What a [ __ ] man. [Music]
Yeah. Anyways, I'm ignoring you now. You're boring. Boring.
You're going to make You're never going
to make me feel ugly like you. You're
wasting your time.
You will never ever ever make me feel as
ugly as you.
So, stop wasting your time. Please stop
Like never, like never ever ever ever.
You're wasting your time. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye. So yeah,
I'm above average. No, I'm ugly, boy. Me?
No, I'm ugly apparently, lad.
No, I'm ugly, man.
No, above average. No, I'm ugly,
bro. I I don't care if you think I'm
above average, and I don't care if
people think I'm below average. I don't
care about your opinion on my looks.
Why are you talking about my looks? I
don't care what you think of my looks,
bro. Whether it's in a good way or a bad
way, I don't care about what people
think about my looks. I don't give a [ __ ] Seriously.
Jesus [ __ ] Christ. Oh my god. What is
it with you in people's looks?
I can put my camera. No one else can put
their camera on. Yeah. Easy. Done.
What the [ __ ]
Imagine I went out approaching today. Eh,
no. I need a um
I don't know the way you know you know
the way I see it is yeah it's not worth
the effort now like when I didn't have
like sexual experiences and stuff and I
was younger it was a bit different you
know but now it's like
yeah the juice ain't worth the [ __ ]
squeeze it's it's not it's even if you
was to find someone, right? The effort
that you what you'd have to go through
in order to meet someone, it just ain't worth it.
You know, I'd have to go out every day
and talk to people. It's not worth it.
It generally isn't worth it. And I'd
have to deal with games and nah, bro.
I'm not dealing with that. I'm not
putting up with that [ __ ]
Which is I should have learned this a
long time ago, to be honest. But yeah,
and that's it. It's like how long it
would take it. It's what you'd have to
go through in order to actually meet
someone. It's just not worth it. I'd
rather just be by myself. I'd rather
just use escorts if I wanted to have sex,
which I don't even want to have sex,
which I don't even I'm not even asked
about sex either.
>> Yeah, but you get what I mean. It's just
not worth it, you know?
You might as well sit home and watch Dobby. Yeah.
Yeah. I was crazy. I used to go out in
the rain and [ __ ] drinking.
I was [ __ ] me, bro.
Now I can barely go out. I don't have
the energy for it. Yeah. Doo doo.
What's wrong with 120 profit?
I won £100 on roulette
uh on Friday. I was happy with that. 50
to 150. I was happy with that.
I paid for my haircut cuz I was supposed
to go out today. But
so I paid money. I paid some good money
for my hair, but I don't think I'll be going out. Not really.
Yeah, I put one I put 150. I put 50. I
got to 150.
That was good enough for me. Yeah.
Yeah. I was talking to you. Yeah, mom. No.
Yeah. Uh, I've earned some good money
over the past couple of months.
What do you think would have happened
today if I ran out approaching boyfriend?
It's so obvious, bro.
It's just so obvious.
Would never change.
Will it ever change, would it? It's like
you can't even approach people nowadays.
It's all online. Tik Tok and [ __ ]
[ __ ] you know,
Instagram. It's how people meet people. Uh
generally feel like I've had Yeah.
enough bad experiences to last me a lifetime.
It's not worth it. Yeah, man.
Hey, Candy. I was going to go out. I was
supposed to go with my sister to go to
the steakhouse, but and then go for
drinks after, but I'm too tired, boss. I
had to cancel it, boss. So
I said I can't come. I'm [ __ ] knackered, man.
Been up since 11. Yeah.
No, I think I'm done. I generally think
I'm done in this country, bro. Ever
trying again? No, I think for real. For
It's been over a month now.
No, I said I'm on my way there and to
meet me at the station,
which she's not Scottish. She's
Canadian. She just lives in Scotland.
But yeah, let's see if she's uh [ __ ]
with me or not. Give it a whirl.
Cuz I think she's [ __ ] with me bad.
Yeah, I give up. I really do give up.
It's not worth it
to any man or relationship or a bit of
sex. It's not worth it. The [ __ ] you
have to go through.
But you can literally just sit home,
chill, get some nice food.
It's just it's not worth it. It ain't
worth it, bro.
It's impossible to get anything as well. So,
let's see if she's um going to actually Yeah.
Yeah. I said come to the train station. I'm there.
What do you think? Do you think she's
going to meet? Candy. Nah.
Nah. I'm too tired, boss.
I'm too tired.
And I'm not drinking and approaching. [ __ ] that. you know.
Nah, I can't, bro. I'm too tired. I've
been up since 11,
so that haircut was for nothing really.
But no, not really, cuz it's nice to
feel groomed. And I did win £100, so
it's just always the same [ __ ] here.
And the weather's [ __ ] as well. So
steak is better than sex. No, it isn't.
If it was nearer, but it's far away. The
restaurant's quite far. If it was
nearer, then I would have just had the
food and then obviously just come back
and I wouldn't drink.
But it's quite far. It's in central
London. It's quite far away. So,
but my mom's taking me for a meal
as well. So,
I don't know, man.
Well, wonder. Well, I wonder if she
turns up anyways.
Well, I got steakhouse cuz it was a
treat, isn't it?
And steakhouse tastes better than the
butchers as well.
I would have been getting rejected today
in front of my sister. Embarrassing it.
See, I don't even get the urge to go out
drink it anymore. It's weird.
I cook my steak properly.
Yes, I do. I don't have any blood on my
steak. I have mine well done medium.
I mean I I well I I cook I do cook my steak properly.
No, no, no, no, no. I do cook it
properly. I don't like blood in my steak
at all. At all. No, I don't have blood
on my steak. I know how to cook it properly. Nope.
But yeah, I don't even get the urge to
go out anymore here. It's weird cuz
normally if I hadn't been out for a few
weeks, I'd be like, "Oh, I really want
to go out." But now I just can't be [ __ ]
But to be fair, that's probably cuz [ __ ]
Like when I went when I went to meet
Finnish Izzy, that was a Sunday.
Oh, I don't even like thinking about it.
It's just so depressing.
The whole dating thing is depressing, bro. Yeah.
All right. Oh yeah, I think I am I think
I'm done, bro. Really think I am done here.
Um, so what to eat today?
>> It would never change, would it?
I put on my community post. Good luck. Um
Yeah, I thought it was a good bet.
Hey, it's a both score no draw though, so
What do you think would have happened
today, Candyman, if I went out approaching?
It would be the same as always.
Same as always, mate. Yeah.
Well, it will never change, will it? And
you'll never change. That's what Adman
said to me. He said, "Well, it will
never change, will it?"
And you'll never change. So, get used to
it or leave. Yeah,
I think it's going to win. Both score no
draw. Yeah, I put 50 on the roulette. I
got it to 150. I was going to put one I
was going to go and put 150 on a
football bet, but cuz I got the 50 to
150, I just took it in it. Yeah, man. Not really.
I don't really care if it if it loses.
Yeah, I was going to put I was going to
put one uh 50 on two teams.
But um thingy wasn't playing. The
northern and south league weren't
playing so I never
I was going to put 150 on slow and kitty minister.
They always both score.
been studying them for a bit now. So, yeah.
So I got trim for no reason basically.
Do you reckon if I approach today I
would have got I got a boyfriend candy man. Yeah, 100%.
You always get that.
You always get that here.
And I'm [ __ ] tired as well, bro.
Like I said, if I was a virgin and I
hadn't been with women in the past, then
it would be worth putting up with the
[ __ ] But I'm not putting up with that [ __ ] anymore.
The games, the mind game,
the mind games. Um,
and I'm not dealing with it, bro. It's
not worth it. It really ain't worth it
for a bit of sex.
Um, it lad.
Yeah. Well, I was on Reddit and then
they banned me again.
This person on Reddit. Yeah. They said,
"Where is it, bro?"
Yeah, this is true. Generally, men make
the first move, plan dates, and pay for
dates. So when ghosted, our loss is our
time and relatively modest sum, we paid
for our makeup and other products. While
men spend less
time and relatively modest sum, we paid
for our makeup and while men spend less
time money getting ready for dates, they
make a considerable
considerably financial investment as
they should. So you lose everything basically.
If you get a date and and the date
doesn't go well, you lose everything
basically what that means. Whereas they
don't lose anything
really but taking time to get ready.
That's another [ __ ] up thing about it. Mad. Mad.
When you actually think about how rigged
the game is,
you would actually see why you don't
want to participate in it.
Cuz why would you participate in
something that's a Mugs game?
It's [ __ ] Yeah. Why would you want to
participate in in something that's
rigged against you?
That's why I don't gamble big amounts.
You know what I mean? Like,
see, this is true as well. 90% of the
time women the only thing a woman needs
to get a date is being attractive. A guy
has to be tall, have a good job, have
money, etc., etc., etc. to even be
considered by a lot of women.
No, it's not like playing roulette.
Roulette's got better odds.
No, no, no, no. Roulette, Roulette's got better odds,
way better odds than Dayton. So,
no, no, no, no. Roulette's got better odds, lad. So,
um Yeah, but they can do their makeup
hair in the house.
Yeah, I know. I know. It's just all
[ __ ] up, isn't it?
This guy I know, he's a 23 year old
virgin and he approaches like every
month. So could you imagine? I've only
just started giving up at 28.
Yeah, they take ages here, too.
I think my little bet's going to win.
not stuck up here.
I think it's got a good chance. Just bet me.
If it wins,
then maybe I'll go out. I doubt it
though, bro. I doubt it.
So, cuz I know that I know what's going
to happen. That's the thing. So, this it
doesn't really matter, you know? I know
what's going to happen.
It's never going to change here.
And someone says, right, dating is like
a part-time job. It's not a part-time
job. It's a full-time job.
Dating is a full-time job. It's not a part-time job.
M. I used to go out approaching 10 hours a day. So So
yeah, man. About 10 hours.
Yeah, no joke. I was I might as well get
a job if I'm [ __ ] staying at the
house this time approaching. It's not a
part-time job, it's a full-time job. That's Yeah. That's it.
Do you like Reddit? Shanghai.
Yeah. Women stuck up in England.
England. Also, what's happening with
this woman? Is she Is she going or
that's kind of mad if she actually
booked that Tell
kind of mad.
So you you you you started speaking to
me for a couple of days and you you've
booked a hotel. Nah,
you're having a wank.
You are. You're taking a piss. Nah, Fire.
[ __ ] up, [ __ ]
in whatever weird country you're in.
Women suck as well, man. They're narist.
They're [ __ ] narcissist [ __ ]
They're narcissists, man.
Oh, [ __ ] them, man.
He's gone quiet. this person, hasn't she?
Yeah. Check in 3:00.
You can check in from 3:00. The wear has just come
Yeah. Why is she going quiet then?
Yeah, she's full of [ __ ] isn't it? Has to be.
I'm so excited to meet you. I've been so
hurt in the past ghosted, but I'm not
getting that vibe from you. I'm so glad we met.
3:00 is in like half an hour.
Yeah. So why is she not [ __ ] answering
So, do you reckon this woman's actually
was actually going to meet me then in Glasgow
or do you think it was a load of bollocks? H
well check in at 3:00 and I haven't
heard from her. Strange.
What's going on,
Shanghai? What's going on? Is she
meeting me or what?
What is it?
Look how many women's numbers I got on
my phone. It's madness, bro. It's actually mad.
King approach above. King approacher. Oh [ __ ]
she just messaged me, man. Oh, wow.
Should have been legit then.
That's crazy. That
Oh, I was going to go, but I I couldn't.
I was too tired.
I had to cancel it. I was too [ __ ]
I'm tired, bro.
Yeah, I was tired. I couldn't, bro. I
couldn't go cuz I I've been up since 11.
This woman's serious, by the way.
I think she's on her way to Glasgow train station. Wow.
She says she's on her way.
Maybe she was legit then.
Oh, she's going to have a nasty shock in it
when she goes there and I'm not there. Crazy.
Oh [ __ ] Is his friend really?
What? His friend's going Thailand as well. Nah.
And man saying that his friend's going
Thailand on Tuesday.
Nah. No way.
He said it's only you that's not here
now. That's what he said. Nah.
Yeah, women on narcissistic hunts. Greasy.
Yeah, but she's on her way to the station.
See, if she was actually good-looking, I
would have actually met her.
Well, I would have took a risk. But I
don't know. I didn't know she was serious.
All right. Do you remember um Timmy,
Mike, and Monty? Well, Mike said to
Monty, Greavvesy, you want to do it
dirty? Do you want to do you want to
have a drink or do you want to do it
bad? Do you want to do it dirty?
I love it, Grezy. I love it.
Or do you want to do it dirty? I'm dead.
Well, I was supposed to meet my sister,
go for steak and go for some drinks with
my sister, but I had cancel cuz I was too tired.
I told her to go to Glasgow station. She's going,
but I'm not trying to [ __ ] with her. I
thought she was trying to [ __ ] with me.
I agree with you. Do you want to pint or
do you want to do it dirty?
Cuz if you want trouble, we go around the corner.
H Do you want trouble or not? We do.
What website is it on, Greasy?
What website is that on that they all
met up on? What website
Do you do you want to do it dirty?
Yep. I can watch Harry Potter on the
same website I can watch Timmy Eldridge on.
Yeah, that's cute.
The same website you I can watch Timmy Aldridge on. Yeah,
it's crazy, isn't it? It's crazy.
Monty shattered though. You have to
admit Monty shat it.
Yeah, I need to go and meet Monty, man,
and smash him up. I want to take that
crown from him. I want the championship. Squeezy mad.
Yeah. That's what makes me laugh. That's
I love it.
I was talking to nonslegs yesterday and
he doesn't know KSI. He doesn't know the Sidemen.
He didn't know One Direction.
I was like, "Have you been living under
a [ __ ] rock all your [ __ ] life?"
He didn't know um
them them people.
I was like, "What the fuck?"
No, he doesn't doesn't know who they are.
I said, "You don't know who KSI is?" The
the one of the people that made Prime.
What the [ __ ]
That is mad. That is mad.
Yeah, it's funny. It's funny. Yeah, but
it's not funny if you can die on it, Grezy. It's not
It's not funny when you can die on
YouTube, do you know?
I don't see that as funny. Do you?
You know what? When I was walking the
King earlier, I was thinking of the time
Prime grabbed me and it was making me
laugh when it shouldn't be making me
laugh, but I was it just reminded me
that you can write Harry Potter on it
and it Yeah, you're meeting me.
Do you remember? He says, "You're
meeting me." Yeah.
Yeah. But that's on the same website.
See, I I can laugh at myself.
So, she's going to the train station
to meet me. Greasy.
I think she wants sex in it. Greasy.
She wants Peter Belly's Pekka. Greavves.
I thought she was trolling me. Greavves.
I'm not sure.
Whoever grieves, someone's gonna get
hurt or sectioned.
Imagine that. Sectioned on YouTube.
Yeah, but think about it. Monty man
could be going prison. It's his court
case in two uh two days. He could be going prison. Greavves.
Someone. Yeah. Do you know who invented
that um line? Mike did. Someone's going
to get stationed. [Laughter]
Yeah, it's true, isn't it?
I'm in the right place, isn't it? Grez
in my little nesticles.
I could have got a [ __ ] today if I
went to Scotland. Yeah,
I could have got a [ __ ] today. Is it Grezy?
The football's playing soon.
Do you remember that woman? You haven't
told me what woman you want, what values
you want in a woman. It seems anyone will do.
Do you remember, Greavves? Seems anyone will do.
That made you laugh, didn't it?
Seems anyone will do. No,
she says she's at the hotel bar. That's mad.
Do you think she's actually there, Grey?
That's a madness, isn't it? I'm not I
haven't got on a wild goose chase. I
actually thought she was trolling me.
Now I'm going to get a [ __ ] bollock
in now, aren't I?
What do you mean if I mess her around?
Obviously, I am messed I've messed her
about. What am I going to do? Go to Scotland?
What do you want me to do? Go all the
way to Scotland now, you silly goose.
What do you mean if I mess her about?
She's in Scotland, you [ __ ]
Yeah, she sent me a photo.
Oh no, I do feel I actually feel bad now.
You know, I'm just going to ghost her.
I'm going to ghost her. I'm going to
No, I I actually feel bad now cuz she
didn't do anything to me. The other one
I didn't give a [ __ ] about. She was
being a [ __ ] But this one I feel bad for
cuz what do you want me to think?
Someone spoke to me for less than a week
and they're booking hotels.
What the [ __ ] did you want me to think? You know they
never actually being [ __ ] legit.
She's probably horny in it, Greasy.
That's insane, bro.
It's not funny though, is it?
It's not funny, mate.
So, you know, Monty when he goes to prison, right?
That's not actually over YouTube though, is it?
That's like riots or some [ __ ]
That's to do with like riots and stuff in it.
It's not YouTube, is it? It's something
that he done like with the riots.
So, it was YouTube then, wasn't it?
Yeah, I was watching um I was watching
the Sidemen earlier, Grezy.
Oh, some of this stuff is funny.
Yeah, I like to stick to that side of
YouTube, the PG side. I don't like to be
on this community. It's [ __ ] up.
This community is [ __ ] up, you know. [Laughter]
This community is [ __ ] up in it. Yeah.
Do you remember a lady was at the old
house and the windows got smashed?
That's not funny. That's scary, bro.
That's scary as [ __ ] An old woman
sitting down and then her windows
getting smashed. That's not funny.
That's not funny, Grezy. That's not funny.
You know, that ain't funny. That's not
funny. Something could got seriously
hurt, you know.
No, it's not funny.
I feel sorry for this woman now.
I weren't [ __ ] her around. The other
one I was [ __ ] around with on
purpose. Yeah, cuz she was being a [ __ ]
She was being a passive aggressive
little [ __ ] So, but this this wasn't
done anything to me.
I feel I do feel bad. Yeah.
Yeah. I can't I can't believe that. That
is just mad. That's madness.
That is actually madness.
Yeah, it is mad. Absolute madness.
Same website. I could have got killed on Grezy
cuz if I was in that house that day, I
could have got killed, you know.
I could have got killed.
It's not funny.
Crazy. It's not funny. Yeah.
If you wanted a good old shag.
I definitely think if USA tried it on
with Greavvesy, he would I think you
would have sex with her, wouldn't you,
Greavvesy? Don't lie to me.
You don't have to lie to me, Grezy. You
would, wouldn't you?
Yeah, right. Of course you would. You've
got needs too, Greavvesy.
Why? But you got needs. Greasy.
Of course you would have sex with her.
You silly goose. Yep. Exactly.
If you want to do it dirty, Greavves,
you come around the corner then.
I don't know. Ant-Man's friend is going to Thailand.
The pretty boy. Really?
He's going to Thailand. Really? That's mad.
That's mad, bro.
[ __ ] everyone's going there now, aren't they? Yeah,
this woman keeps ignoring me on
Instagram to piss me off. Goozy.
doing it on purpose.
Right. I think this football bat's coming in.
I'd love to win a both score, no draw, man.
I think it will win, mate. I definitely
think this bet's winning, bro.
I got a feeling. Yep. M
Bro, I [ __ ] um
watch some songs.
What's the point of doing a bet to win £141?
two and 141 pound
um for fun.
I know it is cold, Grezy.
I like my little nesticles.
Ah, I need big USA to keep me warm. Grievy
King's downstairs, by the way.
Oh, that reminds me. I need to give him his food.
I'm so tired.
Yeah, he doesn't come on the bed for
some reason. He's downstairs, but he
doesn't come on the bed.
You You're obsessed with King, in it,
Grezy. Yeah, King's cute. Everyone loves King.
Cute little doggy.
You like you like him?
I don't even have the energy, mate, to
go [ __ ] going down the stairs. I
ain't even got the [ __ ] energy.
But he needs feeding.
Oh, what's it
the dog can? Oh,
remember that one? Greasy load of old
Bill. You want to see him get fed?
What I'm saying? [ __ ] man. Look. >> Oh,
>> did you see him?
It needs to be
You have the ear like that.
Is that cute? Yeah.
I need to bed. It's cold.
Really? It's cold.
It's cold, isn't it, lad?
I'm going to knock him out, lad. He said
that. Crazy. Remember?
You said that. I'm going to knock him out. Crazy.
Come on, lad. [Laughter] Oh.
She's asking well I am greasy
asking me where I am. We're going to get
a [ __ ] bollock in now. Greasy.
Yep. I think we're [ __ ] now, mate.
Yeah. It's not funny. Greasy.
We're in the [ __ ] doghouse.
So why would you sleep with um USA? Is
he greasy? You've got needs, don't you?
Why wouldn't you get with her?
I reckon this bet's going to win me.
What should I eat?
Yeah, she's messaging me. Wow.
Why when her friend told her the stuff I
said about women? That's why I thought
it was a setup cuz her friend stopped
talking to me because he found out the
stuff I said about women. Breezy, that's
why I thought it was obviously like a
setup, you know. [Music]
could have gone. little [ __ ] today
cuz he's a weirdo.
That's why he's a weirdo. That's why.
Nah, it's not as good as Nando.
Close though. Close second, but it's not
as good as Lando's. No way. Nah.
She don't want to know you.
She don't want to know you. Greedy.
I might get peppers.
later on. Maybe it's mad.
It is madness.
Seems anyone will do. Grezy, was she
right about that? Seems anyone will do
seems anyone will do
that is jokes.
Seems anyone will do.
That is funny.
I just fed him. [Music]
I kind of fancy a KFC.
I don't know. Got no Coke in.
No, that's ugly.
That's too ugly, bro.
She's got black flaps.
Monty's even said that she's got black
flaps. She wasn't even lying about that.
[ __ ] that, bro. Madness.
What should I eat, Grezy? I want a
curry, but the curry shop don't open until 5. We
know Monty's just a weirdo.
I met Nons through Monty says it all. Come on sec.
None of these are scored yet. What's going on?
What the [ __ ]
You can't see to start [ __ ] scoring, mate.
If she keeps ignoring me, I'm going to
send her a dick picture. Uh, Grezy,
cuz I've had enough, mate.
You know, if you sit there ignoring me,
you little snake. That's what I called
her. I called her a little rat.
I called her a rat. This one on Instagram.
You know what's going on here? They haven't scored.
That's a bit strange. Yeah,
I'll go and sleep soon. I'm tired.
What's going on? [Music]
Well, I'll be back I