[ __ ] it up, bro.
Oh man, the [ __ ] up. Yeah.
Jesus for us.
05 guys is Earth. Oh, man. Oh Man,
I want to order this Wendy's.
Never mind. I wonder what is this window. Wow. Madness. >> [snorts]
>> I don't want to die. >> [snorts]
>> There we go.
Say my sleeping pad's [ __ ]
Absolutely [ __ ] This is horrible, man.
Yeah, man. Everyone Everyone sleeping. [sighs]
Hold that virgin boy.
Oh, that virgin boy. That virgin ain't this Yeah, man.
Come on. Wendy's [ __ ] starving.
But yeah, I am coming off this community soon. 100%
weirdos on here that create the same
atmosphere every day.
Same repeating people.
[ __ ] atmosphere. Yeah.
Wendy should be here soon.
I just went for Wendy's
23 [ __ ] pound it cost me
skin like the virgin mate.
blood. It's dead.
Oh, they All right.
They need that power, Terry.
Without that power, mate.
You need Terry. They need that power,
lad. They need that power.
Is everything there?
Oh, thank you, mate. [ __ ] jam
was bloody interested.
I was interested in the skin version the bed.
>> Oh, that's what it was.
>> Yeah, I had a shower, didn't I? But um I
couldn't go out. I was too [ __ ] tired.
I want a puppy.
I will never lose it. [snorts]
Oh, some I know. Yeah,
I just ordered some uh Wendy's.
Yeah, I've not long woke up.
Yeah, I've not long woke up, mate.
I was going to go out today, wasn't I?
[ __ ] But I was too tired,
cuz I've been waking up at 11:00. My
sleep time's [ __ ] So, yeah,
that's the thing.
That is a thing. So, yeah. version.
I'm going to send you my dick.
>> Yeah, we did. But I didn't go cuz I was too tired.
I said, "If you keep ignoring me, I'm
just going to send you a picture of my
dick and be wanking.
They live in South America cuz it's
[ __ ] annoying. Don't sit there and
[ __ ] ignore me."
[ __ ] annoying. No, I just I was just
too tired, bro. So
we did, but I was tired and I figured
there's no point even going out trying
because it's just the same old in this
country. I could always be. Yeah, man.
Yeah, I was too tired, man. I wanted to
go, but I was so [ __ ]
And the weather was [ __ ] I thought I'd
well just stay in, bro.
I would have went drinking and then
obviously it's always the same here,
isn't it? When you approach. So
minutes. How can it be 7 minutes away?
That doesn't make sense.
It's just a two minutes. Hello, King.
How are you? Sorry, I was asleep.
Oh [ __ ] I could have got you a burger
as well. I forgot about you. Sorry, King.
I can't believe Virgin Boy Steven
Howard. He needs to get a life and get
laid. I don't know how someone can sit
on YouTube all day for years willing to
go back and forth.
Help me out, bro.
He seriously seriously needs to get a
life and get laid
cuz all he's doing is showing his up
now. He's all he's doing is showing himself up
to be what he is, a low life. So yeah,
I'm on Wendy's. I'm hungry.
Yeah, good for him. I'm not watching it.
I don't give a [ __ ] He's a low life. He
needs to get laid.
I don't know how many times I have to
keep saying it, bro.
Literally, he needs to get a life. Just
like that. Terry needs to get a life
instead of coming on YouTube every day
creating the same atmosphere cuz they
ain't got a [ __ ] IQ. They ain't even
got an IQ to [ __ ] create a different atmosphere. Where the
I'm probably going to come cold.
That was the first time I saw I just got that. So yeah.
Yeah. He needs to get a life. He's a
little low life.
That's what he is. He's a low life.
Proves he hasn't got a life.
Am I lying? Steven Howard.
Yeah. It just shows that he's got no life.
That's why it doesn't bother me, bro.
got no life. That's all.
He's got no life but YouTube literally.
Where the [ __ ] is this [ __ ] bro?
With the food.
No. Someone only someone that's got no
life will do this every day.
Nothing going for themselves. No life, no money.
It's obvious, but only these kind of
people would do this.
>> Same as Terry, you know. Exactly the
same as Terry. [ __ ] Nothing really.
Just this Terry was on um yesterday
[snorts] till the early hours of the
morning trying to troll me. What a
sadder. He's got another account. These
people really really are sad on here.
really really sad and got alive.
Delivered my food. What happened? One second.
One second, please.
I couldn't be delivered my food when I
didn't even give them the pin.
It doesn't make sense.
They're saying that they've delivered
it, but they haven't delivered it. Huh?
me off ever ordering food again, bro.
Cuz I've literally just ordered food and
it says it's been delivered, but it has
not been delivered.
But it hasn't.
There's no way it can be delivered
because you have to give them a code.
You have to give them a code and only I
know the code.
The driver must have ate it because it
hasn't been delivered because they need
a code and I didn't give them a code.
and now I'm starving, [ __ ] hungry.
No way it could have been delivered
because they need a code and obviously I
haven't got the [ __ ] food.
I'm trying to get the refund.
What do you mean any bets? I've put I
put a bet on my [ __ ] community post.
You [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's always something, isn't it? It's
always something. Always [ __ ]
something about [ __ ] They didn't
deliver the [ __ ] food. How has it
been delivered? It has not been
delivered. There's no way it has been
How can it be delivered when you need a
code and I haven't got it?
>> This outside or something? >> No.
>> Yeah. I've got more money than you would
ever have. I've got more money than you
would ever have, you [ __ ] loser. I'll
prepare prepared to play the money game
again if you want. Yeah,
I've got more money than you will ever
have. You [ __ ] loser. Don't let me
start getting the 50s out again. Please
stop it, mate.
Don't make me start getting them 50s
out, you skin loser, and make you run
away again like you always do, you [ __ ] little.
Don't make [clears throat] me start
getting them 50s out, you [ __ ] ugly
Don't make me go to the bank and start
making you shut your skin mouth again. Benefit boy, [ __ ] loser. >> Right.
Definitely has not been delivered.
You [ __ ] little [ __ ] Low life.
This is why I'm coming off this
community. Because of these people,
these little low life, low IQ that come
here and create the same atmosphere
every day. This is why I'm coming off
this shitty community.
These little lowife little monks that
can't get off of YouTube to save their
life. Yeah. This is why I'm coming off YouTube.
my order from just
How could it have happened though?
Because I've got a code
with with with this. You have with Just
you need to give them a code. So, how
the [ __ ] has it been delivered when only
I have the code?
Because I I'm the only one with a code.
Doesn't make sense.
How with no food and I have to wait 7
days to get this refund. Well, I don't
think I'll be ordering from just eat again.
Then how is that possible when I'm the
one that everyone has their own code? I
have my code. So in order for it to the
delivery to be completed, I would have
had to give the code£23
down the [ __ ] drain and I don't even
have any food and I'm starving, you know,
madness. Absolute madness.
It was 2 minutes away, then he ended up
8 minutes away. Now, how would have been
complete if I didn't give the code? You
need the code to complete the um
delivery. I know I used to deliver food,
so I know exactly how it works.
I know exactly how it [ __ ] works.
Now, I'm going to have to sit here now
hungry. You know,
I don't think I'd be ordering from them
again then. [ __ ] that.
[clears throat] Unless you put where he
couldn't find the address or something. Yeah.
Yeah. Maybe he put where he couldn't
find the address or I don't know.
Well, his account will get banned. Yeah.
definitely hasn't been delivered. So,
uh, no, it wasn't. So, go away.
No, it wasn't.
So yeah, bye-bye little loser. Little Mongs. Yeah.
These people on YouTube are proper
proper mongs, aren't they?
They're proper mongs on here, aren't they, bro?
Let me call these [ __ ]
Little sad little sulking bastards.
Little mongos on here. That's what they
are. They're proper proper Mongs of this community.
Proper proper proper Mongs. See, I would
go to Turnpike Lane and and slap that
Terry up. But the same thing will happen
again, bro. Every time you go to meet
these little mongos, they don't show up.
This is why I don't waste my time. This
is why I don't waste my time with these
little low lives on here. Because every
time you go to their area, they do not
show up and no one says anything about
it. This is why I don't bother with
them. I I I don't even waste my time.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
You think I I don't want to go to turn
and slap the [ __ ] in. But we know every
single time what happens with these low
lives. That's why there's no point even
being on here.
You know what I mean, bro? with these
little lowife Mongs that ain't got a
life that you know what I mean bro
that's what I'm saying yeah
I'm going to get a refund anyways but >> [snorts]
>> these people are very sad on this community. Bro,
they need to get alive. >> [snorts] >> Ah.
Yeah. Okay. I'm getting the money back,
but I've got to wait like seven [ __ ] days.
Yeah. So, I'm getting the 23 pound back.
It could take seven days. Now, what do I
do? I'm sat here [ __ ] hungry and I
don't want to order from them again. now
cuz I'm scared the same thing will
happen and there's literally nowhere
open so I'm [ __ ] basically.
Yeah, pretty [ __ ]
Oh well, I just won't eat in it.
If that really was you from YouTube,
that's just sad because I'm getting the
money back. I mean, to be honest with
you, I was going to change my mind and
not go with Wendy's, to be honest.
But yeah, I was going to maybe change my
mind to be honest.
If that was you, that's just really
silly though, isn't it? Because I'm just
going to get the money back. They've
already informed me. So why why would
you even do that?
I don't think it was you. So I don't
think it was someone on YouTube, mate.
That's just sad. If it was, that's just
sad. What's the point of that when I'm
just going to get the money back? Again,
it shows their low life. Even saying
stuff like that, these people on here
ain't got a life. That's what I mean, bro.
They ain't got no life. Yeah,
>> but what's what what's the point of that
when they're just going to give the money back?
But they're just going to give the money
back. So what what what what's the point
of that though? I don't understand. But yeah,
yeah, I don't know, bro. I'm [ __ ] All
I know is I'm [ __ ] hungry. So yeah,
you The driver. Definitely.
Definitely something to do with the driver, bro.
I don't know, man.
What a life. E life.
Now I'm scared to order food again.
Pretty much. Yeah.
No, there's one thing I could get. Second.
I'm not going to tell these mongos.
Yeah, I know what to do. One second.
Virgin boy skin in his little bed sit
with no bed, no money in it. himself.
Yeah. One second, bro. Please.
A refund for that. Anyway, so that was
just silly to be honest.
That was just really, really silly.
if that was someone on YouTube.
But again, it shows their low life. One second.
One second, bro.
Ah, virgin boy
killing his little bed [ __ ] with no bed, no money.
bed. No [ __ ] money in it.
I'll show you the thing when it comes. Yeah.
You see when it comes lad
That doesn't make sense. 27.
One second. going to try to see what get it come.
There's no discount though, so how can there be?
People are such lowife mongs in this
community in it.
Proper, proper, bro. Proper No.
Why are they such Mongs on this
community? Steven Howard,
they're proper Mongs, aren't they? Oh no. That's why
I'm supposed to [ __ ] get I don't That
doesn't make sense. [gasps] [snorts]
What do you reckon would have happened
if I went out approaching today? Steven Howard,
what do you think would have happened, lad?
No, I don't know what I'm going to do, bro.
I wanted that but there's no deals on
and it's just ridiculous paying that
amount of Hey,
this this might not be. All right.
I don't know, bro.
I'm going to eat.
can't connect to the server. It says
so getting this is just
then it's not worth it.
I really need to start eating him, bro.
Yeah. Did you see my football bet? He got [ __ ]
>> I thought he was going to win me.
But I want a different um thing.
and bad. To be fair,
I think this is as best as we're going
to get it. Uh,
sick of this I am, bro. I'm really sick of this.
So expensive, isn't it?
So [ __ ] expensive, man.
No. One sec. It's like
expensive as [ __ ] bro.
And no deals on as well [ __ ] What? Large one. Let's
get some ice cream as well. H no
can't even take away.
You'll never pop it. You'll never pop
that virginity, mate.
You reckon I'll ever lose it, Steven?
How would finally finally get laid?
into Virgin Boy yesterday on my live. He Make
I ever had to pay
for something like that before. That
must be a [ __ ] new thing, bro.
That must be a new thing. I had to go on
like my [ __ ] online banking and [ __ ]
Yeah, I had to go on my [ __ ] uh online banking.
I do kind of feel bad though cuz look, I
got my hair done, bro. I spent a lot of
money getting my hair done
and I didn't even bother going out. But
doesn't really matter anyways cuz it
would always be the same here in it.
haircut, no haircut, looking good,
dressing good, looking [ __ ] dressing
[ __ ] It'll [snorts] always be the same
here, in it.
It'll always be the same here. So,
that's not really a big problem, is it? Yep.
It'll always be the same here. >> [snorts]
>> That man was telling me that his
friend's going to Thailand on Tuesday.
He said on Tuesday his friends going to be there.
I said, "Really?"
He calls him the pretty boy. You know,
there's like a pretty boy. I was like, "Oh, really?
That's crazy, bro." [snorts] Yeah. Is
that saying that everyone's going there now?
Well, duh. Cuz you can't get laid here.
You can't get a relationship here. So,
people are going there in it.
I was going to get I was going to have a
nice steak today, but yeah,
I was mad about that [ __ ] uh I know.
Oh, that woman showed up today. You
know, the one in Scotland,
she was actually legit.
I didn't even realize she was legit. She actually was.
She was actually there. She's like, "Oh,
I thought you was actually going to
come. I'll give you another chance." Wow.
That's insane, bro.
That's actually insane.
But she was [ __ ] stinking anyway. So, [snorts] yeah.
Wagging, stinking. [snorts]
Do you know who's another one that's got
no life on this community is Clint. No
life. Absolutely no life. If you go on
any um kind of live stream or whatever,
he's always there. He's always on
YouTube. There's not one day that he
ain't on YouTube. Again, equals no life.
Yeah. You'll see him on the Virgins. It
shows they've got no life that they
can't take a day off for YouTube. It
shows it, bro. It literally shows it.
And also, it's not just that they're on
YouTube every day. It's they're on
YouTube all day, every day. And then
you'll always see them on here cuz it's
all they have despite trying to talk
about other people.
Cuz you can go on YouTube 3 hours every
day if you wanted to. you know, wake up,
go to gym, cook some food, and at the
end of the day, you can go on YouTube.
But it's the way these people are on
YouTube every day. They got no life.
It's your job. Your life is your job.
I'll show you her. Look,
it was [ __ ] She's [ __ ] stinking, son.
I do feel bad to be honest. I wasn't
making her go on to wild goose chase. I
just didn't think she was going to show
up. But I didn't [ __ ] her around on
that, bro. She didn't do anything to me.
But the other one, she deserved it for
being a little passive aggressive [ __ ]
That's why I had her going around
everywhere cuz she was being a [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah,
[snorts] that's her. Anyways,
that's somebody I could be in a
relationship with if I wanted to. And other people.
That's what they say. you've not been in
a relationship even though I've had
several chances to be in relationships.
Several chances and they still think
that is having one over on you and it
really really is not because I have had
chances and having chances is as good as
being in one.
Simple. It's not a life experience. It's
not a necessity being in a relationship.
But I don't know why they seem to think
they've got more life experience because
they've been in a relationship with
that's not even a life experience. It's
not it's not like I said it's not even a
necessity being in a relationship. But
people still go on it on about it. You know,
they're always trying to put others
down. They need to look at their own
pathetic sad lives on here.
That's what they do. That's what they
need to do, bro.
Yeah, I should get that refund with him now.
So, they must have knew they [ __ ] up somewhere.
That's £40 I spent. I haven't even left
the [ __ ] house.
Mad. [ __ ] mad. Yeah.
And the more I think about like how much
I've tried in this country, the more I
don't want to try again, the more I
think, "Oh, it's just going to be the
same [ __ ] It's always going to be the
same shit." Cuz it is always going to be
the same [ __ ] here.
It's always going to be the same old in this country,
you know. So,
I was like, can't be bothered.
I won 100 pound on the rouette. Oh, I
just got my hair done and [ __ ] but
still not the Yeah.
Are you sure it would have been the same
old if I went out today?
Are you sure it would have been the same old?
It'll [snorts] always be the same here.
You know this.
Are you sure it would have been the same
old Steven Hard? You never know. I might have pulled
Yeah, I put 50 on the roulette the other
day. I got it to 150.
I hit like 20 and [ __ ] So, [snorts]
I got to 169. I took 150. Uh,
I wonder who that Ricky Millington is.
Steven Howard. Who that Ricky Millington?
Yeah. 50 to 150. I took it. It paid for
the hair and [ __ ] Had to get something
fixed on my phone as well. And I was
planning to go out today, but I just
can't do it anymore, bro. I don't have
the energy for it. It's tiring. It's boring.
It's depressing as well. So,
yeah, there's no point in it. But
yeah. Yeah. 50 to 150. Yeah. Then I lost
20 on the football today. So yeah,
I could go out tomorrow. Well, today,
but we're [snorts] going to have the
same problem again getting back to sleep
cuz my sleeping pattern's [ __ ]
My sleeping pattern is really [ __ ] up.
I probably won't bother to be honest.
It's a shame though cuz I got my hair
done and stuff. But like I said, it
doesn't matter anyways whether you got
your hair done or not. It's always going
to be the same here with women. So
yeah, [snorts] doesn't matter anyways, does it?
I said to this stupid [ __ ] on Instagram,
I'm going to send you my dick if you
keep ignore me cuz it's annoying.
You little snake.
They're going to get banned for typing
for [ __ ] seven days.
Stop ignoring me. It's annoying.
I'm just going to send her pictures of me masturbating.
I told you. Stop ignoring me. It's
[ __ ] annoying. your little rat
snaking little [ __ ] This [ __ ] was
talking to me on Reddit, bro.
And then all of a sudden, they just
stopped replying and it's been a it's
been a couple of weeks.
Seen seen seen seen seen. This is more
This is one of the reason another reason
why I don't bother with them cuz I
realize what they're actually like, what
women are like. So there's no point
bothering with them.
Women are [ __ ] evil. Rub it up. Rub
it up. They're [ __ ] evil. Women are
proper. Proper evil.
It's a shame, isn't it really? How
they're all the same and all evil. It's
bad, bro. [ __ ] proper bad.
I'm going to start sending her my [ __ ]
and my dick and that for being an ignorer.
I really, really am. Don't [ __ ] sit
there and start [ __ ] ignoring me, you little snake.
Yeah, they were like answering me and
that and then all of a sudden they just
keep seeing my message and not replying.
It's annoying. I don't even want them to
reply. I want them to block me. Stop
sitting there ignoring me. It's [ __ ] annoying. Block me
or something. Yeah, I'm just going to
send them my [ __ ] and that and like all
sorts of madness. Corn and that. It's
annoying as [ __ ] Proper proper proper annoying.
Yeah, women are evil. That's why I don't
bother with them.
That's why I don't bother.
I'd ra I'd rather have stayed in bed
today and just watch some GTA clips. I
was tired. I walked the dog and that and Yeah.
So yeah, man. [snorts]
Food should be here soon.
That's 40 pound.
That's 40 pound I spent today on food
and I haven't even received one of them,
but I should be getting money back. So,
who's the blonde?
Oh, just some
manta that wanted to meet me in Scotland.
Yeah, I was going to go out drinking
today, brother Dub, but I just figured
it's always the same with these women
here. Once you've met one, you've met
all of them. They're all the same.
So, I don't bother with them anymore.
All they do is lead people on and play
games or pretend they got boyfriends.
Nothing else they do.
There's literally nothing else that they do.
Always the same. That's why I do not bother.
>> [clears throat] >> Um,
I don't know. There was an issue, mate.
I don't know what the issue was, but
there was an issue. But they said
they're going to refund it in 5 to seven days.
I don't know how they could have
delivered it because only I had the pin.
That's That's what I don't understand, lad.
Yep. She said Oh, she messaged me saying
I'll give you another chance. That's
what she said to me. Grezy,
that's funny, bro.
No, another driver didn't take it. I
didn't get the food at all.
Yeah, I didn't get the food at all at all.
So, but I don't know how it could have
been completed when I'm the only one
that has the code. Doesn't make sense.
He was 3 minutes away, then he ended up
8 minutes away. How does that make sense
if you was following the satnav?
So, same [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
>> I don't know.
Yeah, women are all the same, but that's
why I don't bother with them no more.
They're all the same.
But I believe it until I see different.
They're literally all the same, rubber.
All of them are the same.
Pretend they have boyfriends, say
they're not interested, or lead people
on. The end.
Literally the end.
That's all that ever happens.
I'm back on Reddit now.
doesn't reply. I'm going to send her
pictures of my dick until she blocks me.
It's so annoying.
It's so [ __ ] annoying. Yeah.
The dating thing is [snorts] very very
toxic where dating is very very very
very toxic. That's why I gave up. You
get to a certain age and a certain point
where you think like you got to do
something different now. You got to
leave now. You know,
should have been a lot sooner. I admit
to myself, but you know, happens in it.
I'm a stubborn bastard. So I'm a
stubborn [ __ ] So I always I always
thought there was like hope,
you know, cuz I'm stubborn like that,
you know. I was stubborn for a long time.
50. I put 50 on the roulette uh on
Friday and I won 150. But I've been
winning the past couple of months with
the football. I won over five on the
roulette. So, I've just been saving
money that I've won. Really? Yeah.
Just been saving money. I've won.
And I got my haircut, which cost £60 cuz
I got a full service cuz every time I go
to the every time I go to the barbers,
which is like every month, I get a full
service to help my skin if my skin's
looking bad. And I owed like some So yeah,
cuz they have to split notes. So
yeah, I know. I do it like every month or so.
And I won the money and I was planning
to go out today, but there's no point.
You don't need to. You got your hair
done. You you you feel fresh. It doesn't
matter even if you don't go out. Yeah. What's it?
Even if you don't go out,
I gamble very very very rarely.
So yeah, just been building some nice
money up. Yeah,
but money is not even an excuse really.
I can go out and spend £300 and it
wouldn't it wouldn't affect me, but I
just don't want to waste.
It's always the same here. The food's on
its way. Can't wait.
You'll see what it is when it comes.
[snorts] But the only thing is I had to
get something. I had to add something. I
had to miss something I didn't like
because if I got it, it was it would
have been too expensive.
Like ridiculous because it doesn't cover the TNC's.
But it's all right anyways cuz then I
would have had to like do it from
scratch and it would have cost a lot of money.
Do you get what I mean? But if I stuck
to the uh deal, then it was only £16. [snorts]
Yeah, it was only £16, you see.
But if I added a thing, then I wouldn't
have been able to get a deal, you see.
So, it just wasn't worth it. I'd rather
just go without that.
I can't believe rubber dub. Do you know
who KSI is? Virgin boy don't know KSI
KSI. Virgin boy don't know the Sideman.
Virgin boy don't know One Direction. I
said, "Have you been living in a rock
under a rock?" Virgin boy.
He doesn't know any of these things. We
was talking about this um yesterday.
[ __ ] hell. How do you not know any of these people?
You skin [ __ ] you.
Nah. Nah. I was too tired. I was too
tired. I woke up at 11:00. I'm [ __ ]
My sleeping pattern's [ __ ]
If I If If I wasn't tired, I would have
went out today with my sister, but I
probably would have just got the meal
and then just went back and not drunk,
to be honest. Nah. Too tired.
Way too tired.
He wanted to [ __ ] She booked a hotel
with him. She must have money then, you know.
She's actually Canadian, but yeah. Nah. [snorts]
I'm done with women, matey. They're all the same. So, yeah.
And this little [ __ ] if they keep
ignoring me on Instagram, I'm going to
send them [ __ ] [ __ ] and dick [ __ ]
pictures until they block me. Stop
sitting there ignore me, you [ __ ] arrogant [ __ ]
You know, I [ __ ] hate women, bro. I'm
so glad I gave up in so many ways, but
I'm so glad I gave up and I never have
to deal with him ever again.
Oh, it's lovely. [snorts]
See, I don't I don't contradict anything
I say now cuz I don't try. So, no one
can say, "Oh, well, you're trying. I
don't try anymore." Cuz they're all the same,
literally. So, yeah.
I'm surprised people say women aren't
all the same when they are all the same.
They are literally all the [ __ ] the same.
Like they never grow up. The maddest
thing is they never mature. Even with
age, they never mature.
Yeah, he's a liar. We've been over this
already. He's a liar.
Like I think you know that Finnish
woman, she was two months younger than
me and they're still not growing up in
their head. So December, she was born in
December, I'm October.
So and a lot a lot of these people were
the same age as me. 27 28 and they still
lead people on. They still play games.
All women aren't the same.
Do I do a good impression of Virgin Boy?
They literally are exactly the same.
Same mannerisms, do the same stuff, same
excuses, same [ __ ] But they're not
all the same.
They're not all the same.
Yeah, man. They're not all the same.
You know, the way I see it, rubber dub,
is there's no point going out getting
more bad experiences
just in hopes of finding someone. Do you
know what I mean?
No point in it.
No point in it at all.
Yeah, this is a different way now. You
pay through your bank. That's weird.
That is odd, bro.
That's so weird. Hm.
I want my dinner and I want it now.
You can't do cash with this. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
I had some piggies earlier. Grezy, you missed it. Oh gosh.
Yeah, you missed it.
You just had dog food.
So, Robert, why are women all the same narcissists?
They're all the [ __ ] same, mate.
At least I can go back on Reddit. burning boys
in these little bag [ __ ] with no man no
money in it.
So anyways, Robert, why are women all the same? Huh?
They're all bad people in general.
They're bad people in general.
Mr. G used to say they're good people in
general. I say they're bad people in
general. Oh, you should have saw um
yesterday all the white knights
defending them. [ __ ] embarrassing.
All these little white knights.
I feel sorry for white knights, you know.
Sat there defending women all their
life. Virgins mad.
Yeah, women are all the same.
Did you watch my approaches? Rubber dub,
you can't even finish a [ __ ] sentence
without hearing, "I'm not interested or
I've got a boyfriend." But they say that
women go for personality.
They say women. Hey, listen, bro. Steven
Hour, do you want me to do something
when if Terry comes back on this
channel? Do you really want me to go to his area?
and stamp the [ __ ] all over?
I can do it if you want. If you if you
say the word, I I'll do it, mate.
and proper proper embarrass him. I can
do it if you want. No problem, bro.
And and get his face on camera and start
spitting at him. Spitting at his face,
saying, "Look at this manta. Look at
this manta." You know this. And the only
reason I don't do it, bro, is because
it's like whenever you go there, they
never show up and then they get away with it.
That's what happens. It's It's the same
thing every [ __ ] time,
you know? Every [ __ ] time. It's the same thing.
And I put his [ __ ] face all over
[ __ ] YouTube and and call him the
[ __ ] ugly short muz
I would do him bad. That's what I'm
saying, bro. Like, I will go there and I
would actually do him bad. I'll take his
trainers off and everything, bro. I I
would do him bad, bro. worse than prime.
I'll do it dirty, you know. Do you want
to do you want to have a drink or do you
want to do it dirty? [laughter]
Do you remember that one, Grezy? Do you
want to have a drink or do you want to
do it bad? [laughter]
But I'm being serious, bro.
What do you think would happened if I
went out approaching women today? 14 Maxwell H
Monty says that no one goes for Nonlegs
because Nonlex goes for me. That's not
true because even if I don't come on
here, there's only like two people that
go for him. Shaggo and maybe Harry.
No, no, no, no, no, no. Even when I'm
not on here, people don't go for him cuz
they like nonses. And he is a nons.
He's a low life. That's what nods legs.
He's a [ __ ] low life. S on YouTube
every day. No life.
Wanting to go around in circles with people.
Fragile ego. Like I said, fragile ego.
What do you reckon would have happened?
Right. Could be up here. I'm hoping it is.
It is cold out there, bro. Very cold.
Oh, here we go, lads.
Why would you call me, bro? Oh yeah. No,
if I [ __ ] with no money or that, I would
think twice about it, man.
I was speaking about
but I'm not a virgin. M
got some Pepsi as well.
Seems like I think so.
[ __ ] bro, you [ __ ] virgin.
Yeah. So I didn't get stuff plus because
if I got stuff plus
it would have been over 30 because the
deal I got this piece for 16 but I
couldn't get stuff with it and fall into
TNC's so but
it doesn't matter anyways
stuff is a lot better but it's all right.
It would have been like ridiculous
amount of money. M.
So, do you want to go for a drink or do
you want to do it dirty?
You want to do it bad? M
you think I'll finish Where is it?
I've been having this picture since
I was about 13.
They've had the same picture since about 13.
But stuff is a lot better. But if I had
stuff, I'm sure I'd be able to finish it.
You haven't tried prop
Yeah. How many have this This place
They're not appens. trick.
He said it was trying to for me because
it was sending them the other way. So
maybe there was a problem with the delivery driver. actually
I don't know if I can finish all of this dude.
I don't know about that. [ __ ] me.
I might have to save I might have to
save the other half for later.
That's a lot, bro.
But you can microwave pizza. So, you
know, you can save it for later.
[ __ ] hell, man.
Them onions. I love it. Onion bombs.
I just told you before you die. Am
I doing good?
Come on. Doing good. Yeah.
So we don't have again little copycat.
No mind of your own. [snorts]
If you don't like sh movie
I'm a copycat. I'm following the crowd.
Who am I being? Who am I being? No.
I'm in the bus as well.
If you don't,
you can't deny she's attractive.
Do not sound like
you're gay, brother.
You're gay. Rob is gay. Everyone
it's not it's not cocon
if you don't like cocat
like music we'll copy Copy that.
Copy the trend. Pop in the copy.
I'm going to keep trying.
Oh, this got bas. Oh, it's got pictures.
I reckon to do this to make up for when
his mom star him. [ __ ] Look, I'm doing this exercise.
Yeah, my fat now.
>> [clears throat] >> M now
it was just
I get you because
with SH you should probably have about
you could have probably have about four slices
maximum because of the cheese in the
crust is very thin. So you can't Yeah.
If if it stop you Hey,
are you [ __ ] there?
Are you dead? attractive attractive mate.
What you find objective? Yes. [ __ ]
One, two, four.
That is good. Good.
I can eat this last crust bit and that's
me done until later. [ __ ] me. I really
thought I was going to finish it.
So if it was stuff crust
right then no hair you should do it.
It's getting cold now though. That's the thing.
If it was stuffed crust. Nah, I don't
think anyone in the world could do that,
bro. Unless they're like the world's
strongest man. What do you think, Grezy?
A whole p extra large pizza stuff? Nah,
I'm stuck, bro. I can't eat anymore. How about that? Nah,
not stuff close. Nah,
no. No way. I I wonder if LC could do it. I really,
don't forget this is an extra extra large pizza.
You have to go a day without food. Nah,
even then you wouldn't be able to do it.
Nah, no, no, no, no, no. What? XXL pizza stuffed crust.
That's Papa John's. Nah, mate. Nah, not
Papa John's. Not stuffed crust. I think
Yeah, I think you could I think you
could do it without the stuffed crust
cuz I've only left four slices there.
But with stuff uh with the stuffed grass n
I think that would be very cuz don't
forget the stuff grass adds adds fat to it.
It's called a barbecue chicken from Papa
John's. It's been going for years.
Stuffed crust is good, but like I said,
it was going to be too expensive.
If I got the stuff crust, you're talking
over30 because I got it in a deal and
the deal excludes stuff crust.
So, the the deal excludes stuff crust.
That's why I didn't get the stuff crust
and I don't want to be paying over 30
for pizza. But yeah, but I don't think
many people would be able to do it with stuff crust.
XXL is XXL. Sure.
Yeah. XXL original XXL bar.
I reckon I could finish it if I really wanted to
but not not with stuff. Nah, I'm done at
about four. Bro,
I'd like to see somebody that could
finish it with stuff. I don't think many
people could, bro, to be honest.
Yeah, try it.
Try it, bro. But have get stuff plus cuz
the stuff bust is better. The stuff is very good.
I'm going to be a fat [ __ ] now. [snorts]
Just making friends.
Why don't you like shovel co?
Huh? Are you gay?
Why don't you like Sher C? Huh?
Why the [ __ ] don't you like Sher C?
Why don't you like her? You can't What?
You going to deny she's attractive?
You can't deny she's attractive. Where's
Virgin boy when I need him?
Nah, you're gay, babe. You must be gay.
You're denying that she's attractive.
You're trying to say that she's not attractive, mate. You're gay.
You know the other women that I've been
with that are better looking than her,
you can dislike them. That don't make
you gay. But as soon as you don't like
Sh gay, mate, [ __ ] gay. All the other
women that I've been with, you don't
like the look of them. Okay, that's
fine. But as soon as it's sh
like a trend, doesn't it?
Make myself a cup of [ __ ] now. Yep.
Making myself a lovely couple of time. Oh.
Oh, [ __ ] me [ __ ] man. Magic boy.
>> Yeah, man. I got four slices.
Yeah, I got four slices. [ __ ] me.
[ __ ] me, mate.
You're going to pop it then
[snorts] you're going to lose it.
>> You reckon you're going to lose it.
Virgin B. Yeah. Four sliced then. He
almost [ __ ] killed me. That did
that bastard I am.
Where's the lanky little [ __ ] M.
We're waiting for him. He's not blocked
on the channel. Come and get that little
lanky skin [ __ ] in here.
That little skin flint. Huh?
Yeah. Thank you, man. Thank you. The
lady would never be able to do that. No
way. No way.
Next time I'll do it. If I start going
to the gym, I made myself really hungry.
I think I could do it. Can someone get a
skint lanky virgin in here with no bed,
no [ __ ] money? We need some [ __ ]
We need to uh
have a little combo here.
Why you think it's acceptable to be a
31y old virgin with no bed, no [ __ ]
money? Why you think it's acceptable, Sam?
I want to know why you [ __ ] think is
acceptable. You skidf. [snorts]
Isn't that right? Just making friends.
Greasy. Just making friends.
That's cute. Is it? [snorts]
It's It's the name, not the person. It's
It's the [ __ ] name.
It's the [ __ ] name, mate.
You don't like the show.
What a [ __ ] copycat. And you said
that you don't copy people. You don't copy that.
I always prefer dogs.
That's why I've always preferred dogs. Me.
Never been into cats.
Never ever really been into cats to be
honest with you, Steven Howard. Never. Never have.
Never. Just never been into cats.
It's never been inconscious
looked it up though in his version. He
probably looked it up right and saw the
trend and thought I got to copy it. Go home. >> Yeah.
I've got I've got a copy. I've got a
copy. Got a copy. Got a copy. Copy.
Got a copy, mate. Got a copy, mate. Got
a copy. Got a copy. Got a copy. Got a
copy. That's probably what you said, is it, mate?
Bing the ground. Wanted to fit in there. Yeah.
Oh, my [ __ ] neck's going to hurt me, bro. [snorts]
Should I go out for some drinks
tomorrow? Not Steven Howard. Nah,
it's no point. It's the same old. It's boring.
All women aren't the same.
Nah, [ __ ] that, bro.
Do you think you'd even get numbers on a Sunday? Yeah.
Of course you would.
Monday is the day. Yeah. Is it? [ __ ]
Do you think it's bad I don't go out
drinking anymore? Greasy.
Do you think it's bad?
I don't go out drinking and approaching anymore. Yeah,
it's not a teenager. Some woman that
wanted to meet me.
Oh, I feel like [ __ ] after eating that pizzay.
Oh, I'm stuffed.
I am stuffed. Yeah.
No, she's not. She's a woman. [laughter] Uh,
well, you trying to say she looks like
that [ __ ] virgin, that skin virgin. [ __ ] hell. Yeah. Right,
let me go on YouTube. One sec.
What the [ __ ]
What website is this? Greasy.
Huh? There's no way.
Dude, that's the same website that
[ __ ] Timmy Aldridge is on. [laughter] [clears throat]
There's no way, Grizz, dude. Cuz look,
there's no way. What?
There's no way.
>> There's no way.
You see that channel? The Five Great Guys.
Have you seen the channel The Five Great Guys? Grezy. One sec.
Oh, the gray guys. Yeah.
Do you want to do you want to go for a
drink or do you want to do it bad? Huh? [snorts]
So, it's not letting me [ __ ] do it.
sign in to be able to [ __ ]
do it, man. It's annoying [clears throat]
other ways to sign in.
Why' I have to make an account to get
up? I'm not doing that.
Let me see. Money man and Tim Eldridge. One sec. Monty.
Oh, look. When I type Monty, man, look.
Look what comes up.
What the [ __ ] But KSI is on this website, huh?
Monty man and Tim.
What the [ __ ]
There we go.
Oh, here we go. Look. >> [laughter]
>> down today. Oh no.
You want to do his [laughter]
camera on? Turn the camera on. [laughter] >> [laughter]
>> You're going to get >> [laughter]
>> Let's have a drink this.
It's not chilly
It's nothing to do with nothing. [laughter] >> [laughter]
>> You're going to get
that trouble. Do you want trouble or not?
Do you want trouble or not, bro? [laughter]
>> He told him to come around the corner. >> [laughter]
>> put the camera on lad.
>> Did you hear Jaden?
And then right
if you two seconds after this right right look Hey, [laughter]
say you want to come inside my clubhouse. >> See? That's what me. [laughter] Look,
Goofy. Where's Goofy?
There he is. Donald Donald. [laughter]
There's no way that could be the same website.
There's no way, you know. It needs to be monitored.
It needs [laughter] to be monitored,
doesn't [clears throat] it? It needs to be monitored.
It needs to be monitor. This is a [ __ ] up community. Yeah, man.
It's uh 55 in
Yeah, I just sent this [ __ ] um picture
of my dick.
She was being an annoying ignorer.
I bet we'll get a reaction, won't it, Grizzy?
They sure respond to negativity. They're
all the same. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, they're all the [ __ ] same.
I might send her a picture of my [ __ ] as well.
I just want to be blocked. I don't want
someone to sit there looking at my messages.
I want someone to just block me, you know?
stop [ __ ] I was talking to her from
Reddit like a month ago. Greasy
and all of a sudden she just started ignoring.
I'm thinking, huh?
Being a [ __ ] so I'll be a [ __ ] back.
Oh, I'm under the little blankie, Grezy.
Oh, the little electric blankie.
this is much better than going out drinking. Oh, lovely.
I want King to come upstairs, but he
won't stay up.
Oh, he's cute. This is lovely Lanky, isn't it? Yeah.
So, what are you going to do, Greg? Are
you going to try and find a woman or
do you like my TV, Steven Howard?
I just had a lovely peach candy man and
this woman's been ignoring me on
Instagram. So, I just sent her two
pictures of my dick
cuz she's being an annoying ignorer and
I want her to block me. I want to be
blocked. I don't want somebody sat there
looking at my messages just being a
[ __ ] you know.
Oh, yeah. She said she'd give me another
chance to meet me this one in um Scotland, but yeah, mate. Yeah.
Who the [ __ ] is that?
Is that the virgin in the picture?
Is that the skin virgin in the red suit?
Yeah. Terry is not about that life.
Terry is not about that life at all
at all. At all.
He's a sausage.
That's what that Terry is. A [ __ ] sausage. Right.
I didn't abuse her friends.
I didn't abuse her friend. I didn't
I was talking [ __ ] about women. She
found she saw me talking [ __ ] about women
like from ages ago. I didn't abuse anyone's friends.
I didn't abuse her friends. I was just
talking [ __ ] about women.
Yeah. My sister went out with her friend
today and I wasn't there. Yeah. [ __ ]
So, you actually Okay. So, was you
taking the piss earlier when you said
the women in this country are stuck up?
Cuz I know they're stuck up.
I think. Yeah, they are stuck up.
Nope. It's a Samsung.
Samsung something. It is. Yeah.
Were you being serious? I was being serious.
But my hair still looks fresh and that
what should I do tomorrow? Nothing.
Yeah, women are stuck up here.
That's what some of the on Reddit said.
Too many stuck up [ __ ] in your
country. I'd imagine after seeing my approach videos.
Nah, I'm good, bro. I'm all right.
You said it was going to be the same old [ __ ]
But you said it was going to be the same old [ __ ]
That's what you said. You said it was
going to be the same old.
That's what you said. Yeah.
It will always be the same old
in this country maybe tomorrow.
No, I don't think I'll bother
cuz it's always the same [ __ ] Candy
man, same old.
It's just the same old
Yep. Nothing works. No, nothing.
Yeah, but you're you're the one that
said that women are stuck up in this
country as well. It wasn't just me. You
said it, too.
You also said it as well.
You said it as well, though.
Yeah, you said it too.
Yeah, they are stuck up [ __ ]
Yeah, man. Something like that. Oh, heat.
I'm going to sleep again soon.
We're going to sleep.
I'm tired now. you after that pizza.
Okay. What is it with these Reddit mods
needing that power?
Grezy, what is it with them needing that power? H. Yeah.
I can't believe Greavves is older than me.
Greavves, are you really older than me? Yeah.
People on Reddit say you're going to meet someone
Gregy, why do people on Reddit say that
you're going to meet someone? Huh?
Why do people on Reddit say you got to meet someone? Huh? Graves. today. Yeah. Heat.
I have none.
I'm going to go sleep. Yeah, [ __ ] So,
see you tomorrow. Pety's going back to
sleep after that big pizza.