I got them to um I got that woman to
block me in the end. Yay.
I started uh spamming her [ __ ] Instagram page.
She's like, "Get therapy." I said, "You
need to get therapy and stop ignoring
people, you stuck up cunt." [ __ ]
annoying bastard. I knew I was getting
the [ __ ] to block me. I spammed the
whole page, bro.
[ __ ] absolute [ __ ] Now I'm
banned for [ __ ] typing for seven days.
Seven [ __ ] days, man.
That's what they do. They're cowards.
They're all snakes. They're rats. These
women, bro. Snakes and [ __ ] rats.
Why would I go to Sweden or Norway?
Why would I go there? Oh, [ __ ]
There we go.
No thank you, bro. There's enough stuck
up [ __ ] here. I don't need to go to
another place where they're stuck up. No thanks.
Women are all the same everywhere but
[ __ ] Asia. This woman's from South
America who I just got to block me. She
started being a [ __ ] so I spammed her
whole [ __ ] page.
They're [ __ ] rats, bro. They are rats.
They really are.
My friend just messaged me as well and I
can't even reply back to him
cuz I'm bound for seven days.
You know, I this is what puts me off
going out, bro.
You know, I always keep saying, "Oh, I'm
going to go out. I'm going to go out.
I'm going to try. I'm going to
approach." And I say it and I always end
up not going out, bro. Because the more
you deal with them, you realize all
women are the same.
And that's why you don't bother. That's
why I always end up like just like not
bothering cuz they're all the [ __ ] same. So
I've been saying, bro, I'm going to go
out for the past 6 weeks and I ain't done it.
Bye-bye. Self projecting. [snorts] Um
I've been saying it for the past 6 weeks
since I last went out
and I haven't been out. I haven't tried
cuz it's just they're all the same.
I keep saying I'm going to do it, but I
never end up doing it. You know,
because women are all [ __ ] same.
They're all rats. They're all snakes.
Whether it be Reddit, whether it be [ __ ]
And you'll never meet them on the street
either. You'll never meet them on a
train. You'll never meet them anywhere
cuz they're all the [ __ ] same.
I was speaking to this woman on Reddit
like over a month ago was talking and
she started ignoring being a [ __ ] and
she didn't block me. She kept going on a
message. I was I'm going to keep
messaging this [ __ ] until they block me
until they [ __ ] until this [ __ ]
blocked me. I'm going to keep spamming
them until they block me, bro.
And I and they did. I spam the whole
page. Stop. Don't sit there and [ __ ]
ignore me. You're the one that needs
therapy. You're sick in the head. Who
the [ __ ] Who the [ __ ] sits there
sits there right and ignores someone all
day on purpose? You You're the one that
needs therapy. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] And this is why I don't bother
with them no more, bro. This is
generally why I don't bother with them.
They're all the same. All women are the
same, bro. That's why I don't come as you know.
Bro, why are we talking about this? I
don't give a [ __ ] I'm going [ __ ]
Thailand next month, man. I don't give a
[ __ ] about any of this [ __ ] You know,
I'm [ __ ] going Thailand, bro.
I'm out of here next month.
What do you mean? No, man. I literally
I'm going to Thailand next month.
That's the only place. And even some of
them are [ __ ] there as well now as
well. Yeah. But that's only place.
You're the one that needs therapy. Sat
there [ __ ] ignoring people [ __ ]
for God knows how long.
Stupid [ __ ] Shouldn't reply when I spam
their page though. Is it [ __ ]
[ __ ] Now I'm banned for seven days.
They're [ __ ] snakes.
Yeah. All they care about is money.
That's like most women. All they care
about is money.
Anyways, I'm not talking about this, bro.
I can't be asked.
Can't be [ __ ] So yeah.
That's where we're at, aren't we?
Stuck up [ __ ] here, man.
Stuck up [ __ ] in uh England.
You're the one that needs to go to therapy.
No, they're not, mate. They're the same.
I've met loads of European women. I've
met women from all over the world.
They're all the same.
Doesn't matter. They're from [ __ ]
America, Poland, Australia.
They are all the same.
Why do you think I sound so stable
nowadays, bro? Why do you think I sound
so [ __ ] calm? Because I don't deal
with them anymore.
As soon as I stop dealing with them, my
life I I feel 100 times better.
The peace, the quiet, no. Cuz when
you're dealing and I explain this, I'll
explain this to you. When you deal with
these women, it's toxic. When you deal
with dating, it's toxic. Like it No, no.
It generally generally in is mixed with
alcohol and that [ __ ] And when you
finally get away from it, you feel so much better.
You feel so much better, bro. I I did
anyways. I do. So,
I don't know about you, but yeah. Dude, you toxic
when I need to go to therapy. [ __ ]
sat there ignoring people, you know?
I sent her my dick. [ __ ] I was going
to send her [ __ ] and everything. Don't
[ __ ] sit there and [ __ ] ignore me,
you stupid [ __ ] You know,
don't [ __ ] sit there and [ __ ]
ignore me, you little [ __ ]
Yeah, that's what I'm saying to you,
bro. It's toxic. That's why I quit.
That's why I like
I remove myself from the situation, bro,
because it's just toxic. That's
literally what it is.
And the more I think about it, the more
I don't ever want to try ever again.
That's what I mean. It is mad. It is madness.
It's weird how they have you noticed
it's weird how they just switch
gent that's another thing that that
seems to happen is that you'll speak to
them for a day
maybe two days maybe one day whatever
and then they it's like they switch
does that make sense it generally feels
like they just like it's like a like
pick thing they did. They just switch.
It's madness, isn't it, bro? That's what
makes me think they're not mentally stable.
I don't know if you've experienced that.
They like I was speaking to this one on
Reddit and then all of a sudden the next
day they'll just completely ghost you.
Like dumb. Like it's it's [ __ ] weird.
Like say like I explain say for example
you're speaking to someone on Reddit
or whatever and you say good night good
night and you're trying to message them
the next day and they've just like they
disclose to you. It's weird bro.
Here today gone tomorrow. It's like they
switch depending on the day.
If you have a [snorts]
Yeah, it's madness. It is madness.
Oh, it is over, bro. That's why I'm
going Thailand. It definitely definitely
is over. And if you watch my videos, you
would know it's over. again. Someone
that's dismissed my struggles.
Well, it clearly is over.
Have you not watched my videos? My
approaching videos? My dating app
Guess you just missed that cuz it didn't suit you.
Did you not watch the approaching videos
that I put up? No, didn't didn't suit you.
Didn't suit you. Nah,
it didn't suit you, did it?
Nah, my videos don't suit you. [laughter] One
Sorry about that, bro. Bye-bye.
Huh? What are you talking about, man?
Sorry, bro. I was [ __ ]
these women are [ __ ] man. Oh man. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. So, the more more you think about it,
I say to man, I say to you like every
other week, I'm going to go out and I
just never end up doing it cuz the more
you think about it, you just think
there's literally no point, bro.
Honestly, there's there there's no point
in it. It's always going to be the same
here, you know. So, pointless.
It really is. Yeah. Yeah, man. I'm sorry.
You're nice, bro. You're nice.
Maybe I won't go out Friday.
The more you speak to them and the more
you deal with them, the more you don't
want to ever deal with them ever again
in your life cuz they're all the same.
You know what I mean?
You're the one that needs to go to third
bee, coward, and then they [ __ ]
report you and you can't text for
[ __ ] seven days.
Same old [ __ ] Same old [ __ ]
Same old boring [ __ ]
[ __ ] anymore here, bro.
I feel a [ __ ] the terror. Yeah, man.
Women are [ __ ] snakes, Bob.
Women or snakes?
How did Saturday go? Well, I didn't go out. So, yeah.
I said I was going to go out this
Friday, but I don't think I will. See,
this is the thing. I always keep saying
I'm going to go out, but the more you
think about your bad experiences and the more
you speak to women, the more you realize
that they're just all the same. And like
there's like no point in even going out
trying and dealing with them. It's
toxic. I like the peace. I like the
quiet. This is peace and quiet, bro.
That's what I like in my life now. Peace and quiet. Um, yeah.
So, I don't think I'll be going out this week either.
More you speak to them, the the more you
realize how toxic they actually are.
I just had one on Instagram. She was
ignoring me, bro. And I kept spamming
her, spamming her, spamming her. I w
going to stop until she blocked me. She
just sat there ignoring like a [ __ ]
Someone from Reddit
and then they they sent me a thing
saying go to therapy. I said you're the
one that needs to go therapy. Sat there
[ __ ] ignoring people, you [ __ ] scumbag.
And then that's one of the reasons why I
don't try anymore, bro.
Like that. I mean, that's an example
cuz you realize they're all the same.
Well, it doesn't work in bars and clubs
either. So, and dating apps don't work.
So, that's that.
Yeah, she was being a [ __ ]
I was spamming her [ __ ] uh Instagram, bro.
I think it's so weird, Bob. Like you
will speak to a woman
and then the next day they like
completely change. Have you noticed that?
Because I got a life and I was doing stuff.
We don't all have time to be on here
[ __ ] every day.
um you realize that like
one minute one day they're like cooling
that and then the next day they like
completely switch. Have you noticed that
it's mad like they literally
they literally like switch up the next day
they're like all well and good the next
like they speak to you like yeah and
then the next day they completely ghost
or they just had like a [ __ ] like that
one on Instagram.
They're never stable. You know what I mean?
So obviously women are all the same
because men don't do that.
Not to sound [ __ ] gay or anything,
but like it's
they're obviously all the same. What the
[ __ ] I don't know how much more
evidence you you need, but
yeah. I don't think I'll be going out
this week either.
I like the quiet life.
And since I've quit this dating and
that, I've had no toxicity.
It's just been peaceful and quiet.
No [ __ ] you know? And that's all
you ever get when you deal with women is
a load of [ __ ] and toxicity.
Toxicity. That's all you get
mixed with [ __ ] anxiety and [ __ ]
It's not worth it, bro.
It's not worth it at all. [ __ ] no.
It's a madness.
A [ __ ] absolute madness.
It's not about game. I've got a game.
I've got a game. It's not about that.
They're just not interested
thanks to social media. It's not about
game. It's never been about game.
If you're not their physical type, they
won't even give you a chance.
It's not about game, bro. They either
like you or they don't. Trust me, I've
been doing this [ __ ] a very, very, very long time, you know?
I don't care about it anymore anyways, bro. So,
but it's weird how they switch.
That's that is a big thing with them.
They do switch.
How can you be all hunky dory speaking
to someone then the next that you good
night good night and then the next day
when someone tries messaging you going to weird.
That's why I'm like if I if I ever speak
to someone I'm oh yeah they're going to
[ __ ] me over the next day. Like it's
just typical now. You you expect it.
There was one in New Zealand before.
She's like, "Oh yeah, we'll suck your
dick." And all flirting. Had her on
Snapchat. Next day, you know. Um,
never heard from her again.
Who's the one that needs therapy?
[ __ ] s they're ignoring someone. I
ain't got a life. Yeah,
they really are [ __ ] in it, Bob
Bills. The more you think about it,
they really, really are [ __ ]
Um, well, no, there was a couple of
reasons for that. Um,
I'll get there. You keep telling
yourself that, mate, cuz I'm going
Thailand next month. So, you keep
telling yourself I'll get there. I've
heard it all before. Anyways, uh, to
answer your question, I didn't even
think they were going to meet me
because there's a valid reason why I
didn't think they were going to show up.
And I didn't have them going on a wild
goose chase either. So, no, it's not
evil. I thought they were [ __ ] me
over. And there was a reason for that. So
I thought they were standing me up and I
didn't believe them and I still don't
because of her friend. So yeah,
but I wasn't [ __ ] with her on
purpose. I just didn't think she was serious.
The other one I was [ __ ] with. Oh
yeah, I had her going everywhere. She's a [ __ ]
Just like that one on Instagram. A complete [ __ ]
So here today, gone tomorrow, gone by
[ __ ] magic. I wouldn't expect anything
different from them. They're all [ __ ] same.
It's toxic. So toxic. No.
No, basically what happened is um I was
speaking to this person in Scotland and
they wanted to meet me, but I had only
been speaking to them for 5 days. So I
thought, "Oh yeah, they're [ __ ] with
me." Because her friend gave her my
number and her friend said she's never
speaking to me again because of stuff
I've said about women. She said, "Oh,
I've seen everything you've said." head.
So, naturally, you'd think someone's
just gone come out the blue contacting
you, wants to meet you within 5 days.
Naturally, you think that they're
they're [ __ ] with you, in it. They're
trying to set you up. That's what I
thought. But I And then I said, "Oh,
yeah, come then." Because I thought like
they would say, "Oh, I'm not really
there." No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Of
course, I thought they were going to
[ __ ] me over. Who wouldn't?
Someone just messages you out of the
blue within five days they want to meet you.
So that wasn't done on purpose.
That was not done on purpose at all. Yeah.
And I've had that done to me before when
I went to Nottingham, but I just made a
night out of it.
Bit like she did with the [ __ ] hotel.
She's obviously got money, so you know,
but yeah, they do switch. That is a
thing with them. They do switch. Like if
you speak to them on the same day,
they're not going to be like that the
next day. I've noticed that with them.
So there's just no point.
Yeah, maybe. But they're [ __ ] stinking.
And I still don't trust it.
But it said all the way in Scotland.
[ __ ] So I genuinely thought they were
trying to [ __ ] me over. No, bro.
Bro, I'm not going to Scotland.
I ain't going to Scotland, bro.
Somebody would have to be really good
looking for me to go all the way there. [ __ ] that.
But yeah, they're they're [ __ ]
cuz they change. I noticed that they
What do you mean it's bad? As in it's
cold. The cold doesn't bother me.
Yeah, she's not going to come to me
obviously, idiot. Especially not now.
But yeah, that one on Instagram, she's a
[ __ ] I was sending her my dick and
everything. I said, "Don't [ __ ] sit
there and ignore me, you ignorant cunt."
And that's somebody from South America
as well. You're the one that needs
[ __ ] therapy, you [ __ ]
That's what I mean. It's toxic. You
understand? They're [ __ ] [ __ ] them, bro.
I probably won't go out Friday, to be
honest. Same old [ __ ] I don't even know
why I keep saying I'm going to go out.
I'm I feel like I'm just lying to
myself, bro. Cuz I hope I'm ever going
out here again. Generally
generally don't think so, man. Generally don't.
But there's a woman on Reddit that's 30
and she claims that she can't find
anyone. Now, I've been looking into
this, right? And apparently, yeah, she
said that she lives in London and she
can't find any single man. N. Now, I'm
28 and she's 30. So, let me see if when
I message her tomorrow cuz I can't be
bothered today. Let's see what she says.
If she really can't find someone
and she's claiming she can't find
someone, okay, well, I will show you how
unrealistic their standards are because
I'm going to message that person cuz I
live in London also. And I'm going to
say to them, let's go for a meal. Not
even drinking, no drinks, just go for a
nice meal just like cuz I don't want
anything out of it. and and we'll see
what this person comes out with, if they
come out with anything at all.
And then you can't complain
because you live in London. Uh you live
in London like me. So I live in London.
You live in London. There's no excuse.
You know, you said you can't find
someone. You're trying to find someone.
Um and you want a family and stuff.
Well, we'll see, won't we?
See, that's the difference. If somebody
was trying to meet me in London, I would
meet them. I would meet them because
that I was supposed to meet that woman
from uh Malaysia. Uh that Malaysian
woman. I'm trying to meet that Malaysian
woman. W woman.
And I don't really that into Asian, but
I would meet anyone that wants to meet
me in London, bro.
So, [snorts] she has no excuse. I
thought this woman was going to [ __ ] me
over to the friend and it's all the way
in Scotland. So, let's see what [ __ ]
excuse this woman comes out with.
Why she can't meet me? Huh?
Cuz what am I? I'm average. Yeah. Let's
just say I'm average looking. Okay. So,
that's like an average woman who's not
fat in London trying to meet me and then
me not meeting them. You'd all tell
you'd all tell me that I've got no right
to ever complain again. No. It's the
same that goes for women.
So, let's just say I'm average looking,
whatever. Yeah. Normal looking. So,
you're just a normal looking person.
Okay. Well, who looks after themsel? Yeah. Right.
So you've got no excuse then
considering I've been I've been with
below average looking women. So you got
no [ __ ] excuse.
And people want to sit there and say,
"Well, what would you do if a below average woman
approached you?" Well, guess what? They
didn't. I approached [ __ ] them.
So you can't [ __ ] tell me nothing.
So, we'll see what this woman says. And
she lives in London as well. I've got
her account. See what they're saying.
>> If she came to London, I would have I
would meet her. If she had come to
London, I would have because I
[clears throat] know my city and it's
very unlikely I'm going to get set up
there whereas I don't know people in Scotland.
You get me, bro.
They're all [ __ ] bro. They're all
One second. Anyways, I'm coming back.
Yeah, man. So, so sorry about that.
I don't think I'll eat today, you know, bro.
But yeah, it is it is toxic.
I mean, I'm 28 and I can't even find
someone that doesn't play games.
It's mad. People sit there and say we're
close to 30 now.
I'm getting addicted to the peace and
quiet, bro. I don't want it to end.
No mind games, no makebelie boyfriends,
no leading on. Oh, it's so nice. It's so
good. You know what I'm saying? It's
feels so good. None of that toxic [ __ ]
I feel like I'm on holiday.
It's that mad. I actually feel like I'm
on holiday, bro. It's madness.
It's lush. Absolutely lush.
I'm going to get a Frenchy a French fy,
bro. Just live my life with a little
woof. I'll be I'll be happier, man. Oh
yeah, Grezy. So,
this woman uh was
ignoring me on Instagram
still and I was like, I'm not going to
stop until this [ __ ] blocks me. Um, so
this is basically what I wrote on a picture.
I told you I weren't going to stop until
the [ __ ] block me. You're not going to
sit there and ignore me, ignorant [ __ ]
We were just talking about a greasy. Do
you find it strange how you will speak
to a woman,
right? This is another thing I've never
spoke about before.
Maybe I'll talk about this on a video is
you'll be speaking to someone, right?
And normal chat. You're normal, they're
normal. and you'll wish and you'll wish
each other good night and then the next
day you never hear from them ever again.
They completely like switch like there's
no stability, there's no consistency.
It's like no gone.
Like it's like a completely different person.
Have you not Have you noticed that?
That's another thing I noticed with with
women and dating.
Here today, gone tomorrow.
I'd be very very surprised.
I mean, I I don't know what else you can
describe them as other than [ __ ]
But like there's there's there's nothing
else. I was just spamming words, Grezy.
And she says, "Oh, get therapy." I said,
"You're the one that needs therapy." Sat
there ignoring people like an ignorant [ __ ]
And then she reported me on Instagram
and I got banned for seven days from
typing. And this is exactly what I mean.
It's It's toxic. You know what I'm
saying? And I don't even need to go out experience this.
You know what I mean? I've experienced
it before where they've like been
[ __ ] and they're cowards and then
when you give it them back, they report
you on Instagram. This is why I don't
bother anymore, Greavves. This is why I
don't go out.
I always say I'm going to go out, but I
never end up doing it. I'm going to go
out. I'm going to go out. But the more
you think about it, or like in this
case, you deal with a [ __ ] you realize
there's no point, it's toxic.
Okay. Yeah. Okay. You don't go out and
try. Yeah. You might be a bit lonely.
Yeah. You might not get sex, but it's
worth it to get peace and quiet.
It's way worth it.
Way worth it dealing with that [ __ ] Trust me.
It's madness, bro. Madness.
Yeah. I think I'd rather work to be
honest than [ __ ] go out drinking and
[ __ ] deal with this [ __ ] again, you know?
So you have to deal with the toxic [ __ ]
from dating greasy and then you've got
to deal with the anxiety for two days
which makes it even worse. So it's a
cycle. You see what I mean?
There's loads of projectors on here, bro.
Yeah. So, there's so many there's loads
of projectors on here.
They call people skint. They skint
themselves. They call people ugly.
They're ugly themselves.
Duh. That's what they do on there, bro.
They talk about their own lives cuz they
Well, they talk about themselves, not
their lives, cuz they ain't got a life. But yeah,
but yeah, it is toxic trying to like
date women, bro. It's not They're not worth it.
Not worth it, bro.
They're not even normal people.
But this guy, he's just messaged me,
right? like it's some uh friend.
Oh, is this some woman on Instagram? I
was spamming her [ __ ]
Um because she was ignoring me and I
finally got her to reply and block me. I
just started spamming her pictures. [ __ ] ignorant.
Arrogant [ __ ] And I met him like two
months ago. I was just talking about old
school and now he's just messaging me
saying, "Oh, sorry. I took a while to
reply. He's come back from Scotland.
That's what a normal conversation is.
with women. You'll have a conversation
with a woman and the next day they switch.
That's another thing that's not been
addressed. See, when you're speaking to
someone, it's supposed to stay consistent.
They literally switch the next day. You
never hear from them again or they just
snake you. That's why I can't be
bothered with it, bro. I'm tired, boss. You know?
Yeah. They they switch. That's the thing
with them. They they switch.
But they're not all the same. So they say
women aren't all the same.
So they say, huh? Oh, Franklin.
I don't know why they reply if they're
just going to go someone the next day.
You're the one that needs therapy, you [ __ ] mong.
Therapy for calling you out on your [ __ ]
D. It's so toxic.
And that's not me even going out
approaching. That's just some [ __ ] on Instagram.
So you could imagine the [ __ ] I used to
[ __ ] go through. Like when I used to
go and approach.
Yeah. I'm not dealing with their [ __ ] no
more. They can get [ __ ] I'm going for
this meal tomorrow then. Yeah.
I want to go [ __ ] idiots.
They're so stuck up as well. [ __ ] idiots. [snorts]
Yeah. I don't know why they switch like that.
Must be something in their hormones
cuz they only get a period once a month.
So, I wonder why they switch like that.
That is very weird.
Um, did she not reply today then? What?
No. They've been doing it for a while, bro.
They've been ignoring for a while a while, Bob.
No, they've been doing it for a while on
uh Instagram, but I want to know why
they switch like that. I'd love to know
why they switch like that. Maybe someone
on YouTube will know.
That is strange, isn't it?
There's no consistency there.
It's so weird. H
drains how they switch.
Any dates lined up? Uh well, considering
I've not gone out for 6 weeks.
Uh no, maybe.
And there's not going to be anymore cuz
I'm not going out in this country
anymore. Even though I was saying
earlier, I'm going to [snorts] go out
Friday. I'm going to go out Friday. Nah.
The more I think about it and the more I
think about how peaceful this life is
without these toxic women, the more I'm
just put off wanting to speak to them,
cuz they're all the same. They do the
same stuff. They act the same way.
They're all [ __ ] Why am I going to
waste my time on toxic [ __ ] that
can only play games? It's [ __ ] immature.
No, it was yesterday.
No, a better option didn't come up,
mate. You can't just switch like that.
And we're not talking about options.
We're talking about people even on
Reddit, they just switch the next day.
It's very weird.
Yeah. So, why don't I have any dates lined up?
I don't go out anymore, bro. I haven't
been out for 6 weeks.
I bought some jeans that were £200
earlier. Bought some new Ammani jeans
cuz my one's [ __ ] up. So, uh, yeah,
women all the same, lad.
No, I haven't for 6 weeks.
You thought I touched. Nah, not in this
country. You won't. could always be the savior. Yeah.
Nah, don't approach anymore. 40 max
all the bloody same. [clears throat]
If you don't find sh attractive, you're
gay. Ah, you little copycat.
a little copycat.
Yeah, you're [ __ ] gay if you don't
find her attractive, mate. She's the
only woman in the world. You could be
[ __ ] married, you could have [ __ ] kids,
but if you don't find her attractive,
you are gay, son. Virgin biologic. Two weeks.
two weeks cuz say I go out on Friday,
right? I'm going to drink. I'm going to approach.
Then I'm going to get numbers. I'm going
to text the next day. Then I'm going to
get led on. They're going to play games.
And then the anxiety kicks in. Then I
feel [ __ ] And it just never ends. And
then the cycle just continues and it
never ends. So
that's that's what that will be. So
just go on holiday. Yeah.
I should have gave up after that [ __ ]
USA is he thing to be fair. Well, I did.
I'd say I gave up, but I was still like
trying to meet people and stuff. I
should have gave up after that, really,
to be honest.
I should have gave up sooner.
Really should have gave up sooner, bro.
Well, I thought it was going to change,
but it would never change. Yeah.
You would have thought people at 28
years of age would have matured, huh? But nope.
That would never change. He's in London.
I'll give her my number on my Instagram.
So, we'll see.
>> I don't know. Probably January.
Yeah, it's too depressing here, bro.
It's too depressing in this country with
these women and [ __ ]
They play games.
That's all they know how to do is play
games with people. [ __ ] toxic a as
[ __ ] It's toxic a
toxic piss takers.
[ __ ] all that.
No, they're not my life. I don't give a
[ __ ] about them, bro. It's just that
Instagram thing pissed me off.
No, they're not my life. They're [ __ ]
They're not my life, bro. It's just that
uh that's why I gave up because they're
not my life.
They're not my life, bro. That's why I gave up.
They're not my [ __ ] life, man.
They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
I realize I don't really like drinking
that much. So,
[ __ ] hell, man.
Dead in it, Bob Bills.
Women are [ __ ] absolute [ __ ] mate.
What makes me laugh are the white knights.
They get shown black and white evidence
and then they still defend them. It's a madness. Absolute madness.
Yeah, I bought 200 pound jeans, Bob. Ami
jeans. They cost me 200 pound
[ __ ] bound they cost me mate.
They should have come in a couple of days. Oh,
good old Ammani jeans. Can't beat him,
mate. Can't beat good old Ammani jeans.
What do you mean night out? I'm not
going on any nights out.
Yeah, I'm not going on any nights out, lad.
Don't know why you're talking about
nights out. I'm not going on any nights
Got my hair done as well. Look, I was
going to go out Friday,
but then I realized there's no point. So,
yeah, I'm not going to now.
[snorts] Nope. No point.
I done my football bet as well. Yeah. Yeah. B dab.
So nice. Yeah. playing Franklin, saving money.
Just don't you just don't get bored at all.
Oh, thanks, man.
Well, I can tell you why. Because
they're stuck up [ __ ]
Yeah. Thanks, man.
Yeah. They just ain't interested in this country.
That's why I'm leaving. Delayed. Uh
yeah, I got my haircut
uh last Friday. Yeah, man.
I think I need a longer. Um,
yes, I have. And they weren't interested either.
No, I I I need 6 months, bro.
I think I need 6 months off minimum,
bro. Seriously, I think I do.
6 months to a year,
but probably I don't know. Probably I
probably will never try again. Cuz
you go out, you get the same old. That's
it here in it. [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. I've tried Turkish. They weren't interested either.
No one's interested.
I go on Reddit and say, "How the [ __ ] do
you get a girlfriend in this country? No
one's bloody interested." That's what I
say. Bob Bills,
I say they say I said to them, "No one's bloody interested."
Like that word bloody. Yeah.
I mean that's why I'm leaving. I'm I am
going to I am getting it. I'm going Thailand. Yeah.
and other destinations. Yeah.
What I'm doing?
Did you see my date in that video? Bob bills.
They're not bloody interested.
Bob bills. No one's bloody interested.
What do you think of that?
You [ __ ] dating apps.
They tell me to go on dating apps to get
sex, Bob. I can't even get a bloody match. Bloody hell.
They say go on dating apps is a hookup culture.
[ __ ] liars. They lied to me, Bob.
I got some good pictures on my profile as well.
But no one's bloody interested. Well,
no one's interested. Bob, you need to
help me, lad.
Yeah, I think it's over for me, bro.
Yeah, but they tell me to go on dating
apps on Reddit to get like sex and
stuff, Bob. They tell me to go on dating
apps to meet someone,
but I can't even get a match. And if I
do get a match, they don't reply. Well,
on Hinge, I don't get any matches. Yeah,
no one's bloody interested. Greavvesy.
No, I don't believe you.
Cuz I've been all over the country and
none was bloody interested.
I'm not going to come to Bath, am I? Bloody hell.
Did you see my dating app video, Grezy?
They they told me to go on dating apps,
but I can't even get a match.
Yeah, I saw you get [ __ ]
But they tell me to go on the dating
apps, Grezy. On Reddit, they tell me to
go on dating apps.
What do you think of that?
It's a hookup culture, they say.
It's a hookup culture, so they say,
Gregy. Nothing says hookup culture more
than not getting a match on a dating app, right?
Yeah. Hookup culture. All right. Not
getting any matches, you [ __ ] liars.
That's what I say on [ __ ] Reddit.
They're all a bunch of liars. They say
guard the apps.
They say go on the dating apps. We
take all the dating apps man.
You like my haircut, Greasy?
You like it when I'm groomed? I look new
and improved, don't I? When I'm groomed,
don't I, Grezy?
I look new and improved, Grezy.
New and improved. Oh, [ __ ]
Back in my little nesticles.
I'm playing Franklin. Yeah, Franklin's cool. [snorts]
I want to know.
See, there's this guy, Greavves. He's 23
and he's giving up with dating and he's a virgin.
So, you can see a lot of people gave up before me.
Yeah, you can see a lot of people they
gave up a long time ago.
Well, that's how nons is still [ __ ]
virgin at almost 31. He'll never lose
it. I don't think he'll ever get laid
and he hasn't even tried to [ __ ]
you know, better himself. Do you know
what I mean? Grieves,
he he'll [ __ ] die a virgin. Cool. >> Yeah.
The squeeze greasy.
The juice. The juice ain't worth the squeeze.
Yeah, you know people, do you know why
they don't mention my approaching videos
and stuff? Cuz it doesn't suit them.
My experiences don't suit them. Grezy,
would you agree?
It doesn't suit them. [laughter]
You know what I mean by that? Is it?
I saw you taking a piss out of Monty
earlier on his live stream.
You mad [ __ ] Kerry and Rice. [laughter]
You're a little piss taker. You are
carry advice. [laughter] [clears throat]
You silly [ __ ]
Yeah, I was just watching Harry Potter
before I jumped on Monty's Live.
Yeah, I just I was on I just was
watching Harry Potter. Yeah.
Well, do you remember when that guy used
to come on my live stream, um,
Greavvesy, and he was like, "Don't let
them [ __ ] women win.
You have to go out. Don't let them
[ __ ] women win." Greavvesy, do you
remember? I used to have a troll that
used to come on here and try and egg me on.
Don't let them [ __ ] women win.
They're laughing at us. They're laughing
at you. [laughter]
Do How do you remember it, Grezy? Yeah.
Don't let them [ __ ] women win.
They're laugh. They were laughing at us.
Yeah. He used to come in and bring up
USA, is he? [laughter]
And then all of a sudden they just
stopped coming on in it.
Yeah. How how we doing, Kieran? You all right, boss?
Is that okay with you, boss?
I bought some 200 pound money jeans, Kierin. Yep.
They'll be coming in a couple of days.
It was my birthday yesterday. So, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, I haven't been out drinking
or approaching women for 6 weeks
because you get to a certain point and a
certain age, Kieran, where you just say
it's not worth it. It's toxic.
I've been saying for like a couple of
weeks I'm going to go out and drink, but
I never end up doing it, bro. Because
it's always it's always the same old [ __ ]
I was expect I didn't get a card off you
this year. I like your little cards with
the 20 and Kierin, but you didn't you
didn't get me get me one. But yeah, it's
just so toxic. That's why I don't bother
with them no more.
Last time I went out, I got 10 numbers.
I didn't even get a reply. I didn't even
get a date. I was like, that's it, bro.
Enough is enough.
Enough is a [ __ ] enough, you know.
But that's uh yeah,
there's some guy in here called Hugh. He
comes on the Hangouts. He sounds a bit
like you, Kieran. He's from Lewishim. Yeah.
These these [ __ ] don't let these
[ __ ] women win. They were laughing at you.
You remember um Greavvesy because Peter
Belly has already found his mama.
She wanted to keep it a secret. Do you
remember? Do you remember Grezy? Yeah.
Yeah. It sounds like you, bro. A little bit.
I don't know why. I know. Obviously, I
know it's not you. He snaked me anyways.
He snaked me on Monty's. Yeah.
Yeah. The [ __ ] snaked me, bro. I caught him.
[ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
Did you see the fight between what? Rice and Monty. Okay.
Did you see the Rice and Monty fight here in
all on the same website? You can watch
the Sidemen on if you don't mind.
All on the same website. You can watch
Mickey Mouse on Beezy and Pluto.
Man, [ __ ] mad. [ __ ] needs to be
monitored. I've been saying that for
[ __ ] years. This site needs to be monitored.
Stay website you can watch Timmy Eldridge on. Oh,
I can't even bother to say it, bro. It's log.
It's [ __ ] long, mate.
Yeah, the virgin's still obsessed with
me, Kieran, as you will always be.
These women are snakes caring. They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
Oh, I'm in my little nesticles.
Oh, I can see Franklin on the telly. We
Oh, when's King coming around for a
sleepover again? He's a cute little dog.
Everyone loves Kingy. All right.
No self projection on my channel. Told
you about this [ __ ]
[ __ ] hell, man.
that woman on Reddit and see what she says.
I've got everything already, bro. I've got everything.
Trust me. I've got 161 things on my
folder of that virgin.
Don't you worry. Don't you worry. >> [sighs]
>> How's the gambling been Kieran? I put
£50 I put £100 on the roulette a couple
of weeks ago and I won £500.
I put 50 on the roulette Friday won 150.
So yeah, it's been all right. Yeah.
Hope you've been winning.
Hope hope you ain't been doing your bollocks in.
Yeah, that was online 100. But it
wasn't, bro, cuz I spent £500 that
weekend when I went out and got them 10
numbers, them women's numbers, and I
didn't even get a date. So when I won
the money back, I was like, "Fucking
hell, bro. I'm done." And I didn't go
out since I hadn't been out since 6
weeks ago. I can't be bothered, lad.
It's the same old [ __ ] here with them.
I got a football bet for Saturday.
Uh treble both sky no draw.
Yeah, it is hard to get a win.
I normally just stick to football to be honest.
I'm sure you can win online, Kieran. I'm
sure you can still win online.
Yeah, it's happened to me as well.
Well, good luck.
But the thing is with women is they
always change, Kieran. You'll be all
right with them one day and then the
next day they switch.
Have you noticed they do that? Like
you'll meet you, you'll speak to someone online,
they'll be, "Oh, I want to do this. I
want to suck your dick. I want no real
talking." And then the next day you
never hear from them again. They've
completely snaked you.
That's why I don't bother with it
anymore. It's too toxic. I like my life
the way it is, bro. Just peaceful.
Peaceful. Peace and quiet. you know,
but yeah, good luck anyways.
Hope you do better than me, mate.
How did you meet her, may I ask? I was
supposed to meet somebody two weeks ago
and they ghosted. Surprise, surprise.
I'm fed up with the games, Kieran. I'm
I'm I'm fed up with getting someone's
number and them leading me on. That's
what I got sick of in the end. The
leading on, the piss taking
um the here today, gone tomorrow.
It's not even the boyfriend [ __ ] that
pisses me off cuz that's just always
going to like you just move on to the
next one. It's the leading on and [ __ ]
That's why I just I put some videos up.
I'm sure you saw it.
That's why I can't be asked bro with it anymore.
But yeah, um try and meet her in it.
I can't even speak to women on online,
bro. They're not they don't answer me
unless I approach someone. I can't even
speak to someone.
Yeah. How long have you been speaking to her for?
Yeah, that's all right then.
You've been speaking to her for two
months. Well, why don't you try and meet her?
Two months? That's a long time, bro.
You should be meeting within a month. A
month is long enough.
Yeah. Try and meet her, ain't it? What the [ __ ]
It's happened to me before where I've
lost money and then someone wanted to
meet me, but they'll never want to meet
you when you got money.
That's happened to me a few times.
Yeah. So, why are you still talking? Why
are you not meeting, lad?
Two months is more than enough.
Where does she live?
Yeah. So, just go to her then, isn't it?
Well, I don't What? Where does she live, bro?
You can say no one's going to [ __ ]
find her, are they?
Yeah, just go in it.
Yeah, just [ __ ]
Oh, that is far to be fair. Yeah, that's
[ __ ] miles away, lad. I've not even
been there. That's like Plymouth Way.
Yeah. How much money have you got now?
You got enough to go now?
Yeah. Then just go and meet them in it.
If they're not meeting you when you say
say to them, "Let's meet up this
Saturday." And if they don't want to
meet you, then they're [ __ ] wasting
your time. 2 months is a long time, bro.
See, [snorts] when I approach someone, I
I'm I'm not waiting longer than a week
to meet them.
I'm wanting to meet them in a week,
within a week, within a couple of days even.
But that's cuz I've approached them.
Yeah. You'll have to go there then, won't you? He
can you afford it though? Cuz it's going
to be quite expensive getting the train
and stuff, isn't it?
Bro, how do you think I feel when I got
10 numbers approaching and and I didn't
even get a date? How the [ __ ] do you
think I feel?
You inconsiderate prick.
10 numbers from approaching and I didn't
even get a single date.
Yeah, I know all about getting tired,
mate. I've been tired for the past six
weeks because of it.
The mind games, the [ __ ] leading on.
[ __ ] all that, bro.
It's so toxic. That's the word for it. It's toxic.
And when you quit, you feel so much
better. I felt so much better when I quit.
Yeah, I know all about getting being tired, mate.
It weren't easy getting them 10 numbers
and then I still didn't get a date. So,
and I spent a lot of money as well.
Lucky I won the money back otherwise I
would have been [ __ ] almost. So, I
just got put off.
I got put off lad after that.
I looks maxed as well. So, yeah.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] Yeah, they're
[ __ ] lad. I was speaking to one
woman on Reddit over a month ago. She
was all nice. Then all of a sudden, she
started ignoring me. Then I kept sending
her pictures of my dick. [ __ ] I was
going to send her a picture of me
masturbating as well. I sent her my dick
and she was still ignoring and I just
spammed her whole Instagram page and
made her block me. He said, "I'll get
therapy." I said, "You are the one that
needs to get therapy, sat there ignoring
people, you [ __ ] dickhead." That's
another thing, Kier. When they switch,
there'll be one person one day, then the
next day they're completely different.
That's another thing. Have you noticed
that they switch as well? Um,
yeah. So, [ __ ] them. They're [ __ ] lad.
You're absolute [ __ ]
Don't worry about it, man. Yeah.
Yeah. She's the one that needs to. And
she was ignoring on purpose. She kept
clicking on a message I'd call over and
over and over and over again and she was
just being a [ __ ]
And the more I think about it, that's
all right with me, Grevy. The more I
think to go and try again, the more I
get put off by like previous experiences
and it's just not worth it.
Why do you want to lose even more hope?
We've already lost hope. We don't need
to lose anymore. There's none left to
lose. We left that a long time ago.
We lost hope a long time ago, lad. We
don't need to lose it again.
She's being a [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] sat there ignoring ignorant
Why even talk to someone in the first
place if you're just going to ignore them?
It's toxic, Kieran. Very, very toxic. Yeah.
People on Reddit say you'll meet someone
though, Kieran. People on Reddit say go
on the dating apps. Yep.
Greavves, are you still there?
Greavves, are you obsessed with boobies?
Are you obsessed with boobies, Greasy?
I think you're obsessed with boobies, isn't it? Grezy,
why are you obsessed with women? Grezy,
you're obsessed with women, aren't you? Yep.
So, why are you obsessed with women,
Greavves? Are you obsessed with women?
So yeah, get yourself to Devon and try
and meet that uh woman, Kieran.
That's if you can afford it, obviously.
How How much do you have? Cuz it's going
to be quite expensive.
You should have enough in it. I think
you get the same amount of money as me.
Yeah, you should be all right now.
Me, Grezy, and Kieran get the same
amount of money.
Yeah, you'll have enough then, won't you?
Yeah. See, I can't get addicted to
gambling anymore, bro. Cuz if I lose my
money, I'm [ __ ] It was going to take
me a while to get the money back.
I could do it, but it's like it's not worth it.
Yeah, that's still enough though. 600.
That's more than enough now. Yeah.
Well, it will never change, will it?
Well, it will never change, will it, Kieran? So, yeah.
Bless you then. If you've got £600. Oh, yes.
That's cute though, isn't it? If you got £600, try online.
Just try online. Just just gamble some roulette online.
If I had five 600 pound to my name, I
would just gamble it, bro.
Try to win like 20k or something.
Yeah, just just gamble like 150 in it
or like Yeah, just try 150 and see.
I'll just go all in.
That's what I was going to say to be
fair. Not not the bookies though. Don't
go to the bookies. If I was you, I would
just go there and if she doesn't meet,
just go for a night out. That's what I I
done that in Nottingham. I went to
Nottingham to try and meet someone and
they didn't come out. I just went on a night out.
So, Grezy, are you obsessed with women or what? H
Yeah, just go for a night out in it. [ __ ] it.
Not the bookies though, cuz you don't
want to lose all your money. Will you
when you're that far away from home?
You say that you're going there
Saturday, is it? Bless you.
Bless you, Kieran. Bless you.
Yeah, just do that, bro. It
does she look good? Is she good-look Karen?
Yeah. What? Yeah. But are you going to
get a train there? Cuz you've never
traveled alone before, have you?
Will you be all right going there by yourself?
Yeah, that's all right. Is it? Give it a
little while. There's a woman that
wanted to meet me in Scotland, Ken. I
stood her up.
Yeah, there's a woman that wanted to meet me.
Yeah, she was [ __ ] stinking, mate.
She was in uh Scotland.
But I would give it a whirl, Kieran. I would.
What have we got to lose? Yeah.
Which one? The one in Scotland. Yeah.
Still up. Yeah. Yep.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. I need to go to bed in
a bit. I'm tired, man.
Oh, Ken, lad. Oh. Uh,
I just stood I just made her go to like
three different pubs. I made her go to
two different pubs. Had her running
around and that.
Yeah. And I told her to go get a boob
job. Then I blocked her. Yeah. I just
had her going on a wild goose chase. Yeah.
Yeah. Trying to say trying to be passive aggressive.
[ __ ] her, bro.
But we won't be an item, [ __ ] I'm
better than you and I don't even like
you, brother. You flatchested [ __ ]
You know what I mean? Yeah.
Yeah. I'm going to sleep anyways, bro.
Yeah, I got a lamb shank, but I'm not
going to eat. I'm not even hungry to be honest.
I'll talk tomorrow. Stay.