[ __ ] hell, bro.
>> Friday's cancelled then. Uh, another
week where we said we're going to go out
and I'm not going to go out. So, yeah.
Woke up in a bad mood, bro. I think I
[ __ ] woke woke up most of the [ __ ] neighborhood.
Mad [ __ ] this [ __ ] is so lucky he
doesn't live in England, bro.
really really really really really is you know
madness. Absolute madness, bro.
And this isn't even me approaching. This
is just someone on [ __ ] Instagram.
They are all the same [ __ ] aren't
they? These women. They really, really
are all the same [ __ ] [ __ ] madness.
Don't know why they get these random
[ __ ] ass men to message you. Cowards.
That's what they are. [ __ ] cowards.
Problem to go [ __ ] himself. I had to
reply to the story cuz yeah, can't talk
for seven days. So yeah. Well, the story
is they act like [ __ ] [ __ ] You
give it to them back and then they
report you to [ __ ] Instagram and then
they put you all over their story.
They're [ __ ] such losers. Absolute
such losers, these women. They're [ __ ] losers.
They really, really, really, really are.
They're [ __ ] losers, man. They should
go get raped. That's what they should go
[ __ ] off and get raped. Yeah.
[ __ ] stupid rape victims. Yeah,
it's it's it's a good thing I don't go
out anymore cuz I'll just end up
knocking someone out to be honest with
you, bro. So, it Yeah, it's a good thing
I don't try anymore.
Really really is [ __ ] dealing with
their [ __ ] anymore. Like I said in my
video, every time I feel like, oh, let
me go out again. let me try. The more I
realize that, oh, they're all the same.
They generally are all the same. Even
the ones that you come across, they're
all the same. There's no [ __ ] point.
Put me in a [ __ ] bad mood, you know?
I hate them, bro. I really hate them.
And I'm not really I'm not in a bad mood for weeks.
Not been in a bad mood for weeks. No
mood swings, no nothing. Just peace and
quiet. Just how I like life, you know.
Know what I'm saying?
>> I don't want to [ __ ] hug, mate. You
don't need to [ __ ] hug me. What do I
want to hug for? They're [ __ ] I woke
up, lad. waking up to that load of
[ __ ] Toxic [ __ ] as usual with
them all the time because they're all
the [ __ ] same.
You know, we [ __ ] broke the cycle by
giving the [ __ ] up, you know? We can't
control [ __ ] everything that goes on
[ __ ] Instagram. Do you know what I mean? Madness. Madness. [ __ ] [ __ ]
These women are scumbags.
They're so cowardly as well. They can't
even fight their own verbal battles.
That's how cowardly they are.
Peter Belly comes along, puts them in
their [ __ ] place. Oh, report them.
Report them to Instagram. Get the white
knight. [ __ ] [ __ ]
That's what they are. They're [ __ ]
[ __ ] These [ __ ] women.
someone that um I was talking to. I
said, "Oh, I hope the [ __ ] gets break."
And she's like, "Oh, that's it. I'm
blocking you." H So, it's okay for them
to do what they [ __ ] do. Same old
conversation, same old [ __ ] boring.
This is what this is. It's the same old
[ __ ] The same old [ __ ] boring with
them. They're [ __ ] boring, lad.
Seriously, they're all the same
[ __ ] stuck up [ __ ] [ __ ]
That's what they are, lad. I hate all of
them. That's why I gave up,
you know. I was looking forward to
Friday as well. Mm-
I was looking forward to it, bro. But
no, I'm not going out now. No way. Not
after that. Again, another woman. You
know, it's toxic
to drive a normal person [ __ ] mad.
I've not been in a bad mood for weeks, bro. weeks.
Absolute [ __ ] weeks until this
[ __ ] You know, they're all the
[ __ ] same. How do people sit there
and say that these women are not the
same? They must have [ __ ] in their eyes
and [ __ ] in their [ __ ] ears because
they are all the [ __ ] same. What am
I, bro? Contradicting myself. Nah, I
don't go out and try. I don't go out and
deal with them because they're all the same [ __ ]
How people don't think these women are
all the same. I shall never know, mate.
So cowardly having to get someone else
to fight your battles cuz you're an
ignoring, arrogant little [ __ ] Yeah,
you've blocked someone. Why are you
getting someone else to message me, you stupid [ __ ]
I hate these women, bro. I swear to God,
I hate them. It's probably best off I
never meet anyone, to be honest with
you, bro, because I would just end up
[ __ ] someone over. Like, it it's
there there's literally no point cuz I
would just end up [ __ ] someone over.
[ __ ] madness, lad.
How I like my life. Peace and quiet,
bro. You know,
smells nice. That air freshener.
I said I'll slap her up in front of you
and I'll slap you up in front of her. Is
that fair for you?
See, that's what I'm saying. It's toxic.
It is toxic.
Dealing with women is toxic.
They're all evil bastards. They're all
the same [ __ ]
If I went out on Friday, I'd end up
knocking someone clean out, bro. It's
not worth it, you know? But I can't even
reply to my [ __ ] friend on Instagram now.
who's just come back from [ __ ]
Scotland because of this [ __ ] You know,
they're all big and ugly enough being
arrogant little egoistic [ __ ] And as
soon as someone gives it back to them,
oh, we'll report them to Instagram.
We'll call them a stalker. We'll get the
white knight to defend us.
I just messaged that [ __ ] Damon. I
said, you know what this reminds me of?
Your content X. That's what it reminds
me of. Your content delinquent little
[ __ ] X. narcissist. Yeah,
that's what it is, bro. Yeah,
I'm not going around messaging people's
friends of No, no, no. I'm not doing
that, bro. I want to proper do someone
in, you know? That's what I want to do.
I really want to proper do someone in,
bro. It's not even a [ __ ] joke
anymore. This [ __ ] is so lucky that they
live in South America. I would happily
met this [ __ ] today anywhere. Happily, happily.
You know, not a problem, bro. Not a [ __ ] problem.
Mad. Absolutely mad, bro. Stupid [ __ ]
And some woman I've been speaking to for
a while blocked me because I said, "Oh,
I hope the [ __ ] gets raped."
Oh, wow. Wow. But it's okay for them to
do what they do. It's okay for them to
go around being a [ __ ] and being
immature and arrogant and having some
[ __ ] on my [ __ ] messages. Why?
Why put Listen, listen, listen. Why are
you going to sit there
and put someone in a bad mood if you're
not going to finish it, you [ __ ] If
you're not going to finish it, you
stupid little [ __ ] You know,
I I think there's like that that's what
I would do, bro. If I generally went out
on Friday, I would just go out looking
for trouble. I would just I would just
start on people. I'll just look for
trouble. There's no point, bro. There's
literally no point.
These little [ __ ] defending women,
arrogant, stuck up [ __ ] women that are
all the [ __ ] same year in year out,
year in year out, year in year out. [ __ ]
me, you know,
putting me up on your story. Why are you
putting me up on your story, you
cowardly [ __ ] Why are you getting other
people to message me? Fight your own
[ __ ] battles. They're not the
ignorant, arrogant [ __ ] You are. So why
are you putting me all over your [ __ ]
Instagram [ __ ] story knowing that
people are going to message me?
Cuz you can't fight your own battles.
You're a loser. You're a coward. And
this is what they and where most of
these guys right or a lot of them are
white night simps. They take the piss
and then when they realize you're not
one of them and you can stand your
ground, they all shy away like the
cowards that they are. Cowards. They're
[ __ ] cowards. That's what they are.
Arrogant, snaky little cowards. They
need telling about themselves. Yeah.
Cuz some people, believe it or not, in
life need telling about themselves.
But these [ __ ] women are all the same. You know,
mad. I [ __ ] hate them. I do. I
[ __ ] hate them with a passion. Like,
you really don't know, bro.
Not been in a bad mood for weeks. I'm
not I Last time I was in a bad mood was
when I was dating. Was when I was
Yeah. Well, you know what I mean? Like
approaching and stuff like in the dating
game. As soon as I gave up none of these
mood swings and none of these problems, you know,
and as soon as you deal with a woman
again, the problems start. But they're
not all the same cuz you don't know 9
billion [ __ ] women. But they're not
all the same.
Yeah, they are all the [ __ ] same,
[ __ ] Yes, they are all the [ __ ] same. [ __ ] idiot.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
So, we're going to have to do something
else Friday now. Maybe go cinema or something.
Guess we can go cinema. By we, I mean
me. [snorts] If there's anything on at the cinema. Yeah.
Could you get an escort? Yeah, but I
don't want to because I don't care about sex.
The thing is a bit deeper than that. You
know what I mean? [ __ ] that. But
absolutely [ __ ] that.
I was into sex now. Like I had a sex
drive. I just use escorts. But I don't
even n I generally hate them, bro.
I generally hate these women.
Really, really do.
Putting Why are you putting me on your
story, you little immature [ __ ]
Immature, arrogant, cowardly. Know that
other people are going to message me,
you little [ __ ] [snorts]
You know what I really want to do with
all of these women? I want to ruin their
life, bro. I really want to ruin their life.
Like seriously, seriously, seriously. I
want to give these [ __ ] some back of
what they've gave me over the years.
Like go like getting that person to go
on a wild goose chase. Bro, that weren't
even enough, bro. That generally weren't even enough.
They were royally going to get [ __ ]
over if they went to that steakhouse. I
really need to [ __ ] one of these people
over properly, bro.
Seriously. Seriously, dude.
I might try and get that [ __ ] to come to London
and and then they just not meet her or something.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
[ __ ] That's what they are. Put me
in a bad mood, bro. My mama was trying
to calm me down and everything. It's so toxic.
Toxic is the word. Yeah.
Talking about they're not all the same.
[ __ ] off. Of course they're all the
same. They're all [ __ ]
Your ex. I told D about this. I said
that's your ex. Your ex does that.
Yeah, put me all over your Instagram
story. You know damn well that other
people are going to be messaging me,
other guys are going to message me.
You can't even fight your own battles,
you arrogant [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah. So that's that.
All women aren't the same. So they say.
So they [ __ ] say, mate. They say a
lot of things though, don't they? They
say a lot of things.
But even to be fair, even when they live
in England, right, you'll say to these
[ __ ] "Meet me so I can smash your
face in." And they won't do it. So
they'll put you in a bad mood. This is
what they do. This is what they do.
These [ __ ] they put you in a bad
mood by starting on you, and then when
you want to meet them, they won't meet you.
And the same thing, what was like a month ago
when they have to get other people to
fight their battles, you know? Ah, Jesus [ __ ] Christ. Madness.
So yeah, be I'll be no going out Friday. [ __ ] that.
Dude, I don't even have a short temper
to be honest with you, bro. It's, you
know, it's just not [ __ ] normal.
Why are you getting people to message
me, you stupid dick? And I went on my
mom's phone and started calling her all
the names under the sun. I said, "You
cowardly little [ __ ] [ __ ] off. Get
raped a lot, bro. There was like no
whole bars. [ __ ] off, bro. I don't have
to not say certain things to you when
you're going around being a [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] That's what I said to
him as well. You're a [ __ ]
All toxic, all negative.
All things people don't need in their
lives, you know, madness.
They make you like them. They make you
change as a person, you know. They
generally generally do it.
Mental, bro. Mental.
That's what I mean by toxic.
his [ __ ] nose is [ __ ] [ __ ]
All women are the [ __ ] same. It's so obvious.
obvious, you know,
that has pissed me off this morning,
bro. That really has pissed me off this
morning. Who the [ __ ] do they think they are?
The more I realize how they're all the same,
the more I [ __ ] made the right
decision given up with them.
[ __ ] should have gave up [ __ ] two
and a half years ago. Bro, what the [ __ ]
was I thinking that they're not all the
same when they generally generally [ __ ] are madness. badness. >> Yeah.
Like this [ __ ] I'll say something as
well. How long can you keep this [ __ ] up
for? You know, it's the same thing with
this Red Star. Like, you're still
stalking, man. You're still going on
man's channel every single day, but
you're never you're not meeting anyone.
Like, do you not think to yourself that
at some point this has got to end?
How long are you going to keep being a
keyboard warrior that's never going to
meet anyone for? Like, how long is this
really really going to keep going on
for? It's [ __ ] sad and pathetic,
you know? Like, how long is this going
to go on for where you're just going to
keep being a keyboard warrior, keep
stalking, but you're never ever meeting
anyone? It's embarrassing, bro. Like,
[ __ ] pack it in. Either meet someone
or give it up, you [ __ ] loser.
It's like that, Terry. When he comes
back on it, I'm going to his area, bro.
There's not even no arranger now. I'm
going to that cunt's area as soon as he
comes back on this live stream. And I'm
going to humiliate the [ __ ] bro.
Properly. Yeah. No, no Monty, no rice
stuff. Like, this is just stuff to throw
in there, you know? Like you've been
doing this keyboard warrior malarkey
[ __ ] for how many years now? You haven't
gave up. You're not meeting anyone. You
know, there comes to a point where you
got to think like what the [ __ ]
You You just stalk people every day.
You're never meeting anyone.
Pathetic. It's sad behavior.
But then again, it is a disabled
community. Exactly. I mean, what what do
you really expect? Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
madness, bro. [ __ ] madness.
Does she even look like a [ __ ] I'm
surprised I didn't [ __ ] spo it early
on to be honest. Yeah, she looks like
one of them [ __ ] NPCs just like all
these other women that are apparently
not all the same. Apparently not.
Yeah, she looks like another [ __ ]
[ __ ] hope she gets [ __ ] raped by her dad.
by a [ __ ] dog. The silly [ __ ] >> Yeah,
>> another one that looks like a stuck up
NPC [ __ ] up their own ass.
But these women aren't all the same cuz
you haven't met 8 billion of them. [ __ ]
right off. They're all the [ __ ] same.
They all watch the same [ __ ] They all
act the same [ __ ] way. Yeah. [ __ ] retards.
And this is a 25 year old by the way if
you wanted to know. >> Yep.
[ __ ] they're absolute [ __ ]
These are women. They need to go get
raped. Honestly, do us all a favor.
They might learn a bit of respect then.
The [ __ ] [ __ ]
I [ __ ] hate them. I do.
I [ __ ] hate these women out here.
Really? I really do, lad.
might go get a breakfast.
Bastard. Same. Even when you're not
approaching them, you're still dealing
with the [ __ ]
[ __ ] rape victims.
What they are. Yeah.
Yeah, I wanted breakfast, but it's too far. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, I'm going to go get some breakfast.
We'll carry this rant on later.
that [ __ ] power on Reddit. Don't they
Yeah. Anyways, I'm going to get some
breakfast. I'll be back later.