I need to take my [ __ ] medication, mate.
There's something seriously wrong with
me, mate. But I like it when I'm in this
[ __ ] mood because Red Star won't meet
me because he's a good boy and he knows
what's good for him. See, a man could
could never say that to me. A man could
never ever say to me that you're not
going to meet me because you're a good
boy. If Timmy come on right now and said
that to me, mate, I'm [ __ ] going to
his [ __ ] area right now, mate. Do you
know what I'm saying? Because I'm not a
petrified little keyboard warrior in his
40s sat with no money. Do you
understand? I'm a bit different than
these people. I like to think that I'm a
bit different than these people. You
know, I've been told to to be quiet a
couple of times, mate. Cuz I've got I'm
going a bit [ __ ] mad, mate, in my
head. I really am. You know, you take
the case. It's too much sugar,
you know. It's too much sugar. But Red
Star is a good boy because he knows
he'll never meet me because he knows
what's good for him. He knows he will
never meet anyone because he's a
disabled fat bald bumper in his 40s
that's got no life now. Okay. Know what
you're going to sit here and say now.
Why is that you don't know how much
people have and how much people don't
have. That's what you're going to say.
Well, guess what? I know you ain't got a
life, mate, cuz you're sat on YouTube
every day stalking me, aren't you, son?
[ __ ] stalking me. Cuz I live in your
head and you'll do absolutely nothing about it.
Now I'm going to end up getting a
[ __ ] Asmo order here. It's just like
the skin virgin in out of London with no
money. It will do absolutely nothing.
But run to the police because they're so
much of a [ __ ] loser. You know, it
seemed that it winded you up a bit,
didn't it, mate? It seemed that that
really winded you up.
Grape. I wish grape on someone and you
will do nothing. So why waste your
[ __ ] time writing it?
Why waste your time writing it? Because
you will do absolutely nothing. And I
can say it better than Lord J.
Say it better than this. You're a good
[ __ ] boy. You and your ugly boyfriend
with an ugly rat face with a [ __ ] fat
girlfriend will do nothing. You can't
step [ __ ] toe to toe with me, mate.
Nah, nah. You're calling people skin,
are you? People ain't got no [ __ ]
money. Really? So, you knew where I
lived by myself for the better part of a
[ __ ] year. And you done absolutely
nothing behind behind your little
keyboard. Now, I know that there's going
to be um a big pograph now because I
know how it is. Why did you do
absolutely nothing? Did you do
absolutely skin? Now, at the end of the
day, mate, if you and your [ __ ] ugly
boyfriend with a rat face that can't
attract anything normal, I'm gripping to
you now. You'll do nothing, mate. Was
going to do do something. You would have
done it, but you ain't had the funds.
Speaking of funds, funds to go on
someone's [ __ ] door from wherever the
[ __ ] you live because you can't cuz
you're [ __ ] skit and you ain't got
nothing. Talking of skin, right? I got
200 pound jeans coming today. Something
that you would never be able to afford.
Red star and the skin merging in the bed
will never be able to afford cuz it's a
bit out of your price range. And there's
nothing wrong with that. There's nothing
wrong with something being out of
someone's price range. Nothing.
Absolutely nothing. You just don't have
the FUNDS BECAUSE YOU AIN'T GOT NO
MONEY. I'M NOT TAKING A PISS. I'm just
saying it, mate. I mean, we got one
virgin who ain't got no bed, no teeth,
living in an out of London council
bedset that didn't go abroad until they
were 30 because they could [ __ ]
afford it. Where was I done those times
at [ __ ] 23? You You understand what
I'm saying, son? Cuz I ain't no skinned
virgin from [ __ ] out of London.
London born and bread. Been there all my
life. Not some little cheapkate kept one
cuz that ain't got a [ __ ] bed. You
can only bake disabled people and has to
run to police when they get their ass a
good old whapon. When they get their ass
a good old weapon, the skint virgin has
to run to the [ __ ] police because
he's so much of a virgin loser that he
can't even [ __ ] do anything. So yeah,
they're not all all narcissists are
[ __ ] women. Most of them are women.
BUT YOU LOOK AT THAT LOOK AT THE LANKY
KEMP MERGER WITH NO MONEY. NO, he's [ __ ] moving.
I'm [ __ ] I'm going mad. Groovs is
gonna love this, mate. Groovs is going
to [ __ ] love this.
You know, it's too early for this, mate.
You'll do nothing cuz you're a [ __ ]
good boy, Red Star. You're a good boy.
You do as you tell, son. That's my boy.
But, uh, no, in [snorts] all seriousness
though, still on YouTube being a
keyboard warrior. Oh, man. Something's
got to give now. Come on. You've been
doing this for years. This whole like me
shouting was just a joke, by the way.
But no, seriously, something's got to
give. Stop being online. Stop being a
[ __ ] YouTube online stalker all your
life and come and do something. And you
know what? When you go on these little
on on the little virgins uh
community post, it's the same virgins
from like four years ago again who's
done absolutely nothing. So, I don't
understand. either pack it up and give
up or meet someone because it's getting
[ __ ] boring now, mate. It's getting
really, really boring. You clearly ain't
got no life. You can sit there and
pretend that you got money all you want,
but guess what? You ain't got no life.
You're just a little stalker. Yeah,
I just got told off, mate. See, I I
don't lie about stuff. I just I
literally just got told off. I got I got
told off, mate. I literally got told off.
Sorry, mate. I got told off. I was being
[ __ ] loud to be fair. And that's
absolutely fine. You know, I'm not I'm
not here to to pretend stuff happened,
didn't happen. You know how it is. Just
cuz you got a bollocking, mate. Been
being too loud, you know.
Was being a bit loud, lad.
Sorry about that, mate.
Just can't control myself sometimes.
Sorry. [snorts] It's just how it is. Sorry, mate.
Yeah, Red Star, get a life cuz you'll do
absolutely nothing cuz you're a good boy.
I couldn't say that. Go.
I actually nicked it off Instagram, lad. Yeah,
another year. Still being a loser. Still
having no money. [ __ ] it. Back it up,
son. Back it up, you little YouTube stalker.
Look, I'll even put the link out for you
if you want. Come and join Red Star.
Let's have a little chat,
you little loser.
Oh, one second.
I'm going for some food today.
So, [snorts] I want you to join. I want
you to join, mate. You little stalker.
We know you're sat there watching this
stroking your little [ __ ] micro dick.
Come and join, you little stalker, and
I'll put you in your place. You're not
scared, are you, to join the [ __ ]
Hangouts? What are you scared of? again.
I need to tone it down a bit. I don't
want to get a bollocking again. You and
your skin ugly Kent boy with no money.
Join the hangouts. Come on. Go on, son.
Waiting on these jeans. Something that
you can't afford. Maybe if you sucked
each other's dick, then you might be
able to uh you might be able to just
afford it, you know.
But I doubt it. I very much doubt it, mate.
Oh, I got a suggestion. Sorry about that, lady.
Yeah, I see.
And I vote this right. It's the same
people in your comments. I don't go on
your channel very often. Maybe every
three or four months just to see if
you're still indeed a loser. Still
indeed a stalking loser that ain't got a
life. But it's the same people that
comment, mate. It's the same people that
comment. The same losers that ain't got
a life that will do absolutely nothing.
[ __ ] it up. I'll beat someone. It's
pathetic at this point now, mate. Jesus Christ.
Stop widening yourself up. Like this is
a bit of advice, right, from like me to
you. Don't get wound up with things I've
said because you're never going to do
anything about it. I mean, [ __ ] sake.
How many addresses of mine have you had
and you've still done nothing but been a
keyboard warrior? I mean, the thing is
the problem with this whole YouTube
community, sir, is that most of the time
we don't know where people live. We
generally don't know where people live.
So we generally don't know where to find
them. We can't find them. You've had
like two, three different addresses of
been where I've been at and you've done
absolutely nothing. So there's no point
winding yourself up.
You know, you can try to call me skin,
got more money than you. You can try and
call me bald. I've got more hair than
you. You can self project all you want,
son. But it's never going to change what
you are. A keyboard warrior, cowardly
loser, [ __ ] That's it.
You ain't got a life, mate. And you know
what? You ain't got nobody. We know damn
well that you ain't got nobody. But
that's not even important. You ain't got
no [ __ ] life. You know, you and your
boyfriend, you and your Kent boyfriend
whose dick you like to suck, his little
microscope [ __ ] bent [ __ ] dick
ain't got a life between you both.
Imagine that, mate. [ __ ]
the link's there. You could join.
You know, I'm saying all this mad [ __ ]
about you and you can't even defend
yourself. You [ __ ] loser. Absolute
[ __ ] loser. Ain't got a life. Ain't
got a life, mate. You can sit there and
say that you've got money. Oh, all you
do is sit there on [ __ ] YouTube
stalking because you ain't got nothing.
You little stalker. You pathetic little
YouTube stalker. That's what you are,
mate. [ __ ] stalker, mate.
>> Yeah. There you go. It was funny to me, bro.
You'll do absolutely nothing behind
behind your little keyboard.
You'll do nothing. Just like your little
boyfriends that [ __ ] comment on your
[ __ ] And you know, the thing is, you're
not getting to me. This is funny. I'm
doing this on purpose. You're very much
not getting to anyone. You need to step
up your game, son. You need to actually
meet someone, you know? You need to
actually go out and actually meet
someone now. It's not like you don't
know where I am, mate. What's the
excuse? You little keyboard warrior. You
little m you skip little bastard. Yeah,
that's what you are, bro.
Some little fat, ugly bully victim sat
on YouTube with no life.
Get the [ __ ] a grip, son.
It's pathetic. Well, if it's so
pathetic, why don't you come and do
something about it? [ __ ] keyboard.
Sorry mate, I'm a bit hyper today. I'm a
bit hyper today. I've calmed down now. I
haven't took my medication. You know,
you'll do absolutely nothing.
Right. These jeans, I don't know exactly
what time they're coming, but yeah.
I can't wait.
I really, really can't wait, mate. Oh. Oh, good boy.
Oh, sorry, mate. I am a bit hyper.
I'm looking forward. Today's a big day, mate. [snorts]
The jeans are coming.
The jeans are [ __ ] coming.
And uh I'm going for a lovely meal. So
I'm quite excited actually.
Yeah. Oh, look. Monies on online. Oh.
Right. Tom wanted to put the link up
because I'm uh I I want to join.
Well, I'm going to join his uh I'm going to join.
Look, none of these can afford it
because of skin.
Sorry about that, mate. Just had to go. Yeah.
Yeah. Anyways, I'm gone and I'll do a
video when the dreams come.
Yeah. Right. Save it.