I am
[ __ ] I need some [ __ ] I need some chicken
nuggets. This all [ __ ] yank a lot,
bro. You know what I mean?
I feel like [ __ ]
car. How about that, mate? I like
car. That's what I like, mate. I like
[ __ ] man just got this [ __ ] [ __ ]
bro. Oh, mate. Come on. McDonald's.
McDonald's. Nuggets. Nuggets. Yes. Yes.
Come on. I'm
drunk. Hey, come on, bro. I'm [ __ ]
I like this little yank,
bro. I lost 100 pound on fishing, bro. I
was chatting to this Yank for like an
hour, bro. Man's going to make some
Californian babies, bro.
I swear down I'm going to make some
[ __ ] Californian babies, mate. You
watch that thing and you [ __ ] ru it,
bro. I am [ __ ] bro. I got this woman,
bro. She's from [ __ ] Cali, mate.
Listen, we went chatting, drinking,
[ __ ] madness. I'm going to get her
pregnant, bro. Rash, you believe that?
What's happening, mate?
Yeah, I am fat. I am
Listen, remember people, if you're
watching this, yeah, you should drink
responsibly. Cuz if you if you don't
drink if you don't drink
responsibly, you sort of um you kind of
end up like uh me.
Yeah, that's what you end up like,
[ __ ] You end up like diva, bro.
I swear I'm going to get
this I'm going to get this American
woman pregnant. Bro, we were chatting for ages,
bro. [ __ ] love her, bro. I'm not
going to lie to you, bro. We're talking
for like an
hour. Straight up an hour, bro. I'm
going to [ __ ] her, bro. Watch.
Yeah. A [ __ ] prop American, bro.
Yeah. Yeah, I sent it. But of course I
sent it, mate. I
will send it man out the [ __ ] club
man. I was stranded like street approaches.
That was Of course I went out, bro. Of
it Oh, may
I Oh, there's some food. Oh my god, I'm
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. It's not even a
joke. Yeah, I was talking to this woman from
America. I like her a lot,
bro. She was like proper
I met the woman of my dreams. Who
knows? Yeah, I went out, bro. I [ __ ]
sent it. I got kicked out of this
club. This country annoys me. This
country annoys me,
bro. I'm [ __ ] bro.
I I'm [ __ ] bro.
Bro, I need to be sick,
bro. Cuz I am
[ __ ] I love her, bro. Swear down, bro. Man.
Man, bro, listen to
me. I was trying up this [ __ ] I feel
like [ __ ] clown. Listen, bro. I'll
turn up this I'll shout out this team,
bro. Listen. [ __ ] bro. I'm [ __ ] Listen, bro.
Listen. Just shut up a minute. One
second, bro. This is
serious. Just chill. Chill. Chill.
Chill. Ease on the old, bro. Ch. This
is a minute. It's 10 seconds. Like two
minutes. Where two minutes? Holy [ __ ] [ __ ] me. Listen to listen
man. Got back your knees on the [ __ ]
Listen, it's not funny, bro. It's serious, bro.
Listen, I was um uh in the nightclubs
all night after getting that night uh
that old guy's ina,
right? Sending it boyfriend [ __ ]
madness, bro. Man ended up getting
kicked out the [ __ ] club, bro. B were
chatting [ __ ] in it. So what happened was um
um I thought [ __ ] it I got to send it on the
street of course I was chatting to this
for like an hour. Yeah, she's from the
States. We were chatting and chatting
and drinking, bro. I like her. I was
saying, listen, bro, I like Scooby doing it. From
California, Terry, that's from
California, mate. We was talking,
flirting, all of that madness, bro.
We're going to give her some Cali
babies, bro. I'm going to give her some
[ __ ] Cali babies, bro. I feel like
[ __ ] K. You know what I'm saying,
bro? We all know who that is. I got no
game, bro. What are you talking about? I
got kicked out, mate. I was asking for
the [ __ ] bartender's [ __ ] number.
He was a can. He was a [ __ ] jail
[ __ ] mate. He's on [ __ ] calendar.
He's been a [ __ ] man. I'm banned.
You know what they said to me? Yeah.
They said, "I'm going to ban you [ __ ]
three weeks." So, I was like, "Listen,
ban me forever, mate. I ain't coming
back, bro. You want to try and ban me
for three weeks?" Yeah. I ain't ever
coming back to your premises. [ __ ] you,
[ __ ] You been banning me? You're
not banning If you're banning me for
three weeks, [ __ ] You're
banning me forever, mate. If you're
banning me for three weeks, you are
banning me for [ __ ] ever, mate. How's
about that one? You
cucking two weeks,
bro. But guess what, Tony?
But guess what, Perry? Before all of
that, mate, I did do a lot of
approaches. Boyfriend. Yeah. I had a
good night in the end. Yeah. It was
proper [ __ ] Yeah. I went out in the
club. All I was getting was I've got a
boyfriend. I've got a boyfriend. All of
that [ __ ] Yeah. Ended up getting
kicked out of the club. Yeah. Oh, we've
heard some complaints about you. What
complaints, man? I've been speaking to
people [ __ ] normally. Yeah. there
chatting [ __ ] and then I had to go out
on the street. I lost 100 pound on fish
and frenzy [ __ ] was just chatting up
these [ __ ] women. I got one woman,
bro. She's from [ __ ] California, bro.
We was chatting for over an hour, bro.
Was in the spoons, bro. Man's going to
give us some Cali babies, bro. I got her
number. Yeah. I feel like [ __ ] Car.
You know what I mean? I'm going to get
her. I'm going to get her. I told her,
listen. Yeah, about this, bro. Yeah, I
like [ __ ] scoot. Listen, when you're
going back in a couple of months, I'm
coming back with you. How's about that
one, bro? We were vibing. The vibe was
real, bro. Yeah, the vibe was real,
mate. When man got put out on the
[ __ ] streets, Terry, the vibe was
real, bro. I believe it. No, listen,
Terry. Yeah, I No, no, no, no, no. Just
stay in the club, bro. I was chatting to
people normally, bro. Yeah. And I was
like, "Listen, I'm not coming back in
two, three weeks." You go, "Fuck
yourself. You ban me. You ain't getting
my money anymore." Man weren't harassing
no one, bro. Yeah. I tapped this
bartender. She was from Canada. She
wanted to be a [ __ ] [ __ ] her, bro.
Yeah. And then I spoke to a few other
people that want to be a [ __ ] [ __ ]
them, bro. Cool. I'm not coming back on
your premises then. You want to ban
people? [ __ ] you. 3 weeks. And I stood
up, bro. And listen, let me tell you
something, Terry. Yeah. Hey, bro.
Listen, Terry, let me tell you
something, bro. Yeah. When I was in the
Weather Spoons earlier, man did not back
down, bro. Yeah. He told He's like, "Oh,
oh, well, I didn't say about where you I
said, I'll put my feet where I [ __ ]
want, mate." And if you see, I actually
stood where I was. Yeah, mate. I ain't
scared over. I just basically said that
I am not gonna stay. Listen, listen.
Yeah. Listen. I I said to the bouncers
respectfully. Yeah, I get what you're
saying, brother. But listen, I'm not
coming back in 2 3 weeks. You're banning
me now. You're banning me forever, bro.
Yeah, at the end of the day, this is an
open venue. This is a public [ __ ] place. Understand,
bro? I shut it, bro. How did I [ __ ] it?
I I shut it, bro. I stayed in the same
place, you [ __ ] How the [ __ ] did I
[ __ ] it? I stayed in the I said I put my
feet where I want. How did I [ __ ] it?
[ __ ] off, Terry. How the [ __ ] did I [ __ ]
it? You [ __ ] I was I put my feet up on
the [ __ ] chair and you weren't about
to do nothing about it. [ __ ] off about I
shut it, mate. I never shut it from no
one. How did I [ __ ] it? How did I [ __ ]
it, bro? I was standing in the same
place. I said I'll put my feet where I
[ __ ] want. That's what I said. Go. I
said I'll put my feet where I want,
mate. All I asked was why have you got
two drinks? But mate, honestly,
listen. This woman
from I'm falling in [ __ ] love again,
bro. I swear now, bro. No, no, no. For real.
Yeah, this isn't even a
joke. I know. I said, why you being
rude? Cuz I weren't expecting it. But
man ain't scared of no [ __ ] Listen, I'm
falling in love again, Terry. I'm
falling in love. Uh, hey, listen Terry,
listen. I got the old passport, mate. I
got the old passport back. I was like,
in three, four months I'll come back to
America with that one. Listen, I swear
to God, bro. Listen, Terry, it's not
funny. I swear, bro. Listen. But no,
honestly. No, what it was right is I was
just saying that like, bro, listen, you
shouldn't be in public places. Yeah. If
you don't want people standing you up
and that it all [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] the
West. [ __ ] the West. Yeah. Even though I
said I'm Come on, bro. I'll go back to
America with you, bro. It's [ __ ] the
West, bro. That's how it is. It was to
be fair. Yeah, it was a bit annoying
today. I'm not going to lie to you, bro.
I'll keep it real. It was annoying
because like I was saying to you, yeah,
the bartender is a [ __ ] in it cuz she's
from Canada and she's being a [ __ ] And
what, bro? You're all [ __ ] I'll say to
your face, mate. You don't need bounces.
Listen, the thing is with this country,
bro. Yeah, it's a dive, man. Listen,
last week it was [ __ ] sunny. Yeah,
mate. They're not going to block me. I
was with this American for over a
[ __ ] hour. And guess what, Terry? I
don't care cuz guess what, bro? I've got
a passport and I'm leaving England.
Yeah, you can't leave England. You
can't. You've never left England, Terry.
Are you trying to tell me how I shot
myself? When did man [ __ ] himself, bro?
I stayed where the [ __ ] I was charging
back. But listen, the thing you got to
understand, Terry, is that uh it's
[ __ ] up, bro. Like, I only got one
number today, and that was an American.
We was chatting for a [ __ ] ages. She
was nice, man. advice. But the thing is,
yeah, is it's [ __ ] up, bro. This
country is [ __ ] man. It is [ __ ]
bro. I must have spent about like almost
£200 today, but still, it's [ __ ] up,
man. It's not funny, bro. It's [ __ ] up,
man. One second. I need to get my
charger. Hold up.
Listen, Terry. She's on some [ __ ]
Scooby-Doo type [ __ ] bro. You
understand? Hey, you understand Terry?
Mate, she's on some [ __ ] Scooby-Doo
type [ __ ] bro. But allowed up for
Thursday, man. These [ __ ] get a
[ __ ] I swear, man.
and wave. Come on. Where's my nuggets? I
want my chicken nuggets. I'm starving.
In the [ __ ]
seat, listen. Listen. And I was saying
to man this as
well. This country annoys me,
bro. My [ __ ] will tell you
straight annoys me,
bro. She's a [ __ ] How's that? [ __ ]
was telling me where she was from all through,
bro. Yeah, shutting up, man.
Listen, this country is
[ __ ] Honestly, it is actually [ __ ]
mate. Go away, virgin Sean. Go, you [ __ ]
virgin. But no, Terry, listen, bro. I
was chatting up like a few things. I was
like, mate, listen. But I would leave
your premises easily, bro. Yeah, [ __ ]
you and your premises. I shouldn't have
even been in that. I should have been
just sending it straight on the
street. Um, but she didn't want to have none of
it. There's my food. What's that?
He didn't sound that interested. My game
is bad. [ __ ] you, [ __ ] You
didn't even hear anything. Yeah, I lost
100 pound on Christian. He's a [ __ ] He
will always be a [ __ ] He will always be
a [ __ ] Christian will always be a
[ __ ] He's an old [ __ ] man.
Yeah. What about you, man? You ain't
even got a woman, you [ __ ] Oh my
god. Virgin Sea. Virgin Sean's in the
chat. You're going to [ __ ] lose that
virginity, you [ __ ] virgin. [ __ ]
hell, mate. Sean, you need to [ __ ]
pop that virginity, you little virgin.
You p virgin little [ __ ] [ __ ] When
are you going to [ __ ] finally pop
that virginity and stop being a [ __ ]
YouTube virgin all your [ __ ] life?
You [ __ ] [ __ ] Hey
bro, Sean, man to man, you need to lose
that V play. You're getting on to
[ __ ] 30 and you're still a
virgin. Do you really want to be a
virgin all your [ __ ] life, bro?
Still, you don't want to [ __ ] die a
virgin. [ __ ] from Kent, you [ __ ]
ugly [ __ ] And mate, I told you a
million times I'd want have a big nose
and have that [ __ ] ugly face that you
got. You [ __ ] virgin [ __ ] virgin
who's been starved by his mommy. Hey,
listen. Wouldn't you
love to sit here and eat these nuggets?
Wouldn't you? Instead of being a [ __ ]
virgin all your life, you sloppy second
virgin little [ __ ] ratfaced ugly [ __ ]
on the ground a month. Wouldn't you?
Wouldn't you? Come on, bro. Come on.
Come on. You [ __ ] virgin on a grand a
month. Come on, you little poverty
ridden little [ __ ] You're going to
[ __ ] lose that virginity, are you? Or
you're going to die of virgin, you
[ __ ] little [ __ ] mate. [ __ ] you. You
[ __ ] Where is it? Where's this
[ __ ] straw gone, bro? I think I see Mr. Straw,
lad. I had to end it, bro. I had to end
it cuz of
uh Hey, listen. Terry, listen,
bro. I had to leave the nightclub, bro.
They were being [ __ ] man.
Yeah, I told him I'm not coming back in
six weeks. Um, sorry, three weeks. I'm
not coming back. You kicked me out. I'm
not coming back, mate. [ __ ] you, you
Oh, okay. Terry, listen, mate. He will
[ __ ] die virgin. Listen, Terry. One second,
bro. Listen, Terry. One second, bro. Let
me just finish chewing. This is
hot. Here's the thing, Terry. Right. Let
me ask you this question,
right? When does he have time to [ __ ]
his girlfriend where he is sat on
YouTube every day stalking me? Think
about it, bro. It doesn't make any
sense. I've got videos of me getting
[ __ ] me hotel rooms with women, be
in bed with women in Manchester, mate.
He is literally a virgin. There is
people that are in Bro, there are people
in marriages and they've not [ __ ] for
about three months. How about that one?
People that are actually married. He's
going to [ __ ] die that virgin. I'm
telling you, he's going to die a virgin.
Listen, there is videos of me getting my
dick sucked, being in bed with women,
[ __ ] having women admitted to
sleeping with me, and he's still a
[ __ ] virgin, and he's going to die
one. There is literally, Mate, listen,
listen, listen, mate,
listen, I would rather be single my
whole life than be with a vulnerable
woman that doesn't give me any sex. I
would rather have nothing than be a
virgin with a disabled girlfriend like
he is. I would rather have nothing. I'd
rather sit here [ __ ] chirping in
these nuggets my whole [ __ ] life. Do
you really think I'm jealous of someone
that's 30 years of age, never had sex
with a disabled girlfriend that don't
even give me sex? Well, I'd rather have
nothing and stick to prostitutes. That's
facts. [ __ ] hell. You think I'd
rather be that [ __ ] 30 year old
virgin from Kent that's never suck his
dick up nothing. Here's the here's the
thing, Terry. Right. You're only as good
as what you can prove. Yeah. We've seen
me get my dick suck me being bed with
women multiple times. We have never seen
that [ __ ] Kent virgin stick [ __ ]
erectile dysfunction dick up anyone. And
bro, it's not even
me. Bro, listen. This has been going on
for [ __ ] years as well. That [ __ ]
virgin with his small little disabled
dick. Thank you, man. Bro, I met a woman
today, bro. She's from Cali. We was
chatting for ages, man. Got a number.
Like, she was nice, bro. I got a number.
I'm going to meet her again in a few
days, bro. She's sick, man.
Oh, I had to pay for a [ __ ] Oh,
Terry, stop embarrassing yourself now,
buddy. Come on. Listen,
Terry. I had to pay for a [ __ ]
[ __ ] hell, bro. You're embarrassing
yourself. Come on, man. Stop embarrassing
yourself. If I want to go back to
[ __ ] America, I'll [ __ ] go back to
America. Listen, it bother me, bro. You know, listen,
Jere, there's people in marriages that
don't have sex. That Sean will die a
virgin. Even if he was married, he will
[ __ ] die that virgin. Listen,
Terry, why do you think he goes on about
virgins? Because he's the biggest virgin
himself. He will die.
One, Mr. B. Yeah. Listen, I was setting
up this king. Yeah. Pull my milk off. We
was talking for like an hour. Got her
some drinks, everything, man. She's nice,
bro. You know what I'm
saying? Yeah, man. She's nice, bro. She's cool,
man. Mate, that straw will [ __ ] die.
Virgin, I'm telling you, mate. He will
[ __ ] die. That [ __ ] Kent virgin.
He's been a virgin his whole life. Mr. B, listen. Yeah. All
right. That [ __ ] Kent [ __ ] will
[ __ ] die of virgin. That's why he's
so obsessed with him because he's the
biggest one himself. Mr. B. Listen, let
me ask you this question,
bro. How many times have you seen me
with women? How many times have you seen
me, babe? He is the [ __ ] biggest
virgin going. It's not what I feel, it's
what I know. Listen, Terry. It's not
what I feel. It is the biggest one
going, the biggest virgin. Listen, he's
got a girlfriend. You still didn't
answer my question, bro. Terry, you
still didn't answer my
question, right? He is the biggest
virgin going. Whether he's got a
girlfriend or not, he's a virgin.
Listen. Okay, you didn't answer my
question, Bobby. Yeah. If he's got a
girlfriend, what time does it what time
does he have to have sex with her when
he's constantly stalking me? Mate, that
doesn't mean he's had sex. There's
married people that don't have
sex. You know what I
mean? There's married people that don't have sex.
Honestly, he's going to [ __ ] die a
virgin. You will die one. Literally,
mate, there are people that are actually
married. Yeah. That are on ver divorce
that don't have sex. He's going to
[ __ ] die a
virgin. He's got a girlfriend. Listen,
Terry. He's the one that stalks my
sloppy seconds. I don't want a disabled
girlfriend. I don't want a disabled
girlfriend who I don't [ __ ] like he
does. He's been with her for three
years, but he's never [ __ ] her. used a
virgin. Listen bay, he is still a
virgin. It doesn't matter how long he's
been with someone, he will [ __ ] die
that [ __ ] 10 virgin. Why do you think
he says yeah about how it sounds like a
virgin? Yeah, cuz you rank too much. Cuz
he's the biggest virgin going. He would
know all about virgins. Listen, mate.
The girl that he's with is a [ __ ]
right? She doesn't need her knees
settled. You know what I mean? He is the
biggest virgin going around in Kent. He
would know all about him cuz he's one himself.
Listen. Listen, mate. Yeah. I have shown
I have had sex. I have had [ __ ]
That virgin that virgin come with a rat
face has never shown nothing. But a
disabled girl. Listen, bro. But but he
doesn't ruin me. Terry, listen. Terry,
I've got more money than him. I'm better
looking than him. I've had more women
than him. Who's the one that's ruining
someone? More money? Better looking?
More women. Been abroad. He doesn't ruin
no one. He ruins himself. He's an ugly
little ratfaced little virgin. No money
on a grand a month. Never had sex. Who's
the one that's really being ruined? Bro,
stop embarrassing yourself. He's an ugly
[ __ ] on a grand a month. He's a [ __ ]
virgin. He's never left England. Never
left England. Let that Let that process
in your mind. The Rat has never left
[ __ ] England. Not even Wales. Yeah,
I'm very ruined, bro. I'm very ruined by
a [ __ ] virgin that's never left
England soil. Well, funny
enough, mate, I've had more I've never
had Listen, Terry. I've had more women
than you, mate. Listen, Terry, you don't
have a relationship. Yeah, you and your
kids are [ __ ] ugly. I can talk about
your kids every day of my life, but the
thing is, Terry, you're not going to do
anything about it. That's the thing,
Terry. [ __ ] you and [ __ ] your kids, and
you're never going to do nothing to me.
How does that make you feel? [ __ ] Terry
and [ __ ] these manta kids. And guess
what? You claim you know where I live,
but you're not going to do nothing about
it. Terry and these [ __ ] spasticated
kids. And guess what? Terry's never
gonna do nothing to me. Never. Cuz Terry
is a little [ __ ] manta. [ __ ] Terry and
[ __ ] his family. And he's never going to
do nothing to me. I was like, that's
bad, isn't it? Terry the
mis kids and his m family. Yeah. He
claims he knows where I live. [ __ ] his
kids and [ __ ] his family. How about that
one, bro? Like, do you think anyone can
say that to me, Terry? [ __ ] your kids
and [ __ ] your family and you're not
going to do nothing to no one ever. [ __ ]
your kids and you [ __ ] your family about
how you claim that your family is about
anything. [ __ ] your [ __ ] family. You
mug. [ __ ] your [ __ ] ass family. Listen
to me, man.
Listen, tell you and your m ugly [ __ ]
family to come for
me. Tell your [ __ ] m of a family to
come for me,
buddy. Come on, buddy. Tell me. Tell
your [ __ ] [ __ ] m family to come for
me. You and the monsters. Come on. Come
on, big man. Come on. I'll wait all night,
bro. Terry and his M kids and his
[ __ ] [ __ ] family to come for me, bro.
anytime. [ __ ] it.
[ __ ] Terry can't even say nothing back
to me cuz you know I'm right. [ __ ] you, bro. You're
[ __ ] Terry, you're [ __ ]
man. Stop being a version of your
life. So, Toby, have you established now
that no one's scared of your family? Yeah, you [Music]
gone. I said, "Fuck you, Terry, and [ __ ]
your family." That's what I said for Oh,
okay. You had a drink. Okay, let me tell
you straight to a man from Facebook.
Yeah. [ __ ] you, Terry, and [ __ ] your
family. How about that one? You're a
[ __ ] And your family's all [ __ ] as
well. How about that one, [ __ ]
mate? Your family is not about nothing,
mate. Your family is all a bunch of
[ __ ] Yeah, I heard from LG. All your
family's about, mate. Your family is all
[ __ ] bunch of [ __ ] mate. [ __ ] off
you. Who's your family, bro? Mate,
listen. I've heard about you and your
[ __ ] family, buff. about
nothing. Let me ask you a question, mate.
Yeah. How many times have you seen me
get a [ __ ] blow of a [ __ ]
woman? Sh. You're going to [ __ ] die
of virgin. How does it feel that you got
starved by your mommy? Sean, you're
going to [ __ ] die of virgin. You
[ __ ] ugly rat face son. And I've told
you a million times as
long that [ __ ] ugly face that you
can't. You [ __ ] virgin. You [ __ ]
Listen, mate. You're going to die that
[ __ ] Orton virgin on a grand a month,
mate. A grand a month wouldn't even see
me for a week.
You're and listen
be stop being so ashamed of where you
come from. You're from Kent. You're a
Kent wanker like your [ __ ] non dad.
He's from Cuden, right? London. You are
your dad or your [ __ ] mom that
starves you. None of you little retards
autism [ __ ] spastics are from any
part of London. You're from Ken. You're
a Kent [ __ ] on the ground a month. Stop
all of this madness, bro. It's
embarrassing, man. You're on a grand a
month. You're from Kent. You're a Kent
wanker. Stop being so ashamed of where
you come from, virgin boy. Now, I'm so
sure. Yeah, I'm in square. Listen, if
you mate, listen. You keep telling me
where I am. Why don't you come on the door then?
Stop being in your little opened virgin
bed sit with your fat ugly girlfriend
who you've never [ __ ] Sean, listen.
We understand where all of this comes
from cuz your mom stared you. You're
still a virgin. You're an ugly [ __ ] with
a rat face. Autism. Diagnosed autism.
But man, you don't need to take out the
rest of the world just cuz you're a
diagnosed autistic little virgin. Mate,
you don't need to take out the world.
You'll die a virgin. The sooner you
accept it, the
better. You're going to be that [ __ ]
orbited virgin. The [ __ ] ugly rat
[ __ ] face with a [ __ ] girlfriend.
Mate, the sooner you mate, you're not
from London. You're from
Kent. You're a [ __ ] autistic [ __ ]
Kent [ __ ] with a fat ugly girlfriend. I
don't know how many times someone's got
to tell you, you're from Kent. You're
not from London.
You are from Kent. You're not London.
You're a Kent [ __ ] Like you're not [ __ ] ugly
dad. You understand that face? The ugly
face. You're from Kent. You're a Kent
wanker. You and your fat ugly
girlfriend. You [ __ ] virgin. You
[ __ ] erectile dysfunction virgin on
the ground above. Now sort that [ __ ]
ugly face out. That [ __ ] mate.
Listen. Do we do we need to put your
face up on YouTube again? Listen, mate.
Do we need to put up your ugly face
again? Your ugly virgin face again?
Mate, please don't make me do it again.
Please don't make me put it up. Don't
make me put that [ __ ] virgin ugly
face up again with a greasy face. The
[ __ ] virgin content, mate. You're not
from London, bro. Yeah.
Simple. You need to get YouTube. You
need to [ __ ] lose that video of
yours, you [ __ ] ugly [ __ ] You need
to get back up with your Listen, listen.
Listen. This is embarrassing. Now, let
me put this ugly face up for everyone.
Let me put this [ __ ] ugly face up for
everyone again. One second. [Applause]
Delay. Get an ugly face up again, mate.
For everyone to
see. Oh, McDonald's.
live. You're [ __ ] taking a piss.
You're telling me this ugly virgin rat face. Just
[ __ ] talk about anyone who is a rat
face. Look at this [ __ ] ugly [ __ ]
I'd rather have a Pinocchio's nose than
have that ugly face. Look at that ugly
face. That's why he's still a [ __ ] virgin. That's
why he goes on about Morgan cuz that
ugly face. Look at that disabled face,
mate. He probably gets pit for that ugly face,
please. Look at that [ __ ] ugly face.
Look how ugly it is, mate. Look at that
[ __ ] ugly face. Nich [ __ ]
virgin. Look at that [ __ ] ugly face.
I will take a [ __ ] big nose over that
[ __ ] rat face. Don't know about you
people, mate, but I [ __ ] would,
bro. Sean, what's going on with that
[ __ ] ugly face, mate? If a big
[ __ ] nose was the least of your
problems. Listen, Sean, this is this
facious why you're still a virgin.
You're the Virgin Mary. Virgin [ __ ]
Mary. You will [ __ ] die a virgin. You
ugly [ __ ] virgin. You will [ __ ]
die. One. No matter how many fat,
vulnerable, ugly women with Down
syndrome you show, you're going to die.
That [ __ ] virgin. That virgin from
Kent with the ugly rat face. You're
gonna [ __ ] die a virgin. You really
want to die a virgin? 30 years of age.
Listen, let's sum up your life. No bed,
no sex, no money, no money, no sex, no
wardrobe, no bed, and you're still a
[ __ ] virgin at 30 years of [ __ ]
age. Look at that [ __ ] ugly face.
Look at that [ __ ] ugly disabled
face. Look how ugly it is. It's so
disabled. Look at that [ __ ] disabled
face. Look at that [ __ ] ugly disabled
face. This is why you're still a
virgin. It's a madness. You will die a
virgin. Sean, listen, man. Come on. Do
you really want to die
virgin? You really want to be that 30y
old virgin all your life on the ground
among poverty? Listen, [ __ ] all the
virgin [ __ ] We know you'll die virgin
anyways, but you never left the country.
You never been on a plane, but you
expect us to believe that you've got all of this
money? That's madness. That is one madness, bro.
Nothing wrong with your face. Nothing
wrong with your face. You tell me
there's nothing wrong with that [ __ ]
ugly thing right there. That ugly
[ __ ] face. Why you still a
virgin? You [ __ ] ugly [ __ ] If there
was nothing wrong with your face, you
ugly [ __ ] You wouldn't be with a
[ __ ] disabled woman that doesn't give
me no sex. You are one ugly [ __ ] You
are the most ugliest [ __ ] rat that I
have ever seen in my life, which is why
you're still a
virgin. You are the one [ __ ] ugly
[ __ ] Look at that [ __ ] rat face,
mate. Listen, the only one right that
will defend you is
Terry. You [ __ ] ugly [ __ ] rat bing
[ __ ] mate. Should I show everyone your
[ __ ] rat face again? Like, you know,
you [ __ ] ugly [ __ ] This is why
you're still a
virgin. You will die one. You will die one,
mate. You're going to die a virgin, son.
virgin. That's what you're going to do,
mate. How's it feel being a virgin at 29 years of
age? Oh, let me let me ask you this
question as well. You, however, have
never had a girlfriend. I've had more
women than you, mate. I've had more sex
than you. I'm not still a virgin like
you. I'm nearly 30 and I've had more
women than you and I'm not still a
virgin like you are. That's the
difference. How's it feel? It feels
good. How does it feel still being a
virgin? Being a [ __ ] virgin all your
life. How does it feel being a sexy
little virgin with erectile dysfunction?
It feels great, man. It feels great,
right? Never been in a relationship at
27. But at least I'm not a 30year-old
that's never had sex like you. You
[ __ ] virgin. Bro, do you remember our
conversations? Do you remember how
conversations we used to
have? I would be a 37y old that [ __ ]
30y old version with that [ __ ] ugly
face. Look at that ugly face. Look at
ugly face. It's so ugly.
Look at that [ __ ] ugly face. Let me
Let me put some more faces up. Come
on. Let me put some more faces up,
mate. Look at that [ __ ] ugly face.
Look at that ugly face. Look at it. It's
disabled. Look at it. Look at that
[ __ ] ugly face. No wonder we stole a
virgin. Look at the ugly face,
bro. Where? Why your [ __ ] as well? There
we go. I want to show everybody the ugly
face. The disabled face of yours, which
explains why he's still a
virgin. Let me show the disabled ugly
face. Let me show why you [ __ ] ugly
face. Ugly [ __ ] One minute.
Let me see. Let me show that [ __ ]
ugly face. Ugly [ __ ] One
second. Look at this [ __ ] disabled
[ __ ] Put yourself on private
nowadays. Where is it? There we go.
that that ugly face, that ugly rat face
has ever had
sex. Oh, mate, you look like mate,
please. Bouncing, bro. One second. I've
got it now. Hold on.
I think I'm going to
puke. You're telling me that this
[ __ ] ugly [ __ ] face, rat face,
balding virgin. Look at the [ __ ]
state of it. It don't even look
even. Look at that [ __ ] ugly disabled face. Look [Music]
at today. I'm as ugly as you. I'd kill
myself the day I'm as ugly as you. I'll kill
myself. Terry, listen. You don't even
have a business, bro. I just dissed off
your whole [ __ ] family. I told you
[ __ ] your kids and [ __ ] your family, but
you don't do nothing about it. Yet you f your
ass. Sean, look at that [ __ ] disabled
ugly face. [ __ ]
hell. Terry, listen.
[ __ ] your family and [ __ ] your kids. Yet
you claim you yet you claim you know where I am. [ __ ]
off. Your family's not about nothing.
Suck your family, bro.
Your family's not about nothing.
Terry, where's your
mission? Terry, listen. I've got more
money than you. I've had more [ __ ]
women than you would ever
have. Listen, you're trying to say that
you know where people are. Why isn't
worth you? I'm that [ __ ] nonsense.
Virgin John, you need to lose that view.
You don't want to die. Virgin T. Listen,
let me tell you something, man. I may
have never had a relationship, but guess
what? I've had more women than you and
Sean combined and it kills you. And I
got more money than you. How about
one? Well, I've got more money than you
and a [ __ ]
virgin. And I had better women than you
and I need to get disabled. [ __ ] off, man. [ __ ]
hell. You need to sort that [ __ ] ugly
face out, you ugly [ __ ] mate.
Before I start talking about people's [ __ ]
noses, I would talk that [ __ ] ugly
disabled face out of yours. Look how ugly it
is. Look how [ __ ] ugly it is. It's an
ugly [ __ ] face. That's why he's still a
virgin. Look at that face. It is so
ugly. It is so [ __ ] ugly. It's why
he's still a virgin. You will die one.
It's a madness, mate. It's a madness. I
can't imagine being 30 years old and
still a [ __ ]
virgin. Oh, you
When are you going to [ __ ] lose that
virginity? You [ __ ] virgin
Mary. You [ __ ] ugly [ __ ] Ugly
virgin. When are you going to lose that
vision of yours? You [ __ ] biggest
virgin of all time. Come on. Huh?
George, when are you going to lose that
virginity? You're almost 30. You're still a
burden. You want us to believe, right, that
you have had sex with that fat ugly
girlfriend of yours? Is that all you're
trying to say to me? Right. You and that
fat ugly [ __ ] of yours have had
sex. You and your fat ugly girlfriend,
your fat ugly girlfriend. I can't even
talk. [ __ ] off, mate. Come back when
you've actually got a bit of proof.
You're a [ __ ] fad, man. Come on. Come
on. You like my little game,
eh? Sean, you're going to [ __ ] die
that virgin. Are you [ __ ] Are you
being serious, mate? You are going to
[ __ ] die a virgin. Lose that V plate.
Lose that vinity. You [ __ ] ugly [ __ ]
Sort that ugly face out and you might
actually get some women. You're blocked
now. You [ __ ] ugly [ __ ] Go suck your
dad's disabled dick. That's probably the closest
thing. You will uh get to losing your opportunity, bro.
Yeah. Need to grow up, mate. Oh [ __ ]
Here's a thing though.
Terry, here's the thing though. Terry, please
record. Terry, please record. They
[ __ ] were, mate. They [ __ ] were.
Lord J. Listen, Terry. Peace was cool and
everything. Listen, Terry. Peace was
cool, man. It's not a joke,
bro. This was cool, man.
There you were,
mate. Tell me,
listen, you will never know where I
live. How about that one, bro?
I got a number,
man. And I got a date
you m You will never know where I am,
Terry. You will never know where I am.
am. Keep blessing us. Keep blessing,
[ __ ] You never know where I
am. You You will never know where I
am. Tell me. How about that one?
Huh? You have a bus. You never you never
know where I am. Bye-bye, Virgin. Bye-bye,
Virgin. You will never know where I
am. You know, virgin. Virgin
Mary. Ah, listen mate. Terry, let me ask
you this question again.
Yeah, you say that this little virgin
has had sex. And here's another thing.
Oh, does he? Good for him, man. No one
gives a [ __ ] And here's the thing,
Terry. Yeah. I'm tormenting you. You are
the ones that go on about me every day.
Even when I'm not on YouTube, mate, I'm
tormenting you. I'm living in your head
when free. Yeah. Even when I'm not on
YouTube, you keep going on about me on
and on and on and on. I'm living in your
head. I'm tormenting you. Even five
days, bro, where man don't post nothing,
you're on YouTube. I'm the one who's
tormenting your life. That's why you
keep posting and posting and posting cuz
I'm bullying you in your head every day.
I'm bullying the [ __ ] out of you. That's
why you keep Listen, bro. Listen, no one
cares. Nobody cares,
boss. I'm bullying him. Listen, four or
five days I'm not on YouTube and I'm
still bullying him in his head and he
can't shut up about me. Listen, Terry,
do you remember? Let's tell everybody
when I was in your area, oh, I'm on
probation. Oh, I'm on probation. My
family is about anything. [ __ ] you and
[ __ ] your family. How about that one? Listen, remember
Terry? Oh, I'm on probation. [ __ ] your
dirty kids and [ __ ] your family. You
claim that you know what I had. Listen,
he got me, Nick. No, he didn't get me
[ __ ] No, he didn't. Where am I now?
Living in your head. More money than
you. Better looking than you. You keep
going on about me every day. Terry, [ __ ]
your kid and [ __ ] your family. Listen,
if your family's about anything, tell
them to come round. Terry, [ __ ] your
stock, ugly family that [ __ ] up kids.
Yeah, Terry. [ __ ] your kids and [ __ ]
your family. How's that about that one,
bro? Listen, Terry. Manto man. [ __ ] your
kids and [ __ ] your family. And what are
you going to do, bro? [ __ ] your kids and
[ __ ] your family. And you're not going
to do nothing. Listen, bro. You tell any
of your family to come around, go live
for 20 minutes. No one's cared about
your ugly family, your downy family. No
one cares about him. No one cares about
your soft little [ __ ] family. Shut up.
No one cares.
Terry, [ __ ] your kids and [ __ ] your
family. You know, even LT, I've said
about a million times, your family's
about anything. This little Monttery's
family. [ __ ] his kids and [ __ ] all his
family's kids. How about that one? [ __ ]
off, mate. Your family are a bunch of
wankers. [ __ ] off. [ __ ] your kids and
[ __ ] your family, man. Stop being silly
now, man. Come on. Yeah.
Yeah. You ever been to a
uh put in? Yeah. You're going to put my
windows in, man. Get it quick, bro.
You're not going to do nothing to no
one, man. You're just embarrassing
yourself. Listen, you're a [ __ ] mate. You're a
[ __ ] Shut up. You're a [ __ ] man.
Stop embarrassing yourself, bud.
Yeah, it's embarrassing now, bud. I just
[ __ ] nuggets of a [ __ ] You're
embarrassing yourself. You're an idiot, bro. [ __ ]
off. This is really silly, man.
I got a woman. I'm going to bang
her. I'm going to bang the [ __ ]
bro. Yeah, I would. Terry, I would. [ __ ]
it. Give it a while. You see, and this is what
happens. Yeah. I'll say, "Bro, listen.
Turn up." Yeah. Yeah, man. Listen. How
many empty threats have you [ __ ]
made? How many empty Listen, you and
that rat face, you don't try no one. And
I laugh at you every day, mate. You've
got a whole channel dedicated to me. And
guess what, Terry? I get more money than
you. I'm better looking than you. So, at
the end of the day, bro, no matter what
you do online, I win.
Listen, nonsense. I get more money than
him. I'm better looking than him. So,
whatever he does on his channel, no one
cares. Nobody cares. I'm better looking
and I get more money. So whatever you
put on your channel, on your virgin
channel, man's the winner. I don't
care. Yeah, Terry, I went to your area,
mate, about two years ago and you shhat
your pants. Yeah, shut up. You and
Virgin are not about nothing. [ __ ] you
and [ __ ] your family. And tell your
family. I said that as well. Terry,
listen. Manto man, [ __ ] your kids and
[ __ ] your family.
That's it. And you're not going to do
nothing. So stop fronting, bro. It's embarrassing, man.
Yeah. Who the [ __ ] is
that? Stop fronting. It's embarrassing,
bro. You know about this. [Music] What's say
14th? Tell me you're obsessed, man.
You're just like this Orington virgin.
You're the same kind of people, bro.
What's going on,
man? I met a woman today. I'm
happy. Some California babies, Terry.
How's about that one? Oh, you'll be so
jealous. But guess what, bro? What's the
excuse going to be that time,
man? Oh, chatting her up and that, bro.
We were drinking for like over an hour,
mate. She's on it, bro. She This [ __ ]
is on it,
man. She is on it hard, man. Yeah,
man. Tony needs to get a life, I
think. Oh [ __ ]
man. Oh, I'm [ __ ] sat here. [ __ ]
me. I am [ __ ] loud and I am [ __ ] man.
Yeah, this woman. I'm going to get some [ __ ]
babies. Some Californian babies,
mate. Mate, I'm going to get some
[ __ ] California babies. Terry, up in
this [ __ ] I'm going back to America
with her. In three months, I'm going to
go back to America with her,
man. I feel like [ __ ] coming.
Terry, how's about that one? I feel like
[ __ ] Kanye, man. You know what I mean? [ __ ]
hell. I feel like [ __ ] car.
Terry, Terry, I feel like [ __ ]
car. You know what I
mean? You're a horrible old [ __ ] But we
love you. She wasn't from Canada, you
[ __ ] She was from California.
Yeah. No, she wasn't from Canada, mate. She's from
California. No, I feel like he needs to
proper send these approaches again. You
know what I mean? I'm
fat. I'm drinking Coke. I just had some
McDonald's, man. Spent about [ __ ] 200 quid
today. I spent more than 200 pound.
Where the [ __ ] did that go?
But Terry's never been to America. His
funds won't allow it, will
he? She wasn't from Canada, mate. That
was a full [ __ ] But you know what?
Funny. You should uh bring up Canada cuz
that's where Britney was from. The one
that rejected Joan that [ __ ] didn't
want him. Terry, she she didn't want
him. She didn't want to know him. She
did not want to
know. Literally, she did not want to
know he's ugly. R [ __ ] virgin.
Yeah. You've never been lol. You fud,
mate. You have never been out the
country, Terry. [ __ ] off, mate. You've
literally lit, bro. You've never been
out of [ __ ] England, man. [ __ ] out of here,
bro. You've never been out of
England. I actually think
I'm, you know, like I'm I want to live
that American dream, bro. You know what
I mean? In two, three months. Listen,
bro. You ever heard of like Scooby-Doo,
Terry? You've heard of it. I I assume
you've heard of Scooby-Doo.
And all of this stuff comes from
America, Terry. You
understand Terry? All of this stuff
comes from America. From
America. I was I thought I was going to get three
numbers. I only got one, but yeah. Yeah, man. Oh
man. Yeah. Baba That's it.
Oh, man. That's sick.
Yeah. How we doing, bro? Hold
on. All right. Now, hold
on. Is that him? Yeah.
said to me that like any snaking or any
chat, I'll pull up post of you, mate.
Like Cardiff is not a big
place. Yeah, believe it or not. I'll
pull up post of you saying that you're [ __ ]
launch outskirts of and guess what?
Nobody will care
either. That's what I wrote to him right
now. I just said any kind of back
chatting or anything. I'll put up
posters of you in Cardiff calling you a [ __ ]
pedophile. And trust me, that's that's a
lot smaller than [ __ ] London, bro. Trust.
Easy me, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] about
police. Know what I mean, bro? Tell you
know what I'm saying? Like you and
Terry, the thing is you and your family
is not about nothing, mate. You
know, you know what I'm saying, brother? No cares.
Why is that 8:40 [ __ ] free? What?
I think I need some [ __ ] thing,
bro. Bro, listen. Let me tell you
something, Tony. Listen, man. I don't
give a [ __ ] about this chase. If he
snakes me in any way, shape, or form,
I'm going to pull up posters about him.
Listen, bro. You think I don't know
people that's got printers? He will
never be able to go around Cardiff
again. I'll easily go back to Cardiff,
pull up print, put up posters about him,
and put up posters about nonslegs. Do
you think I give a [ __ ] Bro, listen.
All of my [ __ ] is [ __ ] backed up,
bro. Do you think I care?
Honestly, mate, you have talked about
your family and LT's talked about your
family, too. About how they're this big.
Your family's not about nothing,
man. It doesn't bother me, Terry, bro.
Like, honestly, mate,
listen. I'll do it to Chase as well.
Don't forget, man. Listen, Terry.
Listen. Cardiff. Yeah. Let me tell you
something, bro. Cardiff is not big.
Yeah. I've been to Cardiff about three,
four times. Wales is not big. I will go
to Cardiff and pull up [ __ ] about Chase.
I'll do it around as well. There's no
skin off my nose, bro. I don't care. I
will do it all again. I don't give a
[ __ ] I'll make sure the [ __ ] never
walked around Cardiff City Center ever again.
I've got his picture somewhere anyways, bro.
simple that he's a [ __ ] dirty, stinky
little pedophile. I'll do it to both of
them. And we'll see how much I said, "Bro, listen."
Yeah. No, Chase is this uh guy that I
met years ago and [ __ ] he met Sean.
That's cool, bro. You snake me. I'll
pull up post of you as well. It's no
problem. And I'll put it on my YouTube
channel. It ain't no problem to me, bro.
It's not like you live in Scotland. You
live very far away. You only live what,
an hour? What was it? An hour and 40
minutes. I will happily go back to Wales
and put up posters of you. It's no
problem, bro. I will [ __ ] your life up.
You will never walk around Cardiff
again. I promise you now, bro. Yeah. I
swear to God, you will never walk around
Cardiff again. Yeah. Think of it, bro.
You can listen. You listen. Yeah. That's it.
I'll make sure you get battered, bro, by
some [ __ ] whales [ __ ] I swear to
God, bro. I promise you. I'm like I
swear to God, bro. I swear to God. I
don't even need to know somebody with a
printer. I don't need to know anyone
with a printer, bro. M will just go to
an internet cl like I did last time. It
ain't no biggy, bro. I'll take getting
nicked, mate. If it means pissing you
off, I'll easily get nicked.
I don't give a [ __ ] man. You know what
mean? You know what I'm saying, bro? I
don't give a [ __ ] And listen, Terry
Sean doesn't ruin no one's life. I've
got more money than him. I'm better
looking than him. I've had more birds
than him. Even when I'm off of YouTube
for over a week, he's still obsessed with me,
bro. Yeah. Listen, bro. Anytime that
Terry take, bro, listen. I will post of
him. I will do it, bro. Mother's life. I
will do it, bro. You [ __ ] Look
how I was I look how quick, right? I was
I I was in London, bro. Yeah. Yeah.
Today. Like, bam. Click of a finger. But
I'll go back to Cardiff. I don't care.
I'll get on a drink when I'm there as
well. I'll put up posters of you. You'll
be the first one. You will be the first
one. I swear to God, you'll be the first
one. I've your picture anyways, mate.
I've got both your pictures. Know what
I'm saying? So, it's no problem to me,
mate. I'll put up posters everywhere and
I'll do the outskirts C as well know how
of a [ __ ] notch you are mate. You
won't get away with it like you would in
London. I swear to
God. Yeah. I swear to God,
bro. Simple. You [ __ ] little Welsh
[ __ ] Mother's life, bro.
You're not the one that's sat on YouTube,
bro. You know what I
mean, bro? [ __ ] I will do it, bro.
Terry, you know I'll do it as well,
mate. Like, you know, I've been all over
England. Yeah. If this little [ __ ]
Welsh [ __ ] thinks she's going to [ __ ]
state me, I'm going to get this
[ __ ] killed, bro. I swear to
God. Mark my words, bro. I I will do it
on both of them. I will make sure they
will get the [ __ ] kicked out of them
like they [ __ ] deserve. Yeah. Here's
difference. Yeah, bro. Listen. I will
make sure if that little Welsh [ __ ]
wants to snake me, I swear to God I'll
go all around Cord and I'll pull up post
of the [ __ ] I swear to God, I will pull
up posters and I'll [ __ ] get
that [ __ ] killed. Yeah. If he even
thinks he's going to play two signs,
I'll go c him tomorrow. Simple. I swear
to God I will. Yeah. If this little
[ __ ] Welsh little [ __ ] shagging nanny
little [ __ ] sheep shaggger thinks
she's going to snake me, I swear to God
I'm going to put up posting everywhere.
Yeah. And I'm going to send him that
video as well. Yeah. Don't [ __ ] with me,
you little Welsh [ __ ] Yeah. I swear to
God I'll pass them all around Cardiff.
Like I will go around tomorrow, bro. I
swear to God. It is one stop to live in
Paddington. Test me. Test me. You sheep
shagger. Test me. I swear to God. Yeah.
You want to be a snake? I swear to God,
you're never walking around college
again, bro. And I swear to God, all of
the posters that I put out, I'm going to
call him a nons a dirty [ __ ] I swear to
God. Don't do it with me, bro. Don't do
it in your nanny's house with me, bro.
Yeah. Simple, bro. He said these
mothers. Listen, bro. Listen. Yeah, I'll
be politely. I'll do I'm actually a
polite person. You know what I'm saying?
I'm a polite person. [ __ ] with me and
you're never walking around quiet enough
again. Yeah, you little sheep shagging
little [ __ ] I will go there tomorrow.
Test me. Test me, sheep shagger. I'll
say it to him as well. Test me, you
sheep shagging [ __ ] I'll make sure you
never walk around there again. And I'm
going to go all I'll go all around the
outskirts of Wales to make sure you
never walk there again, bro. Mother's
life, you're not walking there again.
Test me. Test me, sheep shagger. Simple.
Test me. You're only about 10, 20 minutes
away. Yeah. One second,
guys. Simple. I will go there tomorrow.
It ain't no joke. Listen, you remember
what I told you before about these
posters, bro? When was I ever lying,
bro? Come on. You're a [ __ ]
Yeah, let this [ __ ] chat. [ __ ] with me.
Easy, easy, Terry. [ __ ] with Yeah. Simple. That
mean. Yeah. LT. Listen, the question is,
Terry, why didn't you meet LT?
Yeah. Why didn't you meet LT, bro? The
question is why didn't you meet me LT?
Like the thing is like I will do it to
both of them, bro. Listen, I swear to
God, bro, this little [ __ ] thinks he's
going to play two sides. I will do it
both at the same time. Talking about
[ __ ] spend about 4050 pound and post
it again. I'll make sure these little
[ __ ] get their [ __ ] head kicked in.
I swear to God. and they'll know they
never come on YouTube and ever do their
[ __ ] [ __ ] again. I swear to [ __ ]
God. I promise you. I'll make sure they
get their [ __ ] head kicked in. Is
that as random as it [ __ ] sounds, bro?
Yeah. You was ready to meet LT. No, you
weren't ready to meet no one. Yeah, you
weren't ready to meet no one. You was
not ready to meet [ __ ] no one, bro.
Shut the [ __ ] up.
But if this little [ __ ] chase, this
little sheep shagging little [ __ ] who
shags his n he's going to play two
sides. I swear to God that [ __ ] better
move out of Cardiff, bro. I promise you he's
moving. I promise you that little sheep
shagged little [ __ ] [ __ ] better
move out of Wales. I'm telling you.
Yeah. You're telling me, bro, you
weren't you weren't supposed Listen,
bro. Listen. He's going to get himself
hurt, bro. Listen, if you don't
understand, yeah, this is not Cardiff.
Is it? Sorry. This is not Scotland, bro.
But it's about six, seven hours away.
It's Cardiff. Like, trust me, you're
going to get yourself hurt. Trust me,
bro. Look at how many people ran to the
police [ __ ] last
time. I'll tell him that, bro. I'll tell
him that as well. I like, please allow
it, bro. Please. Like, chill. You're
going to get yourself hurt, bro. I swear
down. Keep your calm, man.
You know what I'm
saying? And I'll do both of them at the
same time. You know, cuz one's in Wales
and one's in like, Listen, you're a little [ __ ] Yeah.
Simple. Any of your [ __ ] I swear to
God, I'm going to go Cardiff tomorrow,
bro. Let I'll make the video right now.
I will make the video right now. Tell
me. One second, bro. Yeah.
Why go to corn if listen man listen
listen I went to turn pike lane I went
to turnpike [ __ ] lane listen and
guess what Terry you didn't show up yeah
you did not show up when I went to your
area. Yeah, this little chase, I will
pass a post of him and get his [ __ ]
ugly head kicked in. He was lucky the
first time, bro. This little Welsh
little patchy beard [ __ ] was lucky the
first time. Yeah, Terry, stop fronting,
bro. Man, come to your area two years
ago. You did not come out. Yeah. Do you
understand? Stop fronting, bro. It's
embarrassing. Yeah. I swear to God, bro.
Listen. Yeah. When I'm done with this B
on Saturday, I will go back to Wales for
the fourth or fifth time I've been
there. It won't bother me, bro. Listen,
it will not bother me. I don't care. Do
you understand this little patchy beard
Welsh [ __ ] I will violate him and his
man to his face. How about that one?
It's not No, it's no. Listen, Terry,
bro, listen. You did not come out the
last time. You called me to your area.
You did not come out. Yeah.
Listen, bro. Stop it. It's embarrassing,
bro. Come on, man. Manto man, it's
embarrassing, bro. You're starting to
You're starting to It's starting to be
less and less about it every time now,
bro. You understand?
to go back to Wales. This guy is getting
violated. Mothers, I swear to God, he's
getting violated. Yeah. If I go back to Wales, I
personally violate this country. It's
not a It's not a joke. Yeah. Listen.
Yeah. Go back to Wales and violate this
country. Oh, do it, mate. It ain't no
problem. Yeah. We're not all keyboard
warriors like you. You understand me,
brother? Yeah. We're not all like you.
You need to
understand [ __ ] up. [ __ ] it. Who gives a [ __ ] bro? It's embarrassing,
lad. Mate, if he does not meet me, he's
going to get posters put up about him.
It's mate, it's standard. Listen, bro.
This [ __ ] wants to come on YouTube and
snake me. He will get post put up about
him just like not legs. I don't care.
Listen, bro. Mark my [ __ ] words. I
don't care whether he meets me or not.
He will be getting posters put up about
him and he will be get getting his head
smashed in. End of. Listen, bro. You
want to block someone, that's fine. No
one cares, bro. You in Wales. You want
to snake me, I will come to your country
again and call you out again and again
and make sure you get your head smashed
in. Simple. Simple, bro. It's fine.
Whether you meet, whether you don't,
you're getting posted put up about you.
I promise you, bro. Yeah. If I'm going
to go back to your country, mate, it's
not going to be for nothing. Yeah.
Simple. You listen, Terry. Terry man
went to your area two years ago. You did
not show up. Stop it. It's embarrassing,
bro. Yeah. This [ __ ] wants to state me.
I promise you I'm going to pass a post
up of this ugly [ __ ] all around this
area. A man at his [ __ ] ugly n bro. I
will make sure him and his [ __ ] ugly
sasticated nan will never be leaving
anywhere ever again. Yeah, simple.
That's it, bro. Mothers, that's it, bro.
You want to block people, that's fine.
Cool. No one cares. You want to You want
to You want to You want to You want to
snake people, you know, bro? I'll come
back again. I don't care. Listen, I'll
do on a Saturday. I'll pl them all over
a Saturday and I'll [ __ ] your life up,
[ __ ] No one cares. Simple.
Yeah. Yeah, I got his picture where
they're both together, bro. It's calm.
Cool. Fine. If you want to do it that
way, I'll come to Wales next week. Cool.
I don't care. I got a passport now
anyways. Simple buff.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah. I'm
like I mean that T. Yeah.
Yeah, mind that give a [ __ ] But any
time you think you're going to slate me,
I will come to your country for the
fifth time, bro. I will come to your
country easily for the fifth time. It
ain't no problem, bro. It ain't no [ __ ]
problem. It ain't no problem, bro. It's
no problem to me. Yeah, remember that.
It is no problem to me, bro.