Yo yo on that.
No loudness. No being [ __ ] loud or anything, mate.
About that earlier. I didn't take my medication.
Yeah, I didn't take my medication. So
just how it is, isn't it?
Waiting for my bed in the to dry in the
dryer and um put it out and done.
>> Yeah, be happy with that to be honest.
I'll be happy with that, mate.
No, no, no, no. Mhm.
I do a little video.
Looks like a Here you go.
Yo, vlog one, bro. I went Liverpool
Street, man. I saw a couple of
good-looking women, but obviously I
couldn't approach because I was with my mom,
and I don't think I would have anyways.
It sucks, man. This is why I don't like
going out like far away cuz you see
people that like
you want to speak to
um and obviously if you try to speak to them then
you go around in circles
it's it's [ __ ] in it bro and it
reminds you oh damn I've got to use
[ __ ] escort for the rest of my
[ __ ] life. How depressing is that man?
It's depressing as [ __ ] is it, man? I
should really go out this week, but I
can't stomach it, man.
It's too soon. It really is too soon.
Crazy, isn't it?
And like you should see the look on
everyone's face. They're all [ __ ]
miserable. And a lot of the women, they
just look like NPCs as well. I notic
that in Liverpool Street. It's [ __ ]
Yeah, that's the only thing I've got to
look forward to.
Like if cuz if you try and speak to a
woman, obviously you're going to get the
same [ __ ] Obviously, I was with my mom,
so I couldn't. And even if I wasn't, I
don't think I would. To be honest, I
probably would, to be honest. I don't
think I'd be able to help myself.
Uh, it was nice, man, but it was
depressing cuz I saw some good-looking
women and that obviously I couldn't
approach them because I was with my mom.
It's a good thing I was with my mom
because if I did approach them, I would
have just went around in circles again.
People saying they're not interested.
Mind games. It's depressing as [ __ ]
That's why I don't like to go that far out, bro. It's depressing.
Like I said, I should really go out this
week, but I ain't doing it.
But I got new jeans, but I've worn them
once and I'll keep and I'll save them
for when I go out again.
It's a [ __ ] up country, is it, bro? This
cuz if you approach women, you just get
the same [ __ ] in it. So, like I was with my mom.
the sad fact like I'd have to use
escorts my whole life or [ __ ] live in
Thailand. Oh, Antman's friend has also
moved to Thailand. Some good-looking guy
and apparently he couldn't get women
either. So, he he's in Thailand now and
he's never coming back. Um,
so I was like, "Wow, your friend's even
gone living there now.
Damn." I was like, "Oh, Jesus Christ."
So, we're definitely not all the only
one then, are we?
Yeah. I don't know. It's It's a hard one, bro.
And this guy's good looking as well.
Yeah. I remember the guy An was telling
me he said he booked it to go Tuesday
and he said, "Oh, he might not come cuz
he's scared of fly." And he ended up
going. I was like, "What?"
So, I was like, "Okay, now yeah, you
definitely need to go now, bro.
That's mad. I didn't know his friend
went living there as well. Yeah, man.
I got a football bet for Saturday. I
could go out Saturday. I could go out
tomorrow, but I just don't see the point.
There really is no point.
You're never going to meet anyone here.
You're never going to meet a woman here.
So, there's no point. You know, doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter about the price, bro. We
We got the money to burn.
I told you I'm not skin. No one knows
what I have. No one knows what No one
knows what I don't have, bro. You know,
they fit as well.
cuz I remember my size. That's why I
stick with the same Ammani jeans because
I know my size
and I can't wear cheap jeans. I just
can't. So that's that. No,
they upgraded over the years as well.
The colors changed their trousers.
I was going to get a 100 pound hoodie
today, but I didn't bother.
I'm not really a lover of hoodies. Like
if there's a hoodie on sale for like450
in All Saints, then I'll buy it cuz I
can wear it the whole time. Wear it
inside, but I'm not going to pay £100
for [ __ ] hoodies, jeans. They're
going to last me for two years and I'll
wear them whenever I go out. So that are
my Ruper the Bear trousers. So,
just chilling for the moment. Went to Liverpool Street.
Saw some good-looking women. Obviously
couldn't approach cuz I was with my mom.
That's dangerous cuz if I wasn't with my
mom, I would have had to approach
someone, bro. And this is why what I
wanted to avoid.
Uh 33 waist, 32 leg.
Yeah, we're going out uh not next
Tuesday, uh the Tuesday after the next.
So, we're going to have to work it
around certain times. So, I don't see any women. Um
cuz it's depressing that you have to use
escort all your life when you should be
able to get with someone, you know? It's
not like you haven't done enough pro
approaches. I [ __ ] approached loads
of people. I should have to [ __ ] keep doing this.
I'd love to go out tomorrow. I'd love to
go out Saturday, but it's too soon.
It's too soon, bro.
You need like 6 months off. Like you do, bro.
And another thing is like you get to
save like if you obviously I I've got
money. I can go out, but
say you you you stop for a little bit
more. You you will save money.
So it benefits you better, you know,
like than going out dealing with the
same old [ __ ]
We can go out tomorrow, spend 80, 150,
200, what, 250, whatever. But it's like,
what's the point? It's always going to
be the same here, you know?
I'm sure my my mama catches me looking
at people, bro.
Or maybe we'll go somewhere more local. You know, yeah,
if I was going to do anything sad, I'll
just get an escort. So yeah.
Nope. I had an Indian, bro. Why am I
going to have pizza? I already ate I
already ate a lot of food. I went to a
restaurant. I just come back from a [sighs]
Yep. He's a virgin. nonslegs of the
virgin. There's loads of virgins on here.
I'd love to get with some of them women
that I saw today, bro. It's impossible.
Just not interested in this country in it.
You right, Kieran. I went to Liverpool
Street with my mom. Hope you like the
jeans, by the And I saw some like
good-looking women and I wanted to
approach but obviously I was with my mom.
Lucky I was with my mom, bro, because I
would have ended up doing it and then I
would have ended up depressed and it's
just it's always a cycle in this
country, bro. This is why I'm leaving.
I'm gone in 3 weeks. So
it's bad. It's really really depressing.
Bro, did you go to Devon by the way? You going or?
Yeah, I could go for a drink tomorrow or
Saturday, but I'm not doing it, bro. I
need like literally um
I need uh
I go to Thailand, bro. I need a [ __ ] um
I need six months off, bro. And I think
we're six We're at six weeks now. So, a
month and a half
or at least until December, mid December.
minimum, bro. Minimum
cuz it's not like it's it's not good, bro.
This is why I don't like going out to
central and stuff, bro.
Yep. I have.
Did you see my videos, Kier? my dating app videos,
but people tell you to go on dating apps
to get sex.
I'd go to Devon if I was you, mate. You
got more options than me. I've got nothing.
[ __ ] I got nothing at all.
Have to use escorts for the rest of my
life. Unless I live in [ __ ] Thailand.
How depressing is that?
It's near um
Plymouth and Cornwall and stuff like that.
Yeah, my 200 pound jeans come today.
Kieran, I got some 200 pound money
jeans. They come today, lad.
The skinn virgin could never afford them.
That skint version could never afford
them. That kind of designer.
Yeah. at £200 they cost me, bro. Well, 190.
Show the jeans again. I put them away, bro. So, yeah.
Yeah, cuz he's skin.
Yeah, cuz he's a skin [ __ ] I want my
Stone Island today and my 200 pound
jeans cuz I'm not a skint.
You know what I mean?
You got 600 pound left in it. So yeah,
that should be enough to go Deon and
that ain't it.
But if I had 600 to my name, I'll just
gamble, mate. I would just gamble. Try
and win like 20k. I'm mad, bro. Trust me.
But I have enough money. I don't have
loads of money, but I have enough money. So, um, yeah.
What you wear above doesn't matter, bro.
As long as you got a nice pair of jeans,
nice trainers, it doesn't matter what
what t-shirt you got.
I love basketball shorts and All Saints t-shirts.
I like All Saints T-shirts and basketball shorts,
but obviously that's like the summer.
That's the [ __ ] thing about the winter
is you really got to dress up. Whereas
like in the summer you buy nice All
Saints t-shirt, nice shorts, and white
Vapor Maxes. You're sorted.
But I don't like the heat. I do prefer
the winter cuz I don't like the heat. But
yeah, but anyone can buy trainers, bro.
That doesn't mean he's got money. I can
buy trainers right now if I wanted to.
The guy is not what he says he is. That
L J is not what he says he is.
And there's no need to be jealous, bro.
I've got more money than him. them jeans
is worth more than any jeans he's ever
worn in his life.
Bro, anyone can buy trainers, bro. The
guys on benefits. I can buy trainers.
The reason I didn't is cuz I don't need any,
you know, and there's not many trainers
I like. I like Vapor Maxes and you can't
get them in the [ __ ] um shops
anymore. You have to buy them online.
But vapor maxes are sick. They need to
sort the backs out though. Yeah. Yeah.
As long as you got a nice new pair of
trainers and nice jeans, doesn't matter
what's on the top part of your body.
Like I said,
it's the way it is, man.
You get me? Yeah. Anyone can buy
trainers, bro. I can buy some trainers right now
if I wanted to.
I've only got two pair of trainers.
Harachis and them ones I wore today.
They still look fresh.
Yeah, Vapor Max is a stick. I like Vapor
Maxes. I got the white pair and the
black pair when I won that four grand.
Always lush. It was [ __ ] lush. Not anymore.
I used to have them, but the backs [ __ ]
up on them. I had a white pair and a
black pair. White for the summer, black
for the winter.
So, all you need is nice Well, you don't
even need designer jeans. All you need
is nice trainers, but I just get
designer jeans cuz I'm used to Ammani
jeans. They're the only jeans I like. I
like rubbing my butt and knowing there's
like a badge at the back. I'm weird,
bro. Like certain habits and that in it.
So, but you don't need designer jeans.
I mean, you can go to Next and buy black
jeans as long as you got nice trainers.
Um, the Vapor Maxes are [ __ ] so good,
bro. Like I said, they're the only ones
I like. How much are they the Vapor
Maxes? Let me see. Yeah. 205.
They're outdated though.
Yeah, mine were 214. I might buy them.
Mine were 214.
You know what? I might buy them, bro.
You can't get them in the shop. You've
got to order them.
Maybe I'll buy them,
but they're very hard to um
I might buy them, bro.
What size trainers are you? I'm 10.
How much? No, these are not. No, no.
These are not vapor matches. You can
only get them from one place. I'm sure
these are Air Max Plus.
Yeah, then I like Vapor Maxes.
Yeah, you can only buy them.
No. Oh, they are here. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm 10. I've always I think I'm
like nine and a half now, though. To be fair,
I am tempted to buy these trainers, bro.
But do I really need trainers right now?
That's the thing.
Just the madest the mad thing with this
Kin is like you can go out right look
your best. You can literally go out and
look your best
and you'll still get rejected by women.
That's the most [ __ ] up thing about it.
and you'd still like literally get rejected. Mad.
Maybe I'll buy them next month. I've got
the money, but like
don't really need them right now.
Spin it on roulette. Red or black?
No, I can buy them. I can buy them, bro.
But obviously I need to save for a
thingy in it.
So, you know, you said you got £600 in
your bank. That wouldn't be enough for me, bro.
Even though that is a good amount of
money, like for most people, to me, that isn't enough.
I need like I don't know, bro. But
that's why I would just end up gambling.
That's why I would just end up the [ __ ]
up gambling, lad. Yeah.
I might buy these trainers, bro.
But the thing is with these Vapor Maxes,
the backs go on them.
That's the thing. The backs go on them
after a couple of months.
No, I'm going I I I'll buy them next
month. I'll buy them next month. [ __ ] it.
I got the jeans. I'll wear them a couple
of times, put them away, then buy the trainers.
They're sick trainers though, bro. Oh,
this is a thing about the backs.
Trying to think. Yeah.
Yeah, they're the ones below.
How much does your jeans cost?
How much does your change cost?
Yeah, I like basketball shorts, bro.
They're my faves. Basketball shorts.
And if they're jeans, then like I said,
they have to be expensive ones. So,
they're expens They have to be expensive ones.
So, I've got some stone island jumpers.
So, if I buy the Vapor Maxes,
I don't know.
The money is not as I don't have as much
money as I used to caring. I still got
money in that but
not as much as I used to have.
But I still have money obviously. I can
buy the trainers, bro. It's not a
problem. I can buy them, but um yeah.
I'm tempted to buy these 205 trainers,
Grievy. I'm very, very tempted, lad. Very tempted.
No, it's not that. Like, I've got money,
Kieran. Yeah, but I'd rather save it and
put it towards something else. I don't
go out drinking anymore because I'd
rather have the money. I've got the
money to go out and do it every week if
I wanted to, but I'd rather just
Nah, I don't even think it No, I don't
think it's about the money, bro. With
the going out, I don't think it's about the money.
I don't think it's about the money when
going out. I think I just can't be bothered and
I need to do something else now. I don't
I don't think it is, bro. I've got ways
to get money back and that, but
I mean it's like
the only way to get money nowadays is I
I've been winning money the past two
months, Kieran. That's the only reason
I've been able to do do this stuff
cuz I've been winning money, haven't I?
Like football. I put 50 on the roulette
the other day, got it to 150. I want 500.
There is no side I've got. I mean, yeah.
I don't know.
If I bought them vapor maxes, I'm
definitely going out approaching, bro.
Definitely going out.
Groovy, I'm tempted to get these Vapor Maxes.
Very tempted. Very tempted.
Yeah, I saw some good looking women today. Greavvesy
sucks that I'll never be able to get with one.
He's not bloody interested.
That's my new favorite word now. Bloody.
You like that music? E.
That's my new favorite word here. Bloody.
I don't know.
Sucks. You can't meet anyone. Is it
Kieran? It does suck you can't meet anyone.
You want to see the jeans, Kieran?
You ain't seen them, have you? [ __ ]
I'll put him away, but I'll get them out for you. See, look.
200 worth of jeans. Look,
I I could wear that. I could wear that with this.
Look, this this right here, that's over £400
just on two items, bro.
£400 on two items.
I could still rock the [ __ ] thing.
Yeah, I went Liverpool Street today. I
saw some women, bro. It's [ __ ]
depressing as [ __ ] So depressing.
Have to [ __ ] stick to [ __ ] escort
your whole [ __ ] life.
It's depressing as [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, it's depressing, man. Very depressing.
Very, very depressing. Yep.
But none are interested, are they?
But none are interested.
sucks, isn't it? Well, at least I'll go
to Thailand in 3 weeks.
At least I'll be away from this [ __ ]
forever. Also, another thing, Pokemon,
Ant-Man's friend's gone gone to China
now and he's living there and he's a
pretty boy. We refer to him as uh we
refer to him as pretty boy. And I'm
like, what? He's even in Thailand now?
Yep. He's gone to Thailand. We didn't
think he was going to make it because uh
he's scared of flying, but nope, he did.
I was like, bro, that's how you know
it's getting bad when you got people
like him going [ __ ] Thailand.
So, I'll be gone in 3 weeks.
To be honest, it wasn't that bad.
It wasn't that bad. I obviously I did
see a few women, but it could be worse.
I bro I think this country is [ __ ] you
know bro you know uh there's certain
shops in Liverpool Street that are
closing down and I'm thinking what is
this happening in London now this is
happening in London now where where
things are closing down oh [ __ ]
yeah things in London are closing down now
that's insane saying this country is [ __ ] Seriously. But
it is depressing. It is depressing, bro.
That's why I don't go out. I don't have
to see it.
Yeah. But I didn't expect it in London, bro. Cuz
yeah, the country's finished, bro.
There's a pub near where my mom lives
and it's like a Weather Spoons, bro. We
went past it. No one was in there. And
obviously people go in there. I see
people, bro. No one was there. It's
right next to the tube station. Yeah,
that's madness. I don't know how these
places stay in business.
I don't know what to do.
What can you actually do, Pokémon other
than go to Thailand? You can't do nothing.
Yeah, I've noticed that as well, especially leads.
See, the thing is I can do what I want.
I can go to Manchester tomorrow. I can
go to Leads tomorrow. I've got enough
money to do what I want, you know? But,
you know, I need to take a break from
it, bro. I really, really do. Like, it's
I can't get into this [ __ ] again, bro, anytime soon.
But yeah, leads definitely leads is rammed.
I remember when I went to leads I've
only been leadeds once and bro it was shocker block,
bro. I I had results up north, bro.
Barely. Okay. I went to Leeds, I didn't
get nothing. I went to Manchester 10
times. I only got laid once.
But yeah, I was thinking of going Wales
tomorrow or something. I I don't think
I'd go out in London to go out again.
Women do go out in London, bro, but it's
mainly tourists because everyone's
skinting London cuz it's expensive.
People, they do go out.
And another thing I need to do is I need
to if [clears throat] I was to go out
tomorrow, I'd go somewhere like Wales or
like you said, Leadeds. I need to go
somewhere where there's less competition
because this is what the problem is.
They've got too many s like you need to
go somewhere where there's less competition.
cuz this is always going to be your
downfall. You know, that's the problem in London.
But yeah, leads. I remember leads. It was rammed.
Oh my god, it was rammed. People, there
is women that go out in London, but
there is, bro. But it's not like Yeah,
but Manchester's I don't know why I like
Manchester cuz it's just like London. But
Or maybe I'd go Liverpool to be fair.
I don't know. Or Wales. I don't know. I
got a football bet for Saturday,
but I haven't had results up north, bro. Not really.
London's better for like day game.
London's better for street approaching,
but clubbing out of London definitely.
Would you agree on that?
So, if you're going clubbing, yeah, go
out of London. But if you're a street
approaching, I'd say London's definitely
the one. Um, because there's loads of
people and you stay anonymous. [ __ ]
I don't know, bro. It's [ __ ] up. It's
just all [ __ ]
I don't know.
You like boobs or ass? Lucky for you,
I've got both.
Yeah, Manchester. But I wouldn't go
Manchester. I need to go Liverpool.
I've only been Liverpool once, so I need
to go back there if I was going to go anywhere.
Yeah, it was good when I went out with
Monty. It was a good night out.
Going out with Monty was good,
but they just aren't interested in this country. No,
I didn't know about that. What do you
think, Kieran? Do you think they're
interested in this country or not? I
don't think so because of my experiences.
I [ __ ] with that [ __ ] in South
America. She got my mom's [ __ ] Instagram deactivated.
And the more I think about it, bro, it's
like, should you really be dealing with these women?
And then you think like it's probably
not a good idea. Um,
so what? You don't think they're having
sex, Kieran? You don't think people my
age having sex? Yes, she got my mom's
Insta deleted. And the more I think
about it, bro, the more you need to
think, is it really worth
pursuing women, putting up with women?
It isn't, bro.
And man said it will always be the same
here. You know this.
Yeah, that's what he said. Is he right?
>> Yeah. I don't know. I don't know.
Yeah. You remember going wherever Peter
Belly's little legs take him?
I don't know.
It's just depressing.
I just I just don't like Do you know why
I don't deal with them anymore, Kieran?
Because it's just toxic. That's why I
gave up, bro. Cuz it's just toxic.
You get what I mean, Kier? It's just
toxic. And I just like the peace and quiet.
So, I'm sacrificing my peace and quiet
now to deal with him again. If I deal
It sucks, isn't it?
I should have to be trying again, bro.
I've already tried a million times. You
know what I mean? So yeah.
Yeah. Ken, like I said, if I was you,
I'd just go Deon and approach and [ __ ]
He won't sabotage it cuz he doesn't know
women I speak to, you know.
And I can't deal with the lies. I can't
get with you cuz you're old. You're too
old. You're older than me. I can't deal
with it. It's just toxic, bro. You know,
I wish I could just meet somebody that
my the same age as me. That's normal.
But you can't. They're not normal. They
just lead you on and play games.
So, I'm not prepared to sacrifice my
peaceful life just yet, bro. I'm sorry. I'm not
I could go to Manchester and and see
that escort, that Chinese escort that
keeps messaging me.
Well, obviously my phone's blocked, so
it's going to be a bit hard. I could go
there and send it, but it'd just be
pointless cuz it's always the same.
It is sad, isn't it?
Oh, cuz I didn't pay the phone bill and
so they just blocked my [ __ ] phone,
so I just used my phone on Wi-Fi.
And to be honest with you, it just feels
normal using your phone on Wi-Fi.
Just use your phone on Wi-Fi in it.
I've had no problems. Most places have
Wi-Fi, so I just connected to the Wi-Fi.
Long story. My phone. It's a long story, but yeah,
I'm not going to Devon. Kieran's going
to Deon. Why am I going to go Devon?
I've got [snorts] no reason to go
anywhere but Thailand. It's the same here, bro.
They're [ __ ] They are just toxic
[ __ ] Look at that [ __ ] I had with
that woman in South America. Bro, if any
of these people lived in England, I
would seriously hurt them, bro. I'm not even joking.
I I started messaging her family and
that saying, "Oh, you know your
daughter's uh you know your daughter's
buy and that." Yeah. And she is by and
she wrote it on Reddit. How do I come
out and that? Yeah. Don't [ __ ] with me,
bro. Don't [ __ ] with me. And this is
what I mean. It's just toxic. And people
don't need that in their life.
You know, it might sound funny to you,
but it ain't funny to me. They give it,
but they can't take it. USA is all over again.
Just like I told Adam diamond it the
other day about his ex. I said this is
about this is your ex. This is your ex.
Yeah. I said I said to him, "Bro, this
is what your ex was doing." Yeah.
That was her ex. Yeah.
And even when I was speaking to her
friend for like 5 hours, she's like,
"Oh, you don't want that kind of
negativity. You you would have got
[ __ ] if you come here."
Um, mate, and I was about to say, "Bro,
really? Would I really? Really, bro?"
I'd slap her up in front of her
boyfriend and I'd slap her boyfriend up
in front of her.
Yeah. Good for them. I'm not going out.
I'm staying in.
They can be in they could be going out
naked. I still wouldn't be going out.
I'm not doing it anymore.
So there's no point trying to convince
me cuz I ain't going out, lad.
Nothing's going to change my mind. Been
there on it. Worn a t-shirt. [snorts]
Been there on it. on a t-shirt.
And they've all got boyfriends
apparently, so I don't want to come in between that,
don't they, Kier? And they've all got
boyfriends, so they say.
You don't want to be speaking to a load
of women that's got boyfriends.
Yeah, they've all got boyfriends,
apparently. I don't want to bother
people in relationships.
No, I'll be chilling tomorrow, lad.
I'd rather just save money.
You actually you just rather just save
money in it.
Well, I don't know about you, but I do.
I'd rather save money, lad, [snorts]
cuz I've been through enough [ __ ] with them. So,
you know what else are you supposed to
do? [ __ ] sake.
Everyone you get to a certain point
where you just give up.
Everyone is different. Some people give
up before after.
What does someone do?
given up and they haven't even tried
nowhere near as much as me
and they've given up. Sorry.
I don't know, bro.
I don't know.
And the thing is, Pokemon, you can't
even find someone on the internet
because of the simps and the white knights.
That's the thing is you can barely get a
conversation out of a woman on the
internet because of the simps and the white knights.
But I'm not dealing with their [ __ ]
cuz I'm I've I've got an ego, bro, and
I'm not putting up with their [ __ ]
anymore for the sake of sex. I'm not
doing it, you know. I'd rather pay an
escort, you know. Yeah, okay, it might
not be the same, but it's better than nothing.
you know, you win a football bet and then um
you know, it pays for it and it's better
than nothing. So, what what do you want
me to do? Sit there and put up with
their [ __ ] Put up with their games?
You know, it's not like I've um I've
been getting dates recently or anything.
So, it's not like you've had a date
every two weeks. You've had nothing.
You're not It's not suddenly just going to change.
So, and I'm not putting up with their
[ __ ] I'm not dealing with their
It's like my sister, right? My other
sister that I don't speak to. She wish
me happy birthday, but I will never
message her again cuz of my ego
and she will never message me. I
probably could. I speak to my other
sister and obviously my mom and
and I'm not putting up with their [ __ ]
Simple. It's it's it's that simple, bro.
It's different if you're a virgin, right?
Then it's different, you know? I'm not
putting up with that [ __ ]
Not at this age, lad. You know,
it's that bad Pokemon that I don't even
regret when I don't approach. You know,
when most people, right,
approach, they don't approach and they
regret it. I don't regret it when I
don't do it.
I don't give a [ __ ] cuz I already know
the result. See, that's how [ __ ] up it
is. You see, it should be the opposite.
It should be that when you approach a woman, um
um when you don't approach a woman, you
should regret it. Me, I don't regret it.
I don't give a [ __ ] Like I won't I won't think.
Yeah, it doesn't matter if I Well, I do
know. That's the thing. I do know.
That's how you know it's [ __ ] up when
you don't regret not doing it. Cuz I
already know the result. I have a boyfriend.
I have a boyfriend. I'm not interested.
It would either be one of them two things.
Oh, they'll give you their number and play games.
They they turn you into a nasty person.
That's what they do. They they change
people. That's what these women do.
That's what these [ __ ] women do.
It's like, you know, when you're
addicted to gambling and you stop
and you change as a person over like two
weeks in a good way or if you're
addicted to drugs or anything.
When you deal with women, you change as
a person because of their toxicness,
their tox toxicity that you have to deal
with when you're dealing with these women.
You know what I mean, lad?
It's proper [ __ ] up.
Nah, it's not boring for me, bro.
It's not boring for me. Nah, not for me.
I take a little bit of boarding, bro.
Over toxic behavior and mind games.
I'll take the bor I'll take being bored
any day of the week. I'll sit here bored
out my head. Sir, >> cuz
I I already know the result.
There's three results, Pokémon. I'm not
interested. I have a boyfriend. They
give you their number and then they
leave your ass on. The end. Nothing else ever happens.
Uh, nothing else ever happens. Yeah.
And yeah, like I said, I didn't get any
dates out of them 10 numbers, so why am
I going to try again? It's [ __ ] pathetic, man.
>> No, I won't regret it. I don't regret
it. Me? I don't regret it.
That's what I'm trying to say to you. I
wouldn't regret it because I already
know the result. I can't do it for the
sake of my own mental health. That's
what I'm saying to you. I can't do it
because then it then it becomes depressing again.
You know, they I I I wouldn't get
depressed. I wouldn't regret it because
I know the result.
See these PUA artists, they make you
believe that when you approach your your
life changes with women. You'll meet
someone, you'll get a girlfriend. That's
what they that's what they tell people.
So to think about it, we've been lied to
our whole life.
If you think about it, so back then
before I done it, I'd regret it. Yeah.
I'd be like, "Oh, damn. I wish I'd done
it." Cuz I didn't know what would have
happened. But I know now. I know what
happens. I've approached more than
anyone in the world. I know exactly what
they say. I know exactly what they do.
And I know exactly what they're like.
So that's it.
Yeah, it is depressing. Yeah, obviously
that's why I don't go out that far. But
obviously I went for a meal with my mom.
So yeah, obviously
I don't regret it though. I wouldn't
regret not approaching now.
So it's just depressing lad.
If you don't find the sh co attractive, you're gay.
You little copycat.
The little copycat.
>> I'm going to give you a nogy little copycat.
Why does he say that?
If you don't find shore attractive,
you're gay. Why does he say that [ __ ] bro?
It's so weird. Why does he say [ __ ] like that, bro? [ __ ] weird.
Yep. It's not even about even [ __ ]
Even if you just wanted to get with a
woman and date a woman, say you had to
wait a month, 2 months for sex. So what,
bro? It's not even just about sex. It's
even if you wanted a relationship.
Yeah. Get her. Yeah. Exactly. Even if
you just didn't want sex. That's what
I'm trying to say. Yeah.
Yeah. It's [ __ ] It is [ __ ]
There's nothing you can do.
Even if you look your best and you're
confident, you still won't be able to
get a woman. That's what I mean.
And when they try and say women don't go
for looks and stuff,
they're more picky than men. They're
more shallow than men. I'm decent
looking. And I've had women make excuses
why they won't get with me.
And I look like [ __ ] normal. I look decent. Whatever.
But that's what I'm saying. They
They are more shallow and picky than men, you know.
No, even if you just wanted friends,
even if you wanted to generally just
meet somebody and you could wait a month
for the sex, you still wouldn't do it.
I mean, I've put out videos where I
haven't even finished my sentence and
someone said they're not interested.
sent them to Ricky
and he ran away
cuz he knows what I'm saying is the truth.
This is the truth. This is real life.
What you see on my channel is real life.
The dating app's not working, that's real life.
The women saying they're not interested,
that's real life. None of this, oh, go
on dating apps to get laid. Oh, women go
for personality is [ __ ] It's bollocks, bro.
Really, really [ __ ]
Yeah, they won't be friends. They won't
do anything. Lad,
she went out to drive me mad, bro.
He used to drive [clears throat] me mad
when I had hope. Back when I had hope,
[snorts] you know,
was a madness.
Yeah, not even offering money works. I
thought that was going to work to be honest.
Surprised it never
surprised it never worked.
So you have to be single and sexist forever.
So it seems there.
Did you see the ones where when I tried
to speak to someone, they said straight
away they weren't interested
Pokémon. But they say women go for personality. [snorts]
You know what I mean? Like they said uh
they say that women go for personality,
but I'm sure you saw the ones where they
said they weren't interested straight away. Huh.
So it's for the best that I just gave up
to be honest.
That just annoys me that does.
There's ones where they would just say
straight away they weren't interested.
But women go for personality. It's how
people are acting. That's [snorts] why I
left the comments open, bro. Yeah,
that personality excuse is so lame
to cover up the fact they've got unrealistic expectations.
Yeah, talking about women, I went to
Liverpool Street with my mom. I saw a
lot of good-looking women.
Was depressing to be honest. This is why
I don't like going out far.
Yeah. It's depressing, isn't it, bro?
You can't find anyone interested in this country. Yeah.
It's mad, eh?
It's a hookup culture. Go on the apps, Pokémon.
Yeah. Go on the apps.
Meet women on the apps. They say [sighs]
they say meet women on the apps, don't they?
I don't know.
I don't know what we're going to do, bro.
We're basically [ __ ]
Really is [ __ ]
It's disgusting me of all people,
though. I shouldn't have to go out and
try again, bro. I've tried enough. You know,
think about it that way, bro. I've tried enough.
I should have to try again. I should
have to think about think about trying again. [ __ ] sake.
[snorts] You don't know. Women, they're
not all the same.
>> What can you do, bro? So depressing
these [ __ ] say that, "Oh, it's
a it's like a part-time job, brother.
It's a full-time job." It's not a
part-time job. It's a full-time job,
you know, and you don't even get
anything out of your efforts either. 10
numbers, not a single date.
Why? Who in their right mind would try
again after that? It's [ __ ] mad.
I don't know. [ __ ] It Oh, well.
[snorts] No, it's really bad.
What to do? People
on Reddit say that you can't see the future.
I'm not being funny, lad, but if you can
go out and get 10 numbers and not even
get a date,
it doesn't look good, does it?
I think I can tell you exactly what the
future holds in this country.
I think I can tell you exactly what the future holds.
Me of all people. So,
I don't know, bro. Because they're not
living in the real world. They're fantasists.
They make it seem like, "Oh, getting a
relationship's hard, but getting sex is
easy." I think these people on Reddit just lie.
Generally, uh, I think they do. [snorts]
That woman in South America, I'd slap
her up, bro. I'd love to slap her up,
bro. Yeah, I messaged her family and
everything, bro. Little [ __ ]
And this is what I'll be dealing with as
well when I go out and approach women
again. Mind games, [ __ ]
And then the alcohol will hit me the
next day as well. Bad, bad, bad, bad,
bad, bad, bad.
It's depressing, isn't it? Really,
really depressing. It's not normal.
I don't know what you can do to be honest.
What I don't understand is how people can say
that women aren't all the same.
That's what makes me laugh how they can
sit there and say that women aren't all
the same when they are.
Cuz think about it. What's the chances that
[snorts] a lot of these women you've
met, right, Pokémon?
All say the same stuff, all have the
same mannerisms, all act the same, all
use the same excuses, all play mind
games, but they're not all the same. And
the way I see this is that I'm I'm a
person that's unique and no one's the
same as me.
No one's the same as me, you know? So
that's not really the same. They
literally are all the same because why
are they so similar to each other if
they're not all the same?
Obviously they're all the [ __ ] same.
It's obvious. They're NPCs.
I don't know who's telling you they're
not all the same, bro. you know.
So, well, I'll be getting sex when I'm in Thailand.
So, I'll be getting sex when I'm in Thailand, lad. >> [snorts]
>> You know, when I'm in Thailand, I'll be getting sex.
That's for sure.
But these people that say women aren't
all the same, it's hard to believe
because they do a lot of the same stuff
for people that aren't all the same.
That is very, very worrying. pretend
they got boyfriends, use the same
excuses, same mannerisms,
same mind games,
but they're not all the same. But you
never meet men that do any of these things.
So, how can women not be all the same? I
don't understand that logic.
Virgin boy says, "You don't know all
women, but I know more women than he
does." And I've been with more women
than he does. And yeah, they literally
are all the same.
Every single one of them are all the same.
Cuz if they weren't all the same, they
would act like men. They would do
certain things that men do that men
don't do. So there's two genders, and
this stuff only comes from women. So
clearly they are all the same. It's
obvious. No. What the [ __ ]
They watch Tik Tok. They've got Tik Tok
brains. They're all NPCs.
Of course they're all the [ __ ] same.
But you think just because someone's got
different [ __ ] color nails that they're different.
They are definitely all the same. I've
had conversations before
where um I've had literally the same
conversation with different women
where they've done the same thing and
come out with I've got a boyfriend.
What's the chances, bro? People that
aren't all the same act the same way.
It's a bit weird, isn't it?
Cuz you never come across men that do
any of this stuff. Only women. This is
what I mean.
But women aren't all the same. Yeah. Okay.
Do you know what uh do you know what
Oreo man said? Pokemon
Valentine's Day is just a day to poke
fun out of people that ain't wanted by no one.
Let's make fun out of the people that
ain't wanted by no one.
Boy better leave. Boy, better believe
there'll be a lot of love making today.
A lot of love making. [snorts]
But this is just a day to poke fun out
of the people that ain't wanted by no one.
I'd be laughing my ass off, bro. But
it's true, ain't it?
That ain't wanted by no one.
Yeah, it's funny, bro. Yeah, exactly.
And [snorts] they do and they act the
same way as well. Like they'll say, they
are all the same.
Women are definitely definitely
definitely definitely definitely all the same
because if you have a conversation with
one, you'll realize you've had the same
conversation with others before. [snorts]
Yeah, they're definitely definitely all
the same, bro.
Virgin boy doesn't know that cuz he's
still a virgin and he's never dealt with
women. But no, they definitely
definitely are all the same.
Cuz men would be doing the same thing as
them if if it if women weren't all the
same. You see?
So it's not people, it's women. That's
the thing. You see?
They have the same attitude. It's like
what Ant-Man says. He says, "Oh, how
many times have you gone out?" And they
have the same attitude.
The same attitude, the same mannerisms.
Yeah, they are all the same, bro. Of
course, women are all the same.
But people on Reddit say that I'm going
to meet someone Pokémon. They said, "You
don't know what the future holds."
Okay, put it this right. All right. Say
I go out tomorrow.
What's the chances that I'm going to meet someone?
I've not met someone in 5 years. I
haven't been with someone in 5 years.
So, what's the chances that tomorrow
will be the day where all of this
[ __ ] stops? There is no chance. It's
like less than a million to one.
It's like less than Yeah, it's like a le
It's like less than a million to one.
So, I don't fancy them odds, you know?
I really don't fancy them odds, lad.
Cuz it's obviously you're not going to meet someone.
It's so obvious you're not going to meet
someone, you know? So, it's like, why am
I even going to waste my time and
[ __ ] money, bro? [ __ ]
You need to find a really good escort
and stick with her. And yes, it's not
the same, but what are you going to do,
bro? Keep going out dealing with their
[ __ ] Nah, no thanks.
I don't know. I'll probably just chill.
I don't know what I'm doing tomorrow.
I'll probably just chill out.
I'm not dealing with their [ __ ] I like
peace and quiet, bro.
I like peace and quiet to my light in my
Yeah. Well, there is an alternative. I'm
going to Thailand in 3 weeks and I'll
get sex for free. So, that's the
alternative. Escorts and then Thailand. End of [snorts]
What? What do you want me to do, bro? Go
out and spend £200 just to hear I've got
a boyfriend just to get numbers that
waste my time. I'm not doing it. I'm 28,
mate. Not 18. I'm not doing it anymore.
Really ain't doing it. So that's that
what the [ __ ]
else do you want me to [ __ ] do, bro? You know.
No, it's not funny. It's [ __ ] depressing.
It's depressing, lad.
So, I'd rather just get a lust ex I'd
rather just get a lush escort.
There's a few ways there. There's a few
things you can do. You either join the porn industry.
You keep using escorts. Um,
uh, you keep using escorts or you go to Thailand.
There's no other thing you there's
nothing else you can do. Approaching is
not an option anymore.
Yeah, I do remember. And I remember last
I remember last month when I got 10
numbers and I didn't even get a date. I
remember that as well.
Yeah, I remember that. And I won the
money back and I didn't go out again trying since.
Yeah, I also remember that as well.
10 numbers are not even a [ __ ] date.
[ __ ] that, bro. Absolutely [ __ ] that. [snorts] Nah. Yeah.
So that's it.
Sorry [snorts] if it bores you, bro. I
don't go out approaching anymore. Sorry,
man. But that's just the way it is. I
can't go out trying, bro. For my own
sake. I'm sorry. I can't. So yeah,
there there's nothing else
that can do. So yeah.
No, it won't.
It won't. Cuz they're westernized. No,
no, no, no, no. Cuz they're westernized,
bro. It doesn't work. [snorts]
What do you mean I have to spend
approaching? Of course I do. Cuz I'm
going to be drinking
cuz I'm going to be drinking. So yes, I do.
Uh, yes I do. I'm not doing it anymore,
bro. You're not going to convince me to
do it. I'm not trying. [snorts]
I ain't trying for at least 6 months.
I'm going to get a nice escort, bro,
with like big brooms or something and
then just do that for like 6 months.
Come back from Thailand and maybe I'll
consider it again. I I don't know why I
would consider it again though cuz it's
always going to be the same here.
Until you break a cycle, you're [ __ ]
That's the thing. You are [ __ ]
And with this, there is other alternatives.
Nope. You do get it for free in
Thailand, bro. You can go on Tinder. You
can go on Tinder and you can get women on Tinder.
Yeah, you can, bro. Yeah, you can.
No, you can't, bro. There's women on
Tinder that will just come to your house
and [ __ ] you. Yes, there is. Yeah, a lot
of them you pay for, but a lot of them
[ __ ] you for free. And a lot of them want relationships. So,
I would just say use escorts, me, go
Thailand or [ __ ] Yeah. join the porn industry
because you need to break a cycle.
Unless you break a cycle, you're [ __ ]
So that's where we're at.
We used to break the cycle last. So
no, you there is ones you don't pay. So
So there's no there's no way tomorrow is
going to be different.
There's no way tomorrow is going to be different, lad.
So yeah, man. I need to make this
[ __ ] bed and I'm [ __ ] shattered. Nah, bro.
Yes, but you can go on Tinder and get
women. That's what I'm saying. Dating
apps work in Thailand.
That's what I'm saying to you, bro. It
works in Thailand.
Yeah, it works in Thailand.
Tinder, you know, dating apps, they work
in Thailand, bro.
They'll literally come to your house and
[ __ ] you. It works in Thailand. It
doesn't work here.
That's what I'm saying to you. You can
get laid in Thailand, even on Tinder for
women that don't charge you.
No, they don't. No, they don't, bro.
Look it up.
It's mad how he's never coming back
and his friends moved there now as well.
The pretty boy.
His name's Andy the pretty boy. I was
like, "What? He's even going there now
and living there?
What the [ __ ] Madness.
What about the other guys? other guys do it.
That's what I don't understand. The other guys
Yeah. I don't know what she wanted and
then she said she didn't feel the vibe.
Like did she want to [ __ ] or what? I
don't get it. You know,
I don't know, bro. >> [snorts] >> Yeah.
Does she want to [ __ ] or
weird is it?
Pick up culture. They say [snorts]
I'm not so sure. Yeah,
bad. This is it. [snorts]
Show code is attractive in it. Oh, come on.
Why does he say if you don't find her
attractive, you're gay when she's like average?
It's the name, is it?
He didn't want to feel left out. Poor [ __ ]
Yeah. He didn't want to feel left out copycat.
My sister's got a cat, by the way.
Yeah, he's a little copycat.
You can just fire in the air. The little copycat
wants to bloody well fit in. Wants to
bloody well fit in with the crowd.
All he wanted to do was bloody well fit in. Pokemon.
[snorts] All he wanted to do was bloody
well fit in with the crowd.
Some people are like that. Is it?
Yeah, that's definitely copying.
You can read up anywhere online. People
say the same thing to each other.
You little copycat.
What's the plan? I'm going bed.
I'm going to make my bed. I'm going to
bed. It's in the dryer. I'm [ __ ] knackered.
I'll be chilling tomorrow. Actually, I'm
going to see if anything's in the
cinema. I might go cinema.
Wait, what's the day tomorrow? Friday. Or
I'd have to go first thing cuz obvious
obviously I have to switch times I go to
the cinema cuz of um seeing couples and stuff. [snorts]
I have to work my way around times and
stuff to not match it with like when the
couples go to the cinema and stuff. It's
too it's it's really a depressing
country, but I've only got 3 weeks left. So, yeah,
[clears throat] there's no life for any
young person here
being single and sexless.
No life for anyone, mate. I know. [snorts]
He He compares me and the USA is he thing
to him and Britney.
He [snorts] ly he convinces himself that
I'm a virgin like him. It's [ __ ] sad.
He won't be happy until you admit that
you're a virgin like him. He's such an
insecure little virgin with a fragile
ego. [ __ ] sad as [ __ ]
He still [snorts] goes on about that USA
is he by the way. Such a sad sad virgin. Yeah.
Oh, he's triggering again.
I don't live in London myself. Well,
actually, Runford is classed as London. So, yeah.
Ronford [snorts] is not Essex. Rampford is London.
Yeah. No, this is London definitely.
Yeah. Well, actually is actually London,
but uh London, but where you live
definitely isn't London. >> [snorts]
>> Definitely definitely definitely isn't love.
He can't afford a 200 pound pair of
jeans. Can he poke mom? No. I [snorts] so tired. No,
he's going to be 31 in February and he's
still going to be a virgin.
He's still going to be that [ __ ]
virgin from out of London. Oh,
but sorry mate. I put my bed in the dryer.
But when you finally lose it,
I remember when I was I remember when I
lost it when I was [ __ ]
He's going to have a shock of his life
when he finally loses his virginity. But
I did when I was 17 and I lost it. Yeah.
When you finally pop it,
when you finally lose it.
Oh, my nose, man.
>> My nose is [ __ ]
My nose is actually [ __ ]
You reckon he'll lose it? You reckon
he's going to lose his replay before he's 31?
What do you think? You reckon before
he's 31, he's going to finally get? Huh?
Oh, I'm so tired, man. So [ __ ] tired.
this [ __ ] bed.
So we protect
how we protect his [ __ ] virginity. I'm fat.
I'm going to be sleeping cuz I'm fat.
How do you feel about that? Being fat. I'm fat.
Well, there's going to be women for me
because I'm going Thailand.
So, there'll be no women for you, lad.
But there was going to be women for me. Yeah,
it's going to be weird for me cuz I'm
going Thailand in that.
I'll be going Thailand, mate, in three weeks. So,
you'll be by yourself. I'll be getting
all the women pet hot design. So,
because I know I can go on Tindo and get
what I want.
And to be honest with you, there are
some Thai women.
There are there are some Thai women that
are good-looking, bro. Look at that one
from Australia. I liked her. She was Thai.
So, and you can get sex on Tinder as
well. You can actually get women there
and you don't have to pay. So,
Thailand is the only way, lad.
Oh, you can stay here and keep
approaching and becoming depressed,
but it's going to take a toll on your
mental health. So,
I think like
[snorts] it's not an option, is it?
Just you have to go to Thailand. That's
the only way, bro.
Look at Ant-Man. He was scared of
flying. [ __ ] Scared of flying, but he
knew that was the only way out. Yeah.
You like my game, Pokemon? Yeah,
I keep messaging people on Reddit
saying, "I got a bone to pick with you.
Why are you telling people to go out and
approach women when they're not bloody interested?"
I said, "Bloody bloody interested Pokemon.
Not bloody interested. Yeah.
You remember that Italian one that went
on a date with me just to make me feel
bad about myself,
even though she had no intentions of
even dating me, holding my hand and
everything. But then as soon as I went
to kiss her,
it's [ __ ] stuff, is it, lad? [ __ ] sus.
>> [clears throat]
>> [ __ ] suss
just to make me feel bad about myself.
>> Yeah, I had three dates in that month.
You remember the 32y old? She said she
doesn't feel the vibe.
A and she was 32 and she was a four out
of 10 and she thinks she's better than
me. Get [ __ ]
about you're not feeling it. The [ __ ]
bro? You approached me. You wanted to go
out with me and you're claiming that
you're not feeling it, but you passed
yourself by name
and you're [ __ ] average to below
average looking and and that I was like
I couldn't get over it the whole night.
You could ask these black lads I was
with. I was like, "Bro, it's come to the
point now where you got people that are
in their 30s thinking they're better
than you." When I was 27
and my SMV goes higher as I get older,
theirs go lower. You got a [ __ ] 30
odd year old thinking they're better
than your average looking.
So when these people telling you to
lower your standards, that's what they
mean by lowering your standards. But
even if you're lowering these standards,
they think they're [ __ ] better than you.
Madness, bro. [ __ ] madness.
No, she didn't have kids.
I mean, what do you mean you
So, what would have happened if I didn't
tried to kiss the Italian then? Pokémon
who was holding hands and stuff. So,
what happened? What? So, if I didn't try
to kiss her, do you think she would have
met me again or what? [snorts]
How do you know?
How do you know, bro?
How do you know, man?
But I did try to make the move. was
holding hands and then I tried to kiss
her and then she moved away. Come on.
I did try to make the first move, didn't I? [snorts]
I did try and make the first move.
I don't know, bro.
What do you think was the funniest date
I've been on? Pokemon.
What do you think was the funniest one? Huh? Cool. [snorts]
Yeah, I I lost money in it. I ditched
and I had to go back in it. [laughter] 13. Yeah.
And I had to go back in it.
I ditched her.
I can't do that.
No, it's still a bit damp though, is it?
[ __ ] It's still a bit damp.
>> [clears throat]
>> Just make the bed [ __ ] damp in it.
No, you can't do that, bro.
Imagine that. Getting into the bed ducking [laughter]
honking, is it? I'm tired.
Nice. It's damp, mate. Yeah.
[snorts] Yeah. You remember everything, don't you?
Yeah. You remember everything.
I'm just going to have to make it like this, bro.
It's a bit damp, though. Yeah,
let me see how bad it is.
I'm going to have to make it like this, bro.
It should dry by itself. Did I
So, who's my mama?
Oh, come on. [snorts]
Who's my mama?
The [ __ ] bed is [ __ ] down.
That's dumb, lad.
Well, I'm going to end up falling asleep. Yeah.
Is a bit dumb to be fair,
but will end up sleeping without this.
Okay. Is it the end or is it both sides?
It's the end that's a bit damp.
Getting into a bit dump, huh?
Nah, bro. My sleeping p's a bit better now.
Well, ain't that skin virgin beds it mate?
Yeah, it's the end that's damn
but it all dry.
Let me just try and make this better tired Monday. >> [snorts]
>> One second. Let me make this bed.
I'm so tired. >> [laughter] >> ly. Oh, [ __ ] One second.
Yeah, I could use a blow dryer.
I'm so [ __ ] tired, mate. Oh, look.
This is [ __ ]
I don't know what I'm doing. I'm so tired, man.
Can't even make the bed properly.
I can't even make it properly, mate.
So, you sure I would have got friend zone
if I didn't try to kiss the person then?
I hope that's not back to front.
It might be, bro.
I don't give a [ __ ]
Back to it.
I don't give a [ __ ] I'm just going to
get in it anyways. I'm [ __ ] tired, bro.
It's lumpy as [ __ ]
The bed's lumpy, mate.
I think I can be on
to stop the lumps, lad. I'm [ __ ] tired.
It is back to front. Yeah.
I'll have to modify it tomorrow, mate.
I'm too tired.
I don't understand how it's [ __ ] I just
I'm so tired, man.
Yeah, but when I tried to make the first
move, she didn't want to kiss though. Pokémon,
she didn't want to kiss.
So, well, you look normal
and your approaches are normal. Maybe
too many stuck up [ __ ] in whatever
weird country you live in.
That's what they said to me on the Reddit. Oh, mate.
I'm so tired.
So [ __ ] tired I am, mate.
Just want to get I just want to get some.
Yeah, that Italian one was a [ __ ] I
should have clocked home and she said it
wasn't necessary to buy her a drink. Why
even go out with somebody if you're not
going to be serious about trying to date them?
What do you think the problem is, Dad? One sec.
What do you think the problem is? Huh?
What? What do you think the problem is?
Do you think it's the way that I look? I
think I look normal, though.
I've done this [ __ ] bed.
It's a bit lumpy at the end, but I [ __ ]
It's going to have to do.
What do you think the problem is?
You think it's the way that I look, Pokemon?
I think I look normal, but it's just weird now.
People lie to me and stuff, so I'll
never know the truth.
Oh, I'm in bed now.
What? What is it?
Yeah, it would have been way too easy.
What do you think, Pokemon? Is Is it the
way I look or what? I mean, I think I
look pretty normal. No,
normal. Nice clothes.
But I hear all of these excuses. I can't
get with you cuz you're too old for me.
Then I find out they've been with a 28-year-old before.
They use all the excuses under the sun.
But then when you pretend to be a white
guy with blue eyes, you hear none of these excuses.
So maybe it's my race.
Maybe it's like cuz I don't look fully white.
I think it's cuz I don't look fully white.
I don't know.
I don't know what the problem is.
It's weird, isn't it? Yeah.
So what? You don't think it's the way
that I look?
So what? Do they hate nonslegs as well?
They hate nonslegs and Ricky Millington, don't they?
Ricky Millington says, "I get women,
mate." I said, "No, you bloody don't.
Wasn't you saying [ __ ] last year that
I'm good-looking and women are too
picky? Make up your mind, mate.
No, you bloody don't get women. Just
like the virgin, he doesn't get women
either. No, you bloody don't.
I told you bloody is my favorite [ __ ]
word now, lad.
You don't get women, mate. If you got
women, you wouldn't be saying that
they're too picky,
which is what you said about a year and
a half ago. So, what suddenly changed in two years?
and um and uh Wiki Bington. >> No, >> nonslegs.
Yeah, nonslegs. They hate um
they hate Ricky Millington. Yeah,
there's this guy here on Reddit and he's
a 27y old virgin and he says he doesn't
have the desire to try anymore.
Well, that's like me, but obviously I'm
not a virgin. Yeah,
he called ugly 1998.
Yeah, I'll read you some of the things
that he's wrote. That's his username. Ugly98.
I'm 27 next month. I've never dated,
kissed, and I'm virgin from the UK.
Appearance is definitely the reason I'm
still a virgin. I'm tall. I just don't
have a single good feature on my face.
Does anyone present their genetics?
Same. It's why I just don't have the
energy to try anymore. I would always be
alone and nothing can change it.
[snorts] I haven't tried in a few years.
I doubt I would ever try again. So,
these people have tried nowhere near as
much as me and they've already gave up.
They gave up years ago.
When I turned 24, 25, which is the age
where it's pretty abnormal to be a
virgin. I just took that as a sign that
nothing will change and I should just
give up and accept it. Yeah.
Obviously mine was when I got 10 numbers
and I didn't even get a date.
So we're all different in it.
So they gave up before me.
A mixture of being too ugly today and
not having enough energy to try anymore.
To be honest, I think I'm just not I
think I'm just built to be alone. Yeah,
that's what he said.
Well, Thailand's the way in it. You know,
go to bars, they say on Reddit.
On Reddit they say go to bars. Pokemon
talk to women in bars.
What do you think of that? Speak to
women in pubs.
[ __ ] idiots, aren't they?
He says it's the heman says, "Stop
sending me the same videos.
It's the same thing, just different
characters." He said it's like watching
Jaw but watching different people be
ate. It's the same film just different
people being eaten. You know,
it's just it's just different people
being ate. That's what he said. He said
it's the same
thing, just different characters.
It's like Jaw. It's like Jaw. It's like watching Jaw,
but the people the people being eaten
are different people. It's still the same Jaw.
I was dead when he said that.
Just different characters. Mad.
You can see the Westinity in their eyes.
[snorts] That that nasty. Yeah.
Maybe I'll go Manchester tomorrow. No,
no one's bloody interested. Yep. It's depressing.
Why do these people call me Skint Monty?
Because their skin is that
Why does Bomb call me ugly? Because
Bomb's ugly. It's just like reverse,
isn't it? Yeah. Yeah,
you calling me evil. I remember when I
said before on Reddit, women are evil.
And this woman said, "What? You calling me evil?"
exclamation mark. I said, "Yeah,
I've got to go out tomorrow, don't I,
Pokémon? I can't let these [ __ ] women win.
I can't let these [ __ ] women win. E,
do you remember? Don't let these [ __ ] women win.
Yeah, we need to try and meet one and
get one pregnant and leave them.
We need to [ __ ] up one of their lives.
Bit like what they've done to us over
the [ __ ] years, you know? Give them a
bit back of what they've gave me over the years. Yeah.
No, they're laughing at us
when they're out like when we stay in
and we don't try. They're sat there
drinking, laughing at us, aren't they?
They're sat there drinking, laughing at us. Yeah.
When you were traveling the country,
they were laughing at you, mocking you.
Women don't even need to leave the house
to get sex. Mad. madness.
Remember the [ __ ] in the alleyway, Pokemon,
I really want you, but I don't think you want me.
I do. I do. [snorts]
But I don't think you want me. I do.
They were mocking you, laughing at you.
I think that Ant-Man's a troll, you know, bro.
But when I send them Peter the
Strawberry, they go on a message
straight away. When I send Peter the Strawberry, Yep. Pretty much.
It's mad that there's actually people
out there that's worse than me.
It's actually mad that there are
actually people out there that's worse
than me. If I was still a virgin at this
age, bro, I'd go on a killing spree.
I'd actually go on a killing spree if I
was a virgin at this age. But it doesn't
make it any better anyways, bro. Cuz I tried non-stop.
So, it doesn't make it better really.
Being a virgin, not being a virgin,
I had to put horrendous amounts of
efforts in to even get anything. It's disgusting.
If I had one wish in this world, I'd ban social media
and make society normal again. [ __ ] the
million pounds, millions of pounds. I
wouldn't want it.
I wouldn't want it.
Or I could be a billionaire and then
just buy buy Facebook. I mean, buy
dating apps and then just [ __ ] them off.
I I'd buy them over.
There'd be no white knights, no simps.
There'd be no [ __ ] women. That's if I
had one wish, that's what my wish would
be in life.
That's what my wish would be. Yeah. So Yeah,
I'm watching that Kings. Do you know
Kings Cleans Pokemon? He's all over
Instagram. Kings Cleans.
Yeah, he has some good videos, man.
He's a He's a weird looking fellow, ain't he?
He's a weird looking fellow. Him. Kings cleans.
Yeah, he's a weird looking fella, lad.
Oh, look at Selena Gomez. She's on Instagram.
Have you seen Selena Gomez Pokemon?