Yo yo yo. Sorry I had to make money
lads, but I'm back. I am back.
These weasels really need to stop
talking about themselves in this
community, mate. They need to stop self
projecting, calling themselves skin. I
didn't have to buy them traders, but I
did to prove a [ __ ] point, lad. To
prove a [ __ ] point. People
have you don't love or people don't
love. Little self projectors.
You little self- projecting [ __ ] Yeah,
that's what I mean with these little
weasels on this community. They start
[ __ ] and can't finish it. Just like that
Ricky Millington. They're all weasels.
That That's how you describe these kind
of people here. Weasels. Nothing else.
Nothing else. Weasels. That's what they are. Weasels.
Why wouldn't I be able to buy a new pair
of trainers? What is everyone's skin
like you? Is everyone's skin like you
people that self project? I'm talking
about the self projectors here. They're
not like the other people that don't do
this. I'm talking about the ones that do
self project. So what is everyone Is
everyone skint like you people?
Is that what it is? Is everyone skint
like you people? That's what you really think?
Is that what you really really think? E
mad. [ __ ] mad. They seem to think
everyone lives the same life as them.
It's a maza. Yeah,
>> they think everyone's got the same life as them.
Yeah, I bought myself some nice Air
Maxes. Be coming tomorrow. I'll be doing
a video like the jeans.
There we go. That's that.
Can't go out today even if I wanted to.
It's damp and I'm waiting for the new
trainers. So when the new trainers arrive.
Oh, do you want the link? Monty,
I need to talk to you, Monty. Seriously,
I've had to spend over £500 over the
past couple of days, mate. Because of these people
of these [ __ ] little self-reflectors on here. Oh man. Yeah, man.
Don't do Don't deliver food. You don't
know how I get money, mate. And it's
none of your business. Just know that
you need to stop talking about people
that you don't know. This is a learn.
This is a This is a life lesson. I
didn't buy the trades yesterday because
Greavvesy told me that I couldn't and I
respect Grievy. So, I thought, "Fuck it.
I'll order them to [ __ ] piss this
[ __ ] off, you know, and I'll need them
at some point anyways, mate." And I'll
be going on the piss tomorrow as well. So
yeah, I don't I don't deliver food.
Nope. None of your business. Peter
Belly's got money. Peter Belly's got
plenty of money, mate. Don't you worry
about that. Again, do not talk about
people that you don't know. That's a
life lesson. Why would I be able to
afford a pair of trainers? What are
they? 150 2000?
How much a day, lads? How How could I
How could I be delivering food when I'm
on YouTube all the time? When I'm out
all the time? Really, bro? Do you know
how many hours that you need to put in?
No, I just have money, mate. How can I
deliver food when I'm on YouTube all the
[ __ ] time? It doesn't make that much,
mate. It doesn't make that much. It's
not as easy as that. And I know cuz I've
done the job.
Yeah. No, I've not bend it at all. It's
just I'm just using that as a [ __ ]
You know what I mean?
£200 on trainer, £210 on trainers, £200
on jeans. Stop talking about people you
don't know. And we'll probably be
spending £300 over the weekend. Simple.
Stop talking about people that you don't
know. Simple. It'll get you far in life.
But if it's raining tomorrow, I won't
wear the trainers. I'll just wear
something else. But definitely go out
tomorrow a million%. Yeah.
Got a nice T-bone steak today as well. Yeah.
Nice T-bone steak. [ __ ] hell.
Well, why you asking then if you don't
give a [ __ ]
I've just saved money, bro. That's all.
I've just saved money. That's all I've
done. I don't have a job. Yeah,
I just have enough to do what I want to
do. I don't have a job. How the [ __ ] can
I have a job when I'm sat on YouTube
most of the time or [ __ ] going out
doing [ __ ] How the [ __ ] could I have a
job, bro? Use your use use common sense, you know?
So, no, I don't have a job. I don't need a job,
you know. So, yeah.
One money, save money, put money away, done.
Oh, no. Well, I'm on here a lot, bro,
cuz I haven't been going out approaching
women and stuff, but we'll be going out
tomorrow. Whether it's raining or not,
I'm going out tomorrow. Nope.
Don't do that. I used to do that. And
it's not good money, mate. It's not good
you know? You can't really make a You
can make The only the only thing you can
do with food delivery is [ __ ]
work and then live off what you earn on
that. You're not going to be minted from
[ __ ] delivering food, bro. Okay. How
do I say it? It's like if you was to go
out on the weekend, it will pay for you
going out on the weekend.
That's it. You're not going to suddenly
start getting loads and loads of money
from it. It's [ __ ] hard as [ __ ]
But it is good. Like say you bought a
phone that was £400. You could earn
£400, you know? Like it's that it's that
it's not quick, easy, good money, bro.
What you figured though? I know. I've
done it, mate. So,
and you can't do it fulltime either cuz
it's depressing. So, you'd have to do it
like 6 hours a day every other day or some [ __ ]
Yeah. I don't even have a food account.
I don't have a delivery account. How can
I deliver food? I don't have a delivery
account. My delivery account got banned. Yeah.
But yeah, the moral of the story is,
bro, you don't know how much people
have, how much people don't have.
That's the moral of the story to that guy. Nope.
Nah, bro. Long story.
Yep. No, nothing to do with them. Just
like the sub sublet was nothing to do with them.
Well, it's just a lesson anyways for me
to you. Your trainers are coming
tomorrow, so I'll do a video.
Nice pair of jeans. Nice pair of
trainers. It'd be rude not to go out and approach.
I bought these trainers flat Eric.
Yeah. £210 it cost me.
I thought, "Fuck this, mate. This cunt's
getting on my [ __ ] nerves now. I'm
just going to buy these trainers."
It wasn't about the buddy. I don't know
why I didn't buy them yesterday. I think
it's more of like I don't know why, but
yeah. Anyways, I bought them. So,
I'll be going to the pub tomorrow.
Vapor Maxes. They're the only ones I
like. Vapor Maxes.
So, I'll be going pub tomorrow. Yep.
Yeah, I'll be going to the pub.
Definitely going to the pub tomorrow.
100%. Bro, I don't need my haircut. I
got my haircut last week.
Yeah, last week. So, still looks good.
Anyways, I got the fresh gums, so
whatever. Anyways, Greavvesy, sorry,
man. I know. Please forgive me. I know.
I know. I couldn't help myself. I wanted
to prove this [ __ ] wrong, you know. Not
that I needed to, but I thought, you
know what? I'll just buy the trainers.
Grievy. Sorry. Sorry, mate.
I know. I know. I know. But this [ __ ]
was pissing me off, Grezy. And I wanted
to show him who's boss,
you know. And it'd be very very rude to
go out approaching women with a nice new
pair of jeans but not a nice new pair of
trainers. You know, I've took it a step
further than L J. Now I've got the jeans
and the trainers. He's never done that,
has he? No. [gasps]
It'd be very, very rude and
disrespectful to approach a woman with a
new pair of jeans, but not a new pair of trainers.
No, I can't go out today, bro. I'm going
to my sisters
and it's damp outside. So yeah, I'll go out tomorrow.
It doesn't really matter whether it's
Halloween or not. Really, bro? Does it?
I'm going out tomorrow. So,
no man, I ain't going out today. It's
damp outside as well.
The weather is [ __ ] So, tomorrow
definitely 100% I'm going out tomorrow.
You got my word on that one, bro.
I spent a lot of money on these garbids.
So, the weather's [ __ ] bro. If the
weather was a bit better, then I'd be
tempted. I'm not going to lie. But yeah,
tomorrow, Saturday. It's Saturday.
Tomorrow, so we'll do tomorrow.
It is damp outside, so [ __ ] it. Tomorrow
for sure. And if it's damp tomorrow,
then I'll just wear shoes. I'm going out
tomorrow regardless. We could be pissing
down tomorrow. I'm still going out. So,
I got this football bat as well. Oh,
what did you do with my football bat?
Oh, it's here.
Yeah, I got a football bet as well. So,
yeah. So, stop calling people skint when
you don't know how much money people
have. That's the moral of the [ __ ] story, mate. Yeah.
But I will get rejected to my flat. I
was in Liverpool Street yesterday with
my mom and it seeing all of these women
was depressing me, bro.
Very, very depressing.
It is depressing, is it?
Oh, [ __ ] sake.
And I was talking to some person on
Reddit earlier and again, they're just
dismissing my struggles. I feel like
everyone just dismisses my struggles
flat. That's why I don't bother with it anymore, lad.
No, I don't think they met.
Everyone just dismisses my [ __ ] struggles. son. Yeah.
Like they uh
like I'm showing you women leading me on
and then they're not thrown back by it.
Like I've said, oh, I'm not I'm not
asking for pity or anything, you know. I
just want you to say something,
you know, and they don't they don't they
seem to dismiss it. They're saying that,
oh, you're coming on too desperate. But
as I've shown them where women have led me on.
Do you get what I mean, bro? Like
I've actually shown them where they've
actually [ __ ] me over and they don't
address it. They don't care. I don't
want pity. I want you to say, "Well,
what the [ __ ] That's what I want." But
they don't. They don't seem bothered by it.
And Joseph Farrar said, "Oh, it's not
it's to do with the situation. It's not
black and white. Yes, we know that. I've
admitted that. If you meet some, if
you're speaking to a woman on a dating
app, then yes, ask her to meet after 3
weeks, after a month. Yes. But when
you've met a woman in person, a week is
enough. You don't need to be speaking to
people for months to meet them again.
Why would you?
That doesn't make any sense. It's like
this American from uh I think it was
this year on a Thursday went out. We was
together for like an hour. we were
supposed to meet again and then she used
her ex as an excuse. What? Why would I
be spending over a month before meeting someone?
So, they just they just contradict themselves anyways.
But I don't really care. It's just
[ __ ] up, bro, that they just dismiss
your struggles. They don't seem to they
just say, "Oh,
oh, you're approaching. You might come
across as desperate." Completely
ignoring the fact that these women have
agreed to meet me. It's
It's weird. They do dismiss your struggles definitely
because they said they should be like,
"Oh, well, hold on a minute. They've
agreed to meet you." And then they haven't.
So, but yeah, like I said, they don't
seem bothered by it at all.
Not in the slightest.
Madness, bro. Madness.
But it's all right anyways, man. My
sleeping pattern is a bit better now
anyway, so I'm all good, lad.
You know, you get really depressed when
your sleeping pattern's [ __ ] up. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, you do, bro. It's [ __ ]
Got my nice jeans coming, my nice trainers coming.
My jeans are already here.
coming. My train is coming.
My mom's trainers cost £37. Mine's over £200. Madness.
Absolute madness, bro.
It's worth the money though, eh?
And now you can just buy like cheap
jumpers, cheap cheap t-shirts.
You can buy just cheap stuff now.
Long as your lower lower waist is is is
is good, then you're done, right? It
look at my Stone Island jumpers. I'm
never buying a Stone Island jumper ever again.
They're [ __ ] uh good enough, eh?
I don't know which one to wear tomorrow.
I might wear the light blue one or the
lei blue one.
I might wear the I might I might wear
the light blue one. Oh, I'm going to be
looking the bollocks tomorrow, bro.
The absolute bollocks.
Yo, [ __ ] hell. Yeah, dude.
No, no, no, no, no.
odds on this football bet winning tomorrow.
Odds on odds on this [ __ ] football bet winning.
It [ __ ] better win, mate. Yeah.
Yeah. We trash, lad.
Whatever is trash. I got my sisters
today as well, so
um I can't uh
go out anyways.
Yeah, I saw it. Uh, Joe,
I've done a bad thing. I bought myself a
210 pair of trainers, Joe.
I went again what I went against what
Greavesy said, but I done it to prove a
point, you know, cuz that guy was like,
"Oh, you said you would was going to buy
trainers and that I don't have the
money, but I do I don't have the money
in your skin." Are you sure about that?
because the trainers are coming tomorrow
which is which is going to be another
video. I'm going to do a video on these
trainers tomorrow mate because you said
I can't afford the trainers so I bought
the trainers and I'm going on a piss
tomorrow as well. Joseph Ferrar.
Yeah, I'm going to be uh I'm going to go
on a piss tomorrow.
Yep. You betcha, Joe. You betcha, Joseph.
That's just the norm. Well, it was
actually 205 pound, but had to pay for
the delivery as well.
Yeah. So, I'll be having over 400 pound
below the waist.
I'll be doing some approaches tomorrow
because Joe, I can't I can't go out
approaching women with a nice new pair
of jeans, but not a nice new pair of
trainers, can I? That's almost criminal,
Joseph Ferrar. That's that's that's
almost [ __ ] criminal. That's very disrespectful,
you know, to even go out with a new pair
of jeans but not a new pair of trainers.
Do you not think that's very disrespectful?
Very, very, very, very disrespectful.
Joseph Ferrar, you know,
obviously the Stone Islands, they've
been dry cleananed, so they look as good
as new, but that's all right. That's
okay, you know.
Yeah. Lovely. Uh lovely pair of
trainers. Virgin boy was getting jealous
of the jeans. Did you see his comment?
Someone was like, "Oh yeah, they're nice
jeans." He was like, "They're absolutely not."
And someone said, "Yeah, they are."
And uh he was like um
he's like, "They're not." I was like,
"They [ __ ] are, mate. They're better
than your charity shop. Shitty clothes."
No, bro. They're not to get responses from women.
I can't wear cheap trainers. is I can't
wear cheap jeans. We're all made
different, lad. It's not to do with
women. If it was to do with women, bro,
I'd be going out right now and buying
another Stone Island jumper or [ __ ]
or a new top
or something like that, you know? It's
it's it's not about women, bro. I I
would I always like them jeans. I've
been wearing them since even in the
skint days. Even before I was
approaching, I used to wear Ammani jeans.
Before I'd even approach. Um,
so Joe, um, yeah, I don't understand
your whole uh your comment on that
video, by the way.
I don't understand your your your
comment on that video.
I mean they say that you should be
speaking to women weeks
and months and then they say that you
should try and meet the woman as soon as
possible. So which one is it? Make up
your mind. See all of their advice contradicts itself.
That's why you can't take advice from
people on the internet. You know
they they their advice contradicts
itself on dating apps. Yeah. you need to
speak to someone for like a month
because you've never met them before.
But when you approach someone, a week is fine.
Yes. Yes, it does depend on the
situation. So, in my situation,
considering I only meet women in person,
a week is fine.
Yes. But my situation is meeting them in person.
So, you should be meeting them as soon
as you can cuz you've already met them
in person. You don't need to speak to
them for a month.
That's what I'm saying. On a dating app,
it's different. Yeah. Three weeks, a
month maybe. But if you've already met someone, then
it's a bit different. That's what I'm
trying to say.
It depends on how you've met the person,
how long you've met them for, where
you've met them, you know? So,
obviously, if it's a dating app, Yeah.
you you'd have to speak to them for a
little while. Yeah. But not in real
life. if you approach them though. What the [ __ ] So,
but yeah. Anyways, they dismissed my
struggles. Anyway, Joe, I don't know why
they dis I don't know why they um
dismissed my struggles. I'd love to know.
I don't know why they [ __ ]
I don't know why they [ __ ] dismissed my struggles.
But I've been wearing that [ __ ] before I
used to approach Joe.
Before I used to approach
really, even when I was scared to
approach, I used to wear them jeans.
Yeah, but what I'm saying, Joe, is that
you're dismissing my struggles again
because these women have agreed to meet.
So why have they agreed to meet? So
you're always going to dismiss people's
struggles. There's no point in getting
into this. It's the same thing on
Reddit. They will dismiss what you are
showing them. They don't seem thrown
back by it at all. And then you're
saying to me, "Oh, what do you expect
them to say?" "Uh, acknowledge how
[ __ ] up it is." And say, "Oh, well, I
don't understand why they're leading you
on." No, no, no, no, no. That's [ __ ]
up. I want you to acknowledge how [ __ ]
up it is. I don't want sympathy, but
they don't. it doesn't seem to bother
them, which is strange because I've
shown what they've done, but you know,
I've shown what these women have done
and they don't seem like thrown back by
it at all. It's strange.
They completely ignore the fact that
several of these women have led you on
and agreed to meet you. So
yeah, it is weird, isn't it? There's a
lot of women out yesterday in Liverpool
Street, Joe, when I was with Laney.
This is why I don't go out far anymore.
Yeah, this is why I don't go out far anymore. You know,
because of uh
seeing women and stuff and you want to
approach and no,
it's not about giving me sympathy. I
don't want sympathy. I want them to
acknowledge how [ __ ] up it is.
You know, why are they not talking about
the fact that these women have led you on?
But I've had someone before say to me,
"Well, I don't know what your problem
is. Uh you look normal and you approach
normal. Maybe there's too many stuck up
[ __ ] in your country, which I think
is right. And they're not giving me sympathy either.
I mean, that is pretty [ __ ] spot on
to be honest. I think that is one of the
main that is one of the main problems.
That's not giving me sympathy by saying that.
There's a difference between saying it
how it is and giving someone sympathy. I
don't think you you you know the two, you know. >> [snorts]
>> So that's not giving me sympathy. They
don't seem to be bothered by what
they're doing. They just seem to they
they they go back onto you. So that's
the whole point of they are dismissing
your struggles. Do you not understand?
Dismissing your struggles.
Like it it they're dismissing it. Do you not understand?
I don't think you seem to understand
what I'm saying, lad.
No, I don't. Uh, you haven't watched my
videos. Uh, if you watch one of my
videos that I've put up, uh, you will
see that I've used a pickup line that
was recommended to me. Again, this is
what I'm saying. You dismiss people's struggles.
This is this is my whole point of what I'm saying.
You're saying about how Okay. Okay. I'll
give you an example, Joe. Yeah. This guy
was saying about how you're coming
across as desperate by approaching women
on the street, right? That's what he's
saying. But he's completely ignored all
of the women that have agreed to meet me
and then ghosted.
So it's they're two different things. So
he dismisses it and then they dismiss
your struggles and then just talk about
something completely different like
you've not showed them a load of [ __ ]
[ __ ] That's what I'm saying.
Why can't they
acknowledge it and not give you sympathy?
So them acknowledging it is them pitying
you. No, it isn't. It's them being real.
It's them being It's them being [ __ ] real, lad.
It's like this guy right here. Another
one that dismisses my struggles. You
always use the same nice. Hi, it was
lovely to meet you today.
What else are you? Oh, you mean by text.
What else are you supposed to say? So,
it's like, so anyways, Joe, why do you
dismiss people's struggles anyways?
You agree with what exactly?
What do you agree with?
Right. What? Okay. But again, wait.
Okay. Firstly, what do you agree with?
And also, you're also dismissing my
struggles again, which I'll explain
after you answer this. Right.
No. What do you mean about the two
different things? Okay. You're saying I
need to I need to concentrate on why
women give you the number but not follow
through. Now if you read them conversations,
you would have seen them women have
agreed to meet me. No.
So if I'm doing okay, this goes back to
dismissing struggles again. Because if
you're doing and saying anything wrong,
these women have agreed to meet you. No,
a lot of these women have agreed to meet
you on the messages. No, and then when
it comes to the day, they back out.
So it it doesn't make sense. You can't
keep using excuses. You can only use
excuses when they haven't replied back.
This is goes back to dismissing
struggles again. If some if you get
someone's number and they don't reply
back, that opens that opens doors to why
you know what happened and why they did
not want to. You tell me. You [ __ ]
tell me why not. They've agreed to meet
and then all of a sudden they backed out
because they're time wasting because
they're leading you on. The only thing
could be is that they're leading you on.
See, when somebody does not reply to the
first message, it opens a million
reasons for different excuses. But when
they reply back and they've agreed to
meet you, they are 100% in the wrong.
They are leading you on. There's no
doubt about it. There's black and white
evidence. I don't understand how you can
you can argue with it. They lead people
on for their own entertainment.
It's [ __ ] obvious. And the ones that don't reply,
um, you know, they just they don't
reply. There's What can you say?
Whatever. But the ones
listen. Okay, let me Okay, the last one, right?
Okay, let me get one up here. This is
the last one I went out.
Yeah, exactly. Tiger and Tiger, thanks
for thanks for commenting on my message
by the on my video. By the way, this guy
has been on here for years. Yeah, he
doesn't like me. I don't like him. This
is someone from years ago. Yeah, this
guy right here has been on it years back
when I was 22. And this is an unbiased
guy. Yeah, this guy is not a yes man.
And he even knows it's [ __ ] He even
knows it's [ __ ] Look. Okay,
anyways, back to this. I'll give you
I'll give you uh you know if they if
they Okay, listen. Right. Okay. The the
most recent one.
Hi. Sorry we've been tied up with Uni.
Let me know next time you're around the
area. I'm going to come back on Saturday
at 7:00 p.m. Let's meet then. She was
like, "Oh, all right. Should be okay.
We'll confirm though. Where would you
like to meet on Saturday?" Told her
where we I wanted to meet. Messaged her
again. messaged her on the day. Hey,
sorry. I've been sick the past few days.
Need a rain check on tomorrow, which we
scheduled it 2 days before, which a few
days would have been 3 days. So, I mean,
it's clear they're leading you on. I
don't know what more evidence you you
need to be shown, lad.
I really don't know.
I mean, I mean, that's one example, but Okay.
But she wasn't sick because we planned
it two days ago, not a few days ago.
Okay. But she wasn't sick. And when I
tried to arrange it again, I never heard
back from her. Okay. So, it wasn't confirmed.
And she said that she's been sick for
the past few days. Yet, we planned it 2
days ago and a few days is 3 days. Okay.
So, then we've tried to rearrange it.
So, then we've rearranged it.
and then they didn't reply.
So, you're constantly making excuses for
them. Like, this is what I'm talking
about when you when you uh dismiss struggles.
And that's only one as well. And and
what about the Finland one?
The one that said she was going to meet
me. Then, when I said, "Okay, I might
come to Finland. It was going to cost
like £500 or whatever." She didn't
reply. What about that one? She said,
"Oh, I've met someone who I like, but
all of a sudden, I mean, it's obvious to
normal people that it's bullshit." But
you just like it's Yeah, like I said,
you just make excuses. You just make
excuses for them, bro. I mean, what can
I say, you know?
And now, what about the American one
then? Okay. Okay. What about the
American one then?
Okay. What? Okay. What about the
American one then? Okay. What about that
American one that agreed to meet me and
then two hours before we were supposed
to meet Oh, I'm going to try with my ex.
What? What about that one?
Yes, I know that. But that's my Oh my
god. I'm I'm What I'm trying to say is
that they lead people on. Yes, she
pretended to be sick. Yes, that's what
we're the point I'm trying to get at is
that they are leading people on. It's an
example. We were using this as an
example cuz it was the last one. Yes,
we've moved on, but they lead people on.
That's the point I'm trying to make. So yeah,
and of course she pretended to be sick.
No [ __ ] Sherlock. Jesus Christ. No
[ __ ] Sherlock. Of course she pretended
to be sick.
Oh my god. I mean,
why do you seem to think Can I ask you
this question? Because I'm sure men do
this as well. I'm sure they do it. Why
do you not think women can lead people on?
Like, why do you think they don't do
this stuff? It's It's ridiculous. I'm
sure men do it as well. No.
Yeah. And but that's what I'm trying to
say. Stop dismissing people's struggles.
Exactly. They're full of [ __ ] And you
need to know that and stop making
excuses for them. I'm not concentrating
on them. I'm explaining to you how
they're full of [ __ ] and how they lead
people on. I don't give a [ __ ] about it,
bro. I'm going out tomorrow and I'm
going on a drink,
you know. No, it's not after
consideration. They're leading you on on
purpose. Stop making excuses for them.
That's what I'm saying.
Stop making excuses.
That's the whole point of it. There's no
excuse. They're leading you on and
they're doing it on purpose. End of
[ __ ] There there's nothing else to it.
That's an example.
Jesus [ __ ] Christ.
I mean, Tiger Tiger can smell the
[ __ ] [ __ ] a mile off. And this
guy don't even like me.
Well, their intentions are pretty pretty clear.
I mean, people don't just change their
mind like that. Anyways, we're not
talking about this, bro, because you're
just going to keep dismissing my
struggles and you're going to think that
women do nothing wrong.
No, people don't just change their mind
like that. Stop making excuses.
Stop making excuses. People don't just
change their mind like that unless
they've met someone. People don't just
change their mind like that. That's not
an excuse. Because how many different
women have led you on and done the same
thing? So what? They just suddenly
changed their mind before meeting
someone. Bro, they're full of [ __ ] I
know you don't like to [ __ ] um I know
you don't like to um I have never done
that in my life. I have never ever said
to a woman, "Oh, let's meet up and then
change my mind." Never in a [ __ ]
million years have I ever done that. So,
you'll finish it. You are literally full
of BS, you know.
Okay. So, there's no getting through to
you, bro. I'm finished. I'm not doing
this no more. Like, you can be shown
black and white evidence and you'll
still deny it. I think we're done here
now, bro. We're going round and round
and round in circles. No matter what
you're told, no matter what you're
shown, all you're doing is defending
women. And I'm not interested in it,
bro. I just gave you a prime example. A
prime example. And you're still
nodding your head. I'm not trying to
convince you, bro. Think what you want.
I know what I want. I I know what I
know. There's no getting through to you
people. There's literally no getting
through to you. So, there's no point,
bro. You do you, I do me. I think that's
that's the best, you know. I think
that's the best. Agree to disagree cuz,
you know, you you you're never going to
be shown different. So, it's it's
there's no point, lad.
There's literally no point. If you think
that they don't lead people on or
whatever, good on you, bro. That's on
you in it, you know.
It's fine, bro. Whatever.
Yeah. Yeah, man. Okay.
Yeah. Okay, bro.
Whatever you say. Yeah.
Yeah. Whatever you say, Dad.
Yeah. Whatever. Whatever you say.
Yep. Whatever you say, bro. Whatever you
say. Yeah. Women are perfect. Women
don't lead people on. Yep. Yep. Okay. Whatever.
Yep. Whatever you say, bro. You're
right. And I'm wrong. I'm a 28-year-old
that's never been with a woman. Never
spoke to a woman. I don't know anything.
You're right. Damn. I was wrong all along. Damn.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Whatever.
I mean, I had a woman
message me randomly about a month ago,
started [ __ ] started [ __ ] with me and
I met her. I met her in the Euros.
Wasn't really I can actually show you.
Well, there's no point showing you
anything, is there? Because you're just
going to deny it. Anyways, there was
this woman that I met in the Euros. Uh,
do you remember when the Euros was going
on uh that last summer with and and I
went to the Weather Spoons pub and I
invited her to Nando and she never
replied back, never argued with her,
bro. She messaged me out the blue trying
to [ __ ] with me randomly with some guy.
Yeah, she did. Yeah. Out of the blue.
She wasn't blocked. I didn't block her,
bro. She randomly messaged me starting
to [ __ ] with me
and I don't even know why. There was
some guy sending me pictures of himself.
So what does that mean, bro? Randomly
out of the blue and I'm thinking, "What
the [ __ ] I ain't heard from this person
in a year. I never argue with them. They
just didn't reply to my message. I
didn't message them again." [ __ ]
starts messaging me trying to [ __ ] with
me and put me in a bad mood. So, I'm
going to put that comment right here.
Why would she waste her own time just to
hurt or annoy you? That made me think of
that. I don't know why that randomly
popped up and that was a random person
who I had a 5minute conversation with
you know it's they messaged me randomly
[ __ ] with me bro. Yes they did. Yes
the [ __ ] they did. It was some ginger
woman from Hartford here. Yep. Yeah.
Okay. I'm done with this anyways. I'm
not having this conversation.
Um, you're clearly a white knight and
I'm not here to convince you. Yeah,
whatever, bro. Waste of my time. Like I
said, these people can be shown a woman
murdering a baby and they'd be like,
"Nah, the baby deserved it." There's no
getting through to these people. Waste
of my time. Complete waste of my time.
They can never be shown different. These
people, not even told different. though.
Strange. It is strange. It is strange.
Very, very strange.
They seem to think women can do no
wrong. It's mad. It is. It is mad. But
there's no there's no getting through to these people.
I think I've still Do I still have the messages?
Oh, no. Oh, I do still have the messages.
Yeah. Yeah. I'll show you the message.
Okay. Yeah. So, this woman randomly
messaged me showing a picture of a guy,
the one that I met on the Euros.
Never argued with this person. They just
didn't reply. So, I figured, okay, they
didn't reply. A year later, they've
messaged me sending a picture of a guy.
I put question mark question mark
question mark. They put bang question
mark. I told them to grow up. They're
like, "Fairs. I'll message random women
instead. I said, "Why are you messaging
me after all this time? Do you remember
me?" They're like, "Nah, but you're
messaging me. Let me know if you fancy a
bump." And I'm thinking, "What the
fuck?" Then there's like, "Oh, I miss
you, cutie." So, they were [ __ ] with
me and trolling me for no reason. Now,
let me put this comment back up again.
Why would she waste her time just to
hurt or annoy you? Makes no sense. Uh,
I'm just looking at this when you've
said that, by the way. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. This was randomly out the blue.
That was randomly out the blue. Yeah.
Nope. It was some woman that I met in
the Weather Spoons pub. Yeah.
Yeah, there's a woman I met in the
Weather Spoons pub. Yeah, lad.
So why why wouldn't a woman do do
anything to waste and you know why why
would a woman do that?
I've never known somebody to agree to
meet someone and change their mind. To
me, that's just another excuse for these
women leading people on they've changed their mind.
But how could you change your mind that
quickly if you haven't even met the
person? It doesn't make sense.
It's just all [ __ ] It's all you know?
It's like that one in Birmingham. They
knew that they were never going to meet
me when I met Monty, but they still kept
leading me on.
Never never, never have I said to a
woman, "I'm going to meet you and then
change my mind." Never.
Oh, yeah. The one that was being passive
aggressive and being a [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah.
But well, my intention wasn't to my
intention was to meet her and [ __ ] her
over, but she wouldn't do that. So, I
mean, I was going to meet her and [ __ ]
her over with a steak, but she I think
she clocked on. So, I mean, yeah, but
that was that was me getting someone
back on purpose cuz they were being a
[ __ ] not two people arranging to
normally meet, you know.
Yes. I sent her on a wild goose chase
because she was being a passive
aggressive [ __ ] and there was a reason
for it. These women have no reason to
lead me on. Completely different. Two
completely different things. Two
completely completely different things.
I had done what I done on to her on
purpose cuz she was being a [ __ ] She
was being a passive aggressive stuck up
little [ __ ] That's the difference. I
wasn't being any of these things to any
of these women.
So, I mean, if I had done it for no
reason, then it would be the same thing.
But I done it for a very valid reason.
She was being a [ __ ]
So, that's why I done it.
Um, because they would have blocked me
and they don't know my name. Again, another excuse,
These women don't know my name.
So, and they haven't blocked me either.
I thought it was funny. To be honest,
she wasn't scared. I bet you I I could
make her [ __ ] scared. I could make
her [ __ ] scared, mate.
So, and another thing is, you know, when
you're saying about the ones that if
they've seen you online and that, Joe,
well, what about all of the ones that
pretend that they got boyfriends?
I I can tell you. I can tell you why. I
can tell you why. I I can tell you.
Finger up, teacher. I can tell you. Um
because they're leading you on on
purpose. And yes, women can do it just
like men do it. I know you don't believe
it, but it it's true. And another thing
is, even if that was the truth, Joe,
let's just say that all of these women
suddenly typed your name up, right, and
found what you said online. Okay, but
what about all of the ones that pretend
they've got a boyfriend? What about the
ones that when you try to start a
conversation, they say straight away
they're not interested?
You know, excuses can only get you so
far. You know,
they can only get you so far, bro.
What about the ones that you have been
on a date with and they've been [ __ ] So, yeah. So, yeah,
just excuses upon excuses upon excuses.
I mean, they're just [ __ ] and that's
it. And we just have to accept it. I
don't know what what what what there's
nothing left to say.
Okay. So, what about the ones that say
they're not interested before you finish
your sentence? What about the ones that
pretend they've got a boyfriend? Why?
Why are they not interested?
Okay. Let me use that analogy then. Why?
But why are these people not interested?
Because these people say that you're
going to meet someone, you know?
I mean, how the [ __ ] do you think I
feel? You know, I I've shown you clear
evidence of what they do, and you still
sit there and deny it. So,
um, no. Have I said that I'm always
right? I mean, I've literally gave you
the the benefit of the doubt that if
they don't reply to the message, maybe
you come across a certain way, maybe you
done something. I mean, I've never once
said, "I'm always right." I just know
when somebody has agreed to meet you,
they are leading you on. It's common
sense. When have I said I'm always
right? You try and make it seem like I
say that I'm always right. It's just a
lot of my experiences contradict what
you're saying. That's the difference.
You know understand you know be be
you need to Women don't like nice guys.
So I don't know why you said I need to
be nice. What what's being nice got to
do with anything? Women don't like nice
guys. This guy is definitely a white knight.
I mean it's I I don't know. I feel sorry
for you people.
I really do. But that's the thing, Joe. I've
You've Okay. Okay.
It's like what Ricky said.
It's like what Ricky said. He says that
what I was doing wrong with these women
is I was loving their messages, but it's
okay for them to love my messages. So,
all of these things are just excuses.
And we all know that if I was gay and I
was dealing with men, no excuses would
be had. You understand? I'm using this
as an example. Um, men and women, you
would not be you making excuses for men.
So, it's not because of me. It's because
they're women that you're defending them.
You know, I don't understand the whole
point of these things, Grezy. I mean,
let me ask you, Grievy, would you agree
that these people dismiss my struggles?
And Grievy is not a yes man. We we we we
disagree on most things. The only thing
we agree on is narcissists. We only
agree on like narcissists and how
they're cowards. I mean, would would you
say that they dismiss my struggles?
I don't block people that agree or
disagree, mate. I just block [ __ ]
What What do you think? Well,
it's not from a woman's point of view
because I've shown you them leading me on. again.
Again, like I've said, you're dismissing my struggles
because you've seen this is what I mean
by dismissing struggles.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. I would see it that I'm leading
someone on. If I've said I'm going to
meet someone and on the day I've come
out with a [ __ ] excuse, I'm leading
them on. It's like that one from
Birmingham. She was talking to me for
three weeks knowing damn well you
weren't going to meet me all of a sudden
to come and say, "Oh, I'm not interested in dating."
It's purposely done. It's obviously it's
on purpose. Why do you keep making
excuses for them? I don't know why you
keep making excuses for these women. Why
you think it's impossible for them to
lead people on? I've already shown you
what one done, who I met at the [ __ ]
Euros. Why do you think it's impossible
for them to lead people on?
And maybe, just maybe, they're [ __ ]
with you. I don't understand why you
I don't get it.
Which ones? What were they having led me on?
Well, I mean, okay, I can show you
uh well, I've got messages where I've
messaged someone, they messaged me, I
messaged them back, and they never
messaged me again. I mean, I've shown
you plenty of messages, Joseph.
If you went on, if see, this is again
dismissing my struggles again because if
you saw the messages, there's loads of
messages where they didn't leave me on.
They just didn't reply to the second
message or they just didn't reply.
I mean there did you not see the messages? >> No.
Oh, I wish that woman raped from uh
South America. She cuz she was being a
[ __ ] Yeah. No, she deserved it. Yeah,
she deserved it. She was being a [ __ ]
Okay, I'll give you an example. Uh, one second.
Yeah, Greavves. Exactly. Looking at
Yeah. They mock people and then when you
stand up to yourself, they play victim.
Yeah. That's like this one in South
America. She was a [ __ ]
I mean there's people I mean I've met
women from f from France right that have
led me on and trolled me but it was so
funny that I didn't even say anything
about it to be honest and then there's
people that are just a [ __ ] like her um
and she deserved everything she got and
I messaged her family as well cuz she
was being a [ __ ] and she was trying to
mock me as well bit like what you just
said Grezy so um knowing damn well
people was going to message me so no she
deserved everything getting wrist raped
and everything. That one definitely 100%.
And I wouldn't give a [ __ ] if she got
raped. So I don't care.
That one. Yeah. I don't give a [ __ ] I
wish it to her again. [ __ ] her.
Trying to [ __ ] Yeah. So So
you want um So you want a example of
where someone's not led me on? Okay. One sec.
Hold on a minute.
Okay, one second.
Um, what about that one from New Zealand?
What about this one where I said, "Oh,
thanks. For some reason, I thought you
was going to Uber. You turned out be
super nice." And then she all of a
sudden stopped messaging.
I mean, what happened there?
Um, but one that's not let me on. Uh, I
got one in mind here.
Okay. Okay. Here's one.
Uh [ __ ] Where is it?
Yeah, but these are years ago, lad.
Here's one. Hey, it was lovely talking
to you last night. Shame I had to jump
on the bus and we couldn't finish our
chat. Did you get home? Okay, question
mark. I did, thanks. That's good. Any
plans for today? Never heard from her ever again.
Hi, it was nice meeting you last night
and chatting with you. How's your day?
Hey, it's good. Quite hung over though.
How about you? Same. I just come back
from the cinema. Hey, I was thinking we
could meet up either tomorrow or Sunday
before you leave and go back to
Australia. Never replied.
Hi, it was nice meeting you yesterday.
How's your day going?
Never replied. Hi, what you up to this
weekend? I was thinking we could go to
Burger and Lobster. Hi, that's very kind
of you, but unfortunately I'm flying out
on Monday, so I'm a bit chained for I'm
a bit cramped for time. It was great
meeting you though.
So these ones open a book for something completely different. This basically
basically contradict when people say
they go for personality. Here's one. Hi,
it was nice meeting you yesterday. How's
your day going? Hey. Hey. Yes, really.
Thank you for your approach. You have
you had a great evening. It is good. I
went to Ning Hill and now I'm walking.
How was yours?
So, this is someone that obviously liked
my approach. No problem at all. I just
thought you was pretty and looked nice,
so I had to come over and talk to you.
I've just got back from a walk. Where
did you end up going in the end last
night? Anywhere nice. Never heard from her again.
So, this is going to be a hard one to
talk your way out of because they've
approached, they've said uh they've
messaged back, they said that they've
liked your approach, they're asking you
a question, then when you've messaged
them back, you've never heard from them again.
So that's going to be a very very hard
one to talk your way out of since you
are talking about people not leading people on.
So I mean there's different [ __ ]
that they do
because why have they replied back to
then not reply? It doesn't it just does
not make any sense, you know. And it
also doesn't and it also means they
don't go for personality either because
if they went for personality um
then I mean this one's genuine here.
Hey it was lovely meeting you last
night. How's the hangover? Hey hangover
is not good. Was really nice meeting you
too but I just went I want to be honest
and say I'm not interested. I'm not
looking to date or anything right now.
Hope you had a good night. Which is honest.
That's like as honest as it gets. But at
the same time, it's still not good because
people are telling you that they're
going for personality.
Yet these women are not giving you a
chance. But yeah, I mean that's there's
nothing to say on that one, but it's
still kind of contradicting when they're
saying that, oh, women go for
personality because it's it's
sugarcoating it. You know what I mean?
Cuz it's [ __ ] Cuz I mean, it's
honest. It's not leading someone on, but
it's still not good at the same time. Cuz like,
why aren't they giving you a chance?
They don't have to, but why aren't they
giving you a chance? You can still ask
the question. You know, it is what it
is. There's nothing wrong with how you
look. They haven't got to know your personality. So,
what is it? So that's what I'm trying to
say. You know, they're all different things. But yeah,
it is weird. It is. It is. It is weird.
You can see why people would think it's
weird. And then you you know that one
right there, let's go to Burger and
Lobster. And then they didn't want to go
burger and lobster. But what I mean, why
wouldn't you? People say that they got
And then when you when you state the
obvious, then they just go and say women
don't owe you anything. So it's like
what the [ __ ]
Then they say that women don't know you
anything. So what the actual [ __ ] It doesn't make sense.
Did you completely ignore what I've just read out?
Seems that you
Seems that you ignored what I just read out.
Didn't suit you. No. Guess that might be
the case. Doesn't suit you. No.
Crazy, is it, bro? We're not worried
about this [ __ ] tomorrow. Anyways, we're
just going out for a drink. So
gave it the ick.
And what about the other one? Okay.
Give her the ick. That's a new excuse.
What about the other one?
What about the excuse for that one?
I really feel sorry for you people, bro.
Having to defend women all your life.
It's It's [ __ ] so mad
defending women all your life. It's
[ __ ] insane, bro. Absolutely insane. crazy
madness. They make excuses because these
women aren't interested.
You know, that's what it is. They always
make excuses. Oh, it's you. It's
something that you've done
no when it could just be the way you
look and and they're too picky. But no
one will ever say that. It's madness.
It's madness. We need to stop talking
about I don't I don't understand the
point of talking about this.
I really don't understand the point of
talking about this anymore, bro. This is
No, no, no, no. You are making excuses
for them because they're not interested
as well. Uh well, it's not fine because
you are saying that women go for
personality. So, it's not fine because
you people on the internet are saying
that they go for personality and I'm
proving that they don't even give you a
chance. So, it's contradicting what
you're saying. That's what I'm trying to say.
So, okay. Okay. You're sat there saying
about how women go for personality,
right? And how it's this and how it's
that and how it's this and how it's
that. Yeah, you've seen
clear evidence where they have not even
given me the chance. Even when they've
replied um when they've replied positively,
right? Yeah. You need to tell yourself
that, not me. You need to tell yourself
that instead of making excuses for them.
Yes. So, stop making excuses that, oh,
you gave them the ick or that or
whatever. Yeah. They're not interested
in this country. Yeah, I know. I already
know this. You're telling me stuff that
I already know. You need to tell
yourself that. You don't need to tell me
that. You need to tell your [ __ ] self
I know they're not interested in this
country, bro. I don't give a [ __ ]
And they don't go for personality either,
you know? And that's what people need to
say as well, lad. I mean, they're not
interested in you, me on 80, 90% of the population. Yeah.
Yeah. They're not interested in you
either or 80 90% of people. Yeah. Yeah.
And this is what I would this is what
I'd understand. This is what I could get
more if they if these people, right,
Joseph Far went on Reddit and they said, "Listen,
um, you know, they're not they're not
interested in this country. you play it
at your own play it at your own risk,
you know, maybe you'll get lucky one
day. Then I could understand it and I
like, okay, that's true. But they they
lie. That's what these people on Reddit
do. They lie to people and they do it on
the internet as well. They lie. They
they tell people a lie, you know.
I mean, I'm still going out tomorrow
anyways regardless, you know.
Yeah. you keep telling yourself that,
bro. You're you're a [ __ ] idiot. But
then if they said something like that,
Joe, then I could respect that. Okay,
fair enough. You know,
like they give people warnings about gambling,
right? But they're but people online are
saying that they go for personality.
Right. Right. Right. Right. But people
on Reddit are saying that they go for personality.
So it contradicts what they're saying.
That's what I'm trying to say to you. So
stop saying go out and speak to women
and they go for personality. Then say
stuff like that. Don't don't [ __ ]
and lie. Because listen. Oh my god. They
these people make it seem like when you
go out and you approach women, you're
going to get a girlfriend. You're going
to get laid, but it's not going to happen.
They don't know my personality, right?
We're going round and round in circles,
bro. Like, let's just agree to disagree anyways.
We're going round and round. We're
having the same argument over and over
again. We're not getting anywhere.
Um, so we're having the same argument
over and over again. Let's let's let's
just disagree to let's just agree to disagree.
Nope. I've never been to bingo.
People on Reddit say that.
I mean, I had a woman say to me I'm too
old for her when she's 23 and 28. And
I'm not even ugly. I just look like a
normal person. I'm thinking, "What the fuck?"
No, no, we're not just talking about
sex. We're talking about relationships as well. You know,
you're not getting my point, bro. And
we're just having the same argument.
We're having the same argument.
I put my evidence out there. If you want
to believe it, believe it. If you don't,
don't. That's up to you.
I'm not here to like say anything anymore.
And then women lie and I can't listen I
I here's this here's the thing here.
Yeah. Joe. Yeah. You remember that
Muslim girl that I kept me well I met once she
I said to her not that I care I said
it's Peter why did you block me on
WhatsApp she said hey Pete I'm going to
change my number and purchase O2 SIM
that's why we're moving everyone from
WhatsApp they can't even be honest they're toxic
they're toxic they can't even tell the
truth and just say oh I blocked you cuz
I blocked you when I didn't even care I
just wanted to see what she'd say.
Anyways, they're b they're bullshitters.
They're absolute bullshitters, you know.
Just like they'll be bullshitters um
next week. E. Yep. Yeah. >> Yeah.
Yeah, sister is making a chicken curry, bro.
That's okay with me, boss. I got a nice
t-bone steak for later.
I'm having a chicken curry. My sister's
making me a chicken curry.
Yeah, but it's never going to change, is it?
So, they're always going to white night.
I wish I Joe, you know, when you're sat
there saying, "Oh, yeah, you should live
your life without worrying about women."
Do you know how hard that is?
You know, like yesterday when I was out
with my mom in Liverpool Street,
it's [ __ ] depressing as [ __ ] bro.
I'm going out tomorrow.
No one's blocked by me at all.
No one gets blocked by me at all. I
actually unblocked people. Ricky Millington.
I mean, I literally unblocked people
just like I'm going to unblock that PC
tomorrow, that PC account and saying who
can't afford trainers. Uh, who can't
afford trainers? Say what?
I mean, I actually unblocked people.
Ricky Millington ran away when I put
them approaching videos up. He ran away.
He ran away and he's not blocked. Ever
since I put them approaching videos up,
Greavves, he ran away. Strange
cuz you said it was how I was acting. So
obviously I put the protein videos up. strange. Yeah.
Uh, I put I put messages up there. I put
my approaches up there. I'm not arguing
with you, bro.
I put my evidence out there. I'm not arguing.
me in a relationship? Why would I show
me in a relationship? You would deny it.
Even if I showed you, Joe, why why do
you want to see me in a relationship?
You would deny it.
Huh? What the [ __ ] bro? Why Why would
you want to see someone in a relationship?
You would just deny it. Just like you
tell people that they're skinned and
they can't afford a new pair of
trainers. Trainers are coming tomorrow,
by the way. Yeah.
I mean, what does the matter?
We're not talking about women already to
settle down. I've put evidence, right?
I'm not going to argue with you, bro.
I'm not going back and forth. I put my
evidence out there. I'm not arguing.
It's a waste of my time. And I'm not
blocking anyone either. So, you're
talking to yourself now. If you're that
dumb that you ignore evidence that
you're shown, black and white evidence,
that's your problem, bro. It's not my problem.
So, you deal with it. It's not my problem, bro.
So, yeah. Keep defending women. Like I
said, bro, everyone's everyone's
different in their life. I'm not telling
you how to live your life. You do what
you want. If you want to sit there being
a virgin, defending women all your life,
do that. I don't give a [ __ ]
I'm not here to tell you otherwise.
You know, I'm I showed what I've been
dealing with with these women. You want
to disagree, disagree. You want to
agree, you agree. I'm not asked. I don't
give a [ __ ]
Keep defending women all your life. I
don't give a [ __ ] bro.
No job lives with their mom. It's boring
now, bro. We've heard all of this
before. You don't know what people have
and you don't know what people don't
have. again. Stop talking about
yourselves. Just like you tell people
that they're skin and they can't afford
trainers. It's all self-p projection.
We're bored of it now. Very, very, very,
very, extremely bored of it. You don't
know what people have and what people
don't have. It's a projection of your
own lives. You little weasels have been
doing this for [ __ ] ages now. How
many times has one of you's come on
here, started [ __ ] with people, you've
been proven wrong, and then when you're
proven wrong, you run away. It's
extremely boring. Now,
most of you on here, bro, are just like
fat, ugly people that ain't got nothing
in your lives and you want to bring
other people down with you. You know,
you know that I don't work. How you know
that I don't work. You don't know
whether I work or not. You don't know me.
You don't know what I have. You don't
know anything about what I do and what I don't do.
You know, again, self-p projection. This
is what I mean with you. You people come
on here, right? You're fat and ugly and
you got nothing. And you want to bring
other people down to your skin level.
That's what you people do.
Fat, ugly people trying to bring other
people down. People that ain't got a
life. That's all you people are. You're boring now.
fat, ugly mongrels that try to bring
other people down to their level, you
know, like come on here right now and
show us what you look like, bro. And
show us what you've got. Show us your
gaff. Come on.
Living with my mom, bro. You're fat,
ugly people that ain't got a life. Don't
worry about who I live with. Don't worry
about who I don't live with. Don't worry
about whether I work. Don't worry about
if I don't work. Worry about your fat
ugly selves and stop self projecting.
You saying that I'm blocking bro giving
facts. How can you give facts? You don't know me.
You don't know me. You can't give any
facts cuz you don't know anything about
me. So there are no facts
because you don't know me. I'm not
blocking you. If you was if you were
stating facts and I'm telling you what
you people do. I'm telling you people
what you do. I'm I'm not blocking
anyone. You can't tell the truth because
you don't know me. This is exactly what
I'm I I'm I'm trying to explain to these
people, Grezy, over and over and over
again. They don't know who they're
talking about. Right. Do you remember
what I was saying yesterday, Grezy,
about these trainers? Yeah. Should I buy
them? Should I not buy them? And you
said, "Don't buy them." So, I thought,
"Fuck it. I'm not going to buy them."
And then you get someone jumping on the
jam bandwagon saying, "Oh, you can't
afford them. You can't afford them. You
can't afford them." I was like, "Bro,
I'll buy them right now." As soon as I
saw them, I bought him right now. You
get me, lad. Because you don't know who
you're talking about. You know what I
mean? That's what I mean, bro. Yeah.
You are a fat, ugly [ __ ] That's facts.
You are a fat, ugly, jobless [ __ ] that
ain't got a life, that's never been with
a woman. That's facts.
That is 100% facts. That you weasels
ain't got a life and that you're fat and
ugly. That's facts. And I can tell you
how I know this stuff. Cuz I've
monitored your YouTube activity. I've
seen when you've put your cameras on on
YouTube. The facts are you people are
fat and ugly and ain't got a life. And
that's facts. And I can prove it by
putting the link up right now and you're
not going to join. That's facts. That is
facts. Benefits are paid. [laughter]
Benefits are paid today. Really? I I
didn't I didn't know I got benefits
today. Grezy, again, talking about. This
is what I mean with these people. They
talk about themselves.
They They self-project their lives. This
is what I mean with these people. They
think everyone's got the same life as
these mongos. This is what I mean. This,
bro, this is actually so entertaining,
lad. I swear to God.
You know, benefits are paid. Really?
Really? Benefits are paid. Again, their
own lives they're talking about. This is
what I mean with these people. I didn't
I didn't know people get paid benefits
on a Friday.
I have more money than you will ever
have. The joys of talking about people
that you don't know. This is what I'm [ __ ] saying.
This is my whole point. Stop basing your
life around other people's. We don't all
have the same lives as you. Skin, fat,
ugly, no life. Please listen to me. I'm
I'm trying to help you learn something.
Stop thinking everyone's got the same
lives as you people. You'll go far in
life, bro. You really will go far in
life if you just listen to this, you know?
It's really real, bro. Really [ __ ] real.
I'm never showing you any money ever
again. So there's no point saying how
much you want to show. I'm never showing you anything.
I'm never showing money again. I mean,
I've said that a million times. I'm
never showing money on here. So I don't
know why you're asking me about showing
money. I've never showing money on here.
Been there, done that, worn a t-shirt.
I'm never showing you no money ever
again. Whether it's£10, 20 pound, 30
pound. Next question.
Next question, lad. What's the next
question? Because I've said this about a million times, you know,
I mean, how long have you been on this [ __ ] community?
How long have you been on this [ __ ]
community? Answer that. How long have
you been on it? Huh?
Yeah, of course you do, bro. Yeah, of
course you do, man. You on your Yeah, of
course you do. Yeah, of course you do, bro.
You're just a fat ugly [ __ ] that ain't
got a life. Uh, boring,
bro. Why Why are you asking people to
show you money anyways? Why do Why do
you want people to show you money?
Every time people show you money, you
run off like last time. Why? Why? Why do
you want people to show you money?
Why do you want people to show you
money, lad? Every time you get show
money, you run off. Same boring [ __ ]
same atmosphere. I'm not even going to
block you. I'm just going to ignore you
now cuz you cry when people block you.
[ __ ] You need to get a life, you little bongo.
Yeah. Okay. You okay? Come on right now
and show money.
You people asking you self project constantly
about a 28. Bro, I'd rather be 28 living
with my mom than be like you people in
your 40s sat on YouTube [ __ ] no life,
no [ __ ] money, thinking that you can
talk about anyone. You just self-project
your own lives. You try to bring other
people down to your ugly levels. That's
what you do, bro. I'm never showing you
money ever again. Back down, bro. You've
been shown thousands and thousands of
pounds before, and you people have
backed down multiple times. I'm not
showing you nothing. So, it's not going
to work. I'm not showing you nothing.
I'll show you these traders when they
come tomorrow, but when it's to do with
money, I'm not showing you no money.
No£10, no 20 pound, no30 pound, no
nothing. You could have showed me, you
could have done that when I showed you
them that thou them thousands of pounds
multiple times. I am not showing you no
money. No, you're not seeing no money
from me. And now I am blocking you now
because you're repeating. So bye-bye now.
Repeating. Now I am blocking you because
you're repeating yourself. So bye
little weasels on this community. I
[ __ ] swear, bro.
[ __ ] repeating bastards.
Repeating little [ __ ] mongrels. [ __ ] me.
There we go. Love my own voice. I do,
mate. You know Sorry that.
Yeah, that's repeated.
There's a lot of repeaters on this community, lad. Sh.
No, no, no.
These people need to get alive.
>> [clears throat]
>> And don't lie about your job.
No lie by YouTube.
No, no, no, no.
She ends in the AP
[ __ ] me, bro.
Well, I'm going anyways. See?