Right, Ricky Millington,
you posted something an hour ago, so I
know you on [ __ ] YouTube. Why have you disappeared
since I put them approaching videos up?
Why have you bloody disappeared? And
yes, I'm using the word bloody cuz
that's my favorite word. I see you
comment on a great guy's channel singing
over that woman on the train, but I
don't see you on my channel. You're not
blocked. The comments are open.
Bloody. I got a bloody bone to pick with
you. You bloody hooligan.
Ricky Milling hands. You know what a [ __ ] dipstick.
You said it was how I was acting. You liar.
Don't make me [ __ ] come to hole today
and poke your [ __ ] eyes out cuz I'll
do it. I'm just waiting on the lovely
trainers to to come
and I'll be outside
doing it and that stuff and poaching and stuff.
Oh my god. But again, I'm not backing up
Timmy because you know, you know what
happens when you back up Timmy just
snakes you. But it isn't that [ __ ]
bad. These simps. Do you know what? I
I've made a conscious decision, right?
When these trainers come. Um I'll be off
of YouTube for a couple of weeks. I
can't do this anymore. It's the same
atmosphere. You know, the white
nighting, the singing, the projecting,
the repeating. I can't do it. It's too
much for one person's brain.
It's too much. It's the same atmosphere
and it and it ain't a good one either.
It's not a good one. All right.
That Ricky is a proper white knight.
He's a proper white knight. I caught him
on the [ __ ] great night. Uh the great guy's channel.
>> The great guy's channel.
What? You go on their channel, but you
don't go on my channel, Ricky Minton.
when I literally put up these
approaching videos especially for you.
You know, you little white knight. Had
enough of you, you little white knight.
Who think to [ __ ] defend women, you loser?
You know, right? Get out of the car now, Franklin.
Right. Go into the other car now, Franklin.
Yeah. Waiting for these trainers. I'll
be here today and I'm off
off on an adventure,
you know. Never don't know where I'm
going to end up, but somewhere.
Yeah. Want to find a new mama. That's
what I'm going to do. Yeah.
Yeah. That Ricky Millington's a proper s.
But that woman does not look scared at
all. She doesn't look one bit scared.
That's the funniest thing about it. I
think a man would have acted more scared
than her, you know.
Yeah, that Ricky is a proper proper white knight.
Proper proper proper proper white
knight. He is
he won't he won't come on my live
stream, will he? Nah, he won't cover mine.
[ __ ] white knight. You get women. Do
you [ __ ] get women, mate? If you got
women, you would be white knighting. By
the end of the day, I shouldn't just let
people go for Timmy to be honest because
he just stabs you in the back just like
he used to do with Pat Mustard. You know,
if there was a reason to defend the
woman, then I would defend the woman and
be impartial. But this is just white
knighting. What these people are doing
is literally whiting for argument's sake.
You go on the street and you randomly
attack a woman for no reason. I mean,
that's a bit out of order, isn't it? You
know, but a woman starting [ __ ] and her
getting it given back and not looking
scared. Sorry. I I I don't see too much
of a problem with that. I really really
really really [ __ ] don't.
I remember as well when I done it, when
I shouted in um but I weren't in her
face. That's the difference. I literally
stepped back and gave her the
opportunity to walk away anytime she wanted to. You know,
it's crazy, bro. Really crazy.
Anyone would think that he's they're
just white knights where these people
don't leave the house and they don't get
women. They they think it's it's part of
their autism. They think by defending
women like this Ricky guy, it's going to
get them women. And it doesn't. That's
the thing. It's It's weird. It's so
weird. I'll go out today and get more
women than any of these white knights.
As soon as the [ __ ] trainers come, you watch.
It's mad why they
It's It's just mental, bro.
Why they Why they white
nature? I don't know why they keep
whitelighting women. Like, yeah, I don't
like Timmy and I'm not backing him up
because he always stabs me in the back,
but bro, it's not that bad. like these
people are going on about. It really
isn't. They're such white knights, you
know. They've done it with me as well.
You know, I've put up evidence of women
leading me on playing games and they
still defend them. It's It's pathetic, bro.
But yeah, nature, I'm waiting for these
trainers to come. I've got a football
bet on. I'm going to the pub today for some beers
and doing some approaches and [ __ ] Why
the [ __ ] not in it? Um,
I think I I can stomach it now. It'd be
rude not to. New jeans, new trainers.
It'd be very rude not to.
But these white knights, bro,
do you reckon I'll get some success
today? Nature girl, nice Stony, nice 200
jeans, 200 trainers are on way. They
should be here by midday or something.
What do you reckon?
Yeah, like I said, if if there was a
situation where the woman
needed to be defended, then it's
different. It is different. Like,
but there was this [ __ ] Roy there
that slapped this guy said, "Oh, you're disrespecting women."
Yeah. I'm not I'm not going to hear I've
got a boyfriend today, am I?
Not going to hear that today. Am I nature girl?
Did you read the messages that I uh that
I put up? Did you see the approaches
that I put up?
No. Didn't didn't suit you. No. Probably
didn't suit you to be honest. It's it's
it's okay, you know.
I'm used to my my struggles getting
dismissed. It's just a thing that happens now. >> [snorts]
>> They should call me Peter Struggles.
Do I think he was in the right? Um, I
don't think he was in the wrong. I
wouldn't say he was in the right, but I
don't think he was in the wrong.
Um, because A, she didn't look scared at
all. And B, he just not like he hit her
or anything. What the [ __ ]
So, but I'm not backing that little
[ __ ] anyways because he always
snakes me. But no, there's I mean she
was given it. He gave it back. She
didn't at all look scared.
So I don't understand what the what what
the big deal is.
I don't have any understanding for him.
I would say even if it was a normal
person. I mean I got [ __ ] for shouting
at someone and I was nowhere near them
and I still got [ __ ] These white
knights really need to get off the
internet and get laid, bro. It's
pathetic at this age now.
No, I would have just stayed in my seat
mouthing off. No, I would have just
stayed in I wouldn't have got in their
face. I would have just stayed in the
seat in my seat um mouthing off to them.
That's what I would have done.
Yeah, I would have got in their face. I
wouldn't need to get in their face. I
would just mouth off about them to them
and if they come and put their hands on
me, I'll knock them out. Simple.
If she got in my face, then I'll smash
her face in. Simple. That's it. Yeah.
I'll give her three chances to move
herself. And if she doesn't, I'll smash
her face in. But if she got in my face. Yeah.
Yeah. You mad, bro.
Yeah. It's like the one I shouted at the
park. They defended her even though I
was nowhere near her. I actually took a
step back and they were still defending her
when it's like really, bro. Like what? So yeah.
What do you think of my approaching
videos, Nate? Girl, where they said
they're not interested straight away or
the women that led me on.
Didn't suit you, did it? No,
that didn't suit you. You did it. Nah.
Didn't suit you. No. That [ __ ] then
But it doesn't suit you, does it? Yeah.
Yeah. But I'm just going out drinking
today anyway. I know it's going to be
the same old, but what else do I have to do? Hey,
they told me to go on the dating apps. Nature girl,
people already told me to use the apps
and when I showed them the app's not
working, they bloody ran away. And yes,
I said bloody. That's my favorite word. Bloody.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
I'm tired as as [ __ ]
I'm definitely going out today still. 100%.
I can't do this steak video today cuz my
mouth is still slightly hurting.
I can maybe do it when I get back. Maybe.
I'm going to need to try and eat it at
some point because it's it cost me a lot
of money that steak. So,
I'll probably cook it when I get back.
That's probably the earliest I can do it.
So, I'll probably go to the pub and get some food. Yeah.
I don't want to hear about any bloody
boyfriends today. I don't want to hear
about any bloody boyfriends
in these clubs cuz I want to know where he is.
I'm I'm I'm a nut taste, you know. I'm
worse than [ __ ] Timmy.
So, yeah, we'll see. Anyways,
it shouldn't be this way, should it? Nature girl
shouldn't be this way, bro. It should
not be this way.
For some, for some reason, it is. You know,
I had a long enough break off.
I'll be out next week as well. I think
it's all random. I just go out when I
want to go out. You know,
I'm tired, bro. [ __ ] tired. I had to
take some pills cuz of the mouth again.
She don't want to know you. Anyways,
I'll be back later. Yeah.