All right, just marinated the steaky doodles. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, marinated steak. So, oh lovely.
So many bloody projectors on this
community. Bloody. I know I'm saying it
again. [ __ ] bloody bloody hell.
Here we go. Yeah.
Wonder what these people will be doing
on YouTube. Be doing today. Sat on
YouTube. No life. being mongos creating
the same bloody atmosphere as they do
every day. These fat ugly old people or
maybe they'll be trying to bring other people down.
You know, that's a possibility. I mean,
they do do that, don't they? Try to
bring other people down
to their skin level. to their [ __ ] skin
Know that these bloody people on YouTube
on YouTube no life [snorts] right
coming for 9:30 to 1. So
yeah, can't wait. Can't bloody wait. these trainers.
Ain't no skin virgin. Now, I was going
to invite uh invite virgin boy, but uh
they said that there's no virgins
allowed. It's a no virgin, no skimp
people policy. Now, again, I don't make
the rules. I tried um arguing against
it, but the manager wouldn't have any of
it, mate. So, sorry about that, mate.
They're not forkinned virgins.
>> [snorts and clears throat]
>> Sorry mate. Not poor skin virgins.
Sorry, mate. Yeah, I'm waiting for my
trainers to come. Um,
yeah, I marinated my T-bone steak. I'm
going to cook it in a bit. Wait for
these trainers to come and then go out
and send it. Looking for that change. I
was going to uh invite Virgin Boy out,
but uh it's a it's a no skint no virgin
policy. So obviously he he he's skint
and he's a virgin. [gasps] So obviously
he's not allowed um to to come cuz he's
a skin virgin.
So obviously I tried to say to the
manager, look, can he come? He's he's
getting on 31. He's almost a virgin. And
he's like, no, no skin virgins. So
sorry, mate. had to try. Yeah,
he'd probably scare everyone away with
his ugly face. Know what I mean, Richie?
Yeah. Just waiting for the trainers now, lad.
Yeah, just waiting for the trainers.
Then I'll cook this and then Yeah, I'll
be in the pub later, mate. I'll be out
all [ __ ] day, won't I? Give us a
[ __ ] meal, son.
You're also [ __ ] real, mate. [snorts]
You should see this t-bone, Cory. You'll
love it, mate. You'll love it. You'll
[ __ ] love this t-bone.
It's absolutely [ __ ] lush.
Absolutely lush, mate.
Yeah. Going to cook it with mushrooms.
Could have a headache, man. cuz I had to
take them pills cuz of my [ __ ] toothach lad.
Yeah, man. I'll be getting rejected
today like a [ __ ]
Yeah, I'll be out getting rejected
here and I've got a boyfriend. But it's
all just a bit of fun, eh? Oh man.
Yeah, it's all just a bit of fun.
Yeah, I'm [ __ ] tired as [ __ ] bro.
But I'm definitely going out. I got my
football as well. Yeah.
I wish the virgin could come with me.
You might get laid, but like I said,
it's a no virgin uh no skin policy.
So, obviously, you can't you can't go. I
did try, Cory. See, I'm not I'm not a
narcissist, but you know, I did try, lad. Yeah,
I did [ __ ] try, lad. I did try.
No virgins allowed.
You know what I'm like, mate.
No skint virgins in bed sits allowed
with ugly clothes.
If you must know what the manager said.
Sorry, mate. [ __ ] sorry.
I think I'm going to put this t-bone
steak on shortly.
cost me 15 quid, dude. Sorry.
Yeah, that's why he's still a [ __ ]
virgin. That's why you'll [ __ ] die
one. I'm not doing this [ __ ] bro. I'm
not doing this [ __ ] forever. Like, after
today, we're going to do content on this
channel. Omar like responding to these
people. But I just done this as a thing
as like stop talking about people that
you don't know. Saying that I can't
afford trainers. I've got 210 trainers
coming today, mate. So what I'm
basically saying is stop talking about
people that you don't know.
That was that was the life lesson.
Don't talk about people that you don't
know. We're not all, like I said to you
a million times, Cory, these people on
here on this community,
they seem to think everyone's got their
life. Skin, alone, can't afford things,
[ __ ] fat, ugly, whatever. Bro, they
these people generally think everyone's
got their life. That's their problem.
It's like what I mentioned in the video.
It's the truth.
They think everyone is skint like them.
And I don't know. I don't know why they
feel that way, bro. I don't know why
they think that,
but they do that. So, got these trainers coming. Oh, bro.
I'm going to have my I'm going to have
some food at Weather Spoons as well. So,
I'm going to be having some food in the
pub. I always do that anyways when I go
out. So, I'll eat the steak, go out,
send it, go to the pub,
and go from there. Really? Yeah.
Got a bit of a toothach, so
be a little bit difficult biting into
it, but it should be all right. Should
be all right, lad. Oh,
and did you
you hear Virgin Boy
when he was like, "Oh, absolute. They
absolutely are great jeans." I said,
"They [ __ ] absolutely are, mate.
Better than any [ __ ] thing you've
ever won, you skin bastard.
You skint bastard [ __ ] Better than
anything you've ever [ __ ] won, skin boy.
You know what I mean, Richard? They
absolutely [ __ ] are. Absolutely are.
You [ __ ] virgin. Skip bastard. Trump. Yeah. Anyways,
exactly, mate. Them two I
uh them two items, bro, are literally
worth over £400. Just them two items.
Would you had to believe it, mate? No.
Would you Adam and Eve it?
Rhyme it. Rhyme it up, lad. Rhyme it up.
Did I say things you can't afford? Oh,
one second. I can continue this if you want.
Let me just pop downstairs.
Let me Let me pop downstairs. One,
we've been talking about things that you can't afford.
Oh, look at that. That's been marinated.
Skin boy can't afford that.
Skinny boy trying to afford that. I
think I'm going to cook it now. Why not?
I'm going to be eating again later, so I
might as well.
Might as well, you know, why not?
It's a no skip, no virgin policy.
They have different [ __ ] polies, mate.
I've got a nice triple bet for today as well. So,
oh man, I've got nasty headaches as well.
Pull that out there, but we're doing it.
I said I was doing it.
And again, it would be rude not to with
the new garments, would it, lad?
It would be very rude not to.
You [ __ ] sleeping cat. Oh [ __ ]
Right, just heating the plan up now.
might be a little bit early to fake to
some of you guys, but to me
[snorts] I will finish this day.
Where will be?
It's a no skin, no virgin policy, mate.
Sorry mate. Maybe next week normal. You take it.
Yeah. I'm still
I just wanted to see if I'm just doing
my little mushrooms. Sorry,
it's the no skip no virgin policy. That
made [snorts] you laugh, didn't it?
For people that can afford the morning
jeans and trainers. Any moment you might
hear the door go. By the way, the door
might go at any moment, lad.
Any moment the door might go. That be my trainers.
Yeah, just just just just bear in mind.
Just bear in mind, mate.
Just just just just just keep that in mind.
You know, you hear the dog go, mate.
It's the bloody trainers. They're coming.
And guess what? After I eat this t-bone
steak, so will I be coming. [laughter] Get it?
Get it, mate. Whipping me up a tasty t-bone. Tast. Oh,
did I just cut some mushrooms?
Um, Gravesy, now I was going to invite
the virgin out today, but uh I can't do
that. And you might be wondering why.
Basically, the managers contacted me
saying it's a no skin no virgin policy.
The people that are skin virgins are not
allowed. It's just policy. I I don't
make the rules, you know. I don't I
generally generally don't make the
rules, mate. You know, I don't make the
rules. I don't [ __ ] I I tried to say
to the man that, you know, he he he'd
approach 31 and he and he's still a big
fat virgin, you know, in other words,
and and he wouldn't have it. He said,
"No virgins. No, Virgin. I I I don't
make the rules, mate. I don't make the [ __ ] rules.
I generally don't make the [ __ ] rules, mate.
This cost me £15.
That's a That's a weak shopping crim.
I'm such a little show off, aren't I?
I'm such a bloody show off, aren't I?
Oh, gosh darn it. I'm worse than a
woman, aren't I? Yeah.
Oh, god darn it. I'm worse than a
[ __ ] woman, aren't I, mate?
I'm worse than a [ __ ] woman I am, mate.
Now, we just need to find a woman today, Greezy.
We know we I need to find someone. I
woke up and I was feeling a bit weird,
greasy, because obviously I don't get my vitamins anymore.
I don't get the calcium and stuff.
Oh, I don't get the vitamins and the the
calcium and [ __ ] So, I need to find a candidate.
It's okay in the summer, you know. In
the summer, it's fine. I don't need
anyone in the summer, but in the winter
I do because obviously I need my
vitamins and stuff and my milk, you know.
You think it's going to be my lucky day?
I don't think so, mate. But I'm going to
be going out anyways. If it if it How
many times have you said that to me?
That's going to be my lucky day.
I mean, I don't think so. What's your prediction, B?
My predict My prediction is five
numbers, two reply goes, and the other
three don't reply.
But I'm still going out anyways,
you know, because I want to go to the I
want to go to November Spoons and stuff.
I want to have a burger. Got to have a
burger and chips. So yeah,
look at that steak, mate. I marinated it. Yeah.
Where are these bloody traders?
>> Oh yeah, I know, mate.
How sure are you, mate, that you got my
money stopped and I don't have money?
And I think this is a lesson, Richie,
why you don't talk about people that you
don't know. Am I right? Huh?
Don't talk about people that you don't know, you know.
Yeah. They don't they don't uh Yeah.
Don't talk about people that you don't know.
Is that right? >> Yeah.
Why do I pull traders, mate? Why do I
pull traders? Well, cuz you can't
PC virgin ain't got life.
There's so many weasels in this
community, Cory. So many weasels.
Sometimes I have to take a break off of
it for like a week or two weeks. So
yeah, sometimes I have to come up for
like a week or two, lad. Um, but I
always come back though, you know.
Sometimes you just need a break because
it's always the same atmosphere.
It's like what says it's the same atmosphere, you know.
It's the same atmosphere.
The same atmosphere on here.
I can't wait to go to I can't wait to go
to the pub today. Been looking forward to it.
I wonder what these women are going to think.
I wonder what these bloody women are
going to think when they see this
handsome young chap walking with a nice
jeans and a stony.
Wonder what the ladies are going to think. Miy
can afford it.
Grey's got money.
The skin version of the bed, however, he
can't afford. [ __ ] off.
Yeah, I need to find a new Oh, you made
me laugh with your little um comment,
Grizzy. You can latch on the boobies.
That's cute, isn't it?
You can latch on the doomies.
I know what's going to happen. The
doorbell's going to [ __ ] go. These
traders are going to come.
I need to find a new candidate today.
USA was April, so it was still kind of
cold outside. So it kept me warm, you
know, to latch on to the to the boo and do it. Funny. [laughter]
You want to do you like a little video
of the cat?
Do you like the cat? Copycat. Did you like it?
Did you like it, lad?
Got this football bet today as well.
What a lovely Saturday.
Nice t-bone steak.
[ __ ] got some nice trainers coming.
Fresh jeans. What more could you ask for, Grezy?
You know what more could you bloody ask for?
Do you agree?
You know, you could be stuck in a
[ __ ] bed sit 31 in February, still a
virgin, ain't got no [ __ ] money, you know.
Yeah, I'm going to have to try and eat
this bone even though my gums are not perfect. But obviously but obviously
um I I I don't like leaving
Oh [ __ ] I forgot. Oh no. You
just have just enough butter. Just another
lady. I've got a phone to pick with you.
I've got you.
I'm going to uh mushrooms.
Yeah, I'm just whipping up my little uh
I'm just whipping up my little t-bone.
Done the mushrooms. Going to have an
egg. I'm waiting for the new trainers.
So, at any moment, you might hear the
dog go poke mom. Now, I was going to
take um the virgin with me today, but I
wasn't allowed. The manager says it's a
strictly no virgin and no skin people
policy. So obviously actually I can't uh
I can't take him. Sorry. No skin people
and no virgins. I said listen um you
know he he he's going to be 31 in
February and he's still a [ __ ]
virgin. We need to make this [ __ ] lose
it. We don't want him to die one. And I
explained that I met him seven times and
stuff and he weren't interested. The
manager weren't having it at all at all.
He said, "No, no skin virgin. No skin
virgin inventions." I said, "It doesn't
matter where [ __ ] people live."
He The manager was not having none of
it, mate. And you call me a [ __ ]
narcissist. I find out to come get laid.
No skin people, mate.
Oh, this t-bone.
That's the [ __ ] dog. Yeah.
Well, firstly, how to lose your V card.
You need to sort your ugly face out and
you need to buy 200 pound jeans. 200
Jers, you need to sort your ugly face
out. Then you need to you need to stick
a football bet on cuz obviously your
skin and to get the money for the
football bet, you have to obviously suck
your dad's dick cuz your skin. So, you'd
have to suck your dad's disabled Parkers
stick, get about 80, 90 pound off for
your dad, and then stick on the football bet
and then um
yeah, hopefully win the football bet.
Hopefully, you then win the football bet and then
Oh, this is lovely. You then win the
football bear and then
um get me. Oh [ __ ] One second.
Just concentrate on doing it.
Going to grill that steak.
Yeah. There was this woman on um Reddit
saying that she got friends with
benefits Pokémon. I said, "How the blood
able to get friends with benefits? They
ain't outside bloody work." And you
approach them and they all pretend they
got bloody boyfriends. [ __ ] hell. She
didn't reply. [ __ ] hell.
Gosh darn it. She didn't reply. Yeah.
She didn't reply, mate.
Do I have an egg with it or should I not? Nah. No.
Then what you actually do is you actually it
Oh, you didn't wash the bloody pan. You silly goose.
Oh, it is easy, bro.
Oh, it is easy. All you got to do is go
on dating apps.
Make it easy. They make it easy cuz it is easy.
All you got to do is go on datus. Oh, [ __ ]
One second, bro. Watch this. [clears throat]
Oh, God. Darn it.
should be coming any minute. Any minute
I need to
She clean it.
I need to grill the steak. You see that?
We got to build this [cough] crazy man.
But they tell me to go on the app.
Yeah, but they told me to go on the app.
That [ __ ] is [ __ ] mad.
What do you mean? Like Yeah. But they
say going to date now.
Yo, me and you are mate.
Make fun out of someone just cuz they're
a virgin. [ __ ]
know he's a virgin. Never going to pop [clears throat] that [ __ ] Yeah.
He ain't he he ain't got the buddy. He
ain't got the looks. That's why he's
still a virgin. That's why he sat there
convincing himself. I'm not section of
Little USA, is he?
Because he's the he's the biggest he's
the biggest virgin going. So, we know
all the signs and all the and all the
the little things to suggest how
someone's a virgin because he's the
biggest he's the biggest virgin himself.
The biggest one going. You understand?
So, he know these things. Is that right, Grezy?
Look at this steak, guys. Lovely.
Now, we're going to grill it in a minute.
Well, I'm going to see if Pat's yet with the traders.
Oh, nope. Not yet. I can't wait. I'm
rubbing my hands.
Yeah, I need to find a new mama today.
Pokémon, I need my bits,
you know. I need my vitamins.
I need my bit.
What you do is you cook it nicely
with butter. Cook it with butter. It
gets a bit soggy, right?
That's why you crisp it up. That's why.
Oh, look at that, mate.
That looks the [ __ ] million dollars, don't it?
Wait until it crisps up.
Wait until it crisps up, mate.
It's going to be l
Do you reckon anyone's going to say they
got boyfriends? Pokémon.
Anyone's going to say that they've got boyfriends. Pokemon.
Hopefully not. Shouldn't do not in the pubs anyways. Yep.
But like I said, yeah,
it's your lucky day. Look at that one.
I need a new mama. I need to be fed.
I need feeding in the winter.
I need feed,
you know. I need my vitamins and stuff, you know,
because obviously it will be 3 years in
April. Four years in April where my mama left me.
It will be three it will be four years
in April since my mama left me.
I was I was thinking of contacting the thing again
for some milk, you know.
I need to be fed. You know. Yeah. [laughter] Right.
That needs to go under the grill.
That'll be big. Two seconds.
Yeah, I need to be fed. Oh [ __ ]
I was thinking of contacting Sig again.
She to 19year-old.
Well, she's 20 now. The boob her boobs
are not big enough.
So, I didn't get fed. That's why I was
never really satisfied. Pokémon.
That's why I was never really satisfied
cuz obviously they're not big enough to
be, you know, I'm quite a big boy, you know. One sec.
There we go. [clears throat] Lovely. Oh. Oh [ __ ] Oh, yeah. That
You said I was attractive.
You said she's attractive.
I can't stop. I'm waiting for my little trainers.
Where's my little trainers?
I think it's lovely.
What do you think, Ramsy?
in the state now
like these mushrooms can go on now.
I can't believe him coming on the same
website. You can watch the side men on
clean this [ __ ] up after. Did I take the
pills? I don't think I did yet. Did I?
Let me take them off. One second.
I don't know.
One second. Do that. Yeah.
A million dollar
looking a million dollars, mate.
Should I have an egg or should I not
have an egg?
See, when I had USA Izzy's extra bit
vitamins, I didn't need it. But
I'm not sure.
I think I'll just have the steak to be
fair. And also we don't see [clears throat] one second.
Yeah, it was a day after her boyfriend
her boyfriend her birthday.
[ __ ] Am I talking about boyfriend, bro?
Oh, that's lovely, mate. that steak.
You can smell it.
So, you cook it in the pan. If it's
thick, you can't just grill it because
it's so thick. So, what you do is you grill it.
You cook it in the pan and then you
grill the bastard
to give it that crispiness.
I'm going to marinade it one more time.
Make sure you crisp the fat up nicely.
Oh, I lost man. So,
what do you think? Do you reckon I
should contact again?
What do you think?
It's almost finished.
Look at that. You're telling me that
it's not [ __ ] pain.
Go under longer. [clears throat] [ __ ]
And there's not really enough butter for these butter.
I really fancy egg on my uh stomach, you know.
That's the thing with these mushrooms.
We could have done with more butter.
There we go. Oh man, that
he's going to taste the
smell. Bring your
We know that you can never say no to steak.
We We could have done with more um
butter and muffins to be perfect.
[snorts] What do you want this bit?
You can have the end bit.
better at this. There you are.
Oh, am I? M
I can taste
taste the um
taste the pushy powder. I to
that is lovely. H Nice.
One of the best.
Yeah, I'm a good chef, mate. I'm telling you.
It's still not as good as USA boobies, though.
But it's tasty. [clears throat]
movies were tasty.
This is how I like my steak. Look,
I like it like this. A little bit pink,
but no blood.
Muslims are almost finished. [laughter]
They took a bit longer for the >> Yeah.
What can I say, mate? I'm a good cook.
I could have no cheese, mate. And I
would have still had the steak.
Not wasting steak, mate.
Clean the kitchen after we
not big problem is it
ain't no skin virgin in the bedroom.
That's what I always say, mate.
Right. I got the mushrooms. [clears throat] Yeah. What? Really?
Have you ever wondered how you finish a T-Bo?
Have you ever wondered why what's the
point of the bone?
You ever wondered what's the point of the bone?
There's a point of it.
And the point of it is if you get the
card like this, you just Thank you.
Don't look too fire. Oh
no, my luck. The [ __ ] tra will come
the door now.
I need my milk.
I need more. Remember
I put a polo up? Where was it? Okay. All right. Okay,
I'm stuffed. Mama, what are you going to
do? Put me in the oven now.
What are you going to do? Stick me in
the oven now.
I need to be fed.
Hurry up. These trainers need to come. I
need to go and find a new mama.
A mama that will love me and not abandon me.
I hate April the 12th. Well, actually,
April the 11th.
She didn't tell me it was her birthday.
April the 11th is when I met my mama.
And April the 12th is when my mommy left me.
taking a baby away from it.
And I always sit by that as well. Taking
the baby away from it mama.
Where are these bloody trainers?
Oh gosh darn it. Oh gosh. Gy mama.
Where would you
feel so much better having that on me
You can give baby Peter some milk.
You can give you can give baby some milk. [snorts]
Say what now? [ __ ]
You can't afford training [ __ ]
I know it's true.
We need to get some pictures today
or show his boss.
Is that right?
Show them who's boss. Show them.
That's all I'm going to do.
Show these can't do his boss.
Is that right?
I might even have a burger. The weather spoons.
What happened to Captain? Come on. Is it? Yeah. Captain.
That's his name. Captain Captain.
You captain. You probably wondered what
the [ __ ] happened to the house. Captain
Rushing this is Captain Captain C.
Oh, I'm starved.
What are you going to do for me now?
That was a delicious tea bone and some piggies.
But it doesn't feel quite as much as my mom's babies.
Dude, I need the calcium. If I don't
have the calcium, I'm more groggy. You see?
Can't believe I met my mama 3 years ago in April.
What was the point of you just going to
put me up for adoption?
What was the point of you even getting
with me if you was going to you was just
going to put me up for adoption, you know?
That's very cold.
Is that right? Oh,
[ __ ] hell. Harry Potter.
I'll show you how it's done today. Little Bergen.
I'm in virgin. back.
Sorry about that, dear lad.
Oh, do some washing up
in on these trainers. day.
[clears throat] Mom,
you know your cut and do is done.
Found this silly language that you
speak. Is that cute? English.
I'm going to have to say that he's busy
or something because I I'm going out to
that. I'll just say that he's busy. I'll
just say that he's busy and then call him uh
[ __ ] hell, mate.
The only time you want to go out, you're
not [ __ ] left alone. Yeah. Jesus Christ. What?
This is repeat. Oh, I don't go a lot of
shadow. It's repeaters.
Yeah, Peter is left.
Yeah, isn't it? Yeah.
Let's get these clothes ready
in a bit.
Oh, excited. Boy, am I excited. Cool. [snorts] All >> [snorts] >> right.
Oh my god,
I am [ __ ] lucky, man.
So that [ __ ] gets stuck in your [ __ ] tooth, man. [gasps] That's horrible.
So that was £10. That was [ __ ] that
trans transport for [ __ ] London.
Wasn't that bad then
considering we took two buses.
Trading two buses.
Was it that bad?
Two face is the worst lad.
One second, bro. Let me finish this coke.
I've got a feeling Joseph Ferrar is
going to be joining in a minute. I love Joseph Ferr.
I don't even know where I come from, bro.
And Joseph for real.
Oh, bam, bam, bam, bam, bam. Like in
your [ __ ] foot. [ __ ] off.
That pain is absolutely [ __ ] stinking, son.
Yeah, we took two buses, two trains,
and it was £10.
>> Not bad.
>> Quite cheap to be fair.
Why everybody brush these teeth and [ __ ]
[ __ ] I might have to go to a resting it today. Oh, Joseph Far. Mommy.
Oh, someone must have heard it. Oh gosh. Oh [ __ ]
This is the salt thing. copy.
>> And I said that years ago as well.
Oh, this in box. Salt water.
This [ __ ] toothpick. It's horrible.
I stinky, bro. I stinking [snorts] Mama,
I need to be fed.
You met your mama, mama. Already found where Joseph [snorts]
Oh gosh darn it.
Where are these bloody trainers? I want
to go out and have fun.
I would love to stay today, but
I bet we'd all love to. But sorry, mate.
We got to get approaching.
Need to find my new mommy.
It's not a case of want, necessity.
It's a necessity. Yeah, I need, you
know, the milk for the vitamins and
stuff in the winter, you know.
Why does Timmy keep calling me a virgin
when he is a virgin? Why do these people keep self-projecting? [ __ ] hell.
These people are such projectors.
Jimmy wants the link.
Why does he keep projecting [gasps]
so many projectors on this bloody
community? I'm gone for two weeks after today.
I'm gone for a couple of weeks after
today, bro. Cuz it's the same
atmosphere. I just had my t-bone steak,
Steven Howard. I'm just waiting for my
little trainers now. And I'll be getting
into the shower
and going out there to find a new mama [snorts]
when that can give me milk. Yeah, virgin boy.
>> Oh, you can call me what you want,
Peter. PJ, let's have a serious chat. I
was only bantering about the virgin. You
need to relax on that, you know.
>> No, we can't have serious chat to me.
>> Why? I want to own the manga.
>> Cuz I back you up and you always stab me
in the back.
>> I don't Peter, I'm I mean PJ, I'm
whining you up. Can't you take any
banter, lad? You
>> No, what I'm saying is I I defended you
against that woman.
>> I know. And I'm going to thank you for
that. Can you bear with me at least? >> Okay.
>> Right. Let's talk about the Mongol.
We'll talk about that afterwards. Yeah.
The Mongol is now part of the Bacon
Boys, the Discord [ __ ] nonsies, PJ.
Right now Tramodor can call you a nons
when he said if you watch Rift Batch's
channel before he got shut down that he
said he doesn't care about trolling you
to [ __ ] and a load of kids got [ __ ]
raped. Am I right or [ __ ] wrong?
>> Yeah, you're right. He's a hypocrite.
>> Yes, I will own that fat [ __ ] and I'm
going to smack him to the floor because
there's an award for £500 for his
address, guys. And I will be on the M6
ASP and I will [ __ ] that fat [ __ ] and put his
>> money is a little weasel.
>> Let me own the Mongol. Let me own the
Mongol. Mongol is the gift box, right?
He would think he says he's trying to sh
how he can go to people. I mean, who
would nip someone's [ __ ] feet on [ __ ] YouTube?
>> Well, is it is it true he punched you?
>> Who punched me? Yeah. Now, what happened
was he jud me what and I kicked him in
the stomach and I punched him back. And
the only reason why I didn't see him
hard cuz money might stop me if Mikey
didn't [ __ ] calm me down. He would
have owned I'd have punched him to the
floor, PJ. And I would have put the
camera. There you go, five guys. There
you go. You nonsing
your nons [ __ ] cheese has been
knocked out. And you got Lord Jay,
right? King of Belfast. We'll call him
Skint of Belfast, right? Skint.
>> Yeah, he's [ __ ] skint.
>> Yeah. So, I can show more money right
now than [ __ ] Lord Jay's memberships,
what he gets per month right now, please
ask yourself the question.
>> Yeah. Well, would you rather be on
YouTube and look like a sad bastard and
go with the crowd because you got no
friends in real life. Or would you
rather go out with some people,
socialize and earn £1250 an hour in [ __ ] Tesco's?
>> Yeah. Have a life and earn. Yeah,
exactly. I'm going out later. Me? I'm
just waiting for my trainers to come.
>> Where you going?
>> Just to the pub.
>> Can you own the Mongol in the pub and
go? At least I've got a life. Mongols.
You're on Discord with the bacon boys.
>> I will do. I'll go live later at the pub.
Go live with the pub now. PJ, seriously,
>> you should come to London and meet me.
>> Can you hear me?
>> Timmy, get yourself to London and meet me.
>> Can you hear me, PJ? And I'm going to own PJ,
>> I've got no mercy in me, mate. I've been
too merciful on this website for years.
I will the Mongol because I am going to
organize and meet the Mongol. You said
the Mongol carried it. He was [ __ ]
it on Thursday. I called him out. I was
there and he shat it the long goal and
Jamie [ __ ] Christopher Hughes ain't
about it PJ. [laughter]
>> Yeah, I know. I know.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no. Even me, me and
Mikey were talking last night and we
said there's no mercy on this kid. When
we see him, he is going [ __ ] down hard. >> Yeah.
>> No, no. We're not joking, PJ. I'm being
deadly serious. He is going to get
seriously [ __ ] hurt.
>> He's skinny
skin. He sniffs [ __ ] speed, right?
This is true, PJ. He makes out he's the
man of Birmingham, right? He [ __ ]
doesn't. Right. He was [ __ ] his Oh,
you can't sniff cocaine in the taxi.
He's had a line of coke in the taxi.
>> Timmy, do you remember when you were
shouting? Do you remember when you were
shouting saying, "I'll knock him out."
Do you remember,
>> bro? He was shouting and he was coming
to me because Mikey was too kind in my
opinion, right? And he came over PJ,
>> He came over and he's like, and he's
like Timmy come out like, "Get away from
me, you nons get away from me, you
announce." Honestly, I was like that. I
didn't want to see M. I didn't want
mate. That's why I let Mikey go here. I
can't stand the kid, mate. He may I mean
like Discord and now allowing somebody
in their Discord. He's had a teenage
date and they call me the non. [laughter]
>> Yeah. Yeah. I know.
>> Then you got Lord Jay bigging up the
bacon boys. Yeah. But they've got [ __ ]
in the Discord. I mean I love Prov and
that and I'll say this. I had a chat to
prov you going about [ __ ] Dave, you
know, not David, David UK and that you
got banger [ __ ] kissing them asses PJ
I'm on more top of my game now PJ I
appreciate you have my back right and
I'll talk about in a minute but the one
thing I don't like about you PJ right
you only agreed with that video because
you've been rejected by women don't take personally
>> no Timmy I've been with women
>> so what what PJ it's nothing
>> I agree with it because I hate white
lights that's why I agree with it
>> PJ DJ, right? This
>> you don't even know what that means.
>> Social media like they do it with D.
>> Timmy, I don't like white knights.
>> What the [ __ ] a white knight?
>> People that defend women for the sake of defending women.
>> No PJ, I was in the white. Let me
explain. Right. And that's Steven.
>> Unless they've just beat some random
person up. So if you was in the wrong, I
would have told you you was in the
wrong. If you go out right now to me and
you beat beating up a woman for no
reason, I would say that you're wrong. PJ,
>> that's what I'm saying.
>> You You look at the video. She punched
me. Did I hit her back?
>> Yes. And that's why I said you're not in
the wrong. Yes.
>> Now, the the five guys have done this
because in Discord Bang has done it for
attention because he's a [ __ ]
shitster and he's got no friends, right?
Good vibes. If I saw him in Birmingham
because I know what he looks like, he
would be punched to the floor. Like I
said, I've got no mercy.
>> But how, bro? Bro, how did it start? You
was you was live and she was just
mouthing off. Now, I tell you what
happened was, yeah, I was in the wrong.
I was too loud. Yeah, but if that was
me, I would have went to another
carriage of the train, right? I wouldn't
have caused trouble because me, she did
it because she was bipolar PJ. She She
thinks she's a politician, right? I will
own that one in the House of Parliament.
I will [ __ ] own it, right? >> Yeah.
>> Wait, she's a lefty politician, mate. I
ain't got time for him. She's like a [ __ ] lay.
>> She did. Did you know the mad thing is?
She didn't even seem scared.
>> Yes, because she's bipolar nuts.
>> That's what I'm saying. I know, but
that's what I'm saying. Like, you got
people defending her. Yeah, but she
didn't even seem one bit scared. That's
the maddest thing about it.
>> EJ, she was punching me and I just stood
there and laughed.
>> Where was she from?
>> Um, [ __ ] north. I think she's from
like near Liverpool Street. If you,
>> you know, you know she, you know, the
great guys found out who she was, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Well, sir, what? That just shows
how sad they are sitting.
>> No, no, but how do they do that though?
>> I'll tell you how they do it. Because
they get the photograph, they put it in Google and
>> like reverse image, is it? Reverse image. Yeah.
>> Yes. That's the one. But PJ PJ, right?
I've done nothing wrong, guys. I sat
there and all I said was, "All right,
love. I'll keep the noise down. She
called me sexist. What? I've called
people love." And me and Daff were
talking about this.
>> No, we're not at all, lad.
>> You know, I've called people love, you
know, and that like, well, that's not
being sexist. I called someone love on
the phone yesterday and she goes and I
and I told I was talking to the gas
people cuz I you know pay my gas bill
right and she I was talking about the
video right I even played phone not all
of it but even they said on the phone
just ignore social media geeks in the
real world mate they're [ __ ]
>> but PJ look what's shag you're going to do
>> why you laugh
>> shut up fantasy get off there you're
going to do nothing
blog was calling you all sorts why you defending
No, I'm not defending him. I'm just
saying I don't think he's as wrong as
people saying he is.
>> I'm not defending him, bro. I know he
backstabs people. I know he backstabs
>> He's a fat, right? He turns on
everybody. As soon as someone turns on him, he look
>> Jimmy, do you remember when I used to
back you up with Pat Mustard and you you
didn't defend me, bro? I I don't def I'm
not defending. I just don't like white knights. Fantasy and fire.
Bad boy. You got bad boy.
>> I'm going out as soon as these trainers
come. Kier fantasy spend all day on you.
You haven't done nothing going to the police. She's
>> charges to go to the police. I dare you
to go to the police fantasy cuz I'll take
the police. She's pressing charges to
him. It's been confirmed.
>> Okay, I'm going to kick both of these
out now. Yeah, let me explain it cuz you
asked me a question, right? Cuz they
don't let me talk and I got too fake.
Right. Listen, I have been with women.
I've got no reason to be biased. Yeah.
If he if he went out and he just
attacked a woman for no reason or he
started on a woman for no reason, I
would say that he's in the wrong. I just
don't like white knights, bro. I've been
with women. I've had sex. I've got no
reason to be [ __ ] biased. I'm not a
[ __ ] virgin. But I'm saying he's not
as wrong as people are making him out to
be. That's what I'm saying,
you know. And I've had more women in
these white nights, bro. So why why
would I need to [ __ ] And she didn't
even look scared. She didn't look
scared. He didn't hit her. I mean, [ __ ] hell.
I don't know why people are defending
her to be fair. I'm not backing Timmy up
though cuz he's a snake. But what a
nasty [ __ ] tooth fake, bro.
But [snorts] you got me.
They're weirdos, man.
>> Right. Run. Okay, I'm going to let Timmy
in and not fantasy cuz you keep talking
over each other.
>> Fantasy is a bottle job and fantasy she
can go to the police cuz I can press
charge on her for hitting me. So it
works both ways. Fantasy. Fantasy. I
told her on the train because the police
was involved. I said I'm taking her to
court and I am going to get a solicitor
and take her to court because at the end
of the day she could have moved
carriages. Fantasy. What's she going to
do at the police station go oh I
intimidated her, right? The the police
will look at the video because you know
they've already knew about it right.
They'll say hang on is willing to
cooperate to be quiet. She won't have a
leg to [ __ ] stand on fantasy. See
fantasy. You make out you're a gangster.
PJ, don't say I stab back you. Stop
defending that little [ __ ] nonsome
islands. You know what it is with
fantasy? He doesn't like it because I
own the crap out of him every time and every day. >> Yeah.
>> What's Fantasy going to do? Phone the
police. That's all he can do. What's V
going to do? Phone the police. What's
Pat Muster going to do? Phone the
police. What's Discord going to do?
Phone the police. Even though we could
go to the police on Discord. They'd been
more [ __ ] than anyone. Right. We got
Jaden's address so that we can link that
Discord to be shut down. That's how
[ __ ] stupid Discord is,
>> right? So, at the end of the [ __ ]
day, right, she went to the police. She
won't have a leg to stand on. She ain't
going to press no charges. The one who
can press charges me because I'm the one
who got hits. >> Yeah.
>> No, that's true. Fantasy.
>> No, I know. I know. I know.
>> Fantasy doesn't even let go of the
police, PJ. Because I tell you one
thing, I've still got the bruise on my
chin. She will get [ __ ] prosecuted.
>> So, what about when I was arguing with
that one in the park to me?
>> But PJ, that was different. Can I
explain? Right, PJ?
>> Yeah, you can.
>> I'm not backstabbing you. Look, let's
have a man-to-man talk. Right. Don't say
I'm backstabbing you because you know
me, PJ, I'm a I'm a right-wing. I'm a
man's man and I say it how it is. So,
don't take it to heart what I'm saying.
Right. You was in the wrong PJ. I'll
explain why you cuz she was just minding
her own business having a drink and you
started attacking her right now. If if
she came to you and called you sexist
like with me for example and she
>> I was with her for like an hour.
>> Yeah, but PJ you but you can't just go
and yell at her cuz you was with her for
an hour like PJ I if I'm if you're
serious right and you're willing to
change listen to me right I will meet
you in Birmingham and I will teach you
how to pull women. Me and Mikey last
night had [ __ ] all over. Oh, dear me.
Timmy, come on now.
>> PJ, just own it that you need my guidance.
>> Timmy, stop. You need to grow up, man. Seriously.
>> How do I need to grow up?
>> You need to grow up, Timmy.
>> How do I need to grow up, lad?
>> Oh, I can't be bothered arguing with you, man.
>> No, I'm not arguing. I'm trying to have
a reasonable conversation. Do you want
to get laid next weekend, PJ? Yes or no?
>> No. I'm a virgin.
>> No, no, PJ. I'm being serious. I will
take that. I'm being serious, bro. Well,
come to London today, though. I'm going out later.
>> I can't do London today, mate. I'm too I
haven't got [ __ ] enough money for
London. I spent [ __ ] 100 quid last
night, you know. I was lucky. I actually
won 130 quid last night. I come home 30
quid in price.
>> Just jump on the train.
>> What do you mean skip the train? Yeah,
but I've got to jump over the [ __ ] barriers.
>> How How much money do you have now? >> £3156 Sterling Pence.
>> Until when?
>> Until Friday.
>> Yeah. So you can come though.
>> Yeah, I know that. But I've got to get
my keys as well. So that's going to cost
me 58 quid and it's like fucking10 a
point in London.
>> It's like8 pound. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Maybe next weekend, PJ. And I will
show you how it's done. I like the way
you move PJ. I honestly I will get you a bird.
>> No, I have to kick you to me, man.
You're giving me a headache.
You're giving me a headache. You get I
got tooth fake as it is, bro. And
[ __ ] this guy is is mad.
So why is people defending that woman on
the train anyways?
Why is people defending that woman on the train? Kieran,
I'll be going out approaching today.
Kieran, if you want to join, like I
said, I'm just waiting for these
trainers to come
and I'm going, bro.
Yep. It's true though, is it Kieran? Hey
Kieran, it's true, isn't it? Hey bro, it's weird.
It's weird, is it Kieran? I've shown
people women leading me on everything
and they won't have it. They nod their
head. Even if you show them black and
white evidence, they still deny it. Bro, they're pathetic.
These white knights are pathetic, lad.
These white knights, they they sit and
defend women. It's pathetic, lad.
Even when they do wrong, they still make
excuses for them. It's madness. [snorts]
[ __ ] them, bro.
I'm surprised you didn't call him a stalker, Grezy.
That's a narcissist's favorite word, isn't it?
Kieran, I'm missing USA's boobs. Kieran,
I need to go out today and find a new mama.
I need to go out and find a new mommy.
One that can give me milk.
Okay. I'm going to find a new mommy today. [sighs] [groaning]
Yeah, exactly like that. Ricky
Billington, he's probably still a virgin.
He's probably still a virgin. Yeah, I
know, Kieran. I just thought that they
were genuine, lad. Well, to be fair,
some people did believe it. Like that tiger tiger,
which is not Tiger that you know, he
actually said, "Oh, like they're in
wrong and that
like some people did say
the thing is, yeah, Kieran, most I would
say a lot of these people in here are virgins.
The two guaranteed ones are
Non Legs and Timmy.
They're guaranteed virgins. Yeah, [snorts]
them two are guaranteed virgins, but
like obviously there there are other
virgins on here.
That red star is definitely a virgin.
There's a few virgins on here, bro.
And I think that's why they defend women
Kieran because they think by defending
them it's going to get them women.
Nah, he doesn't even humper, bro. He
can't even get it in.
No, he can't even get in, lad.
Waiting for these 20 pound trainers to
come. Have a shower and [ __ ] off. I got
a football bet for today, Kieran.
I'm so [ __ ] I think it's just too
fake. It's made me feel [ __ ] bro. [sighs]
Yes, I have. And we're not getting into
this projecting conversation,
this self projecting combo. So yeah.
Yes. To answer your question. Yes, I have.
Yeah. The last win I had was 50 to 150.
Right. Blocks. Bye-bye. See you.
Yeah, I spent I got these 200 pound
trainers coming to K and I thought [ __ ]
it and just buy a minute. Got to go to
the pub later.
Bam. [ __ ] tooth fake is [ __ ] stinking, bro. So bad.
I just had a steak Ken.
I need just chill on like that. I wanted
to go b I wanted to get a burger from the pub,
but I can't obviously cuz I have to get
something more soft. Yep.
I've showed me kissing women, me in
hotel with women's, my dick in a woman's
mouth, and they still call me a virgin.
Like I said, Kieran, they're talking
about themselves. Look at that video I
done yet. Do you remember that live the
other day, bro? when I was saying about how
um I can't uh should I buy the trainers?
Should I not buy the trainers? Right.
Uh should I buy a trainer? Should I not
buy the trainers?
Um and then you like, "Oh, you should
put on red or black." It's not cuz I
couldn't afford it, bro. I was just
thinking, "Should I or not?" And then
this little [ __ ] was trying to say, "Oh,
I'm skinn. I can't afford it." I was
like, "Fuck it. I'll just order them now
then." Not that I need to prove
anything, but I just thought [ __ ] it in
it. Kill two birds with one stone.
These people, Kieran, they they think
everyone's got their life. That's the
problem with these people on here.
They seem to think everyone's got the
same life as them. That's their problem.
down to £300.
What you How though did you gamble or something?
I'll probably be spending £300 today to
be honest. Nah, probably £300 over the weekend maybe.
Oh, well, you lost £300.
I spent [ __ ] over £400 on two items.
[sighs and snorts]
Ah, my mouth is killing me, bro.
Yeah, I like that global draw roulette.
I was thinking of sticking 100 on it. I
got this football rep, bro. Uh, treble
both score, no draw.
I might watch the football and then go out.
Watch the football and then go out.
I'm going to have to stick to Guinness
today, but I can't have rum with these
gums. This gum at the back is killing
me, bro. I can only have Guinness. So,
should I take you meeting that [ __ ] in Devon then?
I have had Coco, bro. I've been taking it.
I I've been taking it, bro.
I've already took four today, but I just
had steak. I had a nice steak, didn't I?
So, it triggered it again. I had a T-bone steak.
So, I'll take some more in a bit. And if
I eat later, it's going to have to be something soft.
No lamb, no pork, no because it's just
going to trigger it again. Yeah, I have
cucakota, bro. I took it. >> [sighs]
>> You know, in April it will be 3 years
since I met my mama Kieran.
Three years since I met USA Izzy.
Oh, I need to meet a new woman with nice
boobies today. Keep me warm in the winter, you know.
You should, you know what you should
have done, bro? When you get your money,
if you've got like5600 left, you should gamble
and try and win like 500 to like a
couple of grand. Then you'll be good for
a couple of months, isn't it?
You'll be good for a couple of months.
Yeah, she was a proper narcissist.
She had lovely boobies though, Kieran.
They were very tasty. Very
Yeah. I wish I didn't meet her. [snorts] Yep.
Yeah. She's a 19year-old. Her boobs
wasn't big enough.
You should have saw the 19year-old
Grezy. My dick barely fitted in her
mouth. It fitted but almost just about. Bro,
my dick was so big, bro. It is so big.
She You couldn't even like Yeah, she was
kind of struggling. [gasps]
That's how big it was. She used to come
around and suck my willie. But the
reason I wasn't happy with her, Grezy,
is because obviously she didn't have enough milk.
Yeah, she didn't have enough milk. So
[snorts] I need to be fed we
so that's why
I need I need to be fed you see otherwise Yeah.
Yeah. Left scared for life.
What makes me laugh, Greavves, is
they'll get anyone, everyone to fight
their battles but themselves. Like that
South American ignoring [ __ ] putting me
all over a story knowing damn well that
somebody [snorts] was going to message
me yet they've blocked me. The irony, huh? Yeah,
but they do different things, Greavesy.
They can either get other people to
fight their battles or they get the
police involved or report you to
Instagram. There's different ways they do it.
The police never ever got back in touch
with me for that
[snorts] in involuntary interview. The
police was supposed to invite me for an
interview, Greavvesy, cuz of some woman
on Instagram, but they never ever they
never ever did
uh contact me or anything. Again, that
would have been me giving a woman [ __ ]
that's gave me [ __ ] and then they wanted old bill.
[snorts] Women are put on this earth to
satisfy my needs. Isn't it grievy? Yep. [snorts]
Did [snorts] I do you know my my my
nephew dressed up as Stitch yesterday? Greavvesy.
So, what are you going to do about money then, Kieran?
I think me and you get the same amount
of money now. Yeah,
we get the same amount of money.
Obviously, I've got a bit more money cuz
when I won, I just put it away and stuff
so I knew what I was doing.
But there's a reason why I don't gamble.
as much. I mean, when I mean gamble, I mean like
it'll get to a point where one day it
will, but it do you know what it is? It's like
life is stressful enough to think about [ __ ] women.
So, I don't want to um have to stress
about money as well. Do you understand?
I don't want to think about money and
like I'd rather not have that when I
have to already worry about women. You
see what I mean?
That's the problem.
But if I was down to my last £500 or
something, I probably would gamble to be fair.
I'll probably go big on roulette.
Yeah. Is what it is, isn't it?
Why don't you do the delivery job, Kieran?
You get extra money doing the delivery job.
See, no one helps me. My mom don't help
I just I'm just by myself basically,
bro. I have enough. So I Yeah.
But that global draw roulette seems
good, ain't it, Kieran?
Yeah, but you have 300 now, is it?
Yeah. You get £,100 a month in it like me.
You get £1,100 a month like me, don't you?
Bro, this this toothache is stinking, bro.
Like I said, I need to stick to Guinness
today. I can't drink rum.
That is stinking. Oh my god.
It's like that foot injury I had,
Kieran. You wouldn't have been able to
last with that foot injury.
That was mad. Mad, bro. Yep.
Bless you then if you got £300.
Okay. And pressure.
Hurry up trainers. Man,
I'm going to have a get these trainers,
go for snooze, watch the football, and
go out. I'm definitely going out. Don't
worry. I'm definitely going out, lad.
It's definitely happening, bro. Don't
worry about that. [snorts]
Even if I have to die of a toothache,
I'm still going out.
We didn't buy these clothes for nothing,
did we, Kieran? Yep. 300.
You got £300 to your name, Kieran.
It's not that bad though, is it?
Yeah, it's gave me a disgusting
toothache as well.
You should meet up with me today, Kier,
and we'll [snorts] go for a drink. Yeah.
See these people when I used to sublet
here and I used to have my money in my
other account so they could never prove
it. I wasn't stupid, bro.
I had a different account.
So when they got on to me, I remember
when they got on to me, they was like,
"Well, we need bank statements." I said,
"Okay, I can give you bank statements.
I knew what I was doing, bro. These
little grasses on this community, I only
knew what I was doing. That's why it never worked
cuz I had a different bank account that
they didn't know about.
They did try, bro, many times. It never worked. [snorts]
these little mongos on here. [snorts] Yeah.
Yeah. Three years, bro.
Traveling up and down the country
designing the clothes. But I still have
I still buy stuff now even without subleting, bro.
No, it wasn't [ __ ] bro. I was
getting like three grand a month.
I was getting like 3k a month, bro, for
like 3 years.
No, I'm not [ __ ] at all, lad.
Oh man, that's painful.
Yeah, it's not so much the money. I've
got money. I missed the place, the area,
and the food that was cooked. Obviously,
the money was nice as well, but it's not
just the money, bro.
I missed the house, the room. Yeah, obviously, bro.
got this nice football bet today. I
think it's going to come in me.
Treble both score no draw. I think it's
got a good chance.
Stop. This tooth fake is killing me, bro.
virgin boy skinted in a skint flint Kieran
Kieran these people I know what you mean
sometimes you got to come off here for
like a week or two is it cuz it's the
same atmosphere isn't
I I I see why you come off sometimes, bro.
Same atmosphere in it. Yeah.
[snorts] Yeah. It's the same atmosphere, isn't it?
Same projecting people in it. Yeah.
Don't call me Peter. You creep.
Yeah. Yeah, if you go on Lord Jay's K
and it's the same people, same
atmosphere in it. Is that why you don't
go there anymore?
I can't be bothered with it.
Do you know what's so weird is Timmy and
uh Monty met and they're still arguing.
They're still arguing even though they
met and they're still having the same argument.
So they've met, but they're still having
the same argument. It's madness, bro. I
don't even find that funny, bro. I think
it's [ __ ] mad. I think it's pathetic.
because they've met, right? So, two
people are arguing.
So, then they meet to fight or whatever,
but then they meet up and now they're
having the same argument again.
What the [ __ ] bro? Gives me a headache.
Yeah, that guy is a troll. That Hugh
guy, bro. He's two-faced.
He was all right on mine. Then I caught
him talking [ __ ] behind my back. How
it's like that that Ricky Millan to the
camp. They all do it, bro. They talk
normal to you and then they slag you off
behind your back.
Go away. Too fate. Go away. Go away. Go
He's a [ __ ] Whoever it is. Yeah.
Yeah. Lewis seems like southeast.
I think it's kind of going out the two
fake a little bit.
It needs to just [ __ ] off, bro. It's
hurting. Cuz [sighs and gasps]
you can only take the cocon every four hours.
I took him about half hour ago.
So you lost £300 in the bookies.
That foot thing was the worst, bro.
When I had that foot thing, that was the
worst. Woke me up and everything. Yeah.
No, I muted it. I muted it. No, it
should be coming. It's got another hour
and a half to come. Yeah.
Okay. And I'm going to be approaching
the fresh jeans and fresh trainers
today. Hopefully I don't get the I've
got a boyfriend [ __ ] in it.
You will. It's to be expected, isn't it, Kieran? [snorts]
It's to be expected, lad.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> It's going to be depressing, bro. It's
not going to be depressing cuz that's
that's what's happening.
That's going to be depressing, bro. Last
time I went out, I spent £500.
I spent £500 and I got two numbers. I
got 10 numbers and no date. It's going
to be very hard to depress me now after that, bro.
I'm not there's not I'm not going to get
no action, bro. It's got to be the same
as always. But it's better than nothing, is it? [snorts]
I spent £500 last time I went out. 10
numbers, not a date. So,
it's going to be the same this time as well.
What do you think about that, K? And 10
numbers on not a date.
Crazy, isn't it?
We'll see what happens today. Anyways,
I think last time went out was Friday,
was it? This time it's a Saturday.
I message him on my WhatsApp number. Yeah,
My WhatsApp number is different to my real number
and they don't know my name either.
>> [sighs and snorts]
>> I can't get a match on these dating
apps. Ken, I don't know how people say they work. Madness.
Bro, we know they're lying.
That's already been established that
they're chat and [ __ ] you know.
We know they're lying. We know they talk [ __ ]
hold this guy.
I can't remember that. There's been a
lot of [ __ ] I've dealt with
over the years. So, um,
who knows, mate. Who knows? Polish guy.
No, I don't know, bro.
[ __ ] knows. [ __ ] knows
that Ricky Millington's a white knight.
First he says that I'm good-looking.
Then these women are picky. Then he then
he tries saying that I'm the problem.
And then you're thinking, make up your
mind. Which one is it? Are they picky or
am I the problem? Jesus Christ.
There's no point getting into any kind
of debate or any kind of argument
with these white knights. Do you know
what I mean, Kieran? There's like no point
getting into any of it with these white knights.
Yeah. Which one is it? Is it me or the
women? And he's trying to blame me
loving their messages when they were
loving my messages. They're white
knights that you can't get through.
You You can't get through to these
virgins, bro. Just let them do what they
doing it, lad.
Which one is it? Is it Is it the women
or is it me? You need to make up your
mind, lad. Cuz what changed in two
months? Sorry. What changed in two years?
Cuz society's only gotten worse.
He's a [ __ ] Absolute [ __ ]
Then he goes on the Virgin's channel
trying to say about I'm jealous that
he's got money. I've got more money than
him. I've got more life experiences than
him. I've been to more places. I went on
holiday before him. Why would somebody
be jealous of someone copying someone's holidays
that has a disabled girlfriend? Strange.
Why would somebody be jealous of a skint
person that's got no life experiences?
Do you still watch the side men? Karen,
no. He never used to go in on him though.
But why would somebody be jealous of
that skinned virgin who has to copy
people's holidays? He doesn't even have money.
I don't know why he's writing stupid
stuff like that.
I've already been on holidays more times
than he would ever be on holiday.
And I've got more money than him as well.
So try again. [sighs and gasps]
These people are weird on AK. Very very weird.
very very weird.
Literally, he's a copycat.
Just like the Cheryl Cole thing. If you
don't find Cheryl Cole attractive, you're gay.
It's copying. Copycat. Little copycat.
Little copycat. Are you little copycat?
Little copycat. No mind of your own.
talking about my [ __ ] nose with your
[ __ ] ugly rat face. You [ __ ] ugly
virgin trying to talk about me. You
[ __ ] mad son. [ __ ] off, man.
[ __ ] [snorts] hell, man.
He's a little copycat.
That's what he is. He's a little copycat.
Yeah, but he he calls people gay. If you
say that, he call he will call you gay.
That's what I'm saying. He's a copycat.
[snorts] Yeah, but that's what I'm
saying. He's a little copycat. He's a
Cuz other people used to say that to each other.
Yeah, he's he's definitely copying a little copycat.
You little copycat. [snorts] Oh, yeah.
You little copycat. No mind of your own.
God bless you.
No mind of your own.
You like it when I say that ain't it, Kieran? [snorts]
Yeah. You like that, don't you, son?
Oh, I like Alicia from Riverdale, bro. I
think she's sexy. Me.
She's not ugly at all. She's got big tits, too.
Better than Shevel Carl as well.
He only said Shevil Car Cole cuz he's He
only said that to fit in. That was on
the That was on the in between us once as well.
I know. I know.
Have you noticed he's very insecure as well, Kieran?
[snorts] He's very, very insecure.
Have you noticed that? Yeah.
I've [snorts] got everything anyways. K.
It doesn't matter.
I've got One second. Let me show you
if I can.
I got my whole folder, bro. One second.
I'll show you.
There you go.
I got a whole harassment folder of what
the cunt's done. So he can delete all he wants. [snorts]
So look at this all night mic as well.
Go away m it's just the same people.
That's what I'm saying bro. It's the same [ __ ]
Go away. It's just the same repeating people
[sighs] in it Kieran.
It's the same repeating people in it. [gasps]
[sighs and snorts]
Yeah. Have you show Yep. I sent it all
to them. Yep. I had to show them it.
Yeah. I had to send it to them. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, I did, lad. I sent him
everything. [sighs and gasps] Everything. [snorts]
Absolutely everything, bro.
My mouth is killing me, bro. I need to
take some more code in a bit. >> [snorts] >> Yeah. Yep.
So, how long is that 300 got to last you, Kieran?
>> How long has that got to last you? that £300. [snorts]
Oh, that's so loud. No, I'm still going out.
Today is not cancelled at all, lad.
No, I'm still going out, did
going to get changed in a minute, I think.
No, not at all, bro. [snorts]
Not at all. At all,
bro. They're so loud downstairs, bro.
They need to shift, bro. What the [ __ ]
How long is that going to last you anyways, G?
Well, I'm going to get these clothes
ready anyways. Oh, [gasps]
right. I don't know whether to wear this,
this, this, this. I reckon I'm going to
wear this blue one, I reckon.
I'm going to wear this, I think,
with the jeans, the trainers.
[snorts] Oh, one sec, brother.
This one again, I think [snorts] jeans.
Look at that, mate.
I was just waiting for the trainers.
100% maybe [ __ ] mad. [snorts] Um,
I'm definitely going out, bro. Oh [ __ ]
I need a top to wear under the thing, don't I?
All Saints top under it. I like All Saints. Yeah. Um um
I can talk about these health boxes now.
I've not worn him before.
There we go.
He's uh he doesn't live here, bro. He's
not my dog.
He's my sister's dog.
Yeah, he's my sister's dog, bro.
Do you like that little gear I'm wearing today, Kieran? wearing? Huh? >> [snorts]
>> I've even got chucky boxes. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, lad. [snorts]
Yes, that's where King is.
Yeah, I saw the neighbor yesterday. You
said hi to my mom.
He [laughter and snorts] said hi. He
said hi to my mom, bro.
So, how long is that £300 going to last
you? A month.
[ __ ] hell, man.
Definitely going out.
We just lie these boxes. Yeah. [snorts] Yeah,
I'm a crazy controller.
It's coming soon. I reckon.
Yeah, but what if you spend it all?
You'd become skimp caring. Mhm.
Yeah, but you might spend might spend it
all and become skinned. [snorts]
Then you'll be like the skin virgin in the bedet.
Then you'd be fat. Yeah, man. [snorts]
Then what happens if you're like that
skin [ __ ] in the bed suit?
Yeah, but you might Yeah, but you might
lose it and end up skin
that [ __ ] in the bed sit
with no bed, no money in it.
Will you be [ __ ] then, lad?
You might be skinned virgin.
That skin bastard. [snorts] Huh?
Oh man, what a [ __ ] ass did you hate.
Women don't come.
Money comes and go, but women don't come and go.
Women definitely don't come and go. Not
in my case. I've not had a date since April, lad.
these days. Not for me anyways. Maybe for you.
Money comes and goes, but women don't.
Women don't come in the first place.
[sighs and gasps]
Yeah, you should go to bingo,
make some friends or something.
No, I would have laughed.
You say they come and go, but I've not
had a date since April. Kieran, I don't
think they they they come in the first
place. Dad, [ __ ] hell. [ __ ]
I really want a tea, but I can't.
[sighs and gasps]
>> Could have a team without sugar. Yeah, but [snorts]
>> we're going regardless.
[sighs and gasps]
Do you like my jeans, Karen? >> [snorts]
>> [ __ ] mouth, bro.
I don't know how you can say women come
and go, though, lad.
I don't know how you can [ __ ] say that.
They got bloody boyfriends caring. Bloody German. Bloody.
My favorite word is bloody.
So, it's got like an hour to come.
Well, they can't put their boyfriend on
the phone cuz their boyfriend don't
exist. Hey, Notorious. You all right,
boss? Just waiting for my new trainers
to come [gasps]
and then I'll be having a shower. I'll
be watching the football and then after
the football's finished, I'll go out
and send it. Yeah,
your boyfriends don't exist, Kieran.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> So they can't put their boyfriends on
the phone with dad from Derry.
See, look. They're all simps.
See, they're all simps, lad. They're all
[ __ ] simps. Look at this.
Slug delete YouTube. You absolute clown
of a man. No one here likes you anymore.
Not one person [ __ ] Why do you even
make content? You are a woman abuse.
This is what I mean, bro. I can't deal
with a white knight and [ __ ] Mad,
you should meet me today. Kieran,
would you wear what I wear, Kieran? Nice
Stone Island, black jeans, black
trainers. You'd wear that, wouldn't you?
You wouldn't wear that [ __ ] them
virgin clothes, would you?
Yeah, to be honest, [sighs]
I can't meet anyone, Kieran. They've all
got bloody boyfriends.
They've all got bloody boyfriends.
Kieran um Notorious.
People on Reddit say go on the apps, but
the bloody apps don't work. [sighs]
Can you help me meet someone? Every time
I go out and approach, they've all got bloody boyfriends.
They've all got bloody boyfriends. Gen
sick of it. All got bloody boyfriends. >> [sighs]
>> Do you like my Stone Island jumpers, Kieran?
This is what I'm wearing. That over
there. Black jeans, blue jumper.
It's going [snorts] to be sick.
These trainers should be here any minute.
[sighs and gasps]
How do you meet someone uh Notorious?
Because all they say is that they've got bloody boyfriends.
So, how do you meet them, Notorious?
No, but I can't I've never met anyone
through friends, Victoria. They're all
out for their bloody selves.
My friends never introduced me to anyone
ever. They're all out for their bloody selves.
I've never ever met anyone through
friends, bro. And I've got loads of
friends. I used to go to them all the
time. I never met anyone.
So, if I didn't approach Kieran, would I
be a virgin if I didn't approach?
Do you reckon?
Do you reckon I would be a virgin if I didn't approach?
Sorry. Do you reckon I'd be a virgin if
I didn't approach?
I think so. Is it? Well, except from escorts, obviously. Mad.
Yeah, exactly. That's what I'm saying.
Everyone's out for themselves.
But when you tell people that, K, and
they say, "Oh, you're negative and
you've got the wrong friends." And so
there's no point even getting into it,
there's no point getting into the debate
because then they're just going to sit
there and say, "Oh, you're negative and
you got bad friends." And so
[clears throat] it's no point in it. Yeah.
It's a doggy dog world. Everyone's out for themselves.
But if you say that and you say the
truth, they say that you're negative.
I've never met anyone through friends ever. [gasps]
No, it's not just about No, it's not
only just community. It's even like
Reddit. Even on Reddit, they say like go
on dating apps and stuff.
They say go on dating apps and whatever.
It's not only just community. It's Reddit.
It's women. I had a woman say to me she
wouldn't get with me cuz I'm 28. And I
found out she had been with a
28-year-old before. So why would she lie
when there's nothing wrong with the way
that I look?
It's constant [ __ ] bro. with them constantly.
There's this Muslim.
I had a Muslim say she wouldn't get with
me because I'm mus I'm not Muslim
cuz I'm not Muslim.
And then I said okay well convert to
Muslim. And then she said no she's not
looking for anyone.
Constant [ __ ] bro excuses with them.
Obviously I don't mind today is a one
off in it.
But they're just full of excuses constantly.
But do you know what makes me laugh,
Kieran, is when they try to say that
it's not about looks.
They say with women it's not about
anything physical. When if you're not
their physical type, they won't even
give you the chance to begin with.
That's what makes me laugh at it.
Anyways, [ __ ] it. I can't be bothered
talking about it, bro. We're going out
later anyways. So,
you know how it is.
No, I can never quit piggies. Never.
Nope. I can't do that, Kieran, because
their excuse is that I'm too young for them.
So, they're always going to use that as an excuse.
And she was 50, not 60. But yeah, no,
because then they're going to say that
you're too young for them.
So, that's not going to work either.
Don't worry, bro. We'll be out later.
[sighs and gasps]
Well, he moved to Thailand, didn't he? So,
[snorts] I don't think they ever had
sex, though. They never had sex. She was
just somebody that he used to see that
used to help him out, but they never had sex. No.
Brainers will be here soon.
What's the worst you've ever had?
What's the worst ache you've ever had? >> Ache.
>> I don't know. I got [snorts]
>> Yeah, he he's done it before, bro. I
said there was no me and you. I said
there is no me and you. When you're
talking your [ __ ] it's you. There's no
me and you. Yeah,
I've told him a few times there's no me and you
with these women you can see the
westernity in their eyes is it Kieran?
You can see the westernity in their
eyes. Do you remember that one Greavesy?
The western. You can see the westernity
in their eyes. They give you that dirty
western eyes. Stare at it, Kieran.
That dirty westernized look they give you. They're NPCs.
They're all NPCs. Too much watching Tik
Tok in it, Kieran, because they all
watch the same uh Twitter.
And yeah, you could see it in her eyes.
Yeah. You can see the Westinity in her eyes. Yeah.
like Ken, you know when Antman said
they're just not interested in this
country. Do you think he's right?
Do you think he was right when he said that?
Oh, that one. The one from Liverpool.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Do you think he's right about that,
Kieran? That they're not interested in this country.
Do you reckon that Ricky Millington's a
real person or do you think it's like a robot?
I need to find somebody to latch on to.
Is it Greasy? Latch on to some new boobies.
Yeah, I didn't even see that, bro.
I heard about it. I need to find some
new it to latch on to >> [snorts]
>> Have you seen that channel, Kieran? The great guys.
No, they didn't. No, no, no. I don't No.
Do you know? Let me tell you what happened. Yeah.
I started being racist online years ago.
like back in 2011 and I called them all
packies in school and that ain't it? I
said, "Oh, you all packies." No, no, no,
no, no, no, no. And then they all tried
to jump me, but they didn't run me out
of the school, bro. They didn't run me
out of school. I left like 6 months
after that cuz I wanted to change school.
Yeah, they're weak, bro. All they can do
is try to jump people.
No, they tried to jump me cuz I call
them all Pakis and [ __ ] in it.
They didn't rob me out of no school,
bro. I still been there for like 6
months after that. Are you mad?
They're [snorts] weak, bro.
They only jump. They can only jump people.
I've had I had a lot of fights in
school, bro. I got [ __ ] up once. I
don't know if you know a place called uh
Leighton Kieran. Yeah, there's a place
called Leighton. Basically, I used to go
uh to the gym and used to go swimming
and I used to run my mouth a lot online.
Yeah. And then this guy come I was
calling him a [ __ ] outside the Chesters.
Um I was calling him I was running my
mouth up to him on Facebook. He come
with his friend in it. Yeah. They jumped
me like, but they were weak though cuz I
didn't have a bruise. But I didn't do
nothing. They jumped me, bro. I got
[ __ ] up, bro. And then I messaged my
friend to come help me. My friend come
and they ran away. My friend come and
they ran away, bro.
So like I used to have like people that
back me up and [ __ ] There was two of
them. Funny enough, I was with my
friend, but he didn't do anything. So do
you remember them BBM days? Do you
remember the BBM days back in 2011?
Then I um called my friend to come
and uh he didn't uh I called my friend
to come and then they ran away.
Madness. I used to get in a lot of [ __ ]
bro. But I always I I beat people up as
well before, bro.
I beat people up before as well.
There was this one guy before, lad.
Uh, I punched him in his face. He went
flying, bro. He had like a black eye.
His his whole eye was [ __ ] I swear to
God, bro. And there was one time before
this guy was talking [ __ ] about me. We
used to, you know, he was he was talking
[ __ ] and we used to share a locker. We
used to share like a swimming locker.
And whatever happened, we we got into an
argument in it.
And then I went back to the locker. I
threw all of his [ __ ] in the bush, buff.
He had to call his dad to collect him.
Yeah, he called his dad to collect him.
I remember that, bro.
You know, if Bro
I didn't see him. I heard about it, bro.
Like, if I found out who it was, I'd
meet him right now.
Do do you remember his name
or anything? Cuz I'll meet him right
now, bro. I don't give a [ __ ]
And I call him a py to his face as well.
I'd call him a py to his face.
I call him a little piggy lover. That's
what I'd call him, bro. The guy chat
[ __ ] I heard about it, but I didn't see it.
Maybe. Maybe it was the twins. There's
only two black guys I know. Yeah, there
was there was black twins, but they were Muslims.
If you tell me his name, I'll know who it is.
And I'll call him a little piggy lover.
Yeah. [sighs and gasps] Anyways,
do you like my little outfit for today, Kieran?
I done my bets on Tuesday, lad. I'm just
waiting for the trainers now.
I'm just waiting for the brand new
trainers to come. They should be here any minute.
I got a nice I I don't I don't my bets
on Tuesday. I don't know why, but I done
them on Tuesday.
Treble both score, no draw.
20 to 237. So, it's a good return. 237 pound.
That's definitely coming in, bro.
Yeah, I'll be out soon after the football.
I've got a nasty toothachake, lad.
Oh, it's just evidence I've got against Virgin Boy
that I had to show to um my solicitor and that.
Just waiting for the trainers now. Got
the clubber there. Stony jeans. I'm just
waiting for the trainers. [sighs]
Take some more meds, have a shower,
watch the football, and then go out. Yeah.
What a life.
I shouldn't have to be doing this again,
but sure. Just a bit of fun, eh? Yeah.
I got a heartbeat on my in my [ __ ]
gum, bro. It's nasty nasty pain. Yeah. [snorts]
It's horrible. It was fine, but I I had
my steak, didn't I? I cooked my steak
and then it triggered it again
cuz obviously steak is chewy. Yeah. [snorts]
No, I got the I got the clubber ready.
Nice Ammani jeans. Brand new Stony. I'm
going to wear the same Stony cuz I like
that Stony. Just waiting for the trailers now.
should be here any minute.
Any minute, Dad.
Going to have to stick to the Guinness today, though.
Yeah, we'll have to stick to the Guinness
cuz the ROM will [ __ ] up. [ __ ] our gums
One second. I think I got some Yeah. Oh.
Oh, that virgin boy. [laughter] Oh man,
the toothp is stinking.
Toothpac is [ __ ] stinking, son.
Where the [ __ ] are these [ __ ]
the horn trainers.
We're getting on it today, mate. >> [snorts]
>> Where the [ __ ] are these [ __ ]
They were supposed to [ __ ] be here
[ __ ] a couple of hours ago. Yeah,
it's that lamb. I think it's a lamb that
I had. It
Yeah, it's a lamb that I had, lad.
It [ __ ] me, didn't it?
It's a lamb that I had, bro.
It got stuck in the gums.
Should be all right. It should be all right, though.
Should be all right, you guys.
for today. Like I said, I'm sticking to
the Guinness. So Oh boy.
What do you think of it, Pokémon?
We're getting on it today, lads.
Oh, here they are. Oh, just open the door.
>> No, not here.
It must be coming by truck.
No, it's not here. One second. Something
just come. It must be coming by a
[ __ ] trans fan or something.
But it's not here.
>> Look, this has come by post. Will the
trailer still come? >> Yeah,
>> they're coming by. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. It's like watching draw. Just
different people being a just Yeah. Just Yeah.
Yeah. It's like watching Jaw. It's like,
you know, Drop Jaw, but it's like
different people being in it.
Just [snorts] different people being ate. Nah,
no, you're just being negative.
Reddit tells me I'll meet someone. I'm
going to listen to Reddit, not you.
Hope this gum gets better, bro.
Yeah, it should do. Bro,
like I said, it's cuz I ate the steak.
It triggered it. Is it?
No, I should be all right today, bro.
I think I'll meet someone today.
You just got to put yourself out there.
That's all, lad.
I'd love to stay in today. I would love
to stay in, but sorry, mate.
I said I'm uh I'm doing this. So
So why does Reddit people on Reddit say
I'm going to meet some of them Pokemon?
I could do I could meet my wife today.
Yeah, you never know.
You never know, lad.
So, why does people on Reddit dismiss my struggles Pokemon?
They don't really talk much about how
like where like the women lead me on and
stuff. They don't really say much about that.
Have you noticed that
they don't really like address it? Have
you noticed that, lad?
They did say that, oh, I'm coming across
desperate doing approaches and stuff. I
was like, yeah, but what about the women
that led me on and stuff?
What? So, you're saying my experiences
don't suit them Pokemon?
So what you're saying they dismiss my struggles. Yeah.
Like Joseph Farrell, isn't it?
It's like Ricky Millington. He's a
virgin. Probably never seen a Fanny in
his life. He says, "I get women."
I get women, mate." I said, "No, you bloody don't."
Do you remember that Vog? No, you bloody
don't get women. I get women, mate. No,
you bloody well don't. >> [sighs]
>> that greasy.
You look white knight.
Yeah, that woman on the train was okay
looking, but she had no boobies. So, I
won't be able to be fed. If they've got
no boobies, then why do you think when I
was with that 19-year-old, I was always
looking for somebody with bigger boobies, Greavvesy?
cuz I need to. It's like starving, you know?
Do you know what I'm saying? It's like I
was always looking for bigger ones
because obviously I I I can't be fed that way, you know?
There needs to be enough like milk.
Yeah. Yeah. Did you see the little white
knights defending the woman Pokémon?
Little white knights. Yeah.
I need to be fed, don't I? Pokemon.
I need to be fed. Yeah.
I hope I don't get I'm seeing someone
today. I can't be seeing someone or they
say I'm talking to someone
or they'll say I'm talking to someone.
Someone on Reddit told me to go to Canada.
They said I might find the person that
I'm looking for might be in Canada.
If you don't mind, Pokemon Canada.
What do you mean? Everyone agreed with
me on the bus.
Oh yeah, with the with that guy trying
to stick his nose in. I said, I said,
"Let's get off the next stop." He was
trying to get rude. I said, "Let's get
off the next stop, big man. Come on."
That's what I said. He soon shut his
mouth. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That was a
couple. That was when I was with my mom. Yeah.
I said, "It's none of your I said, "Why
don't you mind your own business?"
That's what I said to him.
[ __ ] [ __ ] And then he started
it. I said, "Let's go. Let's get off the
bus then. See what you got to say." Then
he shut his mouth. [ __ ] weasel.
Do you remember the one where you're too
old? I'm too old. You're too old for me.
You're too old for me. Yet she's been
with a 28-year-old before that weren't Muslim.
What do you think the problem is,
Pokémon? Why it's so hard to like find someone here?
Yeah, but why why do you think that the
excuse Why do you think they Why do you
think it's so hard, Pokemon?
I mean, I look normal, don't I? I look
normal. I look completely fine, don't I?
So, like, what's the problem?
What would you say the problem is?
They use loads of excuses like that
you're not Muslim, you're too old,
you're too young.
Why do you think they come out with all
of these excuses, Pokémon? What's the reason?
And then when I caught her lying, she
said, "Oh, you're a stalker."
When I caught her lying that she'd been
with 28-year-old before, she said, "Oh,
why are you stalking my profile?"
A narcissist favorite word. Stalker, eh?
That's their favorite word, eh? Yeah.
ad man was like, "You know what? They're
so Greavesy, she was on Reddit, right?
And she says she wouldn't get with me
cuz I'm 28.
Because I'm 28 and she only likes people
her age." So when I went on her Reddit
and seen a post that she made that she
got with a 28-year-old before, she
called me a stalker.
How is that stalking me looking on
someone's Reddit that's public?
It's weird, isn't it, Grey?
Don't you think it's a bit weird, Grezy?
Cruz is not weird.
Crazy. Is it not weird?
Why did she call me a Why did she call
me a stalker, Grezy?
Huh? Why does she call me a stalker?
I didn't stalk her.
Now answer me, bro. Why did she call me
Why did she call me a stalker? Huh?
No, I don't know about 15 numbers, lad.
It was hard enough trying to get 10. I'm
thinking about five.
We go about five to be fair.
Yeah, but why was she making excuses not
to get with me? She lives in um South
Africa, but why was she using my age as
an excuse? There's nothing wrong with
the way that I look, is there? Pokémon.
No, there's not better odds. How is
there better odds? I got 10 numbers and
only one replied.
That doesn't mean you've got better odds
just because you've got more numbers. But yeah,
K uh Pokemon.
Well, why why are they making these
excuses? There's nothing wrong with the
way that I look, is there? Pokemon
No, it doesn't.
There's been times where I've got eight,
nine numbers before and no one's [ __ ]
no one's um no one's replied. I've had
it before where I've got three numbers
and they've all replied
and one's met. It's all random.
I'm not playing Frankie. [ __ ] that.
Nope. Not at all, bro. That's not the
way it works.
Not at all.
I got 10 numbers. Only one replied.
Am I agobic Pokemon or no?
some more in a minute.
They should be here soon. Where the [ __ ]
are these trailers? Nope. [snorts]
Not at all, lad. I'm going out.
No, I'm going out, bro. Trust me,
I'm [snorts] going out. No.
What is it with you keep calling yourself virgins?
You need to sort it out, mate.
What is this? All right.
I'm not sleeping, bro.
I'm going out as soon as this
I said simp. I said, "Oh, a s." And the
great guys replied back saying, "Ooh, a
virgin." I said, "Must be talking about
yourself." Pretty sure I put a porno on
my YouTube channel. Yeah,
these people constantly talk about themselves.
Yeah, must be talking about yourself.
The five great guys must be talking about themselves.
Yeah, must be self projected as usual.
Like what they do on here? Self projectors. [snorts]
I feel tired cuz it's too fake. That's
why, bro. They're
[ __ ] stinking. It really is stinking.
Want to take two more pills.
I can't even believe that.
Yeah, I think he was leaving running.
I'm just waiting for my trainers to come. Bob,
I'm going to jump in the shower and uh Yeah,
jump in the shower and [ __ ] go to the pub. Yeah.
>> [clears throat]
>> How can the five great guys call me a
virgin when I've literally put a porno on YouTube? Madness. Self projectors.
Yeah, that's self projector, mad.
Yeah, I got a football bat.
I got my outfit. Nice Stone Island
jumper, nice jeans, and I'm waiting for
the trainers now. So, then I'll be out.
And that'll be it. Maybe for two weeks.
Maybe I'll go out next week. I don't
know. I don't know what I'm doing. What? >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, I got treble. Both score no draw. [laughter]
20 returns 237. I think it's got a good chance though.
I think it's got a [ __ ] good chance.
Yep. Both score draw. Show
you can't deny she's attractive as even I
Can't deny he's attracting even.
Is that right?
You can't deny it. Copycat. Yellow.
You little copycat.
Do you like that video, Bob?
Okay. Who's Who's the copycat then?
See, who's the copycat? Oh,
there we go. Sunny,
are these the babies? being upset.
>> No, it's not, is it? Don't be silly.
It's my traders. >> Yeah.
Oh, god darn it. >> Huh?
The train is over here, lads. Right.
Gosh darn it. I've just Yeah,
you're supposed to lift these and you
can smell them. I don't know.
Oh, look at that. That's lovely. That is
Jesus Christ. They knock you out, mate.
The smell of these will absolutely knock
your [ __ ] bollocks off.
Am I [ __ ] Am I lying, mate? Or am I lying? [snorts]
Oh, I can't believe it. And I got a free
leg spray with it as well.
>> Yeah. Very cute. >> No.
Yeah. I got the tens.
I you can tell if Brad spoke to you, can't you? Would you?
It cost me a lot of money, bar
cost me a [ __ ] lot of money.
He's cost me a [ __ ] an absolute bum, mate.
An absolute [ __ ] bum and a half.
Look at these. Bought him before. Got
him again. [ __ ] lovely s.
Time to jump in the shower, mate.
No skin virgins allowed.
That's the only thing about this this
little uh this this thing, right, is
that there's no skin in the land with this trip.
>> [clears throat] >> Okay,
we need to move these uh
it is a bit cold is it mate?
[ __ ] knows why, mate.
Right them. They're cool, aren't they? Right.
I'm just popping in the shower now, mate. Oh,
they smell nice and there
a certain person's price range. Again,
I'm not here to I'm not starting
anything or anything like that.
a lot. You know, it's a bit a certain
person a skin burden in the bed range.
Going to the pub.
We're going to the pub today.
See what trouble we can get up to.
See what [ __ ] trouble we can get up
to in it, mate.
Yeah. One second. Just jumping in the shower, mate.
just got out the shower. Sorry, mate. Little copycat. Yeah.
You little copycat.
You little copycat. Little copycat.
The little cat. Little copycat.
>> Oh, I got a free deodorant.
I can't believe I got a free deodorant
with my trainers. I'm feeling grand.
Feeling all right, you know.
I'm feeling quite I got I got a free
after shave in my trainers.
My little armpits.
The little cats. Little copycats.
Them little copycats. The little cats. Little copycats.
Do you like my trainers? They're looking
cool, aren't they, mate? I told you I
was going to go out today, mate. But I
meant it this time. I deserve a [ __ ] break.
I like to stick with the devil that I do
know, mate. They're like, they're like the £25.
You like them? I think they look I think
they look quite cool.
Uh after Oh, it's deodorant. It's not
after shave. It's deodorant. It's links.
Yeah, bro. It's links. It's This is It's
just like deodorant.
So, I'm going to use some of this.
Obviously, I've got my Dior. So, yeah.
Them little cats.
Yeah, bro. And then I got my Gorilla
powder. So, yeah. Should be looking
cool. Should be looking all right.
These people are self projectors. 28,
never had a girlfriend.
I said, you people in your 40s and you
still a virgin. Self projection. Hey,
bro. Anyways, I'm off today after today
for maybe a week or two and I'm going to
come back. Um, I'm doing both.
Approaching and getting pissed. Of
course, I'm doing both, mate. So,
yeah, I'm coming off for like a week or
two after today cuz the self projection
and the same atmosphere, it gets too
much. These little bug goes. You have to
take a break sometimes from these
disabled people. I mean, we've got the
great guys trying to say I'm a virgin
even though I proved I've had sex in a
[ __ ] polo video. Too much self
projection. You have to take a break
from it sometimes, bro.
>> Yeah, I'm doing both. I'm approaching
and um getting pissed.
>> Nah, bro. It's the same atmosphere. I'm
coming back. I'm not leaving. This is
the same atmosphere.
You know what I mean by that, Bob?
One second, bro. Change. Hold on.
My hair. Hold on. One second.
I need to get some lotion for my face to be fair.
Them little copycats.
Them little cats.
Them little copycats. No,
no, I'm not videoing me approaching. Huh?
You don't need to see me. I might go
live in the pub. Maybe
if you're lucky.
But them little cats,
them little copycats.
This is nice after [ __ ] Uh deodorant.
That's what it is. It's deodorant. It's
not after shave. That deodorant's [ __ ] pain.
I'm slowly getting ready.
That deodorant's bloody nice. Bloody
Yeah, that that deodorant's bloody nice.
That deodorant. Oh, I'm not going to dox
myself. You know what these little
virgins are like? The little YouTube virgins. Oh,
this is the first bit of it. Yeah.
Oh, that after shave is lush.
Oh, that after shave is lush, lad.
I'm going to be looking a million dollars
for my ston and stuff. Don't watch that. Delayed.
Them little cats. Them little copycats.
Oh, that links is lush. I got rid of trainers.
I'd be looking at a [ __ ] million
dollars, mate. A million [ __ ] dollars.
But isn't that cool? Gota look all
right. I'm going to put some Gorilla
powder on my hair.
If you think I'm taking a piss, I'm not.
It's actually called Gorilla Powder.
Makes your hair curl up very nicely.
So, that's the thing. In case you
thought I was actually taking a piss,
no, don't take the piss me, lad. >> [snorts]
>> Oh l
some after shave on me now.
I wiped my hair back up and I need to
put on it. Them little cats.
Them little copycats.
Look at this. Oh,
that is lovely.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, mate.
That is lovely. Just making friends,
guys. Just making friends.
I'm just going to wear these shorts for now.
I will be getting I will be getting
changed properly. Don't worry.
Oh, I don't feel I could live without Sage. Million dollars.
them little cats.
Them little cats little cats.
There we go.
Yeah. Look at that, bro.
I'm just wearing these for now. These shorts. Oh, hello copycat.
You little copycat.
You little copycat. You little copycat.
You activation copycat.
Oh, bro. It's lovely, isn't it?
Oh, look at that.
hair still looks kind of good as well, doesn't it?
Yeah. So, we're going to crunch our
hair, make it curly. We got to look
sexy, you know. We're going out and
stuff. Not that skin virgin beds it.
I love these shorts. I bought them from
Amazon, actually. Well, actually, my mom
bought them for me.
Like, [ __ ] this year. I'm only playing, you know.
Oh, look at that.
Look at that lovely little beard. Got
some on the beard as well. Even more fun
stuff. I saw all saints top. What What
more could you want?
Well, obviously the stony,
but that's over there.
Look at these trainers, mate.
Whoa, look at these trainers.
Look at these [ __ ] trainers, mate.
Oh, that's so new. They knock you out,
mate. How long are they to join? Does
you like them?
They're quite big, but I'm a size 10.
I'm actually a size 10.
Well, I got size 10. So, yeah.
I like size 10. Size 10's cool.
I think I'm a nine and a half, but I
just get 10.
What I always got. So,
yeah, I'll be looking even better soon.
Oh, who's that? Oh, I didn't know that.
You see that?
Oh, I didn't know. Oh.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Oh man. Yeah, we need to leave the finger on
the football. We'll stay for the
football and then we'll piss off.
How's that sound?
How's that sound? We'll piss off, eh?
That sound good?
We'll piss off. We'll [ __ ] off. We'll
Yeah, I think so, mate.
Oh, I smell so nice, bro.
I smell really good. Yeah.
Who can't afford this? Me? Nah, can't be me, mate.
Should I jump on um Laur's and see what
he thinks of my new trainers? My
I've got to join Lord J and see what he
thinks of our new traders
new edition. Well, they're not new
edition. They're quite old actually. Oh,
>> you like the traders? What do you think
of them? They're [ __ ] brand spanking
new. Look, you can put them on your
face. Look, you can stroke your face
with them. You can you can do that.
Look, cuz they're brand new, you know. So,
my kicks are sh. My traders are bloody
lovely, you little [ __ ]
Look about my trainers. I'll [ __ ]
come and do you.
You're my my kicks are sh. Why are my kicks sh?
They cost a lot of money. They cost me £25.
You can even lick them.
They're not shy. They're actually quite
expensive. They cost me over £200.
I quite like them. Hey,
I wore them 20 years ago. Well, they
didn't exist 20 years ago, so that's impossible.
You wore them 20 years ago. They didn't
exist 20 years ago.
So, he's not putting the link up.
What the [ __ ]
So, you want people to join? Stop selfjecting.
I need to buy a new face.
You're the one who can't show yourself.
I need to buy a new face. Self projecting.
That's self projecting. We've all seen
these fat ugly people.
We've all seen these mutters. They're
self projectors. Literally, the only
reason I'm I'm I'm joining or trying to
trying to join,
right, is so I can show you these kicks.
Mate, you're not going to make me feel
down about my face.
I I'll show my face whenever I want.
You know, you can't show your face cuz
you're ugly. Cuz you're an ugly bastard.
So, stop self projecting, mate.
You know, you people are the fat and
ugly disabled looking bastards. Nothing
you say about me bothers me, mate.
Yeah. No, I'm just going to So, you're
not putting a link up? No.
No. Not put a link up.
Yeah. Just self projectors, right? Leave
them to it. Just the same self
projecting people. Anyways, uh what what
hairstyle? I'm just going to make it curly.
Yeah. I'm just going to make my hair
curly, bro. Just going to curl it up a
little bit. Bit messy.
You like it? I'm just going to add some products.
Yeah, I'm going to add some products,
mate. I'm going to add some uh lovely products.
He's not putting a link up, bro. They
just keep self projecting.
So, we don't want these little fat, ugly
self projectors ruining the mood. Size
of my nose, Kevin. You can't show
yourself cuz you're fat and ugly. I can
show my face. You can't show your face
cuz you're fat and ugly. And that's
something I'd always have against you,
mate. You can talk about my looks all
you want. You don't see me scared to
show my face, but you're scared to show
your face because you're fat and ugly.
And that's what it is with you people.
You fat, ugly people want to make people
depressed and feel ugly like you skin on
YouTube. I mean, didn't eight people
already been got proven wrong. You know,
you told me that I couldn't afford a new
pair of trainers. I bought a new pair of
trainers that cost over £200. So, when
are you really really going to stop this
stuff and realize that you're just
talking about yourselves, mate? These
people don't get me down, Bob. These
fat, ugly people don't get me down.
They don't get me down. They do not get
me down. These fat, ugly self
projectors. You You got to understand,
Bob. It's jealousy with these people.
I'm going out today. I'm going to
probably spend a good £300 getting
drunk, getting drunk in my new gums.
They're going to be sat on YouTube all
by themsel. Just think about it. It's
pretty self-explanatory, lad. We got
nice new pair of jeans, £200. These are
over £200. We'll probably be spending £300 today.
Maybe, maybe more, maybe less. You
understand? These people are going to be
sat on YouTube with nobody skint.
You You understand the difference, lad?
That's the difference with these people.
My life is better than yours will ever
be. You [ __ ] prick. You're a [ __ ]
prick. Where are you [ __ ] coming
[ __ ] Liverpool at? We can't take
somebody that sounds like that seriously, mate.
We can't. We just can't take someone
that sounds like that serious.
We just can't, mate. No. You know, we
can't take someone like that serious.
Anyways, what's the time? Uh 155.
Yeah, Bob. These self projectors don't
bother me. I show my face. Look, I can
show my face. I'm not scared to show my
face. Can Kevin come and show his face?
No, because you're too ugly.
I win. Thank you. Anyways,
you Oh, yeah. You went out last time. It
was Halloween, wasn't it? That's That's
why you went out, right?
Yeah, it was Halloween, wasn't it, mate? Okay. 37%.
Yeah, I'm just chilling for a bit, lad.
might have a tea actually, but I got to
be careful cuz of my gums.
I really need to be careful, lad,
cuz the toothach is [ __ ] absolutely stinking, son. [ __ ] stinking. Yeah,
Bob. These these haters don't get anyone
down, lad. From me to you, they don't
get anyone down.
They really don't get anyone down at all.
Not one of them. Not one of these ugly
fat people will ever get me down, sir.
That's the message for me to you. I'm
high on life right now, son. Yeah, man.
I will need to go to your dentist at
some point though, just [ __ ] get get
better. I can't be bothered going around
and around in circles with you, Kevin.
You know where I live. You haven't been
to London. You're boring, kid. I was in
Liverpool, you done nothing. I was in
Manchester, you done nothing.
And we're not going to go round and
round around in circles, lad. We're not
going round and round and round in
circles. You know, I was in Liverpool,
you done nothing. I was in Manchester,
you know nothing. You know where I live
in London and you ain't done nothing.
Bro, we're not going to go back and
forth with you, son. You're something to laugh at.
You know, mate,
you're a [ __ ] idiot.
Yeah, man. This stop s to be honest.
But after such the blush.
Well, I'm going to make myself a tea. Be right back.
So, do you like it? You like when it's like stuff?
>> I think it's pretty cold.
When do we
uh shortly actually? Yeah, shortly. Shortly, shortly, lad.
Yeah. And I'm going to obviously just
add a bit of products on my hair.
I'll be looking cool.
Sorry about that, mate. We're ignoring you.
Don't look all right. Don't look cool. Cheers, mate.
I didn't go on Lord J for too long, lad.
You hope I pull. I won't pull cuz it
would happen by now.
Uh I'm going to wear this color.
I want to wear the same blue. This one.
I don't know. I still I still want to
wear I just want to wear this one again.
I don't know. It's like my favorite one.
You hope I'll pull. I won't pull, mate.
Trust me. But it'll be a fun. It'll be
It be a laugh. It will be a laugh.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Yeah, I want to wear that one again. Or
there's a lighter blue one, but I like that one.
Well, don't know. Maybe I'll wear the
lighter blue one. Who knows?
I mean, that that's
wear this one.
Now [ __ ] we'll wear this one. Yeah,
cuz this one's straight fresh from the
dry cleaners. I think we'll wear this one actually.
You know what? I think we'll wear that
one. And we'll wear the light blue one.
So indecisive. Gosh darn it.
We need to make up my bloody mind.
I do sometimes really need to make up my
[ __ ] mind, mate. Yeah. Wear wear that
one. Did we wear that? We won that one
for a mill, didn't we?
Yeah, it will, mate.
Look at this. You're tired. You're
trying to [ __ ] tell me, son,
that this ain't a lovely site.
You're trying to sit there and tell me
just these two things alone. Look at
that. It's lovely. Just look at it. It's
just It's just lovely, mate. in it.
Yeah, it's just absolutely lush.
[snorts] Yeah, I'm going to wear that
one. I think I'm going to wear the
lighter one, I reckon.
They're all pretty cool.
Little weird it ready to put it on. Look
at that. Oh, look at that. Beautiful.
It's beautiful, mate.
Oh, look at that. It's absolutely
It's absolutely uh lovely,
isn't it, mate? The the skin virgin and
out of London couldn't afford that,
could they mate? No.
The out of London virgin couldn't afford
that, could he, mate? No. No, no, no,
no, no, no.
Because he's a [ __ ] skimp virgin. That's why.
Stop making me go all into this [ __ ] son.
Because he's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] virgin can.
He's a [ __ ] stint version.
You know what I'm like, mate.
Wonder what LJ thinks of the clubber.
It's a nice bit of clubber, isn't it?
I'm going to have Guinness. Baby Yeah.
Yeah. Guinness. Baby Guinness.
Yeah. Guinness. And a baby Guinness.
I'm just wearing this right now cuz it's cozy.
Yeah. I'm just going to just curl my hair up.
Little bit like messy, you know? Think I
should look all right, shouldn't I?
>> Nah, but I need to be careful with my
gums. We'll drink loads of stuff. We'll
drink all sorts. It's not a problem.
It's okay. We're not skint like the
virgin in the bedsit with no bunny in
it, you know. We We'll take it as it comes.
We're not skint like that virgin in the
[ __ ] bedit with no bed, no money in
it, you know? We'll take it as it comes.
It's all right. It's okay, girl. It's
absolutely fine. It's absolutely okay. You know,
we're not skimp like the virgin. We can
drink whatever we want.
How's that sound, Bob?
We're not skimp like the virgin.
How's that, mate? How's that, mate?
Nice. Nice, mate.
I got some stuff. By the way,
obviously I need to style my hair a
little bit with the powder, but I've I
went for this costume.
Look, that's fresh from the dry
cleaners, by the way. The jeans and the
trainers. I'm thinking they're looking pretty cold.
What do you reckon?
Isn't that cool? B outfit.
That's my I was going to wear the the
the more brighter blue, but I think that
blue is just right. Just okay. I like it.
You like the trainers, Grezy? Oh, I got
a free deodorant with the trainers, by
the way. I've already used it. But
yeah, I I don't need to slow down me,
mate. I keep going. Oh, I can keep going
and going and going and going if you
want me to, mate. The joys of not knowing people.
This is the joys of not knowing what
people have and what people don't have, son.
Oh, they're just gray socks.
They're clean, don't worry. So, I'll be
looking fresh as a bubin. Yeah.
Fresh as a little bubin, mate. [ __ ]
260. I'll be [ __ ] spending about £250
a day, mate. I'll be spending like 250
to [ __ ] day for [ __ ] sake, son.
I've already spent [ __ ] over £400.
Isn't it two things? [ __ ] hell. Yeah, man.
Let me just finish this cup of [ __ ] and
I'll slowly get ready.
Got a nasty toothache still, but
bear with it.
Yeah, I was on large for 5 minutes and
then it just became weird and I left. I
was trying to get him to put the link
up. He's just full of mongos on that
channel. That's why I never go on there.
Just little self-reflectors.
Little self projectors creating the same atmosphere. Bob
Red still stalking me. He popped up. Bob Hills.
He's a little stalker. He's a fat ugly
stalker. Have you seen his fingers?
The [ __ ] skin bastard. Have Have you
seen his fingers, son? It's like this.
He's so He's so obsessed.
These are what your fingers should look like.
They're so obsessed. But he will do
absolutely nothing in real life. That's
what triggers him, sad, cuz he knows
he'll do absolutely nothing.
Just a little keyboard warrior.
That's all he will ever be. He knows his
place cuz he's a good boy, isn't he, mate?
Have you seen his fingers? He's fat,
ugly fingers. He tried hiding them. He's
got these big fat ugly fingers. I told
you, bro, on there, they're fat and
ugly. They're fat, ugly bongos.
Depressed with their lives, trying to
get other people feel to feel like them.
Fat, ugly, depressed. That's all these
people are on this community, lad.
Little low lives. That's what they are, mate.
That's what my sister calls them as
well, to be fair.
Right, I'm going to start uh
putting these arms on soon.
Oh, I could just stay in and have a
snooze, but I'm not doing that cuz like I said,
I'll put the club on in a bit.
Oh, it's so relaxing in just like
t-shirts and shorts, you know?
You know what I mean? Don't you, Greasy?
Just t-shirts and shorts.
So, I do it one by one,
bit by bit, you know.
Right. Should we put the Sony on now?
Right. [ __ ] it.
I'm going to have to do some approaches
so as well. I
come out slowly. Come out. Come out, son.
Come out, sir. Come out. Come out. Lovely. up
for a while. One second.
There we go.
How's that look?
That look all right. Yeah.
Oh, sorry. That's very rude of me.
How does that look?
That look all right. Toilet bulbs
into this. How's it look? All right.
That look all right. How do I look?
I think I look cool.
What about you, mate? Now
I've still got my shorts on.
But why the [ __ ]
do I still have my shorts on?
Think it's time for the Armani jeans. Two sex.
Time for the morning jeans. E.
Oh, don't mind if I do. Green.
They've been worn once before, but they
haven't said they haven't, you know.
Oh, these are looking quite nice. One second.
Oh, this is nice. Oh,
well, one second. One second. Oh,
that's not the best part, is it? Let's move.
That's not the best. All we had about this.
>> That's not the best part. Look at this.
What do you think of this? Do we look
all right? I look at my bum.
Can you see the badge? Can you see the logo?
And if you can see the badge and you can
see the logo,
what do you think of it? Think it looks
cool? I think I look pretty cool.
What do you think, Re? I think I look
pretty a morningly good.
But that's not the best part yet. The
best part can wait.
And yes, it can [ __ ] wait. No skin in
the [ __ ] bed. No bed, no money. You
[ __ ] know the drills. But Grezy
this is the best bit.
This is the moment everyone's been
waiting for, mate. Look it. See,
look at that. You're telling me?
You're telling me you can't. You can say
no to this.
Even Even, you know, I don't think it'd
be possible, mate, to say no to these bad boys.
Unless you're a skinned virgin in a
bedsit. Which you probably are, mate.
You probably are a skinned [ __ ]
virgin in a bedsit.
You a skinned virgin. You a skinned
virgin in a [ __ ] bedit, mate. You a
skinned virgin in a [ __ ] bedit.
But I need to do my hair. One second. Grey
star like virginit.
Oh, you got to do this. Oh, thanks.
One second. Gra.
You have to wet your head a little bit.
You have to go that [ __ ] Got it.
You'll get you'll get thrown out. I'm
telling you, you will, mate.
Do you mean? Never asked about getting
thrown out of anywhere.
See? So, you put a bit of powder on your hair
and then you uh literally just
do that. Turn it up a little bit.
Make it a bit, you know, messy, bit styl, you know.
Like when Virgin boy did the [ __ ] Sarah,
>> you know. Yeah.
Like add few products on it.
I went for
curly look today.
Oh, I don't want the USA. He couldn't
say no to me.
A nice stony.
I reckon we'll be doing it again today somehow.
What do you think, Gre? Do you like the
hair? Does the hair look all right?
You have to basically really crunch the [ __ ] together.
Make it really
sort of curly.
So, I got like curls in my hair. If I
let it grow out of it more, what do you
think? Do I look all right? Well, look,
you know, good enough to I don't know,
go out and speak to people.
Have to run it by grievy first.
No, we'll have to probably modify it a bit later.
I don't even know why I ask because I go
against anything he says anyways, don't
I? You know what I'm like, you know?
You know what I'm like, Grey. I told
you, mate. I asked I asked you if I
could buy a pair of trainers and you
told me not to, but I bought trainers.
But I bought them anyways. Gosh darn it.
What's wrong with me?
Why would you ask someone something PJ
and then just do it anyways?
Sorry, but you could you could
understand, pardon you, Grezy. You You'd
understand if if you're not a skin virgin.
If you got a skid virgin in the bedsit, you'd understand.
You'd understand. If you if you got a
skid virgin in the bedsit with no bed,
no money, you'd understand the same,
mate. You [ __ ] understand, mate.
I feel a million dollars.
I can't wait to get I can't wait to get
a good down me. I generally can't wait
to get a good down me, mate.
Honestly can't. Honestly can't.
I'm not Grezy.
How How does Laney put up with me? I
don't know. Honestly don't know how how
how anyone could put up with me, mate.
I don't know how people do
to be honest with you.
you know, I don't Hey there. Yeah.
Now it's the trainers, isn't it, Grezy?
It's the [ __ ] trainers now, son. Ain't it?
Look at my little curly hair.
This is the same hairstyle I had when I
met USA Izzy.
She just she just fell for me.
And I'm hoping that happens again today.
Someone fallen for me.
Like I I've I've invested a lot of money
into these gars, Grezy. And it's worth
it. If it means I get to find my mommy
and I get to be fed, then who cares?
It's only money,
you know. Who cares about money, mate?
Who cares about money?
Then you can beat your mama, get fed. only playing. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah. Uhuh. That is [ __ ] stinking son.
That is stinking, bro. 54%.
Same people, same atmosphere.
The same atmosphere greaves in it.
I'm so [ __ ] up.
I don't need one, bro.
I don't need one. I'm all good.
No, I'm all good, lad.
That looks good, is it?
Just the train is now.
Just the train is now boss.
So, do you believe I'm going out now, uh, Grievy?
You believe I'm going out now, boss? Right.
Right. Got to put the trainers on in a bit.
You believe me now, don't you, Grezy?
Exactly, mate. Exactly.
Going to put the trainers on in a minute
just to uh show you how good they look. Yeah,
they will fit, matey. I know my size.
You silly goose.
You silly [ __ ] goose.
Isn't he? Oh, gosh darn it, Stephen. receiving
such a [ __ ] ste.
Well, I could be a nine and a half, but
I just get 10 cuz I've always been 10.
So, depending what socks you [ __ ] wear.
Oh, these these are lush. These are
[ __ ] lush, man. One sec.
Oh, mate. Get a [ __ ] dog's bullets.
Yeah, but I've had these trainers before. Oh.
Oh, look at them.
Look at them. Look at them. Look at these. Oh. Oh, mate.
They're the [ __ ] dogs. Beeswax, mate.
There the dogs. They're the dogs. Oh.
Oh, mate. They're a dog. Beadwax music.
One second, lad.
One second, mate.
Look at that. Oh, that is lush.
Look at that, mate.
That is lovely. That's a lovely sight.
That's a lovely site, mate.
They feel a tiny bit loose, but I've
always had tens.
Not just tens with it, but tense. So,
you know, any holes anywhere?
Oh, I'm looking uh looking at the dog beeswax. Greasy. [laughter] This greasy.
Oh, look at that Greavves.
look at these, mate.
What a lovely site.
Oh, right. Let me do my [ __ ] my
hair a little bit more.
Give me that [ __ ] powder. Bollocks, mate.
They're a little bit loose to trainers,
but I've always had them this size, so Oh, greasy.
Don't mind if I go out today, lad. Don't
mind if I do.
Please don't mind if I do.
Going to get Laney to uh lighten this
thing up. Two seconds.
Wait a second. Is that Oh,
do this concept for you [ __ ] Today
I'm doing this all for you [ __ ]
All for you [ __ ] Look. How's that
lovely grievy? Is that lovely enough for you?
How was that? Good. Cool. Yeah, man.
That's lovely, isn't it?
We're going to get Virgin Boy triggered
today, aren't we? Steven,
we're going to get someone triggered
today, aren't we, son?
Going to get Virgin ball.
Oh, we're going to get Virgin boy triggered.
This will be a guide on how to lose your VC card.
And the only the only thing is Bob is
I'll get reject I will get rejected
today all night long. You watch.
That's the most weirdest thing about this.
Yeah, I done my hair nicely. Done my
hair by myself.
Funny thing is I get rejected overnight
but I don't give a [ __ ] It's content in
it, mate. Just have to wipe my phone.
Got a lot of [ __ ] stains on it.
Easy. Do you notice that
lot of crumb stains? I'm only joking.
Oh, one second.
One second, bro.
Oh, virgin. That virgin's always going [ __ ] mad.
You like my boy hair?
Do you like my boyy hair?
You like the hair, Bob? I do hair good.
Please tell me I done the hair good, mate.
I do good. You like it? Cheers, mate. [snorts] All right.
I don't want to comb it. I want it messy.
I I want the hair messy, mate.
We'll come back. We'll come back about next week.
Do you like the curls?
I like the curly hair, mate. Because
it's stony. When you're wearing stony,
you're supposed to have like a messy
look. And obviously, if you um if you
have like a blazer and that, that's when
you get it back. But we'll get we'll get
going back next week,
you know. Yeah.
Maybe I might win the lottery as well.
I might win the lottery.
Is that right, Grezy? I might win the lottery.
Could do. Could win the lottery. Who knows?
Oh man, my [ __ ]
killing again. Let's get salt water.
Let me spray this sage again and put it away
and then we're done. Going to watch a
bit of football and then we'll leave
all over me.
just going into into into the city.
Yeah, I'm just going into the city.
Two seconds, bro.
Oh, that boy.
Oh, that virgin boy. That little [ __ ] You're not Huh?
sorry. I just went downstairs. I went to
see my mama. Oh, Bob.
Now, I was going out with um I I was
going to invite Virgin Boy, but I can't
bring Virgin Boy because the manager
said the manager said no skin virgins allowed.
And I said, "Oh, look, I've got somebody
that I've met several times and he's
still a virgin." Says, "No, no, no, no,
no. You weren't interested." No, no, no,
no. That's what he said.
He says, "No skin virgins allowed, so we can't come.
You can't come and join the fun, right?
Watching this football starts in 15 minutes.
My phone needs a charge anyways. 64%.
No skin virgins.
I know that's what he said. I'm not
starting anything, Bob. I swear to God.
He he he he he literally said no skin
virgins. I I don't know. I don't know. I
didn't even know there was there was
such such a thing, mate.
I didn't know there was such rules. What
the [ __ ] He said, "No, if they're
virgins in this skin, they can't come."
I I don't know. I I don't know. I don't
I don't know. I don't know. I don't
know. I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. Do you know don't know?
Ah, you wish. I've looked a lot better
than this before, mate.
And all I've got was I got a boyfriend. Not interested.
I don't think so, mate. But it'll be
fine. And I like the content anyways.
You know, I'll do some I'll do some
sober, then I'll start on the drink.
Yeah. Unfortunately, it's not as easy as that, lad.
Fortunately, not. You would have thought
so, but no, mate. No.
Yeah, I'm coming off YouTube for a week
or two weeks after this. Um
cuz of um yeah, like I said, it's the
same atmosphere and same shitty people
and that. So, you have to have like a
break of it sometimes, lad. You know how it is.
Where's Joseph Ferrar? He's always away
on the weekends. Say, "Mom,
it's nice, isn't it?" It's was [ __ ]
expensive. I had to buy a new one cuz
some [ __ ] had it away on me, didn't they? Sorry, mate. Yeah. Yeah.
You sure about that? Well, we'll see,
won't we, mate? We'll see, won't we?
Time will tell.
Time will definitely tell, won't it? I
hope this football bet wins.
Do you like this mom? Huh?
We're going out next week, aren't we?
You know, I can't behave.
I'll do what I want.
I'll put like 10 minutes of it on
YouTube or something. You know,
you know what I'm like, Mom.
Mom knows what I'm bloody like. He knows
I can't behave.
She knows a cup, babe. She knows. She
knows me. Everyone knows me, mate.
Everyone knows I'm
Everyone knows why I'm like, mate.
Yeah, he's got that Virgin channel as
well, doesn't he?
Oh [ __ ] I didn't even see that. Oh,
look at this jealous little virgin. He
said it's nowhere near 13k still and the
clothing choice is diabolical or not.
Stus to say the least. On a separate
subject, I'm pretty sure there's a way
we can report him to DWP here. Universal
isn't buying designer clothes. He's
jealous because he got the VM. He's a
little kid skin. That just goes to show
that that was his daddy's savings.
Oh, that just goes to show you, mate. Right.
That That was Daddy Savens, wasn't it?
Wasn't it mate?
Generally in need? Yeah. You want to
talk about people in general need? What
about when you went on that shitty
little virgin holiday to Amsterdam just
cuz I went? What about them [ __ ]
people there then? the people that can
barely pay their bills and stuff and we
got some ugly [ __ ] rat looking
[ __ ] virgin [ __ ] taking his fat ugly
girlfriend on a cheap skate holiday just
cuz I went How do you think them people
feel not being able to eat any food?
Didn't know having more money than you
was a crime. Sorry, mate. You know,
you know, you know that was a crime.
Sorry, mate. We'll shop in a charity
shop like you, you [ __ ] virgin, and
get funny looks everywhere.
Why am I not allowed to buy designer
clothes? I've got the money.
Save the money. What the money? Why am I
not allowed to buy designer stuff? Why?
Cuz you're a skin virgin. Everyone's got
to be like you.
You know what I mean? There's people on
benefits who are [ __ ] who can barely
pay their bills and struggle living
alone without the luxury of loving. Yeah. Yeah.
It's a big insult to them generally indeed.
What a [ __ ] ski virgin. Is that
right, Grezy? The football started in
seven minutes, mate. This is just the beginning.
My sister told me
No, I'm I like m how it is, mate.
I'm good, bro. I think it does suit me
and I'm keeping it. So, thank you. But
I'm leaving it like this. But anyways,
uh not asking for your opinion. If I
wanted on how I should do my hair, I'd
[ __ ] ask you, [ __ ] But anyways, on
to this [ __ ] Why are people not allowed
to buy designer clothes?
Because he's skin. Because he's a skin flin, mate.
Because he's a [ __ ] skin flat, mate.
Cuz he's a [ __ ] skin flin cat, mate.
That's not fair, mate, is it? Why can't
we buy designer stuff if we got the money?
Why not, DWP? Why not?
Why not, mate? I like my hair curly. I
think it looks all right. I think it looks cool.
Oh, well, someone messaged me there, but
it wasn't someone.
Did you die?
This guy is so jealous, bro. It's
unbelievable. All jokes aside, now let's
be serious, bro. This guy is so jealous.
Oh my god. How long can people do this
[ __ ] for, man? It's [ __ ] mental.
But no, I like my hair curly.
Smart hair doesn't suit a Stone Island
J. But depends on what you're wearing, you know.
It all depends on what you're um what you're wearing. Good night. So, yeah.
Oh, you sick nasty virgin.
You nasty skin virgin. Why are you
putting stuff on there?
You can't report somebody to the DWP for
having designer clothes, mate. Looking
better than you is not a crime as much
as you like it to be. [ __ ] virgin.
[ __ ] virgins. But mate, like I said,
I'm coming off after today.
Well, I I'll be here over the weekend
and maybe for Monday I'll be off for
like one or two weeks.
Is that all right with you, boss? One
week, two weeks.
I like these little one, two weeks off,
you know, cuz it shows you like that
these people can't get off of YouTube.
It shows that these people can't get off
of YouTube and it's something they've
got. That's another reason I do like
doing things like this, Grezy,
you know, because it shows that these
people can't get off of YouTube, you know.
Okay, football time,
right? Come on, you three teams. Come
on. Come on.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
Give ourselves £237. We could do with that
saying that probably get reported
having more money than a certain skinned virgin.
Make sure you tell DWP that you was
showing you a daddy savings. That you're
showing daddy savings. You [ __ ] virgin.
Daddy savings. Did you tell them that
you you got daddy savings, mate? Showing
daddy's [ __ ] savings.
That's what it is. Your money, mate. Oh,
so you call someone skin and then when
you get proven wrong time and time and
time and time again, all of a sudden you
report to them now. You [ __ ] nasty
virgin. You're a horrible little virgin
you are, mate.
No, I'm not providing content every day.
I've had enough of you bastards.
I've had enough of you little self projectors. Yeah, man.
Probably doing this [ __ ] today for you
but I did say. So,
here we are, man. 71 71%.
So yeah, what's bit of football will
[ __ ] off. I don't know why I've got a
good feeling about this Yeah,
One sec. Yeah, I'm going out in a bit, bro. Yeah.
Uh, in a bit. One sec.
I've got the garments on, mate. Fresh
trainers, fresh jeans. looking quite
nice, isn't I? So, yeah,
there's an FA Cup. I'm looking at the
wrong thing here. One sec.
I'm looking at something completely
different, aren't I? Yeah,
boy is going to try and get my money
stopped cuz I bought the clothes Cory
and he can't afford them. Typical virgin.
He'll go wherever you go, mate.
I don't understand this, bro.
There's no FA Cup. Where?
Yeah, I done my hair curly. Someone said
it don't suit me, but I like it. So,
I like my little hair like this. Don't.
Where was it?
This doesn't make any sense. One second.
This doesn't make any sense cuz they're
two different leagues, but
seems are still playing um in it.
Oh, it's Yeah, it is. Yeah,
it is. Yeah. One sec.
What's the other one? Slow.
We got slow there, too. I've got a
feeling this bet's going to come in.
What do you lads think?
I've got a feeling it's coming in, mate.
Come on, football. Come on. We're going to get two
Right, the football. We got the
football. This football better come in.
We'll watch a little bit of it and then
I'll just [ __ ] off. Uh,
yeah. I been out for ages, so I feel a
bit weird at first. >> [snorts] >> Yeah.
I've [clears throat] got a feeling this
this is going to come in, bro.
I don't know why. It's an FA Cup, so
it's like the lower leagues, so I think
it will, bro. Yeah. Virgin Boys said
that he's going to try and get my buddy
stopped because I bought some designer clothes.
So, cuz I'm not skin like you. I'm not
allowed the live. Why am I not allowed to live?
I'm going to I'm going to tease you
today. I'm going to the pub.
I'm going to the pub, mate.
Sh. Go away.
Go to the pub, mate.
You don't believe me, do you?
I reckon this is coming in this betad.
Yeah, he said that on on his community post.
He said he's going to try and get my
little money stopped.
Well, I will easily say to them on some
money. I saved some money and I could do
what I want with my little bit of money.
But it's all right for him to to to copy
people's holidays going to Amsterdam,
you know, because I [ __ ] went [ __ ] virgin.
This is what I mean with these people
when they get owned, right? This is what
I mean with these people on here,
Stephen. This is why I need a break
after Monday, son.
Is that they come on here talking about
people that they don't know. Oh, you're
skin. Oh, you're this. Oh, you're that.
Oh, you're this. Oh, you're that. And
then when you own them, they literally
they literally um it's on his it's on
the other channel. It's on the wrong
central one. Um when you prove to them
that you got more than them, they get
jealous and they either try to [ __ ] you
over with the old Bill or DWP. They're [ __ ] losers.
They're [ __ ] weirdos. Jasper lad. Why
I have to take breaks uh from here, son?
That's why I have to take, you know,
they're weirdos, lad.
What we on now? 74%. Right. I need to
go. One sec. [ __ ] way.
I think he comes to jealousy, lad. Desp. Sorry, bro.
I think he comes to jealousy with these people [snorts] like
that. So they want to make other people
feel the way that they do.
Yeah. It comes to jealousy with these
people in this community, lad. Yeah.
Of course he does. He's af. He's a [ __ ] Yeah. Anyways,
don't know. And it's his daddy's money
as well. That 13 grand in is his daddy's money.
It's his daddy's money as well. That's
not his money. That's his daddy's money.
Oh, that's daddy's money. That's daddy's money. Daddy's. Yeah,
my phone needs to uh
he's just jealous because people are
going out and they've got money and he's sat skinn.
That's why bro
cause people skin and he doesn't even
know what people have or they don't
have. Silly little virgin. [gasps]
I know. He's a proper virgin, isn't he?
Proper proper virgin. Proper virgin is it? Uh, right. 76%.
We'll be going soon, lad.
They little meeting,
huh? Yeah, that's never happening, bro.
They've got too much anxiety to meet
each other on here. That's never going
to happen. They've got too much anxiety
to meet each other. So, that's never happening.
That's never happening in a million
years. All right. So, yeah.
This is what I mean with these weirdos.
They say that people are skin. you prove
that you got more than them
and then they they they try to gross on
you. They're losers. They're absolute
losers. Well, I'm on it until Monday,
then I'm off for two weeks. So, come on.
Yeah, I'm going out today. That's sending it. One 7.
But yeah, they never meet and they've
got too much anxiety to Yeah,
such a virgin. You would have thought
these people would just go on with their
own [ __ ] lives in it.
Let me see.
They're not going to do it, bro. I've
already told you they're not going to do
it. It's just games with these people.
It's just silly little immature games.
They need to grow the [ __ ] up. They need
to get a life. They need to get laid and
they need to stop this YouTube [ __ ] And
they need to grow the [ __ ] up.
Yeah, I'm out in a bit, bro.
[ __ ] It's just self projecting. His
disability is so severe that someone
said he can't afford trainers, so he
bought some. So what? Because somebody
proved you wrong, they're disabled.
Sadly, he can't afford a girlfriend or a
car, and he's never buying either.
Already had a girlfriend, already been
with women. This is what I mean with
these people. It's just constant self-p
projection. That's why I come up with
this like for a week, two weeks, because
it's constant self-p projection.
And when you see people talk about
themselves every single day, it's just
like, bro, it's sad to see people talk
about themselves. And then you kind of
lose bra and then you kind of lose brain
cells as well. Everything is about these
fat, ugly people. And I get sick of
repeating myself, which is why I come
off of it for like a couple of weeks.
It's the same atmosphere. It's like the
same vibe every time you come on here
with these mongos.
[ __ ] it. I'm gonna post a meal tomorrow,
lad. I'm gonna post a meal tomorrow and um
if I can go for a meal, maybe. And then
I'll just be off for like two weeks,
lad. Just the same repeating people, isn't it?
I know he's a sad bastard. Anyways, I'm
gone and I'll be live late for like 5
minutes or like 10 minutes um when I'm
out and about. So
yeah, I'll see you all later.
Yeah, man. Over and out. Peace. I'll be
live later 100% even for like 5 10
minutes. So you'll see me later. So
yeah, hopefully this hopefully this
football bet wins and um yeah, see you