It's [ __ ] bad now. >> [laughter]
>> It's a [ __ ] madness, man.
I'm only at two numbers.
I'm only at [ __ ] two numbers, bro.
What the [ __ ]
One of them was sober. It's a load of [ __ ]
>> Roll on free. Roll on free. I'm [ __ ]
out of here. Roll on.
I get back. I f
I want two cocktails again. I'm [ __ ] [laughter]
I got two numbers, but it's [ __ ] bad,
bro. [ __ ] mad.
I got one sober, one drunk, mate. I've
been sending it. I'm mad. It's too hard,
man. It's too [ __ ] hard, bro.
It's too hard, mate. this country
and I haven't in three weeks. [ __ ] yolo, bro.
I have been sent it like a [ __ ]
bro. And it's hard, bro. I done five
sober and I got one and then I got one
drunk, bro. I got like [ __ ] 20
if they're too stuck up in this country.
Hey, it's not better than that. It's [ __ ] hard.
I get to sending it
when I got
[ __ ] hard, bro. It's too hard.
They're all stuck up, bro. upstairs
or drink the thing.
>> Aaron, where you from?
>> Sri Lanka. >> Where?
>> I'm born here, but my parents from Sri Lanka.
>> Where are you in London? Where am I
from? Oh wow. >> Don't
just have to go up and take some cocktail.
It's so hard, but I'm out of here.
>> Yeah, man. 11.
Watch out. Watch out.
Yeah, bro. It's a [ __ ] madness. Like
I tune on my shoulder. That's bit.
That's bit as [ __ ]
That is still more people,
bro. I [ __ ]
I don't I got two numbers. I got one of
them sober. I got one sober. She's from up north pissing out.
Oh, [ __ ] it. Okay.
She was [ __ ] over there.
I can't find her.
I already done them women over there. I
got so many, bro.
So many, bro. We need to wait. There's
no one here. I've already done them all, mate.
That is so bitter,
>> bro. I don't I got two numbers.
The same boyfriend [ __ ] every time, bro.
I'm gone in three weeks. I'm out of here.
But bro, the thing is, yeah, it only
going to piss me off. It don't piss me
off because I know it will always be the same.
It will always be the same. I'm not pissed off.
It will always be the same. It's like
man said, isn't it?
That is bit, bro.
>> Yeah, I'll do it in the pub. I'll do in
That was [ __ ]
That is bit [laughter] but man.
I got one sober. It was pissing rain.
It's not empty, lad. It's not empty, bro.
I chatted him up, but I had a boyfriend. Same [ __ ]
It's so funny, bro. It's just
I want two as well. [laughter]
Right. I'm going to try and chat some
things up. I'll be back. If I chat them
up. See you.