Hey, stop.
Easy. Easy on the
mate. I got some video to go, mate.
I got a video to go.
I've got a video. I've got a video to put up. [laughter]
up for a man. [ __ ] your man, bro. Let me
put this video off, Cad
[ __ ] He won't have none of it.
[ __ ] [ __ ] That's not true,
mate. I [ __ ] own them.
I [ __ ] own a them.
Cheers, mate. Oh, I own them.
All right, bro. [ __ ] I got four
numbers. I know it's terrible, but [laughter] [ __ ]
>> smells like piss, bro. It
>> What's that?
>> Smells like piss, doesn't it?
>> You know, my phone was giving off. He
says it's the tourist.
>> Say again, bud.
>> My son was saying
>> Yeah, man. Where you from? Ireland.
>> From the north. North Island. >> Eastond.
>> Yeah, you can tell by the accent. Well,
where would you guess? Cuz I I would
guess straight away you
>> Oh, yeah. But I see I I said London. >> Yeah.
>> London though. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. The [ __ ]
>> You can't get it right all the time. [ __ ] me.
>> I met To be fair, bro. I met loads of uh
>> I met loads of Irish people today. All right.
>> What's that?
>> You Irish love drinking, isn't it? You
love the drink.
>> We love the party.
>> Yeah, of course. And that's good.
>> That's same in Belfast. >> Yeah.
>> You want to see Belfast and boyfriend?
>> Yeah. See all what would you say is
better, Dublin or Belfast?
But I love Guinness. So I'm I'm a Guinness fan.
>> Have you watched the Netflix thing on Guinness? >> Never.
>> Excuse me. Yeah. Here. I was in Dublin Camp. >> Yeah.
>> Boom. Boom. Boom. See the I sing along
the live music. Hard to beat.
>> Yeah. Hard to beat.
>> So Belfast, right?
>> So maybe maybe I'll do Friday in Belfast
and Saturday Dublin. So >> yeah.
>> Yeah. I've never been to Ireland. I've
been to Scotland and the world. Never been Ireland.
>> Just seen you. Oh, see if you go to
Belfast. Let's go work out whatever cheapest
>> the buses and trains are every hour.
>> Okay. See Dublin. See Dar. >> Yeah.
>> It's like this here. Boston.
>> Boston. Yeah.
>> Boston all the way through the year.
>> And Irish people friendly tourists in
London. They're [ __ ]
I say except for except for East London,
north, west, south, but East London's okay.
>> And you've noticed that as well. I'm
sorry. You know how many times have you
been to London? Skin it. Skin get it back.
>> Not that many. Not that many. I was here
last December playing the I was here for
the Olympics. That's the last time.
>> Yeah. I I lived by the Olympics.
>> Like 10 minutes away. West Ham Stadium.
West Ham Stadium. 10 minutes away. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. There is
a fondest. It's different.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> It's different. It's full of [ __ ] [laughter]
>> you know. Yeah.
>> Apart from the ones east long.
>> I feel like sometimes I've traveled all
over the country, right? And wherever
I've gone, I've never thought I was
better than anyone. >> Yeah.
>> Like I go to the most deprived areas and
I'm friendly to everyone because I
prefer people that are friendly. I don't
think I'm better than anyone.
>> Yeah. But in London, unfortunately, they
do. I don't know what what
>> I don't know what they want. I don't
know what they have. No idea.
>> Yeah. Yeah. But whenever I come to London, right,
>> I think to myself,
>> how could I afford to live here?
>> It's expensive. Yeah.
>> You buy or you rent?
>> Um, I rent.
>> Yeah. Cuz my son, he's he's in a process of renting.
>> A twobedroom apartment. I don't know
where it is. >> Yeah. >> 2,200.
>> It's like if you got out for a drink in
London. I remember last time I went out
was six weeks ago. I went out the Friday
and by the Sunday spent about500 don't
know what they weren't hotels it weren I
don't do drugs it weren't where the [ __ ]
did you go
in here in here is cheap
>> we went to a couple of pubs I went up I
got uh three double
>> rum on the boat
>> right £37
>> [ __ ] for sake
>> it's ridiculous
>> back home that's like a mortgage Yeah.
Yeah. But I heard Dublin's expensive,
isn't it? Like if you if you go That's
expensive, is it?
>> It it is. But then Dublin, I don't know
whe you know this or not. >> Yeah.
>> Like the south of Ireland used to be poor. >> Yeah.
>> It used to be like
>> it's now the third or fourth richest
country in the world for head.
>> Like it's rich.
>> It's rich.
>> It is rich.
>> I know a lot of Irish people got [ __ ]
money. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> So, it it is I go down I was down there
at Campbell Bar about a month ago. Do
you know who I went to see?
>> Let me uh
>> I went to see Robbie Williams. Okay.
>> He was and I went to see if Have you
heard of sexiles? >> Never.
>> Oh, the sex. If you look up in the marquee
about this place here.
>> Yeah. Weather.
>> David Boy, Prince. >> Yeah.
>> Adam and the aunts. You look up. They've
all played here.
>> The biggest bands in the world have played here.
>> This is like this used to be like a real hub,
>> you know.
Yeah. That's used to be real.
>> I didn't even know that.
>> No, I didn't know.
>> Is there
just making friends, guys? Making friends.
Just making friends, guys. >> [laughter]
>> making friends, guys. [laughter] [ __ ] hell.