mad. Um,
and you need to stop calling me mate.
I'm not your [ __ ] mate.
These people on here, bro, they
seriously twist things. It's mad. [ __ ] mad.
This woman right here on my channel.
Well, when you talk the way you do, it's
no wonder you aren't getting anywhere.
I'm so dumb, bro.
But at the end of the day, I put these
videos out there to show Timmy that I
don't give a [ __ ] what people think and
I don't want to talk about this anymore ever again.
I don't know why that's still there,
bro. We are literally going around in circles.
It's [ __ ] toxic, bro.
We change up this content, lads. Seriously.
I'm going to do it in a bit, bro.
Cuz a guy is so full of [ __ ] It's
because of the guy's skin color. That's
what it is.
Yeah, I'll do it right now, bro.
I got a few numbers. I got five.
I'm not doing this anymore, lads.
Listen, hold on a minute. Right. You
want to You want to talk about the what
I've said, mate. Listen, at the end of
the day, I've got approaching videos on
my channel, love,
I've got approaching videos on my
channel. You don't know what I've gone
through with women. So, don't even And
at the end of the day, yeah, I'm not
doing this [ __ ] anymore.
Ain't doing this [ __ ] anymore, lad.
Yeah. You believe what you want to
believe. That's it. I'm not interested.
I don't give a [ __ ] anymore. I should
have went out today. It was toxic. End
the story. I don't care. I would have
just drew this video to this little [ __ ]
Yeah, cuz he's twisting things in it.
It's a race thing. Yeah, it's a race
thing with this guy, bro. That's what it
is. I know him better than he knows his [ __ ] self
about No wonder I'm get Do you know the
amount of [ __ ] I had to deal with women
today, Autumn? Oh, you don't know, mate.
You really really don't know.
But keep thinking of women are in the
right. Do you know why? Because I don't
give a [ __ ] Like you can't get through
to someone that doesn't give a [ __ ] You understand?
I dealt with it today many times where I
had somebody literally speak to me and
then I got cop blocked. People giving
attitude, people pretending they've got
boyfriends. I just walked away. People
getting jealous. It's so toxic.
It's so toxic. I know. I shouldn't have
went out today to be honest. I literally
got cop blocked the [ __ ] out of like I
honest to God
was speaking to this woman. She was born
a day before me. She was born a day
before me. Yeah. And we was talking like
this was this was wasn't one you saw by
the way. and her friend was cop blocking
the [ __ ] out of me. The bouncer and all
of that stuff. It's just not worth it.
That's why I don't go out. It's just toxic.
And I've noticed it's gotten worse and
worse and worse and worse and worse.
People projecting their [ __ ] drug
addiction onto you as well.
I'm done, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] I'm so dumb.
You know, they get more and more and
more stuck up these women as well. It
gets worse and worse and worse,
worse and worse and worse. These women
are stuck up as [ __ ] I think I got two
women's numbers that were from France.
One number, I think I got about five
numbers. The only woman that was all
right today was one woman from up north
and she seemed all right and we just
exchanged numbers. I messaged her
tomorrow. Literally, that's like the
only woman that seemed all right.
Everyone's stuck up here. It's like it's
a waste of time to even try to speak to
someone. And it's toxic. It's toxic,
mate. You know, it's not even just about
the money. It's so toxic.
Stuck up their own ass. And at the end
of the day, I don't care about the
trainers and the jeans. I I wanted to
buy them anyways. Um but it does seem
it's gotten worse and worse and worse.
Um this country with these women and
people. It's not even just women, it's
people. That's why I don't go out.
That's why I chill and do my own thing.
But again, all you're trying to blame me
when I've shown women leading me on and
stuff. I I don't I'm not trying to
convince you anything. You think what
you want to think. I don't give a [ __ ]
at the end of the day.
There was the constant boyfriend [ __ ]
again today. But I may not expect that [ __ ] lad.
I mean, I expect that. I mean, I did
expect the boyfriend [ __ ] and that, but
I mean, like, the other [ __ ] was weird.
Of course, I expect the boyfriend [ __ ]
It's never going to change. Yeah.
So, yeah. Uh, to get to tell you,
Autumn, the women that you're
the men that you they these are the men
that you choose.
These are the men. No, they don't have
boyfriends. And again, I'm not having
this conversation. They don't have
boyfriends. They don't have boyfriends.
There was a good couple of people that
was trying to chat to the same women
in in this bar and they all claim they
got boyfriends. That and and the thing
is, Autumn, when you're moaning about
men, you're moaning about men that you
choose. Those are the men that you
choose to go for. Yeah. Those are the
men that you choose to go for. All of
these men that you moan about, they're
the men that you liked. The women that I
moan about are only women that I come
across. I don't come across any other
woman. So I I can't have a different
opinion. Those are men that you choose,
lad. Yeah. No, it's not. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. It's not, mate. No, it's
[ __ ] not trying to bully a woman.
Why? By telling her about herself. Jay
Willow, listen. I'm not Timmy, mate. I'm
not [ __ ] Timmy. And I need to do a
video to LT, by the way, as well. I need
to put him in his place.
Yeah. And I'm not like these little
trolls that try to wind people up. Yeah.
Yeah. You need a You need a truth, bro.
That's what you need. Yeah.
So, Autumn, the men that you moan about
are the men that you choose to go for.
The women I moan about are only the
women I ever come across. Big difference.
And you know how I can tell you right
now that you're full of [ __ ]
Why don't you meet me? Meet me tomorrow.
You want a man that doesn't cheat on you
and and all of this stuff that you moan
about other men,
you know? Why do you meet me tomorrow? Come on. Exactly.
Anyways, we're not having this
conversation about boyfriends. I mean,
I'm not having this conversation.
Boring. I know they're full of [ __ ] and
that's that. I'm not having this
conversation. There's no point in the
conversation. It's boring. We know
they're full of [ __ ] and and what's the
point of the conversation, lad? You know.
Yeah. I need to stop going out to be
fair. I mean, I don't go out. This was
the first time in six weeks. So, yeah.
I don't regret it to be honest. I mean,
you know, it is what it is.
That's why I don't go out Jay Willow
because there's too many stuck up
[ __ ] in this country now. You want to
keep sugar coating it and you want to
keep defending them. Jay Willow, I'm not
telling you what to do and what not to
do. I don't give a [ __ ] what you do. I'm
not asked what you do. You understand, lad?
Yeah. Kid in the weather spoons at 10:00
at night. Yeah. Okay. She's a kid. Okay,
bro. So, you understand? I don't give a
[ __ ] what you think, lad. I've been to
your city. I've been to more places than
you, Jay Willow. I don't give a [ __ ]
what you think. I don't want you I don't
want to convince you to think. Anyway,
just like LT is completely full of [ __ ]
using somebody being as work as an excuse, you know,
toxic. That's a word for it.
I don't give a [ __ ] mate. I'm 28.
And then there was a woman that was my
age and then she was trying to get like
give me her number and that and then her
friend cop blocked me. It's toxic.
Even if it's not the woman that you're
speaking to, it's so so so
toxic. And that was a perfect word for
it to be honest.
Yeah, it's toxic.
That's why I don't bother lad. So yeah,
[ __ ] pissing down here as well.
Harassing. Definitely wasn't harassing.
Definitely definitely wasn't harassing.
You little white knight.
Go away, you little white knight.
Yeah, [ __ ] off, you little white knight.
Nope. Didn't get turned down as well.
You're making stuff up. You're not going
to rage bait me. I'm not Timmy. You're
not going to rage bait me.
You're not going to rage bait me over
these [ __ ] So, there's no point.
You're not going to rage bait, lad.
Pointless. Point in trying to rage bait
me with your little white knight sings.
the little white knights. It's not gonna
work. Like, I'm the last person to be
trying this [ __ ] with.
I'm not angry at all.
What's there to be angry about, bro? We
know women are [ __ ] We know
they're all the same. What's there to be
angry about? Like, how many times have
we been saying the same old [ __ ] I'm
actually pretty calm, to be honest. I
just want to know what this LT's problem is.
We know what women are like. We know
women are all the same. What is that
supposed to be? A surprise or something?
Come on, man. No.
The [ __ ] am I angry about, man?
Women are all the same. What is it?
Didn't we already know that? Oh, come on, man.
Women playing games, women being stuck up.
Yeah. And you're a white knight. And
you're a white knight that's never going
to get laid.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We're talking about the bouncer thing.
We're not talking about the women thing.
We're talking the bouncer thing. I'm
going to put this LT in his place. Yeah.
I'm going to put this LT in his place,
bro. Yeah. Once and for all.
Yeah. I'm going to put him in his place.
No, I didn't I didn't delete any comments. Yeah,
harassing a woman. Well, your little
white knight comments don't bother me,
so there's no point bringing them on
here. You know,
little white knights. Like I said, man,
keep your opinions to yourself. If you
listen, I've said this multiple times.
If you want to sit there, keep defending
women all your life, being a virgin,
that's on you, bro. I don't care what
other people do with their life.
Yeah. I don't give a [ __ ] what you
people do. No, no. Women are the ones
that are narcissists. Uh, no, no, no,
no. All women are the ones that are
definitely definitely narcissists. That
is self-p projection right there. I can
literally give you a recent story I had
with a narcissistic woman. No, no, no.
Women are the ones that are narcissists.
Not me, mate.
Women are the one that's narcissists.
No, no, no. They're definitely
definitely the narcissist. And again,
I'm not going to sit here and explain
myself to you. You know, you keep
defending women, you keep being a
virgin, you keep white knighting. I
don't give a [ __ ] I'm not here to tell
people how to live their [ __ ] lives. Yeah.
You want to keep white knighting,
defending women, being a virgin all your
life, that's on you. I don't give a
[ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] what people do, man.
I'm not talking about you. I'm talking
about generally. These people that want
to sit there and defend women all their
life, I don't give a [ __ ]
You know, I'm I'm not asked. Let them be
virgins. I don't give a [ __ ]
M I told a guy about himself, which is
another thing that I'm going to be
bringing up to uh LT, and she wasn't
decent either. And that's not the point.
Whether he was with someone, you got
involved, someone told you about
yourself, and you shhat your pants. So
what was the [ __ ] point, you know?
Like I would have slapped him and his
bird up. [ __ ] mind your own [ __ ]
business, you [ __ ] if you watch that
video properly. Yeah, I literally told
you I put my trainers up on my trainers
are worth more than anything that you've got.
Yeah, good for her, man. Good for her.
Yeah, good for her. No one cares. Anyways, yeah.
Our women, you don't have a woman.
You're a virgin. You don't have women.
You're a virgin. I can assure you I've
been with more women than you. There's
no our woman. You're a virgin. You've
never been with a woman. Hence the white
knighting. They were laughing at me and
mocking me, mate. I told them to [ __ ]
back to where they come from again. Stop
twisting things to suit your narrative.
Mocking me. I told them to [ __ ] off back
to where they come from in the clearest
London accent I possibly could, mate. I
literally told them about themselves and
they sat there and done nothing. But we
all know that you people are always
going to twist things.
I said, "Fuck back to Newcastle. Did you
hear what I said?" And they was not
working. They literally was not working.
Yeah, they literally was not working.
Right. I told them to [ __ ] back to
Newcastle. Does that sound like someone
that scared of someone? Bro, this is
what I mean with you little weasels. You
continuously and constantly make up stuff.
Yeah. I I called him a little [ __ ]
little [ __ ] They need to learn to mind
their own business, these little
[ __ ] cuz they're not on no smoke.
They They act big in groups, but they're
not on no smoke. They're typical
[ __ ] All they can do is make sly
comments and I made sly comments back.
But we all know they're little [ __ ]
because we all know when crunch comes to
crunch they're not about it. Same thing
with this bouncer. Yeah. So
making sly comments but won't do
anything. I told him to [ __ ] back to Newcastle.
You little [ __ ] Acting as if I didn't
say that. You know, you make up things
that suit yourselves. You do the same
[ __ ] with [ __ ] Timmy. You know,
so yeah. You have a creepy. [ __ ] off,
you little [ __ ] [ __ ] Bye-bye, you
little white knight.
I done what I was told. No, I didn't.
No, I didn't. This is what I mean. You
always twist things. There's no point
with you little spasticated mongos. You
twist things, you little spastics.
That's what I mean with you little
spastics on here.
You spasticated bastards will always
twist things. I mean, for [ __ ] sake,
bro. There's a video of me sticking my
dick up a woman's throat and you still
say I'm a virgin. You little
spasticating mongos will always twist things.
I mean, for [ __ ] sake, we don't need
to block anyone to say that.
You little spastics always twist things
to suit your narrative. It's the same
thing with this LT. Because the guy was
at work. No, it's cuz the guy was black
and he got told about himself, right?
There's certain things people are
allowed to do in their workplace. Yeah.
Laughing at me. Yeah. And there's a
video of me telling them to [ __ ] back to
Newcastle. Their little [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah, I know. And I called him a little
[ __ ] and to [ __ ] back to Newcastle. And
there was four of them and one of me.
Everyone saw that.
And I told them to mind their own
business and I'll do what I want. Do you
know what I'm saying, lad? That's it, bro.
I told them I'll do what I want and [ __ ]
off back to Newcastle. The silly little
[ __ ] But again, you don't. And you
call people a virgin even when they
prove they've had sex. There's no
getting through to you spastics. Like
we've already been we've already
established that, right? We've already
established there's no getting through
to you little spasticated [ __ ] cuz
that's what you are. You're spastics on there.
I mean, [ __ ] hell, lad.
And I don't agree with LT. And I'll
explain and I'll explain exactly why
what he's saying is [ __ ] right?
It's cuz the person's black. That's not
because the person's at work. It's cuz
the person is black. And he knew he
would have got his ass whooped. That's
what it is.
Yeah, you people are completely full of [ __ ]
It's obvious, bro. You're full of [ __ ]
You little spastics. They laughed at me,
bro. I told them I'll do what I want.
[ __ ] Back to Newcastle. You little
[ __ ] You think anyone could talk to me
like that, bro? Do you think anyone
could talk to me like that? But they let
me talk to them about that and it was
one of me and four of them. So what was
the excuse for that one? LT,
you know, and another thing, I'm going
to bring that LJ thing up, bro. Lj come
here and he stood behind the gate and
done nothing. Yeah. And I and I'll
really whip it into him if he really
wants me to, bro. Yeah. He stood behind
the gate and done nothing. That is not
worth anyone's time since again that
hurts your ego by saying oh someone's
okay I'll word it for you differently
then right he stood behind a gate and
done nothing which is a waste of someone's time
yeah that's it I'm going to do a video
to this little [ __ ] right now anyways Yeah.