Joseph Far.
Don't feel too bad to be fair. [laughter]
All right. Few hiccups. But yeah, look
back on a video. Don't regret it. See,
when I do stuff and I'm drunk,
I don't regret it, mate. The same.
Everyone reacts to [ __ ] alcohol
differently, do I?
Not me, mate.
[ __ ] hell, man. Madness,
bro. That barrel [ __ ] That's the
football I need to show by the way. I
was so close, man. Big up me.
Big the [ __ ] up me, bro. Yeah, man.
Oh, Jesus. What the [ __ ] was that all
about yesterday? It's toxic. It's
negative. I was thinking of doing a
video on this. Yeah. about how attitude
people's attitude is getting worse. I
still haven't text any of them five
numbers. Was it five numbers? I think it
got five numbers. It's either four or five.
Yeah, four or five. Hey man, how we doing?
Bro, these people on here always twist
things, Cory. Like you show them clear
evidence or something and they always
find ways to twist things. It's like
proper proper [ __ ] up. I don't
understand it. Like I generally
generally don't. They'll do anything to
twist things, bro. It's weird.
Yeah. Like LT is always full of excuses,
you know? When we all know, bro, that
when I went to Kenji's area and his
workplace, no one was saying, "No, we
recorded you cuz he's at work."
Like, it's it's [ __ ] It's they're
full of [ __ ] every time, bro. And I
don't regret anything cuz I know what
I'm doing when I'm drunk, you know?
Like it's not like I'm going to wake up
and think, "Oh, look. [ __ ] them, bro.
You don't even know what some woman said
to some guy yesterday, bro, who I was
approaching with." And it wasn't even about me.
Yeah, they've all got the same attitude.
I don't care about that, but I'm like,
"Yeah, whatever. I don't care about I'm
not going to be depressed cuz I know
like what it is here." But still, the
thing I noticed though is the attitude
is definitely getting worse. I was I was
I approached with this guy. He was he
was dressed as a captain, fancy dress.
We got drinking talking. I was like,
"Oh, do you want to do a twoman thing?
I'll approach her. You approach her,
brother." We was talking to these
there's four of them, mate. And it was
we speaking to two of them. And I said,
"Oh, yeah. I'm just trying to help uh I
just called him my friend. Like just
trying to help [snorts] my friend meet
someone, bro." She turned around and
said that he needs to sort his forehead
out that he's got a big forehead.
And I'm thinking, what is this? Even
though it wasn't about me, she said,
"Oh, oh, you're handsome." And I was
like, "No, that's not the point. Hold
on." She was saying, "Oh, he might need
to sort his forehead out first." And I'm
thinking, "Am I am I hearing things,
bro? Are we are we am I actually hearing
things?" And it wasn't even about me.
Obviously, I swear to God, it wasn't
about me, bro. My mom's life it wasn't
about me. And I'm thinking, but Cory,
they tell us about having bad
personality, yet they've just insulted
this guy. Tried to knock his confidence
down. Do you understand? It's
It's mental, bro. I couldn't believe
what I was hearing. Madness. Madness.
So, they're allowed to walk around with
attitude like that. And even and it
wasn't even about about me, bro, you
know? So, they're allowed to walk around
with attitude like that, right? And oh,
we've got the better personality. Boo.
Do you know what I'm saying, bro? Like,
and do you know what I I had yesterday
as well? I I was speaking to there was a
couple of people that I was speaking to
that were right. Right. So, we was about
to like exchange numbers and then their
friends would completely cop like their
friends would get jealous. Like, we was
just about to like exchange numbers.
Then they were like, "Oh, uh, well, you
want a number straight away?" They all
walk around with the same attitude.
Like, and that weren't even about me, bro.
There's like they're so like stuck up
you you can't even talk to them. It's madness, bro.
Really, really is madness.
It really is, lad.
It's toxic as well. I don't really go
out much, Cory, because it's just Yeah,
like I said, it's just toxic.
That's why I tend to
not go out as much.
as I said
as they I don't know it is toxic bro it
is very that's why I like peace and
quiet bro you just get addicted to the
peace and quiet this is what I mean
um but yeah I got four numbers so we'll Yeah,
I done five approaches sober yesterday. Five sober and uh
yeah I'm five sober
and I got one number.
[snorts] Yeah, bro. One team let me down
yesterday for [ __ ] £2 fucking£37.
All I needed was Spenny more to [ __ ]
score. Oh my god.
I need to stick with two teams, bro.
The guy was telling me I'm shaking. Did
you see his leg, bro? His leg was
shaking, bro. If you look at his leg,
right? How did I not pick up on that? I
always say I always there's always
things that I want to say that I realize
after cuz you're so in the moment, but I
mean, I said all I wanted really. Mind
your own [ __ ] business and [ __ ] off
back to where you come from. I mean,
there's there there's nothing more to really uh
I want, bro. The guy's leg was shake.
Did you see his leg, bro? I was stood in
the same place. Yeah. Furthermore, why
are people getting involved?
Did you see the Weather Spoons videos?
Like, they knew not to go there with me,
bro. They knew not to go there with me.
But it's toxic, bro. And like, this is
what I mean by it's toxic. It's very, very toxic.
Um, negative. Uh there was another guy
as well. Um and you didn't see this and
he was walking away. He says, "Oh, you
need to stop taking cocaine." And I
said, "Bro, I'm not a crackhead like
you." Yeah. Stop projecting your [ __ ]
onto me. I don't do drugs. And that's
the thing. And Yeah.
Yeah. She was. And And the thing is,
it's people that are getting involved
when you're talking to their friend.
That's what I don't understand. It's not
even the ones that you're approaching.
It's them getting involved. But that her
talking about that guy's forehead, bro,
that annoys me. Even though it wasn't
about me, it doesn't matter that it
wasn't about me. It's an ick. It's an
ick like like a woman would be put off
what a guy does. Even if a guy's not
talking about her, that is mad, bro.
You're handsome to me doesn't mean
anything, bro. When you're talking about
someone's forehead, why you why would
you even say something like that?
It's mad, bro. That's not even funny.
That's mad, you know.
And then there was other guys speaking
to them as well. I see other guys I'm
thinking, "Oh yeah, they're getting
somewhere here." ones that I would speak
to and I like, "Oh, they they said they
had boyfriends to them as well." So why
the [ __ ] do these women go out, waste
their time, waste their money to tell
everyone they've got boyfriends?
It's mad. Well, why? Why? Do you know
how [ __ ] expensive going out is now?
And it's cold. It was raining as well yesterday,
you know. Why do they do that if they're
just going to tell everyone they have
boyfriends? And there was about three,
four different guys. And I'm thinking,
oh yeah, they're getting in somewhere
now. And there's like, nope, they're
getting the same [ __ ] So I'm thinking,
why why would you even go out? Does that
make sense, Richie? To me, that doesn't
make any sense.
I got a woman's number yesterday from up
north. I got two French women's numbers.
Yeah, it was only the French women that
seemed to be okay. Um, and I got another
number. I don't know if it's real. And
then another one. But they've all got
the same attitude. Like if they're from
Kent, right? Then they're a bit nicer,
but a little bit nicer. But it's still like,
why? It's expensive going out. I I got
an escort yesterday as well. I spent
about over £200.
It's just madness why they would go out
to tell everyone they've got boyfriends.
It's [ __ ] mental.
And then you have to deal with sniff
heads as well.
Toxic. Very, very toxic.
And then people seem to have to get
involved. Why are they getting involved
when I'm arguing with a bouncer? Is it
any of your business?
Is it any of your business? No. Just
shut up. And that's not even me being rude.
That's another thing. I didn't even
notice his leg until I Oh, bro. I didn't
even notice that. Oh, yeah. I I I
approached someone yesterday that were
35. They were 35 and they said I'm too
young for them.
And then it's their friends that cop
block them as well,
which is weird cuz it's not even them.
They the friends actually cop block you
when you're getting in there,
right? It's madness, isn't it, Chloe?
It's actually madness.
They've literally all got the same attitude.
If it's a rarity you would find someone
that's different, lad, right? Uh
it would be on the street, mate, or
something somewhere else, but a bar in a club. Cuz
what I don't understand, Cory, yet is
how they say that they're not the same
when they literally have the same attitude.
They walk around with the same attitude,
the same mannerisms.
And again, I don't care if none of these
numbers reply. I don't care. I expect
it. It's to be expected.
You know, it's I I'm think one of them's
got a good chance of replying at least.
And that was the most Yeah, it's getting
worse though, bro. It's getting worse. Wait,
I got an escort. Anyways, I paid 120 for
a [ __ ] One [ __ ] 20 madness. £120
for a [ __ ] [ __ ]
We've done somebody in the past couple
of days, mate. We
are talking about that guy's forehead as well,
but they want to try and tell other men
that they've got a bad personality.
Yeah, he was he was he was dressed as a
captain. There was a few like it was a
dress up thing. So,
and there was one I was speaking to, bro,
and she was born a day before me and
she's a year older than me, and we was
talking. She was about to give me her
number. Her friend come in and started
like dramas for no reason. She's like,
"Oh, uh, yeah, uh, can someone stop?"
And I was like, "What the fuck?" Like,
her friend is sat there talking to me.
She's about to exchange numbers. We were
getting on. We were getting to know each
other. And then all of a sudden, she's
started dramas. Not like fights or
anything, but like, how do I explain it?
She was just trying to stop me and stop
her friend us talking to each other. I'm
thinking, "What the fuck?"
So, it's toxic, bro. It really, really,
really is toxic.
That is weird.
So they does their friends not want
somebody to find someone then,
huh? Does their friends not want someone
to find someone? I don't understand cuz
I'm sure they've moaned about their ex
to you many times and then you know it's
weird. It is it is very very strange.
Sometimes their friend will just sit
there and then they'll talk to you
normally and they won't get involved and
it's nice, you know, but uh I don't know
why their friends are getting involved
when they're talking to you and you're
talking to them.
Oh, and I got banned uh from this club.
I got banned from this club
cuz three months ago I called someone a
[ __ ] So I'm banned forever, by the way.
Yeah, I called a staff member a [ __ ]
cuz she's being stuck up.
I mean, it is it is fun once in a while
going out, bro.
It is fun to be fair, seeing how toxic
it is, how bad it is.
Yeah, I literally I called her a [ __ ]
She was being No, I think I said, "Oh,
she was acting like a bit of a [ __ ] and
I didn't say it to her and I got banned forever."
Yeah. Yep. Now, I thought it was
something to do with someone on YouTube,
but it wasn't. I think I said on YouTube
to someone that she's acting a bit of a
[ __ ] and I got banned forever,
huh? Madness, isn't it?
The the staff can walk around with
attitude, but you call them if you tell
them they're being a bit of a [ __ ] you
get banned forever, mate. You get banned
forever. Who is who runs this country,
bro? Like, who actually makes up these rules?
Who makes up these [ __ ] rules, lad?
Really? Really? Who [ __ ] does?
It's insane, bro. It actually is insane, man. [clears throat]
The new Ed Matthews. I don't think so, bro.
I don't think so, lad.
But it is toxic. It is It's not funny,
bro. Cuz these things can escalate.
And they only act big when they're in
groups. That's another thing. And I'm
not scared of them, bro.
You know, that's the thing.
LT trying to say that the guy was at
work. It's always excuses. It's always
excuses. If you listen right to what I
said in that video, I said, "Come and
meet me after work. I'll give you my
number." Did I not say that, bro? Did I
not say that? Right. And anyone that
who's about it would have gave me their
number and met me after work.
Do not kiss up your teeth to me, bro. Do you know?
Don't [ __ ] kiss up your [ __ ] teeth
to me, bro. And the woman, there was a
woman sticking up for me as well, like
an older woman. She was like, "Oh, why
why are you asking him for ID? He's
clearly of age." No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. And her friends was like, "Oh,
let's get uh let's just get in." Like
they they were on his side. But she was
very much saying, "Why are you asking
this man for ID when he's clearly of age?"
You know, she was like on my side, but
obviously she was with other people and
they wanted to get in. So they were just
like, "Oh, just shut up, you know, so we
can get in. Simple. Yeah.
She was actually on my side. It must
have been, I don't know, 30s, 40s. She
was on my side.
She was like, "What the fuck?"
This is a random woman cuz it is
ridiculous. It's not like The thing is,
um, Cory, it's not a It's not a licensed
club, right? Whereas licensed clubs,
obviously, they have to scan an ID or
like a casino. I get that. But that he
was doing it to show off, right?
And then he started kissing his teeth. Yeah.
That is a is a pub. That is that is a
Weather Spoons. Yeah. And I went into a
pub after that and they didn't ask me
for ID, bro. No. If it's like a club and
stuff, you know, it's a bit different.
asking me a grown ass man.
You know you mad asking me for ID. Nah,
bro. You ain't asking me for ID, bro.
That's that's weird. Do you know I've
not been IDed?
Sometimes my sisters still get IDed. I
don't get IDed. Uh when I buy cigarettes
sometimes for my mom, whatever. I never get IDed.
Never. Cuz I look like a mate. It's pretty clear.
Yeah, it's pretty clear,
right, that I'm of age.
I was thinking of tipping that the drink
on that Australian girl. I was very
tempted, bro. I was very tempted, bro.
But I just didn't. Very tempted.
I said to the guy, "If you want to meet
me after work, they're all stuck, bro.
You don't know how many stuck up [ __ ]
I had to deal with yesterday, bro. Oh my
god. It's getting worse. It's getting
worse. And Thailand's almost finished,
by the way. It will be finished in 10
years, bro. You don't know the amount of
stuck up women I had to deal with yesterday, bro.
They all walk around with the same attitude
literally for people. People that are
not the same as well. And they weren't
even insulting me.
There was this guy that they insulted
um talking about his forehead. And I'm
thinking, I don't care if you've called
me handsome, that is an ick. You're
talking about the guy's forehead. Why
are you Why are you insulting people's physical appearance?
That's not nice. If somebody started
talking about you, you've got no tits,
you would go mad. So, you shouldn't be
insulting people. And some white guy
they were saying it to.
Yeah, but you get my point. Like it's
Why are they talking about the guy's forehead? You know,
well, you you said you talk about
personality. Yeah. And people go for
personality and that's what you go with
every time, right? Yeah. Why are they
talking about my man's forehead, bro? I
don't care that that's not you're not
talking you're not talking about me.
That's [ __ ] rude as [ __ ] you know?
And then you deal with these [ __ ] cokeheads,
right? Trying to give it a big when
they're with their boys.
It's mad. Absolute madness.
I still don't back down, bro. Still
don't back down.
Why do they seem to think everyone's a
crackhead like them? But I barely drink
nowadays. I don't vape. I don't smoke.
Why would I be on crack? Bro, you're Why
would I be on cocaine? I said to him,
"Bro, you're the cokehead.
You're projecting. Go away, you little
projector. I didn't record that one,
bro. That was like by the weather
spoons, but he just walked off.
Yeah. Nah, bro. Not me. Not me, bro.
Definitely definitely not me, bro.
So, yeah. Very toxic. It is very toxic.
It's getting worse, bro. It is getting
worse. I can't remember it being as bad
as that, to be fair.
And what's London Taylor saying now,
Bob? He's not saying nothing cuz he
knows that the only reason he was
sticking up for that guy is because the
guy was black
is because the guy was black,
not because he was working. Cuz he told
me before, there's a story, right,
that he was in McDonald's with his
friend and his friend kept starting on a
bouncer time and time and time and time
and time and time again. You know what
they're about to done? They're about to
smash these teeth in. Yeah. Did the guy
lose his badge? No, bro. You could have
easily escalated that if he wanted to
cuz if he kept running up his mouth, I
would have got in his face. I would have
got in his face, bro. And then and then
he could defend himself. Yeah. If he if
he if he started running his mouth, bro,
I would have made it easy for him to defend himself.
Yeah. It's cuz the guy's black. You
constantly twist things on here, bro. Yeah.
What about them four people that I told
I told them to go [ __ ] themselves. [ __ ]
back to Newcastle. What about them? No
one No one stood up. No one done
nothing. They were laughing at me. But I
was laughing at them. I was arguing with
five different people, you know.
Madness. Absolute madness. Blad.
Does he think we just randomly started
on a guy because they're black? No, I
don't think it was that, mate.
Imagine that. A grown ass man
being IDed by someone that's not even
from here. And I'm not even racist.
Imagine that, bro.
And he's talking about me shaking. His
[ __ ] leg was on our [ __ ] shaking,
wasn't it? Again, I didn't even notice
that when I was arguing with them. like
your leg is shaking. Another pedigree
dog, you know,
you know, they always twist things and
they're still and you're still going
about LJ, bro. L stood behind the gate
and he done nothing.
Nothing at all. Yeah.
I think they were talking about my belly
cuz I've got like a bit a tiny bit of a
beer belly. Not a beer belly, but And
I'm thinking, "Oh, is that all you got, bro?
Is that all you got, lad? Is that all
you?" Bro, the irony is my trainers
probably cost more than all of their outfits.
But it's not good, bro. It's not uh It
isn't a good thing. It isn't a good thing, bro.
It's not. It's It's toxic. It's very
very very very toxic, you know.
It's narcissistic if you think about it as well.
Very, very narcissistic.
But I don't understand why they're getting involved.
That's why I don't understand why
they're getting involved when it's got
nothing to do with them. It's strange, bro.
But yeah, the the woman did defend me.
You always deal with [ __ ]
and it's not about who's right, who's
scared, who's it's like, do you really
want to be dealing with that [ __ ]
Like I said, that's why I don't really
That's why I don't really go out drinking much, you know?
There was this guy, right,
ous and he said, "Oh, you shouldn't
generalize." I said, "I'll generalize as
much as I want." Um, it didn't turn into
a fight or anything. I said I said I'll
make a deal with you, right? This was
just like a friendly chat. I get shown
different. I stop generalizing. How's
that one? How's that one, mate? I will stop generalizing
when I'm show when I'm proven wrong.
You didn't say anything to that. Yeah. [ __ ] idiot.
Absolute [ __ ] idiot.
>> [cough and snorts] >> Yeah.
One second, lad.
It's [ __ ] mental, ain't it, Cory?
[ __ ] TV. I don't know. Oh,
madness, lad. [ __ ] mad.
That's what it is. Mad.
Can't be ass, lad.
Right. He's come from another country. I
don't give a [ __ ] his skin color. And
you're asking me for ID when I'm clearly
clearly of age.
Clearly of age. Do you understand me?
Like I'm [ __ ]
um it's not like I just turned 18 or I
was 22 and I had no beard and I was 23
and I had no beard and no no and you
definitely generally looked younger and
you're asking me for ID.
Is that what you're really doing?
You know, oh you never stand up for a
man. And then when you stand up to a
man, so so you don't stand up to a man.
And then when you stand up to a man, oh
well, he's at work and he can't do
anything. Okay. What about them other
four people that weren't at work then? You know,
I've I've done it to people before that
were [ __ ] white and Polish, you know,
asking for ID to show off. I told him
it's his little fragile ego. I said to
the woman, "Yeah, he's asking people for
ID because he's got a little ego. It
makes him it makes him feel better,
you know." That's what I said to her.
And then he starts giving me a dirty
look. I was like, "Bro, do not look at
me like that, man.
[ __ ] idiot. [ __ ] faggot." Yeah.
No, I'm not Albanian. You're mad. Well, yeah,
it is negative, bro. I don't like that
kind of negativity.
It is very very negative. And we're not
even just talking about the women.
So yeah, England's the same old England, Richie.
And then you say that someone's acting
like a bit of a [ __ ] and you get banned forever.
Madness, isn't it?
Everyone's got the same attitude. I
don't know if it's the same thing in
[ __ ] uh Newcastle.
Well, I haven't been for a long time. Yeah. Yep. [ __ ]
It is a madness, isn't it, lad?
women have exactly the same attitude.
I'm I'm going to do I'm I'm going to
talk about this on a video as well.
You have immigrants asking you for ID
when you clearly look of age.
Allow it, bro. Come on now. It's embarrassing.
So, what are you suggesting? If I hit
him, he would have defended himself,
bro. If I hit him, he would have got knocked out,
bro. He would have been knocked the [ __ ]
out. He wouldn't be defending himself.
you know, one punch and it would be over, you know.
Yeah, I went to an escort at the end of the night, whatever.
But I didn't spend that much. I don't
know how I spent [ __ ] so much money last time.
No, but I mean I' I've put a porno out
there and they still call me virgins.
They still call me virgins. Like
the LT can't fathom a black person
losing. I don't know what it is with
with this race thing. I don't know what
it is, but he can't
um accept the fact that sometimes black people lose.
I don't understand why. What? What the
[ __ ] bro? It's like he's got this
little ego about his race. It's mad.
Reminds me of the skint virgin in the bedset.
Um, in many ways,
but I mean in terms of like the ego and that
Yeah, she dropped my drink as well.
That's another thing. Why did one of
them drink my drink?
It's very [ __ ] toxic, is it? It's very toxic.
Yeah, I told him about themself. Bro,
stop getting yourself involved. You
don't want that smoke. Trust me, you
don't want that. Because when someone
because when someone says something back
to you, you don't like it. We're not
even talking about fighting. When
somebody says something back to you, you
don't like it. So, stop getting yourself involved.
So, stop getting involved. You know,
I was speaking and that Australian one,
her friend couldn't even say anything
because she knew I was in a right. She
said nothing. It was her friend. Do they
do they not want people to meet someone? Like,
do they not want someone to meet someone
or something? cuz they cop block a lot
of their [ __ ] friends to be fair.
It's not even funny, bro. I don't know
how you can think it's funny, Richie. I
don't think it's funny me.
I don't think it's funny me, lad.
It's weird. I got one woman's number,
but she's from up north, so doesn't matter. Um,
yeah. It's funny how LT was there
straight away, wasn't it? When he saw
the black guy.
That's funny, mate.
I didn't tell. Apparently, I lost.
Apparently, I was scared in the guy.
Which one did I tell about himself? What
did I say?
Was I shaking? Maybe because I was
freezing cold and it was pissing down
with rain, bro. I wasn't shaking because
of any of you. I wish I said that thing
about his leg, but I didn't even caught
on to it.
I didn't even caught on to it, bro. Cuz
when you're so in a moment arguing
Yeah. Again, self-projecting. He was sat
there and his leg was shaking on that table, bro.
And I said to him as well, I'll meet him
after work. Yeah. I said to him, I will
meet him after work. Did I not say that?
Yeah. Which would have been what, 30 minutes.
He doesn't like LG doesn't like the fact
that a black guy took an L, bro. That's
what it is.
He seems to think every single black
person is stronger than a white person, you know. Yeah, man.
Yeah. He could have ended me, but he
didn't, did he? He shut his mouth and he done nothing.
Yeah. Yeah. But he didn't though, did
he? And I offered him out after work.
Yeah. See, excuses. This is what I mean
with these people in this community,
lads. They constantly make excuses. This
is what I mean with these people. This
is why I don't travel to meet anyone
because they're full of excuses, mate.
With these It's same thing with LT. He's
full of excuses,
you know? They're full of excuses. This
is what I mean with these people, man.
Also, when I [ __ ] prove I've had sex,
she still call me a virgin. The five
great guys called me a virgin.
Yeah, I put up a video of my dick in a
woman's mouth, but they called me a virgin. Huh?
But they called me a virgin. Do Do you
understand what I'm saying, bro? All
right, Pokemon. You're not going to
believe this. Yeah, I can tell you're a
mad one. This is how bad their attitude
is, right? There was this guy dressed as
a captain, right? They were all on the
fancy dress. I said, "Oh, do you want
to?" We we got into combo, right?
Because obviously I was drinking and I
was, "Oh, do you want to like try and do
you want to try and chat to some women?"
He was single. Obviously, I was single
and he was single. I said, "Do you want
to go and like try and meet some women?"
And he said, "Yeah.
And we went over to these two women.
They were with four people, Pokemon. And
yeah, I said, she said, "Oh, uh, she's
married." And then I I said, "Oh, like
can you like maybe help my friend or
whatever?" I just called him my friend.
She's like, "Oh, he needs to sort his
forehead out first." And I'm thinking,
"Huh?" She said, "Oh, yeah, you're
handsome, but he he I was like, "Bro,
that that gives me the ick. You've just
said, hold on, about this guy's forehead
being too big." Now, hold on a minute.
You We are the ones that are supposed to
have a bad personality, and even though
it wasn't about me, I don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah, you're saying that we are the ones
that have got a bad personality. You're
talking about this guy's forehead when
he doesn't even look that [ __ ] bad.
It was just some white guy. He was from
Cornwall. And I'm thinking that gave me
the ick. Then I was speaking to her
friend and then we were talking. We were
getting along. She's 29. I'm 28. She's
born a day before me. I met a lot of
Scorpios yesterday. Um same as me. And
no, he was white.
And uh the thing is you'll be speaking
to a woman Pokémon and you're getting
along and then all of a sudden their
friends will cop block or their friend
will cop block rather and start [snorts]
drama. Like one was like, "Oh yeah, he's
talking to her. Can you can you and and
her friend is literally they're about to
exchange numbers with you, bro. Like
you'll actually find you come across
people that actually like you and then
so it's like their friends are stopping
them meeting people only for them to
complain about their ex again.
It's it is a madness bro. I swear to God
it's so toxic.
It is so toxic man. It's unbelievable. You know,
you know, her friend didn't say nothing
to me. If her friend said, "Oh, I don't
want to speak to you." Well, I would
have just walked away. I don't give a
[ __ ] bro. And you see them people on
the left. They were try they were going
to try and get involved, weren't they?
The little white knights. They were
trying it, bro. It in the Weather Spoons
with the Australian. They were trying.
They were They were trying, but it they
couldn't, mate. They couldn't.
They're really trying to white knight.
Really trying. But it weren't going to
work, was it?
And her friend made made a big drama
saying, "Oh, look. He's talking to her.
Can someone can someone stop when we're
having a normal conversation, bro? Like,
we ain't no Ant-Man." So, it's like,
"Hold on." So, oh, it's cop blockers
now. And then I see Pokemon that these
other guys were talking to the same
women that I was speaking to. Um, and
I'm thinking, "Oh, they're they've got
in there now, is it? Obviously, they
they're different. They look different
than me. Maybe these women didn't tell
these guys that they have boyfriends."
Oh, no, no, no. They told them that they
had boyfriends as well. So, I'm
thinking, "Oh, so it's not just me then.
That's interesting." So, you go outright
in a cost of living crisis. There's a
cost living crisis by the way that
applies to probably 90% of the conver
the country. So you go out drinking in a
cold spending money just to tell
everyone that you've got a boyfriend
when they try to talk to you.
Seems a bit weird to me, doesn't it,
mate? Cuz it's not exactly cheap. Cuz
I'm thinking, oh, like it's me and
they're just saying it to me. No, no,
no, no, no, no. They they sent it back
to two, three other guys as well. So you
would spend money,
your hard earned money that you have to
work for going out in a pissing rain
just to tell everyone that you've got
boyfriends when 90% of the time they
[ __ ] don't in them situ in that
situation. Make it make sense, you know?
That is [ __ ] wild. Weird.
[ __ ] weird as [ __ ] lad.
I just assumed they were getting in
there, but no, they said the same thing
to them as well.
So, it's like
if if they told me that you can go out drinking, but
you can't uh speak to anyone new, I
wouldn't do it. I wouldn't do it. I
wouldn't go out, spend money drinking if
I couldn't meet anyone new. That's ridiculous.
>> Anyway, I got four numbers. I'll message
them in a few hours.
But it is getting worse.
It generally is getting worse, bro. I
went to vacies. It was a bit [ __ ]
to be fair.
Yeah, but why would you waste your time
and effort just to tell everyone that
you got boyfriends or most people even?
Cuz they said they said the same thing
to them as well.
Madness, bro. Absolute madness. They
want to sort their personality out
talking about someone's void. They might
want to They might want to sort their personality out. You know
that LT is an absolute [ __ ] idiot,
bro. He is an absolute idiot.
Cuz me, if I worked and I knew I
couldn't hit someone, I wouldn't I
wouldn't say anything. I wouldn't act untowards
cuz what you're doing is cowardly
because you're acting a certain way
knowing that if somebody wants to start
on you, oh
uh they can't hit you, you can't hit
them because they're at work.
So then don't act untowards then cuz
then that's cowardly cuz maybe maybe you
was pissing me off yesterday and I might
have wanted to give you an uppercut but
you can't do that because he's at work.
You see, it's full of excuses with these
people, bro. What about all the other
people that weren't at work?
I got a video where I stood I stood it
on this guy, bro, and he had just
finished work. Yes. And I've still got
the video. No one's ever seen it.
You know, bounces hit people all the
time and they can easily escalate it and
go people, but he never. LT is full of
excuses, mate. Just like all of these other people.
Yeah, of course they were scared, bro.
Of course they were scared.
And the security I said to him, "Don't
touch me." He come behind me. I said,
"Don't touch me, bro. Do not touch me.
Don't touch me, bro. Do not touch me."
Then he walked away.
[ __ ] joke of a country it is. Really is.
Mad. Mad, bro.
But look, they're talking about someone's forehead.
Yeah, I hated them as well. I told them
to [ __ ] off, mind their own business.
Yeah. I mean, I don't regret anything. Uh
Yeah. And I wasn't even being rude. I
wasn't even being threatening. I was bit
I was like, why are you getting involved
when I'm speaking to your friend?
You know, it's like she did not say
anything. That's the thing. It's never
the women that you actually approaching,
is it? That's what I'm saying.
You know, [ __ ] little [ __ ]
You know what I mean? And that's I was
waiting for that perfect opportunity.
Mind your own [ __ ] business. Yeah.
Cuz there's been times where I should
have said that, but I didn't think of it
or you know the things I wanted to say,
but I didn't think of it. I still stood
my ground, but that is the perfect word.
Mind your own [ __ ] business. You know,
bloody Pokemon. That's my favorite word. bloody.
And then you got a woman talking about
some white guy's forehead. What the
[ __ ] But we're the ones with a bad
personality. When are you going to wake
up and smell the [ __ ] coffee? You know,
and I'll say the same thing now when I'm sober.
You know, I should have said, Pokémon,
we can either have a drink or we can do it bad.
or do you want to do it bad?
Yeah, exactly. It's because he was
black. Think about it. When I went to
Kenji's area, right, when I went to
Kenji's workplace, LT said nothing about
him being at work. Yeah. And we all know
bouncers fight people. Yeah. He told me,
this is the story. Yeah. By the way,
Yeah. His friend was in a McDonald's
before. Yeah. In my end, and he kept
chucking on this bouncer, chucking it on
this bouncer, chucking it on this
bouncer. And the bouncer had enough and
he smashed his teeth in. Yeah, that's a
true story. Now, this guy was a bouncer.
This guy fired back and he never lost
his badge. So, doesn't make any sense.
You didn't tell everyone that's still on
YouTube that I know of. You know,
bro, I would have loved for that guy to
try and smash my teeth and I would have
uppercuted him one in the forehead,
straight in the jaw, and that's it. You
know, it's always excuses. Always excuses, lad.
Always [ __ ] excuses. And then and
then it's like, oh, well, if you're in a
if you're in a betting shop, you never
start on the man. You never start on the
man in a betting shop. So then if we
start on a man in the betting shop,
you're going to use the same excuse. A bouncer is,
you know, has got more chance of filling
someone in and getting away with it than
anyone working in a [ __ ] betting shop.
You understand? You know, if they if
someone works in a betting shop, I mean,
and there's been people at work before
that has wanted to go. There has people
there's been people in betting shops
before, bro, that have wanted to go.
Yeah. So, I'm pretty sure a bouncer
Think of that, bro. Look at that [ __ ] in
in Look at that [ __ ] in Wales. What
happened there, bro? When the bouncer
Yeah, bro. There was a They had a
full-on fight. They had to get stopped. It's [ __ ]
And I remember that time as well on the
bookies as well, bro. But I was I was in
a pub opposite. I remember. Yeah. I was
on and off cooking with my mom at the
time. I wasn't living there. And I said,
"Bro, I really want to go to that
betting shop and smash that [ __ ] over
the counter, bro." And she's like, "No,
I'm never going to talk to you again.
Oh, I'm never going to talk to you
again." It was right opposite the bet
Fred. I remember I was drinking
Guinness. I said, "Let me show this
little fat cunt." Yeah. And he's another
one. You didn't get stuck on that bad,
but I just left it cuz my mom just said,
"Yeah, I'm not going to torture you
again if you do it."
But that's a betting shot, bro. That's a
bing shot, bro. Yeah.
Oh, my football bet was so close
yesterday. Poke mom.
It was so close yesterday. This football bet, lad.
So close. I got two. Both scar. No draw.
I just needed another one. I just needed
[ __ ] spenny more to score and I would
have got three both score no draws. Damn.
So [ __ ] close. So it tells me that I
can get [ __ ] two both score no draws.
I'm proud of myself for that. You know
almost got three.
I was thinking spending more. Come on. Score man.
Score. Score. Score. All I need to do is
score. That would have been a treble
both score. No draw.
You know, [ __ ]
Yeah, it was for £237. I could have done
with it. I could have done with it. I
wish I I don't need the money, but I
could have done with it. Who the [ __ ]
couldn't have done with it, mate? You know,
you want to poke Pokemon or do you want
to do it dirty, lad?
Do you want to go for a pipe or do you
want to do it dirty?
Come on. You want to do it bad?
Do you want to do it bad? [laughter]
No, it's not funny, bro.
I think I might watch Mickey Mouse on YouTube. [laughter]
Yeah, man. [laughter] Yeah.
And I think her friend liked me in it, Pokémon.
I don't know why she was drinking my drink.
And obviously they were of age. You
can't get in that Weather Spoons without
ID. And knowing them, they would have got IDed, you know.
You drunk my bloody drink.
They've all got the same attitude.
They've [snorts] all got the same attitude. Yeah,
they've all got They're all [ __ ] NPCs.
Oh, they're all [ __ ] NPCs, lad.
All of them are [ __ ] NPCs.
And I got a [ __ ] from this escort.
Cost me 120.
Yeah. Spun to her mouth and everything, bro. Yeah. Oh, bloody bloody. >> [snorts] >> Bloody
bloody. But yeah, it is to do with race.
It is to do with race.
It's not cuz the guy was a security guard.
You know, it's because the guy was black.
And you know what these people like on
with their autism? Oh.
Oh. Oh. Oh, you never go for a man. You
never go for a man. But if you go for a man, right?
I'm having sausage and mash.
Yeah. With onion gravy.
Yeah. I'm having sausage and mash.
He needs to stop this race [ __ ] bro. He
really needs to stop it. I could be
beaten by a black guy and I could lose
by a black guy. I could lose with a
You know, it has not to do with race.
And you would have known that if the guy wanted it.
Yeah, a security guard can fight. A
security guard can absolute. And he
could have also mouthed off as well. And
he could have goded me into doing
something where he could defend himself.
He kissed his teeth at me, bro. Don't
kiss your [ __ ] teeth at me. You
[ __ ] bum clot.
Yeah, that's a [ __ ] Jamaican thing.
And this woman was defending me as well.
She was in her 30s, 40s Pokémon. She
said, "Why are you iding him when he's
clearly of age?" No, no, no, no, no, no.
Then her friend was just like, "Oh, just
shut up. we're trying to go in
like these people need to know to mind
their own business cuz they don't want
it when somebody gives it back to them.
This is what it is. There's no This is
what it is with in this country, right?
There's no there's no uh deterrent,
right? Just like with the law and all of
that. So, they go around acting like
entitled [ __ ] And it could be men
as well. It's not even just women,
right? And then when someone gives it
back to them, right, then they've never
had somebody give it to them before.
That's what I mean, bro. They've never
had someone like tell them about
themselves, man or [ __ ] woman. That's
why they go around acting like [ __ ]
you know, cuz they've never been taught
a lesson, you know?
So, I don't know why people don't just
mind their own business.
It is strange.
And if you are going to act bad, act bad
by yourself and actually respect it a
bit more. I'd actually respect it a bit
more if these people could actually act
hard by themselves, but they can't.
They have to do it in a group and still
[ __ ] themselves even when they're in the group. So yeah,
>> did you see the Australian Pokémon? She
was a proper [ __ ] weren't she? Proper [ __ ]
Yeah, proper [ __ ] lad. Mad. Madness.
Did you see the white knights on the
other table? [laughter] Oh,
they butt in and then [ __ ] themselves.
They butt in and then shut up in the
end. It's like what happened when I used
to work, bro. when I used to do the Uber thing.
Mind your own [ __ ] business, bro.
Mind your own [ __ ] business. Yeah. [ __ ] madness.
But yeah, this is uh
yeah, I got I got a couple of numbers, five numbers.
So, we'll see.
Two of them might be fake, but I know
definitely three numbers I got 100% legit.
What can you do? Sausagees and mash baby.
Make it scooter. You like the Vapor
Maxes? Uh, so I got the Vapor Maxes, the
jeans, went out drinking, got an escort.
We're going to go skid at some point,
mate. Nah. Nah, never, mate.
[ __ ] never, son. [ __ ] madness.
They're so stuck up. So so so so stuck
up. And then the irony is is that the
French women are not stuck up.
This should be the other way around.
It's just [ __ ] bad.
Wait until Joseph Ferrar sees this.
Joseph bloody far joker.
Them little white knights.
Yeah. But no, apparently I lost.
Apparently I lost. Yeah. Yeah.
Apparently I lost according to LT. Okay, mate. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, mate. I lost, didn't I? Really?
I was going to go to this bar, but it
was closed. They've closed it down. Bad.
And man says, "You're going to end up in prison."
He says, "You need to leave because it's
going to get worse and worse and worse
and you're going to end up getting
stabbed or end up getting nicked." >> Yeah. >> [snorts]
>> I would have thought they would want
what's best for their friends, you know. Yeah.
You don't tell me where to go. I I do
what I want. I don't know who they think
they are coming to this city trying to
tell me trying to tell me what to where to go.
Nah, bro. Nah, bro.
Nah, bro. Bro, that ain't happening.
Mad. Why does Why do people hate the
Timmy one more than I did? I wasn't home
early. I got home at like 12.
Why did people Why did people give Timmy
more [ __ ] than they gave me Pokemon?
They people didn't give me much [ __ ] for
standing my ground
from that woman in the pub.
No one hated on me like they did to me.
But they seem to think that it's the men
that have got no personality.
They seem to think that it's the men
that have got no personality. Okay. Yeah.
Who did this stupid amber woman? What
was her name? This autumn woman was on
my thing yesterday. I said, "Oh, you're
generalizing men like I'm generalizing
women. You This is the thing. The men
that you're complaining about are the
men that you choose. They're the choose
that you they're the men that you go for." Yeah.
Yeah. At the end of the day, you are
what? Listen, imagine it was like I
said, imagine it was a [ __ ] um
I forgot what I was saying now. Yeah.
Like you're you're moaning about you say
about men, right? And you have had bad
experiences because they're the men that
you choose. They're the men that you
pick to go for. I can prove it. Let's
meet tomorrow. Come on. Come on. I can I can [ __ ]
stop your generalization right here, right now.
right here, right now. I can stop your
generalization right here, right now, if
we can meet. But you won't do it. And
you'll continuously go with the same men
and then continuously moan right
about the same men that you go for.
Do you understand Pokémon? Me, it's
every woman I come across. I mean, I
come across a woman yesterday that was
35. She said I was too young for her and
her friend was trying to cop block me.
Again, same attitude. You know, they
have they walk around with the same
attitude everywhere you [ __ ] go.
Same cop blockers, same attitude, same
excuses, same boring [ __ ]
You generalize men that you choose to
[ __ ] go for. Big difference.
Do you understand that mad?
Well, the one in the weather spoons. No,
no, no, no, no, no. I've had some bad ones.
I've had some bad ones, lad. Bad ones.
No, that was actually quite minor to be fair.
But it's men that have got the bad
personality. It's men that have got no
No, it's them being stuck up [ __ ] in
this country. I know that. You know
that. We all know that.
Yeah. There's been a lot of bad ones.
I've had Americans try to take the piss
out of me.
Bro, you don't know. It's
What's the woman's situation?
It's the same stuck up [ __ ]
Um, the situation is that all women are the same,
but hopefully one of these numbers go
somewhere when I text them.
It's 28 now. I'm 28 now. It's [snorts]
time to stop playing games. Yeah,
it is really time to stop playing games
with these these [ __ ] people,
dude. They're so stuck up.
I I was thinking of going out next week, but
I don't know, bro. I probably won't go
out for two weeks, to be honest.
That was quite negative, wasn't it,
Joker? Wasn't it Pokémon?
Need to brush my teeth in a minute.
I survived the [ __ ] tooth fake for this bollocks.
You know the thing is I spent about £40
in like 20 minutes.
In like 20 minutes, you know, lad.
Literally like 20 minutes.
No, I'm not going out again tonight. [ __ ] off.
[ __ ] off, mate. No,
no, I'm good, lad.
[ __ ] that. I'm [ __ ] Anyways, I spent
£40 in about 30, 20, 30 minutes. You
know why? Because they water down the
rum. So, when they water down the rum,
you can drink it like a fish. Whereas
when you drink beer, you can't get it
down you as fast. So, they can't water it down.
You know when you're out last. Yeah.
[ __ ] madness, mate.
Yeah. You Yeah. You
Why? I don't cuz she wasn't the one
arguing with me.
Uh cuz she wasn't the one arguing with
me, was she?
And do you know what she said? I don't
think you heard it, but she was like,
"Oh, I don't think she doesn't she's not
going to kiss you." I was like, "I don't
want to kiss her. Thank you very much."
I was actually trying to speak, right?
To see get to know them and maybe get
their number. I don't want to kiss
somebody in a Weather Spoons. Like what?
That's not I don't think you heard that.
Maybe I didn't recall that bit. She was
trying to say that, "Oh, um, no, she's
not gonna kiss you." I was like, "I
don't want to kiss somebody in a Weather
Spoons. Thank you very much." You know,
I mean, do you think every guy that
approaches you want to kiss you within 10 seconds?
They're so entitled, mate. Like, you can't even
Yeah, you didn't hear it. That was
before I recorded. Like, you they're so
entitled and it's it's mad. It generally
generally is mad. They're so stuck up and entitled. Um, it's unbelievable.
Really, really is.
They're so stuck up and they talk about
men's personality. This is the This is
the contradictory, though, is that they
talk about men's personality. Madness. Madness.
Yeah, it's just the same old, lad.
[ __ ] madness, bro. They're so entitled. America, Australia,
it's just the same. They're all entitled in it.
Madness, bro. Madness. Don't know.
You see the little white lights
and this is the kind of [ __ ] you have to
put up with when you go out and then you
say to yourself, is it worth it? And to
be honest, it's not even the money. I
didn't even I spent over £200, but it
wasn't as bad as last time. But you need
to say to yourself like, is this
actually worth it, bro?
It's so negative and so toxic.
No, insulting that person that wasn't
even me. It's not It's just not worth it, you know.
It isn't worth it to go out, is it?
Madness. I should have just got my dick
out in it, Pokemon. You know what I
should have done? I should have just
pulled my trousers down and put my
[ __ ] ass on her face.
Yeah, I should have Do you know what I
should have done? I should have stood on
the table and been like I should have
showed my ass and been like other guys.
Come on guys.
Boozy would have loved that in it. Yeah,
imagine I done that, bro. [ __ ] other
guys and just put my ass in their [ __ ] face.
You know. Yeah. Madness. Madness.
Ant-Man said, "Well, it will never
change, will it?"
Yeah. I was I was thinking of it. I was
thinking of it to be fair. I was
thinking of it.
Ant-Man said, "Well, it will never
change, will it?"
Is he right, Pokemon?
But it will never change, will it?
And you will never change.
Well, it will never change, will it?
I can't believe I got I got I got two
both score no draws
yesterday and I almost got a third one.
All I needed was Spenny more to [ __ ] score, man. Yep.
So, they don't want anyone talking to
them. It's like you try to speak to them
and then they're just like not
interested. It's mad, mad, mad, mad, mad, mad.
Yeah, like I said, I'm having a sausage
and mash today. So yeah,
they definitely water them rum and cokes
down. They definitely definitely water
them down, lad.
They definitely do.
Just drink it like a [ __ ] Yeah, man.
So, who do you think was right in them videos?
The same website you can watch Harry Styles on.
Pokemon. The same website you can watch
Harry Styles on.
You know, same website you can watch
Harry Styles on. And that guy is still
rinsing that L J thing, bro. Okay. He
didn't hide behind the gate. I'm sorry.
I'll rephrase it. I'll rephrase it, bro.
He stood behind the gate and he done nothing.
Yeah, he was. He stood behind the gate
and he done nothing. Is that Is that
better for you?
Oh, we offered you out. Yeah, but he
done nothing. So,
he done nothing. That's not even a W, bro.
That L J done nothing. He come for
clout. Yeah. and he stood behind the
gate. That's what he done. He stood
behind the gate and he ain't about anything. You know,
yeah, he's got something wrong with him, bro.
It's to do with his race. He's all ego in it.
Madness in it. It is a madness.
Don't know why they go out spending the
money they do if they're just going to
tell everyone they've got boyfriends. Yeah. Mad.
Well, go out today, bro. No one stopping
you. You're saying that you'd go out
today? Go out, then. No one's stopping you.
No one's stopping you from going out.
No, he didn't bore me. He asked me for
my ID and then he started kissing his
teeth at me.
Um, so no, they didn't bar me. He I
didn't get in in the first place. He was
asking me for ID. Then he started
kissing his teeth at me.
Uh, was I in the wrong? Uh, no. I wasn't
in the wrong Jay Willow because at the
end of the day, right, let me tell you
something. At the end of the day, Jay
Willow, I know what I'm doing when I'm
drunk. I don't regret it the next day.
So, no, I wasn't wrong. I was right.
Which is why I'm not deleting them videos.
The guy asked me for ID to be a come. He
kissed his teeth at me and I gave it
back to him. And then I told them other
four people to mind their own [ __ ]
business. What did I do that was wrong?
What did I do that was wrong? I got
another I got a thing to tell you Jay
Widow since you like to uh be a white
knight. So I was uh you want you know
when you want to talk about people's
personality, right? And people uh women
not being interested and stuff. I'll
give you I'll give you a good one. So, I
sound like [ __ ] a broken record cuz
I've already said this, but you haven't
heard it. So, I was out approaching uh
with this guy yesterday,
right? Cuz I met him. We was talking. I
he was dressed up, you know, he was
dressed up as a captain. So, we went and
we uh approached these women, right? And
uh she said, "Oh, she had a boyfriend."
I said, "Oh, okay. Well, can you maybe
like help my friend and that?" Cuz he
was talking to her friend. And she was
like, "Oh, he needs to sort his forehead out first."
Did What do you think about that, Jo?
And there was nothing wrong with the
guy. He was just a white guy from
Cornwall. And she she said, "I'm
handsome, but she said about his forehead."
That's suggest a bad personality,
doesn't it, J Willow? Doesn't it mate?
They They might want to stalk their
personality out on their attitude,
right, before claiming that they go for
personality. You know what [snorts] I
mean? It's [ __ ] mate. You know, and
it weren't even about me. And it gave me
the ick, you know, and you want to talk
about these women going for personality.
Jay Willow, you're a [ __ ] idiot.
Yeah, that's what you are. Just like
London Taylor is a [ __ ] idiot. Yeah,
I can't wait to see his reply on my
video. I'd love to see it, you know,
cuz I'm not going to lie, you do kind of
come across as a white knight.
Not a s, a white knight. There's a big
difference, you know,
and then you're and then you're sat
there as an impartial person, right?
That has been with women, had sex. So,
I'm impartial. And then I'm and I'm
going out and I'm seeing what is
happening and I'm seeing what they're
doing. And then you think to yourself,
how the [ __ ] are these people still
defending women with the attitude that
they have and and what they say and how
they act and you still have these people
sat there defending them? It's [ __ ] mental,
you know, like they're so toxic.
That is that is that is crazy. A lot of
them have got more balls than me to say
what they say. And I'm a crazy [ __ ]
That's why I can never fathom how people
defend them. I'm not a virgin. I've been
with women. I have no reason to to to to
sit there and lie. This is what you
don't understand. I've got no reason. I'm impartial.
You know, I can tell you what happened.
I got five numbers yesterday.
And then the only people that didn't
seem like the only women that didn't
seem like they were [ __ ] were the
French ones. Don't know why there was a
few French people. They didn't um
American was a [ __ ] There was an
American. And they're so they're so stuck up.
Like it's it's it's insane, man. [clears throat]
So yeah, that's what I don't understand.
J Willow, why am I What? Am I a virgin, bro?
Am I a virgin?
No, I'm not a virgin, am I lad?
Be honest. Am I a [ __ ] virgin? S.
No, I'm [ __ ] not, [ __ ]
Crazy, isn't it?
So, yeah. You don't say anything like
that, do you, bro?
Their toxic, their toxicity.
It's not about boyfriends. It's about
loads of different things. This is
something that you don't understand. It's mad
cuz you live in Liverpool and and the
women in Liverpool are [ __ ] And how I
know that cuz I've been to Liverpool and
there were [ __ ] there as well, right?
Yeah. There. There's been some bad ones,
bro. There's been some bad ones. I tell
you one before. I can think of one. Uh
I uh there was one before. It was a
couple years ago. I met I met friend
from I met uh my friend from Brazil.
I got a friend from Brazil by the way.
We met in Fabrics. So, we met up in
Liverpool Street and uh this woman,
again, it wasn't even someone I
approached. It was probably was her
friend. It's never the people that you
approach. That's the worst thing about
it. It's always their friends. And uh
she was stuck. I think she said, "Oh,"
she said, "Oh, you're ugly or you're
this or that." I said, "Have you seen
yourself, you little [ __ ] slag?" Um
and then and then she kept running up
her mouth. Bro, I was going to knock her
out, bro. I was going to knock her out.
I'm not even joking. Like, it's lucky
that guy pulled me back and he was
obviously bigger than me as well. My
friend obviously was bigger than me,
brother. Is it? So, um,
and, uh, there was one before obviously
in Nottingham. I asked someone for
directions. They told me to [ __ ] off. I
spat on them, bro. Straight spat on
them. Not in their face, but I spat it
towards them and it went on them.
Um, there's been some mad ones, bro,
over the years.
I can think about more and tell you. Yeah,
there's been some bad ones. There's been
some bad ones. And how did it how did it
start? Well, I was talking to a friend
and then she started uh No, my friend
was from Brazil. She was from England,
the one that I was arguing with. I was
speaking to her friend and her friend
started getting involved hyping up
like being arrogant and I said, "Hold on
a minute. One sec. I'm not talking to
you. If your friend doesn't want to
talk, your friend doesn't have to talk.
I don't know why you're getting
involved. She's got a mouth of her own."
Like, and then she started hyping up,
hyping up. I said, "Hold on a minute.
You're not going to tell me where I can
and can't go."
And that's all you do when you deal when
you go out. You just deal with these
entitled, stuck up women
that apparently go for personality.
That's why I don't [ __ ] with it anymore.
That's why I don't really go out anymore
cuz it's just toxic.
I just chill, bro. Play some GTA, kick
back, go to a restaurant. I can't be
bothered with it anymore.
Yeah, but it's always ended up in tears,
so it doesn't matter, does it?
And it's dangerous as well because they
you got all of these simps inflating
their ego online, right? And it gives
them an attitude and it makes them brave
and it makes them think they're better
than someone. And then they're going to
keep they're going to come across the
wrong person one day, bro. Just like
when they come across me and I tell them
about themsel like when when I'm telling
them about themsel I'm deflating their
ego back to normal again. You know, they
seem to think like it's just
the boyfriend [ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ]
about. I just think it's weird how
people pay money to go out when there's
a when there's a cost living crisis just
to tell everyone they've got boyfriends.
But at the end of the day, if they want
to do that, they can do that. I'm not
going to I don't give a [ __ ] That's
their life. It's not my life. If they
want to do that, that's up to them, is it?
They're literally NPCs,
especially in that Simmons bar. They're
dead in that Simmons bar. It's literally
It's the same situation, just different characters, you know.
It's crazy, bro. Crazy.
It's one of them. I need to have a
shower in a minute. Anyways,
put my shoes back in the box. I'll wipe
them. Oh, they're lush.
Oh, look at these. Look at these. L. They're lovely.
Absolutely lovely, mate. >> [snorts]
>> I spent less on the night out than I did
on the trailers.
How bad is that? Oh,
[ __ ] hell, man.
I need a shower, man. Oh, [ __ ]
The same website you can watch the
sideman on. Mad.
That is a madness.
Anyways, I'll be back later. Yeah, I'm
going to have a shower and wash some clothes and [ __ ]
I'll be back later. 100. Yeah.