Yo yo
the TV not on now.
Yeah, man. [ __ ] bollocks.
Absolute bollocks, man.
onto his chicken shot. Some chicken. Oh,
you got to wait.
You got to wait [ __ ]
What was it? You got to wait for [ __ ]
You got to wait 9 minutes. So, I thought
[ __ ] that. Anyway, [ __ ] wait. No on. Yes.
I'm [ __ ] starving, man.
Absolutely [ __ ] starving.
Bing more bing.
Hey, you're right, lad.
Yeah, I [ __ ] got four numbers. I've
messaged them all. I think three I got
five numbers. Three of them are
definitely real. Um, so we'll see what
they say, but if they reply back.
Notorious. It's [ __ ] lad. It's
[ __ ] This country, bro, I'm [ __ ]
Thailand. I'm in a bad mood today, bro.
I was in a bad mood earlier cuz I
happened to wait for it. It's so toxic.
Notorious. This is why I don't go out anymore, bro.
I don't go out anymore because it's so toxic.
You know what I mean? That's why I don't
really like try anymore, lad. Too toxic.
Just ordered some food, but I'm starving.
I got sausage and mash for later.
We got an escort yesterday, boss.
It's mad, is it? Notorious. Mad.
It's toxic, man. Nothing to be proud of,
bro. It's toxic.
Very, very, very toxic. Uh,
just making friends, guys. Just making friends.
Yeah. Um, I'll be out again.
I don't know.
Yeah, she gave me a [ __ ]
I think I spent like 250. That's not
that bad. That's more like it. But
obviously I got an escort as well. So
yeah, what two
with the food? What? 250? Yeah, that's that's normal.
250 is not bad, bro.
Just when you're going over like 400 and [ __ ]
Yeah, it's just when you're going over
the four mark, you don't want Yeah, I'm
happy with that. Well, I'm not happy cuz [ __ ]
you know, it's just toxic.
They're so stuck up. These women,
notorious, they're so so stuck up.
Very very very stuck up. Um, yeah.
So stuck up. It's mad.
Can't wait until this comes. I'm [ __ ] starving.
It happened a few times.
It happened a few times, bro,
where I was getting into someone and then [ __ ]
their friend gets involved.
This country is full of [ __ ]
Did you watch the bouncing video?
Yeah. This country is absolutely full of [ __ ]
Did you watch it, Nurious? [ __ ]
absolute. That's why I don't go out,
lad. It's too toxic. I'm addicted to uh
peace and quiet, you know?
I'm addicted to the [ __ ] peace and
quiet. It's why I don't go out. much.
Yeah, I got couple lumbers.
It started raining there.
It's so bad in it. It's so bad.
This one's got one tick. Must be on a US store.
Something like that.
I don't know. Lord knows One.
Hold on. One. Two. Yeah.
So that's it, it lad.
We can't wait.
I'm tired, boss.
Yeah, it's all toxic, though, isn't it, bro?
The LT was trying to use that guy as
being at work as an excuse not to do anything.
The guy, he makes up such [ __ ]
excuses. This LT, he's so full of
excuses, mate. What about them four
people then? Right. What about the four
people that that weren't working and I
told them to [ __ ] back to Newcastle?
What about them? But they at work, guys.
Full of excuses. That's how you know
that. This is what I mean with this
community, bro. They're all full of excuses,
you know? That's what it is. I mean,
like, think of, let's use this analogy,
right? They call me a virgin. Yeah. I
prove I've had sex.
I mean, [ __ ] what the [ __ ] bro?
That was my first time approaching in 6 weeks. Yay.
I don't know. I I done an approach to
the train station.
They're too stuck up. Notorious.
Too stuck up.
Thank you, boss.
This country is disgusting, bro.
This country is [ __ ] vile, man.
A message back would be nice
from this woman. Just met a Bess's back
would be nice, but you know
nothing, man. I had a shower, lad.
I had a shower, man.
[snorts] Getting hairy again. Huh?
Sometime [ __ ] hung over, ain't it?
hung over after
using I can't get any bloody matches
on Tinder notorious. I can't get any
bloody matches on Hinge or Tinder.
I can't get any bloody matches. Bloody notorious. Bloody.
I can't get any matches, mate. That's
why I deleted them.
I don't know.
Country's dead in it.
So, notorious was was Ant-Man right then
when he said they're just not interested
in this country.
Was he right then, Notorious,
or was he lying?
Yeah, but was you lying when they said
that they're not interested in this country?
Yeah, they ain't interested in this country.
Madness. It's so toxic going out and
dealing with this [ __ ] bro. That's why
I hardly ever do it. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ] [clears throat]
It's mad why they go out if they're just
going to tell everyone they've got boyfriends.
It's mad. Is it Notorious?
Let's see if there's anything coming at the cinemas. They're mad. Not really.
Hey Jasper, you right lad.
Oh, Scream 7 is coming out in February, mad. Yeah.
How you doing, man? You all right? Just
ordered some food.
Starving, lad. It was very toxic yesterday.
Yeah, I got I think I got five numbers.
I know three of them are definitely
real. Message them.
No reply back yet, but it's good old
England, isn't it, Dad? It will never change.
I mean, what what what what's there to
say, lad? And I got an escort and I and
I paid I spent 250, so I'm happy with that, you know.
Yeah. Hey, what did you think, bro?
That's never happening in this country.
So, don't ever waste the hope, lad.
You're never going to meet anyone. You
don't know the amount of stuck up women
I dealt with yesterday.
Trust me, you're never going to meet
anyone in this country, especially London.
So, there's no point wasting the hope,
bro, cuz it's never happened. You don't
know the [ __ ] I had to deal with yesterday, bro.
That's why I don't go out. That's why I
rarely go out, lad. Cuz it's too toxic.
I like just chilling. A peaceful life.
That's why I don't go out much
because they're just It's just the same old thing.
Stuck up people, [ __ ] [ __ ]
That's why I just Yeah. prefer peace and quiet, you know?
anything about the women being [ __ ] or
just dis just missed it.
Don't shoot you or no.
Don't shoot you now.
You wouldn't be the first one, lad.
You would be the first one.
I mean, I tell you what happened yesterday. Yeah.
I done five approaches. So, when I got
one number, she seemed all right. I
messaged her. She hasn't reply back yet.
I got five numbers, but I think only
three of them are real. I don't know.
One block me. Um,
and I don't give a [ __ ] So it would
always be the same in this country,
you know. It's it's getting worse as well.
Like it's uh it's it's getting worse.
It will never change, bro. It will never
change. It will change.
I'm done with it, bro. I prefer my sanity.
So Scream 7's out in February. Trust him.
That's good, man. Yeah.
So, yeah, I was speaking to one woman
from up north. She seems all right. I
got her number reply. But
so, it seems Thailand is the only way. Yeah.
I almost won a football bet yesterday,
man. I done a treble, both score, no
draw. And all I needed was one goal. I
got two, both score, no draws,
and the last match was 2-0. All I needed
was one goal. One goal.
One goal. Oh my god. And I got a treble.
Both score no draw.
That would have been ace.
That would have been [ __ ] ace, man.
Yeah. Even Thailand's not what it's like
10 years ago. Now this country is
completely finished, bro.
So many stuck up people
saying the same [ __ ] thing. Toxic.
Where's my [ __ ] food?
I ordered a five guys. [ __ ] starving.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't in that.
But you see, they all make up excuses on here. Jasper
stuck it on a bouncer. Stuck it on them
poor people. And these people still try
and tell me I'm wrong.
You know what I mean, bro? That's what
they're like on here.
Oh, you never stand up for a man. You
never stand up to a man. And then you
stand up to a man and then it's like,
"Oh, uh, you know, we can't do anything
because he's at work." But yet you want
me to fight a man in the bookies that's
also at work. That's what I mean with
this community. It's disabled, bro.
It's proper proper disabled. They're
full of excuses on here, lad. Absolutely
[ __ ] full of them. This guy, bro.
This guy, they say to me, "Oh, why don't
you start with a guy in the bookies?
Why do you start in a guy in the
bookies?" Yeah. Why don't you start with
a guy in the bookies? Yeah. But then
when I'm starting on a man that could
actually have more chance of doing
something to me, oh, he's at work. Oh,
he's at work. Trying to use his badge as
an excuse. But I I offered to give the
guy my number, bro. And we can take it
outside of work. You know,
these people are full of excuses.
Honestly, they are full of excuses,
mate. I'm done. I'm done with them, bro.
These people are here full of excuses.
This guy messaged me [clears throat] on Instagram.
He says, "I like how do you like London
so far?" I can't message for 3 days, but
I'll tell him exactly what I think about London.
Nah, London would be all right if it
wasn't for the people. If it was better
weather in this country
and the except the people, it'd be good.
There'd be no problem with England. It's
the people and the weather ruin it.
[ __ ] having to wait around for everything.
Oh, it's just a YouTube uh channel.
Why is there so many stuck up women in
this country? Jasper £23
for a burger mill. I've got sausage and
mash later. So
yeah, sausage and mash.
That is [ __ ] man.
That is really [ __ ]
I almost won that football bet. Almost won it.
Yeah, these people are saying that I didn't win.
Ended up there. Not this problem again.
Not this problem again where they can't
find a place. Oh, not this problem again.
Not this problem again. We had this
problem the other [ __ ] day.
Uh, not this same problem again.
If it isn't somebody trying to make me
[ __ ] wait 9 minutes.
Not this problem again. Yeah,
it ended up
92. Yeah. Yeah.
I got myself
with that bag. They're not like
When you lose when you lose [snorts]
I call that guy ugly son I
your own [ __ ]
Do that outside.
King's not here. He doesn't live here.
LG makes excuses.
He makes excuses.
LG defin makes excuses that burger
virgin boy to 5. Probably not. What do I still
crispy onions, basil and jalapenos?
That's the business. Oh, hello. [clears throat]
Let's eat this. One second.
Back in five minutes. M.
You know what I love about P? It tastes so
that is nice.
Yeah, of course you would agree with all white
and I went in on one of them. I didn't
go on both of them. I went in on one of
Well, I agree with it. And I went on one
of them. If I didn't go for both of those
five, is good
thing with five, guys. It's so expensive
for what it is.
What do I say? It's like a cheaper
McDonald's. No way. Five.
No, it's way better. No. Oh,
nothing like McDonald's.
It's not as good as [ __ ] DBK, but
it's it's good. It's up there, man. Oh,
I'm having a five.
I'm still waiting for this side. It's
okay. I'll just wait
till it's been made.
I'll wait until it's been made.
The punch is for the district.
Even if you knew where I am, what are
you going to do about it?
Yeah. So why do you care where I am?
Where the [ __ ] the boy at? Why? Oh, [ __ ]
The LT is such a bullshitter. [clears throat]
Who is a [ __ ] bullshitter? [clears throat]
Oh, I'm stopped.
Have you ever tried lobster?
You can't even meet a woman in this
country nowadays that aren't stuck up. Matter. Oh.
Yeah, he would be crying. He He's reaction
is probably the same as the virgins when
he does it now.
Yeah. Bro, it's like my that girl
telling I gave her some of my vindaloo.
and uh she literally I couldn't even
have one bite of it, mate. She was
struggling. And there's me just yamming
it just coughing it down me, you know,
as I do.
I love this. M.
That's lovely. That burger.
You can't beat right a homemade burger
with proper beef
and a pop and a and a nice vindaloo
curry at a restaurant. Yeah, it' be hard
to beat in it. Them jalapenos are nice.
They're very green. You like them in it? Right.
Too hot for you.
Yeah. The chips are obviously like the
steakhouse ones, but they're nowhere
near as bad as the KFC ones are the
worst, isn't it?
That is [ __ ] done.
You can see the people on the table looking
Did you see when I stuck it on them two girls moving
and um I was and the white knights were looking
Yeah, I'd love to see his reaction to Vindaloo.
Vindaloo. Was he struggling?
Yeah, like I said, that girl tenn was struggling.
She literally could barely chew it. It
was that hot. Oh, well.
>> Yeah, mama. I'm stuck. Yeah, man.
Sorry about that, mate.
Oh, virgin boy. Yeah, man. Sorry, bro.
All right, virgin boy.
>> Oh, mate.
I'll be sleeping in my little bed sit
right now. I'm fat.
I'm so tired, bro.
all of the alcohol and bollocks. E,
you never lose it then. Uh,
you reck you never pop it that card. That replay,
you'll never lose it. Only joking. Oh, we help. So tired.
Oh my life.
We're being rejected.
I was talking to a friend. All
>> [clears throat] >> right. Oh, pass. >> Yeah. [laughter]
But it will never change, will it? So,
and you'll never change. So,
What is it? Huh? Yeah. Yep.
[gasps and sighs]
Ah, I love it, bro.
I'll be back later.