Oh, [ __ ] hell, man.
Ricky still being a white knight.
Ricky still being a white knight. White Knight Millington. Jesus Christ.
These [ __ ] white knights are mad.
evil. Why did you say people to be clear? One sec.
How many bloody white knights are there? It's unbelievable.
[ __ ] white knights everywhere.
Yeah, man. Madness. Where the [ __ ] is
Joseph Ferrara when we need him?
Yeah. So, you can't defend yourself
against a woman because you're bullying.
You defend yourself against a [ __ ] woman. Bullying.
Uh, that's these white knights logic,
bro. They're so pathetic. I don't think
there's anything more pathetic than
these white knights. You def So, your
logic is you defend
yourself against a woman that's trying
to bully you. You're a bully.
Absolute white knights. Absolute white
knights on here. I can't think of
anything more pathetic than these white knights.
Like Ricky White Knight, Virgin
Milinton. This guy is clearly a virgin.
You know, the more and more these people
do this. Yeah. more and more of these
people write this stuff, it shows that
they've not been with women. It shows
that they're virgins. It really, really
does, bro. And I'm And I'm not just
saying that. It's the truth. The way
they just dismiss all the bad things
that they do, it shows that they've
never dealt with them
ever. They're such virgins on this community, bro. Seriously.
Such little virgins. I swear to God,
they really, really are, bro. I'm
telling you, 90% of these people on here
are virgins. Absolute guarantee, bro.
Little simp little virgins that's never
been with a woman. It's so obvious now.
The way they defend them. It's obvious.
It is obvious now, bro. I woke up and
read some of these comments from these
little white night fat ugly people.
Yeah, it's so clear that they're
virgins. It's true. It is the truth with
these little mongos on this community.
Bro, this might I'm not going live again
after today for a little bit. Anyways,
yeah, I just wanted to say absolute
virgins on this community. Never been
with a woman. That's why they sit there
defending them because they've never had
them. They don't know how to conduct
themselves. That's why they sit there
virgins defending women, you know.
Yeah. I can't go for men. I went for
five different men on Saturday. Five
different men. But oh, I don't go for
men. You little virgin. You little white
knight virgin. You talk [ __ ] You talk absolute [ __ ]
That's what you do. You talk wank.
They're [ __ ] absolute virgins on here, lad. >> [snorts]
>> Uh, did you watch the videos?
You had [ __ ] without Okay. So,
okay. Well, did you watch the videos?
There's a lot of videos up. Well,
basically I'm having problems with LT again.
Well, I went out yesterday. Okay. Well, well, so, uh,
well, I I don't even know where to
begin. I mean, I went out.
So, um, am I not right with what I said
to LT? So, apparently I'm a bully. I
bully women basically. So, because I
don't let an entitled woman raise her
voice to me, I'm a bully. Ricky
Millington logic. And I'm scared to go
for men. Even though I went for four
different men on Saturday and none of
them wanted any of it, but I only go for
women. Okay, mate. I'm done providing
content on this channel, you know? I'm
I'm not doing this anymore. I'm not
doing this. I'm not doing this anymore.
These white knights are pathetic. Why is
there so many white knights on and and
Yeah. And [ __ ] uh LT was saying about
how he wanted to meet me yesterday,
but he had no problem with me going for
a white man in the bookies. He had no
problem with a black bus driver giving
me [ __ ] But then it when it's to do
with me defending myself against a black bouncer. Yeah.
It's [ __ ] It's [ __ ] bro. It's
And I of And it's not even about the
bouncer. I stood up to several different
men on Saturday. Several different men.
Yeah. So, okay. And I said, "By that
logic?" I said, "By that logic, then the
bus driver didn't beat me then, did he?
That black bus driver didn't beat me?"
Nope. Because then, by your logic, then
if I went for him, he couldn't go for me
cuz he's at work. So, that bus No bus
driver ever beat me then. So, anyone
that's worked has never beat me then? Yeah.
Yeah. Okay, bro.
Like, so even when you stand up to men,
they still have excuses. I'm done.
Greavves, I'm a bully, by the way. Uh,
if you stand up to a narcissistic,
toxic, entitled woman, uh, you're, uh,
you're a bully. Do you know what that
reminds me of? That reminds me of these
narcissistic women that call you a
stalker when you stand up for yourself?
That it doesn't that just remind you of
that? I was thinking about this. I was
like, "Oh, that's that's exactly what a
narcissistic woman uh would say if if
they're uh if they're like trying to
habitually mock someone and then they
stand up to themselves."
The these people really really really
don't ever have they've never been with
a woman. It's so obvious, bro, that
these people I'm I'm sure, Joe, 90% of
these people are virgins cuz anyone that
goes out in the real world would know
that women are stuck up. They know that
they've got attitude problems. I don't
care about it. I'm only responding to
these [ __ ] comments. You know,
anybody that has a life would know that
because it's England. So, it's like
what? They might not agree with
everything that I say, but they would be
like, "Oh, well, yeah, they are kind of
stuck up women." In other words, they
wouldn't be defending every bad thing
that they do if they had a life.
They're mad. They're actually mad.
Madness. Absolute madness.
So by their logic then if a woman's
giving you [ __ ] you're not allowed to
defend yourself because it's not a man.
So you have to go for a man if you
defend yourself against a woman. That's
their logic. But yeah, even if you
defend yourself against a man, we hear
another million one excuses why they
can't hit you. So anyways, we just
realize that it's just a waste of time
posting anything on here anymore. Yeah.
How long have these people been asking
you to do a video,
sticking it on someone, sticking it on
someone, sticking it on someone? Then
you stick it on someone and they still make excuses.
Joe, I don't care about what happened on
Saturday, bro. I just I don't care. I
got two replies, by the way, and I don't
give a [ __ ]
I'm not asked about that. I'm asked
about the comments. What do you you
think was going to happen?
What? Suddenly women weren't going to
stop start stop start stop start stop
start stop start stop start stop start
start stop being [ __ ] they're always
going to be the same that's not I don't
care about that you know
I might do a foul today I might do a
foul challenge I might I might have a lamb foul
I saw that vindaloo thing that l done
and he could barely he could barely
stomach it so I might I might try a foul
see how see how good I
might go to like a curry house or something.
But yeah, it is a race thing. Of course,
it's a race thing, bro. What else would
it be? What else would it be?
Madness, bro. You do have to question
these people. You do have to question
Did I not say to the guy, does he want
to meet me outside of work? It doesn't
matter if I was going to do anything or not. You
was going to and then he and and yeah
and he he's and then he's trying to
stick up for them students, bro. Them
students were just being entitled
[ __ ] They probably didn't even
realize what was going on, right? What
was what was their first comment, Joe?
That he's going to spark you out. I said
he could try it. He's going to spark you
out. Why would someone say that, bro?
They're full of excuses. Full of
I'll tell you something, Joe. You know
what he told me before? He said that if
you went if you went if you go to
America and you beat that Charles up,
then he would go for me.
He would go for me.
So, it's a diff It is a race thing. Of
course, it's a race thing. I don't know
what his obsession is.
I don't know what his obsession is with
black people or white people, but
they them people were pissing me off
more. Them four people were pissing me
off more than the bouncer.
They were pissing me off more than them
and they were [ __ ] white.
[ __ ] all [ __ ]
So yeah, Joe, that's why I don't really
go out much anymore, bro. I like the
peace and quiet.
It's too toxic. I like peace and quiet,
bro. How can you get bored?
How can you get bored of [ __ ] uh
peace and quiet?
You can't, eh? No.
I [ __ ] can't.
Oh, Joe, I almost got a football bet in
by the way. I got [ __ ] by a goal. I
got a treble both score. No, I done a
treble both score. No draw. [ __ ] I
needed one goal. [ __ ] me proper, man.
[ __ ] me good and proper.
We got two repliers out of five.
So, is it okay for women to bully people then, Grezy?
Like that woman talking about that man's
forehead. So, it's okay for women to bully people.
It's okay for women to bully people. Bye-bye.
So, by by their logic, it's okay for
women to bully people.
It doesn't matter if it wasn't me. I
don't care if it wasn't me. It's still
the whole point.
I would never get with a woman who said
that, bro. That is ick. That is ick.
Even though it wasn't about me. No, that
is ick. Like you wasn't speaking about
their appearance. You were setting the
record straight. Not bullying.
Again, not bullying. You need to learn
the concept of bullying.
You telling someone about themselves is
not bullying. What people here try to do
every day is well, they try to bully
people, but they don't bully people. So,
but it's okay for women to bully people.
They're allowed to bully people, but we
we can't sign up for ourel cuz we're bullying. It's okay. Interesting.
Interesting, boss. Interesting.
Yeah, that is interesting. Very
And then the other people just make
excuses whether they're black or [ __ ]
white. So yeah,
madness. It is mad. It is mad.
Oh, dear me.
What do you do? Eh, mad.
Yeah, I might try that foul.
I'm just asking questions, Greavves. I'm
just making f I'm just making I'm just
making friends here, you know.
I just want to know why everything they
do gets dismissed.
Well, [snorts] that's that.
Well, I'm going to make a couple cut in a minute. Yep.
I don't know.
But what I'm saying, Grezy, right? If
you stand up to a woman who's being
toxic and rude, they're calling you a bully, right?
Yeah, when you go for several different
men in one night, they're full of excuses.
And then when
uh but then when a woman talks about a
man's appearance that they don't know,
that's not bullying them. So there it's
okay for them to bully people. It
doesn't matter if it wasn't me. I don't
give a [ __ ] if it wasn't me. It still it
still annoyed me, right? So they're
allowed to bully random people, but you
stand up for yourself and you're a bully.
Okay then, bro. Yeah. And you're right.
They don't need white knights.
So it's like it's weird. It's so weird,
man. It is weird.
And if that guy defended himself, he'd
be called a bully. Do you understand?
These white knights are pathetic.
really really really really are prophetic
and you can just tell that they've never
been with a woman. You can tell this
Ricky Millington is clearly a virgin,
you know, clearly. It is clear now.
I'd love to see that uh L do the
Caroline Reaper burger. He would be [ __ ]
He would actually be [ __ ] bro.
He'd be [ __ ]
That would actually kill him like it
almost killed me.
I reckon I could do the foul. What do
you think, Greasy?
Well, obviously again, I have to run it.
I have to run it by you first, boss.
Okay with you, boss.
Make it so.
Joe. Okay, boss.
Okay with you, [ __ ]
You little virgin, Kanya.
You nasty virgin. Um,
you're not going to pop it like that
now, are you?
One day you
Oh, [ __ ] me, man. [ __ ] me.
How's that working?
I'm [snorts] deleting a video soon. I'm
going to block him from my channel.
Yeah, I'm going to block him from my
channel, lad. I should block a few
people from here to be honest.
Yeah, I reckon I could do a foul to be
honest. I think I could do it. Members only
$2.99 a month. Bro,
white nights are pathetic. Is it Jasper?
Do a steak.
What do you mean do a steak?
Yeah, I was thinking of going for a foul, bro.
Yeah, I know, man.
I could do a steak. Yeah, but I got to
go to the [ __ ] butchers.
The butcher is not open on Monday. That
butcher, there's only one butcher you
can get the t-bone from and it's not
open on a Monday. Not sure.
I don't know what I'm doing, guys.
So many bloody white knights on here.
Women don't need white knights. Yep.
What's that? Yeah. Dude,
no. No, no. Going [snorts]
to make myself a tea in a minute. Yeah.
>> [clears throat]
>> I need to make it too, Man, [ __ ] sake. >> [snorts]
>> How are you going to pop it? How you
going to lose it?
How you going to lose it? Virgin boy. another time
been delus since I was a bubian like the virgin
take it the virgin
the skinn virgin in a bed Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Tippy and the TP and the TP and the
so westernized. It's disgusting.
You owned me, did you? [ __ ] to me. Link. Yeah.
Hey, is that Kieran? Hello, boss.
You all right?
Had a bit of madness over the weekend. Um, yeah.
Had a bit of a madness, lad.
Madness. I need to make myself a tea in
a minute. uh might go for a foul today.
Yeah, that LT Yeah, was saying about how
he started [ __ ] with me because he was
trying to say about how the guy can't
defend himself cuz he's at work. That's
what I mean. It's always excuses with
these people, bro. Whether it's women,
even when you stand up to a man, I can't
be bothered with these simple tins.
Really can't be bothered with these
simple tins, lad.
It's just like, yeah, I got five
numbers. Uh, I got five numbers and only
two of them replied casual. So,
that's that in it.
It's some madness in it.
Like it, bro. Like it madness. It [ __ ] sake. Yeah. Yeah, man.
What do you think of all the madness? Kieran
deleting it uh later. Uh
[ __ ] light on uh
Why don't you shut up? You stupid [ __ ]
You stupid [ __ ] Huh?
You shut up.
You [ __ ] [ __ ] >> [snorts]
>> Did you see [ __ ] Lord J with the Vindaloo casual?
I've been eating it since I was a baby.
I've been eating Vindaloo since I was a Bubba. Say, you know.
[snorts] Yeah, Mom.
you need to keep up with them filters, love.
Them filters are not they're not [ __ ]
they're not doing you any any any good, you know,
now, isn't it? Yep.
Yeah. I might go for an Indian today.
Try that foul. Yeah.
do a little foul challenge. See how how
how uh how good and I'm not going to
make you pay for it. I'm not going to
pay you. I'm not going to make you pay
for the video.
Mate, I saw L J. Yeah, he was struggling
that Vindeloo. He was struggling, bro.
He's like the girl tenant. She was
struggling to have like a bite. And
there's me just whiffing it down. I'm
yamming it. I'm yamming it. You know
what I mean?
Yeah. I'm [ __ ] yamming it down, lad. So,
I was like Lord Jay when I had the
Carolina Reaper burger and that's the
hottest thing in the world.
Nah, that burger, mate. It kill you, it
will. It almost [ __ ] killed me. So,
I'm going to try this foul, you know.
But he's like nonslegs. They both can't take spice.
Yeah. Some people just can't take spice.
Nah. K. I love a vinderoo, lad.
What did you think about them four [ __ ]
trying to get involved?
You [ __ ] off. I said you [ __ ] off.
Glad I [ __ ] defended myself.
It wasn't so much the bouncer. I don't
give a [ __ ] about him.
The the the
I I I'm just glad I [ __ ] defended
myself against them pricks. Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Imagine that, bro. I was talking to
their [ __ ] girls like that, bro. And
they weren't going to do nothing. Who's
that? They weren't gonna do nothing.
They weren't about to do nothing.
That's why I don't go out much, Kieran.
That is full of [ __ ] in this country.
It's just full of absolute [ __ ]
That's why I just like nah, can't be
bothered with them.
full of [ __ ] in it.
Nah, bro. Nah,
me and Timmy is a tag team now. Did you know this?
Uh me and Timmy's a tag team uh now, bro.
Give the time. You should have noticed. [snorts] Yeah.
You shouldn't be saying about her being
washed. You know, Kieran, you shouldn't
be telling her that she's washed. You're
going to get all the white knights after
you. The little white knights
that defend women [ __ ] they're
they're the worst kind of people. White knights.
Have you noticed that Kieran? Right.
They dismiss any bad thing that they do.
Like I told these people yesterday that
I was approaching with a guy and this
woman told him to sort his forehead out.
He's got a big forehead.
They didn't uh have anything to say about that. Nope.
Nope. They have no opinion on that.
Why do they dismiss that stuff? I don't get it.
They don't dismiss anything that you do. Nope. Yeah.
Sounds about right, lad. Sounds about right.
I think I need a filling, you know.
I think I do need to fill in.
Oh, he's he's a he's a he's a crazy
virgin. He is, mate.
He's a crazy crazy virgin. That [ __ ]
That Ricky Millington says that I'm
bullying women because I stood up for myself. Bullying.
Bullying. He said he would never say
that to a man. Yeah. Yeah. It's not like
I stuck it on like four men Saturday, is
it? Nah. Nah. Nah, bro. Nah.
Nah. Nah nah nah nah. Only women, mate,
in it. Yeah. Yeah. Only go for women. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's no point entertaining these
little mongos on here, bro. There's no
point going back and forth with these little mongos.
I stood up to several different men on
Saturday. Yeah. And there was one that
you didn't see. Someone was like, "Oh,
you need to lay off the cocaine." And I
said, "We're not all crackheads like
you. We're not all [ __ ] crackheads."
Yeah. I don't do that [ __ ] The only
thing that I do is drink. Yeah. We're
not all crackheads like you. You might
want to mind your own [ __ ] business.
I didn't I didn't upload that because
they say that you only go for men, right? Women
yet. When you go for men,
several excuses are to be had. Oh,
they're at work. Okay, they're at work.
Okay, let me try and meet the guy after
work then. Nothing. Okay, so then
there's two people sat there drinking. I
start on them. They don't want any of
it. So what, bro? You know, it's just
you can't win on here. They're full of excuses.
Even when you stick it on men, they're
full of excuses.
But when that black guy on the bus, Kieran,
was having a go at me, you remember the
black guy on the bus, there was no
problems there. No problems to be had.
No problems whatsoever. When that black
guy was going for me on the bus, no one
said that he was a coward because he
knows that, you know, he can't do
anything to me and I can't do anything
to him cuz he's working. Nope. Had no
problems with it. But as soon as it's to
do with someone backing down against
you, oh, they can't do anything cuz
they're at work.
See, [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. It's
bollocks. They're all little mongos. The
best thing to do is just to not get into
it with any of these people in here anymore. Yeah.
So, what's your honest opinion on the
videos then, Kieran?
What's your honest opinion on them?
I had a go at that girl because she was
running her mouth up and she was
shouting, trying to tell me what to do.
What did you want me to do? Sit there
like a [ __ ]
You know what I mean? Sit there like a [ __ ]
No, bro. No.
That's what I mean. It's like it's one
rule for one, one rule for another.
You know what I mean? A woman, she can
bully a man. That's no problem. She can
verbally bully, she can verbally bully a
man. But you dare put any of these women
in their place, mate. You're a bully.
[ __ ] retards. I swear to God, they're
[ __ ] retards on here, bro. I'm so
done with them, man. Um, I [ __ ] am. They're idiots. Yep.
Yep. Yeah. Well, he asked me for ID
knowing that I was clearly of age. I
said, "Okay." Then he started Then he
started kissing his teeth at me.
So what was I supposed to do?
I said, "Don't kiss your teeth at me and
give me attitude." That's what I said to him.
And I also had a woman defend me as
well. Like I said, I didn't record it,
but there was a woman that actually did
defend me. She's like, "Why are you
asking this guy for ID when he's
obviously clearly looks of age?"
And then her friends were
Yeah, them four people. So, them two
guys, they knew they were going to get
[ __ ] up. That's why they didn't do
anything. Them four people that was sat
at the table knew they were going to get [ __ ] up.
Yeah, that's the only Imagine that. Is it?
Nah. Nah. He sounded African, but imagine
I think he come here yesterday as well.
He said, "Yeah, when you come here
yesterday, he was waiting outside."
Mad, is it? [ __ ] mad.
Yeah, I got five numbers and two replied.
It's the same thing, right?
One messages you
one messages you, you message them back,
and then they don't reply. Same [ __ ]
Nice to meet you as well. I said, "Did
you get back to France?" Okay. No
response to be had.
It's the same thing. That doesn't bother
me, bro. It's these [ __ ] stupid people commenting.
I'm surprised this one reply back to be fair,
but it is what it is, man. But that's
what I'm saying. Anyways, it's too
they're too stuck up. Uh
they're still they're too stuck up. Um
K and lad.
Yeah, they're too stuck up, bro. Yep.
Oh, another thing, Kier. I don't I don't
know. Treble both score a low draw.
Uh Saturday, bro. One team let me down.
All I needed was [ __ ] spenny more to
score and I would I would have got a
treble both score. No draw.
Bollocks, mate. [ __ ] bollocks. I got
two out of three. I both score. No draw.
I was so close. [gasps]
So close, man. So close.
This much away. This much away, bro.
The bollocks there.
So they reply back, but they don't want
to get into it.
I don't know, bro. They're [ __ ]
weird, is it?
But it will never change, will it, Kieran?
Oh, don't say that.
I was really hoping they were going to
score, man. I was so close.
Kieran, I was so close, lad.
Yeah, two of the games was 2-1 and that
was 2-0. Just if that was 2-1 as well,
that would have been lovely. Bastards.
He's not coming for no one. The little
puff. If I can stick on that amount of
people, bro, you think I'm going to be
scared of some little wimp like Terry?
Some little wimp like Terry, bro? Come on. Please.
There was a woman I was speaking to from
Manchester um casual and she said, "What
are you doing?" And I told her, I
approached her sober. It's the first
number I got. And she seemed all right.
She seemed down to earth and she didn't
reply. I'm surprised to be honest.
That is weird.
That is very, very strange.
Yeah, that's very strange, isn't it?
That is strange lad.
That is a bit bit weird.
Never change, would it? Ken,
I had sausage and mash yesterday, bro.
I'm having some uh
I'm going to go for an Indian today. Yeah.
No, it's just uh it's just they're all biased.
That's all it is on here. K is they're just biased. Biased people.
That's what they are. Just biased people, lad.
Vindeloo chicken ticker pillow rice
cheese naan. Done.
Yeah, cheese naan.
Sometimes I get madress, but mostly it's
vindal, especially in the winter.
So, I'm going to make myself a tea now
anyways. Oh, [ __ ] [snorts]
You're virgin. You're virgin, can't you?
Your virgin [ __ ] Yeah. [snorts] [laughter]
We gave him a good hiding. What do you
think of them four people mouthing off Ken? Huh?
Yeah, but they weren't about it though, were they?
But they weren't [ __ ] about it, were
they, mate? Do you want to see my little boxes? Chucky boxes. Chucky. Yeah. Yeah,
we don't train. [laughter]
I wish you was with me, Kevin.
I wish you was with me, lad. [laughter]
Can't move that football bet, mate. [ __ ] S. [laughter]
So, we know that he's always watching
me. We know that London T is always watching me. Yeah. >> [laughter]
>> Isn't that right?
I think so.
You like my little videos, Kaye? [snorts] [laughter]
These women are so bloody stuck up.
Ricky Millington is never going to get
laid. He's gonna die a virgin
just like Nons. Kieran.
Kieran, he's gonna [ __ ] die one.
I need to [ __ ] I need to start working soon.
Kieran, before the fun start drying up.
Before the fun start drying up, lads. [laughter]
Yeah, it's always and and again it was
cuz the guy was black. It's not cuz he's
the bouncer. It's cuz the guy was black.
Them students was like, "Spark him out."
I said, "Bro, he's not even he that's
never going to happen.
That's never going to happen."
Yeah, that's never going to happen. They
got involved and then they shut it. So
what's the point? This country is full
of [ __ ] bro.
It actually I swear down it's full of
[ __ ] This country
full of absolute [ __ ]
I can't believe he's going to be 31 in February.
He's still a virgin hearing.
I might give him a tip on how to lose it
over the weekend. I'll do a little football bet.
I'm going to do a little football bet
and [ __ ] uh
I'm going to do a little football bet and um
yeah, I'll do a little football bet and
say you're going to win it. I got an
escort on the Saturday as well here. And
yeah, I got a
I done a football bet, lad. Sorry, I got
an escort. What am I talking about? Got
an escort. Sorry, bro. [ __ ] Yeah. Oh
yeah, me 120. So
I'm so tempted to go big on roulette,
you know, bro.
but I'm not going to do it, bro. So I
still get sometime. Not really. Do you
know what it is? It's more when I've drunk.
I tell you what it is, Kieran. It's
more, you know, when you've dr, I don't
know about you, but when you've drunk
and you've had these bad experiences with women,
you think, and obviously the alcohol,
I'm still a bit hung over and [ __ ] you
feel, oh, let me just go on roulette to
get a buzz. So, that's what I'm saying.
It's a never ending um
it's a neverending um
cycle in this country
until you leave. That's what I mean.
Like, obviously, I'm not going to do it,
but it's a it's a never- ending cycle here.
You know what I mean? It's a [ __ ] country, bro.
Mainly because the people, to be honest with you.
The people are just such [ __ ]
Such [ __ ] in this country, bro.
I know. He's a crazy virgin. He's a
crazy mad virgin. What I don't
understand, Kieran, is why when I go at
him calling him a virgin, everyone backs
him up saying, "Oh, uh, he's got a
girlfriend. He's got a girlfriend." But
then when he slab is about me, oh that's
completely all right. That's completely
okay. No problem there.
So he can sit there slabbing about me,
calling me this, calling me that, and no
one talks about the porno that I put up.
But him, oh, he's got a girlfriend. See,
they're bullshitters on here, bro.
Bullshitter. That's why I left for two
weeks, cuz they're bullshitters.
It's the same atmosphere. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't even watch Monty man anymore.
I go to I don't know if to go to a
restaurant today. I'm not sure. I know
what I'm doing.
The women are stuck up in this country.
Ain't it Karen?
Well, that person's not reply back.
Same old, isn't it?
They reply, then you reply back, and
then they don't reply,
which is weird.
Then this other one replied back saying
they had to go Simmons bar cuz I had
problem with a bouncer. They move a
voice note and then they stopped.
Then the other ones didn't reply. So weird.
Good old England. E Karen. Good old
You could always count on England for
bad experiences, mate.
So it's weird how I got two replies out
of five, but then out of 10 I got one.
So it's random. It was just a It's just all random.
You need to be very very very very very very lucky. Um yeah,
you need to be very very lucky, lad, to
even get a date now.
That's why Reddit is [ __ ] cuz Reddit
sits there and say they get sex and
stuff. Kieran, they're liars, isn't it?
They're too extreme on Reddit. They're liars. Yeah.
They're liars, lad.
They say they got they say go on the
apps to get sex.
Bollocks, mate. [ __ ] bollocks. Is it? [clears throat]
I want to play some roulette, Kieran. Not.
Nah, bro. [ __ ] that.
Absolutely [ __ ] that lad. I might go
to a restaurant.
So yeah, Joe, I got five numbers, two
replied, but one stopped. So good old
England, eh? I think I needed what I
needed that to happen, you know, last
month. I needed me spending that amount
of money and getting them 10 numbers to
really accept what it's like here cuz I
was like, it's just good old England,
isn't it? What can you say? You know,
there's nothing to get annoyed about. It
would always be the same here. So that
was actually a cheap lesson to be honest, lad. [snorts]
Just good old England. What else would
you expect, you know, in this [ __ ] country?
I fancy going big on roulette Joe.
They're going to have to do something
soon because the funds are going to
start drying up
12 days. Yeah,
but it's getting worse. It is definitely
getting worse this country.
But I got an escort on Saturday anyways,
Joe. So I spent over the weekend 250
which I I was I didn't think that was
bad, but I got an escort which was 120. So
yeah, I thought that was all right to be honest.
I don't know where 500 went last time, but yeah.
Oh, Joe, I was saying that I done a
treble both score no draw and two of the
games was 2-1 and the last one was 2-0
and I just needed one goal and it didn't win.
Yep. And to finish in their mouth.
You know me, mate. I'd pay a million dollars
just to get that.
No, I'm joking, bro. But yeah, it did.
Yeah, cuz they don't like people coming
in their mouth.
Oh, almost, bro. I almost got a treble
both score, no draw. [ __ ]
One go off. I could have done with that.
237 [ __ ] quid.
I'm going to do a double both score, no
draw on Saturday. I'm going to put like
100 pound on it.
Maybe 80 pound on it. It returns like
600 700 in it.
I'm going to do slow and kitty minister.
[ __ ] bastard, man.
If I had 80 pound on it, that would have
been brutal, bro. If I had 80 pound on
that, I would have been brutal.
Not me, mate. The funds are okay so far,
Joe. The funds are all right. The funds are okay, you know.
I always get an escort after going out
drinking. It's always what I do. I don't
know. I do it most of the time.
Yeah, I do I do Northern League. I do
the Northern League and the South League.
If I had £80 on that, bro, I would have
cried. I'm not going to lie to you. If I
had 80 pound on that same bet, I would have cried.
That's like over £1,000 in it. So
[ __ ] sake, man.
I might give roulette a little while. Joe Joseph.
Now, do you believe me, Joe, that I'm
not scared of anyone? And LT even said
that if I went to America and I beat up
Charles, then he would beat me up.
So, it is a race thing. It's got nothing
to do with somebody being a bouncer.
I'm going to block that dude off my
channel anyways. He's weird, bro. I'm
gonna block him.
Yeah, I'm gonna block him, bro. I think
I'm gonna have to block him from my
channel eventually, bro. It's too weird.
The atmosphere is too weird.
Nah, I can't, bro.
I can't afford to be losing money nowadays.
I'll do the football on Saturday and Yeah.
Can't believe I was one go off £237
or£20. [ __ ] sake, man. Well, I
couldn't spend any more. Just [ __ ]
And I heard they missed the penalty as well.
It's bollocks, isn't it?
It's bollocks, isn't it? Joseph for
Yeah, but I'm going to have to put money
in it. I'm going to have to put money on
it though, are I?
So, it's not going to be one spin, is it?
Yeah, but it's not going to be one spin,
is it, bro?
Let's be real, huh? Yeah.
So, what? Like £50 or something? No, I'm
not doing that, bro. If I want if I want
to do it, I want to go on a big session.
There's no point doing one spin.
Nah, there's no point.
No, I'm all right, bro. I'm not ging.
[ __ ] it. I can get out I can get out
out. I can get out an advanced loan.
>> I'm not even short of money, but I'm
short of money compared to how I think
I'm short of money. Not short of money
to most people.
I think having £1,300 is short of money.
Some people don't see it as that. 133,400 pound.
I think that's kind of short of money.
Even though realistically it's [ __ ]
not, is it? See, that's the thing, bro.
So, I don't want to have to worry about
money. I don't want to be worrying about
That's the thing.
I the first woman the second woman I
approached on Saturday um Kieran guess
what she said that she's 16 even though
she clearly wasn't
even though she clearly wasn't
see the NPCs
how nonsleg say they're not the same
he's got [ __ ] in his eyes how that
virgin can go around saying they're not
the same is mad he is
He's a He's an idiot, lad. How he really
can can think that they're not all the
same is beyond me. Oh, yeah.
I'm already timed out. I'd have to untie
myself out. And I'm not doing that, bro.
I can't be bothered.
She was obviously older than 16 obviously, bro.
That's what they say. I said, "Oh, I
think I I think I don't know. I I think
I complimented them. I was sober as well
and they said, "Oh, I'm 16."
Yeah, they're NPCs.
They literally say the same stuff. They
have the same mannerisms. They're all
the same, bro. What the [ __ ] How does
he sit there and say they're not all the same?
How can he sit there and say that these
women are not all the same? I shall never know.
Well, we do know he's a [ __ ] s.
She clearly was older than that, bro.
They're just [ __ ] in it.
They're just [ __ ] delayed.
He He wouldn't have the balls to do it.
He's got anxiety. He can't chat at
women. He's got too much anxiety.
So, how much do you think we should deposit, Kieran?
I don't want to gamble, bro. I'm not
gambling. [ __ ] that. I'm not gambling.
No, I'm not doing it. No point even
bringing it up, bro. I ain't gambling, you lad. Nah.
No, I'm not doing it. [ __ ] that. No.
Yeah, you have to be autistic mole to huh?
What the [ __ ] you're talking about?
I don't know what I'm doing, bro. I'm not gambling.
They say we get too deep in it and we
lose money, Ken. We're [ __ ]
That's the thing. We'll be [ __ ] then.
So, we would actually be [ __ ]
See, £600 in your account might be
enough for you, but it ain't enough for me, bro.
Let's just say hypothetically I lost all
my money. Yeah. And I get £800.
I'll have like £800. Yeah. It's not
enough, is it? So,
I get money this week. I get 800 this
week, but I always carry over or like to
carry body over.
You know what I mean?
You know how it is, isn't it?
I always end up coming over the same
amount of money every month though to be fair.
Yeah, I end up coming over the same
amount of money.
Let me have a look. Hold on.
Yeah, but what about the virgin in a bedit?
They charge you a two pound fee to
deposit, by the way.
Yeah, they charge you a two pound fee to deposit.
So, how much money will you have when
you get paid this week? How much money
will you have when you get paid? Yeah. Oh.
Oh, so you got £300 to last you the month.
It's not a good idea. I can work if I
want to. I've got the opportunity to
work, which is probably to be honest
what I'm going to have to start doing
soon to be to be fair
cuz the money will dry up very quickly.
I mean, I could go out drinking every
week if I want to, but I'm not short of
money like what most people would think
is short of money, but you get what I
mean, ain't it?
Don't know. It's [ __ ] up, is it?
Yeah. So, you've got that to last year
for you. Yeah.
What the [ __ ] are you going to do, bro?
Nah, there's no point, bro.
I'd rather just do a football bet on Saturday. One spin.
There's no point, bro. There's no point.
I'll just end up losing it all, bro. So,
there's no point.
But I'd want to put 250 in.
I'd want to put 250 in, bro, and have
like a big session, like 50 pound spins. But >> yeah,
that'll leave me with like a thousand
and something I think. So yeah.
Yeah, it's harder to afford nowadays,
Joseph, for uh
leave me like a thousand and something. So
then I'll be [ __ ] So yeah,
cuz I'd want to do, like I said, like 50
lb spins. I'm not I'm not doing one spin, bro.
It isn't enough, bro. It isn't enough.
Cuz if I want to go out drinking, it
isn't enough. Because if I want to go
out drinking, I'm be I'll be [ __ ] So,
so that's the thing. And I would need to
get a haircut again in like a couple of
weeks. So, it wouldn't be enough. yeah,
we'll be [ __ ] up in it, Joseph. For real.
We [ __ ] up.
I had to buy some trade. I have to
be [ __ ] bro.
I'll get this loan thing out. I can get
this loan thing, but
I can't be bothered bringing them up.
And that that's the thing.
Yeah. I can't be bothered bringing the bastards up.
Yeah. Uh just an advanced loan. You get
an advanced loan every year once you've
paid it off. You pay it back. No
interest. It's only like £350.
Might as well just get in it.
You pay the same amount. It's interest
free. So they just take it out of your
um take out of your money.
There you go.
No, I paid it.
No, I paid it, bro.
I always get every year anyways. I
always have. So,
so obviously I could gamble and then if I lose,
we could do that, but I don't really
like the thoughts of gambling anymore,
bro. Too many bad memories. I like to
learn from my mistakes.
I like to really learn from the mistakes delayed.
That's the thing.
No, I'm not doing it, bro. I can't do
it, Dad. I can't do it. [ __ ] that.
I can't do it, bro. Sorry, man.
Sorry, bro. I just ordered the football
bats and stuff, but I'm not doing that.
I'll do the football bets. I don't mind, lad.
Doing the football bets every week.
I wish I could just win a football bet
every week for a month.
Is a National North League and South
League playing next week?
Tell me if you know.
What did I think? Uh, he's a [ __ ]
That's why I thought he was a [ __ ] No,
I'm joking. I I didn't I didn't see
anything wrong with it. What did you
think of my videos, Joseph? You didn't
give your opinion on my videos. Yeah.
I thought I was a pretty cool [ __ ] Me.
I'd love to win some money though, bro.
Where the money would be lash, would it [sighs]
I like that global. I like the global
draw through that.
Do you think I was in the right or do
you think I was in the wrong
in the videos? Huh? Oh,
I hear that in the casino when I watch
Seven Neighbors sometimes. That that
voice, no more bets, please. It's just
like so like it gets my heart going,
bro. I remember all them. I just
remember it from like the casino days.
I remember it from the casino days.
Oh, it's terrifying.
The atmosphere in the casino, you know,
it's Oh, it's a madness. So,
yeah, I'd love to go. I I'd love to try
it, but I can't try.
I can't gamble, bro.
can't risk losing. Then I'll be [ __ ]
Then it's have then I'll have to get the
money back somehow. So then I'll be screwed.
No, I'm not gambling, bro. [ __ ] Oh no. Nah.
I need to start work soon as well. Yep.
[ __ ] It [snorts]
look at my hair, bro. It is grow fast. Nah,
my hair, bro. Think I'm going to go out next week.
I think my hair will still look good,
though. So, I might get a haircut the week after.
Kind of winter now, is it? So, I think
I'll be out on
maybe Friday this time. I don't know.
I'll be out this week again.
make use of this haircut. I think it
should be all right for another few days.
What do you think, Joseph Farah?
What do you think, Joseph Fra?
Yeah, but that's not going to happen.
You're going to lose the [ __ ] You're
going to lose the 100 pound, though.
Yeah, but you're going to lose the Yeah,
we're going to lose £100. So, what's the point?
No, I ain't gambling, bro.
I won money gambling, didn't I? So, [snorts]
I saved some money so I was able to buy
jeans and stuff.
Ah, that' be a lovely site, wouldn't it?
Imagine that. Eh,
be a lovely site.
No, [clears throat] I'm not I'm not
wasting money, bro. Sorry, matey.
Peter Bell is poor nowadays. lad.
So, I'm going to go to a restaurant
today, get that curry, that foul curry,
see what it's saying.
Yeah, I put 50 on the global draw roulet
and I got it to 150, so I just took it.
Is that okay with you, boss?
No, I'm just going to stick to the
[ __ ] football bets.
Yeah, I'm just going to stick with the football bets. Wow.
What do you think of that, Greavves? Uh,
what do you think of that? Joseph Farah.
Joseph Farra. Sticking with the football
bets. Joseph Farra.
Do you like that Joseph Ferrar? Joseph Ferrara.
But what you think 11,200 pound is enough? Joseph Farah.
Is that what you're really saying? Joseph Ferra. [ __ ] sake.
What's only once a week?
How is 111,200 enough? You silly goose?
Uh, not really, matey.
Well, I spent £400 on Well, it depends
what outgoings you have.
I had 7 I think I had 1,700. If I had if
I could get to that again, then I'll be
all right because
I need to buy a new phone at some point
as well cuz this phone's blocked. And yeah. So yeah,
I don't know, man.
Are you doing a football bet on Saturday?
Yeah. What do you think of the hair? Do
you think I can go out on Saturday
looking like this, or do you think I'll
need another haircut?
Nah, I think this is all right. Me, I'll
get a haircut next week.
Got to make use of the jeans and the trainers.
I done good for someone that don't work
in it. I got this TV, got the trainers,
got the jeans.
I done pretty [ __ ] good to be fair.
Well, of course it's going to be washed and clean.
The annoying thing is getting your haircut.
I hate getting my haircut. It's so
boring. Sitting on a chair for an hour
is boring. So, I'll be out on Saturday. And
I need to start having somewhat of a
[ __ ] life now. You know,
I was in saving and it wasn't cuz I
didn't have the money. is because I was
[ __ ] sick of [ __ ]
It was cuz I was sick of um
It was cuz I was sick of these [ __ ]
uh these [ __ ] and that these women.
That's why I That's why I stayed in.
Won some money. Bought some trainers,
bought some jeans.
So, I put I would put 300 pound Joe on
two teams. But
if I was to do that, I would just
[ __ ] I'd rather just put it on the
roulette and do 50 spins, you know?
I do [ __ ] 50 spins to be fair.
Like even like 250, what's the [ __ ]
point, bro? Put on the football. You
might as well put on the [ __ ]
roulette in it
if you think about it. Is it
Yeah, that's what I'm Yeah. Exactly. Exactly. Exactly.
I remember the first two season, the
first games of the season, I won money
on roulette, sorry, on the football and
there were nice wins as well. 80 to 280,
then 80 to 230,
which is pretty [ __ ] good. Yeah, it
might not be huge profit, but bro, it's
still [ __ ] money, is it? If you won
that every If you done that every week,
right? If you done that every week then um
well you'll be laughing in it
if you won every week. You'd be [ __ ]
laughing about it.
So you said the most you put on a
football is 100, is it? Yeah.
Yeah. [ __ ] thank you days of done, bro.
So I know these numbers.
No more reply backs. Nope.
I just said to this person, "Did you get
back to France?" Okay. And I haven't replied.
I don't understand why they reply then.
Don't reply to your next message.
Strange, isn't it? Very, very, very strange.
It's strange yo. It's strange but it
will never change. So
you know strange but won't change.
Grezy not greasy. Sorry Joseph for
saying [ __ ] why I just said greasy.
You're not greasy.
But you get me in it. You get me lad.
You [ __ ] get me lad don't you? You know,
madness, bro. Madness. Jo, [snorts]
you're an addict, Joseph, fella.
What's the time? 9:56. I'm going to go
to this restaurant in a couple of hours.
I want to copy LJ's channel.
I'm the copycat for today.
Isn't that right? I'm the copycat.
No, I can't afford it, man. I'm skint.
I'm skinn like the virgin.
I'm skimp like the opened virgin.
Yeah, I'm skipping like the orbiting virgin lad. Oh, [ __ ]
I'm scared, mate.
[ __ ] skip, mate.
if you want. Yeah, like I won last time,
is it? That was a lovely site. That was
a [ __ ] lovely site, lad.
That was a [ __ ] lovely sight.
Yeah, but what if I lose Joseph Ferrar?
Then I'll be screwed Joseph Farra.
If I lose, I'll be screwed. Joseph
Farah, won't I? Huh?
[clears throat] I'll be [ __ ]
When will be [ __ ] won't we? When will
we'll be [ __ ] Yeah,
Joseph. Then we'll be [ __ ] won't we?
Huh? Then we will be [ __ ]
Remember when that guy What that guy
Birmingham said? When that guy in
Birmingham said that. Yeah. [snorts]
Nah, bro. I'm not I'm not doing it.
Can't be doing that them things, matey. >> [sighs] [snorts]
>> I'll go to the restaurant today and put
a video up. But yeah,
that's that, lad. >> [snorts]
>> They charge you like a two pound fee
when you deposit as well. Joseph for
even though when they send you your winnings,
but when they give you your winnings,
they don't. It's weird. Yeah,
Red Star stalking me again. Leave me alone.
You fat ugly [ __ ] You little stalker.
You fat ugly stalker. You little sausage fingers. [snorts] Yeah.
What do you mean? Don't be taking a
detour like going to the bookies. You
mean ain't it?
Nah, don't worry.
Nah. Why' I do that, man?
Why the [ __ ] would I be doing that? Dad. Huh?
>> [snorts and clears throat]
>> Nah, not at all, man. I go to the
bookies. I go past the bookies all the time.
I go past the bookies all the time, man.
Why the [ __ ] would I do that?
Why would I do that? Yeah, LT was
outside the house yesterday apparently.
Gre uh apparently Joseph Ferrar.
Huh? Yeah. Apparently so.
Apparently so. Joseph Farra.
It's strange, isn't it?
All because I argued with a black bouncer
and I questioned his logic and he
started getting assy with me.
Then he started getting ary with me, lad. Yeah. Bit weird,
right? Do you want me to do this through
that thing? Really?
No. I can't afford to be losing money,
bro. Really can't afford to be losing money.
That's the thing. Yeah.
No, I'm not doing it, bro. [ __ ] that.
Pointless. It's pointless. Absolutely Yeah.
Cuz then I'll be screwed if I lose. Matey matey. So yeah. >> [sighs] [gasps]
>> Now we [ __ ] them. So yeah, [snorts]
that's what you want. You want to see me
skint like the virgin, don't you? To zip it far.
You want to see me skint like that
Orington virgin? Don't lie to me, mate.
Don't lie to me, son.
You want to see me skint like the Orington virgin?
It's not happening, mate. Ain't happening.
That's what you want to see, don't you,
mate? Yeah. It's not going to work,
mate. I know your little plan.
I know your I know your little your
little game, right?
And I'm I'm not having it. I'm not
falling for it.
You want me skint like the opening virgin, don't you?
that skin virgin, don't you? It's not
going to work. I know you know your
little games. I know your little games.
I know your little you know.
>> No, I know what you're trying to do and
it ain't going to work, mate. It ain't
going to [ __ ] work.
Trying to make me skint like him, ain't
you? Like that [ __ ] virgin.
[ __ ] off, mate. [ __ ] off, mate. [ __ ] right off.
You can absolutely get [ __ ]
See, I've got plans. If I didn't have
plans, I would I would I would do it.
I'm going to go out next week. So, yeah.
Like, I'm going to go out next week. So,
obviously that's that it. No, I don't
want to be losing money. So,
I like You're trying to get me like that
skin virgin, aren't you? Be honest.
You're trying to get me like that skin virgin.
Don't lie, mate. Don't [ __ ] lie.
You trying to get me like that [ __ ]
virgin? Skint. You trying to get me like
the skint version in the bedset? [ __ ] off, mate.
[ __ ] right off. Yep.
[snorts] Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Why do you want me Why do you want me
skint like the virgin? Joseph Ferrar,
why the [ __ ] do you want me skint like that virgin? Huh? >> [snorts]
>> I know your [ __ ] games, mate.
Mate, I've wiped the smile off his face
multiple times, but again, you don't
remember them times because it doesn't suit you.
I think I think we we've all established
that you're [ __ ] biased on here, lad. >> [gasps]
>> You know, we've all established that you
cuds are biased on here.
So, that's that.
So, yeah. [sighs]
Well, it will never change, would it?
Joseph Ferrar, you will never change. So
that's starting it. You will never change. So yeah,
will it never change? Will it Joseph?
No, I ain't gambling, bro. [snorts]
Absolutely [ __ ] off and eat a dick [ __ ]
Eat a [ __ ] dick, [ __ ]
How about that one, mate?
Like I said, I'll do a video at the restaurant.
It's the best I can do for you.
It's [snorts] the best I can do for you, mate.
The best I can do for you, mate.
All right. If you come on here, if you
join the panel and you talk, I'll do it.
I'll deposit £200. If you come in the
panel and talk, I'll deposit £200.
Okay. With you, boss.
[snorts] I think that's that good. I I
promise you as well. You come in and you
you join the panel and you talk
for 10 seconds. I'll deposit £200.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come
on, [ __ ] Come on, mate. Come on, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Come on, you [ __ ] [ __ ] Come on. Come
on. Come on. Come on, mate. Come on,
mate. Come on, mate. Come on, mate. Come
on, mate. Come on, mate. Come. Come.
Come. Come on, mate. Come mate. Come
mate. Mate, mate. Come on. Come on. Come
on, mate. Mate, mate, mate, mate. Come
on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Why not?
Why not, matey?
Good old roulette. Eh, [snorts]
good old roulette. Oh. Hey,
why is it not worth it? Joseph for Huh? [snorts]
Why is it not worth it, Joseph? Huh? [snorts]
I'm asking you a question, Joseph.
I'm asking you a question, Joseph Farra.
Don't be so bloody rude.
Oh, [ __ ] sake, man.
I can't afford it. I'm broke. Those are
for I can't spend it. I'm I'm poor.
I can't. I'm too poor.
Sorry, I can't I can't spin the wheel.
I'm poor, lad. [snorts]
Sorry about that, man. I'm poor.
I'm poor, lad.
Why do you want me to spin the wheel? I'm poor.
Huh? I'm very, very poor.
You're a bully. You're trying to get
people to waste their money and stuff.
You're trying to get me like that skin
little virgin in the little bedit,
but like I said, no, it ain't happening.
[ __ ] off, you silly goose.
You silly goose.
Bugger off, you silly goose. I know your
little games. I know your little games, Joseph Ferrar.
I know your little games and it's not
going to work. It's not going to work. Joseph Farah.
[snorts] Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Joseph Fana.
[snorts] That's your name. Joseph Fuana.
Is that your name? Joseph Fuana.
[snorts] Joseph Fuana.
I get 800 pound this week. Joseph,
I like to carry over like 600 pound. Yeah.
Yeah. I like to carry over around six.
So, uh that's that.
I like to carry over a certain amount of
money, matey. I don't like to go below
a,000 pounds, matey. Nah,
nah, man. Nah, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, I said I was going out with my sister.
I'm going to a restaurant soon in a
couple of hours. Kieran Fra, I'm doing a
little bow challenge. I thought I wanted
to get my little self involved.
I said I was going out with my sister,
didn't I? Oh,
I did, didn't I?
[ __ ] I kind of want to go out by myself though. Joseph,
I want to go out by myself. Joseph Fana, [snorts]
little copycat. Why am I all copycat?
No. Virgin boy is a copycat.
Joseph, he went he went to Amsterdam
just cuz I went to Amsterdam.
He went to Amsterdam just cuz I went to Amsterdam.
Little copycat. Little copycat. You little copycat.
You little copycat. You little copycat. Huh?
Are you a little copycat? You know,
Jenny's a copycat virgin. She calls
attractive, isn't she? Yeah. You can't
deny she's attractive. Nah, you can't
deny she's attractive, can you? Nah.
Can't deny it, can you? Nah. Nah. Of
course you can't.
Of course you can't. You little copycat.
You little copycat. Oh, you little
copycat. You little copycat. You little
copycat. You know, you know copycat [snorts]
with a bouncer.
Timmy wouldn't batter nobody. He
couldn't even [ __ ] batter me or Monty
the silly goose. Let me have a look what
this little silly goose is going on about.
What's she going on about?
He's calling me a virgin even though I
put a porno out. I don't understand
this. I'm just watching this video. He's
calling me a virgin yet I've proved I've
had sex. Joseph Ferrar.
Madness. Absolute madness, lad.
Why are these people calling me a bloody
virgin, Joseph? I proved I've had sex.
That's why I fell out with you, Joseph.
Cuz you kept back you kept backing up the virgin.
Kieran, you know this Joseph Ferrar?
Yeah. When I used to go out virgin boy
by, he used to say, "Oh, uh, how could
he be a virgin? He's got a girlfriend.
How can he be a virgin? He's got a
girlfriend. How could he be a virgin?
who's got a girlfriend.
But yet when Virgin Boy goes at me, no
one mentions the porno that I put up. No
one mentions that I've been in women's
bed. [ __ ] off,
little biased [ __ ] Isn't that right, Kieran?
Okay. He wants the link. I gave him the
All right. Can you answer me, Kieran?
Can you answer my question?
You answer my question, Kieran. Huh?
Answer me, Karen. Stop ignoring me.
No, no, no. Kieran, I'm asking you a
question. Why is it that when I go at
Virgin Boy, people keep bringing up his
disabled girlfriend and that's
apparently why he's not a virgin? Yeah.
When people go at me, no one brings out
No one brings up the porno that I put up
which got my whole channel banned.
Defo, bro. Yeah. No one ever brings up the porno,
you know. It's a bit weird, isn't it?
That's very, very, very, very weird. Why
do you not bring up the porno that I put
up, Joseph, and the women's bed that I was in? Strange. Very strange.
Yeah. Very, very strange, mate. >> [snorts]
>> That is strange. [snorts]
Yeah, that's what it is. Cuz even when
you're not on here, even when you're not
on here, right, they they still go for
you. They still won't go for him. The
only people that go for him is Harry Fraud and
Harry Fraud and um what's the other one?
Harry Fraud and uh
Harry Fraud and [ __ ] one second. Uh
Tim, I'll let you in. Harry F and
Shagger. They're the only ones that go
for him. Yeah, cuz they like nons.
That's what That's what I was saying to Monty before.
Right, Timmy? Right, PJ? Why haven't you
not unblocked me?
I have unblocked chat.
>> PJ, I've just typed in your chat and I
couldn't. But PJ, I've tried to support
you and help you and you haven't. Okay,
if you unblock why, Timmy, why is LT
making excuses for the bouncer? I I
stuck it on in fair and square to me.
>> Right. But PJ, can I explain my bouncer
situation to yours? It's completely
different. Right. The bouncer physically
grabbed me, PJ. That's why I hit him.
Right. Physically attacked me. Right.
The bouncer didn't attack you
>> right now. So what's happened is PJ I'll
explain what's happened is
>> you he looked at you in one way. You
didn't like it. You told him
>> he kissed his he kissed that he kissed
his teeth at me as well.
>> But PJ, you can't call a bouncer out for
a fight when they're doing their job.
PJ, it was different. >> Okay.
>> PJ PJ, he's not going to come around the
corner and hit you, is he? Because he's
going to lose his job. Lose his. You
know what I mean?
>> So Oh, okay. Well, okay, Timmy. Well, I
told him to give me his number and I'll
meet him after work. What was that excuse then?
>> Well, that's different, PJ. I didn't
realize you did that. So, if you did that,
>> but you watched the video. No,
>> I haven't seen it, PJ. No, I need to
watch it. I ain't going to lie. I've
said I've watched it.
>> How have you How have you not watched it?
>> Cuz PJ, I've had my own [ __ ] to do with
I'm catching up on the Tuesday. All I'm
going to do, PJ, is white. I want the
Mongol. I'm in a bad [ __ ] mood. I'm
not going to lie. Right. I'm going to go
live in Birmingham. I'm going to get him
at Canill Park because you know and I'm
telling you this now PJ hear me out and
if he gives it the bigon when I've gone
back home back to Wolverampton and he
gives it the [ __ ] big and saying oh
I'm about it Timmy noise and all that I
am just going to laugh at the clown
>> so you're meeting him today
>> well he won't meet me PJ because he
knows he'll get [ __ ] filled in and he
knows me and Micah about it
>> Natalie G Natalie G will be telling him
don't go don't go because you'll end up
you'll end up in Canada Hill [ __ ]
park buried The bears will eat you.
>> You been Have you been gambling, Timothy?
>> You know I did my balls in the weekend,
PJ. My family.
>> No, I didn't. No, I didn't. No, I
>> Yes, PJ. I'll tell you what happened was
I paid the bills Saturday. I had about
80 quid left and I [ __ ] went on that
puby roulette. I [ __ ] maxed the buy
about four, right? And this is how
[ __ ] rigged it is, right? I knew it
was 36 because I can read that wheel. 27
right around there. Right. This is no
lie. land on the [ __ ] double zero, right? >> Yeah.
>> Next spin, same section, right? 3627.
Guess what it lands on again? Double [ __ ] zero.
>> Oh, gosh darn it. It's a load of
[ __ ] isn't it?
>> Yeah, it is, mate. And what it is with
me, I'm not Skint PJ. I have family
relatives hold my money because I'm a
bad gambler. Right. Now, that's why my
brother gives me little drips and draps.
Like, and yesterday he said, "Fair play.
Didn't gamble. He had a few beers. Had a
laugh with Mike and had a Chinese."
Right. How much did you spend
>> last night? Probably about 40 quid, 35.
>> That's not bad then, is it?
>> But but PJ, it's not about money,
brother. Right. It's not about money,
right? People on this community think
it's about money. It's how you live your
life, PJ. PJ,
>> I know it is. Yeah.
>> PJ, I don't need to show off £10,000 on
YouTube to prove a point to a bunch of Divos, right?
>> Yeah, it's the same. Yeah.
>> Do you know what Divvos means, don't
you? It means basically
>> it means like I call the trolls divos, right? >> Yeah.
>> No, no. I don't call them trolls
anymore. I call them divvos. >> Yeah.
>> So don't call them trolls. B is this is
this Joe F a troll. Um uh Timmy cuz
you're trying to get me to gam. You're
trying to get me to gamble £300.
>> It's probably [ __ ] Harry Ford. Harry
Ford is a massive troll. I'll explain
about the fraud. Yeah. Harry Ford's not
a bad guy deep down. He's a [ __ ] wind
up but he is a low life sad bastard.
Right in the out I won't call Harry for
a dbo. I'll just call him a troll.
Right. But right basically with Harry is
he's got a lot of time on his hands and
he's got there's a few people on here
like the male version the bojo wear them
big earphones look like ET. Right. >> Yeah.
>> And Harry Ford looks like ET cuz he's
got them gigantic earphones.
>> You're such a silly goose Timothy.
>> Why you calling me a goose? What the
[ __ ] in a silly goose.
>> So anyway, you got Shaga who's the
second one is like like the Bojo because
he's got he wears them big earphones and
he looks like ET as well.
>> Bang is the out of the group the only
one and I'm not defending him who
doesn't look like ET because he doesn't
wear them gigantic earphones. It's
Banger. So I can't call Banger the male
versus [ __ ] Bojo big earphones.
>> You all right, man?
>> Yeah, not too bad. How are you?
>> Just chilling, bro. Yeah, man. Still a
bit hung over from the other night, ain't it?
>> Who's Cormal?
>> How's yours? Kieran.
>> Oh, I said Kieran. So, I thought you
said Coral. All right, Kieran, lad.
>> Yeah, Timmy, I was only joking in your
li about the bacon thing. [ __ ] [laughter]
>> I thought I thought it was V. Sorry. I
thought it was V. I didn't realize it
was you, lad. I didn't realize it was
you. [ __ ] hell. I thought it was that
trap from Ireland.
>> No, it's because Listen, you take it too
way too personally. It was a joke.
>> No, no, you know what it is, mate. I'll
be [laughter] Can I be honest to you,
brother? I'm in a bad mood because last
night I was listening to Neil Young and
it reminds me of my dad.
>> Get you,
>> you know, like if you listen to the song
Old Man, it's about your dad. Like, cuz
I lost my dad at 21, mate. And that song
takes me back so many [ __ ] years,
lad. It's ridiculous. And that's why I'm
in a bad mood because I, you know, I
thought about my dad last night and I
haven't thought about him in about 10
years because, you know, time goes by
and that's why I want to knock out the
Mongol. I want to hurt him. And I said
to Mikey, "Don't hold me back." Cuz the
problem is, why? Hear me out, PJ. This
is how you deal with PJ. PJ, right?
Listen to me on this slap, right? No,
it's not funny. PJ, listen. You know,
you don't show anyone any mercy, PJ. You
know, when you get in a fight, hear me
out. Do not The problem with you, PJ,
you're like me. You show kindness. And
if you show kindness, you're going to
lose the fight. I I'm not showing
kindness anymore. I'm just going to get stuck in
that monster. Oh, no mercy. No, I have
no He ain't going to show up. I'll tell
you what's going to happen. Ke [ __ ]
going to [ __ ] himself hiding behind
Natalie G's [ __ ] bunk beds, right?
And he's going to give it the big when
I've gone home back to Wolverampton.
>> He's [laughter] a He's a [ __ ] little
[ __ ] mate. He is. He's pathetic beyond
repairing his little stupid press ups on
YouTube and he can't even do a press up
properly for [ __ ] sake.
>> Oh, no. He's He's a He's a dweeb. He's an idiot,
>> mate. I hope he dies of cancer. I can't
stand the nonsense.
>> I don't Okay,
>> here in this community is weird, isn't it?
>> You might you might Okay, you might
think, well, that's cool. Now, not being
funny. I wouldn't wish my worst enemy
cancer, but a [ __ ] bacon a nons. I
hope they get every disease under the
[ __ ] sun. [laughter]
>> I hope you get cancer, Mongol.
>> Yeah, you like this community, though.
Timmy, I thought you made up with mom.
>> No, no. I tell you what happened was Can
explain my side of the story. Right.
It's Judas me. You know what Judas
means, don't you? >> Yeah.
>> Basically, when I was live at
Birmingham, I didn't realize it was
behind me, right? Cuz I had the camera
on. I I thought I was going to have to
go to the address, right? He Judas me.
He punched me, right? And it was that
pathetic. Seveny old A seveny old
scouser could have done.
>> You remember Michael? I want to go in
the house. I want to go in the house.
>> A seveny old a seveny old [ __ ]
scouser. A seveny old [ __ ] scout, you
know punch me [ __ ] harder than
Mongol. Right. [laughter]
Right. But what it is said that
>> what it is. Yeah. What it is Cuban lad.
Right. What it is. Right.
>> Mike got away. You do realize I did hit
wrong. I hit him hard.
>> If it wasn't for Mike holding me back,
if Mikey didn't hold me back, I think I
[laughter] would I would have put him in
the back of an ambulance, mate. He's
like, look at the fight with him and
it's the most pathetic [ __ ] [ __ ] I've
ever seen. No, I know. Yeah, I saw it.
>> And he make and everyone's making out as
a gangster, right? With Welsh and me,
right? Can I explain the difference
between me and Welsh? Right. I had a
bender for three days. I was on every
drug under the sun. And when you ever
come down on drugs, let's be honest, you
couldn't fight yourself out of
paperback. Right. But but Welsh called
me out at my weakest. And to be fair, I
should have been the bigger man and said
no cuz I knew I was going to lose.
Right. Anyway, let's get to the [ __ ] point. Right.
I turned up because I'm no [ __ ] I'd
rather took a beating and got humiliated
knowing that I've shown than be a [ __ ]
and not turn up. Right. But next time, [laughter]
but next time like when I'm on a
comedown, I'm going to say that's it's
not my problem. You turn out 100 miles,
get a travel lodge and we'll fight the
[laughter] next day.
>> Timmy, why did you hit that person next
to the bouncer?
>> Which one you on about? Like I think it
was two weeks ago. Did you see that one,
Kieran? Yeah, cuz cuz he was a [ __ ]
farmer's boy. Cuz he was a farmer's boy
giving it the big gun. So I
>> You hit him then. [laughter]
>> You hit him behind the bar. The thing
the metal barrier.
>> Yeah, but he was giving the big He was g
the bigger. So I broke his [ __ ] nose. [laughter]
>> Little farmer boy Trout. Want to
[clears throat] do to Marco next? I'm
going [laughter] to get Marco and grab
him on the [ __ ] end. I'm going to I'm
going to grab Marco off the top of the
suspension. Give me the bigger now,
sunshine. If I let if I let go your
[ __ ] ankles, mate, you're you're
drowning in quick sand in the river seven.
>> Timmy, you don't know what I'm talking
about, do you?
>> Yes. The shoes thing, man. I know.
>> When you was arguing with
>> Yeah, but they're a bunch of [ __ ]
farmer [ __ ] up there, you know. PJ, [laughter]
>> did you see it? Did you see it, Kieran?
>> I most of this I haven't seen. I know
about the rice fight, but that was the
won. No. When Timmy was arguing about
bouncer. No, Timmy. No. When you was
arguing with a bouncer and she was a
woman and someone's like, "Don't go for
women." And you hit them. Do you remember?
>> I didn't hit a woman. I hit the I hit the [ __ ]
>> You hit the guy. Yeah. Who was defending? Yeah.
>> No, it's going to be the biggest over
the b and [ __ ] prompt him. And the
police [laughter] the police turned up
and the police turned around and said I
said, "All right." And nick me. I said
because I had so much on them bounces. I
actually wang up the the Albert shed the
next day and the Albert shed looked at
your back and said, "That girl shouldn't
have laughed at you cuz you're autism."
They're very autistic friendly.
[laughter] They are. I will say one
thing about Shupshshire and I will give
Shuptshire this. They're very autistic
friendly like Birmingham. [laughter]
They're horrible [ __ ] bastards to autistic people.
>> Shout out to Shshire. They are autistic
friendly. I'll give them that.
Birmingham, West England. [laughter]
They're a bunch of bullies to autistic
people like London.
>> What do you say autistic friendly? They
are autistic friendly means basically.
>> Obviously I know what it means you idiot.
>> Okay. What does it mean then?
>> It means it means they're more um they
are they give like sympathy to people
that are um autistic.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Basically if you if you
>> I know what it means you idiot.
>> Hear me out. If you if you get in shop
if you see get caught bullying an
autistic person they will intervene.
Right. Fing is right. I I I'm from
Wolverampton and where I live in
Wolverampton, I've got a community based
people, right? And they're very autistic friendly and
>> so you're from Wolverampton. >> Yes.
>> So you're Yaman then?
>> PJ I think someone's trying to get in in
the back. [clears throat]
>> No, they're not.
>> If it's not PJ PJ, if it's fantasy, I'm
leaving. I can't deal with that [ __ ]
>> Wait, hold Timmy. Are you So you're a
yam yam then?
>> Yeah, I love the yam yams, mate. You
know, you know Michael um Bassid's from Warsaw
>> apparently. Sir, you're from Warsaw.
>> Yeah, I am.
>> Yeah, he's from Warsaw. Yeah.
>> Yeah, he's from Yeah, he's from Warsaw.
Didn't you know that?
>> Of course I knew that. I [ __ ] been to
his gaff. Oh, I'm going PJ. I'm not
>> Run along. Run along.
>> PJ is your new hero now. You know the
attack coming. [laughter]
even run along.
>> You beat women, Tim.
>> So do you. So do you.
>> You're worse than PJ.
>> That's the mad thing. You're worse than
PJ. You attack women on site.
>> PJ starts on women and he's a m
guess what? And you ran away from Pat Mustard. You >> nor must
listen. Timmy. Timmy. Timmy. [laughter]
Timmy. Listen. One second. Listen.
Timmy. Timmy. Don't argue with him. He
ran away from Pat Mustin. Let him hold
that L. Let him hold that L, bro. Let
Let the Northern Ireland M hold that L,
[ __ ] Let him hold it, bro.
>> He ran away from a fat old man. A fat
>> Listen, ever since that happened to me,
Yeah. Ever since that happened,
he he ain't been the same. He ain't been
>> PJ PJ.
Yeah, you are alone. You Northern
Ireland. You are alone. Lonely. You
bottle job. You blew job. You got
bullied by Pat Busted. You buck the
Irish. The Irish are weak. Do you think
a fat old man could ever bully me?
Fantasy is a fat old man could ever
bully me off YouTube for a year. You
bun. You ran away for a year. You bully
victim. No matter what happened.
>> You ran away from Pat. You bully victim.
>> He doesn't have the confidence to women.
But then Slug such an artistic [ __ ]
he attacks women and that woman's
pressing charges to him.
>> But guess what? At least Timmy turned
up. You don't turn up anywhere. You
pressing charges. Don't forget that. I have right
out your Irish accent. You are a mun though.
>> Speak English, you [ __ ] spam.
>> You are a monk, KJ. That's a woman.
Yeah. Yeah. Put your camera on.
Yeah, you are. Yeah. Put your camera on your camera.
>> PJ, relax, PJ. You're having a panic
attack. Listen, I'm relaxed. I'm going
to run off of YouTube for a year. PJ
YouTube for a year cuz of yourself again.
>> You ran off of YouTube again.
>> Relax, bro.
>> All right. Relax.
No, you're not YouTube for a year because you're
relaxing, bro. I'm trying to relax.
>> Okay. I didn't run off of YouTube
because PJ PJ didn't run off of YouTube
because of Pat Must.
>> Why do women reject you though? Why do
they call you more women than you? I've
had more women than you. We've never
seen you with a woman, fantasy. Why do
women call you with a woman? Because
you're an ugly sper
your face, PJ, relax. Like, no one has
ever, bro. No one has ever
run off of you. I mean, with this guy,
>> all he does is talk over people. He's a
[ __ ] He's Irish.
All this Irish bun does is talk over people.
>> All this disabled [ __ ] does is talk
over people. That's all he does.
>> Okay. And I answered your question
in a coffee bullied online.
>> I didn't run away from Pat. You did. I
didn't get bullied off a YouTube for a
year. You did. You did. You can recover, lad.
>> I didn't get bullied off a YouTube.
You'll always be a mother again
personality which you need to change
like a slug. Imagine 20 years time
you're shot like Timing on YouTube,
bro. He couldn't even be that. Listen,
this guy is so disable.
He's so disabled. You're slowly
one thing. You're a slow figure.
You reckon this guy could ever meet a
guy like me? He ran away
and fat old man and he's coming on YouTube.
>> He got on YouTube
for a year, bro. I don't need to calm
down this little trap.
>> I don't need to calm down. I didn't get
run off of YouTube by a fat old man. I'm I'm extremely
quick. I'm gonna put a knife in your
head. Go and send that. [laughter]
You've owned him, PJ. You've owned him.
[clears throat] Everyone [laughter] is
>> Kevin. You see what I mean?
>> You always do. Go get your silver spoon
at your mom your [ __ ] kid. Go and ask
your mom [laughter] skip TV.
You pathetic imbecil.
>> I can't talk, [laughter]
>> bro. How could this guy run away from
Pat Mustard and try and come and give it
the big and >> Kieran?
Well, I mean to be fair, Pat Mustard
would never meet anyone. So,
>> yeah, but bro, he he he offered to meet
this guy. Yeah. And he bottled it. Do
you not remember that? That whole thing that happened.
>> Yeah, but Pat M was never going to meet him. So,
>> but but he didn't call his bluff though,
did he? He let him use excuses, bro. So, like
>> that's what I mean. He's a [ __ ] idiot, mate.
But ain't that bar crest though that you
>> which I tell you one thing fantasy
>> I will bar
>> no they got similar accent cuz they're
from Northern Ireland is it just accent your wedding
>> oh [ __ ] I thought they were both the same person.
>> No no no no no bro similar accent is it
Northern Ireland. No he's a [ __ ]
little weasel at uh Fantasy Stories man.
He's an absolute keyboard warrior. He's
an absolute [ __ ]
>> I don't know much about him. I I see him
around, but I don't interact with him. I
don't know anything about him much.
>> Yeah. You still there to me?
>> Yeah. Can you just kick him, man? I want to talk.
>> Yeah, man. For real. Yeah. They ruin it,
bro. Yeah. Go on.
>> Yeah. Anyway, it's [ __ ] mad week weekend.
>> What did you What did you think of them
videos, LT? Yeah. He He come outside the
[ __ ] uh the house yesterday. Yeah.
cuz he's trying to use the guy as he's
like it's cuz the guy was black in it.
It's not because the guy was [ __ ] at
work. It's [ __ ] in it every time.
>> Yeah, but I don't think he was outside
your house. I mean, you could have just
called his bluff by going out there, but
I don't think he was out there. But I
mean, I don't know. I don't care.
>> Can you What did you think of the
videos, though? It's mad, is it, bro?
>> Uh, I watched the bouncer one. I watched
a little bit of the one when you were
arguing women, but to be honest with PJ,
I don't once I get a gist of where the
video is going, I just tend to I tend to
just not watch it all.
I'm not having about you. I just think
>> it's like Lord Jay and all that lot if
you watch 30 seconds of it, you've
watched it all. You know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. But I mean uh the women one Well,
it is what it is. You got into an
argument. a bouncer one though. But I
mean with that one he probably started
on you before. You know what I mean?
>> Kissed his teeth at me, bro.
>> Yeah. I mean I would have knocked his
[ __ ] teeth down his throat, man.
>> Did you see them other them four people
trying to get involved? I stuck it on
them as well, bro.
>> Yeah, I need to go the videos. Have you
deleted them or they're still there?
>> No, no, they're still there, bro.
They're still there.
>> Oh, I suppose you are going to delete
them. I suppose I'll have have to look
after this. Have a proper look, you know.
>> But why is it okay? Yeah. for women to
give people attitude, care and as soon
as you defend yourself, you're bullied.
This is what I mean with these people in
here, bro. That's why they're [ __ ] simpletons.
>> Yeah, I know. But that's the world we
live in now. That's the western world,
you know? Like the last 10 years or 15
years, it's now gone the other way where
[ __ ] women have the power and we
don't, you know?
>> Yeah. There's so many white knights,
isn't it? So many white knights. It's unbelievable, bro.
>> You know, I mean, I was talking to
someone online the other day. He was a
lawyer and he always as he said to me,
he said there's no such thing as a
feminist in a divorce court, you know,
like they're all out for the [ __ ]
selves. You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Like the minute they go into divorce
courts, they'll play like the [ __ ]
you know, like
uh put upon woman and all this [ __ ] I
mean, he was [ __ ] really going in on
it, you know, telling me the [ __ ] that
cuz he obviously he's he's a divorce
lawyer. This one he says he is. I don't
know if uh but he was talking about it.
It was really interesting listening to
him though. But yeah, he he [ __ ] put
it on them like saying what they're
like, you know?
>> Yeah, they're [ __ ] bro.
>> They want equality until
you know until they want something, you
know what I mean? Then
>> the system. [clears throat] So you're
[ __ ] on both sides, you know?
>> Yeah. Exactly.
>> [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
>> Yeah. This is weird talking to you.
Usually I come on when I'm [ __ ]
pissed or something. It's the first
time. The thing is, bro, like they just
make excuses for the minute and that just [ __ ]
>> What are you doing today? You going for
the curry or something? He says,
>> "Yeah, I'm just going to go for a curry,
bro. What are you doing?"
>> No, I don't know. I was going to go into
[ __ ] town, but I don't know. I don't
know whether I'm just going to [ __ ]
sleep it out or what.
>> You drinking yesterday? Yeah.
>> Uh, last night I was. Yeah. But I tried
to come on but you I think I left a
comment but it was gone by the morning
so I don't leave it there or >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. But I mean just just don't >> Huh?
>> No. I don't know why you just don't do
what I do. Just like you know come on
for a couple of days and then [ __ ] off
for a few weeks. It's the same what I do
sometimes, bro. Because it's just the
same [ __ ] on it, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> It's the same atmosphere, isn't it?
I mean, just don't worry about it. Just
don't [ __ ] stress it.
>> No, true. When are you gambling again,
bro? I I was going to play some
roulette, but bro, I just I I don't
really want to lose money anymore, you know?
>> Oh, okay. It was fantasy. I saw you said
you still having a panic attack or
whatever the [ __ ] you
>> You're borrowing, bro. You're not
getting attention. You're not coming up.
[ __ ] off, you little keyboard warrior.
But yeah, I just can't be bo losing
money anymore, bro. Do you get me?
>> Yeah. Uh, I I gambled 100 yesterday. So,
>> did you win?
>> Do you know what it is with I find with
William Hill and you know the machines
that you get in William Hill and Paddyy Power,
>> I find it gives you a little win at
first to draw you in
>> and then it and then you feel confident
and then by the 10 minutes later you're
[ __ ] down again. >> Yeah.
>> Where Lab Brooks they just [ __ ] take
take. But with William Hill and that I
find that their machines are a bit more
clever. They get they they draw you in.
You know what I mean? Yeah. Yeah.
>> I don't know. It's going to get a lot of
[ __ ] work because the they're talking
about taxing the [ __ ] machines
when this budget happens. So
>> when that happens, you know, like I mean
even some of the [ __ ] RTPs now, like
they've lowered it, you know, like it
used to be even if you were doing
[ __ ] pip [ __ ] states like 20p or
something 25, they used to be 86
>> RTP. Now they got putting down to 84 83.
It's just a [ __ ] joke, man. can't win on them.
>> Yeah, exactly, bro. I get you. I get
>> But, you know, once you're [ __ ]
hooked, you're hooked, aren't you? So,
>> I mean, the thing that I I mean, I could
traveling to London to go to casinos.
But the problem with that is in the past when
>> they don't mind taking three or four
[ __ ] grand, but if you win three or
four grand, they want ID. They want they >> Exactly.
>> It's ridiculous.
>> Yeah. Do you remember what happened to
me in Knots, bro? Do you remember what
happened to me in Nottingham?
Uh, remind me
>> when I was with Ant-Man. So, basically,
yeah, I went to this, it's like an open
casino. It's called um
Oh, it's called Aloe Casino, I think
it's called. It's a private casino.
Anyway, I think it's there's one in
Glasgow and there's one in Nottingham.
Anyways, when I was with Ant-Man. Yeah.
I put £200 in. I was there for like 40
minutes. Yeah. And I got it to 350. So,
150 profit. It was over a period of
time. It wasn't just like one straight
away. I tried cashing out the money.
They have you got anything with your
name on it? No. No. No. No. No. No. And I said,
Why do you want to see ID? It was £350, bro.
>> £350 and I was £200 in. I was like, what
the [ __ ] But they paid in the end, but still like
>> Yeah. I've never heard them do it for
that low amount. Usually it's over a
grand or something. But >> yeah,
>> when I used to be self-excluded and I
used to win like 1,200 pound, they said,
"Oh, we can give you it, but you have to
come back with ID." So obviously they
would give me it. And I'm banned from
all the casinos. I can't get into the
last casino I went in was the Napoleon's
one, but but they've got face
recognition now, so I can't get into no
casinos unless I go [ __ ] France or something.
>> I'm [ __ ]
>> No, I've never I mean, I did it up in
Groless Square like you up in central London. >> Yeah,
>> I went there a couple of times. That was
before lockdown and I haven't really
bothered with it since lockdown, but I
just remember the aggro like trying to
get that [ __ ] three and a half grand
that time and it was just
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And it was
>> at least with bookies. At least with
bookies, you win, they pay. And I mean,
that's the fairest you're going to get
an arcade, isn't it? Yeah.
>> Yeah. But even I've known people though
who have won big in the bookies and they
might get a bit of grief, but it doesn't
affect me cuz I don't win that [ __ ]
much when I do.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> I mean,
>> yeah. It's like even even like Okay, so
you've been Hippodrome, right? The casino.
>> Um, no. I think I've only been
>> in central the one in the corner. No,
that's Grove. Or was that's not Groves Square.
>> No, no, Lester Square. Lester Square.
>> No, no, I haven't been. I just went to I
know it was called Groves Square and the
other time I went in Reading, but that
was another one.
>> Yeah, I tried to get into the Readen one
and they would let me grow one. I tried
to get into that one like last year.
>> Yeah, that's meant to be [ __ ] quite
easy to get into. They're not supposed at all.
>> Maybe they at all, bro.
>> Yeah, but I mean, this is what I mean. I can't [ __ ]
But then again, they [ __ ] You got Who
was it that got you banned? Was it V or something?
>> V. Yeah, but it doesn't matter. I'm
saying I'm a like we're talking about
like even when you win, they give you
grief. Like that's true. Like the thing
is, bro, I remember when was it? If you
go Hippodrome Yeah. and you win like
470, 480, you can take it out the
machine. You can keep going to the
machines. Yeah. And then but the thing
is if you try to take 500 they start
asking you for ID and [ __ ]
>> Yeah. And then do you know what it
annoys me because they know what they're
[ __ ] doing. They know people don't
carry that [ __ ] with them. And and
>> also bro also another thing is another
thing is have you noticed that when you
go to a casino they'll ban a lot of the
machines. Like they'll ban a lot of the
um cash out machines so in hopes that
someone's banned so they have to pay
out. Why do you think there's like four
or five machines all out of order?
>> Think about it. that [ __ ] like they
they do this cuz they know I mean the
time it happened with me in Ger Square I
don't [ __ ] carry passports and [ __ ]
with me you know
>> and I didn't have a passport I've got a
driver's license but I didn't
>> you need Yeah but you need I need to get
in these ones from these things. Yeah, I
know. But I had a a driver's license so
I could use that. But even though I
don't drive, which is weird. That's a
long story. Anyway,
>> I got provisional, but I don't Yeah,
>> I needed it for ID for the [ __ ]
because they kept saying about there's
no point getting a passport cuz I'll
never [ __ ] travel. Well, I'll never
fly, so it doesn't matter. But uh >> Yeah.
>> But I had to get a driver's license cuz
the bank kept [ __ ] saying they wanted
a photo ID and that was the only thing they accept. >> Yeah.
But it's all changed now. You can just
get a [ __ ] one of them.
>> When I when I won four grand, they paid
out quite quickly, I think, when I won
that four grand. But yeah, they I have
had hassle and agro trying to get money.
That's why it's not worth it, is it?
>> Online once you're verified, they pay
you in it. It's done.
>> Yeah. But I sometimes feel like they're
trying to get you to [ __ ] rage so
they could be like, "Nah, [ __ ] off." You
know what I mean? Like you you being
abusive. That's what I feel like that's
what they're trying to do. like they're
trying to get
>> the last time the last time I won on
roulette. Yeah, I put £100 in I got to
five something and they were asking me
for I verified myself in the end but bro
I was reading these reviews yeah and
they were saying how they didn't get
paid. I was like oh [ __ ] I'm in a bit of
trouble here now bro like what if I
don't get this £500 cuz I needed it at
the time in it. Well obviously bro who
doesn't need £500 but they paid in the
end so you can't even look on reviews
bro cuz some of these reviews are not
are not um legit. They're not genuine
because they were saying how they didn't
get paid and they got scammed but they
paid in the end.
>> I mean
>> I was like I mean if you're going to
Europe and that it's meant to be more
easier you know like but I was thinking
about making a weekend in Paris at some
point and then just [ __ ] trying it
there. But the thing is I don't really
talk French so it's hard.
>> Yeah they obviously a lot of them are
going to speak English obviously in it.
>> Well the immigrants do cuz there's a lot
of [ __ ] immigrants there. So they
come from countries where they speak it.
But I find that with the white French
people, they don't really
>> But I I remember when I was in uh
Belgium gambling and Amsterdam, it was
mad different, bro. Like I couldn't even
figure it out. It was so different. Like
the roulette, like trying to work the
machine. I couldn't do it, bro. Didn't
know. Just was
>> someone told me to go to [ __ ]
Holland. They said that they all speak
English there. So >> yeah.
>> Yeah. But that what I said earlier
though that nonsle he I mean I find that
weird going on a holiday somewhere that
you don't like someone but copying
someone is just [ __ ] weird as I was
telling you the other day.
>> Yeah cuz he's a copycat.
>> Yeah. I mean who the [ __ ] goes on
holiday just to copy [clears throat] I
don't know. He's a [ __ ] that that
woman though he's with she's definitely
a [ __ ] downy. I'm telling you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. 100% in it.
>> He tried to get her to speak one time on
a [ __ ] video. She couldn't even
[ __ ] read what was on the She's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Yeah, 100% though. 100% a [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Anyway, I don't really have much
to say. I was only coming on just I was
going to start.
>> When you When are you gamble? When are
you gambling again? Uh
probably in the weekend if I do a football.
>> What do What do you think of that
football bet, bro? That was sickening, isn't it?
>> Yeah, but you usually have quite some
luck on it. You just didn't get lucky this week.
>> I know. I just don't know. I don't know.
Treble both score. No draw. Not a both
score. That it was it was a specific one
in it, bro. So, it was harder. But I got
two I got two out of [ __ ] three, man.
I got let down by one [ __ ] goal cuz
both the other matches was 2-0. Uh 2-1.
I just needed the other one to be 2-1.
Oh, but yeah. But
>> are you coming are you going to be on
tonight or what?
>> Yeah. Yeah. After I come back from this curry. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I might come back on later.
It's It's the first time I [ __ ] spoke
to you levelheaded. You know what I mean? Usually,
>> it's usually when I'm [ __ ] drinking
or come on. But
>> God bless you then.
>> These I hear these women are really
stuck up though, man.
>> Yeah. I mean, I don't know what to say
to it. I mean, it is what it is, is it?
>> Yeah. But they are stuck up, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Do you reckon you get in trouble
with that though? Like, >> no.
I suppose I don't know you in it. I mean
I I don't know. I mean I don't like
Timmy though. He's definitely in trouble
though with that [ __ ] woman. I think
I do think [laughter]
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Because you see her [ __ ] wipe her I
don't think he spat her but it's the way
he spoke when he spoke you ding. So I
think spit went on her face. So but you
can see her wipe it off. If she [ __ ]
turns around and tells the police he
spat me he's in [ __ ] trouble.
>> I've spat at a woman before once. Not in
her face, but I spat her. [clears throat]
>> [ __ ] hell.
>> Yeah, she was being a [ __ ] It was
in Nottingham. It was the first time I
went Nottingham. I spat she said I I
asked for directions and she said, "Fuck
off." I just spat at her. Bro, you mad
[ __ ] The maddest one I saw you with
was when you were in that [ __ ] park
that time and you wanted, you know, you
want to I don't know if you want a date
and then it turned and you started on
her. Do you remember?
>> Yeah. Who Who could forget, bro? Yeah.
>> Yeah. That was [ __ ] I don't know.
Yeah, it was [ __ ] nuts.
>> It was funny, isn't it?
>> I don't know. I mean, I don't mind
people defending themselves, but I
wouldn't start on someone for no [ __ ]
reason. You know what I mean? But again,
I don't know the context. I wasn't there
at the beginning of it or, you know, so
I keep my opinions to myself.
>> But that that one in the pub, she was
running her mouth in it and she was like
trying to tell me like she was being a
[clears throat] [ __ ] She was being a
[ __ ] bro. So, what am I supposed to
do? Let someone talk to me like that. Huh?
Anyway, I want to go and have a bath and
all that [ __ ] and get ready for the day.
But I'll talk to you later then. Yeah, >> man. >> Lers.
>> I'mma get you,
Mikey. I'mma get you.
You're nasty. And I
[snorts and clears throat] like nasty.
You're nasty. And I like nasty.
You're going to be nasty for me. [snorts] You're nasty.
Look, I'm going for a nice curry today.
[snorts] Yum, yum.
Yeah, I need to have a shower to be fat.
I don't know what I'm going to wear today.
That fantasy story needs he needs a slap
right around his head. [ __ ] stupid
Guy sat there still a [ __ ] virgin.
How you going to lose it? How are you
going to pop it?
Don't know what to wear today lad. [snorts] [clears throat] Um,
that was so depressing, bro. My [ __ ]
sleeping pattern was [ __ ] up. It was aggressive, man.
How you going with it? How you going?
Why you going boy
in the dead when no money in
them [ __ ] chucking that? What are
they [ __ ] me doing?
I don't know what to wear.
My belly is rumbling. Oh, I got a track
seat on I
just [ __ ] I'm a [ __ ] baby, you know.
My [ __ ] belly is crumbling.
I just wear [ __ ] shorts and a [ __ ]
t-shirt, mate. I'm a [ __ ] crazy
for [ __ ] content.
Yeah, Joseph Farav is definitely not one
of the Bubs.
No, he's definitely not one of the BRs.
No, mate. No, M. Not one of the Bubs, [snorts]
He defend He's a He's a He's a N defender.
Well, he's got a girlfriend. He's got
girlfriend, but you don't [ __ ] talk
about the porn that I put up. It's not
going to be me a virgin. [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Yeah, do you you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Am I lying? Grezy,
did Joseph ever once bring up the porno
that I done?
Did he ever, Grezy? Tell us. Huh?
Did he tell us, Grezy? Go on.
Tell us, Grezy.
Did he [ __ ] once? Nah, cuz he's a non lover.
Yeah, I'm just having a shower and we're
going to get into these. I'm going to
get into shorts and a top car video coming.
Hope you're looking forward to it. It's
going to cost us a lot of money. Hope
you're looking forward to it, lady. Hope
you're looking forward to it.
I hope you look I hope you're looking
forward to it, lad. H
I'm going to have a foul. Going to have
a lamb foul.
Yeah. One second. I'm just popping in
the shower. Give me about 10 minutes. Greasy.
You might hear me sing about Virgin Boy
in the shower, by the way, cuz it's just
just catchy things, catchy sayings and stuff. All right.
Where's a skin virgin? [ __ ] hell.
Where's a skint version in the bed sit?
Let's have you your virgin [ __ ]
This is a lot [ __ ] louder, isn't it, son?
If I knew that you was projecting your
virginity all along,
[snorts] you [ __ ] skank virgin, I
would have [ __ ] told my [ __ ] mom
to waste my bloody time on you.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
I wouldn't have got my mom to bloody
waste her [ __ ] time explaining about
the escort story and whatever, but I
know that is cuz he's the skin virgin in
his little bed set. I want to bloody
wasted my time bloody. And yeah, I said
it again. Greasy. Bloody. That's my
favorite word. Bloody.
You [snorts] know
these bloody [ __ ]
Bloody self projectors.
Little self projector.
[snorts] Anyways, I'm gone. Right.
I'll say for a little bit. I know. I I
used to tell him these stories about
like the escorts and stuff, Kieran, and
he would keep like saying that it never
happened and he would keep like ignoring
it and stuff, which I thought was quite
strange to be honest with you. And later
I realized it's because he's a virgin. I
didn't even know it was cuz he was a virgin himself.
He's a big virgin himself.
I come off of YouTube for two weeks
scaring because whenever I'd go at this
little virgin, they'd say, "Oh, how can
he be a how can he have a how can he be
a virgin if he's got a girlfriend?" And
then when I'd show and then when he'd go
at me, no one says anything. These
little [ __ ] simple Tim Mongos. And
when I tell Joe F about it, he doesn't say anything.
How can he have a How can he be a virgin
if he's got How the [ __ ] can I be a
virgin if I [ __ ] put a porno up?
I know he's a big virgin as well.
Biggest one going. The amount of sex
stories he used to make up said about
how he's had sex in a uh he hasn't had
sex with nothing. He's never had sex
with nothing. Did never believe that virgin. Yep.
Yep. He he was talking about someone in
a park bench. He's never had sex in his
life. He's he's still a virgin. He's
still a big virgin. A big virgin. That's
what he is, Kim. Big big big virgin. You
can even ask the judging it as well.
That's why he used to call me a virgin
cuz he's a virgin. Big virgin. He gets
assy when you say that as well. Don't he don't care.
Don't killing that. Don't he [ __ ] car in that.
You cried over some GI in [ __ ] You
cried over some girly in Canada that
never wanted him. That never wanted a
null. [ __ ] weird. Yeah, he is [ __ ]
weird. Some girly in Canada that that
don't want to know him. Don't care.
Don't want him.
Don't want him, mate. Yeah. madness.
He's all over some [ __ ] girly in
Canada that didn't want to know.
Didn't want to know him.
Simply just didn't want to know.
Just Just didn't want to know. Nothing
wrong with people not wanting to know. Yeah.
Isn't it caring lad
just because someone didn't want to
know? Didn't want to know you. Didn't
want to know you. Simply [snorts]
didn't want to know you in life, mate.
Do you know? Just didn't want you.
Didn't fancy you wearing a cuppper.
So, I might be wearing this next week.
Uh well, not this this this week. Uh
Kieran, I might wear this.
Tell me if this is good to wear cuz
we'll be on the Guinness again. So,
I'm going to be wearing this.
Oh, that's my little towel. I was
thinking of wearing this with the Ammani
jeans and the trainers. How's that for show? Nice.
Is that nice with the with the nice new
Ammani jeans and the trainers? Thinking
of wearing that, you know, wear wear a
different one every week, you know, see
see what happens, you know. What do you
think about that? Might wear that, Kieran.
Yeah. His mom his mom used to uh his mom
used to throw the dog on him as well. Yeah.
Yeah. His mom used to throw the dog on him.
[ __ ] virgin. Yeah, she used to throw
She used to use the dog to abuse him. [gasps] Yeah,
she used to bully him with a dog.
Yeah, man. That's why he's bitter That's
why he's bitter about people living with
their mom because his mom hates him.
Yeah. It's cuz his mom hates him. You see?
I'm excited for this curry. I really
want to know. Yeah.
What it tastes like.
Really want to know what it tastes like, lad.
Yeah. I'll be back later, lad. I'll be back later.
I'll put the video up as well of the
curry. Right. I need to go in a bit as
well, mate. Got to get got get doing
stuff. You know how it is, mate. You
know how it [ __ ] is, mate. So, yeah. [snorts] Yeah.
Oh, is it raining out there? Yeah.
Oh, it actually is raining as well. >> [snorts] >> Anyways,
I'll be back later. Yeah.