Get up there.
I'm waiting for this case to kick in.
Yeah, man. About to wait for this
chicken to be made. But it's okay. I'll
wait until it's been made.
Trying to pour me off with a [ __ ] wing.
[ __ ] that, mate.
There's Joseph Ferrar in this fine.
I need to go out today, mate.
You know what I mean by go out?
Yeah, I went just come out the dentist,
mate. I had to get a fit in. [ __ ]
hell. I come out leading to one [ __ ]
side about an hour and a half ago. Come
out the dentist. So, going to have this
lovely KFC chicken, get changed, and go
out, send it, you know, cuz I'm bloody
sick of this [ __ ] Bloody hell. I had a
bloody enough of it, you know. [ __ ]
telling me to go on the apps. I don't know.
I've had a bloody enough of it, man.
Yeah, I was going to go out tomorrow,
but I'll just go out today. [ __ ] it.
>> So, brother, brother, two two legs, two
pie, two side B. Yeah. Okay. No, but the
specific ones cuz I have to wait. Yeah,
that's good, man.
is going to love this, mate. >> Yeah,
>> mine ain't bloody ready, mate. I tell
you that now.
My mouth, bro. It's all numb.
Take a little trip to dentist.
How cute is that?
>> I need to start going to the dentist
more often to be fair. Maybe every 3 months.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] that.
Where the hell is Jo?
>> I want to treat tomorrow like a
Saturday. Just do a football bet.
I'm just going to do a football bet on Saturday. >> [snorts]
>> Can't wait for this bloody chicken.
All that talking to KFC was making me hungry
with a bloody win.
But I hit a boy page today. [clears throat]
I'm just going to sit here.
I'll wait until we made
this virgin. He's been quiet. Hey [ __ ]
Hope it wears off soon. That [ __ ] >> [laughter]
>> What if I was sticky for weather function?
>> [clears throat]
>> I believe nothing to do this [ __ ] again brother madness madness bro
I'm well I'm virgin
Well, I'm virgin boy. Don't forget about
that. Would have been virgin.
He thought he thinks Ricky Millington's
me. He thinks that I'm him under a fake
cow. That's how obsessed he is with me.
Such a bloody virgin that
we go, wash the bed, get changed,
shower. I might try and have a couple of
hours rest in the mouth, but
Oh, hot mess.
I just call them chicken.
Now I'm at KFC. I just come out the
dentist. Gregy, I'm just waiting for the
chicken to come out. He said it's going
to be 15 minutes. I said that's okay.
I'll wait until it's been made.
You'll see. Greasy.
Now, Grezy, I want to run something by
you first, though, because I'm out anyways.
and whatever. I was thinking, could I go
out today instead of tomorrow?
Oh, see I have to run it by you first.
So, I'll go out today instead of tomorrow.
I'd have to run it by you first.
Is that okay with you, boss?
Yeah, I went dentist.
I had to go dentist, bro. Get a [ __ ]
filling, bro. [ __ ] mad tire.
Cheers, boss. I'm just going to have
this KFC and go home, shower, get
changed, but try and get a couple of
hours. I had a feeling, Greasy.
My mouth is swollen. I had a feeling. Ow.
I got a McDonald's Coke, but they don't
do normal Coke in.
Bad thing is that we have to wait for
the chicken to cool down. Come out. [laughter]
Hopefully we get somewhere today and it
go far. He's been awfully quiet.
You think it's possible I won't get a
number today? Grievy,
you think it's possible? Oh, I think
that's the chicken coming out.
I don't think it's possible, is it, Grezy? [snorts]
Oh, the chicken's just laughing.
How How do you know I'll get one?
How many numbers are you predicting today?
>> How many numbers you predicting, boss? >> [panting]
>> I'm thinking five.
Five or six
chicken. I'm getting impatient now. Greasy hungry.
Where's Joseph? Bloody Ferrari. We need
him. Where is he?
I got eight. I got eight pieces.
I'm so greedy, aren't I? Grizzy,
ain't no skin version. Come out landing. [laughter]
That's funny, is it?
Where's my bloody chicken?
>> I know you like the single burger,
Grezy, but you're just going to have to
make do with uh [ __ ] Christian.
>> Are you proud of me for going dentist today, Grezy?
Hopefully it doesn't rain today. That
will [ __ ] everything up. Don't think it will.
Where's my bloody chicken?
I want specific pieces as well. >> [laughter] >> probably
these bloody women.
Think of it.
What the [ __ ] is this chicken, man?
Stuff up there, man.
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
Don't worry, baby. It's coming.
Who's having believe KFC at 20 to 11 in
the morning? Okay.
>> Can I get two leg, two fire, two middle
breast, two side breast. Two leg, two
fire, two middle breast, two side breast.
Thank you, Captain.
So, it's it's worth the, you know, 15 minutes waiting. Yep. Captain, captain. Captain.
Captain. That's an old saying, is it
boozy? Oh, it's coming. It's coming.
It's all right. I'll eat it here. Yeah.
Oh, it's fine.
>> Yeah. Yeah, it's fine. Yeah. Okay.
Thank you, Catherine. Thank you.
Oh, greasy. Look at this, mate. Anyone?
Please come out. bag. Like us.
This is nice.
Hot there. Very hot.
>> Come out.
Look at that. [clears throat] Look at that music.
This is very hot. Come out.
Steven's going to Stephen How is going
to love it when when I'm out. Um it with me greasy. We'll
be on the internet. [snorts]
I wish you was here to have it.
So, we'll see if the manager will let um
Virgin [clears throat] Boy come with us today. Greasy.
So ask the manager
say I ask him
I as last week but he said my virgin
It's not bad. I can't overite what man says.
I don't even have a badge, bro. Ages now.
I have every other day. Oh [ __ ]
This is the best place.
Very hot. Very hot. Very very hot.
Oh, I didn't McDonald's.
some lost content today.
Very looking forward to it.
Hope we're looking forward to it later.
Oh my god, this is it's so [ __ ] chickeny. Remember
let them wind come in.
Let them win.
It's been delayed again. Really? When's it out? No way.
It can't be delayed again.
This is so hot though.
November. That's over a year away.
What? That's my next dentist
appointment. Well, for this year, I'm
not going to see about it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, we'll just wait, won't we?
It's been made.
I wait for the chicken to be made.
The version has been openly quiet
since the last time
on the long blocked him. Non Stegs
blocked him yesterday, bro.
Thinking that it was me. See, anyone
that doesn't agree with him, he blocks him.
He blocks anyone that doesn't agree with
him. [ __ ] loser.
Such a virgin loser.
What's this music?
I'm getting stuff now. Where is it? Oh gosh.
Jesus Christ. [ __ ] me.
It's a heat. I swear that heat makes you
fools you up. Moment.
Come on. Come on.
Where is it? That's lovely.
It's ping me up. [clears throat] Yeah.
So, I tried the grim reaper burger
challenge again. Agree with you.
That carine reaper burger on
probably kill me though to be honest.
Not my financial advisor.
Everything is still Oh [ __ ] Yeah, true. Yeah.
You reckon I'll be able to do it this
time, Greasy? I don't know. I don't think so. Whoa. Middle breath.
I'm get my vitamins in
I just said to this person on Instagram,
"Stop ignoring me. I'll spam your whole page."
You know what I [snorts] mean? I'll spam
the whole page.
You know what I mean by I'll do it. You
know what I'm like.
You like that last content, didn't you?
You like that Weather Spoons video,
didn't you, Ruzy?
You like that Weather Spoon video,
didn't you? Last week,
you like that, didn't you, boss?
I show them Boston. I grew.
But look at all the stuff it calls. to
cause LT to get involved and Timmy
argued with LT.
I was a root cause, wasn't that greedy? [snorts] No.
I told you I'm going to spam your
Instagram. I'm going to do on my other account
so that way that account gets banned.
Nothing to do with me. Sorry
being an ignores.
So being a bloody ignore. [clears throat]
Look at this piece of chicken.
my other account and show her me doing
on my other account. That way she won't
be able to ban my main account. Well,
she greasy. So, they'll lose that power.
They'll lose that cowardly power without
being able to ban you. Is it? They won't
be able to report you on that account.
That's another narcissist worst
nightmare, isn't it, Grezy?
not having power to ban people.
They will hate that they
will hate that. [clears throat]
system right now being control.
You know what I mean? is like I thought
there some Reddit moderators there
and she probably broke up with him as
well because it's the women that break
up with the men. It's not the men that
break up with the women. You understand
Grezy? So yeah, good man.
So some people live to be in [snorts]
control. losing. You might laugh at this, but
it's like Reddit mods, right?
Without sitting on Reddit and banning
people every day, what they have, they
live for that power,
they need to be in control.
If they can't, if they can't be in
control, then they lose it.
I'm warning them. I'm warning them in
advance. Don't sit there with the
zombies. I'm spam the whole chat
page. Spam the whole chat. Spam the whole page.
Will I be hitting the bars later, Gy?
Will I be hitting the bars?
Think of people ignoring Grezy.
Oh, it's not a crime. Yeah, it's not a
crime, but it's annoying.
Would you agree that it's annoying?
>> Yeah, it's proper annoying, is it?
Finish the drink, get on the train, go
back, rest a little bit, have a shower,
and piss off. There's your name. Okay.
Right. I'm going to go home now. I'll go
live when I'm back. All right. You crazy, boss.
Well, I'm going, bro. I'll see you later. [ __ ]