So sleepy.
Sleepy as [ __ ] Die, bro. Oh [ __ ]
Jesus Christ. I was out hours, wasn't I? Oh [ __ ] Oh. Where's everyone?
Oh, I'm so tired.
I need to jump in the shower a bit, but
I'm [ __ ] tired, man.
Rest in the twoies.
[sighs and gasps]
I'll be out here soon. I'll be out here soon, man.
We just have a little rest.
Took some pills as well.
We won't be drinking straight away. I'll
be I'll do some approaches and then I'll
do the drink. Drinking >> [gasps]
>> Are you all right?
I don't know whether to wear the the
Tommy Hilfiger coat, the black t-shirt,
jeans, trainers, or just the stony jeans
and the trainers. I was thinking the coat.
I think the coat. Greasy, what do you think?
What do you think?
I think the coat and the black t-shirt,
jeans and the trainers. Yeah.
Do you reckon we'll get a boyfriend
today? Weebsy, I need to put my bed in
the wash as well.
Do you think we'll get ah boyfriend?
You reckon we'll get in a pub? Grezy,
cuz obviously people on Reddit say go to
pubs and stuff, don't they? People on
Reddit say go to the pubs,
speak to women and [ __ ] in it. So
reckon we'll get in the pubs. Hopefully
not in it
cuz people in say you have to go to the
pubs and stuff.
We'll go we'll go to the clubs as well.
We're going to the club as well.
Okay with you, boss. Can we also go to the clubs?
Yeah. After they are old people and
families until a certain time.
Until a certain time.
Yeah. Until a certain time. Yeah.
Just rest in my eyes.
Rest in. Rest in.
I do some painkillers just to take them.
You know, Greasy
just to take them.
I'll rest for a little bit, have a
shower, and then get ready and stop
making my way.
Oh, man. How many numbers we predicting, Greasy?
How many numbers are we predict predicting today? Four.
Okay with me, boss. That sounds okay Hopefully. Yeah.
Just love the last. You just love the
lush content, don't you?
You just love the lush content. I know
what you're like, Greasy.
You silly goose.
I tried to speak to the manager again
and he's still saying no virgins allowed. We
That's nons legs [ __ ] isn't it?
Yep. No virgins. I don't know what it
is. This is just a no virgin policy. You
said the same thing last week, Luzi.
It's a no virgin policy.
Why? Just there's just no virgins allowed.
He says no skin virgins.
Don't know why.
Oh, [ __ ] me.
I'm so tired. But
I've been up since [ __ ] six. Squeezy.
Yeah. Anyways, I'm going to have a rest
and I'll be back later at the pub for a
little while. I'm not going to be live
all day in the pub, but
yeah, I'll do uh I'll do some content.
Anyway, I'm going to try and get an
hour, half an hour, hour sleep and yeah,
go from there really. So, yeah, man.