Oh, that breakfast was [ __ ] lush,
man. It was [ __ ] lush. Yeah.
Yeah. Got this [ __ ] virgin trying to
call me. [ __ ] off. You're not getting my
attention. You little
rat. You little rat face [ __ ] Stop
[ __ ] calling me, you
weirdo. Go get laid. Get off your
YouTube and go get laid, [ __ ]
Stop calling me
weasel. Stop calling me the weasel, man. Yes,
she stop calling me, you little you
little virgin. I'm blocking your number.
[ __ ] off, you virgin.
[ __ ] [ __ ] obsessed. Jesus. I swear
to God this virgin wants my ass. I swear
to God. I'm back on YouTube,
man. I swear to God, bro. This little
virgin wants my [ __ ] ass, mate. Keeps
[ __ ] calling me.
God. So weird. [ __ ] creepy little
virgin. Creepy creepy creepy little virgin, man. Oh,
damn. Yeah. What the [ __ ]
lad? Stop calling me little
virgin. Yeah, [ __ ]
virgin. Yeah, bro. Trying to sort it
away from [ __ ] last
night. You know, man.
God, [ __ ] off you little stalker. You
little virgin. I'm coming off of YouTube
tomorrow anyway for a little bit. I got
some content to put out. I'll put some
content out on the main, bro. As you know.
as you know
that I will 100%.
Yeah. Who the [ __ ] are them people?
Joe, you need to help me, bro. I've got
some people that want my ass. These
little YouTube virgins want my ass,
lad. Stalking. Next level stalking.
Chase is a [ __ ] man. He couldn't even
let anyone know when he was in London. A
pair of cowards. Pair of
[ __ ] Get a [ __ ] life, mate. Oh my
god. Some people really are in desperate
need of a life, man. I'm I'm telling you. You
know, stop calling me, you ugly virgin.
I don't want nothing to do with you.
Just like Britney don't want nothing to
do with you, you [ __ ] virgin.
call after miss call. I blocked your
number, you [ __ ]
virgin. There you go. You can't call me
now cuz your number's blocked. Try again,
virgin. Try again, virgin. I'll save
these for if the police ever come, by
the way, as well. See how much you you
keep calling me, you little [ __ ] rat,
virgin. Yeah, I got your number now as well. You
[ __ ] called me 23 times. You [ __ ]
virgin. 23 times, bro. That's enough for
an harassment charge, bro. That's got to
be. You've called me 23 times. And I
blocked your number, by the way. 23
times. You're obsessed with
me. You are obsessed with me. You
virgin. Oh, bro. 23 [ __ ] times. I've
saved you as PJ, by the way. I don't
know why. I'm going to show everyone on
YouTube. I don't know why I just saved
you as PJ, but you've called me
uh Oh my god, you are
upset. You need to get laid. You need to
You'll be a much happier person when you
finally get laid. You [ __ ] virgin. Oh
my god. Look at this, bro. I saved it as
PJ. I blocked the number
now. Look how many times this virgin has been calling me. 23
times. [ __ ] You're
obsessed. You're obsessed with me. You
are obsessed with me. virgin.
God, this virgin is obsessed with me,
bro. Look, 23 times. Like, he's lo he is
actually stalking me.
[ __ ] hell, bro. 23
times. 23 [ __ ]
times. You need to get laid. You need to
lose your virginity. You'll be a much happier
person. Been saying it from day
one. 23 [ __ ] times, bro. What the
[ __ ] I'm leaving this community, bro.
These people are too weird. I swear to
God, man. These people are too weird,
man. I'm so They creeping me
out, bro. I swear that, bro. What the
[ __ ] Yeah, you're weird,
man. 23 times.
Look at that 23 times I've got. Man, you
know, you're a proper
stalker. I can only imagine what Britney
[ __ ] went through, mate. You're
[ __ ] doing it to
me. [ __ ] girl in Canada who rejected
your ugly ass. [ __ ] you're doing it
to me, you ugly bastard. So, God knows
what youing what you do to her. You ugly
[ __ ] You [ __ ] ugly
[ __ ] Yeah, weirdos,
bro. I got some
mail. You weirdo. Obsessed.
Obsessed. These people are getting starved,
bro. Tomorrow. 100%. They're getting starved, bro.
I'm not giving them no I'm not I'm not giving no
content. I'm not even going to put
content on this [ __ ] channel. It's
creepy. All nonsense. It just goes to
show he's a virgin. Look, how the [ __ ]
do you have time to call someone 23
times? I could show the police that as
well if they ever come that this [ __ ]
keeps stalking me and calling me and harassing
me, you know, but there's no point doing
posters because even if you do posters
of this little virgin, he's still going
to do it two weeks later anyways. Like
you might as well Yeah. just upload
stuff on a new channel where none of
these people can find you. You're living
in their head every day as it is, bro. You know,
I don't know how these these people must
they just must hate being themselves.
Like they they must really hate their
lives to do what they do every day. Crazy.
Yeah. Oh, I asked her I asked for her
number. I didn't call her a [ __ ] to her
face. I said to somebody else that she's
a [ __ ] Hey, Gary. This virgin has
called me 23 times. I've had to block
his number. This creepy little virgin.
I'm leaving YouTube tomorrow, bro, for
two weeks. [ __ ] hell. These people
are creeping me out again. She wasn't
talking friendly. She was being a [ __ ]
cuz when I asked her out,
Yeah. she [ __ ] was making up [ __ ]
She was just being a [ __ ] man. I
don't [ __ ] I hate Canadian
women. Brooke, if you're watching this, [ __ ] you.
He put my number out. I'm going to
screenshot that as he I'm going to
screenshot that. Yeah, I'm going to
that. Come, bro. Yeah. And guess what?
Do you know the thing is though, uh,
Gary, is that none of them will ever
show me where they are. You remember
that chase share when he was pretending
to meet me before like four or five
years ago? You might have not been on
it, bro. They can easily come to London,
right? They will never show me where I
would beat both of them with one hand.
That's how bad it is. I could beat both
of them with one hand. That's how mad it
is, bro. Like, it's that bad. Like,
trust me, you will never go drinking in
my pub. Let me know where you are.
That's that's the madness about it, bro.
Yeah. [ __ ] them. Anyways, I'm leaving
tomorrow. Anyways, for a couple of
weeks, lad. Yeah. I got with this
American bro who's like I think she
wanted to [ __ ] there and then bro I'm
not sure but I wanted to like play it
cool. Yeah I was with her bro
[ __ ] when I um I went to so um we was
talking and that is it. She literally
just come she's here for a couple of
months and that we was talking drinking.
It was a street approach. I didn't get
no numbers from the club and the first
approach I done on the street I got the
number and I got we was just drinking
and talking. I'll be meeting her again tomorrow.
So, yeah. And I got banned from the club
as well cuz what? Cuz I used the word
[ __ ] [ __ ] them, bro. If they don't want
your custom, they don't want your custom in
it, you know. [ __ ] them, bro.
Hate. So then I just went to the street
approaches then where I done one only.
They only took one. He only took one.
That's mad, is it?
But I'm kind of scared of Americans.
Like I am sort of scared of him,
bro. Not scared of them, but like as in
you know the [ __ ] they doing that. You
know what I'm saying? Scary, bro.
Yeah. Yeah, man. But 23 times you sad
bastard called me 23 times. No one in
this community is going to call me. You
can put my number out all you want. No
one's going to call
me. And if I if they call me, I'll block
him. And if they call me, I'll just block
them. Like, it's calm. I mean, like, it
is what it is,
man. He seriously needs to get laid. I'm
not even joking, man. He He seriously
seriously cuz we know they're both
cowards. Both Sean, both Chase. Don't
ever show anyone where they are. They're cowards,
bro. Yeah. You, bro, they're cowards, man.
Honestly, they're proper cowards,
lad. Yeah. The Canadian. I didn't even
like her that much, but I thought, "Fuck
it. I'll try
it." Yeah. They were having none of it
in the clubs.
Um, the club. I only stayed in one club.
Remember, Gary? They weren't having none
of it, mate. It was hard, bro. It's
[ __ ] hard. I didn't even get one
number from that
club, mate. Joe, do you know the problem
with it is is there's no point even
doing posters because if you do posters
of them, right, all that's going to do
is stop them for like two, three
weeks. That's all that's going to happen
is is is is it's going to stop them for
like two, three weeks maximum. You're
best off here posting content on your
channel and just completely ignoring
them because you're already living in
their head. You're already tormenting
them every day making posts about you.
This virgin Joe has called me 23 times.
This little virgin has called me 23
times. You're already living in their
[ __ ] head rentree, man. All you got
to do is post like good mad content that
that will destroy him, bro. It will kill him.
23 times this little virgin as as so
when you try to tell me Joe that oh he's
not a virgin because he's got a
girlfriend. Well, explain to me like
I've wanted to be explained many times
how somebody can sit and do this all
their life on YouTube yet they have sex with their
girlfriend. There's only 24 hours in a
day. Most of his day is stalking me. So
where the [ __ ] would he have time to
have sex with his girlfriend? He's never
had sex. He's still a virgin. Hit the
trigger. Look, 23 times he's called
me. I don't want nothing to do with you.
Just like Britney didn't want nothing to
do with you. [ __ ] off. Leave me alone,
you [ __ ] virgin. [ __ ]
sake. [ __ ] me, man. They're [ __ ] so
obsessed. Oh my god. I couldn't imagine
being obsessed with someone every day,
bro. It's a madness.
He needs to get laid his rigidity man. So
yeah, no 23 times
e. Crazy, isn't it? Crazy. They're the
ones that are psychologically being
affected. For them to hit that call
button 23 times, right? and for them to
do what they do every day. These are the
ones these are the people that are being
psychologically affected, not me.
They're the ones that are being psychologically
affected because they're wasting their
life on you being obsessed with
you. You know what I'm
saying? [ __ ] hell, bro.
I'd say I'd pay for a restraining order,
but a restraining order wouldn't even stop then. You
know, it's a it's crazy. It's [ __ ]
crazy. It actually
is. It actually is. But Chase is a
[ __ ] I told him, "Go suck his n
[ __ ] Welsh patchy beard [ __ ]
[ __ ] Go suck your n." Yeah. When
you're back in London, why don't you let
me know where where you two are? You
would get the [ __ ] head [ __ ] You'd
get your head kicked
in one [ __ ] hand, bro. Not even
joking. You know, I just don't like
snakes, bro. He doesn't have nothing on
me anyways cuz I knew that was going to
be a thing. But he's just like, you know
what I mean? They're too And you know
what? They're just as cowardly as each
other. That's the thing about it.
They're just as cowardly as each
other. Know what I'm saying?
And that's it. He was trying to act hard
that time when I was in Bristol, like
walking down train station. Bro, you get
[ __ ] up. Like you both would get
[ __ ] up at the same time. Come on,
man. You know that's
it. And you know what? If I go Cardiff,
yeah, I'll call out Gouna at the same
time cuz we know that he will never meet anyone.
Chan, these people are very sad
individuals. Very, very sad
individuals. I feel bad for them, bro.
Yeah, I'm I'm feeling it now. That
breakfast on me good though, Joe. Bacon, sausage, hash
browns. Oh, it don't be me good, bro.
Don't be good. [Music]
Was people ever
disobed? I don't think they were, you
know. I don't think they were ever ever
obsessed with Timmy like this. No, I
don't think they were.
What do you think, Jonah? No.
No. [ __ ] hell, bro.
tomorrow, bro. For two weeks, 100%. It's
just It just creeps me out, bro. These
people creep me the [ __ ] out. It's okay
for one day, then the second day is
like, "Nah." Yeah. But by the third day,
it's just so
creepy. Like, uh, they give me the ick.
They're so obsessed. Like, it gives me
the ick. A bunch of people that are
older than me, obsessed with me. It's
It's weird. Like it's I I know I'm doing
something right because they want to be
me, but at the same time it's
cringey. It's so weird. It's so weird. You
know, think of that, bro. You know, when
they're on their deathbed, they're going
to realize that they spent all these
hours and all this
time on on on on me, bro. Imagine that.
Would you want that to happen, bro? No.
Jealousy is a disease. It's killed many
people, bro. Many
people, many people
that. But yeah, I could do the post, but mean that
means, you know, in two weeks it's just
going to start all over
again. You know what I'm saying?
saying I think this will probably be my
last live bro for like two weeks. I
reckon these people are creeping me out again.
Yeah. Like this chase guy tries to act
big. But if any of them were big, why
didn't they let me know where they were
when they were in
London, you know? Like
it's they're bad, bro. They're bad.
There's a madness. [Music] I'm tired,
bro. That's drinking. I feel paranoid today as
well. Too much
booze. Too much booze. major. Yeah.