Nope.
Not even a single goal.
They might as well have just not even
went into [ __ ] work today to be
honest. If they weren't going to [ __ ] score anything.
anything, there was like no point of
them even going to [ __ ] work.
Not even a single goal. Oh my god. They
must have saw me coming, mate. [ __ ]
hell. Not even a single girl. And
they've won four weeks in a [ __ ] row. [ __ ] mate.
It's absolute bollocks.
Not even a single [ __ ] bastard goal.
Not even a single [ __ ] goal.
And the odds were worse on this one as well. Wow.
Yeah. Well, that's depressing. I'll be
giving up on life for a month then or
two if this bet don't come in.
That's depressing. It doesn't matter how
much money you have left. It's depressing, bro.
If this bet loses,
which it looks like it is going to lose
cuz four teams are not going to score in
the second half. [ __ ] bro. Absolute
They are literally doing nothing.
They are doing nothing at all. One
scored and then it went back to nil nil. Nope. Nothing.
They are doing [ __ ] all today.
Might as well have not even played.
I might as well just bet on a [ __ ]
two a team that doesn't even play, bro.
Two teams that don't play. Yeah,
scoring. None of them, not even one of
them teams have [ __ ] scored a [ __ ] goal.
It's [ __ ] bro. It's [ __ ]
I can't believe that one of them scored
one single goal.
But this is the cycle we're in and we'll
always be in.
So yeah, that's that, isn't it?
[ __ ] that. I'm in bed for a month now
after this. A month. More than a month.
I have to do Christmas shopping next
month to be fair. [ __ ] that. That's
depressing. [ __ ] losing to this
Same old cycle. This is why I do not go
out, bro. We're just going round and
circles. Round and round and round in
[ __ ] bastard circles. That's all you
ever doing in this [ __ ] country.
If I didn't go out yesterday, I probably
wouldn't have put this football bet on.
To be fair,
I don't understand how not one team has scored.
You know, they've had ample for the
chances, you know, ample ample for the
chances and they just will not score.
They will not give for whatever reason.
I don't [ __ ] know. But that's that.
Well, I'll be getting some food and
going to sleep. Depressed
cuz that is depressing. That is [ __ ]
to be honest with you. [ __ ] that. That
is depressing as [ __ ]
How these teams have not scored, I shall
never know, mate.
It's both of them as well, isn't it?
I knew that would have happened to be
honest. I knew it.
I [snorts] knew this would have happened, bro.
This week, I knew it.
It was going to happen eventually, wasn't it?
eventually, mate. So, yeah,
even I'm still massively up from [ __ ]
the past two months
cuz technically I have more money to
live on, but no, that's depressing. [ __ ]
that. So, I'll be canceling plans next
week then. It's fine.
This is the mood I get into. This is why
I don't like losing and [ __ ] That's why
I don't play online roulette or anything
like that because I can't stand losing, you know?
Doesn't matter how much money I have.
This is what I mean, bro. I wouldn't
have done that bet today if I didn't go
out yesterday. I swear to God, maybe
like a couple of weeks I would have, but
I wouldn't have done it today.
It is the same cycle. It never ends in this [ __ ] shitty country. So yeah,
can't say ain't scored a goal. I shall
never know, mate. Your guess is as good
as mine how they ain't scored a goal.
They've had plenty of chances to plenty
of chances to plenty plenty of chances to.
They're just sat there doing nothing.
Literally just sat They're sat there,
bro. Doing [ __ ] nothing.
You know what I mean? They're sat there
doing [ __ ] all.
You know what I mean?
They all sat there doing absolutely poor Hey, not [ __ ] man.
Bye-bye. One go. No spastics on my channel.
I'm giving up on life for a month.
So that's that, bro. That is literally
that. I'm giving up on life for and the
thing is I'm not even short of money.
I'm nowhere near short of money. That's
depressing, bro. That is [ __ ] depressing.
So I'm going to have to cancel plans
now. That's depressing as [ __ ]
This is like when you used to go out and
used to go to the casino and stuff. It's
so depressing. I wish I didn't go out
yesterday, bro. I wish I didn't go out
yesterday, bro. I swear to God. You know,
I can't be bothered listening to you.
[ __ ] off, man.
I'm not in a mood.
Reporting people to Universal Credit,
bro. You can report me to Universal
Credit all you want.
Yeah, you're allowed you you're allowed
to win money and buy designer clothes
and put a small profit on a football
bet. Yes, that is what it's for,
[ __ ] You little mongos. Instead of
trying to like ruin other people's
lives. Yeah. Why don't you get off your
fat ugly asses? Get yourself a job. Get
yourself some money so therefore you
won't be jealous of other people.
Simple. It will do you good, man. It
will actually do you good.
So yeah, I'm not wasting my own money.
[ __ ] I have like 1,500 pound left and
I'm not wasting any more money in this
country. So you get [ __ ] Get [ __ ]
mate. So that's that, bro.
I would have been staying in anyways to
be honest. though. But no, that is
depressing. That is so depressing. So yeah.
So I take it this is a loser. Yeah. It's
not going to win. Of course not. It
would have been too easy.
Yeah. It would have been too easy, wouldn't it?
Bye-bye, [ __ ] No spastics on my
channel. I told you this. Is there a no
[ __ ] zone? You should know this, man.
You should know this [ __ ] by now. One second.
So yeah, anyways.
Oh, Darlington did. Darlington did
score. Darlington did score. I didn't
even see that. Oh, did they? Well, we
got a small chance this bet might come in.
A very small chance.
I mean, there's one goal, so all they
need is three more goals.
So, then obviously I would still had profit somewhere.
I'd still have profit somewhere along
the way because I don't get 1,500 a month. So,
yeah. And I'm not I'm not wasting any
more money. So, that's that.
Now, we need Kitty Mester to score and
them two [ __ ] Come on, man.
Even if it's like a 2-nil or 1-1 or
whatever, I didn't realize they scored
on that one.
Like these [ __ ] really need to
really need to score, mate.
Otherwise, we're [ __ ] basically. This
whole bet is [ __ ] basically.
I'll be back later when this bet wins.