Depressing, isn't it?
>> Couldn't even score a [ __ ] goal.
That is so depressing, bro.
I don't even want to eat now. I don't
want to do anything. That's how it gets
me. It gets me in these moods, bro. 100%. 100%, bro.
Yep. Couldn't even score a [ __ ] goal.
Well, that's put me off my food and
wanting to do anything now as always.
So, that's that starting. It
seems later than that to That is [ __ ] depressing, bro.
[ __ ] so depressing.
That is [ __ ] depressing, isn't it?
I thought they was going to score, you
know. I actually thought there was a
chance they were going to score, but
nope. That's never going to happen, is
it? No. No, of course not.
Yeah, I'm depressed now, bro. [ __ ] that.
That is depressing. I don't even want to
eat or do anything now, bro. That is
depressing as [ __ ] When I was watching
it the last few minutes as well, that is depressing. it.
Yeah, mate. I've got more money than you
will ever have.
Yeah, I've got more money than you will
ever have. But that's the difference,
though. More money. Yeah. more money
than you would ever have. More money.
And I never have to beg for money
either. You're 40 years of age. You're
disabled. You got a bad back. You got no
driving license. You got no money. How
are you going to come on here and talk
about me, bro?
Huh? You got no money, no life. All of
the people that you talk to are scared
to meet you. You're a loser. And you're
in your 40s as well. You're not even the
same age as me. Disabled, no money, ugly, ginger.
Bro, seriously. And and you're trying to
talk about me, someone that's younger
than you. Please, bro. I have more money
than you will ever have. Believe you me,
mate. More money than you'll ever have.
And guess what? I don't need to beg
anyone for money. I don't have to beg
anyone for money cuz I'm not skint like
you. You know when you come on here
every day calling people skint is cuz
you are skint. You need to stop talking
about yourself. Skint is your life.
Begging for money on benefits. That
ain't my life, bro. I'm not skint like
you wearing them shitty [ __ ] cheap
trainers that you wear. You skint
bastard. Look at the [ __ ] that you wear.
Lying to people that you [ __ ] own
[ __ ] what was it? Six properties,
bro. You're on benefits. You don't get
more than £1,000 a month. Behave. Have a
word with yourself. You're a liar. You
sit on here continuously. You got no
life cuz you got no money. Coming on
here talking about other people that you
don't know. We're not all like you.
Skint, lonely, talking to people that
will never [ __ ] meet you.
I have more [ __ ] money than you will
ever have, you skint bastard. I will I'm
not the one that goes to Weather Spoons
begging for money cuz we're not skint
like you. I don't know why you seem to
think I've I've said this millions of
times. Why do you think we've all got
the same life as you, bro?
Come on, bro. Why do you seem to think
that we're all skin like you, bro? You
know, then that's it. 40 or bro, that
£13,000 is daddy's savings. Show that
money again right now. You can't do it.
We've been over this millions of times,
mate. Your daddy's savings does not
count. Yeah. Show that same money. Say,
show that same amount of money now and
say the date. Showing daddy's bumchain
savings is not a flex, bro. It's It's
really really not a flex. Oh, what?
You're saying nothing to me now? Why are
you saying nothing back? Because you
know I'm right about you. Everything I
say about you is the truth. Bro, you beg
for money. I would not ask anybody on
this community for money. I don't want
their [ __ ] money. Cuz we're not skint
like you, LJ. Only people that do that
are skint. Don't let them tell you
otherwise, bro. Don't let them say, "Oh,
it's a business." And no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. Bro, you're [ __ ]
skint. Yeah. Let me tell you something.
Them trainers that I bought them
trainers that I bought are worth more
than your [ __ ] anything that you've
got in your wardrobe, mate. Yeah, that's
that's that's the facts. You [ __ ]
skint Irish bastard. Yeah, I've noticed
how you've gone for Timmy multiple
times. Come back here, bro. Come back
here. Come back here anytime, you
[ __ ] fat [ __ ] with your [ __ ] ugly
kids. You know what I mean? Bring your
[ __ ] stinking kids as well. And I'm
talking about your kids. And you're not
going to do nothing. You would have
thought, right, that would have been a
trip to be honest with you. You would
have thought that would have been a
trip. You know, London, all of these
people, and you're not going to do
anything. I'll tell you to suck your
kids to your face. Them people, right,
who I started on last week, bro, they're
bigger than you will ever be. Ever be,
bro. Yeah. Ever [ __ ] be. And you
still make excuses. Don't suck up your
dirty kids, bro. You're going to do
nothing because you know that I'm not
Timmy Eldridge. So that's why you
learned your lesson the first time, did
you [ __ ] boy? Yeah. Because it's not
how it planned out to be. Yeah. It's not
how it planned out to be. Go and suck up
your kids and you're going to do
nothing. And I am talking about you.
Yeah. And I'm talking about your kids.
Go and suck them up. Suck up your kids.
You're going to do nothing, bro. Yeah.
Someone that's got all of this money,
bro. Please. You want about £1,000 a
month. You want about a grand a month.
Behave, bro. Stop it. You don't own
properties. Shut up. Make your lies
believable. If you was if you was to own
property, if you was to own property, if
you was to o own property,
imaginary £1,300. Again, we're not all skintike people.
We're not all skint people. I don't know
how many times I have to say this.
There's no imaginary about it. We're not
skint like you [ __ ] sat on YouTube.
No life, no future old. I don't know how
many times I have to say this. There's
nothing imaginary. We're just not skint
like you people. You You base your life
on everyone. You base your life on
everyone else's. That's what you do.
You know, I can't even afford to eat now. [laughter]
Projection. This is what I'm saying with
these people. It's It's [ __ ] projection.
I can't afford to eat. [laughter]
Where the [ __ ] does that even come from?
Who the [ __ ] comes out with something so
random like that? I can't afford to eat.
Oh my god, [laughter]
that is [ __ ] funny, bro. That is
really, really, really funny. Yeah,
[laughter] I can't afford to eat. Okay, bro.
Oh my god, that's funny. Where do these
people come out with the this
foolishness? I I swear to God, they're
talking about themselves,
you know? I can't These people are
generally speaking about their [ __ ]
selves generally. I can't afford to eat.
Where the [ __ ] do you get these things from?
You know, where the [ __ ] do you get
these things from? You You base You talk
about your own lives. These people I
don't know what it is with these people.
keep talking about them their own lives
and then they get proven wrong multiple
multiple times but they're so [ __ ]
that they don't even realize.
Yeah, they I couldn't believe they
didn't score. They must have saw me
coming, mate. They must have saw me coming.
Yeah, they must have saw me coming.
That's all right, though. I've still got
well over a thousand, so I'm not skin
like LJ, so that's not a problem. M
£130 ain't a lot of money to me. It's
not that much. I'm up I'm up way way the
past two months. I just want to gamble again now.
I just want to gamble again.
[sighs and gasps]
No, cuz then I wouldn't have got much
much uh much back. It's fine. It's not a
problem. I just won't gamble now.
So that's fine. I mean, I'm up anyways.
You know, I spent 400 over400 pound on
gums. I spent £500 last week. I spent
300 pound over the weekend. So
really, if you didn't gamble in the
first place, it wouldn't even happen.
But anyways, doesn't matter.
He gets paid on. You don't know what I
get. Again, we don't all have your life.
I don't know why these people seem to
think that we've got their life like L.
He seems to think everyone's skint like
him. I don't know. I don't know what it
is with these people. Who's that?
Yeah. I don't know what it is with these people,
Candy, man. I don't know what it is with
these people. Keep self projecting.
Yeah, it's annoying losing a bet. It's
[ __ ] [ __ ] But we're not skint
like you people. I don't understand why
these people think everyone is skint like them.
And no matter how many times you try to
[ __ ] explain it to them, they're [ __ ] skint.
These people based that they think
everyone's got their skint lives. I
don't know what it is with these people.
They seem to think because they're skint
and they're on benefits and they get
paid every month. They think everyone's
got their life. I don't understand.
I'm not bothered. It's annoying, bro. I
won more than that, bro. I won £500 on
roulette. I won a couple of football
bets. I don't care. It's a [ __ ] It's
annoying as [ __ ] Yeah, it's annoying as
[ __ ] It is annoying, but it is what it
is, isn't it? I still have money. I've
still got my gums. I went out last week.
I went out the weekend. Whatever, bro.
Was that all my benefits gone? Bro,
again, we don't live your life. I don't
know how many times we have to explain.
We're not skin like you people. We don't
have your life. I don't know how many
times, bro. I have to say I have to
explain myself to these people, bro.
We don't all have your benefit skin
life. I And I'm being nice about when
I'm saying this, bro. We don't all live your life.
Skin on benefits. Nobody. Stop thinking
everyone's got the same life as you.
Like I go, you know what I'm saying,
bro? [ __ ] me. It's madness.
Why would that be all my benefits gone?
Bro, I've told you millions of times
I've got money. I've got enough money to
do what the [ __ ] I want. It's just
[ __ ] It's [ __ ] annoying.
It would have been the same with any
[ __ ] mount on it. It's [ __ ] annoying. Yeah.
So, stop adding me to these stupid group chats, you know?
They they think everyone's got their
life. It's [ __ ] It's It's It's funny
really. They think everyone is skint
like them. That's why they come online
every day calling people skin because
they think everyone's skint like them.
It must be their disabilities, bro. It's
got to be these people's disabilities on
here. It's got to be these people's
[ __ ] disabilities on here, mate. No,
I wouldn't be showing it because I'm
never showing you skint people money
ever again. Never in a million years am
I ever showing you money again. Just
like when I won that bet last week. I
will never show you little skin self
projectors money ever again. Not even5.
So get the [ __ ] out of it, bro. Get your
self projecting ass. If I win, would I
be going out tonight? No, I wouldn't.
And I can go out tonight if I want to
because I'm not skint. Yeah.
Simple. No, I wouldn't be going out. No,
I wouldn't. Nope. Even if I won, I still
wouldn't be going out, bro. I'm not
going out now after last uh well this
week. I won't be going out now for
I said I was going to go out next week
with my sister but nah probably like
eight weeks to be fair. Yeah, done with it, bro.
Done with it. Yep. I won't be doing
anything now for probably eight weeks.
Yep. That's what happens.
Nope. I am never showing you money ever,
ever, ever again. So there's no point
asking me because I'm never showing you
money ever again. So there's no point
asking me if you want to keep projecting
your skittness onto me. You you you be
my guest, bro. That's I'm never ever
showing you money ever again. You biased
people. So there's no point in you
asking me. I'm never showing you
nothing. And you can say I've got
nothing. Okay, I've got nothing.
Whatever. You're not going to bait me
for your little self-p projecting ways.
It's not going to happen, mate. It's not
going to happen.
So yeah, I won last week. won the other
bet. I won on the roulette.
It's just [ __ ] [ __ ] and annoying,
isn't it? So that's that. And it Yeah,
that's it. I don't know why these people
seem to think that
seem to think everyone is skin like
them. I don't know why they seem to
think everyone's got their own lives.
They think people have got their lives. Weird.
No, I'm good, bro. I sell my jeans. Why
would I sell my jeans? I've got more
than enough money. Why would I Why would
I sell my jeans? I've got well over
£1,000. I can go out when I want. I can
go out whenever I want, mate. Nah.
Nah, bro. I'm good, man. I shouldn't
have went out. Do you know what? If I
didn't go back yesterday, bro, I'm not
doing the next one. I'm not doing
nothing now for eight weeks. I'm doing [ __ ] all.
I'm absolutely doing [ __ ] all now. So
that's that. Yep.
That's me. If I didn't go out uh
yesterday, I wouldn't have done that
football bet to be honest. It's it's a
negative. It's a constant negative in
this country. Women [ __ ] then you
gamble. Boring. Not doing that again, mate.
So yeah, [ __ ] that, bro. Wasting any
more money now.
And why am I why would I sell my dreams?
I've got more than enough money to go
out and go out whenever I want. I'm
going to get a curry in a bit, I think.
Yeah, I'm going to get a curry in a bit.
And so there you go. You've seen
someone's gambled responsibly,
right? You've seen someone's gambled responsibly.
Right. And obviously I'm still up as
well. Majorly up. And it still affects
me. See, there you go. There's no such
thing as gambling responsibly.
There's no such thing as gambling
responsibly. There's no such thing.
responsibly. No such thing.
No such thing as gambling responsibly.
There's no such thing.
There's no such thing as gambling responsibly.
No such thing.
And I was in a position to do that as
well. I was in a position to do that as
So what I done 120 that returned 360.
What did I lose? 13. 130, bro.
But I've won a lot in the football the
past I've won a lot the past two months, obviously.
So, yeah, I'm not doing it anymore. [ __ ] that, bro.
Yeah, I just lost 130 on this football bet.
But I still got well over a thousand,
but I won't be going out now for eight weeks.
No, I won't be doing nothing now for
eight weeks. I was going to go with my
sister next week, but I'm canceling now.
That's depressing as [ __ ] bro. That is
depressing as [ __ ] This is why you
shouldn't go out, bro. This is why you
shouldn't go out drinking.
This is why you shouldn't go out
drinking cuz it's one negative thing
leads to another. It would always be the
same here. I It's my fault. I shouldn't
have went out drinking to be honest.
You know, I shouldn't have went out
drinking to be honest, bro. It's my own
fault. You know, negative after negative
after negative after negative after
negative after the size. [ __ ] this, bro.
[snorts] You know, so I wish I didn't go
out now, bro.
No, none of these numbers replied, did they?
Nope. Not a sausage. Same old England,
eh? Same old England. Never change.
Good old England. never changes.
Well, I'm breaking the cycle anyways cuz
I ain't going out now for six weeks. So,
now I won't be doing anything, but I'll
be in bed for like eight weeks probably
now until mid December. That is
depressing as [ __ ] [sighs and gasps]
That is depressing as [ __ ] bro. No,
I'll be I'll be depressed, bro. [ __ ] that.
[clears throat] That is depressing as
[ __ ] bro. [ __ ] that. So yeah,
I'm going to have to somehow make it to
the shop now. So yeah.
Yeah, I won't be doing no more football
bets now anyways, bro.
I won't be going out drinking. I won't
be doing nothing. It's too depressing, bro.
Yeah, I won't be doing anything now. But
staying in bed,
that's all right, ain't it? Yeah, I'm
good, bro. So, that's that.
That's how it gets you, bro. It's
depressing as [ __ ] Very, very depressing.
It's the same thing as a dopamine. See,
you get You need a rin to get a dopamine
rush. If you don't get a dopamine rush,
then you're [ __ ] Basically, it's
nothing to do with money, bro. You can
have loads and loads of money. That's
depressing, bro. Along with the women
and all of that. That's why I I stopped
going out, bro. That's why I stopped
going out for as long as I did, cuz of
this. And I'm not getting into I'm not
going into that cycle again, bro. [ __ ] that. So,
yeah. I'm not going into that cycle again. Yeah.
Imagine every 1300 pound. Why would
somebody make up that they've got 1,300
pound? These people seem to think
everyone's got their life. And I don't
know why they do. I don't know why they
think everyone's got their life, but
they do. So,
yeah, it's just a cycle, lad.
It's always It's always a cycle in this
country in nature. You go out, you try
to get women, they give you attitude,
you gamble to try to get a bars, it backfires.
Um, and it will just always be the same
here in it. It will always be the same here. So
[snorts] that's that. And it that's
[sighs and gasps]
I feel hung over as [ __ ] today even
though I stuck on I stayed on a beer.
No, I just lost. Uh it's not depression,
it's the depression from the women, the
bad experiences with women. Yeah. It's
not we have depression, we are depressed
because of the bad experiences with
women. Then we gamble to try to get a
bars and then it backfires. And it's
always going to be the same cycle in
this country. This is why I'm leaving,
bro. This is why I'm out of it, bro.
Don't really know where I'm going, do
you? There you go. So, it will always be
the same here, bro. And that's me. And
I'm still up from gambling as well. I'm
still up from gambling and better off if
I didn't gamble and it's still affecting
me. It's so depressing. It's not It's
not a [ __ ] form of entertainment.
Bad experiences with women. Gamble, more
depression. It's the same thing every single time.
you go out.
And I went out the past two weeks as
well. So yeah, I won't be doing anything
anymore now. So that's me done.
Yeah, he's not getting a link. He can
[ __ ] off. Simple.
He can [ __ ] off. He ain't getting a link. So yeah.
Yeah, I went out. I got seven numbers
yesterday. Slim messaged them. None
replied. The one Snapchat replied, "Good
old England, eh?" Another £300 down the
drain with not a step closer to getting
an eight. But I'm sure you'll find
someone. I'm sure you will find someone,
my son. What was it last week? Was it
£500? Yeah, but you'll find someone.
You'll find someone, bro. Don't you
worry about that, mate. It might just
take more and more going out and more
and more more wasting money and being
hung over the next day.
Yeah. So that's 300 over the weekend.
Well, anyways, that's me anyways. So
it isolates you as well.
See, the thing is, Slim, I'm still up
from gambling and I've still got plent
I've got more plenty of money. I've got
more than enough money. It doesn't make
a difference. It doesn't make a
difference. I'm still up more than up.
Got my gums. It doesn't matter. It's
literally It does not matter, bro. If
you've still got money or not. I don't
know why people seem to think that
because you've got money, it's okay. No,
it's not okay, bro. Losing is [ __ ]
annoying. It doesn't matter how much
money it is, you know? It's more
depressing depressing than anger to be
honest with the football bets. It's more depressing.
And that's I would say that's gambling
within my means to be honest. Won the
last week, one before that, calculated
wins from the past two months. I would
say yeah, it might seem a lot to some
people, but 130 that's definitely gam
that's definitely gambling within your
means and still depressing. So there we go, bro.
You know, it doesn't matter, bro, if you
if you gamble or it doesn't matter if
you still got money or I'm up as well.
I'm up again from the last two months.
I'm up as well. That's another thing.
Doesn't make a difference. The shit's
depressing as [ __ ]
I think I'm going to give my mom some
money actually cuz I won't be going out
now for a month. So, I'd be more than
happy to give her money at the end of
the day. It's not a problem. Yeah,
but [clears throat] I don't care. I I
went out uh slim and I done some
approaches yesterday. I went to um the dentist.
I went to the dentist, bro. And I done
some approaches sober, bro. It took me
40 approaches to get one number. You know?
Yeah. You ain't got no money. Yeah. It
took me 40. sober approaches to get one
number slim. H it's getting worse here,
bro. It's getting worse. Oh, unless
people are going out now cuz they're
skin. Uh that's another thing.
Yeah. It doesn't matter if I'm still up.
I don't care. It's depressing, bro.
It's depressing. So, yeah. Yeah.
But I know when to stop. That's the
difference. I know when to stop the
gambling [ __ ] I know when to stop, bro.
That's the difference.
So, some people don't. So, yeah. [gasps]
Yeah, I'll be depressed now for eight weeks.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] that, bro. It's depressing.
That is depressing, bro.
That is [ __ ] depressing.
So, yeah, man. I don't know how Slow
didn't score to be honest, but the [ __ ] never. So yeah,
well I won't be out now anyways unless
one of these numbers want to meet me.
I'm not wasting any more money.
More than happy to go on a date and
spend £300, but unless that unless that
happens, I will not be going out trying.
Simple as that.
So that's it.
No, I'm not doing it again next week,
bro. I'm not doing nothing.
Maybe there's something on the cinema or
something. Maybe there's something in
the cinema. I might go to cine or something. Nah.
And unless one of these numbers meet me,
I won't go out now for a month. So
simple. Longer than a month. I say a
month. Longer than a month. Probably
eight weeks. [ __ ] that, bro.
[ __ ] that. See, you need these wins to
make you not see what it is. But then
when you don't win, you're back to
reality. Oh, it's [ __ ] It's just a
cycle in this country. You're just going
around in circles. That's all you're
doing. You're constantly constantly
constantly going around in circles, bro. Women,
you know, it's just never ever ever ending, bro.
You know, yesterday was a oneoff, so I
didn't mind doing it. So,
yeah, basically. Yeah. Yep.
No need to waste any more money here.
Time or money here? No, bro.
Yeah, that's that, bro.
Depressing, isn't it?
It's so bad because people will laugh,
but I'm still up loads of money. That's
what makes me laugh. They will they will
laugh, but I'm still up loads of money,
but they're so low IQ. They realize that, bro. So
last week then I went out this week obviously. So
I knew he was going to lose. It would
have been too easy, bro. It would have
been too easy. What? You just going to
win again like that? Nah,
it's not happening, bro.
But yeah, I was supposed to go out next
week, Slim. I'm not doing it now. Too depressed.
There's no reason for me to go out
drinking, bro. I went out last week. I
went out yesterday. I'm not going out
again. I approached about 100 women
yesterday. There's no need for me to go
out anytime soon. And I've got the
money. I've got more than enough money
to if I want to, but I'm not going to. Simple. So, yeah.
I [snorts] need to go and order a curry
in a bit. Get some food. I'm [ __ ] starving. Nope.
And I'm not doing it again, bro. Just
call it a bad week. I'm not I'm not
doing this dating [ __ ] again, bro, for a
very long time. Slim. It's too
depressing. It's too too too depressing. Depressing, bro.
No, no, no. I'm canceling my plans. I'm
not going out. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no. I'm not going out. There's no
there's no reason for me to go out
drinking, bro. I've been there, done it,
worn a t-shirt. The attitude I had to
put up with yesterday, bro. Um,
yeah. The amount of [ __ ] I had to deal
with yesterday, bro. Never again.
Never again, lad.
So, not for a long time, anyways.
I just went dentist yesterday. So,
so yeah, I had to deal with a lot of
[ __ ] yesterday, bro. A lot of uh bad attitude.
A lot of it, Slim, bro. A lot of it.
But it was a one-off in it. So,
yeah. Well, my football bet lost
Greavves. I'll be depressed now for eight weeks. Yep.
And I've still got money, but it's not the point.
It's [clears throat] not the point
whether you got money or not.
It's not the point whether you got money
or not. Greasy.
This is what these people think. They
think, "Oh yeah, if you lose money
gambling." Bro, as long as you've got
money, it's not about money. Whether you
still got money, bro, you could have
£10,000. It still wouldn't make a
difference. I'd still want to go and
[ __ ] kill someone. Bro, you don't
understand. It's annoying. So,
so well one Snapchat replied, so
nah, it's not a mental condition.
Nah, it's not a mental condition at all.
It's annoying. It's [ __ ] annoying.
It ruins everything.
That's what it does. It ruins
everything, Greavvesy. It ruins everything.
That's what it does.
>> So that's that.
See, whenever I lose, I just want to
give I just want to give someone money
when I lose, bro.
I just want to give someone money when I
lose. So this is what I mean. It just
[ __ ] everything up. I just want to give
people money. Greasy.
Like it sounds weird, isn't it? So
I've got like 1,300 left.
It's depressing, is it, bro?
It's depressing as [ __ ]
Well, I'm going to leave whilst I'm ahead anyways. So, yeah. Yeah,
that's starting it.
I knew it was going to I had a feeling
it was going to lose. I had a feeling it
to be honest.
Nah, you're all right. Thanks. So yeah,
that's sickening. It sickening, bro. Yeah.
Well, I best get this coke anyways. Yeah.
Yeah. Story of your life in it. Skint J.
Skint law J. Could be worse, mate. I
could be skint like you. Begging for donations.
40. No driving license, no money,
no job on a,000 pounds a month. I could
be like you, bro.
But you're [ __ ] skint. That's the
difference, mate. You're [ __ ] skint.
Yeah, that's the [ __ ] difference.
you're [ __ ] skint.
Yeah, you skimp bastard.
You skiint [ __ ] bastard. Who the [ __ ]
goes to Weather Spoons and begs for [ __ ] money,
begs for drinks.
Who the [ __ ] in their right mind does that, bro? Yeah. Anyways,
I'm going to go get this coke and order
some food. Anyways,