Yep.
Just ordered this food.
Well, I'm speaking to this person on
Snapchat, but [ __ ]
one reply out of all of that. That's mad.
Of all of them people, what the person
on Snapchat replied, "This is bollocks, mate." Yep.
for that amount of money. 20 for that.
[ __ ] hell. Cheap as [ __ ] Is it? Yeah.
Okay. Bad. This kid madness.
Yeah. Well, that's me done anyways
for 8 weeks.
[ __ ] that, mate. [ __ ] that. Yeah.
[snorts] Depressing as [ __ ] bro.
That just tells you that there's no such
thing as gambling responsibly.
Cuz normally you gamble an amount you
can afford to lose. But in this case, we
didn't even lose any money because it
was money that we hadn't won.
There's no such thing as gambling
responsibly then, is there? No. Clearly not.
No. Think is gambling responsibly?
Cuz that's as responsible as it gets really.
[ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that.
Just wait until this food arrived.
It's so embarrassing having to cancel
plans, isn't it?
It's very, very embarrassing having to cancel plans.
Well, it's embarrassing for me. So yep. Yep.
So, this person's replying on Snapchat.
One reply out of [ __ ] eight different
socials, eh? [ __ ] [ __ ] mate. Absolute [ __ ]
Absolute bollocks, man. So yeah, last week
went out this week.
Yeah, [ __ ] that. I ain't doing it again.
See, I'm actually better off gambling
than if I didn't gamble. That's how
[ __ ] up it is. People like me really
shouldn't gamble, should they? They They
really shouldn't gamble.
Really shouldn't gamble, bro.
Probably have a better life now than
when I was subleting.
Really shouldn't gamble.
That secular slot is [ __ ] full of
absolute [ __ ] He is absolute He's full
of absolute [ __ ]
It's got a lot of [ __ ] food for 20 quid. Oh yeah. >> [snorts] >> Yep. Yeah.
got a girlfriend had more sex than you
got more money than you talking about
yourself. This is why you don't get
blocked because you're talking about yourself.
Everybody knows that you are the one
that's skin. Look at your life and look
at my life. You're sat on YouTube
begging people for money. You wear the
most trampiest clothes. Like, you need
to understand. I know you've got
disabilities, but you are the one that's
got nothing. You are the one that is
skint. You need to let that process in
your brain. You are the one that has no
woman, no sex life, no money. That is
you. You can't even afford to go out.
[ __ ] women. You're so skinn you can't
even afford to go out.
You can't even afford to go out. Like
me, I just can't be bothered. I'm done
with this [ __ ] You can't even
afford to go out. And then when you go
to a Weather Spoons, you have to beg for
drinks. You have to beg for drinks. If
you had any kind of money, you wouldn't
swallow your pride and keep begging
people for money.
You know, you beg people for money in
Weather Spoons. You wouldn't do that if
you wasn't skinn. You know, you wouldn't
do what you do if you wasn't skinned,
mate. You can't pull the wall over my
eyes. You really really can't pull the
wool over my eyes. Seriously, you know,
I I know you better than you know your
[ __ ] self, kid.
You can't even afford to go out. You're that skin
lying that you've got six properties in
Belfast would, which would be the equivalent to what? £5,10.
Come on, man. Your lines don't even make
sense. Anyone that's not disabled would
would be able to see right through you.
You're full of [ __ ]
full of absolute [ __ ]
So that's that. They're bastards, bro. These slunts.
>> So why do you beg So why do you beg for
drinks and weather spoons if you've got money? Huh?
That doesn't make any sense.
That doesn't make any sense at all.
Nah, I'm good. Thanks. So, yeah.
I wish I bought some Ugg boots. They're
like 165 and I just lost 130 on the bet.
Madness, bro. Madness.
[ __ ] in it.
Well, my day is done anyways.
It's bad, isn't it?
It is bad to be fair.
It is bad, bro. Yep. Let's
see if there's anything in the cinema.
I don't think there is. I already catch
You all right, Captain?
All right, captain. Oh [ __ ] there
might these UGG boots.
They're [ __ ] expensive though. 165 lb.
That's what I always feel like whenever
I lose money, even though like it's
obviously I've still won a lot of money,
I'm still well up. It's not the point,
bro. It's like you could have bought you
could have just gave someone that money
but depending on how much it is
obviously you know what I mean. It's madness.
I don't know about anyone else but
You just feel bad in it. That's the thing. Yeah, that's Yeah.
Yeah, my body is ugly
at some stop it to someone else for a change, you know.
Look how mad that escalated.
Look how mad that weekend escalated
bad bad bad in it.
That escalated badly, bro. Very badly.
It doesn't even sound [ __ ]
believable, does it? No.
[ __ ] mental, bro. Men,
I might as well [ __ ] my sleeping pattern
up now. I won't be doing anything. So, Yeah.
Yeah, that's starting it. Yep.
No, that's you. You're the one that
skimmed. You're the one that skimmed.
You are the one that skin. You're the
one that begs for drinks, matey.
Not me, matey.
You are the one that's skin, matey.
Not me, matey. I don't see you putting
£130 on a football bet. No.
No. That's you. Your skin.
That's why you always talk about money.
You always talk about money, bro.
No, you don't. How How much is your watch?
Oh, really? How much is your watch then?
I don't think so, matey. Mate, my
wardrobe is worth more than your whole
life and your kids' life.
Bro, my wardrobe is worth
more than your life and your kids' life.
Like, it's that sad.
Yeah, that's how sad it is.
It's it's it's really really sad, bro.
Really really sad.
Really really really sad.
It actually makes me feel quite bad, to be honest. Nah,
no, he doesn't, mate. I've got more
money than both of you.
I got more money than both of you.
That's not possible, matey. I've got
more money than both of you, matey. I
don't beg for money, matey.
Thank you, matey. He's your skint matey.
You are skint matey. Nah,
my jeans and trainers are worth more
modding your whole wardrobe, let alone
the [ __ ] Stone Island [ __ ]
Stone Island um
Stone Island jumpers.
Sounds like someone's getting [ __ ] shot.
Sounds like someone's being [ __ ] shot
outside, bro. What the [ __ ]
Someone being [ __ ] shot or something.
Bro, it sounds like someone's being
[ __ ] shot or some [ __ ]
So, this person is messaging me on Snapchat.
So, one reply out of all of them numbers
and the person that replies is Snapchat.
Get [ __ ] man.
That is [ __ ]
>> One second. above.
Sorry about that. Am I good, Bob? No.
No, I'm [ __ ] not. [laughter]
Do you like that one, Grezy?
I've ordered some lush food.
Grezy, I got a lot for 20 pound. Big Indian.
Are you good? No. No, I'm [ __ ] not. Yeah.
No, I'm [ __ ] not. Yeah, I got ticker,
tandoori, chicken, cheese, naan. Yep.
No, I was just downstairs talking to Laney.
Yeah, I won't be going out now for a while.
Oh, I got one number reply.
So, I got one number and one Snapchat.
Yeah, I won't be going out um unless
someone wants to meet me.
Not spending money unless someone wants
to meet me.
It's true though, ain't it, Grey? Isn't
that the wise thing?
Went out last week and I went out the week before.
That's mad. I've gone out a lot in it.
Yeah, [ __ ] that, bro.
You actually think I can't afford it, Grezy?
You actually think I can't afford to go
out every week? Of course I can, you silly goose.
But I'm not [ __ ] doing that, bro. [ __ ] that.
Lady said I'm getting a bit too greedy
with going out.
Why am I getting too greedy? Greasy.
[snorts] Why am I getting too greedy?
Am I a greedy [ __ ] [laughter]
You're getting too greedy. We see
[ __ ] hell, man. [snorts] What's up?
My food's 15 minutes away. Captain.
All right, Captain.
You're right, Captain. Oh.
So, we got one number that replied and
one Snapchat that replied.
But that woman's full of [ __ ] She's not
going back to Russia.
She's full of [ __ ]
She's full of [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. No way.
That's the food, captain. >> [snorts]
>> One sec.
What do you think, Grezy? If you've gone
back to Russia, no way, bro.
It's just the same [ __ ] same mind
game, isn't it?
There's no way you're just even though
you've got a Russian number
like [ __ ] is it?
One second. I'm going to go eat this
food and I'll be better later, bro.