Yeah, I just ate some food. Yeah. [ __ ] dying. >> [snorts]
>> What the [ __ ]
But it will never change, would it?
You'll never change.
Never change, will it?
You'll never change. Here's the deal. Thank you.
Sorry, man. I went to eat.
Yeah, I went to eat.
Yeah, I lost 130 today. So, I got seven
numbers. One Snapchat. One number replied,
one Snapchat replied.
That's me done for the month. So yeah,
I'm not doing this [ __ ] anymore, lad.
[snorts] Yeah, man.
Yeah, I'm not doing this [ __ ] anymore.
It's bollocks, mate. So that's that.
that is that bro. Yeah.
Yeah. I won't be going out now for maybe
6 weeks, bro. I think.
Yeah. Cuz I see where this is going. I
can see where the spiral is going, bro.
and it ain't good. So,
you need to catch it early.
You need to break the cycle and you
don't want to go into the same cycle
again. You know, it's not good. Just
need to leave now. That's it. So, that's that.
That is that literally it. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. You know, I was doing good
until I went out again. Until I started
going out again, bro. I felt good until
I started going out again.
Drinking. I went out this week and I
went out last week. What the [ __ ]
Spent like £800 between the two days on
doing that [ __ ] again, bro.
Yeah, I ain't doing that again.
At least you are, mate.
I won't be gambling either, bro. I won't
be drinking and gambling now for a long time
cuz I see where this is heading, bro. And
I know when to stop [ __ ] You know what I mean?
Attitude mind games and [ __ ] I'm I'm
not doing it, bro. But
yeah, man. That's that in it. So yeah. Yep.
Yeah. They [ __ ] me up, mate. They
[ __ ] me up. So,
yeah. I was supposed to go out next week
with my sister, but I'm not doing it
now. I'll just be chilling.
I'll just be chilling, bro. basically
back to a boring life in it. Oh well.
Laney says you need to cut the guy out.
You're getting greedy.
There's [ __ ] [ __ ] going out in this
country, bro. [ __ ]
Yeah, I went out last week and I went
out the week before. I don't even know
why I bothered, bro. I won't be going
out now. So,
I've got enough numbers, mate. So
if someone wants to meet, they can.
Yeah, I've got enough numbers. So more
than enough numbers. I'm not going out
trying again. [ __ ] off.
I got an escort. Wait, I got escort
twice, didn't I, bro?
Yeah, I did. I got an escort
yesterday and I got an escort last week.
Yeah, I've lived the life, bro. I I
[ __ ] well have I did, didn't I? I got
one last week as well. Jesus.
Yeah, I did.
Yeah, I'm all right, bro. I'll I'll I'll
be good, bro.
What a month anyways.
Yeah, the last one was 80 and the other
one was 120. That's 200 in escorts.
Hundreds of pounds going out I've spent. So
yeah, I don't need to uh do anything more.
Yeah, I didn't realize I got an escort
last week as well.
[snorts] Jesus Christ. I'm living a
better life than when I [ __ ] was
doing a sublet. That's a lot, bro. in
one month when you're [ __ ] not
getting that kind of money anymore.
Two escorts gums.
Yeah, that's that's good, bro.
Escort garments drink
and I got like 1,300 left. But I I'm not
wasting any of it, bro. I'm not wasting
any of it.
I just want to chill in, bro. I don't
want to go out waste money. [snorts] No,
I just realized did go escorts it. Yeah.
We got loads of numbers too,
but none no bloody interested Steven
Howard. So that's that.
Time to give up. You tried your best in
this country. So
it's time to leave now.
Yeah, it's time to leave now, bro.
No, I messaged them all. I didn't need
to save them. I've messaged them all,
bro. Only one replied and one Snapchat replied.
So, and one said, one has a Russian
number and she says that she's going
back to Russia tomorrow.
Um, which I don't believe that. It's
just [ __ ] bro. It's [ __ ] And
at the end of the day, it was just a
oneoff anyways yesterday.
Like going out approaching for that
long. I won't be doing it again, bro. So,
some some other [ __ ] can deal with it.
I won't be dealing with it anymore, bro.
Like, it's so bad. Obviously, it was a
one-off, bro. I'd rather be sat there by
myself and have nothing then deal with
them. That's how bad it is
that I wasn't expecting it to be that
bad. I generally wasn't expecting it to
be that bad, bro. I'd rather sit here with nothing.
Like, that's bad. That's how bad it is, bro. Yeah.
So, actually, I have been out a lot.
I'm sure I went out the week before that
as well. No.
[ __ ] that, bro. I'm not wasting any more money. I don't.
I didn't realize that.
So, I actually do have a pretty good
life to be honest.
Two escort garments. Yeah,
[ __ ] slow continent.
Pretty good life. Well,
obviously the escorts are the big
expense as well.
Yeah, that escort was 80. The other one was 120
cuz whenever I go out drinking
I wasn't sat on YouTube last weekend.
Well, I went out yesterday.
I went out last Saturday. then
I don't need to go out again.
And I'm not trying to justify it because
I can't afford it because I can afford
it. I can [ __ ] afford it. I just
don't want to, bro. you know. Yeah.
You need to leave.
That's all there is to do now. Just leave.
That boyfriend [ __ ] Steven Albert gets
really old, bro. It gets really, really, really old.
Really old, bro. Really fast.
And I don't even date that much anymore. You know,
what would you off? Yeah, it's boring as
[ __ ] It's boring, bro.
I just done it yesterday as a oneoff. It
is boring, isn't it?
The boyfriend [ __ ] is boring as [ __ ] bro.
Proper boring. Even when you're drunk.
Bors me, bro.
I don't exchange numbers cuz I have a
boyfriend. [ __ ] off.
It's [ __ ] bro. It's [ __ ] in it.
I'm sick of that [ __ ]
So, that's starting it. Yep.
And man said that's why he left because of it. Yep.
Lies as well.
I can tell you as well that I know for a
fact that these women are compulsive
[ __ ] and liars. Bro,
we done some [ __ ] money and bro, we did. So,
yeah, I can tell you for a fact they're
bullshitters as well.
I can tell you how, you know, but they
are generally I feel sorry for any guy
that puts himself through this. Any guy
that wants to put himself through this,
I I feel for them, bro.
Germany feel bad for them.
Not putting up with that [ __ ] anymore,
bro. [ __ ] that.
How many of them do you think have
boyfriends that say say that Steven Howard?
You know when they say they've got
boyfriends, how many do you actually think do?
I think like [ __ ] two out I think
like three out of 10, bro.
Yeah, I'm not doing any more gambling.
No more gambling. No more drinking.
No, I'm done with it all, bro. Yeah.
Don't know what I'm going to do, bro.
Name you a number. What do you mean, bro?
I might stop working, bro,
cuz I have nothing better to do now. So,
I could earn and make some I could earn
some money, but the thing is
just cuz there's nothing else to do, you know?
But then the problem with that is then
I've still got to deal with [ __ ]
But who cares? You're making money in it. [ __ ]
I'm going to do something, bro. I don't know yet. [snorts]
Trying to think of stuff I could do. I
don't want to waste any money. I don't
want to waste a lot of money, though.
That's the thing.
Yeah, I ate it, Greavvesy. Yeah,
I'm just trying to think of things I can
do now. Now I've given up with the
dating again. I'm trying to save money. Uh,
I can't go cinema cuz there's nothing on.
I was just saying, Greavves, I got an
escort last night and I got an escort last week.
Got the gums, went out drinking. So live a pretty
still live a relatively good life, you know,
greasy, but relatively good Yep.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. Greasy. Are these
women still giving you grief, lad?
Grieves you. Are these [ __ ] women
still giving you grief?
How much do you
How much do you live on a week? We How 50 quid lesser.
Yeah, it's one of them, bro. It
Yeah, it's only a small amount of
winnings, bro. I'm still well up.
I'm still wet up. So yeah,
what is it normally? 80 I'm guessing. Normally 80. Yep.
and yeah, I'll just be chilling now anyways.
Nothing else to do now, is there? Yep.
Is that okay with you, Greasy Boss? If I
don't go out for about 8 weeks,
I have to run it by you first. Is that
okay with you, boss?
Okay with you, boss.
They okay with you, boss. Nope.
Not planning to either.
I can't believe I got an escort
yesterday and I got an escort last week
and I got garments. That's insane, bro.
cuz I don't want to.
We're cute together. Uh Yeah.
Is that okay with you, boss? Yeah.
Get the cut good. Get it cut good. Yeah.
Why do you go out drinking, Grezy? Huh? >> [snorts] >> No.
Do you know what I mean by I'm giving up
Greasy because it will spiral.
You know what I mean by that? And it's spiraling.
I can see where it's going, bro.
I can see what's going to happen if I
keep doing this, bro.
Cuz I've been pretty good, bro. I've
been a pretty good [ __ ]
you know, cuz say I go out, say I go out
next week, right? And I go out the week
after, I decide I want to gamble all my money.
then I'll be [ __ ] You know,
it's just a negative.
That's all it is in this country is a constant negative.
And it would always be that way. Sir,
that's it. It [clears throat]
will never change, would it? We'll never change.
and you'll never change.
There we go.
Yeah. I approached some girl in Oxford Circus
and I was like, "Oh, can I get your
number?" She's she's like, "I don't
really give my number.
You got Instagram?" I said, "I don't
have Instagram. I always tell them I
don't have Instagram."
And then they're like,
they're like, "Um,
you got uh
I just don't get my number." I was like,
"Oh, bad experience." Yeah.
So I turned around and said, "Oh, give
me your um have you got Snapchat?" And
then they added me on Snapchat. So
just been talking to them.
Bless me. E doing these approaches sober.
Oh, that's me. >> [snorts]
>> You don't really go out, do you? Crazy.
You don't got that much, do you? That's Yeah. Badness. Anyways,
I'm gone. I'll see you later.