Joseph,
where are you?
You leaving me hanging here, Joseph?
[ __ ] hell, mate. Oh, Franklin.
Yeah, that was depressing. Yeah, that
was depressing yesterday. That [ __ ]
football bet, wasn't it?
Yeah, that was [ __ ] depressing, you lads.
Don't have to put anyone on a bloody downer.
Isn't that right, Joseph? Joseph for
I'm going to start [ __ ]
that was [ __ ] in it today.
Oh, [ __ ] tired, bro. Yep.
Another weekend for nothing.
It's always going to be the same here. You notice
like a certain person said I'm actually
in my little gowny actually keep you
warm. I say keep you warm. I got my fan
on. I don't know. Yeah. Seeing
[ __ ] madness, it Yeah, man. Franklin
little Franklin. I don't watch Money Man anymore actually
for some no reason.
I don't watch. Yeah,
still talking to that person. Anyway,
I won't be out for ages now, mate.
[ __ ] that [ __ ]
I'm not doing that. I thought I thought
another number would have replied to be fair,
but only wondered. That's really bad.
Really, really bad.
It gets bad to worse, doesn't it?
Truly no hope in this country.
It's a hopeless society delay. But uh yeah,
I met someone
I met someone in Oxford Circus. Yeah.
Yeah. I met someone in Oxford Circus.
[ __ ] hell. That was a load of
[ __ ] wasn't it? [ __ ] Friday
stuff some of these people come out with.
I feel sorry for any man that's willing
to put up with that [ __ ]
I really feel bad for them. You have to
question their models, don't you?
Really? If someone's willing to put up
with that [ __ ] every single day, it's mental, bro. Mental.
That is insane, bro. And I only done it
as I only done that as a tester.
[ __ ] that, bro. Absolutely [ __ ] that.
That is mad. That is mad. Yeah, man.
For the [ __ ]
By the end of Friday, I got I had a [ __ ] migraine.
Hearing that [ __ ] bro. Oh my god.
The boyfriend [ __ ] It gives you a headache.
It's not even just that. It's other
thing as well.
They are so full of [ __ ] bro. These people have many [ __ ] medical Yeah.
Where the [ __ ] did Joseph go?
He's probably on one of his outings. You
know what Joseph's like? Yeah.
I still [ __ ] me.
My wife was so tired. [snorts] Yeah. Heat.
Yeah, them them Reddit mods need that power.
Without that power, mate,
without that power, they're bloody
nothing. Bloody nothing, guys.
Power is everything to some people,
mate. Without that bloody power [snorts]
They love banning people on Reddit. I'm
not sure why,
but they Yeah. Heat. >> [laughter]
>> They just weren't interested in England.
I've got matches um from Thailand, you know.
Yeah, that's how I know that they just
weren't interested in England in England.
In Thailand, they are. Okay. But but in
in this country, [snorts]
that is [ __ ] funny as [ __ ] That's funny.
Skinn virgin. He's been awfully quiet.
That skin bastard. [ __ ] me.
That skin bastard has been bloody quiet. He
a spooking skin flint.
But skin and
can't believe there's someone that
comment yesterday saying that's not what
Universal Credits for. I'm reporting
you. They're such little bongos of this
community that little grass and little
bit little bongos ain't got no life. If
they actually put effort into fixing
their own fat, ugly lives, then they
wouldn't feel the need to even write a
comment like that. [ __ ] complete mongos.
How they sit on the internet, right,
year in year out [ __ ] with people for
for free. Like they don't even get paid for it.
They're just complete bloody losers in
life, aren't they?
To tell you the truth. Yeah.
This guy in France ran away. When I show
him the evidence and the bad
experiences, these people keep running
away. Joseph and I have to chase them
like chase a cloud. back
on that do that. Oh [ __ ]
I am [ __ ] [snorts]
urgent post on that channel anymore.
Well, insecure, fragile ego, little rat
face. Only you see pay out today as the
eight falls on a Saturday. Just count for anyone.
Ah, Jesus Christ. If only these people
knew how much money people have. They
they they literally
base their own lives on anyone on
everyone else's. They think everyone's
got the same life as them.
They think everyone's skin like them. I
don't know what it is with these people.
You got bloody L coming in begging for
donations, begging for drinks and
weather spoons, but apparently I'm the
skinn one. Bloody hell. You know,
doesn't make any [ __ ] sense.
No, no, no. doesn't
make any sense.
[snorts] You're getting too greedy with
going out now. Laney said, "I know. I
know. I know. I'm so bloody silly, aren't I?
Don't get greedy.
Oh gosh. Darn it.
Yeah, I'm quite silly. [snorts] I'm
quite greedy as well.
It's just me though, isn't it?
P, isn't it?
Why I feel so tired today? I think I'm
still [ __ ] from that uh Friday, you
know, the walking around the approaching. Yeah. Yeah,
I get paid on the ETH. That's loose to
me. I didn't know I got money on the
eighth. You learn something new every
day with these little skinned virgins. A you, mate.
Why would I get paid on the eth? What
the [ __ ] Where the [ __ ] would somebody
get that from?
Yeah, they base their lives of other
people's. They think everyone's got the
same life as them.
Like when we lost that football m
yesterday, oh, your skin. I had to say
about 28 times to be exact.
We don't all have the same life as you
people. And it doesn't seem to drill in
their [ __ ] head. I don't know why,
but it doesn't.
[ __ ] you got that. so skinny he can't
even afford to go out like the kind of
can't afford to do nothing. You can sit
properties in Belfast would be about a pound each.
So I mean you're not making money off
properties in Belfast mate. Anybody with
a cooting would know that you know
properties you don't own properties you
[ __ ] idiot. Stop lies. Stop the lies.
I don't know what it is with these with
these people. They happen to lie.
It's ridiculous. It's it's it's ridiculous, man.
You don't own no bloody properties. You see sausage.
So, some fat ginger [ __ ] with a disabled
back has suddenly started to own
property even though the property
wouldn't even be worth anything in
Belfast. It's just [ __ ] The guy's
on guy gets about£1,000
a month maximum.
He's a silly goose.
He's a very very very silly goose. That one Silly silly silly silly.
See if this person wants to meet me.
We've been talking.
See what they say.
They're buying back a lot yesterday. So,
even like me, so we'll see.
That's me done, bro. [ __ ] that.
Out like two, three weeks in a row. I'm
not [ __ ] doing it again. But literally
it's too toxic. Way way way too toxic. >> Yep.
I miss Joseph Ferrar
[ __ ] skin. Big nose, bro. What the
I'm not the one showing daddy's peanut
savings. That's not me, bro.
Only one that's skin is you, me. Takes
one to no one.
It takes one to no one be. That's how
the old saying goes. Hey sunshine,
you are the skid one. You didn't go
abroad until you was 30 cuz of lack of
funds. No, no, no. The skin one is you,
matey. The skin one is you. Nothing else.
the fing virgin.
No, that's you.
Not me, matey. That's you, matey. Not Check the
I'm second, bro. H. But yeah.
This person was like, "Oh, um, do you
have friends that have partners? How did
they do it?" I don't know. I don't
compare myself to other people. We're
all different. We're all We're all
unique. This is what I used to say to Mr. Mustard.
Yeah, I really don't compare myself to
strangers. It's a complete waste of time.
It's a complete waste of time comparing
yourself to strangers.
It never gets you anywhere. So, and for
the record, most of the people I know
are single. So, even if they wasn't, I
mean, that's not going to help my situation. Anyways,
I'm going I'll be back later.