Oh gosh,
that was a lovely meal. Oh gosh,
that was delicious.
I was thinking of greasy before I ate
it. I'm tired now. Bit sleepy,
you know. I'm like, "Oh gosh.
What The fake
Oh, [ __ ] hell, man.
Yeah, knocked me out. I'm [ __ ] tired now.
Where the [ __ ] is
Where the [ __ ] is Georgia for all? Enjoy. Hello. Oh, [ __ ]
That lamb was as soft as a baby's backside. Oh gosh,
that is has made me really really tired ass. That's greasy. Oh,
they don't do cies like that, mate, in [ __ ] Kent.
No, they don't do it like that in
[ __ ] Kent, son.
Don't do bloody cover like that in Kent. Oh, no mate.
Not in bloody can. They don't That's strange.
Where's bloody Joseph? Joseph. No.
Hey Grezy, I got a lovely Indian. I was
s I wanted to go to the restaurant.
It was really It was really delicious.
Really delicious. The lamb was as soft
as a baby's backside gy.
It's really soft.
It went It went down like a tree.
you know, good on the old toothies and stuff, you know.
Oh, now I feel tired. Yeah,
I was going to get some donuts, but I
didn't really fancy donuts. Greasy. Yeah. Yeah. Remember,
Greavvesy, you've spent your um you've
already reach your monthly budget,
your clothing budget. I'm so naughty,
aren't I, Greavvesy? I'm so greedy.
I'm such a greedy goose. That should be
my new name. Greedy Goose. Even Laney
said it. She said, "You're getting a bit
too greedy with going out. >> [laughter]
>> I'm greedy in it.
I like restaurants and beer. What can I say? Greasy. You know,
I love beer. I love chicken ticker a curry.
Oh, that chicken tickle was lovely. Musicy. Oh gosh.
Oh gosh. Darn it. Greasy.
I need to get my haircut.
I need to get my haircut uh this week.
Okay with you, boss.
okay with you, boss?
Getting a bit long and my beard's
getting a bit long, too. Is that okay
with you, boss?
Is that okay with you, boss, or not?
I got my little haircut.
Thank you, boss.
I'm going to get a full service at the barbers. Cheers, boss.
>> [clears throat]
>> Where the [ __ ] is this Joseph gone?
Greasy, I'm starting to get worried.
What is that? To save your little money, Greasy.
I've tried to be good, but I can't. I'm too greedy.
Oh, is that is that to save a couple of bobsy
that to save a couple of Bob in your
bank account then? A
Yeah, I wish I could say the same thing,
but I'm just [ __ ] greedy, bro.
I went out last week, banged an escort.
Went out the week before that, banged an
escort. I'm too greedy, grievy. I'm too bloody greedy.
When did you last have a Mackis? Greasy.
Oh, bless you then.
Oh, quite a while ago then.
Last Wednesday. Yeah, quite a while ago. Ah,
quite a while ago, bro. M.
Well, bless you then.
Oh, King's coming round on Friday,
Grezy. So, I might get him a five, guys.
I might whip him up a homemade burger.
Yeah, King's coming on Friday for sleepover.
You like King, don't you, Grezy?
I can't believe you only saved 420
[ __ ] from last month. Grezy, what the
bloody hell did you spend it on?
You bloody greedy goose.
You greedy goose.
You must have spent it all on McDonald's.
Yeah. How much was that?
must have been quite there now.
I spent so much money, bro.
200 jeans, 200 trainers. Escorts was 200.
We're going out. [ __ ] hell, bro. [ __ ] hell.
This a [ __ ] madness.
Yeah, you're getting too greedy. Greasy.
You're getting too greedy.
Would you actually say that I'm greedy? Greasy.
I don't think I'm greedy.
You're getting too greedy with going
out. I'm dead.
That is jokes, bro.
Where's grand a month boy Grezy? He's
been quiet, ain't he? That bloody skin plonker.
What do you think, Grezy? He's been blooming quiet.
The skin bastard. [laughter]
Where's that bloody skin bastard? [ __ ] hell.
That skin [ __ ]
He's been quite that skint [ __ ]
So what did you do when you spent £300
on that? What did you do? Just live off £900, Grezy.
So what did you do? Just live off £900. Hello, captain.
Yeah. Did you struggle?
Oh, bless you then.
Bless you then, Grezy.
Oh, [ __ ] me.
Oh, gosh. So, you like the look of the
Indian then, Grezy? Yeah. Imagine I took
King to a little restaurant and he was
sat at the table as well.
Oh, bless grieves. You imagine he was
sat on the table opposite me.
Them Indians are so nice, bro.
Oh, I think I spent £40 today
almost. Me and I got another coconut.
Oh, [ __ ] me.
Bendy wife Sky. Who's that? Oh gosh,
that curry was so yummy. [gasps]
If you gone to the card factory, they've
got a Stitch section. They've got a
section dedicated to Stitch and Spongebob.
Yeah, I saw it the other day when I was in town. Kazzy,
I'm doing all right. I just had a lovely meal.
I want me channel.
Yeah, check it out.
I'm all right. I've just had a lovely
meal. I'm just chilling now. There's not
much on Timmy's channel. [snorts]
Don't go spending all your money, Grezy.
We know what you're like, you silly goose.
We don't have silly rumors on this
channel, do we, Grezy?
We don't have silly, immature rumors on
this channel, do we Greavvesy?
We don't have immature, self-protecting
people in this channel, do we grieves lad?
Obviously, I have to run it by you first.
We don't have that. Yeah.
Oh, good for you. Well, you can [ __ ] off
back around with them rumors and see you later.
We don't have uh immature projecting
people on this channel, do we Grezy?
This is a channel about food and stitch and Franklin.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
You know I'm not part of this community.
You do realize that, Grezy?
I just post my videos
and people come on my I would even say
I'm part of this community, bro.
I don't argue with them. I don't even
watch any of them.
I ain't part of this community, bro. Oh [ __ ]
I done the dating video in the end.
Graves, obviously I needed your
permission and you gave me the you gave
me the thumbs up. So yeah,
he's a silly goose. A really silly
And I'm a greedy goose.
You just got out of prison,
huh? Good one.
Just cut out prison.
Yeah, that's funny, man.
Oh, these people, bro, are idiots on here.
Isn't it crazy? They're [ __ ] idiots.
[ __ ] idiots on here, bro. Oh, [ __ ] Yep.
N no no no no No, no, no.
Why don't you go to your Weather Spoons, Greavvesy? Oh. Oh gosh. You crazy.
Yeah. You think Do you live next to a
card factory, Grezy?
Yeah. Made me think of you cuz I know
you like your little stitch. I'm set.
Where's grand the month boy gone? Greavesy.
Where's that bloody grand the month boy gone?
He's done a runner, ain't he?
There's that grand boy by gun.
There's the skint virgin gone. Is he
that skint virgin can't [ __ ] avoid
afford Indian graves.
Calm down a bit, haven't I? Greavvesy,
I've calmed down a bit. Have you noticed that? Where Indian?
Can't see it.
Where is that [ __ ] skin virgin? Cool. Oh,
you should play some roulette, Grezy.
Why don't you play some roulette, Grezy?
You can play some lovely roulette.
to go a bit. I'm bloody tired.
I'm bloody tired. Greasy.
Oh, so tired. [snorts] Virgin boy.
skin in his little bed [ __ ] with no bed,
no money in it.
Do you like my amines? Greasy, do you
like my trainers?
You like them, Grezy? I'll be wearing
them again on Saturday.
and I go out for some drinks.
Is that okay with you, boss?
What? You don't like black jeans, Keezy?
Why bloody not?
What? You don't like I'm going to have a
tea in a minute. Yeah.
Why you don't like black jeans?
They cost me [ __ ] 200 quid. A
I like black jeans. I I only have two
jeans always. Black pair and a blue ripped pair. That's it.
I've got two I've got three trainers.
They're all black.
I am [ __ ] knacked, bro.
There's been no [ __ ] horrors in the cinema.
Did you see I lost 130 on the football grievy?
It's not that bad, is it?
Considering I'm still up a fuckload.
I'm still up a fuckload, is it? So,
it's not that bad.
Just that first is [ __ ] annoying, bro.
Don't forget, Greasy. Every time I go
out, I get an escort, don't I? So, so always
that's mad that I have to get an escort
every time I go out drinking.
Don't think I've never I've never not done it.
Crazy to be honest.
I'm a greedy geese.
What am I greasy? My little greedy goose. Oh, bless.
Yeah, I got my vitamins from the curry. Yeah. Hey,
you all right, Bob?
Oh, you like my little voice, don't you,
Greasy? No one could do it the same as
me, can they?
Yes, I did.
Yes, I [ __ ] did.
I know cuz I was out all [ __ ] day. I
think in the end I must have done about 100.
Yes, I did, bro.
And I got one number and one Snapchat.
I was [ __ ] by the end of it.
I'll be out again Saturday anyway. It's
just my sister.
No, it's not impossible.
Not in a place like London, mate. It
isn't impossible. How is it impossible?
It's a busy place. What? How is it impossible, bro?
It's not impossible at all.
It really really isn't impossible at
all. It's it's it's London. Why? Why
would it be impossible? Oh, [ __ ] So,
yeah, I got two escorts past two weeks.
Went out drinking. Yep.
Uh because I've been doing it for years.
Why wouldn't I manage it?
Do you know what I mean, Grezy? Why
wouldn't I bloody manage it? I've been
doing it for years.
It used to be about one in seven to be honest.
It used to be about one in seven,
one in eight. But yeah, it was really
bad. Really, really bad. And a lot of
them had really bad attitude problems as well. So
not starting it. It will never change
with it. So
yeah, get used to it or leave it. That's
But yeah, it's normally about 1 in 8.
I w going to stop until I got a number
sober. I got a number and a Snapchat.
And then the Snapchat come up with some
[ __ ] why she couldn't meet me.
So yeah, it will never change. So yeah.
Um because I'm used to it. It will never
change. That's why cuz when I got the 10
numbers and I didn't get a date, it
doesn't bother me anymore, bro. Because
it will never I know it will never change.
So there was there was no expectations
there. I just done it just to do it.
Because it will never change, bro.
That's that is it.
Nah, there's no point. There's no point,
bro. Because people just dismiss your
struggles. So, there's no point
because people are just going to dismiss it.
That's why I don't provide content like
that on this channel anymore.
I'll put like the restaurants up and
whatever, but I'm not.
No, I'm not doing it, bro. No. No.
Why am I going to do that? Record a
whole night out. That's ridiculous, bro. That's ridiculous.
I mean, it's a good idea. Yeah. I mean,
I guess I could do it once,
but people are just going to dismiss it anyways. So,
it's just bit pointless, isn't it? Yeah.
Yeah. I'll never change, will it?
I banged the escort as well, so I'm not
asked. Even though it's not the same.
I mean, what do you expect? What What do
you actually expect? It's going to
change. It will never change, bro. It
will never change.
So, I don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah. I came back from the dentist, then
I come back and I was like, let me get a
couple of hours sleep.
Um, even though I didn't manage to sleep
and then I just thought, [ __ ] it, is it?
I was out since 3:00 p.m.
and I come back at like 11. I like to be
in bed by like 11 or 12 nowadays. Yeah.
Don't know why that is, but I do. So,
um because I had nothing better to do.
So, I thought, why not?
I don't know, bro. Why not in it?
There was that one on Snapchat I was
speaking to and she come out with a
[ __ ] excuse why she couldn't meet
me. I met her in Oxford Circus. I just
deleted her, bro.
So, I'll be out Saturday cuz my sister
be playing this with my sister
and then Yeah. Yep.
It was all [ __ ] day, mate. It was all
[ __ ] day. And I tried to go back into that Simmons,
the other one, and there, oh, you can't
come in here. You're banned. They said,
"Oh, for for talking to people." I said,
"Oh, what?" So, a single person is not
allowed to uh speak to women to try to
get to know them. And then they're like,
"Oh, yeah, they I said they didn't
complain. No one complained about me.
I've never had someone ever complain
about me in my life unless I was arguing
with them." Um like, think of I've been
approaching for years, mate. Like, it's
in my DNA. So, stop lying. Stop talking
[ __ ] Cuz people don't just go and
complain to staff for no reason, bro.
unless you're having an argument with
them or you're abusing them. So I'm
thinking, well, what the [ __ ] has this
country come to? So you can't you can't
talk to people in a I quote socially acceptable place.
Strange, isn't it? So like it's a it's a
grocery store or whatever, but just just
England, is it, bro? You're used you're
just used to this [ __ ] now.
It will never change in it. So
yeah, they said that um they said that
basically um cuz I was like approaching
people in the in the club like in the
bar and that Yeah. They said that they
complained even though they didn't
complain. It was the staff that
complains. No one else complains but the
staff because it never happens. It will
never happen because I've done it in
Weather Spoons and people if you
approach people and they say no, they're
not just going to complain, bro, for no
reason. I was stood I was sat somewhere
I could see everyone. No one complained
about anyone, bro. You saw me do it and
then you didn't like it, so the staff
complained. That's exactly what happened.
Which doesn't make any sense cuz he's a
[ __ ] bore in the first place, but anyways. Um
yeah, it was that time of the Polish
bouncer. Do you remember?
Yeah, I know. And and and they didn't
complain either. None of the women
complained, trust me. Cuz it was about
6:00 7 in the evening. It was about 6:00
7 in the evening and no one complained
because when they said no, I just walked
away. So why would they complain to who?
I was I was watching the whole time.
Nobody complained, bro. And no one
argued. There was no argument. There was
nothing. So what what what they just complained really.
This it never happened. That's what I'm
saying. It never happened. Cuz don't
forget, I've been into a lot of places
like Weather Spoons and stuff. Um,
and I know why I got banned from that
weather spoons. Cuz I stuck it on some
guy and then he complained cuz I stuck
it on him. Yeah. Think of how many
people that I approached in these
Weather Spoons and I never got banned
for it. Never. So, you're making stuff
up. And as as the other one goes, right,
your staff are walking around with
attitude and all I said was they were
acting like a bit of a [ __ ] cuz they
were acting like a bit of a [ __ ]
That's not the worst thing to say. And
then you got banned for saying that
someone's acting like a bit of a [ __ ]
That was the other one. Yeah. But
because I said someone's acting like a
bit of a [ __ ] I got banned. This
country, bro, one day it will make
sense. It will make sense one day.
But yeah, they didn't they didn't
complain. It's the staff that um
it's the staff that complains. Trust
trust me and no one no one complain bro
stop lying I saw everything you know so yeah
that's that in it so yeah man
I'll be leaving soon anyways bro so I'm not bothered
I'm really really not bothered Um, [sighs] yeah. So, yeah,
it's like the O'Neils.
How long was I going in that O'Neals,
bro? Years. Years and years and years.
was approaching all the time, had
arguments, never got banned. Never ever
got banned fully. Like they never said,
"Oh, you can't." When I got banned for 3
months, that was because, what was it
again? It was something to do with the
bouncer trying to put his hands on me.
It was nothing to do with women. So, yeah,
they've got attitude problems, but a lot
of people uh in London, they they have
this attitude about them. I don't know
what it is. They seem to think they're
better than everyone.
Why? I don't know, bro.
I shall never know, but that's the way
it is. So,
yeah, I got seven numbers on uh Friday.
One replied and obviously the Snapchat replied.
So, I banned two escorts in two weeks.
So, it's probably why I don't care to be honest. Yeah,
sort of like that.
That football bet [ __ ] lost. But
doesn't matter where I'm up anyways. So
last two times I put 120 on the football at one
that Tuesday with the [ __ ] um finish [ __ ]
Won that 380 then 360 and then so it was
annoying when it lost but at the start
it was annoying bro.
But yeah it's not that bad.
I just thought that if I didn't gamble then
I wouldn't have as much as I do now and
I wouldn't have been able to like buy
the gums and [ __ ] Well, I would but
like I wouldn't have as much money. So,
what's there really to complain about in it? So,
it's what it is.
Yeah, it's [ __ ]
Did you hear about that one from
Amsterdam? She was a [ __ ]
Oh, I can't I can't be bothered. Oh, I
can't exchange numbers because I've got
a boyfriend. Oh, do you really? See,
we're so full of [ __ ] mate.
Oh, cuz I've got a boyfriend. Oh my god,
bro. That gets so boring, bro.
Seriously, it gets so boring, hearing that.
Yeah, bro. I walked all around central
London and if I like the look of
someone, I just went and approached them. Yeah. Yeah.
They were even not they were either like
they either had attitude problems or
just walked away or they spoke as they
were walking away. Um,
it was just a similar sort of thing.
I've noticed them Dutch [ __ ] lie about
having a boyfriend as well. That's
that's become a thing, which is a shame
cuz Dutch people used to I really used
to like Dutch people, but they they've
become [ __ ] now as well with the
boyfriend [ __ ] That's happened a few times actually.
Something happened last month as well.
They're getting a bit [ __ ]
as well to be fair.
And they're so full of [ __ ] as well.
It's not like they generally have boyfriends.
It is. They're generally just so full of [ __ ]
Um but when they say it,
um yeah, the one I got a Snapchat from,
I had a kind of a long combo.
Uh there was one from Greece.
They seemed all right and they said they
were visiting and they said that they
come here with their boyfriend. I
believe they they actually did have a
boyfriend though. But the rest of them
are full of [ __ ] Like you can tell like
when when when someone's just completely
full of [ __ ] Trust me, bro. Trust me.
If someone generally had a boyfriend,
they're just walking away, bro.
They would just walk If someone actually
had a boyfriend, they would just walk away.
Um, straight bro. Like that's it.
The ones that get in combo and then
start saying it, they're they're
chatting [ __ ] bro. Trust me, they are
chatting [ __ ] Cuz you wouldn't
entertain another man if you had a boyfriend.
You wouldn't even be polite. You would
just walk off. So they're full of [ __ ] bro.
Mate, I It could have been a thousand
approaches. I weren't giving up, bro.
[ __ ] that. I was in it too deep.
That'll show me how it's done. No
thanks, mate. If I can't [ __ ] pull, I
doubt they're going to [ __ ] pull. You know,
you know what I mean? So, yeah.
No, I weren't going to stop, bro.
I was only thinking it was going to take
eight to 10 approaches. Ah, it took [ __ ] hours.
But remember, all women are different.
Bob says the all pink virgin, right?
Well, they say a lot of the same things
for people that are different.
I'll tell you that much.
They have a lot of the same mannerisms
and they act the same way for people
that are different. Let me tell you that, mate.
It's strange how so many different
people act the same, huh?
Would you would you calculate the odds
of that for me, please, boss?
So, who's um who's sick then, Bob?
Who's sick in USA? busy.
Well, yeah, it was either that or [ __ ]
Well, I'll be out with my sister
Saturday, so I'll be doing some
approaches then as well. But we're
staying local cuz uh
we're staying local because
she wants to stay local. I'm not used to
local. I always go far out. But good
thing is it won't be as expensive. Yay.
If you go, if you go to like a pub
outside of like central London, you're
only paying £3 something for a Guinness.
So, you can get wrecked with like less than 20.
So, you probably spend about
you probably spend about 30 40 50
Yeah, about 30 40 50.
No, they were all the only the only ones
that kind of act slightly different are
like Indian ones
or something. They're the only ones that
don't really have an attitude.
But yeah, that Snapchat one come. She
said, "Oh, you're a sweet guy. Thanks
for approaching me and talking to me and
stuff, but I'm not looking to meet new
people and stuff." So,
that doesn't make any sense then because
they're moaning about all men being the
same and [ __ ] yet they have
somebody come along that actually
approaches them. So, they don't even
need to put any effort, but then they're
not interested. So I'm like, "What the
[ __ ] We have to go looking for people
to find people.
Yeah, I'm a virgin apparently." Yeah.
You know, everything that he says is about himself.
Virgin skin. That's all him.
That's him, bro. His disability gets um
himself confused with me.
Mr. Grand the month boy.
Yeah, he [ __ ] he's he's a
he's a disability gets him gets himself
confused with me.
He's the biggest virgin [ __ ] going.
But yeah, anyways, uh we have to go out
and and approach women to see um their
that they to try and find someone that's
different, but then when they come
across someone that's different, they're
not interested. So, I don't understand
why they complain. I don't understand
why they moan.
I really don't understand why they why
they moan and winge
to be honest because they've had chances
ample full of chances, you know.
Yeah, that's the only way I could I I I
could see why someone would do it cuz
for sex it's not worth it. I would just
use an escort. Yeah, okay. It might not
be the same or whatever, you know, or
you go to Thailand, whatever. But I
mean, that's the only way I could see
why someone would put themsel through
that [ __ ] every day, you know?
It is. It is. It's like you're
disrespecting yourself cuz they're not
even like they're not even nice about it.
They lead people on, they play games,
they're full of [ __ ] You know what I
mean? It's not like they're um they're
even normal about it.
That's the thing about it, bro. It's [ __ ] madness.
And there's some people Yeah, that's all
they say. Yeah.
Like even Ant-Man's friend, the
good-looking one, he's in Thailand now.
He's not coming back.
That is actually mad when someone like
that is is actually doing that as well.
The one that annoyed me was that Dutch
one cuz he's so full of [ __ ]
Like it's just [ __ ] It's [ __ ]
bro. That's the one that sticks to mind.
That one is just [ __ ] bro. You know
about, oh, if you see me later, you see
me, we can have a drink. A drink with
me. But you got a boyfriend apparently.
Yeah, [ __ ] Oh, I also went to Waxies
as well, Bob.
I also went to waxies as well. And I
think I got I got a boyfriend about five times.
I think it was about Oh, it was a lot,
bro. It was to be fair. It was a lot to
Yeah, it did happen a lot. I don't know
why they even go out if they're just
going to tell everyone they've got boyfriends
because you see the thing is you see
other people do it as well. You see
other people approach the same women and
then you're thinking to yourself, "Oh yeah,
uh oh yeah, you're obviously it's the
way that I look in it." Yeah. Yeah.
They're going to give the other guy a
chance. No, they get the same [ __ ] as
well. So they go out, spend money. Bear
in mind there's a cost of living crisis
as well. So they're prepared to go out
and spend money just to tell everyone
that they've got boyfriends.
That's just [ __ ] mad to me, bro. Why?
Why people would actually Well, the ones
that are from different countries,
right? Okay, maybe that's a bit
different if they're visiting. Maybe
they don't care what money they're
spending their tourists. But I mean,
people from this actual country, bro,
most of these most people in this
country are [ __ ] skint. So, they will
go out, spend their spend their own money
just to tell everyone that they've got
boyfriends. It's [ __ ] mad. Like, do
you do you see how many people go up to
the same woman? It it's quite a few and
they get the same [ __ ] and I'm thinking,
"What the [ __ ] bro?"
But it might get a bit delayed and then
Yeah, it's just It is weird. It is. It
I would never go out drinking in central
London if I couldn't meet new people.
That don't even make sense, bro.
Yeah, I know, bro.
It's very sad.
That USA easy thing was once in a lifetime, Bob.
That was once in a lifetime. Definitely
And she turned out to be a [ __ ] as well.
But yeah, that was that was definitely
once in a lifetime. You know,
winter's right around the corner.
It's already win. It's already winter, matey.
Yeah, we still got until uh
we still got a hold of November. We
still got a hold of December. And then
we're [ __ ] until March. Basically,
we're [ __ ] until March then. Yeah.
After well, midFebruary really. But I
won't go out from uh
I don't go out. I try to not go out
until January until March. But normally it's midFeb.
MidFeb you can go out. But yeah, no one
will be out until midFeb after that. You
got this month and you got next month.
I'm not going out every week, so Yep. Yeah.
I don't even know. I don't even know
what you can do in this country, bro. I
really don't even know what you can actually do.
So, I take it you watch my dating video then. Yeah.
Thank you, boss. Yeah.
But yeah, that Orington can't cause me a
virgin cuz he's a big He's a big virgin
himself. The biggest virgin going.
He's also skint as well. He needs to
stop throwing daddy's savings. It's
getting embarrassing at this point.
I can't believe that football bet lost,
man. [ __ ] sake.
I've had some good wins. So,
so yeah, I'll stay local with my sister,
see what the score is, and then maybe go
out the week after that
cuz obviously I'm getting my hair done
so I don't know what I'm doing.
But there's no point putting £500 on a
football bet, bro, because you're
basically capping your potential. Cuz if
you put £500 on roulette and online, you
could win a lot more, bro. A lot more.
Yeah. See me, I was like, at first I was
like, "Oh, yeah, it might be nice to
have someone and whatever, but it's not
worth it if you have to go through that [ __ ]
It ain't worth it.
Yeah, I've never I've never wanted to
have a baby. I just wanted to get
someone pregnant for a laugh just as a
joke. But I don't actually want a [ __ ] baby.
Have I ever been on busy public
transport brush up against potties?
Why are you even asking that, bro?
That's just weird.
What a weird question to ask.
But um yeah, but it's not worth, like I
was saying in the video, it's not worth
putting yourself through that just to
find someone. It's just not worth it.
No, I don't. No, I [ __ ] don't.
No, I bloody don't, matey.
No, baby. No.
No. I'm being serious. I actually don't, bro.
You know, cuz I need to do stuff. I need
to start traveling and [ __ ] soon. So,
no, I really, really don't. It would
[ __ ] my life up.
No, I really, really don't, bro. You
know how many celebrities don't have
children? A lot of celebrities don't
have kids, you know? A lot of them
don't. A lot a lot a lot of them don't, bro.
because obviously their career and [ __ ]
So obviously if you want to do the [ __ ]
I do, you can't. So that's that.
>> It's not even affordability. It's uh Yeah.
No, they haven't.
A lot of people don't have kids, do they?
I guess I guess I could try and get Sig
back in it, Bob. I could probably find
her. I could probably find her number somewhere. Bob
Yeah. Yeah. But a lot of them don't have kids.
But that's what I'm saying. A lot of
them. Yeah. They might be married, but a
lot of them don't have kids.
A lot of them. Not most of them, but a
lot of them don't.
I can name you a lot of people that
don't have kids. Baby Peter.
But if I spun up sick a couple of more
times, Bob, there would be a baby Peter, wouldn't there?
I was watching this Alice in Wonderland porn, bro.
Yeah, I was watching some porn, bro.
some vintage porn from the 70s.
Yeah, I like vintage porn. Uh
yeah, I'd call it
baby Peter the third Bob. Yeah.
So, what if you go on So, what if you
use dating apps then, Bob?
You could uh You could use dating apps, couldn't you?
could use dating apps now. Huh?
People on Reddit tell me to use dating apps.
Yeah. Updated apps.
You know when Ant-Man said, "Yeah,
they're not interested in this country."
He's just chatting [ __ ] in it.
You think he's just trying to demotivate
me or something?
You think he's just lying?
Try dating apps. Yeah, I've tried dating
What does that mean, self?
What does that mean?
You told me that they're not interested
in this country.
You tell me that women aren't interested
in this country,
Bob. Don't know why he says that.
He's just negative, is he?
He's just negative, Nancy. Yeah.
I mean, of course they're interested in this country.
Why wouldn't they be interested in this country?
Like, look what happens when you go out,
bro. What could possibly think that?
What would what could possibly make you
think that they're not interested? You know,
he's so negative, isn't he? I mean, you
get like a date every week, you know,
like they never say they've got
boyfriends. They never say they're not
interested. You don't go out on a
weekend spending £600 and getting
nothing. Like, I don't know what the
guy's talking about really.
It's just negative, you know?
really really negative.
I get a date every week. Me? Yeah.
Yeah, exactly. And they even say that
I'm nice as well. That one on Snapchat
even said that, "Oh, I'm a nice guy and
um thanks for coming over and speaking
to me. You seem sweet." So, you would
have thought that's everything they
would want in a man.
You would think that that's everything
that they would want. No,
you would have thought that's everything
that they would have wanted. Bob,
think about it. It's everything you
would have wanted,
you know, and a woman. So why? Yeah.
Trying to tell me I look good, bro. Are
you [ __ ] a homo or something? Are you a homer?
Yeah. What reason do they to not? Yeah.
They don't really have no reason.
But then if you say something like that,
people tell you people don't know you anything.
So it's just Yeah.
How could he have the women to himself
when he doesn't even live in this country?
Have the women to himself? He doesn't
even live in this country anymore.
He lives in Thailand. Why?
Why? Why would he want the women all to himself
when he doesn't even live here?
He left to get away from this [ __ ] He
lives in Thailand now to get away from this [ __ ] You know,
you don't live here, bro. He's never
coming back here.
Nah, I watch him on Snapchat.
Nope. I watch him on Snapchat. His best
his friends lived his friend lives there
now as well. Andy the pretty boy. We
call him the pretty boy.
Yep. Even he's even he's left.
No, I watch him on Snapchat, bro. He
doesn't he doesn't ever come back.
These benefits have been stopped.
So if you come back, you you have to
start everything all over again.
It's madness, isn't it?
What I said to this woman, yeah,
on Snapchat that that was all right at
first, then she started ignoring me. Then So
I said, "So if you keep ignoring me, I'm
going to spam your page."
ignored me and then deleted her picture.
The only picture she had. Um and then
um I said if you if you and I said if
you don't stop I'm going to message all
your friends. She soon blocked me then.
They're so narcissistic. They're such
[ __ ] bro. It
one in South America was a proper proper [ __ ]
Who gets 400 quid a month? Who gets £400
a month, bro?
What the [ __ ]
400 quid a month. Who gets 400 quid a
month? Where did you Where have you come?
I might never got 400 quid a month.
I haven't lived off a grand a month for
a little while to be honest cuz I've had
them wins in it.
So I can do what I want when I want
really. And man didn't get £400 a month.
He got like grand and a half.
Do you remember phrase Bob? Good old phrase. Yep.
These people on here think everyone's
got their life.
People on here think everyone's got
their life. Bob skinned. Can't afford to go out.
They think everyone's got the same life
as them. Oh, you're so skinn you can't
buy trainers. Bought the trainers. Uh,
did you like that one, Bob? I thought,
"Fuck it. I just buy the trainers, mate."
You know what I'm like? I'm a [ __ ] like
that. Oh, no.
Yep. He's gone, bro.
400 quid a month.
That's what Virgin Boy was trying to
say. I got £400 from UC. I thought, what
the [ __ ] News to me.
I didn't know I got £500 from UC.
You learn something new every day, don't you, Bob?
These people are projectors on here, bro.
You like my Ammani jeans, Bob?
200 lust jeans?
I saw your comment about500 pound on the
football, but there's no point doing
that, bro. If you're putting 500 pound,
you might as well put it [ __ ] on roulette because
it's too much to put on a If you put 500
on roulette, you could win like 10 grand.
There's no point putting I don't think
I'd put more than 130 on it. And yeah,
it might not be a big amount to win, but
that's why you try to win them every week.
There's no point, bro, because it's
with roulette, you got multiple chances
if you miss, whereas with the football, you're
not like Yeah,
you can win. Look, I put £100 on. I won
550 on the roulette. I think it was last month. Yeah,
I lost one last week. 130 quid cuz of
[ __ ] slow man. [ __ ] bastards.
Yeah, I was looking forward to that
[ __ ] free [ __ ] 70.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ]
But 70 chart. Yeah. On on the National
League. Yeah. But not the League One, League Two.
Yeah. Depends on the league, isn't it?
Not normal leagues though. They're hard,
bro. League One, League Two, they're hard. Yep.
You bet on the football every week or what?
I've won a couple of them both teams to
score, bro. A couple of them.
I've done good on the football really.
If they were playing home, I think it
would have won if SL was playing home in it.
I'm sure if you put five 600 pound on
roulette, you've got a good chance of winning. No,
I'm sure you have some. Yeah.
my I got both teams to score on the
first [ __ ] half the week before that, didn't I?
Yeah, I know, mate. I wish I had a both
score no draw the week before. It was a
both score no draw as well. Bastards, bro. Bastards. [ __ ] bastards.
Yeah, it would have been like a thousand I think.
Imagine having a five.
Imagine having um
imagine five imagine putting five 600
pound on both score no draw. Winning it
twice in a row in a week. Woo.
be lovely in it.
Imagine getting that mate.
Yeah, it be a love it would be a lovely site.
That Indian was lovely. up. Yep.
But I'd rather just put it on roulette, bro.
You could easily turn 500 on into free
grand on roulette. I'm sure you could. You know
what? What would you do if you had 600
pound to your name and you needed to win
more money? Would you put it on a both
teams to score? Both score no draw. Pull
it on the roulette.
I think it'd have to be the roulette in it, you know.
It has to be in it.
No, I don't.
What do you think, Bob?
It have to be roulette it.
[snorts] It's like if you put 80 pound
on a both score no draw that's like 600.
Yeah. But the roulette, you can win
[ __ ] thousands if you was to put that
kind of money on it. Ain't it?
Yeah. But it's not safer though because
if one team don't score, you're [ __ ]
I wish that [ __ ] bet won last [ __ ]
Saturday, man. What the [ __ ] bro?
Didn't score the [ __ ] [ __ ] me, man.
But if you put 80 pound on Yeah. both
score a no draw. That's like 6700 pound
which is quite a good return isn't it?
It's happened a couple of times where
it's been a both score, no draw, and
I've only done it. Both teams score.
Yeah, that's the thing, is it? But I put
£100 in last month. I got it to over
500. I took it.
I was happy, bro. Yeah.
It's a losing number seeker in it, Bob.
Poor little house edge. Gets the blame
for [ __ ] everything, don't he?
It's only 2.7.
Do you reckon you can still win? Do you
reckon you could still
Yeah, I think so, Bob.
I think so. Yeah.
Do you think you could still win big
money on roulette online though?
I think I'm going to do a four. Both
score no draw on Saturday. I'm going to
put a tener on it.
Or maybe three teams. Five score. No draw.
It always attacks that [ __ ] zero section, bro.
It's annoying as [ __ ] is it?
That is annoying, bro. when it used to do that.
Your [snorts] only option is either the
football or online roulette because you
can't win big on [ __ ] slots. Cranky
and [ __ ] Not really. No.
Imagine you done a£500 both teams to
score every week for three weeks, bro.
And you won. Like say you was just
traveling, approaching and you kept winning.
[ __ ] hell. Imagine that, bro. That
would be mad, isn't it?
You'd be [ __ ] minted, it
would be [ __ ] minted, bro.
I used to do that when I used to travel.
I used to like do football bets and I
used to like collect him in the city
that I was in.
I remember I went Manchester Mother's
Day uh day before Mother's Day. I won a football bet. Uh Yeah.
Who's that guy from Indonesia, Bob?
Who's that guy from [ __ ] Indonesia?
Yeah. They tell me that you you never
know. They say you can't predict the future.
Yeah. They say that you can't predict the future. Yep.
They tell me that my time will come. Bob,
why do the virgins say that if I don't
find Shel Co attractive, I'm gay? I'm not gay.
I like boobs and vaginas and stuff.
Why would I be gay, bro? What the [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm excited. Candy man, did you
see my Indian video?
We were just talking about gambling.
Why would I be gay? Cuz I don't find
Cheryl Co attractive. Why would I find
her attractive? She hasn't even got any boobies.
She ain't attractive. [ __ ] virgin.
Why does he call me skin? I'm not skin. Bob,
why does bomb and virgin call me skin?
Well, they're both virgins. Um, yeah.
No, she's definitely not attractive.
Definitely. Definitely not. I think
she's [ __ ] ugly.
No, I don't think she's attractive at all. Me?
Not my type. Definitely not my type.
Yeah, definitely. Yeah, he's a little
copycat. He's a little copycat.
You little copycat. Little copycat, are
you? Nah, she's definitely not attractive.
Only people that copy people. Well,
she's overrated. That's it. That they
they all copy each other.
She was also mentioned uh on the
Inbetween Users as well. If you ever
watch the Inbetween Users Yeah.
Why am I going to go meet him, bro? The [ __ ]
It's never going to be any different with women.
Why do you think I'm not pissed off
about it anymore? Cuz I know it will
never change and I'm leaving. So,
yeah. I don't know. I don't know why
they say that. I just I put it like
this, Bob. Yeah.
Is if you was really going to meet
someone, you would have already met someone.
Laney says that I've been too greedy
with going out lately. She says, "You
need to stop. You're getting too greedy." Um
because if it was going to change, it
would have changed by now, obviously. Is
it? So, you theoretically you got more
chance of winning the lottery.
than finding someone.
Theoretically, you've got more chance
because if it hasn't happened now, then
the chances are it's very unlikely that
it's going to happen. That's just common
sense, though, is it? Like, it's
what would make the next time so
different? I go out
cuz there's nothing else to do. So, I
mean, I'm not just going to sit in and do nothing
cuz my sleeping pattern's fixed now
cuz uh my sleeping patterns fixed. So,
now I have somewhat of a life now. So,
yeah, it's um
Yeah, that's it. Yeah. Mhm.
They dismiss my struggles, Bob. They
dismiss my struggles.
People said that I should be like um
I should be like Ed Matthews. I watch He
comes. He comes up sometimes, Ed Matthews,
but his content is similar to my content basically.
I think he went to Liverpool. Yeah.
Yeah. East content is similar to mine.
Well, I've only been to Liverpool once.
Do you remember when I went to Liverpool, Bob? Yeah.
Yeah. It's cuz he's got lots of followers.
It's because he's got lots of followers. That's why.
No, he's got lots of followers, bro. That's why.
And he's a [ __ ]
People on Reddit say go on dating apps
to get sex.
Yeah, I saw it, bro. I saw it.
But if that guy didn't have followers,
he wouldn't get he wouldn't get anyone.
He'd be the same as me, bro. It's just
cuz he's got followers.
Yeah, I see him, bro. He's uh
But if he didn't have followers, he
wouldn't get that.
I've only been Liverpool once and
they're stuck up, bro. Liverpool,
they're stuck up as well. Yeah,
I've only been once. It was a few years ago.
Yep. But their girlfriends are not even
all that though, to be honest with you.
I've I've been I've been with better
women than some of their girlfriends.
Like that [ __ ] Talia. She ain't that good-look.
And that Ethan's girlfriend. They're not
even all that, bro. Really?
Their girlfriends are like average, bro.
They're not even like all that. You
would have thought like for millionaires
they would have a lot better.
They're not even I I've had better women
than them, bro.
That's how weird it is. That's how mad
it is. [ __ ]
Talia. She ain't that good looking, bro.
She's like a
Yeah, she's like average. Yeah.
Yeah, I deleted the videos of the
bouncer, Bob, because they made they
made excuses. LT was making excuses cuz
the guy was black in it. It's pathetic,
really. I stuck it on him.
I stuck it on [ __ ] two other [ __ ] guys
and they're just full of excuses.
I thought I hit that all, bro.
Do you know who Johnny Sins is, Bob?
Yeah. Do you know who Johnny Sins is?
I couldn't win that football bet last
Saturday, bro. It would have been too easy.
Yeah. I can't watch Johnny Sins. I can't
watch that kind of porn. It looks too
fake. Obviously, it's all fake, but I
can't I have It has to be like old
school vintage story, otherwise I can't watch it.
I was watching some British one where
this woman was getting [ __ ] and it was
from the 70s.
I can't watch anything like Johnny Sins
and that, bro. It's too It looks too fake.
So, it's like it's just a turn off.
Yeah, I can't watch I can't watch that [ __ ] bro.
Well, I do get laid. I get laid by
escorts. I've had two in the past two weeks.
I came in one as well.
It's because I' I've banged a couple of
escorts, bro, the past two weeks. So,
I'm not [ __ ] you know what I mean?
That's why, bro. I mean, obviously,
again, it's not exactly the same, but
it's um it's better than nothing. So,
thinking of porn stars, they do it for
the money. So, that's probably why I'm
not asked because I've [ __ ] quite a
bit recently. Well, two weeks ago, I got
a [ __ ] came in her mouth. Last week,
I just got a [ __ ] and [ __ ] the [ __ ]
out of her. So,
I've been all right. It's calmed me down
for a little bit, bro.
So, that's probably why
every time I go on a night out, I always
get an escort at the end. I never not I
never don't get an escort.
Nah, it's not the same thing, bro.
It isn't the same thing because I
remember when I used to get mood swings.
Yeah. I used to get mood swings,
right? Really bad mood swings. And even
if I'd wank, it would it would go it
wouldn't go away.
And then when I'd had sex, when I have
sex, I'd be good for like 2 weeks. Then
it would go for like two weeks. So yeah,
good luck getting a girlfriend. And you
can't even get a conversation out of the [ __ ]
Good luck getting a girlfriend, bro.
You can't even get a bloody date. I'm at
24 numbers now the past 3 weeks and
still no date.
Still no date. Bob. Yep.
Still no date, lad.
But people on Reddit say I'll meet someone.
Still no date, baby.
probably. Yeah, probably.
Probably about that. Yeah.
And then even if you get a date, they're
just going to waste your time anyway, isn't it?
So, I don't know why people make out
that getting laid is easy.
They must be lying in it, Bob.
You need to use an escort. If you don't
use an escort, you're [ __ ] You need
an escort to keep stable. If you don't
have that option of an escort, you're
[ __ ] It doesn't matter that you need to pay.
It don't matter that you need to pay. I
mean, it's it's not the same thing, but
it can at least keep you sane.
It it's better than nothing. It is a lot
when you find a decent one. And if you
couldn't if you can't find one, then you
know it's bad, bro. At least once a month. Oh [ __ ]
that Indian was large.
Yeah, I went to a dentist and I got a
fill in. up. Yeah.
Who's Tam, Bob?
Some guy called Tam.
Who's that? Tam.
Yeah, it feels better now since I've had
that fill in.
Yeah, the dentist reminded me of uh he
reminded me of Q a bit. You know Q, that
black guy that I met? The dentist
reminded me of him a bit. He was black and westernized.
Yeah, obviously that's why they gave me a filling.
But they need to give me a filling on
another one. I'm going back there in two
weeks. So, I'm going to bring it up.
I actually did tip. I tipped him two pound.
Yeah, I need to get another one.
I did tip. I actually did tip today. I
tipped him two pound
cuz he said he gave the drink on the
house. I said, "Okay." The lamb was That
curry was so nice, bro. Oh my god. The
lamb. Yeah. Was so succulent.
I don't know.
And man said that he almost shot his
underpants. I was dead, bro. Who still
calls it an Who still calls it
underpants? I've got Chucky boxes, Bob.
Do you like my little Chucky boxes?
It was very, very nice that lamb, bro.
It was very, very succulent.
Oh, you like the look of the chicken, did you?
What? And record it in it. and record
it. Hey, Bob. Oh, man.
So, when am I going to find a woman then anyways, Bob? Huh? Never.
Yeah. I'm going to go out in Romford on
Saturday with my um sister.
Do you reckon I'll get any numbers? Cuz
I never normally go out in Roford, Bob.
I normally go central London, but she
wants to stay local. So,
you reckon I I'll get any numbers there or
should do. Yeah.
How many though? I don't know.
I ain't been out there in like [ __ ]
two and a half years, bro.
I go there all the time. I'm not
drinking. I always go central when I
drink, don't I? Yep. Interested, Bob?
I'm sick of it. Yep. Madness.
So, when do you reckon I'll get laid?
When do you reckon I'll get laid
normally then, Bob?
Yeah, they literally just they they do
dismiss your struggles.
That's what they do. They actually dismiss it. They do.
See, it feels like they do. Yeah. Uh £33.
Well, £31. Well, £3350. It was £3150,
but I gave the guy a two pound tip.
So, Liverpool Street is not a bad spot
to drink, you know, cuz you got loads of restaurants.
Loads of uh you got loads of restaurants and
you've got loads of restaurants.
Very very unlikely, bro. Very unlikely.
It's very unlikely you're going to meet
someone here, bro. You got more chance
of winning the lottery. Seriously,
that food was yummy, bro. That food was
That food was yummy, bro. It was worth every penny.
I love Indian food. So
I always go Brick Lane. That's where the
best Indians are in it.
So what happened to Sig then, Bob?
I don't even know how I've got laid in
the past to be honest.
It's mad, eh?
Yeah. Sick in it, bro. It's sick. Yeah.
It's It's good, bro. Um, no.
Nah, bro. Nah.
You remember the alleyway [ __ ] Bob.
Bob, I really want you, but I don't
think you want me.
I really want you. I wonder how that
John's doing. I ain't spoke to him in years, man.
I met up with him once and we went approaching.
Oh, have I got a lot to tell him.
He never ever got back in touch with me, did he?
I wonder what happened to him if he
still approaches or Yeah, I remember I
went out with him. We was doing it together.
Do you remember him?
I'm not sure, bro.
She gave me a [ __ ] the other one.
I was sucking her boobies.
But a lot of the time I couldn't come
because where I'd masturbated so much
and I never thought I was going to get laid.
I couldn't, you know what I mean? It
happened quite a few times.
It's not even about getting laid. I
mean, you can't even get a [ __ ] date.
[clears throat] For [ __ ] sake,
you can't even get a date that makes you
wait for sex. It's not even just all
about that, bro. Cuz you can meet one
person, they make you wait like 3 weeks,
then you can meet someone else. But you
don't even get given a chance.
You don't even get given a [ __ ]
chance. That's what I'm trying to say. So
There's [ __ ] in it.
No, it was it was not last October. It
was the October before that. I got laid
on my birthday.
Yeah, I got laid on my birthday.
It was a Saturday. It weren't last
birthday. It was the It was the birthday before that.
And Sig was before that. Yeah.
Do you remember USA is Bob? I don't know
how I approached someone and they
offered me their number and messaged me first.
How cute is that?
So, it's okay for her to want to meet me
straight away, but if you try to if you
speak to a woman and you try to meet
them within a week, Bob, you're moving
too fast. You're being desperate. Oh,
really? It's okay for them to [ __ ]
message me the first message wanting to
meet me, isn't it?
Bloody double standards.
No, I never.
No, I didn't.
Argument video guy. No, I haven't.
Yeah, that's one in a million, bro.
Getting someone offering you their
number, then messaging you like that is
that is never happening again, bro. Nope.
No, I didn't. The 19year-old wasn't from
there. She was just before that,
dude. I can't even remember saying that.
Steven Howard, do you reckon that man's
telling the truth though when he says
that they're not interested in this country?
>> You think Antman's lying or telling the
truth? I think he's telling the truth in it.
These be Hey, bro. Last time I went out
Yeah. these Belgian [ __ ] were laughing
at us, mate.
I'm sure these Belgian [ __ ] were
laughing at us.
Yeah. Yeah. When I see like babies on
the train and that in it with their mama
taking a baby away from its mama. I
don't know why I said that, bro.
I don't even know why I said that.
I think it was because the boobies in it, you know. [laughter]
No, like when I see like a baby on like
the train or something, it makes me
laugh, isn't it? You know,
Peter Belly can't get attached anymore
because he already found his mama.
I said to LT, "Why do these people on
YouTube mock me?" He said, "Because you
bought it on yourself coming on here
with them sayings and that in it." He
said, "You pulled on you pulled it on
yourself in it. [snorts] Mad. Yeah,
I'll light up your battleship.
That was jokes. But I still remember that.
No. Do you know what made me laugh with
him? Yeah. When he done that video to
Bomb when he says this little prick from
Lancaster, I was dead, bro. I was dead. Yeah.
What what does April mean to me, Bob?
What does April mean to me? It's not a
special month, is it? April. The 11th of
Yeah. That's funny. Then [laughter]
yeah, April 11th doesn't mean anything, does it? [laughter] No. >> [laughter] >> Yeah. Heat.
Yeah, time goes so quickly, isn't it?
So why did she abandon me anyways? Bob,
I actually met her on her birthday, but
she never told me it was her birthday.
But it was actually her birthday, but
she never told me that.
Yeah, she didn't tell me that.
Yeah, that was nasty. there.
So, how do you know that she was my mom then?
What's the evidence that she's my mom?
That how do you know that she's my mom? H
What? She actually looks like me. Do you think that?
What? My mama.
Oh, that's cute, isn't it? [laughter]
Do you remember when I was messing
Damon? Why did you and mommy split up? Yeah.
Yeah. That's cute, isn't it?
So, why did my mom have sex with me? Why
did my mommy want to have sex with me?
That's a bit weird, isn't it, Bob?
Maybe she then realized that she was my
mom and that's why she ghosted Bob.
Maybe that's why then she she she tried
putting the blame on to me in it.
So, she put me up for adoption and then
she come across me again and then she
didn't realize that and then she found
out that it was she was my mama and
that's why she ghosted
to not feel disgusted with herself. Ah,
now I know why. That makes sense, isn't it? Yeah.
cuz she don't want to admit that she had
sex with her child, is it?
Oh, yes, please, Captain. >> Yeah.
So, who the [ __ ] is Laney then? Isn't
Laney supposed to be my mom?
Isn't Laney is supposed to be my mom? Oh,
so what? Was I born in America then? And
then I So how did I end up here? Yeah.
So what? Was I born in America?
Do you know my niece? I make up a story
um about her. I say that you don't know
the story about how you was born. You
was you was actually born in Darlington
and then you came from Darlington.
You got uh deported from Darlington to here.
[snorts] Yep. That's how you was made.
That's what I tell her.
You actually come from Darlington.
Yeah, but how can I be Yeah, but I'm not
American. I'm English. Ah,
so who was is so who was Isabelli then
Bob? Who was Isabelli?
So who was Isabelli?
Yeah, I always say to lady that you got
the wrong baby cuz uh I don't look
anything like you and I don't look
anything like my dead dad. So So
why was she a meanie? [laughter]
and mainly how
What's your favorite month? Mine's October.
Yep. You USA gave me vitamins.
She gave me vitamins. Yep.
That coffee was lost, bro.
That was lush.
So nice, bro. So nice. [snorts]
I found USA Izzy's YouTube. Do you
remember that, Bob?
That was cute, isn't it?
I don't like Joseph Ferrar, Bob. He has
favorites. When I call uh virgin boy a
virgin, Joseph Farrar comes to his
defense saying, "How can he be a virgin?
He's got a girlfriend."
But when nonsense goes for me, Joseph
Far's nowhere to be seen. Talking about
the porno and how I proved I've had sex
and how I put a video up and getting my dick sucked.
Joseph for nowhere to be seen when he's
slated me off. Have you noticed that, Bob? Stranger.
I ate the [ __ ] lot, mate. The [ __ ] lot.
It was delicious. Mhm. A a
she would have been such a little cutie
if she wasn't so rude
and stuck up. Bob, there's no way you're
still messaging me. What do you mean, mama? You disappeared.
Of course I'm messaging you, mama. You've disappeared.
What the [ __ ]
We can't go separate ways, mama.
They haven't cut they bit called off yet.
You nasty bastard.
Her friend, bro, was making me want to
go there, bro. I swear down her friend
when she was like, "Oh, you don't you
don't want to do that? I was going to
get seven people to to do you in and
shit." I was like, "Oh, yeah. Yeah. Is
that Is that what you're really saying,
bro? I'm not scared of you or no [ __ ]
seven people, bro.
That's mad. I could have ended up in
death in it.
You think it's funny, is it?" Nah. No. Nah,
[ __ ] you and your seven people, but I
would have shot every single one of them.
How do I get into these situations, bro?
Yeah. Now I want more.
Yeah. I said to her, um,
she kissed me and she said I'd be her
25th and stuff.
She's like, "Oh, she did that?" I was like, "Yep." Yeah.
Yeah, she said. Yeah, I said she [ __ ] did. Yeah, dirty [ __ ] Yep.
I was watching Undertaker Royal Rumble
yesterday in 1997. Bob, it was be I was
born in 1997. [laughter]
How cute is that? I was still in the tummy.
I was still in the tummy when that was made.
Yep. On my birthday,
I kept betting on the number 25. >> [snorts]
>> Do you remember that Indian that I met
on my birthday when I won when I kept
putting money on 25? I met her well the
day before my birthday. I met her
the day before my birthday and uh she
ghosted me. I never heard from her ever again. H Strange. Yeah.
Nah, that was a different one, bro. That
was a different one. Yeah.
I can't believe when Undertaker was in
WWE, I was I wasn't even born.
That's mad, isn't it?
That's [ __ ] mad, bro.
And I was still a baba
and some of them I weren't even born. Um,
I haven't really watched many of them. I
might have to.
The kids nowadays will never know what
WWE was like when we was a kid. I still
watch it, you know, like the old ones,
old old ones when I'm bored.
Like Mark Henry, you know, Big Show and
that these kids will never know what it
was once like.
Royal Rumble is the is the best though. [snorts] Yeah,
I like John Cena, but his finisher is so [ __ ]
I like the rock bottom. I like the stone
cold stunner. I like the pile driver as well.
John Cena's finisher is so [ __ ]
Like if someone done that to someone,
bro, it wouldn't even do anything to them.
He's a good wrestler, but his finisher is [ __ ]
I like the pedigree and the stunner. I
think I think they're my two favorites.
I like Kane's uh uppercut, though.
Yeah. I like Kane's uppercut, man. He
does it like so perfect. Yep.
I know. Don't remind me.
Yeah. I don't know. I think my favorite
wrestler I think it must be Kane, you know. Bro,
I like Kane's uppercut. [snorts]
Yeah, it's fake. But they do get hurt.
They do get hurt for real.
They do, mate. Trust me.
I don't know how that John Cena [ __ ]
picked up that Mark Henry. Big [ __ ]
He was, isn't it, Bob? Big [ __ ]
Imagine trying to lift that [ __ ] up,
bro. Oh my god.
No, that's mad, bro. That is mad.
No, that is mad, bro. That is some
That's one big [ __ ] bro. No, that's mad.
Yeah, Mike Tyson, he's a beast.
That was my father's uh favorite boxer.
So, why did this USA do all of this
[ __ ] then, Bob?
Why does she do all of that [ __ ]
The ghosting and stuff.
Now I want more.
It's like tasting something. Yeah. It's
like having a little taste, like a little tester
taste for something, right? And then
you're like, "Now I want more." cuz it
tastes so good. You want more in it.
You won't just you you wouldn't just
want it once, would you?
You know, why would you want something
or someone once?
That's a bit boring. Now I want more.
It's like having a nice fresh chicken
ticker come out and only having a bite of it. No, you know, [snorts] [laughter]
do you remember
You're my mama, nobody else's.
You remember Bob? You're my mama, no one else's.
Was that cute? Yeah. I don't know what
was the point of that.
And then she tries calling me poor.
I'm not [ __ ] poor. I wasn't poor then
and I'm not poor now. Why are you
calling me poor? You bully.
You big bully.
Yeah, she's a nasty bully, bro. [snorts]
And then when I stood up to myself and I
stood up for myself, she called me uh
she said I was a stalker because I defended myself.
I said, "No, I'm not having your abuse anymore, mama."
you know, and as soon as I defended
myself, she said I was a stalker
and then she called the old bill and stuff.
What was I not going to let you bully me, mommy? You know, you know,
she calls a lot of [ __ ] that [ __ ] did,
but LT said that I'm the root cause. Bob,
me posting that bouncer video. Yeah. the
other day that got LT arguing with me
and LT and Timmy arguing just simply
because I uploaded that video.
That's mad, isn't it?
That is mad, isn't it? Okay. Yeah.
I really want you, but I don't think you want me.
And then she sucks my dick and then she
blocked me the next day. I don't get that.
There's nothing for dindins. I've
already ate. You [ __ ] idiot.
I already ate. Why am I not eating
again? I'm having a Coca-Cola.
My mommy bought me it.
Yeah, that American gave me a really
good [ __ ] Bob. A Listerine.
No, I can't remember that.
No, I don't need more grub. I'm on a diet.
list of rain. No,
can't remember that
the [ __ ] A listister rain.
No, I can't remember that.
I've never had strep throat since I've
been on this community.
I've only had strep throat once.
That was years ago. And it was bad, bro.
Bad. It was bad.
Strep throat is really, really bad.
Like, and I'm not talking about sore
throat. I'm talking about strep throat.
There's a big difference.
It's [ __ ] vile, bro. It's like you're swallowing knives.
When I had it, I could only eat uh chili concardi.
It would take me like half an hour to finish it.
Yeah, but I didn't walk around with a lististering.
I think it was the flu.
We can't let these [ __ ] women win,
Bob. We got to go out every week now,
don't we? We can't let these [ __ ] women win. Listerin,
that doesn't make sense, bro.
I wouldn't walk around with Listerin. No.
So if I go to Thailand and go on Tinder,
would it work then? Bob, dups work in
Asia and South America. They don't work here.
Yeah, but people on Reddit say that you
need to go on dating apps.
They don't say that you need to approach
every day. They say that you
they say that you need to wait and stuff
and go on dating apps.
You can't approach every day, bro. It's
tiring as [ __ ] I'm not doing it, bro.
I'm not approaching every day. [ __ ]
yeah. Approaching every day. [ __ ] that. No way.
Seven numbers was good though. Is it
that I got seven numbers in it, Bob?
Don't let them [ __ ] women win in it.
Yeah. You can't let them [ __ ] women win, mate.
They were mocking you, laughing at you
when you was when you was traveling
around the country. They were laughing
at you. I was dead when that man said
that. They were mocking you. Mad.
They were laughing at you. >> [snorts]
>> They were mocking you, laughing at you.
I think that's my McDonald's Coca-Cola. Oh gosh.
Oh gosh, Bob.
Right. I'll be back uh later. Yeah.