got some bloody matches on him, but no
one bloody replies. What's the [ __ ]
point of that? They're not even going to reply.
You know, if they're not going to even
bloody reply, what's the point?
You know, [ __ ] weird. Really weird. It is bloody with Oh gosh,
this dump web is making me really sleepy.
Really, really sleepy. D D ch. Huh? Middle finger. Franklin.
So, I've actually got matches on this uh
hint, but no one replies.
But if you wrote something negative,
they would reply though.
I still have this downloaded for some
reason. I don't know why. Yeah,
it was more than 350. But yeah,
I didn't even know they missed a penalty.
I didn't even know that to be fair.
Did they actually miss a penalty? I
don't even see it. Oh, well,
I'm still well up. Isn't it?
It is what it is.
If they were home, I would have won. I think.
Yeah, I think if if they were playing
home, I would have definitely won. I think. Yeah.
So tired, bro. [ __ ] me. Oh,
no. It wasn't 350. It was 360.
I'm sure 370 maybe.
Have a look.
Oh, it was 370.
It was 370.
I don't know why he said 350. I thought
it was 360.
That's [ __ ] is it, man?
That is [ __ ] bollocks.
Yeah. 378 man,
is it? 370.
[ __ ] hell, man.
[ __ ] sake, man.
Anyways, why you still talk about that?
That was last week. Yeah.
I love it when people like come on here
and try and mock it though because it's
like they actually think I'm scared.
They actually think I've got nobody cuz
they got nobody. It's mad these people are here.
Like I've said many times before, they
think everyone's got the same life as them.
Why they do, I don't know, but they do
It's weird, isn't it? It's weird. Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no. It means
So these people in here, they seem to
think everyone's got the same life as
them. Skin, no money.
Must be part of their disabilities, bro.
But they seem to think everyone's got
the same life as them. Yes. It's uh
it's part of their disabilities. Definitely, man.
weird, ain't it, bro?
It is weird. Yes. Virgin boy.
spinning little bed [ __ ] with no bed, no
money in it.
That's so catchy, bro. Catchy saying, isn't it? Yeah, [ __ ] [ __ ]
They cost me [ __ ] um
Got a nice curry cook for me later. Yay. Yeah.
>> [clears throat]
>> Never mind. Yeah.
Num chuckle. Num chuckle.
That red star is some big fat ugly freak
that ain't got no life.
You can just tell ain't it, bro? Some
big fat ugly disabled Mong that don't
leave his mommy's basement.
It's so obvious, isn't it? For someone
to sit on YouTube every day, year in
year out doing that, bro.
Just just thought I'd just mention it.
Just odd time.
Ain't got a life with fat ugly fingers.
You can tell, right? if someone's um fat
by the way their hands are by the way
their fingers are and he tried so hard
not to like show it but he's a fat ugly bongo
proper proper fat ugly bongo bro
for real man
ain't got no life
no life a YouTuber Uh
you know I buy the job for YouTube.
talking to these nine people that are watching me,
but I can't comment because they're blocked
or they just don't want to comment.
That's who I'm talking to. Matey, when
are you going to get a life? Matey,
smoky be matey, you got no life, matey,
when are you going to get a life, matey,
you've got no life, matey.
Matey, matey, matey, matey, matey,
you've got no life.
You got no life but your job. I see you
on it all the time.
Nah, your life ain't good. If your life
was good, you wouldn't be on here all
day every day like you are. People
that's got a good life doesn't don't
come on here all day every day on here.
Nah, you wouldn't be on here, lad. The
way you are if your life was good. Come
on. You can't lie to me, man. You
really, really can't lie to me.
Can't lie to someone like me, matey.
Like, you just just can't, man. Just
you you you just can't, mate.
You just can't. No, it's not likewise,
cuz I'm not on here all the time. No,
it's not likewise, cuz I'm not on here
all the time.
Not at all. Not at all. It's my first
time on YouTube today.
So, no, it isn't likewise. And I can
take a day off of YouTube. You can't.
That's the difference. I've took weeks
off of YouTube before.
So, no, it isn't likewise. It isn't
likewise at all.
Like, not at all.
Nowhere near the same thing. You can't
take a day off YouTube, lad. Very shortly,
I went to get some washing stuff today, Grezy.
Yeah, I went to get some washing stuff.
I'm having a curry for tea today. Grieves. Yeah. Okay, boss.
I will do for you. Greasy boss.
No problem, boss.
I can't believe some of these hotel
prices in different cities in [ __ ]
the UK, bro. What the [ __ ]
Like £300 for normal hotels?
No. They would laugh, mate. It's not even December. What?
People would be [ __ ] insane to pay
that, bro, for one night at a [ __ ]
hotel. That is insane, lad.
That's insane, Grezy.
What the [ __ ] These are like 370
450 for fourstar hotels.
That is insane, bro.
Who in their right mind's paying out, bro?
That's ridiculous. You can go a holiday with that.
Yeah, you can get a holiday with that,
Grezy. What the [ __ ] Who would pay
that, man? That is mental.
Bloody mental, mate. Bloody mental.
Yeah, that's ridiculous, bro. You can
get a holiday with that. [ __ ] £350,
£400 for a [ __ ] hotel. I've never
paid that, bro.
That is mad.
That is mental, is it? waves here.
That is mental.
No, no interest.
If you're going to try and suggest
that's a way to get women, it's not
going to try and suggest that
[ __ ] church. I'm not a [ __ ]
Christian. Jesus Christ, I'm atheist.
Isn't that right, Grezy? I'm bloody atheist.
I don't know. Slow [ __ ] missed the penalty.
Wow. Did I actually miss a penalty?
It would get me out.
Uh, bro, I go out every day. Would it
mean it would get me out? I was out
today. I was out yesterday.
Again, we're not all like you, bro.
Again, you seem to think everyone's got
your life. No offense.
No, that's not a normal It's It's It's
not a normal price, bro. It's not
summer. It's not New Year's Eve. £360
for a [ __ ] four-star hotel.
I would never pay that, bro, in England.
I've got the money to do it, and I've
had the money to do it plenty of times,
and I still wouldn't pay it. That is insane.
What the [ __ ] bro?
That is ridiculous. No. No. That is
ridiculous. I think the most I've ever
paid for a hotel was I think it was 170
when I went to leads
and that was like a Hilton. I've never I
can tell you how I can actually go on my
um bookings when I used to travel
actually. I can actually tell you how
much I've spent.
I can actually get it up when I used to
travel. One second.
Yeah, I don't need I don't need to be I
don't need to get out, bro. I'm out all the time.
Right. Anyways, one second. Where's uh
I'm going to get I'm going to see what's
the most I've paid.
Just curious, you know.
Oh, here we go. And trips.
The last one was Ibis in Stratford.
Doesn't price doesn't come up on this one.
That's when I was almost homeless.
Greavves over YouTube. I don't know if you remember
strand. Ah, I do remember this one.
This was with a 19year-old.
Yeah, I do remember that one. £168. That
was in London.
£168. That was the one with the 19year-old. Yeah. Okay.
Ibis Cardiff [snorts]
£99. That one was
uh Cardiff again.
That was 76.
And that was
Yeah. £76 I paid.
Uh, these are all good hotels as well.
Park, Plaza, Nottingham. They're all
good hotels. None of these are [ __ ]
hotels by the way. 98.
That one was Manchester.
That was in the summer. 110.
These are all good hotels as well. Oh. I
don't think I've ever paid more than 170.
Oh, this was Middlesbrough, Birmingham, Sheffield.
I think this Edinburgh one was quite uh 125.
The Scotland one was. See, I've never
paid more. I don't think I would pay.
Not in this country anyways. Hampton by
Hilton Newcastle. See, these are all
Hilton hotels I used to stay at. £127.
There you go.
So, I never stayed in [ __ ] hotels ever, bro.
They were never the price.
Mental in it, Grezy. [ __ ] mental.
[ __ ] mental, son. No,
no, no, no, no, no. Oh, man.
So yeah, I don't know where they get
their prices from, bro.
I really don't know where they get their
prices from, but when you go on a
Friday, it's a lot more um it's a lot more cheaper.
Yeah, it's a lot more cheap if you go on a Friday.
I think I used to go on a Friday but
still busy in it.
Why the [ __ ] are you going to Northern
Ireland? What the [ __ ]
Why' you pay over £700 to go to Northern Ireland?
It's a bit weird, isn't it?
Yeah, that is a bit weird.
Northern Island of all [ __ ] places.
You still bloody gambling. Smokey.
Told you many times to pack that in. To
pack that gambling bollocks in. >> [snorts]
>> I'm going to have a pot noodle, man. I'm
in a package, but I don't find anything.
I don't find anything. Um,
do your thing here. I'll be right back.
All right, I'm back.
>> You know what, Smokey B. Right, let me
tell you something, mate.
>> You might technically have more money
than me, but I've got a better lifestyle
than you, buddy.
Went out last week, banged an escort,
gambled. Went out the week before, got an escort,
This is what you're failing to realize,
son. You're not out every week banging
escorts, are you, son? Sunny Jim.
Oh, [ __ ] sake, bro. Yeah.
This pot noodle is nice.
Yeah, but you don't you don't pay for
different women like Peter Belly does.
So, what do you do? Do you go out
drinking every week or
tell me what your lifestyle is?
Come on. Give me a rundown about what
your lifestyle is, mate. Come on.
Do you go to nice restaurants like me?
Do you have 400 lb jeans like me?
200 trainers like me, mate.
I don't think you do, matey. Do you
[ __ ] slow [ __ ] me over for [ __ ] 370, bro?
They missed the [ __ ] penalty.
I'm still well up anyways, but still
[ __ ] bastards. [ __ ] bastards. Go.
Yeah, but it's boring every week though,
is it? Going out drinking every week is
[ __ ] boring, bro.
You have to admit, yeah, that the longer
you go without it, the more you enjoy
it. Sometimes the reason I do it every
week is because there's nothing better to do.
There is literally nothing better to do.
That's why sometimes I do it, but I like
to do it every two weeks. I find you
enjoy it more. But
I don't know.
Yeah, it's good, man. Um, but
you enjoy it though if you do that every two weeks.
Don't say I can't afford to go out every
week cuz I [ __ ] well can.
I went out last week, went out the week
before, I'm going out this week cuz my sister.
But it depends. Like when I was at the
old house when I was living with people,
I had company in it. So when I'm here,
if I'm bored, I have money. I can just
go out. So that's why sometimes there's
nothing better to do.
But I like to be in by 12:00. I don't
like to be I don't like to be out late
cuz of um I just like to be in bed by a
certain time. So I'll just go out all
day, drink, then come back. So So
I guess if you was working hard every
day, then maybe look forward to the weekend maybe. But yeah,
I'll be out this week. Anyways, I need
to get a haircut as well.
I don't play roulette anymore. Smoking.
It's too dangerous.
It's too dangerous, mate.
Yeah, it's too dangerous to rulet.
Too too too dangerous.
It's too [ __ ] dangerous, mate.
It's too dangerous, bro. The last time I
played it was [ __ ] um last month.
Remember, bro, I went out. I spent loads
of money and I just put £100 on
roulette. I think I got to like 550. I
just took it. I ain't played it. No, I
played in the bookies. Well, I played in
the bookies. Well, actually, like two
weeks ago, maybe.
But not serious like that, bro. I don't
I don't play that [ __ ] I just I just do
the football really.
You know, I've had some good wins on the football, so
I want to do 500 pound on a double both
teams to score, bro. But I don't know,
man. Trying to have the bottle to do that.
If I If I was short of money, I would do
it. If I was short of money, I would do it. But
that's a lot of money to lose on a
football bet, is it? And the thing is is
like with a football bet, it's you only
have one chance. Whereas if you was to
put that money on roulette, then you'd
have multiple chances to hit on it. You
know what I'm saying?
But if I was short on money, then I would. But
other than that, that's insane if it loses.
Cuz if you lose 500 pound on roulette,
you can say that you, you know, you've
had multiple chances.
You had multiple chances to hit if you
were doing 70 80 pound spins. as a
football bet. It's a bit
um you know what I'm saying? Also, your
potential's capped as well. That's another thing. Yeah.
Did it win?
I've just been winning football bets.
That's why I was able to buy the jeans
and [ __ ] Um
I lost that one. I lost one.
I can tell you the ones that I won
the football. The first season, the
first game of the season, I put 80, got
that to 280. That was a nice return.
Then another one I put 80, got it to 230,
lost 100, then 130, then put 120, 1380,
another 120, 1360. Obviously I lost 130
over the weekend and obviously the
roulette win. So, I'm up I'm up along
the lines. Definitely definitely up
along the lines somewhere.
Oh, [ __ ] obviously. You know what I'm saying?
Cuz I have more money this month when I
bought the garments and [ __ ] So,
obviously I do.
And I've gone out and spent a shitload
of money as well. So,
gone out and spent a shitload of money.
So, garments and I've still got money,
more money for the rest of this month
than I would have before.
Wow, that's good. Is it?
That's serious gambling, bro. That's
serious serious gambling.
When was when was the last time you
played roulette, boss?
I've already been out. What is it with
you people? I don't need to go out every
single bloody day.
Are you going out? I'll just come
[ __ ] back. I went to get some washing
stuff and whatnot. Don't need to go out
every bloody day.
Jesus Christ, it's damp out there. Why
you going out doing? Bloody hell. I'm
just eating this pot noodle. Yeah,
I've never played blackjack. I don't
have the [ __ ] patience for it.
Have a beer. No, I'm going out Saturday.
What is it today? Tuesday. Man,
that's like Timmy. Timmy goes out like
every day drinking, don't he? No.
No. I'm not doing cold potion until Saturday.
Yeah, that Timmy drinks every day, don't
he? Like every day. Every other day. I
don't know how people do that, bro. [ __ ]
that. You won't be able to do that in London, mate.
he'd be skinned after the second day.
But I said, I don't know how they do it,
as in like do it, and not afford it.
That's mad, bro.
But yeah, there are people that do go
out drinking um every day or every other day.
Guess in the summer you could do like
three times a week, but
I don't know how I don't know why people
would want to do that, though. What the [ __ ]
You know the thing is smoky be you know
in London yeah
they water the drinks down. So say you
get a rum and coke £7 something right they [ __ ]
water that [ __ ] down bro they water it
down so you get it down you very quickly
and then you buy more and more and more
and by the time you realize it um 30
gone you know you've spent £30. It
happened to me when I went out the last
time. Not last time, the time before. I
spent about 4030 40.
Drunk it away, bro. Cuz it's so watered down.
It's so watered down. Even if you got a
double, what's that? Like£14? It's watered down.
Whereas, you know, Guinness, right? If
you get Guinness, okay, it might be £8 a
pipe, right? But
realistically, you're probably not going
to spend more than 40 quid cuz they
can't water it down.
They can't water it down like they do uh um
[ __ ] 14 [ __ ] 7 to 14 and shit's
watered down, bro. What the [ __ ] You know,
and also when you drink rum, it gives
you anxiety the next day and it makes
you tired. The hangover is 100 times
worse than if you was to um drink beer.
That's why I tried to stick to beer to be honest.
That's why I tried to stick to beer. [sighs] Yeah. N
[ __ ] run. They water that [ __ ] down, bro.
We out on Saturday. So, [ __ ] sake.
Sick of this [ __ ] you know, bro.
Sick of this woman [ __ ]
Well, I'm used to it now, it
was watching that Ed Matthews um
yesterday, right? I was like proper
proper watching him before I went to sleep. And
I don't know what Ant-Man means. I mean,
yeah, the guy gets [ __ ] but he still
gets [ __ ] rejected. He still has to
They still have an attitude. A lot of
them still was pretending that they've got boyfriends.
I was watching him. Yeah, he went um
he was still dealing with their [ __ ] I
was watching it, man.
Yeah, they weren't a walk in the park at all, bro.
But it was making me think, but I want
to go back to Liverpool. I've only been once.
That was years ago. I was like, "Wow, it
actually looks lively there.
It looks proper proper lively there, bro."
I've only been there once, so [snorts] Liverpool.
I've been to Manchester like 10 times,
but I've only been once.
Oh, this pot noodle is nice, man.
Excuse me. Excuse me. Excuse
One second, please.
I can't believe it took me to [ __ ] 28
years of age, right,
to realize it was never going to change. [snorts]
Oh, Peter B is so stubbing. Hey. Hey. Mhm.
Oh, that was yummy.
That was a lovely party noodle. Pot noodle.
I prefer the black one, but they didn't
have the black one.
I like Well, I like the brown, green, and black.
You should bloody watch it.
You need to come back to [ __ ] London. One second.
to turn that [ __ ] um thing off.
I'll be back later anyways.