Oh, sorry [clears throat] about that.
Where's that blinking virgin?
Sorry about that, man.
Where's the virgin?
Where's that bloody virgin then?
The skin virgins been going on about me. [ __ ]
Oh, these [ __ ] really all have the same
attitude, don't they? Yeah.
>> [clears throat]
>> I'm good, man. Just chilling.
>> Yeah, I'll be out on Saturday and then
that's me done, I think, for a couple of weeks.
I need to save some money now, bro. I
spent a lot the past couple of weeks and
yeah, it's just no point going out
anymore. Really, is there
simple as that? Is it
always the same [ __ ] So that's that.
Spent 300 last weekend. [ __ ] 600 prof.
just bought a Christmas present.
So yeah, man.
I have got the money to, but I don't
want to waste it. I don't want to keep wasting money
just to get the same result. I've got
the money to. Of course, I've got the
money to. It's not about having the
money, bro. It's called, you know,
there's a point where you need to save
money to do other stuff.
Whether you have the money or you don't
have the money.
Simple as that.
So that's that, bro.
So I'm taking a break until December
anyways. I did say I was going to, to be
fair, it just makes more sense just to save money
cuz every time you go out, it's just the
same [ __ ] same people, same attitude. So
why would you keep wasting 400 pound every week
when it's always going to be the same [ __ ]
Yeah, I went out earlier.
I won't be doing anything after next
week. I'll be hibernating. I'll be
hibernating and saving some money.
Well, I'm going to message these numbers
and if one of them wants to go out, then
obviously I'll go out. I don't mind
spending money then.
Yeah, I don't mind spending money then.
But other than that, no.
If someone wants to me, I don't mind
spending the money. No problem.
But other than that, [ __ ] it. There's no
point. Is this the same result?
Nope. You know, I don't gamble much.
So why are you asking stupid questions?
It's not about having the money or not
having the money, bro.
Waste [ __ ] £400 every week
or whatever it is just to get the same
outcome, same attitude. [ __ ] bro. It's [ __ ]
No, it's [ __ ]
What am I supposed to do, guy? every
week of my life just cuz I've got the
money to. Nah, bro.
Really? Really? Nah, it's pointless. Yeah.
Also, you should be saving for like
December and stuff, New Year's. I just I
just bought my mom some Ugg boots. £165.
So, that's what people should be doing. >> [snorts]
>> Yes, I have twice.
Yeah, just bought some UGG boots. £165.
Starting off early, eh? Starting off early.
Yeah. Did you bet?
Yeah, I'm on a detox, matey.
I'm on a detox now, matey.
I'm getting too greedy, matey. Too [ __ ] Yeah, man.
I need to pay for a Netflix subscription as well.
I need to seriously be saving money now, bro.
Just cuz I have money, it doesn't mean,
you know, go out, spend 300 pound, 400
pound every [ __ ] week.
I think it's like $6.99. I need to get a Netflix subscription. Yeah.
You go out, you deal with the same attitude.
It's literally the same.
It's the same attitude.
I already had a curry. I had a homemade
You [ __ ] go out, bro. You spend all
that money just to get the same attitude.
It's just the same attitude, same
atmosphere every time you go out, bro.
I'm hibernating for a bit now. I need to
save some money. So,
like I said, yeah, I need to save some monga.
I just bought [ __ ] £165 [ __ ] Ugg boots.
So, I need a detox anyways to be fair.
I'm getting a bit out of control, matey.
Well, it makes sense, grievously, isn't
it? I mean, December's uh December's a
expensive month. No. So, I mean, yeah, I
could go out every week,
but you might as well just save money for December.
Greavves. I think it makes more sense to
save money for December. No.
went out last week, went out the week
before that. I think I went out the week
before that. I'm going out next week.
I mean, just makes sense, though.
You got New Year's Eve as well. Yeah,
I think it makes more sense.
Don't know about you, Grezy. Yeah,
December is a good month.
What do you think, Grezy? Do you think
you should go out every week or nah?
I need to calm down, bro. I'm getting too greedy.
I am getting too [ __ ] greedy, matey.
No, it's just more busier.
You never pull in this country. But I
went out last week, the week before
that, the week before that. I've
constantly been going out spending
money. So, I might as well just save money now
until December or like mid December.
It just makes more sense to go to the detox.
If I stayed in the past two months, I
would be at like six, sevenk.
Yeah, I'd be at like six, seven [ __ ] K, bro.
But obviously I have a life in it. So
unlike Virgin Boy cuz he's [ __ ]
skinny. He ain't got a life.
And in January, I'll be saving up until March.
You need to stop trolling, Bob. You're
really bad at it.
You really, really need to stop.
You're really really bad at it. Like the
the trolling is really bad, bro. You
need to stop it.
Then you say you're [ __ ] genuine.
You're not genuine, bro.
Exact. Who says exactly?
Who says that? Monty.
Yeah. You don't pull more in December.
It's just um
you you never pull in this country.
This Bob guy needs to stop trolling though. Greedy.
That's quite sad.
It is quite [ __ ] sad at this point, bro. Bird boy.
I'm going to put 500 pound on the both
teams to score Steven Howard.
Bro, stop trying to troll. You're bad at
it. Stop it.
You're really, really, really, really bad.
Bro, I I need to go out and believe
stuff can happen, bro. I've spoke to
more women than you. I've met more women
than you. I know what they're like.
There's nothing that's ever going to
happen. It's never going to change in this country.
It doesn't bother me. I don't give a
[ __ ] about it, bro. That's why I don't
care about it.
cuz I know deep down that it's never
going to change.
So at the end of the [ __ ] day,
why? What? What's there to be positive
about? Stuck up [ __ ] with attitude.
That's what they are. Stuck up [ __ ]
with attitude problems. What's what's
there to be positive about? Nothing. Oh, bye-bye.
No mongos on my channel.
Uh, okay. One second.
I need to save some money, bro.
Oh yeah, he's on the train again. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm watching. One sec. One sec.
Oh, he's funny. He
He lost 140. I'm dead. He said he lost
That is funny, bro.
Is that funny that he lost uh 140 gy?
Is that funny?
Fruit mad world.
And why do why are you telling me to be
positive anyways? Bob Bills, are you
dismissing my struggles?
Well, if you're not trolling, then you're uh
If you're not trolling, then you're
dismissing my struggles.
I'm watching him. I'm watching him.
Yeah, he's proper addicted to gambling.
Greasy. Do you think I'm addicted to gambling? Nah.
Nah, obviously not.
not like him. He He still plays that
[ __ ] ball roulette.
Yeah, I'm addicted to cold approach and
he's addicted to gambling.
No, I don't.
Yeah, but why are you telling me to be positive?
Why are you Why are you telling me to be
positive when you know
you know it's always going to be the
same here? You know this.
Just like I know it.
Just like Greavesy knows it. It's always
going to be the same here. You know this.
You know I played a bar roulette what?
Two weeks ago. Okay.
Okay. And what? Bro, I'm not like Timmy.
Timmy gambles all of his money.
There's a big difference.
I wish I put 500 pound on a on that pro
team to score, bro. [ __ ] me.
It will always be the same, bro. Women
with attitude pretending they have
boyfriends. It'll always be the same.
Stuck up [ __ ]
It would always be the same.
My activity is to get off YouTube, bro.
Oh, it took too many minutes to get off YouTube, man.
A lot of people go for Timmy now, don't
they, Gre? A lot of people go for um A
lot of people go for Timmy now, don't they, Grezy?
You said Virgin Boy went live, did he?
Have a look.
Oh my god. He needs to get laid.
He needs to lose his virginity. He needs
to [ __ ] get laid, man. All
right, this Timmy's a [ __ ] Did you
hear what Timmy said, Grezy?
To one of the people, he said, "You've
got a heart of gold.
You've got a heart of gold." [laughter]
He's a [ __ ] idiot, isn't he? He
really, really is an idiot.
You've got a heart of mode. Madison.
>> [clears throat]
>> I don't understand. Hey, Greg. I don't
know how this Timmy drinks every day.
Do you think that's mad how he drinks every day?
What is he mad?
I don't know how someone could drink
every day to be fair.
That is mad.
Stop talking [ __ ] to me about [ __ ]
He would have flawed me, bro. He would
have got his head smashed in about LJ
would have [ __ ] flawed me if he
didn't have family. Are you mad, bro? He
would have got slapped the [ __ ] up.
Stop talking [ __ ] mate. Yeah, if it was
to do with [ __ ] family, he wouldn't
have come all this way.
This Timmy. Yeah, he's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
bro. I swear to God, he's a [ __ ]
You [ __ ] mad, bro.
[ __ ] tired, man.
Why do you think Timmy will ever get off
YouTube? Graves there.
What do you think of USA? Izzy's boobies.
Am I doing much tomorrow?
No, I got no plans. Probably just chill
and watch a movie. I'm going to match on Saturday. Yeah.
He Is that true, bro? Are you serious?
He's the one that blocks everyone that
doesn't agree with him.
He literally blocks everyone that
disagrees with him, bro.
I mean, he blocks every single person
that disagrees with him. Anyone that
thumbs up, he gets he gets they get
blocked again. He's projecting, bro.
Just like he projects his skittness,
just like he projects his virginity. All
it is is projection, bro. Literally,
Ricky Billington got banned.
Yeah. He thinks anyone that disagrees
with him is me. He's obsessed.
He's a projector.
And any luck with what,
bro? He blocks everyone that disagrees
with him. Everybody.
I don't block people that disagree with
me. I block people that talk [ __ ]
That's what I I
You know, if I was blocking people that
disagree with me, I'd be I'd be blocking Greavesy.
Considering we just we basically
disagree on everything except from narcissists. So
yeah, I'm going to go watch a boxing
boxing match on Saturday.
Uh yeah, go for a few drinks and that's
me done, I think, for a little while.
Like I said, I'm saving money now. So,
yeah, that's good, man.
Yeah, my sister bought me some boxing tickets. though.
I bought my mom a pair of UGG boots.
£165 UGG boots. Jesus Christ.
£165. I wonder how much money we've gone
through the past two months.
Quite a [ __ ] lot, is it?
Yeah, it's got to be quite a lot. my 40? Nope.
Silly question to ask. Nope.
And even if they did, they wouldn't
introduce me to them cuz everyone's out for themselves.
Silly question, really.
Yeah, I need to take a break from going
out, man. Spending too much money.
I need to save, bro.
You need to save, mate.
Yeah, we spent a lot of money the past
two months, bro.
300 last week, 600 the week before.
Garments. [ __ ] hell, Grezy.
The lovely restaurants. I know you like
the lovely restaurants, Greavvesy.
But I'm getting too greedy. I need to
pack it in, matey.
don't agree with thee. God bless. Yep.
Yeah. Uh, Virgin Boys project him. He
blocked Ricky Millington. You know Ricky
Millington when he decided to come back
to this side. He blocked him. He seriously
He seriously needs to get laid, bro.
That virgin seriously seriously
seriously needs to get laid. When's he
going to lose it? I don't think we'll
ever know Greavves. When's he going to
lose it? But he needs to [ __ ] lose it.
He's going to die one. He's going to die a virgin.
He's a big big virgin. I was thinking of
this, you know, when I was [ __ ]
washing the dishes earlier.
There's a big big big big
There's a big virgin.
There's a big virgin, you know.
Big [ __ ] virgin, man.
He's going to die. One, Gy. He's going
to [ __ ] die one.
He's going to bloom and die one.
We need to put £500 on a both teams to score Steven.
That'd be lovely. Maybe£600.
I [ __ ] wish I had it on it the other day, mate.
That would have been [ __ ] lovely,
mate. Absolutely lovely.
No, you never will, bro. That's too much.
No, that's too much, bro. That is too much. Imagine
doing it though every week for three
weeks and it winning. Oh, [ __ ] hell.
That'd be lovely. Is it Greasy?
That' be like 6K. I think
it would be lovely, bro. Lovely.
No, it would be good.
Would you actually put £500 on two teams?
>> I don't know about that, bro.
No, it's too much.
It's too much, is it? Greasy.
Nah, it's too much, bro.
How long would it take them to pay you
if you win? If they've got to pay you
18,900, how much do you reckon it will
take them to pay you?
what you reckon it'll take a week for
them to pay 1900?
That's mad, bro.
I'd love them to pay me like 17,800 pound. But
you can't put five on a pound, bro, on a [ __ ]
way. Here you go. That's mental. That is mental, man.
I don't know about that, mate. [sighs]
I don't know about that. I risked that
one last week, man. [ __ ] sake.
It's bad, is it, Grezy?
I need to go piss. One sec.
I'm addicted to uh
I'm addicted to [ __ ] um old approach.
I'm addicted to [ __ ] cold approaching camp. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh no, Greasy. [ __ ] that.
No, no, no, no, no. Oh, [ __ ] Don't stop. virgin boy.
Greasy virgin boy.
>> [clears throat]
>> Skin in the bed [ __ ] with no bed and no
money in it.
Why is the virgin getting so defensive
over women again?
Have you noticed that Steven Howard?
He's getting very He said, "Oh, if they
are if they're not uh
interested, take the L and [ __ ] walk
away. How about you [ __ ] mind your
own business, you [ __ ] skin virgin.
And worry about that disabled girl that
doesn't let you [ __ ] her every night.
I bet that made you laugh, didn't it, Grezy?
How about you [ __ ] mind your own
[ __ ] business, you [ __ ] virgin?
How about that one?
How about that one, mate?
Yeah, I'm on it now, bro. I'm on it now. One sec.
Yo, [ __ ] Oh [ __ ] Oh [ __ ]
Oh, he talks [ __ ] mate, about because
I've got autism. That's He was trying to
say, "Yeah, oh, LJ didn't do anything
because he's got kids." This guy is a
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. He literally is
the biggest [ __ ] going. You know,
even if this guy Yeah. gets [ __ ]
knocked the [ __ ] out, he will still come
on chatting [ __ ]
You know what I mean? He will still come
on here chatting [ __ ] you know?
He didn't [ __ ] let anyone off. He let
me off, bro. He tried to kick me and
missed how many times?
How many times did he try to [ __ ]
kick me and he missed?
How about he [ __ ] let me off? That is
a [ __ ] idiot, bro.
He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. I should
just go to Birmingham and just smack him
up in it.
Like, literally should just go there and
smack the [ __ ] up in it.
What do you think, Graves? Obviously,
I'd have to run it by Grey first,
you know, cuz Grez is the boss.
Yep. I'm out on the road. It was
actually No, no, it was actually this.
It was actually I'm out on the road.
Of course I remember that, matey. Was
that nice of me buying my mommy some mug boots? Grezy.
That was cute, wasn't it? Easy.
I'm out on the road.
Any progress with what? Women. Well, you
already know the answer to that, so I
don't know why you're asking if that's
what you meant.
They're all the bloody same No. [snorts]
Oh man. Oh gosh.
Oh gosh. Darn it. [snorts]
I don't have any cats.
But but Virgin Boy is a big copycat
though. He's a little copy. He's a little copycat.
He said that She Cole was attractive to
fit in cuz he's a little copycat.
A little copycat.
Is that right, Steven Howard?
your little copycat. Little copycat.
Little copycat. Little copycat. Boy, you
little copycat. Little copycat. Little
copycat. You want a fan? You're a fan.
Bless you. You want to fit in little copycat?
I read a community post where he was
like, "Oh, if they say they're um not interested,
they've got a boyfriend and they don't
they're not interested. Walk away and
take the L." And I'm thinking, "Shut the
[ __ ] up, you skin virgin. Mind your own
[ __ ] business. Go lose your
virginity. Defending women is not going
to make them like you. They don't like
you. You little virgin.
Go lose your virginity.
You [ __ ] virgin [ __ ] You
know what I mean?
Uh, none of them. They're all [ __ ]
London [ __ ] England [ __ ]
No, I didn't see it, bro. I only saw the
community post earlier.
He needs to lose his virginity. He's
going to die a virgin.
I've said it from day one.
Everything he says is projection.
Virgin him skin him blocking people that
don't agree him. Everything is him. Little copycat.
A little copycat.
He's a little copycat. He's a little
copycat. He's a little copycat.
He's a little copycat. And he's got no
mind of his own.
He's a little copycat.
He's a little copycat. He's a little Little copy.
This is no copy.
This is little copy.
Yeah, they're weirdos.
One second. Let me
Yep. Exactly. Exactly.
Exactly, bro. Exactly.
When you finally lose it.
When you finally pop it.
When you finally lose it. When you
finally pop it. You'll know.
You know, mate,
you finally lose it. No longer a virgin.
Do you have my little voice?
He gets a grand a month. Spicuous.
He gets He He's called £1,000 a month,
boy. We call him
Yeah, he's uh he's £1,000 a month, boy.
Grand a month.
You get You get a grand a month, mate.
You get a grand a month. A month.
How's it up boy?
You're the grand a month, mate. You're
the ground a month.
You're the ground above,
mate. We need to thank the football
Steven Howard, man. The football has
been kind to us.
Jeans, trainers, UGG boots, nights out, escorts, restaurants.
We need we need to we need to uh we need
to thank the football mate.
I spent £200 on escorts. It's [ __ ]
wrong. [ __ ] hell, bro.
Virgin can't do that. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Your major f your major. No. No. No. No.
Virgin can't do that.
No. No. No. No. No. Just stop it. Stop
it. Stop it. Virgin boy can't do that,
mate. Virgin boy can't do that.
Virgin boy can't do that, mate.
But [ __ ] off manga. What the [ __ ] are
you talking about, bro?
I've gone out a lot as well. Yeah,
my life's been pretty good, but I need
to chill out for for a little while now.
I do need to save some money, mate. I'm
getting out of control.
I'm out of control. Greasy. Oh, gosh
darn it. Grezy,
we call him grand a month. Boy,
he said he was going to p report me to
benefits cuz I got designer jeans and
some trainers. He said he was going to
try and get my money stopped.
Yeah, he's talking [ __ ] bro. We've been over this.
Yeah, he's talking [ __ ] Just like he
said that I spied um at my sister in the
shower. Of course he said it cuz he's
full of [ __ ]
That's what he does, bro. When he gets
owned, he makes up weird stories.
Yeah, he makes up weird stories just
like the skin virgin. >> Yeah.
That bloody skin is light. Um,
but it will never change.
It won't get worse. It won't get better.
It just will never change.
Them pretending our boyfriend given
attitude, it will never change, will it?
M well it will never change will it
but it would never change would it? on step.
I fancy a McDonald's, you know,
but I won't get one, I think.
I got some curry in the thing, but I
don't have any coke. get one.
I need to be I need to actually save
some money, bro. Serious. I don't think
you understand. I actually need to save
some money now, bro. Should
I get a McDonald's? Should I not? Well,
never think. Just wait. McDonald's. No McDonald's.
Well, I'm not on a grand a month just
yet. So, I think I'm going to [ __ ] it. Why not?
It's almost £200 spent without even
leaving the house. All right. That's all
right then, mate. All right. One second.
Going to get myself a little McDonald's.
Why not, Grezy?
We only live once, don't we?
I'm not I'm not on a grand a month. So,
one second. Let me have a little look.
You know, I fancy though. I fancy um
20 Oh, there's a new menu. Yeah.
20 garlic and pepper McNuggets.
What the [ __ ]
Oh, no, bro. That looks wrong.
Yeah, there's a new menu.
I'm just going to get
No, no, no. I'll tell you what I'm going to get.
Uh, no. I'm going to get one second.
I'm going to get a McChick sandwich meal.
Oh, it says if you buy one, you get one free. Okay.
So, if you buy one, you get one free.
Well, obviously you don't get chips with
that one, huh?
I'm just going to get the mill. one second.
No, I'm going to get the
I'm just going to get the meal.
Oh, that virgin boy.
Oh, that [ __ ] virgin boy.
That skin virgin boy.
No money, no life. No money, no life.
Nobody no life me. [snorts] >> Uh
extras. Yeah, I want some C's. What?
I got an extra I got a slice of cheese.
Yeah, I got some cheese with it as well.
I'm getting you going now, don't I, Greasy?
But you got to be a bit careful cuz
you're on a grand a month. I'll be on a
grand a month soon, mate, at some point
if I keep going on like this. Um, but
you know what I'm like, Grievy. I might
have to put £500 on a on a football vet
soon. You never know. You You need to be
a bit careful though, Greasy.
You [clears throat] know,
I'm not like the Virgin. I get myself a
Get myself a McDonald's, you know.
Okay, I've just ordered myself a McDonald's.
[clears throat] Is that all right with you, Greavvesy? [snorts] Boy, boy.
Well, that's all right that I I got
myself a little backies.
Uh, I could win the m
Oh, I'd win the money game. Yeah, but I
wouldn't show anyone, though.
I've got the balls to do it, but I don't
need to do it right now. I have money,
bro. Like, I have like
But if there if there comes a point
where I've got 600 pound to my name,
then I will do it.
Yeah, but I wouldn't show anyone, bro. I
don't think I would show anyone.
Yeah, I lost 130 on Saturday, bro. Why
should I [ __ ] care?
Yeah, I lost [ __ ] 130. Oh, well, £500.
I wouldn't show anyone, bro, because uh
and if it won, I still wouldn't show
anyone. I'd show the bet, but I wouldn't
show the money.
There's no point showing people money on
here, bro. They just project their skim this.
Yeah, but you're not really down. You're
up. I don't know how much I'm up. I'm up
a lot of money, bro.
I don't know how much I'm up, but I must
be up a lot of money because
I got jeans that was 200. Trainers that
was 210. I bought my mom some UGG boots.
I spent £300 over the weekend. Spent
[ __ ] 600 the week before that.
I still got like Yeah. Well over a grand. Bro,
yep. I don't need to prove myself to
these mongos anymore, bro. Yeah.
What? Even if the bet lost,
I don't know. I'm up I'm up a load of
money, bro. I know. I'm up I'm up a load
of money. And I wish I got escorts as well
because if I just got my normal money,
bro, I wouldn't have been able to afford.
No way, bro.
And I lost 130 as well. So,
I'm definitely up somewhere along the line.
Yeah, but then if the bet loses, they'd
be [ __ ] laughing at me, bro.
I'll put 600 on it
if you really want me to. I'll put 600
on it, bro. On a on a football bet.
But then if I'm losing, I'm basically [ __ ]
I'd be a bit nervous. I'd have the balls
to do it. I think I could do it, bro. I
think I could do it.
Yeah, I think I could do it.
Imagine them just going on the community
post and seeing that. No, I don't need
to be 600. 500. Yeah, £500 enough. Yeah.
And one of them just seeing the £500.
Oh my god, bro. Imagine. No, 500 is enough.
Imagine that. You put £500 on it and
then you go out drinking and it comes
in. Oh my [ __ ] god, bro.
Yeah, they call me skin, bro. Do you
know the thing is? Yeah, spa spaz took I
actually live a a decent life, bro. I go
to restaurants. I've been out a couple
of [ __ ] times
and whatnot, bro. Like, got designer clothes.
I bought some [ __ ] bro. But [ __ ]
I do need to chill. I do need to save
money though until December, bro.
Cuz all of this going out, wasting money
is for nothing.
It's for nothing, bro.
It's all right now and again, but I just
got greedy with it again, bro.
But if the bet loses, then it's a lot of
money to lose, isn't it?
It is a lot of money to lose.
If the bet loses, it's a lot of money to lose, bro. Oh,
it is a lot.
I could do it though. Like I said, I
could do it, bro. I wouldn't be scared
to do it.
You have to be a good lineup though for
me to put that kind of [ __ ] money on that, bro.
I'm saying this to my sister though cuz
we're going out this next week that
every time I go out I always get an escort.
So, I'm going to watch some boxing on
Saturday, come back.
But I seriously do need to budget now. I
do actually need to start saving some money, bro.
No, we're talking 5 No, no, no, no, no.
They're talking 500 on one bet, bro.
No, we're talking 500 on one bet, bro. Yeah.
Oh, you could put 500 on roulette.
Well, that's even riskier.
I can't believe SL [ __ ] me up, bro.
They're bastards, man.
Oh, come on, Greasy. Get yourself a
Mackey's. I've I've ordered myself some.
Let me tell Let me Let me ask what lady thinks. One second, mama.
I done a really bad thing. I ordered
myself some McDonald's.
Are you sure, mama?
Your boots should be coming in a couple of days, huh?
Are you actually going to wear them?
I spent a lot of money on them. Mama,
you better [ __ ] wear them.
Is that cute? [laughter]
That's cute. there.
Look at that. Look at that.
There's some really expensive boots.
They come from Australia.
They cost me £165. >> [laughter]
>> Do you remember Ronald Pump Grezy?
You're better looking than them. You've
got a better life than them and you've
got more money than them and it kills them.
We still have a pretty decent life to be
fair, but don't know about the money so
much nowadays, mate. It's kind of dried
up a little bit.
It's kind of dried up a wee bit, but you
know, should should be all right. Should be okay.
You know what I'm like, Greasy. Oh, gosh darn it.
You know I'm like, Greasy.
I got myself a McChick sandwich.
One more piggy. Mama,
I'm going to eat as well.
I eat lots of food. Mama, you know the drill.
Everyone around you is radioactive.
[ __ ] me, bro.
You can wear them with your little tracksuit, Ma.
Everyone's going to be so jealous of
your little boots,
they're going to try and rob them.
Yeah, I suppose that is kind of funny, isn't it?
You don't like any other color in it.
Did you like black? Nah.
You could wear your little track seat, ma.
Everyone here is going to be jealous of
you in your new little beats.
That's a cute little voice, isn't it, Grezy?
You do the loop loop and pull and your
shoes all look in the bollocks. You go
over and back
and you do it again. You loop and pull.
And your shoes are looking the bollocks.
And your shoes are looking the balls.
And your shoes are looking in the pockets.
Oh, don't talk about my mama like that.
Not an old hag.
No, I didn't get any nuggets.
Why did virgin boy show daddy savings?
How about you show a good life?
Can't do that, can you?
You fing skin flint.
Yeah, [ __ ] Skint Flink. Yeah,
I have the best voices, mate.
You can't get someone's f You can't get
benefit to stop because they can afford
the sign of clothes and you can't, you skin bastard.
That's they can't stop your money for
that. You know, you're allowed to buy
stuff, you know, if you've saved up and
you know, you trying to get my money stopped.
What? Because I can afford designer
stuff and you're a [ __ ] skip bastard.
Don't understand these people's problem.
Really, really don't, mate.
Yeah, something like that.
when you finally lose it.
When you finally pop it,
Stephen Howard, when you finally pop
that V card, mate,
you just you just died on the star and
you finally lose it, mate.
I I lost it when I was 17. Yeah. [ __ ]
>> Yeah, they done it. They done it to me,
bro. After they done it to me twice.
They done it to me twice, bro. When I
done the subleting and that. Yeah. Um
they called me twice and then after that
they stopped. Yeah. They said, "Oh, can
you show bank statements?" I said, "Oh,
yeah. Yeah, I can show you bank
statements if you want. Cuz I had all
the subletter money going on another account.
So I said, "Oh, absolutely. I can show
you whatever bank statements you want if
you if you want." Cuz I had it in a
different account, you see. So yeah.
Yeah, mate. Yeah. After the second time
to no one, mate.
Thanks one to [ __ ] no one.
I lost it at the old house when I was 17.
And no matter what you told this guy, he
wouldn't believe it.
You were telling these sex stories that
you had and for some reason he wouldn't
believe it because he's a virgin. He
would convince himself that you're a virgin.
That's how it used to go with this
weirdo, mate. It was so creepy.
Really, really, really creepy. He's a creepy virgin.
Creepy creepy creepy [ __ ] virgin. I
mean, I put a [ __ ] porno out there
and they still call me a virgin. What
[ __ ] M do they want? Honestly, I don't know.
What more do these [ __ ] [ __ ] want? I
honestly don't know, mate. Really don't.
I'm sick of it to be fair, you know. Yeah, man.
Never been to Logan in my life. [ __ ] what?
[ __ ] Legoland. What the hell is bells?
He'll never get laid, will he, mate?
He'll never get laid. Yeah, I went Chinatown. Yeah,
I don't know why he whites tonight. Why
he white knights? Women don't like him.
He would never get laid and he still defends them.
These white knights, mate, are [ __ ] crazy.
Oh, that's [ __ ] bad.
He needs to get laid.
He's going to [ __ ] die a virgin. He
He's going to [ __ ] die one. He's
He's going to [ __ ] die on me. Yeah.
Yeah, he lies. He He said that my my
pregnant sister slapped me up. He's a bullshitter.
He's an absolute bullshitter.
He's a projector. He's the virgin. He's
skint. Um, and yeah,
he's skint as well.
He shows daddy savings.
He shows daddy's life savings.
Can't show now, can he, mate? No. Can't
show. No, mate. No.
No, you can't.
No, you can't. You little copy cat.
Hello, cubby cat.
Yeah, man. He was all right arguing with
people when their kids and [ __ ] um spaz,
but as soon as I turned a certain age,
he he played victim and started running
to the police.
Typical with these people, it mate.
Typical with these people.
Typical with these people. You never
ever meet me and project your [ __ ]
virginity onto me at this age, would
you, mate? Because you know you get
[ __ ] up. You get a slap.
You little virgin.
You little skin insecure virgin with a fragile ego.
Is that right, mate? He's got such a little ego.
Yeah, my dad's never beat me up. I only
saw my dad a couple of times. He's a liar.
Complete liar, bro. Complete and utter liar.
My dad's never beat anyone up. Yeah. [ __ ]
The only thing I ever told him was my
dad died when I was 11
and he wasn't even in my life anyways.
That's the only thing I told him cuz it
come up in conversation. He's a [ __ ] bullshitter.
And he was always chasing this [ __ ]
he was all he was always chasing this
[ __ ] girl in Canada that didn't want
him. Just didn't want him. Just didn't
want to know him. Just didn't want
nothing to do with him. Didn't want to
know him. And all he would do is
constantly talk about this [ __ ]
Britney from [ __ ] Canada. And she
[ __ ] know [ __ ] want you. Don't
know how many times I had to say she
don't want to know you.
She don't want you. Yeah.
He'll wait until until she [ __ ] wants
him. She'll never [ __ ] want him.
She'll never [ __ ] want you.
Never [ __ ] never [ __ ] want him. Never
[ __ ] want. No.
She She'll never want She'll never want me.
Never wanted me.
And why is he so obsessed with my sloppy seconds? Spaz.
He's so obsessed with my sloppy seconds.
All he does is convince himself that
I've not slept with them every day. It's
so weird. I don't care about these
people. Why does he keep going on about them?
Why does that virgin keep going on about
him? He needs to go get laid and get
himself some money so he's no longer a
skinned virgin. And none of these things
will bother him anymore. Franklin,
you like that, didn't you, Grezy?
But yeah, you get what I'm saying, mate.
Get you, mate.
You get what I'm saying, mate. Yeah. Vacuum me. Whoa. Franklin.
Franklin's gone flying. Greavves. He's
gone absolutely flying. Yep.
Why is this guy so obsessed with my sloppy seconds?
He's the only one that goes on about
USA, is he? I don't give a [ __ ] about
the [ __ ] We make jokes sometimes.
That's about it.
>> [clears throat]
>> Timmy literally drinks and gambles every
day. That is mad.
How can someone drink and and gamble
every day, bro?
How does he even get the money? Does he
just spend his benefits or something?
My McDonald's is almost here.
That's mad, bro.
So what? Greasy. Um, Timmy's addicted to
gambling and I'm addicted to cold
approaching. Is that what you're saying? >> [laughter] [screaming] >> Really?
The silly case.
Okay with you, boss.
Where's my bloody macke? I'm bloody hungry.
What are you doing, mama? Oh,
I heard you come up the stairs, mama.
And I don't know what happened.
You like the way I say that, Grezy?
What are you doing [ __ ] about by yourself? Mama,
if you don't be good, Ma. If you if you
misbehave, I'll give your Uggs to Next. >> [laughter] >> Sorry. Nah,
I'm sure next door will have him away, would they?
Some kind of will have that away, mate. [laughter]
Make sure Yeah. Whatever you do, they
don't leave it behind the bin. Mom, sorry.
Some god will have that away in it. [laughter]
I'm saying make sure. Yeah, because
someone will have it away in it. [laughter]
Some [ __ ] are on their way. [laughter] Daniel, [clears throat]
[laughter] I can't stop giggling, mama.
It's what I'm think. That's what Daniel
Thompson Sullivan said before. So, I'm
going that way.
It's an old saying that, is it, Mom? >> [laughter]
>> some that way, mate.
Where the bloody hell is my mackies? I'm
getting a bit hungry now. Oh,
somewhere completely different.
There's no signal in this area.
What happens is there's no signal in
this area and then they end up down there.
Comes cold. Huh?
I don't know. But something the signal
gets lost, I think.
>> What are you doing, man?
Sit out and be good.
Where the [ __ ] am This this. Okay.
They [ __ ] end up somewhere.
[ __ ] idiots, man.
Where the [ __ ] are these [ __ ] We
[ __ ] annoying. Why the [ __ ] do I
always end up there? My bloody mack is
He's asking me to call him. I'm going to One second. Sorry, mate.
He ended up by the [ __ ] A12.
The A12 or something.
The [ __ ] bloody [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] damp out there. Grey,
[clears throat] very very damp. Hurry up.
I wonder where do Ferraris is. He's gone. sake, man.
I got the goods.
I've got the goods moving.
Look at this. Captain
tips are a bit cold.
that. Well, they're a bit warm.
I was just captured.
Is this all right with you, Captain? Captain.
All right, Captain.
Oh my god.
The toothies are better now.
I don't have a problem with the toothies anymore.
What do you think about that, Captain?
One thing me and Grey agreed on is
McDonald's is lush and narcissist of Howard.
Isn't that right?
I can't say narcissist.
They get the white knights to fight
their battles, don't they? Boozy.
What's a waste of money? McDonald's. I love McDonald's.
Well, bless him then movie.
Bless him if he didn't want to feel left out.
Less him than if he didn't want to feel left out.
I think that's good to be honest. [clears throat]
M. This is yummy. Mhm.
I love the dentist. They help me. They
help my little toothies feel better.
When you come out the dentist, you're
just tired. I want you moving. [clears throat] M something.
Your skin a fing skin flint. M.
This is delicious.
This is lovely.
Absolutely lovely music. No.
Oh gosh, I'm so tired now. Woozy. Oh gosh.
We're checking one
Grezy, you're not trolling me, are you?
You're actually a genuine viewer.
You're a genuine viewer, aren't you,
Grezy? You're not trolling me.
You're not trolling me, are you greasy? No.
You don't trust. Oh gosh.
You like You like it, don't you, Greasy?
Thank you, Captain. You like that little
word, don't you?
You like that, don't you, Grezy? You all right, Captain? Oh, [ __ ]
I'm going to bed soon, Grezy. Is that
okay with you, boss? >> [sighs]
>> I love these kind of crazy.
>> Oh god.
>> Yeah, if you leave the Uggs by if they
leave the Uggs by the bin, some [ __ ]
would have that away, won't they, Greavvesy?
Can't have that away. [snorts] Oh gosh.
Well, I'm going I'll be back tomorrow.
I'm going Betty B now. Bye night.