D
There's Joseph Farra.
He's just another two weaker where he's
gone far. You reckon?
Bloody Joseph Farerra. Joseph Farah.
Joseph Josie Farra.
I'll come up with the best thing, you
know. Oh, look
that Bob account. E. Yeah.
Where's that bloody skin virgin? He's
been going he
the skin virgin can't bump bump. Oh, okay.
I might start going out every day
approaching, you know.
Don't really want to, but oh, [ __ ]
nothing better to do, mate. I end up
[ __ ] fat like [ __ ] L if I [ __ ]
stay in, mate.
For real, man.
I have the [ __ ] energy for it nowadays, though.
That bloody skin virgin.
He's the only incel. He's the one that
sits and dates disabled people. He's the incel.
He's the bloody incel. He's the one that
has to [ __ ] target disabled people
cuz you can't get anything normal. He's
[ __ ] more of an incel than I'll ever
be. [ __ ] virgin. So yeah. Yeah.
Right. Anything on the hinge?
Nope. Not a bloody sausage.
Not a bloody sausage, mate.
Not a blooming sausage.
[ __ ] hell, man.
[ __ ] tired, man. [ __ ] tired.
That's the thing though. It takes up so
much energy from you, man, when you go out approaching.
It's [ __ ] long, man. It's [ __ ]
long as [ __ ] bro.
I can't believe this is the lengths
people have to go through to to to get a
date. To be honest with you, it's
insane, bro. It's actually mad.
The people on Reddit. No, you just go on
the apps. They say you just go in the bloody apps,
you know, [ __ ] idiots.
It's not worth it at all, bro. But I'm
just like so bored in it.
I don't think Joseph Farah is ever going
to come back, is he? Nope.
Bloody Joseph Farah's never going to
come back then, is he?
Oh, Joseph Farra.
That's cute, isn't it? Joseph, that's cute.
What? That blooming virgin.
That blooming virgin. That blinking
[ __ ] hell, man.
He's a bloody virgin.
Big big bloody virgin.
Let me have a Yeah. Antman's
trying to bring me down to his level
again. Greavesy, I keep having to say to
him, there's no me and you.
There's only you. When you're talking
down about yourself, it's what you're
It's what you're thinking.
Oh, really? Send him my way, Gregy. Send
the [ __ ] my way, mate. I'll have a field
day with him, mate. Really?
Ant-Man trying to bring me to his level.
Grievy, there's no me and you. I keep
having to say there's no me and you.
There's no people doing better than me
and you. There's people doing better
than you. There's no me and you. I don't
know how many times I' about to say to
him, Gregy, that there's no
there's no me and you. There's only you
and you're talking about yourself. So,
yeah. But yeah, send the [ __ ] my way,
man. Send the [ __ ] my way.
Please do, son. Please do.
Thank you, Captain.
I [ __ ] g the cut out, mate. No, I'm
like I hate white knights.
I caught that money mic sing as well,
by the way. I've caught him sing on uh
what's the cunt's channel again?
Oh, what's that cunt's name now?
Yeah, I've caught him being a a dirty
little sip, mate. It's tomorrow.
It's not tomorrow. I never said it's
There must be in your head that it's
tomorrow this week, but it's not tomorrow.
I never said it was tomorrow.
Where is this?
No, I never said that. Nope.
Yeah, this money mic's a simp, bro. I
saw him on that. What's the What's the
channel called? That woman that uses filters.
What's that woman that uses filters, lad?
Which one? I want to use the filters.
No. [ __ ] Tik Tok.
No, the Sony's are in my um Yeah, he's a
S. And guess what? Do you know the
funniest thing is GG? He's probably a
virgin as well. He's probably like virgin boy.
Yeah, that guy is probably a virgin. You
do realize that? That's the irony of
these white knights and these simps is
that they're probably [ __ ] virgins.
Do you know that? Uh, greasy.
They're probably virgins. They think by
defending women, women will like them.
It's mad, isn't it? You would have
thought they would learn from each
other, but nope. You know, yeah.
Do you want to see the ugly boots when
they come, Grezy? Do you want to see the
ugly boots when they come?
Joe, I might just go out approaching all
day and then just get a curry at the end
of the day. Oh, [ __ ] hell. Then I can
actually say when I come back, Grezy,
what a [ __ ] day I had.
But would I actually be able to say it then?
Greasy. Would I actually be able to say then? Huh?
What a [ __ ] day I've had. Is it?
What a [ __ ] day I've had. I could
actually I would actually be able to say
that in it, Grezy.
I like Ticker.
I like chicken ticker. Is that cute?
Well, you don't like the approaches in
London by now. Why don't you like the
approaches in London?
Is it because it's always the same [ __ ]
or is it a different reason?
Yeah, that Ant-Man needs to stop trying
to bring me down. There's no me and you.
There's only you, bro. There's only you.
I don't compare myself to other people.
I don't care about Tik Tockers making
money or whatever. I don't bring me
down. He seems to bring everyone down to his level.
I don't know why he does it.
I just I don't understand. He's He's got
this obsession with comparing himself to other people. I mean,
it's madness, bro. It's really really madness.
Why does he do it, Grevy? It's so weird.
Why does he compare himself to other people?
It is weird, isn't it?
Why does he do that, bro?
Do not think it's strange.
And I said, "Yeah, there's there's no me
and you, bro. There's no me and you.
There's definitely no me and you."
So that's that.
Because I want to. Why not?
Isn't it grievous? Why not? It'd be a laugh.
Yeah, it' be a laugh, matey. Oh, boy.
It was your mom's [ __ ]
It was your mom's [ __ ] She's on her period.
Yeah, it was your mom's [ __ ] you
Yeah, it was your mom's [ __ ] She's on her period.
Sorry about that, bro. Yeah,
it was your mommy's [ __ ]
Yeah, you have got autism. It's not nice
to talk about yourself like that.
Yeah, you need to stop talking about
yourself like that. It's not good. Stop
putting yourself down.
Got no mates. Yep. Talking about yourself.
Yep. That's self projecting. Talking
about yourself. Try again.
Say something that's not self-
projecting, bro. We might take you serious.
Yep. you are special needs. Say
something that's not about yourself and
then come back to me.
Yeah. Then we might actually like take you serious.
That's why no one can take these people
serious because you just self project.
It's just something to laugh at.
No money you. No mates you. No life you.
Everything that you say is about
yourselves. That's why no one really
cares what what you say anymore.
Who lies about going to Thailand? I have
no idea because I'm not lying.
Who sits on YouTube all day every day in their 40s?
You do cuz you ain't got a life.
Yeah, you do because you ain't got a
life. You little spacker.
Who the [ __ ] sits on YouTube all day
every day in their [ __ ] 40s, 50s,
ain't got a life, can't take a day off of YouTube.
That's the real question. Yeah.
Why don't you join the Streamyard and
have a chat, man?
No, mate. That's you talking about
yourself. Got plenty of friends. People
have seen me. People see my friends.
Everything with you people is self-
projection. Let me guess, you came from
L J's channel. Typical with you self-p projectors.
All the self-p projected Mongs come from
that side of YouTube.
The skint lonely people, they come from
So, I'm not even in this community. I
just go live and [ __ ] you know, have people um
I mean really
that's it, man.
I'm never live all day. Self projection.
I'm never live all day. That's your
boyfriend, LJ. I'm never live all day.
I'm live twice a day maximum. Yeah.
Ew. A white knight.
Ew. I'd rather be a white knight simp
than a thirsty virgin himself. What are
you calling? Wait, hold on a minute.
You're call You're calling me a virgin
or you or do you mean in general?
Wait, you're calling me a virgin?
Oh, you do do you mean in general? One
second, lads. We're trying to have a
conversation. Just chill. So you're
calling me you're calling me a virgin?
You're calling me a virgin, right? Or
you or do you mean in general?
You must be talking in general because
you you can't be calling me a virgin.
Like you you can't be calling me a
virgin. You really really can't be
calling me a virgin.
You must mean in general, right?
Don't answer any of these questions. uh
Grezy this little [ __ ] If he's got
anything to say, he can come on the
hangouts. If you've got anything to say,
you can come on. You can come on the Streamyards.
That's that's fine. I can put the link
up. So, anyways,
I wake up, go to bed. No, no. I was out
all day Saturday. No, no. Anyways, um
Rudolph, uh one second. Um Rudolph, so
are you calling me a virgin?
Oh, you calling someone else cuz you
can't be calling me a virgin, mate. You
can't be called a me a virgin.
You must be You must be talking about
yourself. And I can I can back up what
I'm saying as well. I mean, yeah. No,
that's you by now. You wake up, you
spend all day on YouTube, and then you
go to bed. That's self projecting.
That's your life.
That's your life. You're on YouTube
right now, so you can't talk about
anyone. You're on YouTube right now, so
you can't talk about anyone.
You're on YouTube right now. Get off
YouTube. If you've got a life and you've
got all of these mates, get off YouTube.
That's how I end it with these people.
And the thing is, you can be a white
knight simp all you want, but it's never
going to get you laid. That's why women
don't like you. See, all of these white
knights, right, they think that it will
get them laid. They will sit there and
constantly defend women. And women don't
like them. And no matter how many times
you tell them, they still they still
don't get it because I think deep down it's autism.
And a lot of people have autism more
than you think. I think it's autism.
They think by defending women,
women will like them and sleep with
them, but they don't like them. That's
what I don't understand why they do it.
It's autism. It generally generally
generally generally is autism with these people.
And you're trying to call me a virgin
even though I put a porno up there.
Special deeds to the [ __ ] maximum.
This is why I don't show these people
money grievy. This is exactly what I
mean at like you can show these people
you [ __ ] and they'll still call you a
virgin. They're simple tin projectors.
They're not worth anyone's time. So when
they sit there and say, "Oh, you're
skin." Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Skin. Yep.
Yep. Yep. Because they're just serial self projectors,
you know. Anyways, why are you on
YouTube? Get off of YouTube.
You're sat there saying that I've you
know about me. Get off of YouTube. Go
see your mates that you don't have. Stop projecting.
Yeah. You can tell that I'm a virgin.
What? Even though I put a porno up there
and I've been in women's beds. Really?
So you can tell that I'm a virgin
because of how I act. Yeah, I've
literally proved I've had sex.
Simple thing. Projection.
self projection. No, that's you. You're
the 40-year-old virgin. Me? I proved
I've had sex.
No. The only virgin is you. And
defending women ain't going to get you
laid. They don't like you. Listen to me
when I'm saying this stuff, right? Trust me.
I've proved I've had sex. I put a porno
up there. I've been in women's beds. And
you're still calling me a virgin. Come on, man. Come on. Seriously.
Seriously. Now, these people are [ __ ] weird.
So, I'm a virgin even though I proved I'
had sex. Okay, bro. Yeah, I'm a virgin. Okay, man.
You'd rather be a white knight? Ew. A
white knight? A s.
A simp appears. I hate simps,
bro. How many white knights have I
[ __ ] stuck it on in my time, bro?
How many whites white knights have I
stuck it on in my time, Grezy? A [ __ ]
hell of a lot, bro. A hell of a lot, lad.
Yeah, I hate white knights, bro. I
[ __ ] hate him, bro.
And it's not even that. It's even people
that just get involved in people's
business. It's not even white knights,
bro. It's not even just white knights.
You remember that guy? He was saying,
"Is this weirdo bother you?" I said,
"I'm the weirdo bothering her." Yeah.
And you're going to do nothing, you
white knight. You [ __ ] white knight simp [ __ ]
I am the biggest weirdo and your white
knight s ass ain't going to do a damn
thing about it. You [ __ ] s [ __ ] And
you're going to do nothing.
Oh, Greavvesy, you love the content,
didn't you, man? Be honest. Grievy, you
love the content.
You loved the content when I [ __ ]
went out, didn't you? And [ __ ] stuck
it on them [ __ ]
Grezy. You loved it, didn't it?
You loved that, didn't you, Grezy?
Them four [ __ ]
So, you call me a virgin even though I
prove I've had sex.
Yep. Self- projection. This is all it is
with these people on here. It's just
constantly talking about themselves.
That's why I ban most people. I don't
let self projectors come on my chat.
People that talk negative about
themselves, calling themselves virgins,
calling themselves skin, bunch of people
talking about themselves.
Who bloody wants that, mate? Who bloody
[ __ ] wants that? We Yep.
Yeah, it was a lovely weekend to be fair.
[ __ ] hate white knights.
Oh, a s
Do you remember that? Greasy. Ew. A simp.
A wild A wild simp appears.
A wild s appears.
Am I Am I getting greedy with going out,
Grezy? Am I going Am I getting greedy
with going out?
That's what Laney said, isn't it?
Yeah, that's what Laney said.
I mean, it doesn't it doesn't matter. It
doesn't matter the way I react. I mean,
I've proved I've had sex.
So, I mean, again, this is part of your
disability. I think a lot of the
people's disabilities on here is they
get themselves confused with other people.
So when you're calling me a virgin,
you're actually talking about yourself,
but you don't actually realize that
you're talking about yourself. You're
talking about how I'm reacting. Well,
yeah. I think it's weird. I mean, I've
literally proved I've had sex and you're
still calling me a virgin.
I mean, yeah, I'm reacting because it's
just weird. I mean, I've proved I've had
sex multiple times and you're still
calling me a virgin because you're a virgin yourself.
And being a s is why you're a virgin.
Women don't like simps. They will never
get with you ever. You'd rather be a s,
right? Lick women's asses and they don't
like you. Then what? Be someone that's
not a s. I mean, which one would you
[ __ ] pick, Grezy?
Jesus [ __ ] Christ.
Uh, how have I? I've put a porno up.
I've shown me in bed with women.
Anyways, you keep self- projecting your
virginity, bro. All your life. See where
that gets you.
Little self projector. These people's disabilities
get themselves confused with other
people. It's part of their disability.
Like when they call people skin, when
they call people a virgin, uh when they
tell people they've got no mates, when
people have got anxiety, they're just
talking about themselves.
But they don't even realize it because
they're that disabled.
Yeah, man. Disabled virgins that ain't
got a life. That's why they're on here
all day, every day.
Trust me, bro. It's true. It's It's true
what I'm saying.
Have I ever been wrong about any of
these people in this community? Never.
Never. Potter. never ever you know.
So that's that starting it basically.
No, no, no. Your virginity definitely is
in question. You're a virgin.
You're a virgin. I proved I've had sex.
No. Your your virginity is definitely in
question because it's still there. Cuz
you're still a virgin.
Anyways, you need to grow up. How old
are you? 40s 40s 50s and you're sat sat
on YouTube calling me a virgin. Yeah, I
proved I've had sex.
What a loser. You need to go and do
something with your life, man. Proper
proper loser. Sat on YouTube in your 40s
and 50s projecting your virginity onto
other people. What a loser.
You must have the mind of a [ __ ] child.
What a [ __ ] loser. Imagine
somebody saying that they'd rather be a
white knight and a s. Take that [ __ ]
L, bro, and hold it. Hold it forever.
That is [ __ ] funny, bro.
You said you said you'd rather be a
white knight. That is [ __ ] hilarious, bro.
That is hilarious. Who the [ __ ] would
even say that? Jesus Christ.
Yeah, you need to get a life, you little
version. Get off of YouTube. How old are
you? 40s, 50s.
Yeah, we know I'm younger, bro. We know
that I'm younger than you. We know that
I'm better looking than you. We know
that I've got more than more of a life
than you. You should know all of this.
If you know me, you will know all of this.
Not some [ __ ] middle-aged fat wanker
sat on YouTube all day every day like you.
I agree with you. Do you remember Timmy
on the train yesterday?
I fell asleep to that. You know,
I fell asleep to that live stream. I was
watching it back. Yeah.
I'd rather be a s. What a loser. [ __ ] hell.
But guess what? You would never do it in
real life. Go ask them three guys in
Weather Spoons that tried to white knight.
They wouldn't even dare go anywhere near
me, bro. Everyone saw the video. So,
>> yeah. But again, bro, I don't I don't
care what people do with their life. I
don't even know why this comes up. If
you want to defend women all your life
and be a virgin, that's that's on you,
man. I don't care how people live their [ __ ] life.
Some people are content with that. It's
how they've been brought up.
Like this Rudolph guy, he he might be
happy being a virgin, licking women's
asses, getting old women.
Women don't like him, you know. A bit
like Virgin Boy. That's their life, bro.
They can live life
how they want, you know.
That's um that's on them, bro. I don't
give a [ __ ]
Same as the the open virgin. So yeah,
G, I think I need you to step in as my
financial advisor. I'm getting quite
greedy again with the restaurants and stuff.
I'm [ __ ] greedy as [ __ ] bro. I fancy
going to another restaurant today.
Can't be doing these kind of things, you lad.
I'm [ __ ] greedy as [ __ ] man.
Yeah, tell send them my way, bro. I'll
have a lovely debate with them.
I'm so greedy, man. So [ __ ] greedy.
Yeah, send the con.
This guy on uh Reddit posted, "I'm a
male, 25, I'm still virgin boy." Virgin
boy. I know a virgin boy.
I know a virgin boy. He lives in Kent in
a bedit. He's a virgin.
He's a big virgin.
I know a virgin boy.
We We all know a virgin boy.
We all know a virgin that's never been
anywhere near a woman sexually and never will.
You know, we know that. Yeah, man. Oh [ __ ] Yeah. What's up
But do you agree, Gregy, that Ant-Man
tries to bring me down to his level? Yeah. Yeah, 100%. Why not?
I just basically said to him straight,
bro, that like there's no me and you.
So stop saying me and you. There is
literally no me and you. There's only
So there's no me and you. I don't give a
[ __ ] about Tik Tockers making money or
not making money or people that are
skinned, people that are rich. So if you
want to compare yourself to other
people, right, that's on you, bro.
You know, there's no me and you. I don't
know how many times I have to say this.
It's [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. You know,
he's a [ __ ] he's a he's a he's he's a
I have to just say that he's taking a
piss in it. He's got to be taking the piss.
He's got to be taking the [ __ ] piss
in it. He has to be.
Jesus Christ. Oh, you little skin Flynn.
Oh, you little skin. You've never been
to Thailand because you're [ __ ] skin.
You have to [ __ ] beg for drinks and
Weber spoons cuz you're [ __ ] skin.
You must be one of the only Irish people
that have got absolutely [ __ ] all. Isn't
that right, mate? Isn't that [ __ ]
right? You got to be. You've absolutely
[ __ ] got to be, mate.
You know, skinted and a [ __ ] skinimp.
That's what you are, mate. You You're
like nons. Oh, well, sorry. He did
actually show his daddy savings. You
know, his daddy's life savings, but you
know, he's he's skinn. He's a bit like
you. Begging for drinks and Weber
spoons. Give it up, kid. You don't have
property. Your skin.
You've got six properties in Belfos, do
you really, mate? Well, how did that
come about? How the [ __ ] did that come
about? You know what are they worth? You
know, it doesn't make any sense.
You need to really, really step up with
your lies, man, because they don't make
any sense. You don't own no property. Shut up.
You got a bad back. You're on benefits.
You've never been to the continent of
Asia. Give it up, kid.
Give it up. Give up the lies. You talk
about [ __ ] Timothy Eldridge lying.
You You lie a lot. Actually, you're full
of lies. Pack of lies, you know. Pack of [ __ ] lies. D.
Isn't that right, Grezy? Pack of [ __ ] lies. Yeah.
I'm so addicted, bro, to [ __ ] these restaurants. Greasy.
I'm very, very addicted to going to
these little restaurants.
They're very addicting, lad. Yeah,
I like mint sauce.
I'm going this week. Yeah, I'm going on Saturday.
Okay with you, boss.
Is that okay with you, boss?
Yeah, I'm going on Saturday, boss. Is
that okay with you, boss?
Did you see Timmy drinking cans of beer
on a train? Who the [ __ ] bro? Who the
[ __ ] drinks cans of beer? Okay. Yeah,
you can buy it from the offlic license, but [ __ ]
like bottles, glass bottles. He he he
drinks [ __ ] cans of [ __ ] beer.
That is mental, bro.
Cans of [ __ ] beer. Jesus.
cans of [ __ ] beer, bro. Jesus. Yeah,
my fingers are a bit better now. Greasy, look.
Look easy. Bit better, aren't they?
Yeah, I bite my fingers.
I bite my fingers, Grezy. It's just a
habit I've done for many, many years now.
Do you like that little voice, Grezy?
What are you up to today, Greavves? You
just staying indoors.
Oh, you just staying indoors, boss.
I might go butchers and do some
approaches in the mall. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know.
Don't know what the [ __ ] I'm doing, bro. Um
well it's pointless approaching is it but yeah
it's just pointless
but it will never change.
Yeah he spent £150 to get his iPhone
fixed. Remember Grezy? Uh,
well, it will never change, will it?
It will never change. So,
don't forget, Greasy, we've got Kingy
coming. We've got Kingy coming, don't
we? We got Kingy coming on Friday.
You all right, Captain? Captain.
Yeah, King is coming for a sleepover.
You like it when King comes by, don't you, Greasy?
What should I do today? Homemade
burgers, t-bone, steak, or what? What
should I do?
I'm trying to think what I should do, bro. Um so
I'm trying to Think
what would you like to see? Gym made
burgers. T-Bone steak.
I'm trying to think, man.
I don't know.
You want to see a homemade some homemade burgers? Grezy good. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. Well, I'm going to get going
anyway. Sort myself out. I'll be back
later for some
do some homemade burgers. Okay with you, boss.
Oh, no, no, no, no. We got to get crispy
onions. There's crispy onions. Uh,
there's actually crispy onions,
but I'll be back later anyways.