I'm just using my other number now so
these little stalkers can't get through to
me. Stalkers can't get through to me,
buddy. You want me to comply with you?
How about you [ __ ] suck your disabled
dad's kick when I think about it? Don't
get stalled by your mommy again. Maybe
when you get starved by your mom again
and you suck your dad's dick, I might
comply with you. Look, [ __ ] Don't
[ __ ] sit there in your little tent
[ __ ] little bed sit on the ground a
month and try and dictate dictate to me.
Don't sit on that virgin bedsit in your
little ground a month flat trying to
dictate to me, rat boy. [ __ ] off and
suck your disabled dad's dick. How about
that one? You [ __ ]
[ __ ] You are [ __ ] having a laugh.
You think you're going to sit there with
your virgin bedsit with no bed in it and
[ __ ] dictate to me, you silly little
rat face [ __ ] Are you having a
wank? Are you having a [ __ ] two Tommy
wanks, mate? Good luck trying to call me
now. Anyways, I got two numbers.
Switzerland. Bye again, buddy. You are
having a Tommy [ __ ] tank. Don't
[ __ ] sit there and try and dictate to
me, you ugly [ __ ] You ugly lanky [ __ ]
with a fat ugly girlfriend. Everyone
knows my [ __ ] sayings, bro. Don't you
dare make YouTube videos on me in your
[ __ ] virgin bed sit with your rat
face, you ugly [ __ ] I'm coming off
YouTube tomorrow anyways. So have fun
and you ain't got my number anymore.
[ __ ] stalkers. Absolute [ __ ] stalkers, mate.
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. These people are
stalking me hardcore, Harry. Bro,
they're stalking me [ __ ] hardcore. I
had to like switch my um sim. I got two
Sims on the in the phone. It's a
madness, bro. These people keep stalking
me, man. It's [ __ ] I'm coming off
YouTube tomorrow, bro, for a couple of weeks.
So, probably about two, three weeks,
buddy. Yeah, I I got this woman to meet tomorrow as
well. Yeah, I got [ __ ] to be doing
tomorrow, man. I was on the pitch last night. So,
uh and and you know, the thing is,
Harry, I was just sat there thinking I
might as well just give it a whirl,
would it? I would. I [ __ ] would give it a
whirl. I [ __ ] would. He's proper
obsessed with me, bro. I'm leaving
YouTube for two, three weeks.
One second, bro. Let me just back up this
[ __ ] Yeah, but I got two numbers. I've
got a phone that's got two slots on it,
so they can't even get through to me
anymore. Sad little B. Sad little
bastards. Yeah, I got two numbers, don't
I, bro? So, it's all good. It's all
good. Proper obsessed with me, man.
He needs to go lose his [ __ ]
virginity. Get off of YouTube. [ __ ]
virgin. Got this woman to be seen. He doesn't. She's
autism. But yeah, Gary, it was
definitely worth a
while [ __ ] You think you're going to
sit there in your little council bedsit,
but your virgin face, you little rat
[ __ ] and dictate to me you and your rat
face with your ugly fat girlfriend is
going to dictate to me. Go and have a wanky
wanker. Go and suck your dad's disabled
dick. You might actually lose your
virginity, mate, by doing that. [ __ ]
try and dictate to me, you ugly [ __ ]
like you suck my dick. You can put
whatever you want out there, you
obsessed little [ __ ] Get a life, get
a grip, go lose your
virginity. So, yeah, I'll be off
tomorrow cuz I need to um Yeah, it's
perfect. Back up some stuff.
He takes it out on the world that his
mommy starved in. His mommy starved in
and his dad and her and her boyfriend
slap the [ __ ] out of him. The only one
that's been bullied is him by his mom's
dad. You know what I'm saying? Philip
Campbell of Leads. If you look him up,
Philip Campbell leadeds, he's the first
person that comes up. He had you up
against the wall and you were spitting
yourself and he tried to make an excuse
like me yesterday. I won't [ __ ] myself.
I said to the Scottish guy, I put my
feet where I want and I stayed where I [ __ ] was. You
know that's it, mate. No one could ever
[ __ ] themsel as much as you, mate. Not
even in the [ __ ] same [ __ ] road as
you, mate. You know what I'm saying?
[ __ ] off, man.
You need to go and [ __ ] pop that
virginity boy. You'll be a much happier
person, mate. He's jealous of loads of
things. More money than him, better
looking than him, had more women than
him. Think about it. Been abroad unlike
him. Got teeth unlike him. Not a lanky
stringy yellow piss like him. Of course,
bro. Yeah. I spoke to my sister today as
well. Actually, she called me. Yeah. I
don't have a dysfunctional family.
Yeah, that's what it's my sister say
actually. We'll see her soon. These
people on YouTube don't know nothing,
mate. These people on YouTube don't know [ __ ]
nothing. But yeah, and it's probably
good to come off YouTube for all, but
anyways, for my own safety cuz these
people are beyond
obsessed. Beyond obsessed. But what I
don't understand is this guy does not
know where I live. But why is he trying
to find out where you live? Because
every time you go to his area, he
screams how he's not a fighter and he
runs to the police. So why are you
trying to find out where someone lives
and you will never know where I live?
And why would you want to know where I
live? You're never going to go in
anyone's door. You couldn't even meet me
three times when I went to your virgin
area. Like the [ __ ]
man. Give your [ __ ] head a good old
wobble. doesn't make no sense. The whole
purpose, right, to find someone's
address is to actually go on a door.
Well, yeah, most time. But you're not
ever going to do that. You're just going
to be a little YouTube keyboard warrior,
you know, and everyone's sick of it now. It's
boring. Same projectors. And I need to
meet this woman tomorrow as well, so I
need to focus on this, you
know. Children's never had an American,
has he, Gary? Me? I've had I've had a
few, but I'm the ugly one. Remember, I'm
the M. Even though I've had better women
than him, way better than him. I'm the
M. Isn't that a madness? Eh, and all he
has ever been with is disabled.
Crazy, isn't it? But I'm the M. Remember
that, Gary? I'm the M. The biggest M of all time.
Yeah. Okay, buddy. That's why you have
to resort to vulnerable people.
What I found so weird yesterday, Gary,
is I went to the club and I got I don't
know how many I think I done about four
or five approaches. I got nothing. Just
same I got a boyfriend, same old [ __ ]
And as soon as I went out on the street
on the first one, bam, I'm in. Like, but
isn't it that people tell you that you
need to go to bars and clubs? They've
got it they've got it the wrong They got
it the wrong way around, buddy. They have a
around. They definitely do. I'm
saying that is crazy today.
Yep. The street is your best bet. But
the problem with the street is you can
only do so many sober cuz you'll just
get fed up of it. I mean that was the
first one I done and the only one I
done. So just right place right
time. But you you can only do it for so
long like sober because after a while it
just gets balling bro. If I do eight
approaches sober I'll get one number
then I'll just give up. I was like oh
[ __ ] it then I'll just go on the
drink. It's not as easy as that. Trust
me, it's not as easy as that, bro. And
like it will get waste time having a
conversation with someone only for them
to say they've got a
boyfriend. Trust me, bro. It's like it
it will just exhaust you, bro. Trust me.
It takes a lot of energy. Like, it's
it's a full-time
job. It's no different than it's it's no
different than a full-time job. You do
realize that. You burn a lot of energy.
You eat a lot of food because you need
the energy. it. I don't think you understand. It's
hard. Like, this is my first date. I've
got two dates scheduled
for this whole year,
bro. That's terrible,
man. I don't think I've had a date. They should
know. Yep, she was. But now another USA
is But they're ones that I just done,
not expecting anything to happen.
Yeah, they've all been most of them have
been from the street. The
19year-old, that one, that one. They've
all really been from the street to be
fair. I think was from a club. The other
one was from a club, but
yeah, it's mad, lad. It is. But after
like seven, but after like seven or
eight, I think I got too sober the other
day, but I must have done about 18
approaches. Oh, it was [ __ ] hard,
bro. It was hard. I don't like 18 sober,
but it was so not scary, but just like
the energy, you know, like it's um it
takes up a lot of
energy. Yeah. Mike Buffet. Yeah.
[ __ ] me, lad. Had a nice breakfast. But
yeah. Yep. USA. He was from the street
just like a lot of them
was. Another woman that I've been with
that Sean's obsessed
with. Do you know why he gets obsessed
with the women that I've not even you
know do you know that one from
Manchester? Do you know Do you know why
Gary he gets obsessed with these people?
It's because he knows that he can't get
attention from these women. He can't get
these women. Why? Because he's ugly and
he's autistic. So that's why he hates
saying that like you ain't slept with
them because he will never sleep with
them because he will never get with them
and he has never got with them. That's
why he does all of that stuff, bro. He
doesn't he doesn't do it to annoy
people. He genuinely does it because he is
jealous, you know, and that's and and he
is the only one on this community that
that has done it apart from any of them.
Think about it, bro. Listen, he has to
go to these old man events full of
autistic people. He doesn't even go to normal places, you
know? Yeah. I won 20 on fish and frenzy.
Need to get him in link. Huh? I'm not
getting that [ __ ] virgin. He's not
getting attention on my channel. Oh, I
got a date tomorrow, Joe, with that
American I was spending time with
yesterday. Yeah. It only took about a million years.
Yeah. Yeah. I won I I won um money won
20 pound. I went to the pub and had a
coke. Oh, yeah. Um, I fancied a [ __ ]
today, but I can't do it for two reasons
because I don't really have money to be wasting. And
um, obviously I'm meeting this woman tomorrow,
so it would never happen. His ugly looks won't allow
it. His ugly looks will never allow it.
And his autism won't allow
it. I did
sp Yeah. And she's from America, man.
Another [ __ ] American one. See, I was
a bit scared at first when she said
she's from America. I was like, "Oh, not
again. Not a [ __ ] game,
bro." But I didn't get anything from the
bar. They just all had boyfriends
apparently. All had boyfriends, even the
not so good-looking
ones. I was like, and I lost 100 pound
on Fishing Frenzy. And I was like, "Fuck
this. I'm getting a number before I go
that, you know.
Yeah, I'm not showing you. Are you
[ __ ] mad? Hell no, bro. She's not
from Boston. I'm not going to say where
she from. You know, she's American. I'm
not [ __ ] showing, mate. You think I'm
going to [ __ ] show you a [ __ ]
woman when you got [ __ ] Virgin Sea on
the loose? The creepy virgin. [ __ ]
have a word with yourself, mate. When we
got a [ __ ] virgin on the loose.
When we got virgin
Sean, [ __ ] off, mate. What? You got You
got the biggest virgin stalker on here.
Are you [ __ ] mad,
mate? You can get [ __ ]
mate. Um, actually, you didn't change my
number. I actually just switched my
number. I've got two numbers. Try again.
I didn't even change my number. I didn't
even change my number, man. Hey, I
didn't even change my number. I just
switched it over to my other number.
I've got two numbers. I just switched
the SIMs on the device. So, yeah,
without even without it didn't even take
one second. So, try again,
buddy. Yep. Try again. You didn't make
me change my number. Yeah.
Anyways. Yep. Try again, man.
Yep. I've actually got money here to be
fair. My pocket, but I'm not showing no on anything. So, yeah.
Yeah. Remember, Gary, if you don't like
shovel cole, you're
gay. If you don't like shovel cole,
you're gay. Nope. I'm never playing the
money game ever again. I'm not showing you people
nothing. And you can hear it's money as
well. Look. No, I'm not showing you
nothing, mate. There's no point. I've
already won the money game. I showed
[ __ ] 5.7 grand. I don't need to play
no money game anymore until someone beats me. Anyways,
um yeah, is a real person. Yeah, he's
[ __ ] ugly. I need to get my haircut
tomorrow as well before meeting this
woman. Oh boy.
Baby Peter from America can still be on
the cards. Baby Peter from America can
still be on the cards. [ __ ] me.
Yeah, I might get a nice Thai coffee
today, bro. P our stomach right up.
Yeah. Yeah, man.
That copper tea is
cold. And you
fly. Nah. [ __ ] Am I taking her to a
fancy restaurant, bro? I don't spend money on
hoes. Nah. [ __ ] no,
bro. [ __ ] no.
No. Hell no,
bro. Them days are done,
mate. Them days are done. But
yeah, just like the good old days.
Burger Lobandos. Nah, man.
Nah, I think she wanted to [ __ ] but I
didn't want to I didn't want to push it
like the first time we meet him, but I
think they would there,
bro. I'll probably try and [ __ ] him,
bro, to be honest when I meet him
tomorrow. We need to have a baby, man,
to make that [ __ ] We need to make
that [ __ ] virgin jealous,
man. Could you imagine having a baby
with an American?
Oh, mate. He literally would kill
himself. He would kill himself, bro.
Literally, he would kill himself out of jealousy. [ __ ] virgin. Yeah. Crazy, man.
[ __ ] I'll never get a USA, is he?
Well, I had one yesterday. I've already
had one and I'm going get another one
tomorrow. Try again,
buddy. Nah, that's what Sean does.
That's what Sean Listen, listen. Let me
tell you something. Um, Harry. Yeah. I
met this virgin. I met this virgin,
right? I met this [ __ ] virgin,
right, [ __ ] 11 years ago, and he's
still obsessed. How about that one,
Harry? He's still obsessed. He still
goes on about madeup stories that that
kind of autism, right? Needs needs
sectioning, bro. Needs sectioning. I'm
not even joking. Imagine that 11 years
ago, bro. Imagine that 11 years ago. And
he is still
obsessed. He's still obsessed. Imagine
that one, bro. Still obsessed. It's
crazy, isn't it?
Yeah, it's [ __ ] up,
bro. Yeah, you keep telling yourself
that, buddy. You keep telling yourself that. Yeah. Okay.
I'm sleepy, man. The drinks really got
to Peter Bennett, man. See, this is why
you do Thursday and Saturday. You don't
do Friday and Saturday, cuz you don't
have time to
recover. Peter, there's no reason to
keep talking about you, Peter. You got
about No, no, no, no, no. I went No, no.
I went on about that Morgan, right?
Because I actually got with her. I
actually [ __ ] her and she gave me
false hope and then she tried making up
stories about me. Yeah. Which I didn't
like. That's why I went on about them.
That's why I went on about them. Yeah.
So, no, he he really doesn't have a
reason to. He doesn't have a reason to,
you know, cuz Okay, if you want to go
around that logic, am I still talking
about them? Am I still trying to meet
them? No. But he's obsessed with me
every single day.
Do you see me posting about this [ __ ] in
America every day? No. No. No. And when
I did used to do it, it wasn't constant.
It'd be like every month, every two
months. Not like that. And it wasn't 11
years later, man. And big difference.
And that was a woman.
Yeah. I am not a [ __ ] woman. So what
are you gay then? So you must be gay in
it. You must be [ __ ]
gay. Yeah. You must be gay. That was
somebody I got with, you
know, and I didn't like I didn't like
what they done and it was
annoying. So, I had to, bro. You know,
that's it. It's a big difference, bro.
But I don't go on about anymore, do
I? You know what I'm saying? You see me
going on about Conrad every day? No. Do
you see me going on about Monty every
day? No. Think about it, bro. doesn't make
sense. So, he doesn't have a reason to
keep talking about people. He's
obsessed. Unless you're gay or you get,
you know, you gay or something,
bro. Maybe you're gay in it. You're gay.
Just saying it, bro.
What was I saying,
bro? I'm surprised she wants to meet
again. I thought she was just going to
ghost me to be fair, but
nah, maybe she doesn't have any friends in London
or Yeah, we had a little hug.
Goodbye. Yeah, it was nice, bro.
She can't consent. Well, he's never had
sex with her. He's never had her. He's
never slept with her ever. He's still a
virgin. But, um, theoretically, no, she can't
consent. And, you know, when you keep
saying that he's got a relationship,
he's got a relationship. I would rather
have no relationship my whole life than
be with with that. I'd rather never have a relationship.
I'd rather never be I'd rather never
have a relationship than be with that.
You know, listen, he ain't been abroad.
He's got no money. He's never been out
of England. His life sucks, you
know. And like I was saying to you
earlier, I couldn't even be in a
relationship anyways because when I go
solo traveling, how can I be in a
relationship when I go solo traveling?
You know, it's not going to work.
So, I'd rather have no
one because you can say with Natalie G.
Yeah. Oh, um, you know, if you had seven
beers, seven beers, seven beers, right?
I still wouldn't go near her. Even if I
had 10 beers, I I swear to God, I
wouldn't. Maybe. Who Who would I with? I don't [ __ ]
know, bro. Natalie G, it could maybe
happen, you know?
You know what I'm saying,
bro? I would never get with that. And
you can tell Joe that he's not happy
with her and he wants better, but he
can't get better cuz he's ugly and he's
autistic. Why do you think he goes on
about Morgan? Why do you think he goes
on about Izzy? Because he wishes because
he wishes that was him that had
them. You know what I'm saying? What
about that trendy lady? Yeah, she
weren't trying. And she is way better
than Sarah. No, she is not as bad as
Sarah. She is not as bad as Sarah at
all. Not one little bit is she as bad as
Sarah. [ __ ] no. Hell the [ __ ]
no. You know, so I'd rather have
nothing. I'm not even joking. I would
rather have nothing. I would never go
there, bro. I swear to God. If I did, I
would tell you I would. [ __ ] mate. [ __ ]
man. Who's Lady Zed? I don't know who
that is. Who the [ __ ] is
that? Lady Zed? Don't know who that
is. It's like some like Scottish Stacy.
Stacy. If I was drinking probably I
would if I was if I was that [ __ ] and
they started coming on to me I probably
would. But I'm saying not no not Sarah. Not
Sarah. Nah bro. No
way. And I think Sean will be that 19y
old as well cuz that 19y old was quite
cute. Don't know who it
is. Um yeah that 19year-old's better
than Sarah. Like every woman I've been
with is better than than his girlfriend.
But I'm the ugly one. And this is what
I'm going to say. It doesn't make any
sense. I'm the ugly one, yet all the
women I have had is better than anything
he's ever had. How does that make sense?
Every single one of them. It's
crazy. He's restricted with his autism. Yeah.
Definitely. Why myself over, bro? I'm
going to have to have another shower
later. Get some more. Have a nice
curry. I was spend 50. I spent like 200 quid.
What? That [ __ ] fishing crazy, man. Nah, nah,
bro. Yeah, his autism restricts him from
meeting normal women. And um also
um he's his ugly looks restricts him as
well cuz he's an ugly
[ __ ] He's an ugly bastard.
He was with a single bum
before. I tell you the video that
triggered him. I tell you the video that
triggered that version, Gary. It's when
I bought that new Stony, right? The one,
the first one I bought. And I went out
on a Thursday with a nice trainers. And
I was like, should I approach this
person? So, I just approached this
person. And she was like, do you want my
number? He got [ __ ] mad, bro. He done
a whole community post on it. He done a
whole community post on it before we
even met up again. He went [ __ ] crazy
because you you got to understand, you
have met this
person quite a few times, you know, when
you when you were younger and he hates
to see the fact that you're better
looking than him, you got more money
than him, you've had more women than
him, and you're three years younger than
him, you know, and he can't he can't
stand these things. So he has like a
epilepsic ep episode in his brain and
then that's what it is. It's because
where he has met you
um when when you when you were younger
you're better than him and you're
younger than him and he can't stand it
and that's why he does what he does
every day. That's the truest um words
spoken cuz think about it bro think really really
logically. in every way, you know. He
got so mad, bro. He got so mad. Oh, man.
He used to go mad, bro. Like when I used
to meet Izzy as well. But remember when
I used to meet Izzy, Gary? I'll never
forget it, bro. I used to have hate on
YouTube. I used to have hate on YouTube,
right? Mustard, everyone. And you know
what? Yeah. That day Izzy met me, you
might not remember it, like [ __ ] five
years ago, right? Six years ago, baby.
People was like, "Oh,
congratulations. Congratulations." Pat
Mustard was like, "Oh,
congratulations." People was like being
all right and stuff, man. You know, and
Sean was like, "No, you didn't [ __ ] her.
You didn't [ __ ] her. There's no evidence
that you didn't [ __ ] her." All because
Britney didn't sleep with him and she
rejected him. It's like his mom stove
him. Everyone gets to blame for it.
And then times when I used to bang
escorts, he never used to believe me.
Well, he did believe me, but he just
convinced himself I didn't have sex
because he's still a virgin. He was
still a virgin and he is still a virgin.
He used to say, "You haven't slept with
Escort. They ask you for ID. They ask
you for ID." I was like, "No, they
literally don't." Um, I have I have
literally, right, I have used escorts
many, many times. I have done it since I
was 17. Probably more than most people
my age. A lot of people probably do it,
but they just don't. I swear to God,
bro. I went to a a brass house about two
months ago. I see a black guy come out.
And you would have thought, "Oh, black
guy doesn't need to pay." People do it,
bro. They just don't tell you they do
it. It's the oldest oldest tradition
going. And he used to try and say to me,
he used to try and say to me that, "Oh,
no. It never happened. It never
happened." I was like, "What do you mean
it never happens?" And then my mama
said, "Yeah, it did happen." Um because
she caught me once. So that's how you
know he is a
virgin because he's been using the same
insult since he was like 21. And the
only virgin is him, you know. So that's
why he calls people a virgin cuz he's
one himself. He's probably he probably
has that. Um my friend had a problem
with his dick. Um had to go to I think
it was St. George's Hospital.
Um, and uh uh it was St. George. I went
with him, not in the room with him, but
I went to with him to support him in
that cuz I don't think he liked
hospitals and stuff. So, I went to the
um hospital with him, not in like the
room where they check his dick, but I
was like, "Okay, I'll come and support
you, whatever." And um I think it was
St. uh I think it's uh it's um St. Yeah,
it's St. George is in Twitter. So that's
probably what Sean's got. He Think about
it, man. How can he possibly have sex
with his girlfriend if he's online every
day stalking me? There's no there's only
so many hours in a
day. But that's what makes me think is
that even when you proved it, he's still
calling you a
virgin. That's cuz he's one himself.
Simple. That's because he's a virgin
himself. He's like, "Oh, well, yeah.
What? You masturbated three, four times
a day. It sounds like something a virgin
would do. Well, you'd know you are the
virgin. So, you tell us. You like my
little reverse jo. It's sick, isn't
it? You know what I'm saying? See, he is
actually a virgin. Me, I'm not. I've
walked up to I've gone into [ __ ] the
red light district going up the stairs
in Amsterdam. I've shown videos of me
getting my dick sucked. I have shown
videos of me in bed with women in man a
woman in Manchester. I have shown a
video of me in a hotel room in London. I
have shown me of me in a hotel um room
with a woman in Nottingham that
literally admits that she has had sex
with me and you still call me a virgin.
That's because you're one yourself. No
one cares that you've had a [ __ ]
[ __ ] you know, not I don't do it as
much anymore. I've calmed
down. Like I fancy a [ __ ] today, but
I just go without. I don't care, bro.
I've sort of just like calmed down now.
Yeah, I've just sort of calmed down now to be
fair. I don't really care about the
women. I just go out and send it because
Yeah, I know you can't. That's why I'm
not doing it because I might be getting sex
tomorrow. You never know, bro. And and
it would always happen as well. I tell
you what. Yeah. This is the most [ __ ]
up thing about it. Like going on a night
out. Yeah. If the day that you would
pull was the day that you masturbated three
times, that's like you'll masturbate
like two or three times. You'll go out
and then you'll actually get laid when
you've masturbated and you basically can't prov
perform. So, you know what I'm saying?
It's like I wish I could predict the
[ __ ] future because I would have done
it for three [ __ ]
days like with Sig, like when I was [ __ ]
Sig, you know? But um yeah, yeah, it has
happened before. I still came in the end
obviously, but you don't know when
you're going to get laid because 99% of
the time when you go out, what happens?
You don't get laid. So you're expecting,
oh, I'm just going to go out and get
some numbers for another time and then you get
laid. You know, you you can't predict.
So that's and that's the problem with
it. Guess you could eat loads of eggs
every time you go out, maybe, but it's
hard. Yeah. I've never had a woman
apparently. Apparently I'm a virgin.
N I've got a date tomorrow with this
woman. Ah, you and your little ways. Bye-bye. Bye-bye. [Applause]
Yeah, but Chase was trying to get
information out of me and I would never
tell him because I knew that was a
thing. Like he was trying to ask where I
live and this that and the other and I
would never tell him cuz I had it in my
mind that yeah, he might he might, you
know, do something and that. So I told
him about the gambling and his videos
would be spitting on the machine. Yeah,
go put it up. I don't give a [ __ ] But
no, um nothing else. Yeah.
cuz I knew like that there's a chance of obviously that
happens. The only people I tell people
the only person I tell people things is
Ant-Man and I don't tell him everything. You
know, how do you think people get
killed? How do you think people get
robbed for their [ __ ] Rolexes, man?
Because they tell people too much. You
know what I'm saying? They don't tell people nothing.
It wasn't last year. It was the year
before that. Yeah, I do remember it. I
need to go back to be fair.
Yeah. I hope that French one meets me
though. I really want Baby Pierre from
Paris. Gary. Baby
Pierre. Oh, bless
you. Yeah. Did you watch you? I was I
was messaging Ant-Man last night. He was like,
"The got I said to him, bro, I [ __ ]
He's like, "How's your night going?" I
was like, "I approached four people.
They all got boyfriend." [Music]
Yeah. Yeah. I didn't cry. I got mad because it's
annoying. I don't think these people
will understand. It's not about the
amount of money you lose, Gary. It's
just annoying losing. I don't No matter
how many times you try and explain it.
Yeah. They don't listen. They see it as,
"Oh, well, it's just 20 pound gone." No,
bro. You put 20 pound in the machine.
It's [ __ ] with you. It [ __ ] with
your head. And now you're pissed
off. I'm saying that was You don't know
where I live, buddy. You do not know
where I live.
You don't know where I live and you will
never know where I live. So keep trying.
You try hard. You will never know where
I live. But I am definitely coming off
YouTube tomorrow. Anyways, I'm going to
go see this woman and
um yeah, I got some stuff to
do. Probably on here entertaining
[ __ ] bongs, you know. Oh
[ __ ] I'm watching that. Get these clothes [Music]
ready. But guess what? I've had more
women than you, Jamie. How's
that? No. Women don't bother me. Women
don't hurt me. Women don't bother me at
all. It's just gambling that annoys
me. Mate, you can get entertainment
somewhere else. These people are too
obsessed, stro, I have to think about my
safety. Dam Thompson and Sean is very
very obsessed with me. I need to think
about my um It's about the principle. If
some guy stole one pound off of you,
you'd still be pissed off, right?
Uh no, no, no. It's very very different
with like even when I got my phone
robbed, right? Remember when I got my
phone robbed? I just put it down to
experience. I was like, "Shit, man. It
was I weren't even as angry as if I was
to lose 20 pound. It's gambling, bro.
It's hard to explain it unless you
you've done it yourself. It's annoying.
It gets under your head. It gets it
controls your whole body and your whole
mind. It's [ __ ] annoying, bro. It's
[ __ ] so annoying. Like, I can't I
can't explain it, bro. I can deal with a
women [ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] about
that, bro. I had yesterday. I've got a
boyfriend. I'm meeting someone tomorrow.
I literally don't care. that won't piss
me off. The [ __ ] that pisses me off is
gambling, you know? That's it. There's
nothing else. It's
gambling. That's the only thing that's
impossible to accept. I lost 100 pound
yesterday on fishing frenzy. I was going
[ __ ] mad, bro. And I was drunk as
well. It's annoying, bro. It's [ __ ] annoying.
That's why I always do it right at the
end of the
night. So like you're not going to ruin the
whole I wanted to watch that marching
powder, but I don't really really want
to watch it. But I could do with
watching it. That marching powder in the
cinema, but I don't know, man. I kind of
I want to watch it, but I don't.
Look at that ugly face. Look at that
ugly [ __ ] face. You ugly [ __ ] Go
through out your ugly face. You will
never know where I am, buddy. You will
never know where I am. I thought you
said I was in Plaster. You saw me in
Plaster. Make up your [ __ ] mind. You
will never know where I
am. But yeah, bro. I need um I need to
protect myself, bro, from these stalkers,
Gary. I have to protect myself from
these stalkers, lad.
If you don't find Gary
What was all of that about, bro?
Honestly, if you don't find shovel co
attractive, you're gay. What the [ __ ]
was that all about, bro? Sounds like a
trend. Well, it sounds like a trend.
That does. What do you think? Yeah,
that's a trend. That is little copycat,
aren't you? Oh, you little
copycat. You little copycat. Bye-bye.
You little You little
copycat. You're a little
copycat. Even though, right, you you you
were saying about Cheryl Cole being
attractive, you're still gay and people
still think you're
gay. That's some madness, bro. I
couldn't believe it when he was saying
that. He's literally just saying it to fit
in. Just saying it to fit in. Literally,
he's a copycat, bro. You're the little
copycat. You little
copycat. Literally no
originality. The only reason you like
Elvis Presley is because he's a nons like you are. [ __ ]
[ __ ] Sher car. The most average
looking person out there.
Yeah, it'd be nice not to get stalked
for like two weeks though. It be It
would be a lovely
feeling. [ __ ] all this [ __ ] D, bro.
[ __ ] me. I'm tired now, bro. I might
have to steam the shower
room. [ __ ] I'm hanging, bro. Why do we
have to get [ __ ] hangovers?
I'm [ __ ] [ __ ] Nothing a little
beef curry can't sort out though. It
nothing a little beef curry can't sort
out. Nothing a beef co
out. No, only humans can hang out with us.
Did you hear me in the pub yesterday,
Joe, with my feet up living a
life [ __ ] Scottish PR? I said, I'll
put my feet where I want, so I'll keep
doing it. That's what I said, you know,
put my feet where I [ __ ] want,
mate. Scottish prick.
You get a lot of Scottish people that go to that
uh that pub to be fair. Well, not You
get them, bro. You get
them. Everyone was being so rude to Peter
Belly. He was so rude, isn't
it? He was so
rude. But um see, they say that you
should mind your own business, but
people in London don't mind their own
business. They literally never mind
their own business. Like sometimes
you'll go and you approach a woman and
everyone will be looking like and
they'll stare, bro. And then they'll
butt in when like they'll butt in and
things that it's got nothing to do with
them. I thought that was a London thing
to get into people's
business because they seem to love doing
it so much. They've done it with me. But
the old guy did though, did he Bob? And
then I met an elderly gentleman, Bob.
Joe, do you remember the elderly gentleman? He
was He was a pretty good [ __ ] He
was Yeah. First time lucky. Somebody
that wasn't a [ __ ]
[ __ ] Somebody that wasn't a complete
eh? Good old Bob.
Robert. Yeah, he was a he was he was
a he was a gentle
man. He was a nice gentle man, wasn't
he, Joe? He was a lovely gentle
man. He was a lovely gentle
man. Yeah, he was a lovely gentleman. He [Music]
What's the most money you've ever lost
in one go? Gambling. 3k, 4k. Tell us. Tell
us. What do you think? Honestly, what's
what's the most you've ever
lost? Probably the 15th tomorrow. Oh [ __ ]
man. I need a I need a curry, bro. I
need a Chinese curry. A nice beef curry,
man. I love beef curry. Beef curry is the best
chicken. I bet you wanted to kill yourself. Yeah.
No, it's not funny because I went to I
was going to go cinema the other day and
the the I had to go somewhere and the
the mall that I was in they had the
bookies and I lost and I spat on the
machine and I literally just left
because I was getting paranoid bro like
cuz I didn't want to get lifted in it
cuz there security and police everywhere
so I just I was going to go cinema but I
was like no it's dodge I just I just sp
I got a video spat on it bro it was
disgusting she was like calling me saying, "Excuse
me." I don't know, bro. I don't care
about them, bro. Stop bringing them up
on my channel. [ __ ] bro. It's to be a
good year. It took me a good year to get sorted.
Wow. That's crazy, bro. I should show
you my new passport. It's brand spanking new. Yeah, [ __ ]
bro. I don't care about them anyways. [Music]
because a lot of people met Sean once
and never met him again like that Kenji.
I didn't trust him. There's loads and
loads and loads of things I didn't tell
him. He doesn't know where I live. He
doesn't know nothing.
Yeah, I might have said stop and spout
machines and show that, but I never told
him 95% of stuff, bro. Tell my business.
You know what I'm [Music]
saying? What the [ __ ] is [ __ ] shadow
or some [ __ ] bro? What the
atro [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] why are you too cowardly? Um the
same reason you're too cowardly when
I've come to every three times and you
would come out and I made you run to the
police station screaming
u screaming screaming how you're not a fighter.
The same way you were too cowardly to
come out when I was in your area three
times and you didn't meet me and you
claimed how you weren't a fighter. Yeah. Bye-bye.
Now you're going to be bored for two
weeks, mate. Cuz I'm coming off of
YouTube. You're going to be very, very
bored for two weeks. What are you going
to do for two weeks? You're still going
to be obsessed. I guarantee you, Gabby.
Yeah. Even when I'm off of YouTube for
two weeks, I swear to God, I'm not going
to go on. I'm deleting the app.
I'm going to What the [ __ ] is that, bro?
I'm deleting the app for
like Yeah, I'm going to delete the app.
I'm going to delete the app for a little bit.
Um, yeah. And I swear down I'll show
you. I'll delete the app. I'm not going
to check nothing. And I bet you I'll
come back in two weeks, go on all the
channels, and they've done it every day.
They're still stalking every day. I'm
going to delete the app, bro. the
streams thing is uh different, you know.
So, when I want to watch stuff, I'll just
um just search it manually on
browser or something like
that. He's going to [ __ ] bop
that up that virginity.
Yeah, I really want to w me.
But yeah, you keep telling yourself that
you don't have nothing. I need to um I
um I need to wank, bro. But I'm saving
my sperm tomorrow for this woman in case we bang. You
know, do you know what I'm saying, Gary? [ __ ]
hell. That's an
actual That's an actual [ __ ]
badness. You got weeks of content, mate.
You'll be talking to yourself cuz I
won't be on here for two weeks.
No man, I can't. I want to try and save
myself cuz I don't know. But you don't know these
things. Which Izzy are you talking
about? There's a few different Izzies,
Joe. Which one are you talking about?
Oh, he's just some attention seeker on
YouTube that hasn't got a
life who's obsessed with me, man. Just
just same old. I like your name, by the
way, bro. Well, which is he though?
There's a few different ones.
No, I've never masturbated over
um USA. Is
he? Maybe once, maybe twice. No, I'm joking, lad.
Nah. Nah, bro. I don't masturbate over
people, bro. Well, I don't need to
masturbate. already had the [Music]
[ __ ] Oh, two weeks. The horror films
coming out in two weeks, Joe.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm I'm uh You know what it
is, bro. Yeah. Uh, bye-bye now. Bye-bye
now. Nah, bye-bye now,
bro. No, I never I'm never going to the
cinema with someone. I don't want to go
to the cinema. She's only here for 2
months, so I've got to go [ __ ] America.
But I'm not going to the cinema with
someone. I had to go by myself. I just
would rather go by
myself. But I guess if you went with
someone, you know, Uncle B such could
come into effect. No, I just never been
on a date to a cinema. I don't see the
point in it. I do want to watch that
marching powder, but I'm more like a
horror thriller person, bro. You know, I
like I want to watch it, but I don't
want to watch it that bad. I wouldn't
want to pay money to actually see it.
Yeah, it's got that guy in it, but like
I wouldn't actually want to pay money
like a horror film. I I will watch a
horror film any day of the
week. You know what I'm saying? Any day of the
week. I love horror films, man. The way
it gives you
goosebumps. I just love horror
films. I just love horror films, bro.
You can't beat
them. Uh, hold
hands. Yeah. So, it was Yeah. Even you
were saying yesterday, Gabby, give it a
whirl. I thought could do. Yeah. Why not
give it a
whirl? It's all right sometimes to give
something a whirl, Joe. There's nothing
wrong with giving something a little
whirl. Know what I mean, bro?
Yeah, these people can't call me now. I switch
numbers. I can't believe when I used to
get like with women and that they like,
"Oh, what? You don't want to fuck?"
They'd give you a [ __ ] and they'd be
like, "Oh, what? So, you don't want to
fuck?" cuz they thought it was weird
that I just didn't want to [ __ ] and I
just wanted [ __ ] But um yeah. Yeah. [Music] Food.
Yeah. The fetch food. is expensive.
Bye-bye. Oh, there you go. You said the same thing.
Bye-bye. Listen, no matter what you put
up on your channel, right, you're not
going to get me back on YouTube after
today. I'm leaving for two, three weeks.
So, whatever you put up, well, no one
cares. I'll tell you exactly what I've
done. I've spat on two machines.
Um, got mad at this guy. Punch the
machine. I think we spoke about USA Izzy
a few times. That's literally all you
have. You don't have anything. Nobody
cares. Like, I will tell you everything
before you even put it up. I'd put it up
myself if I had half the chance. Go
away, you little virgin.
You know, learn to accept when people
don't want anything to do with you. This
two weeks will will give you a good
lesson. You know, he's going to be
forced to stop. Cuz I feel like Joe,
what is honestly the the the solution to
this? You put up posters, right? It's
not going to stop them. It will stop
them for two, three weeks, but then
they'll do it again. So, it's either
they go to prison, they end up dead, or
you ignore them. Because when you ignore
them, think it, they're wasting their
energy, they're wasting their life on
you, and you're living in their head.
So, any any of them three options will
do will work,
bro. You know, any of them three options would
work. Trust me, they're the ones that
are obsessed with you. They're the ones
that are already wast wasting their life
on you. So you already you already
winning, bro. You know, [Music]
literally I got this woman to the
meeting tomorrow as well.
What would happen if
women found out the women that I I was
meeting? Joe, what do you what do you think would
happen if he like found out like the
women that I've been meet like women
like potential women that I'm meeting?
Bye-bye. What do you What do you think
he would do,
Joe? This is what he would do, right? He would message
them to be fair.
Yeah, it does, bro. Yeah, it does get me
like that, bro. Well, you shouldn't know
that. That was weeks ago as
well. And the only reason I didn't go
back in and do that guy in Well, I
didn't run away from him anyways, is
because my mom said, "If you do it, I'll
never talk to you
again." Like, so I thought, "Fuck it."
Like, there was a time where I was near
a pub. This was like 3 days after I was
drinking when I chat with that bartender
and I was like, "I got a good mind to go
back in there, bro." Like all or
nothing. But I was just like, just allow
it in it. You know, even my was just
like, oh, allow it, allow it, allow it.
I was going to go back with a [ __ ]
hammer. I was just going to go back with a [ __ ]
hammer. I was going to go back with a [ __ ] hammer,
bro. You know, I swear to God I
was. I gave him my address and
everything. I said, "Why don't you come
after work, big man?" That's what I
said. I said, "Why don't
you come? Why don't you come after work
to my address? I gave him my
address instead of doing all this [ __ ]
on camera, you [ __ ] That's what I said to
him. But yeah, that was weeks ago, bro.
That was like That's got to be almost a month ago
now. No, it's annoying, bro. I wasn't in
tears. It's annoying. Losing is
annoying, bro. You should have took it
serious. How come people accept it? And
it is gambling because with the women
thing, I see it as like you do it.
You're going to get the same [ __ ] but
you do it anyways. You can accept the
women thing, but you can't accept the
gambling thing because it's so
annoying. Like, you never It's
impossible to feel any different. It's
literally impossible to feel any
different when you lose. It is. It is.
It generally is, man. And it will take
you like maybe 40 minutes to calm down.
I remember one time. Yeah. Sunday. Yeah.
I was around my
um around my mom's area. It was Sunday.
I remember. I think I lost I can't
remember how much. 100 50 something
silly like that. And I physically
couldn't calm down for like an hour and
a half. I swear to God. I couldn't sit still. I
literally I literally Yeah. couldn't sit still,
bro. Like I go [ __ ] mad. And then
eventually I calm down.
It's just annoying. It's just [ __ ]
annoying, you know? And it's not the
value of money because look, you can
give your mom three, four, £500. Would
it piss you off? No. So, it's gambling.
That's what I'm saying. It has to be. It
all points to gambling. You know, you
can't blame the women thing
anymore. Life is thought it's going to
be this way. It will always be this
way. There's nothing really you can do like to
um change it. You just do it in it. Like
it is what it is. But the gambling is so
different. It ruins your whole day. Like
even the other day when I was going to
go watch that Danny D film, I lost 40
quid. I just done a U-turn and went back
home. Like simple. No, that's it, bro.
It's annoying. Annoying as
[ __ ] It is so [ __ ] annoying, man. It
is annoying, bro. And I don't think you've got
ADHD because it only seems to be with
this gambling now, you
know. But it's not the amount you lose
cuz I used to hate losing on
FIFA. I used to go [ __ ] mad. I used
to lose on FIFA. I used to go [ __ ]
mad, bro. That's why I had to stop
playing it. I didn't like losing on FIFA.
I remember it, but I think it was FIFA
17 I used to play. Oh, that's the worst
game to lose on. I think I just don't like
losing. Doesn't matter what what it is.
So then if you don't like losing, you
shouldn't do it. You can't change how
you are, bro. If you like losing, okay,
simple. I used to play wrestling games
as well. I used to go [ __ ] mad,
bro. Nah. Nah. But it doesn't have to
be. You don't have to lose. Damn.
Losing. No, not in that way. Not in that
way. Not in that way, mate. Not in that
way. Cuz you don't need to lose. It
doesn't have to be that way. You know,
simple. Yeah. It's not about money,
mate. Again, it's not about the money.
I've explained this about a million
times. It's not about the money. But no
matter how many times I explain it, you
understand. So you keep thinking it's
the quantity of money, then bro, I can't help
you. It's not about the quantity of money. It's
annoying. Simple losing is annoying.
Losing money on them machines are not
part of life though. That's not a part of life.
life that is not a part can be a part of
life and it doesn't have to be that way.
It's not part of life.
mate. Women are always [ __ ] rude. I
dealt with rude
women. Listen, bro. Women are always
rude. What are you talking about?
Sometimes they're always rude.
London. Yeah, that's
London. That's westernized countries where you make all
rude. First of all, most of them are
[ __ ] I'm sleepy. I'm so tired, man. Why am
laughing? Get some food.
Yeah, I'm gone, but I'll be back live
later. Yeah, I'll be back late,
bro. What's up about that? Yeah.