[ __ ] madness. It will never change.
>> [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's a [ __ ]
>> It will never change. It will never change, bro.
Good old Thursday. [ __ ] laugh.
I'm [ __ ] going back, bro. I'm [ __ ]
knacking. I [ __ ] [ __ ]
They put me off wanting to go out Saturday, bro.
I know, bro. You stuck up [ __ ] in
this country. They [ __ ] put you off
wanting to go.
>> Anyone you think anyone can tell me anything?
Bro, they can't tell me another bro.
It ain't like that, bro. Will never be
like that, bro. It will never be like that.
>> [ __ ] madness.
Same old story, Candy man. Same old
Satong. As you know, lad, it will never
change. And I went to the most stuck up
area ever, bro. I went to like a
different area this time. Liverool
Street. All the [ __ ] are stuck up as
[ __ ] I'm on a pat trading, bro. I don't
give a [ __ ]
>> They're all stuck up [ __ ] and no
one's going to tell me nothing, bro.
>> Um, it was like, bro, it was a wor It
was bad area to be fair. It will never
change in this [ __ ] country full of
[ __ ] Can you hear me? Can you hear
me like well enough rail services?
I used to put this
You got DC. You got DC. All right, bro.
Tell the guy weap in. We'll have this
debate from the server. I'll wreck you
roughly. I will plot you a new hostile.
You're not more intelligent than me.
You'll never be more intelligent than
me. You [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
guy look pants. He's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
bro. He's a [ __ ] I'm saying this
straight on the train, but yeah.
He ain't about that life, bro. Trust me.
I'll message his mate. I've got a couple of his
I've got a couple of his mates on [ __ ] um
what's it, brother? socialist. See what
the guy's on. He ain't about nothing,
bro. He's a [ __ ] bro. Little posh
little [ __ ] [ __ ] He ain't at me,
bro. Trust me. Yeah. I'm not no Timmy
Elers. I'm not no [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
Do you understand?
[ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
[ __ ] absolute [ __ ] bro. [ __ ]
Where are we? I didn't know we're here,
but to be fair, what do we get? [ __ ]
Liver was bad, bro. [ __ ] hell.
They're for the They're [ __ ] in
this country. [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] NPC stuck up. [ __ ] man.
saying it straight though makes
straight bro you know
anyone try to move to me kind of let
anyone try to move to me bro Timmy is a
[ __ ] is a [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> he ain't about he ain't about that life
he will never be about that life believe
that he will never be that life
[ __ ] you [ __ ] [clears throat] bro.
>> I need a dance to this Saturday, bro.
Cuz I'm I've been put in a bad mood cuz
of this [ __ ] bro. Yeah. My ass
[ __ ] in it times before.
This is an service man. Nothing else forever.
When will it change? Never, bro. Never.
>> Yeah. Never, bro. Never. >> Change.
>> In the bar. He actually thought he was
intelligent, but he wasn't intelligent.
I whoop piece off, bro. Trust me.
>> Yeah, he really thought he was
intelligent, wasn't he?
Huh? Thank you.
>> Good for you.
>> So, you
to say that to someone that you don't
know, you must be a loser yourself to be fair.
>> You started on me, though.
>> I know. I've seen it. Yeah.
>> I don't Doesn't matter. Just be the
bigger man and just
>> If she says something to me, I'm gonna
say something to her.
>> She says something to me. I'm gonna say
something to her.
>> That destroy the character.
>> That's me defending myself, brother.
>> Defend yourself against what?
>> Talking [ __ ]
>> I'm just saying something back to her.
Is it? So, I'm allowed to say what I
want. What I want, brother.
>> Don't turn on me.
>> I'm not turning on you. I'm just telling
She's saying [ __ ] to me. I'm saying [ __ ]
back to her.
Okay, show you.
>> Thank you. Show you. [snorts]
>> She's the one being rude, bro.
>> No one's talking. No one's talking to
her. She's being rude. But if she wants
to be rude, I can say something about
her. That's my fault. Cool. Thank you. [snorts]
That's the thing with these people.
They've got attitude. They they can give
it a mouth, bro.
>> But they can't they can't give it back.
That's the thing, bro.
>> I understand.
>> That's the thing, though.
>> I [clears throat] understand. But at the
same time, just
>> you already know.
>> Good for you.
>> If you already know, you don't have to say to
>> I will defend myself.
>> You know what I'm saying? Like in in a
way though I would defend myself though. >> Yeah.
>> No, I miss you. Okay. Yeah.
>> This is the next stop and
>> I'm not being rude to you. I'm not saying
>> you don't have to deal with each other
in 30 seconds, bro.
>> Well, she should be rude to people then, should she?
>> I'm talking to someone else.
>> You know, said it. One, two, three, four, five.
>> Yeah, good. Leave it there.
>> Yeah, good for you.
>> Yeah, look at you as well.
>> Yeah, I saw you.
>> This is your
>> chill, bro. Get off the stop and leave.
>> Yeah, it's all you. So, get off the stop
and just leave me. >> Yeah.
between the training back [laughter]
>> I don't know him and I don't know >> exactly so precious
>> have a good night
>> precious man
>> look at you look at my
>> oh my god
>> yeah my trainers yeah >> understand
over 200 pound Yeah, >> cool.
>> You're [ __ ] embarrassing.
>> So you as well.
>> No one cares.
>> Okay, cool.
>> Yeah, thank you. You come out, but you
can't pay just now. See you later. See
you later. Byebye.
>> She tired, bro. I won't talk to No, I
won't talk to her.
>> I'll just watch this.