[clears throat] [snorts] Oh, [ __ ] boy. >> Oh,
that [ __ ] virgin boy, mate. Are you
[ __ ] mad? [sighs and gasps] Yeah, man.
Bro, [ __ ] uh I didn't go to the
boxing today. I was going to go to the
boxing, but um I didn't, but I might
still be going out later if my sister
makes it in time. But yeah, one of the numbers replied
and yeah, they might need but
that's in it. But just ordered some food. Yeah,
I was just watching that Ed Matthews.
I've been watching a lot of these uh live streams.
Madness, bro. And he even he gets the
same [ __ ] What the [ __ ]
That is mad. Mad just Indian.
I can't stand Americans, bro. I can't stand Americans.
Yeah, I just been watching it cuz
there's nothing else to watch.
It's a madness though, bro. It's an absolute madness.
So many [ __ ] in it in England and America, bro.
I can't stand anything. West.
He can't get any girl. No, he can't. No,
he [ __ ] can't. Even he gets rejected.
He even gets rejected. No, he [ __ ]
can't. I felt like I was watching myself
on some of them.
No, he can't. Even when he's in America,
bro. Yeah, think about this. He goes to
America, he's got an accent, he's got
followers, the guy's rich, and he still
gets rejected. That's mad.
What chance does a normal person have?
You know what I mean by that? I've been
watching a lot of the [ __ ] bro. Bro, he
gets rejected a lot, bro. A lot.
Trust me, bro. He gets rejected a lot,
you know, which is mad because [clears throat]
he's in another country with an accent.
He's got followers and he's got [ __ ]
money. What the [ __ ]
They're stuck up as [ __ ] So, no, you
can't get any woman. I'm just on his
Birmingham video where he's gone to
Birmingham and he's getting the same [ __ ] Boyfriend,
[ __ ] same [ __ ] Like, he might get an
odd one like if he's in America, but
bro, he he gets rejected as well. Trust
me, even by the people that come up to
him, it's mad.
That's actually mad, bro. So, what what
chance does a normal person actually have then?
We ordered an Indian if that's okay with you, boss.
So, yeah, some of them they they want to
take pictures with him and stuff.
No, he's been rejected a lot. No, no,
no, no. He's been rejected a lot. You
might want to go in his actual live
streams. He's actually been rejected a lot.
Women have given him attitude. No, no,
no. He He gets rejected a lot, bro. I
would say he probably gets
30 40% of women.
I would say he gets 30 40%.
Yeah. You know, he he does get rejected
a lot. You might want to watch some of
his live streams, bro, properly. He does,
especially in America as well. So So
how how I understand how
No, you haven't, bro. No, you haven't
been watching longer than I have. I've
been watching him all day cuz I quite
like I quite like the content to be fair
and it's like I'm watching myself and
some of them. Obviously he gets some people but
Ant-Man goes on like if you got loads of
followers they just instantly want you
which is [ __ ] because if you watch
some of them videos you'll see where
they clearly look him up and a lot of
them reject him. [ __ ]
But obviously he's got a higher chance
than the [ __ ] You know what I mean? Yeah.
Yeah. Well, you might want to watch his
uh you might want to watch his recent content.
If you've been watching him for 5 years,
you would know that he can't get any
women that he wants. If you've been
watching him for 5 years, you would know
that he probably gets about 30 40% of women.
to be fair, [snorts]
which is still good. 30 40% of women is
still [ __ ] good to be fair.
So, think about it, right? He's above
all of these women in terms of followers, money,
and he's still getting rejected by a lot
of people. How does that even make sense?
That doesn't even make [ __ ] sense, bro.
What would you say he is? He's average.
What's he average looking? So he's not
ugly either. So what the [ __ ] bro?
That's mad. That is actually mad.
And you got these people telling you,
right? Yeah. Telling you [ __ ]
that if you go to America, bro, you'll
pull like a normal guy. That's what they
tell them, Bob. Really, bro? Really?
If he wanted to pull a woman, he could
pull them. Most of the women he just
insults on purpose. No, he doesn't.
There's loads of them that he doesn't insult
and he gets rejected. Trust me, bro.
I've been watching him all day and he's
been rejected a lot.
He's better than average looking. He
looks like TGF, bro.
I don't know why he looks like TGF, bro.
I don't know if you ever watch TGF, bro.
Yeah, I've seen it. I've se Yeah, I saw that.
Yeah, I might have to go on that, bro. I
don't know. He looks like TGF, bro. Man. Yeah.
But no, there's there's loads of times
where he got rejected. Bro, I've been
watching him all day.
Yeah. And man, don't like him. I just
I've been I've been watching uh
Yeah, I like the content, bro.
But these Americans are so stupid. We
air. You get these American guys that
see him and they're like, "Ah, it's you.
Let's take a picture."
I'm thinking, "What the [ __ ]
What the actual [ __ ] bro?" But like I
can't tell you how many times yet I've
seen Cal Freezy. I've seen Cal Freezy.
I've seen I've seen some of the side men
cuz I used to live next to them. And
bro, I never ever reacted like that. I'm
figing what the [ __ ] That's mad.
That's mad, bro. So yeah.
Well, then you know he's been rejected.
Well, if you've been watching him for
years, right? then you know he gets
rejected a lot then wouldn't you? So yeah,
that's what I'm saying, Bob. That's what
I'm trying to say to this guy right here. So
you'll get like the odd one, but nah,
bro. Antman doesn't know what he's
talking. I think he's still wrong.
Ant-Man, I think Ant-Man's still wrong.
I think Bob Yeah. And I don't I don't
mind the guy. I don't dislike the guy. I
like some of the content, bro. It's
Ant-Man is He's wrong with this, bro. I think Yeah.
I don't know cuz the guy's got
followers. Yeah. And he's got money and
a lot of You've seen it yourself. I'm
thinking, so what the [ __ ] If he's only
getting 30% of women,
then how the [ __ ] is a normal guy going
to get anyone?
That is That is mad. That is mad, bro.
No, he's not messing around for content.
No, he's not because he there is Bob,
have you seen it where he's legitimately
tried and got rejected?
No, no, no, no, no, bro. He has
legitimately tried with some of them.
Even if he was joking, he might have
been joking, but he was still
he was coming across as he was trying
even though he might be joking and he
wasn't insulting them. There's loads of
ones where he didn't insult. There's
loads of ones where he didn't insult
them and they still weren't down to [ __ ]
He might have been joking like he might
have actually got with him.
Bro, I've been watching him for hours.
I've been I've watched him before. Yeah,
I I know exactly what I'm seeing. Yeah,
he might be joking. I might not actually
want them, but he's not insulting every
single woman at all. there somewhere.
He's tried to talk to them and then he
they just said straight away, I've got
I've got a boyfriend.
That's actually mad.
That's mad, bro.
He doesn't have a girlfriend anymore. He
had a girlfriend. He doesn't have a girlfriend anymore.
Again, you must not been watching this
guy recently. There's a channel where
he's got him in America [ __ ]
No, he doesn't have a girlfriend
anymore. You said that you've been
watching this guy for years, lad.
Yeah, exactly. And yeah,
bro, he hasn't got a girlfriend anymore.
And man, don't watch him. He doesn't
like him. I I don't mind him, bro, to be honest. So
[snorts] one second.
Still in progress.
What videos have you seen, Bob?
Of his. What videos have you seen?
That is mad. That is mad, bro. The [ __ ] That's mad.
But he's been rejected multiple times.
You haven't been watching him for years.
Because if you've been watching him for
years, you know that he's he's been rejected
just like Bob has seen it where he has
legitimately tried even even if he
didn't mean it and he got rejected. So
yeah, I'm just on the Birmingham one right now. now, bro. Um,
I'll watch some more later.
Nah, he's got more than five grand, bro.
He He's got £5,000. Really?
No. He must have had more than that
or had more than that. He must have had
more than that. Maybe now, but he must
have had more than that.
So, what did you see, Bob, when he was
trying to chat to the Americans then?
They're [ __ ] unbearable, them ants,
aren't they, bro? I remember when I used
to go out Thursday used to be full of
Americans. Oh my god, bro.
Yeah, he looks like TGF, bro, with a different accent.
>> Yeah. No, I'm not. I'm I've ordered
food. I'm going to eat, but I'm chilling
today. I just want a day of doing nothing.
[ __ ] tired, man. I might go out late
if my sister um
went back in time. Yeah.
Yeah. But the guys knew him.
Yeah. But Bob, what would happen when he
tried to get with him?
And he's not above average looking. He's
like average. What the [ __ ] And I'm not
hating, bro. I'm not I'm not hating.
Ant-Man doesn't like him.
doesn't like him. I actually don't I I
actually don't I don't hate the dude,
bro. I was watching some of his content.
I guess you're one of his big fans, but
yeah, I've seen it in America, bro, where like
Yep. Seen it.
I could approach with him. [ __ ] that.
It makes me laugh when he goes and says,
"I'm Jimmy Savile." [laughter]
And obviously the Yanks don't know who
he is, in it. But you get these American
guys saying, "Oh, can we take a photo?"
You know, let's take a photo. I'm
thinking, bro, like I said, I've seen
Cal Freezy. I've seen [ __ ] some of
the Sidemen. I've never reacted like
that. That's [ __ ] mad, bro. Them
Yanks are the world's full of [ __ ]
It's like what Ant-Man said. It's the
the the West is absolutely full of [ __ ] bro.
I mean, who even [ __ ] reacts like
that? That is that is insane, bro.
That is that is crazy, bro. Like, I
understand people saying, "Oh, like, I
watch you. Can I take a picture?"
Whatever. If they're fan of someone,
like if you're a fan, but that is that
is mad. Like, I'm sure you've seen it, isn't it?
Oh, is that Oh, has he got a new girlfriend? Oh,
well, whoever that woman is in the
picture, she's not even good looking.
The blonde one I'm looking at
average with filters, I'd say.
Where the [ __ ] is um Joseph Farra, man?
Yeah, he went to America. [ __ ] that's
mad that he's getting the same [ __ ] there.
getting the same [ __ ] there. I was going
to do a football bet today. I didn't.
Luckily, I didn't cuz um the Kitty
Minister match would have uh let me down. Defo
defo, bro. [ __ ] defo.
Good thing I didn't do it, Bob.
I was thinking to I think we want to go
to the rookies,
you know. It was 3-0.
Yep. I saw Cal Freezy um twice.
I've seen Call. I've seen Toby from the sideman.
Yeah, I saw him in All Saints. I was in
All Saints. I saw Calzy. I tried talking
to him, but he wasn't really saying
much. But I didn't go, "Oh, man. Let's
take a picture." Americans are so like
dramatic, bro. It's It's insane.
Like, it's it's actually mad. They're so
I can't What's the word, bro? [ __ ]
I can't explain it, bro.
>> You know what I mean? Yeah. I spoke to
him. He answered back and that but he
didn't really say anything.
It was in the All Saints. I think it was in 2019.
Then I saw him again.
But yeah, I wouldn't I wouldn't act like
that, bro. That is that is mad. What the
[ __ ] Who even acts like that, Grezy, bro?
I was supposed to be going watching it
today. Um, my sister paid for my ticket,
but I can't be asked.
Yeah, if you got loads of followers,
they might be interested for like 5
minutes, but they're not going to [ __ ]
you. So, I don't know where Ant-Man's
got this information from. I mean, I
think if he was like really really
tall and really good-looking as well,
then I think maybe I think that would be
the only way to be honest.
Who tries to take out that [ __ ] you
know one of these things you get any
woman you want? He's don't know where he
got that information from to be honest, bro.
To be fair,
that's [ __ ] man. That is [ __ ]
Loads of people have looked these people
up. They still rejected them. So, what the [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm not going. I can't be bothered.
I can't be bothered to go, man. I just
want to chill today. I said to my
sister, if you come back in time, we'll
go for a drink.
And I don't really want to see my other
sister either. I don't speak to my other
sister and she's going. So that's thing.
That's a thing. So yeah.
He will show me how to pull. Well,
that's a bit hard because he's a virgin
like notch legs.
So, I don't think a virgin can [ __ ]
show me how to [ __ ] pull.
Did you do a football bet, Steven Howard?
[clears throat and snorts] Yeah.
Yeah, nonslegs is a virgin as well. Nonss.
Nonsle is a virgin. Bob's a virgin.
Bro, them cocktails the other night
[ __ ] me up, Bob. They [ __ ] me up completely, mate.
Bro, it's nothing to do with LT. I'm not
scared of LT.
Why are you Why are you talking about
LT? This is what I mean with this
community. You twist things. You twist
things all the time and I'm sick of it.
Why would I be scared of LT when there's
going to be four other people with me,
bro? He wouldn't even see me even if I
was by myself. This is what I mean with
this community. You always constantly
twist things. This is what I'm saying.
You twist things. You make stuff up
every single [ __ ] time.
No one's scared of LT, firstly.
Secondly, he wouldn't even see me.
Thirdly, I would have been with four people, mate.
Oh, no. No. He's definitely definitely a
virgin. He's been with disabled girls
that can't consent to sex. No, he
definitely is a virgin. He definitely
will be a virgin. He is a virgin. He
definitely definitely is because these
disabled women can't consent to sex. So,
if he went anywhere near them, he would
have been locked up. He won't be a
virgin. He is a virgin. So, um, he's
definitely definitely a big virgin and I
know him better than he knows himself.
Oh, he Yes, way. He is a virgin. He 100%
is a virgin. 100% way down the highway.
He's a virgin. Just like Timmy, just
like Bomb and other people, but they're
the ones that we know about. Oh, he's a
million% a virgin. 100 million% he is a
Otherwise, I wouldn't say it if I didn't believe it.
Having a disabled girlfriend don't prove
you've had sex. Somebody that's done a
video of having sex is proof that you've
had sex, which is what I done.
How do I? Cuz I know the signs. I know a
big virgin when I see one. I know a
[ __ ] virgin when I see one, mate.
The way he stalks my ex, one one night
stands. How he constantly tries to call
me a virgin even though I've proved I've had sex.
Um, so he's he's just a big big virgin.
He's a big virgin. And I know and I I
know him better than he knows himself.
And when you constantly would tell him
stories of people that you've had sex
with, he'd keep denying it all cuz he's
a virgin. You don't understand that a
lot. What it is with this guy is
projection. Virgin, he's a virgin.
Skint, he's skint. You know, it's it's
What's the other one? There's another one. Um,
ugly. He's ugly. You have to understand
that with this guy, most of the [ __ ] is
self-p projection. Virgin him, ugly him, skint him.
All self-p projection. And the virginity
being one of them. And I said about a
million times, I've had sex with this
escort. I've had sex with this escort.
I've had sex with this escort. Well, how
can someone be a virgin when they've
proved they've had sex? But he calls me
a virgin. I mean, answer yourself that
question. So, anyone that's proved
they've had sex,
you know, is
I mean, everything what I say or what he says.
I mean, I've proved I've had sex. So, I
I mean I proved I've had sex. That's
that's that's more than a relationship.
But again, with you simpleton, you just
believe what you want. So,
um, so no, he definitely definitely
definitely is a virgin.
Definitely is a virgin. And you I would
tell him stories I've had sex multiple
multiple times and he wouldn't believe
it. And again, they say that you're an
adult at 18. Yeah, you're an adult at
18, but bro, you do mature, you know,
during years of your life. You do you do
mature like you know more now than you
did when you was 18. Just like I I
didn't know he was projecting his
virginity onto me back then. It's
because he's the virgin. I didn't I
didn't know that. I I used to say to my
mom, "Can you please tell this guy that
I have [ __ ] proved I've had sex and
he wouldn't have it?" And it's because
he's the virgin. The penny dropped in
the end. Oh, it's cuz he's never had
sex. So his projection, the fact that he
dates down, 100% a virgin, and I bet my
life on it, he's never had sex with
nothing. Never have, never will. And
being with a disabled girl absolutely
doesn't prove he's had sex. What I pull
up prove I had sex.
And I'm thinking, why wouldn't you
believe? And the fact that he goes out
of his way to get women to say they've
not slept with me proves he's a virgin.
It just proves he's a virgin. And he
calls me skin when I've got more money
than him. I mean, what the [ __ ] bro?
It's It's weird.
Why? And and another thing is, okay, so
I tell you the first story, right? I
told him that I had sex with an escort
when I did have sex with an escort. And
I told him this story and he would find
any little thing to not believe it. Like
he made up stories how escorts ask for
ID. He would not have any of it that I
paid for sex. paying for sex. And you
know, in 28 years, I've never ever met
anyone else that never believed somebody
paid for sex. He Nope. Didn't believe
it. Didn't believe it. They didn't
believe it. And it's because Oh, he's
the virgin. I get it now. He's the
virgin. I get it. He's probably got
something wrong with his little dick
like Ant-Man. Ant-Man's got like a lot
of skin on his dick. He needs to be
circumcised. But he owns it. He owns it. >> [snorts]
>> You know, maybe he's tried to, you know,
uh, bro, listen. I, if I had over a
grand, it would be over a grand more
than you. And you don't know how much
money I have. And I can flex what I want
because that would be more than what you
have and nonslegs put together. So, if I
had just over a grand, that's more than
you you and non legs have combined. So,
more pennies than you. So, yeah.
Only a stupid [ __ ] person, bro. Yeah.
Would sit there and say over a grand
nothing. Only fantasists. That's what it
is with this community. It's full of
fantasists. I mean, I went out on
Thursday and I spent £100. I got a lot
with £100. I mean, I literally got a lot
But you're sat there saying about how
over a grand is nothing
and you're probably working. No. So, do
you think you would ever find someone
else that sits there and says, "Fuck
off. Over a grand's nothing." I mean, my
sister has probably got about 20 grand
in her account, right? And I don't think
she's going to sit there and say over a
grand's nothing. I don't think my other
sister's going to say over a grand's
nothing. And I don't think anyone is
going to say over a grand's nothing
unless they're [ __ ] multi multi-millionaire.
You know what I mean? So,
I mean, mate, if I if I had £1,400, I'll
flex about having 1,400 pound. So,
yeah. Well, it is something in the
scheme of things because it can get you
a lot of stuff. Over a grand is a lot
and it can get you a lot of stuff.
It is something because you can't pay
your rent with nothing. And I'm not
going to keep having this conversation
over and over and over and over again.
Okay, you're a millionaire. You're a
billionaire, but you're on YouTube.
Okay, bro. Whatever. Have a word with
yourself. No normal person sits there
and says over a grand nothing. Not one
person. Only a fantasist on YouTube
would say that. Literally, only a
fantasist on YouTube would say that.
Only a fantasy that don't have money.
Trust me. I I can figure this [ __ ] out,
bro. Trust me. Yeah. You know, I can
figure a lot of people out on this
community as well.
Do you know what I'm saying? I spent
[clears throat] I mean, like I told you,
I spent £100 on Thursday. I spent £100 [ __ ] pound.
But it doesn't even matter anyways, does
it? Does it really matter? What? What? You know,
it doesn't really matter, does it, man?
Does it really matter? Not really.
But yeah, if you have 14,500 pound, you
can flex it all day long, bro. No one on
here is going to show you more than that
now. No one on here now is going to show
you more than that.
No one. Not one person is going to show
So, uh, yeah, that's that. No, no, no,
no, no. Because he was making it out
like it [snorts] was a million pounds.
He was No, no, no. He was making out
that daddy's savings, right, was at a
million pounds and the fact that he's
got no life experience. He's traveled
nowhere and he's got no clothes. It's
took him three years to save up 16 grand
and he's going on like it's a million
pounds. It makes absolute sense. Bomb.
Who's under that account? Yeah, it makes
absolute sense when it's took somebody
three years to get to that amount and
losing life experiences because of it.
Acting like it's a million pound. Acting
like it's a million pound sat there with
no lifestyle. I know it is. They make it
so obvious, bro. They make it so
obvious. It's probably Dusty Showbiz.
Another low life. £16,000
that took you three years to save and
you've had no life because of it. That's
nothing for 3 years of not living,
right? That is nothing. So, it does make
sense now. Bye-bye now, [ __ ]
This is why I don't really come on here
anymore, bro. This is It's because it's
just the same [ __ ] with these people
every day. these mongos.
I'm coming off here for a couple weeks
anyways, bro. Um, from probably Monday,
probably two or three weeks. It's the
same atmosphere. It's the same mongos.
[gasps] Same disabled people. They ain't
got a life. You know what I'm saying?
It's boring, bro. It's the same atmosphere.
It's boring, bro. Same little [ __ ]
same little fat virgin that ain't got a
life. It's boring, bro. You deacon.
You give me K vibes, bro.
So, and then I've explained how the
guy's a virgin.
So, yeah, I went out uh Liverpool Street
Thursday, Deacon, bro. It was dead.
There's a few people out. There was a
few people out. See, I told you, bro. I
can I can spot accounts, Deacon. I can I
can spot accounts.
I can spot accounts. Bye-bye. I can spot
accounts, bro. I told you this.
See, now I went out uh on Thursday. Oh,
did you watch the approaching videos?
Hope you liked him. And there weren't
many people out to be honest. I was by
like shortage. Um I was hung over as
[ __ ] bro. I thought I was going to die,
bro. Them cocktails and [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] ruined me, bro. Ruined me. It's
put me off ever wanting to drink rum
ever again, bro. I was waking up being
sick, everything, bro. Oh my god.
Yeah, of course I always get you. It's
too obvious. It's too obvious, bro. It's
like Dusty Show the [ __ ] I know all
of these accounts. I know all of these little accounts. Yeah,
he's like the approaching videos. Uh Kieran,
I was going to do a football bet today,
but I didn't bother. Save myself some money. Yeah.
Yeah. I got you, bro. I got you.
Got you [ __ ] good.
Guy's a [ __ ] idiot, bro.
Yeah, he's a proper Ed Matthew s, isn't he?
uh one of them
some uh Asian one Indonesian. Yeah, I
said, "Oh, we should go out sometime to
let's see." So, I might go out next week
and invite her or invite her out. But
apart from that, not really, bro. 24 numbers in
and not a single day. Why would I be due
a successful cold approach? It would
always be the same here.
Look at that guy on TikTok. He's got followers
uh you know and whatever. And he he gets
rejected most of the time as well. So
what chance does a normal person have like me?
You're not due um
a successful cold approach. It will
always be the same here. Why do you
think it doesn't bother me, bro?
Yeah, I know. It put me off wanting to
drink rum ever again, bro. I was
drinking cocktails and [ __ ] There was
some guy I met. Yeah, he's a cool guy. D uh
came and he was drinking in Reading
yesterday. That's where he was from. And
I was tempted to go meet him, bro, and
get on it. He's a cool guy, ain't it? I
could just get the Lizzy to Red.
It could be maybe maybe two years, maybe three years.
It could take years, bro. It could take years.
It will take years, bro. Trust me. I
haven't been on a date since April. So,
go figure. You've seen the approaches.
You've seen I've gone out and been
confident. I done it sober. So, yeah. Was
it giving you anxiety the approaches?
Yeah, but it could take years. Could
take years, bro.
Could take years.
I just ordered some nice Indian. Oh gosh. But yeah,
it's not as easy as that. Uh Kieran,
it took me two years till I found USA, is he?
Yeah. Yeah. That's what I noticed. Uh
Deacon, is that you know, Liverpool
Street, even on a Thursday? Listen to
me, bro. Yeah. Listen to me, bro.
Um, I mean the street is still good. I
mean that's the street is the only will
be the only way soon. When I was in
Liverpool Street Thursday, it was dead
and Liverpool Street is second to
central London. It should be busy on a
Thursday. Obviously, it won't be as busy
as Saturday, but there should still be
some people, bro. There was about five
people in a bar, bro. Five people. It
was dead. [ __ ] dead. And it's also
hitting central London as well now
because last week I was in central
London. Um and you can see bro it's
really hitting there now as well. Is it
really hitting central London the cost
of living crisis? So um
uh he gets rejected by women as well.
He goes and approaches women women and
he still gets rejected. believe it or
not. Yep. He still gets rejected.
No, you would think so, but he still
gets rejected, bro. Believe it or not,
I don't know what the [ __ ] man was going
on about saying that if you're a
followers and that,
I don't think it's as easy as that, bro.
Maybe if you're like a 10 out of 10 and
you're like 7 foot tall maybe. But
but yeah, it took me two years of trying
before I met USA is he?
So I mean could take years to find to
even get sex ever again.
It's not as easy as that, bro.
And if you can't even get a [ __ ]
date, Kieran [ __ ] What does that tell
you, bro? If you can't even get a date,
you know what I'm saying?
It's not like I've had recent dates.
Don't I've had nothing.
It never used to be this bad two and a
half, three years ago.
Never used to be this bad.
It was still hard, but it was never like
this. It was never like this. Madness. [ __ ] madness. Yeah.
Well, you've been thinking of um
thinking of approaching Kieran, huh?
I think it will get to the point where
it's just would just be completely impossible
in westernized countries.
I think it will get to that um it will
get to that point.
What do you think, Kieran?
The only thing I'm interested in is
[ __ ] food, bro. Yeah.
I'm [ __ ] hungry. Nice. Indian
vinderoo ticker rice. Done.
That's okay with me, boss.
And yeah, Kieran, he said that Cheryl
Cole was attractive to fit in. Tried
saying that I was gay because I didn't I
don't find her attractive. What a loser.
What a [ __ ] loser.
Projecting his gayness onto me. [ __ ] loser. Bye-bye, weirdo.
Proper proper [ __ ] Proper [ __ ] virgin.
Who the [ __ ] wouldn't believe someone's
paid for sex? What a virgin.
You're saying it's on its way. Where the
[ __ ] is it?
No, it's not. Oh, did you order KFC? I
ordered Indian, bro.
No, I ordered India and me mate. I had
K. Oh, I had more fried chicken earlier.
Greavves. I went to the chicken shop. Yeah.
I saw the um
I saw the ka the chicken ka obviously
virgin boy has a ka don't he
virgin boy has a chicken ka don't he
that's more for him
yeah he likes ka Yeah.
No, no, no, no.
You all right, Captain?
One second, bro.
See, I was right. Your word means completely nothing.
If you see if you see me, it will be
fake. But yet, you lie about loads of [ __ ]
Oh, but you lie about so much [ __ ] And
L J lies about so much [ __ ] But that's
completely okay then, isn't it?
Okay. So, it's okay for you to lie about
[ __ ] and it's okay for Lord J to lie
about [ __ ] H, that's interesting, isn't
it? I'm sure Kieran can uh can agree
with me on that one.
Bro, listen. You want to talk about fantasist?
You lie about how much money you have.
You lie about loads of different things.
LJ has proven to lie about multiple
things multiple times, but I still see
you in his chat. So, if you don't like
people that supposedly, I quote, lie,
you might want to not go on another lies
chat, aka LJ, biggest liar going.
So, you won't be in he chat then, I take
it. Why bring up L? Because I I can
bring up what I want. You said that
you're not coming on my chat anymore
because I'm apparently a liar. So, why
you going on other liars chat? Was it
one rule for one, one rule for another?
Come on, man.
So, it's one rule for one, one rule for another strange.
I mean, don't make me get into these
lies. Jesus Christ,
it's pathetic. I don't know why people
feel the need to lie on here. I was
saying this earlier, Greasy. Don't know
why people feel the need to lie on here
the way they do. I told you how much
money I get a month.
I don't give a [ __ ] You know what I mean? [clears throat]
So, yeah. Here's the thing, Joe. If I
was really really going somewhere, you
wouldn't even know.
You wouldn't even know until I come back.
Uh, name five of Law J's lies. Okay.
He's got six properties. He's not on benefits.
Um, he was supposed to go to um, was it
was the other place? He was supposed to
go to Jaden's, didn't come. He was
supposed to come back here, didn't come.
I mean, do I do I need to keep going?
that he's not skint when he is. I mean,
do you want me you want me to keep going?
You really really want me to keep going?
Said that he met Izzy, he never
I mean, I can carry on and on and on and
on and on and on. So,
listen, listen, listen, listen, bro. So,
I just listen to them. So, you really
think I'm going to tell you where I'm
going, when I'm going? Really, bro? You
you actually believe I will tell you
where I'm going, when I'm going.
Come on, man. You're not stupid, you know. You know? So, yeah.
So, yeah, I listed five liars. Okay, now what?
He lies about everything. He literally
is the biggest liar ever. I just I've
just listed you his lies. So, if you
don't like liars, don't be on e channel then.
Don't know what what what what's the
lies about. Don't understand the lies,
you know. It's just silly. And he his
life is a lie. I just said I was going
somewhere I didn't go. His whole life is
a lie. His whole life is a lie. Pretends
that he's not on benefits. Pretends that
he um they are six properties, which
doesn't even make any sense. And at the
end of the day, they wouldn't even be
worth anything because they're in
Belfast. His whole life is a lie. I
don't understand why he needs to lie. I
told you how much I get a month. £1,100.
I've won some money over the past couple
of months. I have enough money to do
what I want to do. I don't need to lie, bro.
I don't [ __ ] need to lie. You know,
because because you do it. Oh, so I
can't so I can't compare myself when it
when it doesn't suit you. Oh, but it's
okay for you to compare me to other people.
H strange. So, when you're proven wrong,
it's comparing. But then when you're
not, it's it's completely okay. Yeah.
Okay, man. Whatever. Whatever.
Tell you where I was going, bro.
I don't tell you where I was going, bro.
If I was actually going to go somewhere,
I wouldn't tell you where and when. That's ridiculous.
That is absolutely ridiculous. And you
know exactly why that's ridiculous. I'm
not even going to tell you why, but you
already know why.
Let's just bastard. I'm starving.
So that's that.
Who's proved what?
[ __ ] sake, bro.
>> Yeah. Okay. Yeah. How about this? Why
don't you show us your face, Joe?
Why don't you pro Why don't you prove
you're not fat and ugly?
H Why don't you prove you're not fat and
ugly? Cuz you like to talk about people's looks.
How about that one? I'll stick the link
up for you right now if you want. Can't
prove that though, can you, Joseph?
Can't prove that one. Joseph Ferrra. Nah.
Can't prove that one, mate. Nah, you you
can't you can't.
He's lying about other things as well,
but those are the ones that just come to my head.
Just admit your own benefits, bro.
There's nothing just, you know, it's
it's uh uh because when you judge other
people's appearance, I think the person
that does other people's appearance
should show their face, aka you.
So, I mean, you've judged the way I
look. Not that I really care. I don't
give a [ __ ] what anyone says about
colors. But why you why are you judging
another man? Why are you judging another man's looks? H.
Anyways, you said you don't want to come
on this channel anymore, so see you later.
I would say I'd see you on Laur, but I
don't even go on that [ __ ] channel, so
Oh, yeah. Lied about that. Made loads of
excuses not to meet LT.
I had no problems with LT until that
bouncer thing to be honest. In all
fairness, I would say everything was
justified until then to be fair. That's
why I don't speak to the dude
cuz it was too weird.
It's It's too weird.
How can I be Who said that you're on benefits?
What? Why? Why are you talking about you
being on benefits? Who said that you're
So what? You're making stuff up.
He's making stuff up, Mr. B. Joseph
Ferrar's making stuff up. I said, when
did I say you was on benefits?
No, I said Lord Jay is on benefits. If
you listen properly, we are making stuff
up. No one said you was on benefits.
Joseph Farah's making stuff up.
Well, go anyways. You said you don't
want to come be on this channel anymore.
I'll be waiting for my lovely Indian and
you can s off.
Simple as that. No, I'm not going to the
boxing, bro. I just want a day of staying in.
I just want a day of staying in and that
could be my food.
>> Hopefully it is.
>> No, it's not. [ __ ] starving, mate.
>> No, it isn't.
>> Yeah, you should listen properly, bro.
No one said you was on benefits. Stop
making stuff up, you silly goose.
before I come there and beat you up and
take your car for
I'm sure there's other channels you can
go on like the skinned virgins and [ __ ] laws.
You're not welcome here anymore.
Is that cute? You're not welcome here anymore.
[laughter and snorts]
Yeah. See you tomorrow, Joe. See you
tomorrow when I'm live again. [clears throat]
See you tomorrow, Joseph. For real. Joseph,
you like that, don't you, Grezy? Where
was this bloody Indian? I'm bloody starving.
You said you was going. I don't know
what you're still doing here.
You silly goose.
Why don't you sod off? I'm sure your boyfriend's live.
H I'm sorry. I'm sure your boyfriend's
live. Look, I'm in my little gowny. Yeah. [snorts]
Hurry up, man.
Where the [ __ ] are these [ __ ] Oh, hungry. Come on. [clears throat] I'm peckish.
Grieves. I just want to shove these
tickers down my mouth. You know what I'm
like? Oh gosh. [laughter] Yeah.
Yeah. I didn't want to I don't want to
really see my other sister either to be honest.
So yeah, I didn't want to see my other
sister and then I have to come all the
way back. I just wanted to chill today, man.
I've done a lot recently. I just want to
chill. Just want to have a little chill out today.
Is that normaly? Just having a little chill out.
Yeah, I just want to [ __ ] out, bro. Barry, Joseph, Farra,
bro, where is this food, man?
[ __ ] dying, mate. >> [laughter]
>> [ __ ] are you? Mine stole saying estimate arrival quarter.
quarter to um quart 8. Still not here. [clears throat]
It's not funny, bro. I'm [ __ ] hungry.
I'm my little chicken ticker buncher. Grezy,
my little chicken picker muncher.
So, you like the UG boots then, Grezy?
The 165B UGG boots.
They're bloody lush.
You're not seeing the hug boobs.
Would you like to see them? Grey.
Okay, boss. It's like you know that uh
guy from Oxford. Yeah. I said, "Oh, did
you see me uh do that approach?" He was
like, "Yeah, I had a peak." He said,
>> He said, "I had a peak." [laughter]
I was talking to something at the bottom
of it. He said, "I had a peak." [laughter]
I'll show you, Grevy.
I got an electric toothbrush, by the
way, but I can't have it until Christmas.
I can show you, but I need to be careful
cuz they're not mine.
These are the UGG boots.
They smell lovely.
They've got the certificate on them as
well, so they're real.
They're for Laney. They're not They're not mine. Yep. £165, [laughter] it
bro. Where is this food, man?
[ __ ] hungry, bro.
Where do you order from, Grezy? Do you
do Just eat, Deliveroo, or Uber?
What the [ __ ] I just treaded on a
[ __ ] snail, bro. Oh my god.
[ __ ] snail. What the [ __ ] is a snail doing there?
Not I didn't kill it, but
it was there.
No, it's horrible out there, mate. It is
horrible out there.
Yeah, Deliveroo is the best. I think
I don't know where this food is, mate.
This This puts me off wanting to like
order food, you know, bro.
This this [ __ ]
It puts you off wanting to order food.
You know what I mean? Just go in and
eat, you know?
Don't know where this food is.
Is that it?
No, it won't be a laugh. I'm [ __ ] hungry, bro.
Let's discard it because it says it
can't be trapped.
We might be on to something here,
Captain. Oh, lovely.
Cars just pulled up.
Oh, cars just pulled up. Greasy.
Oh, there you are. Yeah, man.
>> Yeah, it's me. Thank you.
>> I couldn't wait. I was standing by the
door. I'm so hungry.
Let's have a little look.
Thank you, Captain. [laughter]
They gave me three pop of them. They did
to be fair.
They gave me Oh, they gave me a couple problems. That's
You can tell We a fat [ __ ] We know
you're a fat [ __ ] Grezy.
It's always watery though. Like you know
the mint sauce and that right
whenever you order it. It never tastes the same. Never ever.
One step, bro.
One second, Grezy. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Nah, not starting any [ __ ] here, mate.
But a certain person would [ __ ] dare
go anywhere near that. Wouldn't [ __ ]
dare go anywhere near that, mate.
No, he would [ __ ] not go anywhere
near that at all.
>> Oh, some ticker as well.
Look, I've got clear air razor. Mhm. [clears throat] Good morning.
It would always be crap compared to the restaurant. Go away.
It always will be, bro.
You'll never beat the You'll never beat
the restaurant. Never in that area, but nothing. M
take this on a [ __ ] big boy. Trust me. Let
Yeah. You'll never be the restaurants ever.
You'll never be the You'll never ever be the restrooms. Never.
This way, isn't it?
Oh, look at your music. 4 minutes.
This is all that's left. I've done the ticker.
Can Peter B take spice music?
Yes, I can.
Peter belly takes spice. Mhm.
Now certain virgin we know that would be
gone by now cuz you [snorts] can't take spice.
No, it's mint sauce. I love
hopefully 2026 will be the year where
Virgin boy loses it. What do you think?
I reckon he might lose it.
Or or he might end up a 40-year-old virgin.
Oh, crazy. This is delicious.
Stubble. You don't have stubble. We
can't grow beard.
That [ __ ] You're trying to sit there
and tell me
that [ __ ] skin virgin can grow
stouble. [ __ ] off.
They're giving you a lot to be fair.
You're going to sit there and try and
tell me that version.
Go a bit.
I sit there virgin bed. That's lovely.
And I've almost finished mine.
Nothing about it. Lovely.
Virgin boy is [ __ ] skin
and a [ __ ] skin printer.
What is he? He's [ __ ] skin. Yeah,
[ __ ] off for and never come back.
Jeez, that gave me so much, bro. [ __ ]
He's [ __ ] full. Uh, nothing.
What was that name? [ __ ] hell.
That is bad. Look, I forgot my coat. That's [ __ ]
I think I'm done, bro. [ __ ]
Oh, mate. All of that. Gosh.
Yeah, I'm [ __ ] stuck.
I'm stuck, mate. Steven Howard
Steven Howard is uh does Virgin Boy
still post about me?
Does Virgin Boy still post about me? I
don't go on the channel.
I haven't been on the channel for like a week. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, I never go on it. I don't go on virgin channels.
This is all I have. I don't go on skin
virgin channels, mate. You know me, man.
Oh, I don't go on it, bro. I don't see anything.
There's no point going on a skin virgin
channel that just wants to be a keyboard
warrior. That's the That's the That's
the mor of the story, is it? A little
virgin keyboard warrior that's never
going to beat anyone.
[ __ ] waste of life.
There's plenty of other things to be uh doing. Captain
Paxi's virginity of the people cuz he's
a big big virgin. [snorts] Oh, he's a
He's a big Oh, he's a big virgin.
What a virgin. He actually
what a virgin.
Silly virgin he is.
You need to get laid. Been saying it
since I met him. You need to get laid. You didn't.
He made up a story about he had sex on a
park bench. No, you kiss him. No, you
bloody well didn't. Remember that Aisha
Bout school you told
trying to say that he had sex at a park
bench? No, he did not.
You had sex on park. Shut up.
You're still a virgin. Typical virgin.
Shut up. You didn't have no sex on no
park bench. You've never had a [ __ ] Shut up.
Oh god. What is it with these? What is
it with these blooming virgins?
What is it with these blooming virgins?
They all seem to be the [ __ ] same, mate. The [ __ ] get
you have sex on a [ __ ] park bench.
Did he have sex on a [ __ ] park bench?
[ __ ] ain't had sex with nothing.
The only the only [ __ ] he's ever had is
his mums when he come out of it. Yeah,
he made up a story that he had sex with
on a park bench.
No, you [ __ ] did not. You didn't have
sex on a park bench. Shut up. Stories
are not even believable.
[ __ ] didn't have sex on a [ __ ]
park bench. You [ __ ] silly virgin.
What do you think? We were born
yesterday or something.
Oh, remember and uh remember Steven
Howard, he calls me a virgin, yet his
channel got banned because of my porno.
Yeah, similar to what similar to what uh
Kieran said. I'm a I'm a virgin apparently,
but his channel got banned from me
shoving my dick up a woman's mouth, but
I'm a virgin. Interesting, eh?
Doesn't exactly make sense, but
doesn't make any sense at all, does it?
No, he can't get it up. He's a virgin.
He's a typical virgin.
You can't get it up, mate. He's got
problems with that little tiny dick.
Big big big big big big virgin. Massive
virgin, mate. Bigger than the great
Collie. Big big big big virgin.
He didn't believe any of the escort
stories. Steven Howard, my mom had to go
on the phone. He would not believe that
I had sex. No matter what I said,
what I proved, he literally right
would not have any of it because he's a virgin.
You're a [ __ ] big virgin, man. with a
[ __ ] big big big
Why would you believe someone's had sex
with an escort?
Why would you believe it?
Noble person would not ever believe it.
And if you a virgin yourself,
unless you a big virgin yourself,
why else wouldn't you believe it?
You've never had sex. You [ __ ] never
had sex. You big virgin.
Trust me, mate. You've ever would go up. [ __ ] virgin. Yeah.
Why wouldn't you believe someone's had
sex with an escort?
Why would you believe someone
And what's the story he made up? He said
that my um my dad beat me up on my sisters. [laughter]
I laughed when I heard that. Bro, you
can't even make up stories.
He's such a stupid little virgin, is he?
He really, really is. Just one stupid
little virgin that needs to get laid.
You know what I'm saying? That's all he is, mate.
But oh, mate, that [ __ ] virgin's mad.
That little in real life, he's proper
proper socially awkward as well. He's a
little [ __ ] virgin in real life. He's a
[ __ ] [ __ ] virgin in real life, mate. The
biggest [ __ ] [ __ ] virgin you'll ever
come across. would say boo to a goose.
Very shy in person. Very very shy.
A shy uh introverted virgin. What he is [laughter]
jumped out of school windows?
>> Really? That's news to me, mate.
No, more like he jumped out of college windows,
right? cuz people at the college used to
think he was gay. Then he was like, I'm
not gay. I like co
if you don't find what you're gay. I
said, [ __ ] off, you little virgin gay
copycat. You little virgin autistic gay
copycat. Don't [ __ ] come [ __ ]
You're going to [ __ ] sit there in
that [ __ ] skinned virgin bed sit
yours and try and tell me I'm [ __ ]
gay, you ugly.
My my voice is more [ __ ] purple. You
eating. Have a word with yourself, Virgin.
He's attracting. You can't attract.
You're gay. That's copying.
That's doing anything to fit in with a crowd.
I mean, Grezy, that is literally being
nothing but a little copycat. How can
you like someone that has to copy other
people? He's so scared of saying that
she's not attractive because people in
college bullied him because they thought
he was gay. That's literally what
happened, bro. I swear to God. He's
attractive. No, he's hot. If you don't,
you're gay. I was like, "What the fuck?"
I brought this up because people kept
going on about it. I said, "Have you
heard of this show?" He's like, "Yeah,
she's that [laughter] copycat virgin."
If you go, if you literally go on the
student room form, remember the student
room form, Gez? Literally, everyone says
it to each other. They all copy each
other. They used to do it with Beyonce as well.
They used to do it. Uh,
they used to do it with Beyonce.
Yeah, just copycats. It's a trend. It's
called a trend that people do to fit in.
You fit in with the crowd.
You know, heterosexual men are allowed
to find one thing attractive and not the other.
I know. Do you still go on about the
same thing, the same madeup stories? And
you know what's even more? Like I said,
I haven't been on the channel for a week
and I'll never go back on it to be
honest. It's It's all made up. That's
That's the worst thing about it. All of
these stories are so made up. He's not
even good at making up the stories.
He's It's literally like not even believable.
That's what makes it even worse is that
it's clear that they're made up. like
saying that my mom my mom my dad sat to
me and my sisters about
I mean that's that's that's a bit hard
to do because the guy weren't even in my
life but they're just made up stories.
They're literally made up stories. I was
just talking about the Virgin 14 Maxwell
the burger making me hiccup. Yeah, you
can never you could never have that
burger. You can never have that burger.
Um greasy lad. You could never be too
much for you. I've just made myself a
lovely cup of K.
But I'm going to have this cola first.
I'm not having all of it. Just a couple of sips. So yeah. Yeah.
I mean hiccups is normal. I mean I
hiccup. I mean,
it depends if you can carry on. If you
can't carry on, it's too hot for you.
Like, for example,
when I had that Carolina Reaper burger,
I couldn't continue it. It was too hot.
I wanted it to stop. I mean, if you're
just hiccoping, but you can still do it.
I would say it's too hot for you. I
mean, you'll know if it's too hot
because you wouldn't be able to do it.
No, I was supposed to go to the boxing
match today. My sister paid for my
tickets, but I couldn't be bothered to go.
I'm tired and I just wanted to chill today, so
uh Carolina Reaper burger is the hot
hottest burger in the world. We spoke
about it before. You have to sign a leaf
before trying it. It's the one I had.
Remember the one I had months ago?
We have to sign a leaf. I don't know if
anyone remembers it. I I I done the
challenge and what almost [ __ ] killed me.
Yeah, he needs to uh
No, Dave's chicken. Do them.
I can do the challenge again for you if
you want, Greavves. E, at some point. Yeah,
it's called Dave's Chicken. You get it
from Dave's Chicken.
Oh, you're not the only one, bro.
There's a virgin called non legs and he
can only have karma.
Yeah, if you remember it, that's the
burger we're talking about. It almost
[ __ ] killed me, bro. [sighs]
Oh, bro. Almost killed me, bro. I had to
sign the lead. That's how you know if
you like the tenant, right? The girl
telling I I let her have some of my vindaloo.
She took one bite and she's like, [panting]
I mean, and she can go on. If you can't continue then
see, look, this
sugar's got this tea's got three sugars
in it. Now, Britney's cup of tea might have
two sugars in it.
Yeah, but you're not but you're not her cuppper.
At the end of the day, you're not her cuppper, mate.
You're not her cuppper. I like three
sugars. Britney might like two sugars.
So, you just weren't her cuppper.
Yeah, I'm all right. A Timmy, you're
right. Just made myself a cup of tea.
Yeah, this Jamie Thompson guy is a
[ __ ] stalker, bro.
Just gave my number to everyone. I got
people calling me.
I think Jamie Thompson was bullied in life.
Did you watch my approaches all? Hope
you like them.
Yeah, that uh that uh Jamie Thompson's
definitely a bully victim, bro.
Definitely definitely a bully victim.
100% a bully victim, bro.
He's a loser, bro. Proper loser.
Proper fat losser.
I got his WhatsApp picture as well. I
should screenshot it. Proper proper loser.
Proper proper loser, lad.
Yeah, he's a proper [ __ ] loser. He is.
Yeah, he's a loser, bro. Yeah.
proper proper stalking loser. I've got
um like these things calling me for like
job interviews and [ __ ]
>> Yeah, he's a loser, bro. He's a proper
proper loser and he's messaging me on
like other numbers as well.
I think the guy's jealous of me or something, bro.
I think he's jealous of me or something,
bro. Some fat ugly loser. Have you seen
him? Well, here above.
One second, man.
Do you know what I hate about lamb? How
it gets stuck in your teeth?
Anyone else experience that?
That's horrible, bro. So, um, Autumn,
what's your name, kid?
Do I greasy? What's your name, kid?
So, uh, what's your name, kid? [laughter]
I'm such a silly goose.
That's a lovely cup of [ __ ] [laughter] Yep.
[snorts] Yeah. Just to let you know,
Stephen Howard, I don't go on the Virgin
channel anymore, bro. You know,
he needs to get laid and stop making up
silly little stories.
[snorts] Silly little stories about
people. It's immature.
[ __ ] hell. It's just self projection
on that channel, you know.
skin you virgin you m you. So yeah. Yep.
Oh, does he [ __ ] the silly little
virgin? He's have a [ __ ] word with himself. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. >> [laughter]
>> He gonna die one, mate. He's going to
die one. He's going to die one. He's
going to [ __ ] die one, man. Die a
virgin. Just Just die a virgin. Is he just one?
He's going to die one, mate. He's going
to die one. He's going to die one. He's
going to die one. He's going to die one.
Going to die one.
I want to watch some Ed Matthews in a bit. Yeah,
[laughter] he goes up to people and say,
"My name is Jimmy Sav."
The guy is such a [ __ ] isn't it?
The guy's a [ __ ] [laughter] [snorts] Yeah, man. >> [laughter]
>> The Spain one didn't reply. Steven Howard,
the Spain one didn't reply.
>> I just got done it for the lows, you know.
That coffee was lush.
No, she won't. It's been two days. She
see Peter Bennett get a number live. Did
you? Oh yeah. Yeah.
She didn't speak good English.
No, I need to go in a bit anyways, bro.
But it's never as good as the restaurants.
Never as good. It's never ever as good. Obviously.
Obviously. It's never
Boy was jealous of me and little USA is his affair.
Our little honeymoon honeymoon period.
Isn't that right, Steven Howard? Nothing lasts forever.
>> He was jealous of our little honeymoon period.
Virgin boy. Virgin boy was jealous of me
and USA Izzy's little affair.
[ __ ] hell, mate.
Yeah. [ __ ] Al Virgin boy boys mad,
mate. Al Virgin boys [ __ ] mad. Did
you do a football bet today or not? I
was going to do slow and Lemington and
the Lemington match would have [ __ ] me up. Yeah.
Yeah. I would have lost.
I might do a 500 pound double. Both
teams to score next week. Steven Howard
and go out drinking. [ __ ] that, bro.
Imagine it loses. Nah,
can't do that, bro. It might lose.
Nah, I'm going to get [ __ ] up. You'd
be [ __ ] up then.
No, you'd be [ __ ] up. Yeah.
Imagine that. Going on a drink and you
got 500 both teams to score on and
you're waiting for it. Nah,
>> imagine that, bro. Madness.
I might go to Reading next week. Go meet
that guy. Getting a piss with him.
He seems like a jolly fella.
He seems like a jolly good fella.
Yeah, I normally win on Tuesdays. It's
normally the Tuesdays that I win on normally. Yeah.
Do you remember that 120 to 380? That
was a nice win.
That was a nice win. That was
Yeah, you need to do them on Tuesdays.
They're the best days to do them. It's
kind of like almost midweek, isn't it?
Next day is like the midweek. So, yeah,
Tuesdays, it's good to do it on Tuesdays. M.
What? The most you'd put on it is £50.
That's the most you put on it.
I was thinking of playing some roulette
earlier, bro. Like a nice little roulette session,
but nah, I don't do them things anymore.
So what what you only put £50 on it now maximum? Really?
One second. Let me
really Why only £50?
So, what would your what would your max usually be?
What would your max usually be? >> [snorts]
>> Yeah. What's the most you would ever put on it?
See, I want to put like 300 pound on it,
but then I I think I might as well just
go roulette if I'm going to put 300
pound on something like that.
Yeah. Well, what's the maximum you would
ever put on a bet?
I think honestly me. Yeah. Honestly,
money I hadn't won like normally. Uh
No, I'm saying what's the most you'd
ever put on a football bet?
I would say me. Yeah,
it'd have to be like 130 120 130. I
don't I can't put more on that, bro. I
can't put more on it.
No, I'm saying what's the most you would
ever put on the football?
Mine's Yeah, it's got to be like 120
130. I'd love to put £500 on it, but
that's a lot of money to risk on a
[ __ ] football bet, bro. You know,
I don't think I can do it, bro.
Yeah. So, what I'm saying is what's the
most you would ever put on the football Yeah,
I put one I think the most I put was
130. I've done 120 a few times, but it's
one, isn't it?
80 pound. Yeah.
Do you know what wouldn't be bad? 80
pound double uh both score no draw. That
would be like 800 pound 7800 pound.
I think that would be a good bet, you know.
So what? You never put £300 on the football,
Steven Allard? No.
I think if I want money on roulette
here, I'd put some of it on a double
both score no draw. So a double both
teams to score on the Tuesday.
I reckon that's the only time I could
put more than 120 on it, bro.
Other than that, I can't really
Yeah, there is a prayer. I got it last,
but I won. That was a double B card. no
draw. I didn't have both score no draw
on it, but it was a it was a both score no draw. You know
it does come in.
Glad you enjoyed it.
So, uh, watch this, Grezy. You're only
letting Steven How would put £50 on the
football now. Are you his, uh,
financial, uh, advisor as well?
Are you, uh, also his financial advisor, boss?
I'm stuffed as well, mate.
What's this about? He can only put uh50
on it, boss. Oh,
do you remember if I had a baby it'd be
whisked straight into care. Greasy.
Oh, don't say that.
Risk whisked straight into care. Oh, bless.
Nah, that baby wouldn't be in care.
He'd be with his daddy.
Is that cute?
No, no, no.
Where's that [ __ ]
Where's that [ __ ] skin?
See, sometimes it just comes out.
Yeah. Every time I do a bet on Tuesday,
Greavesy, I win. I win the Tuesday matches. >> [snorts]
>> straight in the car. I always win on the
Tuesdays. I like the Tuesday ones. It's
like I said, it's it's closer to
midweek, isn't it? So,
I might put 150 on the football next time.
Greavves, is that okay with you, boss?
Okay with you, boss.
This Jamie Thompson needs to get a
[ __ ] life, bro.
He really, really needs to get a life.
This [ __ ] Jamie Thompson, bro.
I was thinking about that [ __ ] I got
in the alleyway, Reezy, um earlier.
It was nice. Lovely little [ __ ]
She was dirty. She was very, very dirty.
Very, very dirty.
I've tried to get her a few times, Grezy,
on social media, but
she keeps avoiding me.
I said that I've got I had my dick in your mouth.
Yeah, she's from Georgia. I can't tell
you her name though. Um, Grezy cuz
obviously the virgin, the skint virgin.
You know what he's like, that [ __ ]
skin virgin, mate.
You know what that bloody skin virgin's like, mate.
You know what that skin [ __ ] is like. Yep.
Well, I know it can't be Georgia, is he?
Cuz George is in America.
That was a lovely [ __ ] That was
Yeah, I will be doxing them. Don't
worry, bro. [ __ ] loser.
This guy is jealous, bro.
He's a weirdo.
No. No. The state in America.
You remember Grezy? You need to latch on
to other boobies, isn't it?
Yeah. Latch on to other boobies. Am
I your favorite YouTuber? Grieves on his community.
Yeah, he's a proper stalker. Proper
Well, which ones do you think provides
the freshest milk?
That Bob account was saying there's no
um there's no change in this [ __ ]
situation. That Bob account keeps
mocking me. Greasy.
Why does he keep mocking me?
Oh, I feel better today, Grezy. I was so
[ __ ] on uh Friday. Ask Steven Howard.
I was being sick and everything.
Yep. I was [ __ ] almost dead.
Yep. We need new meat.
Greavesy. So why did um why did USA pull
her top up
to show her boobies? Greavesy h. [snorts]
Yeah, because they're not interested in
this Downey community, bro. To be fair,
because they're not interested in this
[ __ ] spasticated community. I mean,
can you [ __ ] blame them?
Imagine I added wine greasy on Thursday.
I think I legitimately would have been dead.
I think if I drunk wine with the
cocktails, I would have been dead. I
would 100% been dead.
I think I would have been finished. Yeah.
Not even joking.
Yeah. The last two bets I've done on a
Tuesday, Stephen Howard, I won. Yeah.
Yeah. And that one on my mom's birthday.
I won a football bet on my mom's
birthday. 120 to 380.
Then uh 120 to 360. Yeah,
I like the National League.
You know, the normal league like League
One, League Two, they're too hard, bro.
It No, they're too [ __ ] hard. Whereas
the National League, there's loads of goals. Yeah.
>> Yeah. It's too It's too hard leaks.
Going for a little pee.
I'm going for a little pee pe
any any uh any national league.
Even even the south one is good. The
south one is good, bro. Yeah,
even the south one is good.
Lenny National um league.
Oh gosh. Oh gosh,
Greasy. Oh gosh.
Do you reckon I should do that one day?
go out drinking on a Tuesday
with a football bat on a Tuesday.
Tuesday's dead though, is it?
Yeah, Tuesdays are dead though, bro.
Tuesdays are [ __ ] dead.
Where's this Joseph Farel?
Right. I'll be back tomorrow anyways. See you.