Sorry about that.
Someone call me mate.
Sorry about that, matey.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, someone call me.
Who the [ __ ] is that? No,
leave me alone. You skin virgin.
Delete these community posts. Let's
do these football bits. [ __ ] bro. [sighs]
>> [clears throat]
>> Coming back for Huh?
[ __ ] That's why we're not letting you
in. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
Trying to put nudes up. You [ __ ]
stupid little [ __ ] [ __ ] off. Go get a life.
I swear people on here really need to
get a life some people, bro. Seriously. [clears throat]
Oh, [ __ ] get life. Evil warriors.
You know, I'd be so sick if any of these
channels had different insults.
No different insults. Just the same
repeating. They killed a whole community off.
They're [ __ ] boring. [clears throat]
These people are here, man.
Oh, look at these little self-p projecting comments.
Got my benefit. PJ was born to be one of
life's complete loser. Poor little no
job, had a job. No money, got more money
than you. No women had more women than
you. No friends got more friends than
you. No house in a house right now. No
car, don't need a car. Have had more of
a life than you would ever at 20 [ __ ]
eight. It's just self projectors. Like
this is the thing what I mean. Yeah. It's
these people come on here, right, and
think that they can criticize other
people's lives when, bro, they're
literally sat on YouTube all day. They
can't take a day off of YouTube, bro.
They could never ever call anyone a
uh a loser.
They literally they literally can't.
They're living their worst life
and they think that they can call
anybody a loser. It's pathetic. How can
you say that someone's got no house when
they're literally in a house right now
and saying that they've got no money
when I've literally got more money than
you have? Spoken me. I guarantee you
right now I have lived slav of a life at
28 than you have at your age now.
However the [ __ ] old you are, 30s, 40s.
I can guarantee you that. I really
really can guarantee that. You know
these people think everyone's got the
same life as them. [snorts] They
generally generally look in the mirror,
they see themselves, and they project
their life onto other people.
That's what they do on this community.
That's literally all they do.
They self project.
That's what they do on here. That is literally
literally what they do
on here. It's so weird.
And don't forget these people are older
than me as well. Yeah.
Oh, I found his account.
Where is he? Who's that? Huh?
No, I was just saying they're just
weirdos on here. I'm just on this
account um that does uh videos of me,
Monty, and Timmy.
They're just weirdos, bro.
Bro, what's this [ __ ] up? I'm just
reading this up. Money Mike saying I'm
about it, bros. Run from a 20 from 11y
old. If someone gives me the address in
Ronford, I'll pay now Bane and who a
visit. Bro, I will give you my address
right now, bro. Like, I won't even make
you come all the way here. I will
literally meet you in London if you
want. Yeah. Wait until this guy comes
out, bro. I'm going to [ __ ] him up, bro.
I swear to God, this money mike. Yeah.
Let me sub to this channel. I'm going to
sub to this channel. You're going to pay
me a visit, bro. I'll break your [ __ ]
jaw. Like, it's it's not even a joke,
bro. You're going to you're going to
come to this address. Really? I'm just
reading these comments from this thing, bro.
You know about it. Bro, you got beat up
by a woman, bro. A woman slap, bro. A
woman. Yeah. Put your head on the table
multiple times and you didn't do
anything. Yeah. Don't come to the
address. You don't even need to come to
the address, bro. Just come to the train
station away from it and I will meet
you. Simple. That's that.
Yeah, I'm seeing this money m's
comments. I'm clipping these, by the
way. I'm going to start on this [ __ ] so
we can't try and say that he's he's not
said these things.
But when you come to London, you was
like a pedigree dog. You was like a
pedigree dog, bro. You were [ __ ] yourself. Yeah.
You're not paying no one a visit, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, he's commenting on this um account.
The UK's um biggest nonser.
This Smokey B is such a projector, bro.
He's a proper proper proper projector. Projector.
No house, no money, no job. I was like,
bro, I'm sure you're talking about yourself.
I'm sure you've definitely definitely
definitely got to be talking about yourself. Like,
no. I've never been that guy's friend,
bro. He's a snake,
bro. You're just a [ __ ] projector.
No house, bro. What am I in right now?
No money. I've got more money than you.
Like, bro, you're a joke. You're a
Milton Kings joke. That's literally what
you are. Where is it? Here we go. Here
we go. PJ was born to be one of life's
complete losers. Poor little special
Pete. No job. Had a job. No money. Got
more money than you. No woman. I've had
more women than he has. No friends. Got
more friends than he has. No house. I'm
in a house right now. No car. I don't
need a car. I live in London. And no
life. Bro, I swear this guy's talking
about himself. I'm I'm I'm I'm pretty
sure, right? This guy has got us mixed up.
I'm pretty sure this guy has got has got
us mixed up. Like his disabilities has
definitely definitely got himself mixed
up with me. Bro, you've just said that
I've got no friends and no life, bro.
Are you being for real? Are you
literally literally being for real?
Really? Are you Are you actually being
for real right now, bro? Come on. It's
embarrassing. Stop it.
Stop it, bro. It's It's embarrassing. It
really really really really is embarrassing.
I'm sure these people's disabilities get
them [ __ ] confused with they get
themselves confused with other people.
I'm telling you, bro. I'm telling you,
it's their disabilities. It's definitely
definitely their disabilities.
No life, bro. The guy doesn't even leave his house.
Let me see if this guy
I'm going to give this I'm going to give
Money Mike this address, bro.
Yeah, I'm going to call this [ __ ] bluff.
Yeah, if he replies back, I'm going to
call his br his bluff, bro.
Watch. I'm I'm coming on his channel right now.
He's going to pay me a visit. Really? Yeah.
You sure about that, buddy? You sure about that? [ __ ] idiot.
Yeah. [clears throat] You sure about that?
Yeah, man. Anyway, Steven Howard,
what is it with these projectors on this community?
What is it with these [ __ ] projectors?
No life, bro. I've been up and down the
country for years. I've been traveling
for years to places
whilst you've been sat on YouTube. Don't
even leave your house. Stuck in Milton
Kees. Can't take a [ __ ] day off of
[ __ ] YouTube. I mean, bro, you
seriously, seriously need to stop
talking about yourself.
You really, really, really, really do.
This Mo is definitely definitely
definitely talking about himself.
100 million% he's talking about himself.
No money. How could you
possibly know how much money people have?
Like, how could you possibly know how
much money people have? That doesn't
even make any sense. You know, in the
last few times you've said that, you've
been proven wrong. Just like you tried
to say about how people um you know
can't afford new trainers. You was wrong,
bro. You're talking about yourselves.
You don't know how much money people have.
I'm telling you, bro, it's their
disabilities. It generally generally is
their disabilities, bro, that get them confused.
Um, it doesn't it doesn't matter how
much I don't I didn't go out at the
weekend. I went on I went out on
Thursday. I didn't go out on the weekend.
Oh, sorry. Um, did I do much of the
weekend? Sorry. No, I didn't do anything
at the weekend. So, I thought you meant
how much I've done. Sorry. No, I didn't
do anything at the weekend. I went out on Thursday
and um yeah,
so yeah, they definitely they definitely are.
Greavves. I went on that UK's biggest
nonser account and that money mic
saying, "Oh, if you give me um
Diabanian's address, I'll pay him a
visit." I was like, "Oh, really? Yeah,
really, really?" Okay. Well, I went on
his channel and I said, "Oh, you about?"
And when he comments, I'm going to start
a load of [ __ ] now, bro.
Is he? Good for him. No one cares.
Anyways, um yeah, so at the end of the day, bro,
um yeah, I'm going to say, "Oh, really?
Really? Really? Is that what you're
going to do? Really?
Oh, really? Is that what you're going to
do? Are you going to come to my address? [snorts]
Yeah. No one cares about the virgin. If
you keep bringing him up, I'm going to
block you. But
just like Monty says to all the people
in the chat, no one gives a [ __ ] bro.
Go and get a life. You people seriously need one.
Virgin boy, [ __ ] Smokey Bee, you
seriously seriously need a life.
And that's me actually being honest.
That's not even me joking. Yeah. So,
call the police on me. Crack on. No one
gives a [ __ ]
So, yeah. You people seriously seriously
need to get a life.
And then that smokey be self projecting non-stop
nonstop self projecting
nonstop self projecting.
And you got some [ __ ] saying he's going
to come to my address.
Yeah. Okay, bro.
I think these people seriously need to
get a life on here.
I'm going to come off um tomorrow for a
couple of weeks, I reckon. Yeah.
Yeah, definitely, bro. Definitely. Absolutely. Definitely.
So, yeah, it's weird. It really, really
is weird. It's cringe.
That's why you need to take like a
couple of weeks off of it before like coming back.
very very weird obsessed autistic lowife people.
So yeah, I'm not laughing when I'm saying that.
Not even laughing, bro.
[ __ ] weird, isn't it?
It is sad, isn't it? is sad.
I don't know because it's cuz it's a
pedo. Whoever's behind it is a [ __ ]
pedo, bro. Obviously.
Obviously. Po [ __ ] pudo, aren't they? [clears throat]
I just think these people need to get a
life. That's what I think.
I don't know who's behind it.
I think the Skint Virgin needs to get a
life. I think Smokey Bee needs to get a
And whoever's behind that [ __ ]
account needs to get alive.
That's what I think, mate. Yeah.
So, what he said that he's calling the
police on me? What a loser. So, you come
on YouTube every single day cuz you're a
[ __ ] lowife loser. And any chance you
think you've got of running to the
police, trust me, it's not going to
work. Then you say that you're calling
the police. What a [ __ ] loser.
Obviously, I know people on here don't
have [ __ ] um any pride on here, so
they don't really care what you call
them, but what a [ __ ] loser.
Yeah. What a loser.
What a [ __ ] loser.
acting like the big [ __ ] on YouTube,
then running to the police, you [ __ ]
virgin loser. If I had a brother, yeah,
I would say, "You [ __ ] loser." If he
was doing [ __ ] like what he was doing,
I'd be like, "You [ __ ] virgin loser."
And I actually would give him a back
slap around his [ __ ] head. I said,
"You're nothing but a fling loser." And
I'd give and I'd give him [ __ ] I'd
tell him straight.
Who said you he clipped you?
>> Oh, good for him. No one gives a [ __ ]
Yeah, did he call the police?
Yeah, send it to the police, you loser.
Yeah, go. No one gives a [ __ ] They're
not going to do anything anyways. So,
no one gives a [ __ ] So, yeah,
you [ __ ] loser.
>> [clears throat]
>> It's all right. I've got plenty of [ __ ]
on you anyways, you [ __ ] virgin.
You know, I've got plenty of [ __ ] on you
anyways, mate. That's already been sent
to the barristister. So, no problem,
Virgin boy. Crack on. Crack on all you
like, matey. Not a problem.
You know, they just ain't seen your
virgin channel yet. I don't go on it cuz
I don't go on virgin channels. That's
what I told you. I told you I literally
don't go on that channel, but I have
loads of things from it. It's I don't go
on Virgin's channels. It's a waste of time.
So, but yeah, crack on anyways.
Crack on anyways. I've got loads of [ __ ]
on this [ __ ] anyways. So,
you [ __ ] loser.
[clears throat] Whoever's behind that
account, they're a [ __ ] coward just
like him. Anyways, so
nothing but a bunch of losers.
It's probably Chase behind that Red Star
account to be honest. Pair of virgin
losers. That's what they are. A pair of virgin losers.
They ain't got a single life to stand on. So yeah,
coming on the internet like you're some
kind of big [ __ ] You [ __ ] skinny
little virgin. And then any time you
think you can call the police, you run
to the police. What a loser, man. What a
skint loser. I've never known, right,
such a loser in my life. I I swear to
God, bro. Honestly,
whoever the [ __ ] it is, they're a coward.
Whoever the [ __ ] it is, bro. Like I
said, I don't go on any of the channels anymore,
but obviously I know what they do
because obviously it's the same [ __ ]
But I don't go on any of the channels.
So when they're doing content of me, I ignore it.
I completely ignore it.
I completely ignore it, mate. So,
>> I don't go on any of the channels cuz
there's no point
cuz um there's no point arguing with
keyboard warrior losers that are never
going to meet you
that are never ever going to meet you. So, low lives >> [screaming]
>> One second, bro. [snorts]
So, we'll wait for that uh
money mic. See if he responds.
Yeah, he's a stalker. He's a stalking
little virgin that can't get laid.
That's why he hates the [ __ ] when I
say stuff about him because it's the
truth. He's the biggest virgin going. He
hates that he can't get laid and Peter
Belly's had some. That's all it is, mate.
He hates the fact that Peter Belly's had
some and he's still that virgin and it
kills him inside, mate. [ __ ] kills him.
Knowing that he's a big virgin kills him
every day knowing that he's never stuck
his dick up nothing and he never will.
Oh, did you did you go on the account, Gregy?
How did you find him, bro?
Yeah, it was from 13 days ago. But yeah,
I commented on his channel. Anyways,
I say I don't mind giving you the address.
What? Did you look him up, Grezy?
What? You actually looked him up on
Instagram? What the [ __ ] [clears throat]
Yeah, but it was in Yeah, but it was in small writing.
Yeah, but it was in small [ __ ] writing.
It It was in small writing, matey.
So, how did you [ __ ]
Oh, okay. So, yeah, just just don't just
don't just don't say the Instagram account.
Uh, that's probably why he wanted to uh
stop the fight in it, Scooby. Yeah.
Yeah, it was a like small item.
Oh, just cuz I told him that I really liked him.
Yeah, it makes sense now.
Bro, that sucks.
Yeah, that sucks. Eh,
what do you think of the money mic situation, Scooby? Yep.
Yeah. Adam's a cool fella.
Don't put his uh Instagram up, Grezy. Yeah.
Yeah. This nonsense is a proper loser.
He probably wants me to like message him
on WhatsApp and rage so he can get the
police involved. What a [ __ ] loser. Low life.
That's somebody living their worst life,
bro. That is somebody living their worst
life. What a [ __ ] loser.
Imagine that though, bro. Like, imagine
getting kicked down to the floor. Yeah.
And you've got no fight left in you
whatsoever. You're so much of a loser.
You got no fight left that you have to
run to the police. Imagine being that
much of a loser. Would that not hurt
your pride? Not even a ounce of fight
left in you. What a loser.
There's a few of them on here though,
bro, that run to the police.
There's a few of them that do it, bro.
They're losers. They always run to the
police in the end of losers.
A lot of people do it on here as well.
[ __ ] losers. Ain't got no life.
Wait until I show the police again all
the [ __ ] that he's been doing. I've got
everything, mate. So, I'm not asked.
[snorts] I've got every little bit of
stalking, all the harassment calls,
[ __ ] everything, mate. So,
I've got [ __ ] everything on that
[ __ ] Skint virgin. So,
everything, mate. [ __ ] everything. I
tell K every time he comes on, bro.
I've literally got everything. Oh yeah.
Yeah. But why did he rape a woman in a park? H.
That's a madness, bro.
You would have thought I would have been
the one to do it, didn't it, Greasy? Nah.
Why would he do that though? I don't get it.
Oh, so it wasn't proper rape, was it?
I mean, I got a [ __ ] before in the al anyway.
I got a [ __ ] before in an alleyway.
And she was drunk, but I was drunk as well.
Well, I was drunk as well, but I mean,
she was drunk and she kept coming on to me.
She's like, "I really want you, but I
don't think you want me."
You remember that one, Grievy? I said, "I do,
but I don't think you want me. [laughter]
I really want you, but I don't think you want me.
Yeah, I got a [ __ ] in an alleyway,
Scooby, from some drunk American. [laughter]
It was lush, Greavesy. Absolutely lush. [snorts] [laughter] Yeah.
So, is he done for? Huh?
So is he done for? [snorts] Yep.
That's not going to happen, mate.
Because I've got so much evidence on
this [ __ ] It's not going to happen.
It's not going to happen. He wishes.
Trust me, it's not going to happen. So,
you wish, mate, that would never happen.
That would never happen. You can call
the police all you like. I'm not I don't
give a [ __ ] They're not going to do anything anyways.
Having broken know nothing. So,
it's never going to happen, mate.
Uh, you're more than welcome to call the
police. I'm not asked.
It just shows how much of a loser you are.
Doesn't bother me.
To me, it shows you're a loser and
someone's got you by the balls. If you
have to call the police, it just shows
that you you're a loser.
[snorts] That's all it does. It just
shows that you're a loser. When you have
to get police involved, you're just a loser.
Just a lo a loser that's been owned. So,
you've had to get the authorities
involved because you're so much of a
loser. You had to involve the
authorities because you got owned.
So, you're more than you're more than
welcome to call the police. I'm not
asked. I don't give a [ __ ] So,
I don't give a [ __ ] matey.
And that just shows how he is so
obsessed with me. His virgin skint life
revolves around me. Have you noticed that?
The [ __ ] must be jealous of me or
something. He says that he's got this
girlfriend, Scooby, right? But he spends
all his life stalking me. Every second
of every day stalking me. Yeah, I'm the
one that's supposed to be ugly. I'm the
one that's supposed to be skinn. But he
jeopardizes his life stalking me every
day. That's not someone that's happy.
That's not someone that's got money.
That's not somebody that's in a happy relationship.
Someone that sits online stalking all
day. That's a low life. That is
literally a low life.
That is someone that's not happy with
their life. It's the truth. I know these
things, bro. All the things I've said
about Bomb before was true. Like all the
things I've said about other people.
It's jealousy. It's got to be something
like jealousy or gay or obsession. It's something, bro.
It's definitely definitely something,
you know, someone someone with a good
life doesn't do this
has a has a virgin channel dedicated to
someone every single day that I don't
even go on it. I don't post anything. I
don't go on it cuz I don't contradict
what I say. Do you understand? I'm not contradicting
what I say. What I say about you, I say
about you. your skin. You look like a
rat and you're a virgin. So, I don't
need to post every I don't need to post
things every day because what I'm saying
about you is the truth. If I waste every
second of every day posting about you,
I'm contradicting what I'm saying. You see?
Like, you're [snorts] contradicting what
you're saying when you talk about me. [ __ ] loser.
Absolute [ __ ] loser, mate. [gasps] Oh, [ __ ] loser.
Life dedicated to stalking somebody that
you claim you're better than. Make it
make sense. Loser.
Absolute [ __ ] loser.
And then you've got this [ __ ]
ghosting account, right?
Telling you to let these people in.
So yeah, what a loser, mate. What an
absolute [ __ ] loser.
Running to the police. What a loser, mate.
Just shows that you get owned. You don't
own no and you little loser. Shitag.
You can't even meet anyone and you have
to run to the police every time you get
a good ass whooping.
[ __ ] [ __ ] [snorts]
That's what they are when they are
losers, bro. Absolute losers.
[snorts] And you want me to let these
people in the [ __ ] Streamyards?
[ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that. Let some
letting some skint virgin in that run to
the police. Some virgin. [ __ ] that. I'm
not letting no virgin come on my channel.
That's why I don't [ __ ] go on their channel.
You can delete and delete and delete.
I've got everything. [snorts]
I've got literally everything, mate. So,
[ __ ] weirdos, bro. Weirdos.
and also I can I can also show the
police where I've reported this [ __ ]
multiple times for stalking me and
calling me a million times. depends on
his number, right? And you've not done
anything about it. So, if you really
want to go legal, mate, we can go legal.
I don't give a [ __ ]
I can put everything up. The golden, the
stalking, um, where I've reported it and
they've done nothing and this little
virgin keeps posting about me every day.
I don't give a [ __ ] Simple.
So, that's that. I don't watch any of these people.
I go live and people come on my channel.
I don't go on anyone else's channel.
Only Monty's sometimes. I don't go on
any other channels
cuz it's just self projection.
Self- projecting virgins. Yeah.
Yep. Self projecting virgins. [ __ ]
Yeah, you didn't need to hear that.
You didn't need to hear that, matey. So yeah,
so VR is back stalking people, huh?
Back stalking people. Wow. Did I?
Let me see.
I'm going to tell him to come on my
live. Oh, yeah. One second.
Yeah, he just replied. I told him to
come on my live right now, bro. I'm
going to give him this address. Okay.
Yeah. Yeah. I said, "Yo." Yeah. He
replied, "Yeah, thanks." I told him,
"Come my live stream right now, bro.
[ __ ] this [ __ ] [ __ ] this [ __ ] bro." Yeah,
cuz don't say something if you're not going to
[ __ ] do it. Let him come on this live stream.
Guy's a [ __ ] bro. [ __ ]
Guys are [ __ ] [ __ ] [clears throat]
But yeah, I'm coming off tomorrow for a
couple of weeks anyways, bro. So
Don't expect you're going to be seeing me, matey. Yeah. [ __ ] weirdos.
[ __ ] weirdos in this community.
Don't know. don't care. They're weirdos
on here. I don't know why they're
putting [ __ ] people with um family
members up and [ __ ] as well. I'm coming
off anyways after tomorrow.
So, for a couple of weeks. So, that's me anyways. [clears throat] Yeah.
Same people every day. No life. Yeah.
Anyways, let this [ __ ] come on my
channel. I'm going to I'm going to give
him this address since he said he's
going to pay me a visit.
Oh, he's going to pay me a visit, bro.
He's mad. This is what I mean, bro. It's
the same atmosphere with these people.
It's the same [ __ ]
Pay me a [ __ ] visit. [ __ ] off. I'm leave, bro. Oh [ __ ]
It's weird. These people are weirdos.
Anyways, is this guy coming on my live
stream or what? [snorts] Huh? Come on.
Mike's replied to me, Scooby. So, that
was a load of [ __ ]
Nah, it's weird, bro.
This community is weird.
[sighs and gasps] It's weird.
And then they're making up stupid rumors
and Oh, [ __ ] that, bro.
Yeah, it is.
It is on It is him under that account
cuz I'm on his channel.
Come to this address tomorrow, bro, and
I'll make you say sorry, bro.
I'll make you say sorry. Come on.
Let's Let's see what he's about.
Too many little weasels on this community. Weasels,
isn't it crazy? Yep.
I think these people need to get a life. Yeah.
Virgin boy is such a loser. I've never
come across such a loser in my life.
Well, at least you know what to do anyways. People
never meet anyone with autism.
Never meet anyone with autism. Yeah.
Never meet with autism, mate. That's all
I can say.
Well, say I mean,
not every single autistic person is
going to stalk you, though. So, I mean,
it's not everyone, is it?
You can't get rid of that virgin. No
matter what you do, you literally can't
get rid of that virgin.
Copies my holidays. Says Sher Cole's
good-looking to fit in.
No, he's not a loony. He's not mad. He's
just a cowardly loser virgin. He's not mad.
He's a He's a coward. Loonies. Mad loies
meet people. He's a coward virgin.
He's a He's a He's a coward virgin
loser. He's not mad. No, no, no. He's
not mad. Mad people meet people. Mad
people are not keyboard warriors. So
yeah, not not not mad.
Definitely definitely not a loony.
Definitely not mad. Just a just a
[ __ ] complete obsessed weirdo is the word. Yeah. Yeah,
probably somebody copied my holiday.
That she [clears throat] cole thing. I
can't get over that bloody Shevel Cole thing.
What a loser as well. Getting the police
involved. What a loser.
I couldn't believe it when he done that.
What an absolute loser.
This is what I mean. They're all losers
on here. Obsessed losers. I mean, like I
said, I don't even go on their channel
anymore. I never never will ever again.
Never will ever again. Just losers.
can't do that. Steven Howard, as you
know, he's going to get the police involved.
That's not going to work because he's
going to get the police involved.
That's what his whole whole aim is. He's a loser.
That's what his whole aim is. Is getting
the police involved. He's a loser. He's
never going to meet anyone. He's never
going to say anything to anyone's face.
Just like that Red Star.
They're just losers. That's what I'm
trying to say to you. They're never ever
going to meet anyone. They just want to
get the police involved.
It's the whole trying to bait people to
meet them and that it's all to get the
police involved. That's all it's ever
been. They need to grow up. They need to
get a life. They're absolute losers. And
I'm coming off this tomorrow for a
couple of weeks. Anyways, it's the same atmosphere again.
Same repeating people. Same [ __ ] off
this money mic as well.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Listen, listen. I'm not playing these
games, brother. I'm 28 years of age. I'm
not playing keyboard warrior games.
Yeah. You understand me? I'm not playing
silly little keyboard warrior games with
silly little virgins.
Yeah. I'm 28. Yeah. Not 8 18 months.
Yeah. I'm not I'm not 28 days, should I
say? Should I say I'm not 28 days old?
I'm 28 years old. I'm not playing these
silly little games.
These silly little virgin games.
You like the way I say it, lad?
You know what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah. Well, if he's really called the
police and the police will come, I'll
show them what he keeps doing. I've got
the whole harassment folder that this
[ __ ] will not leave me alone. He keeps
harassing me. So if he has called the
police then it's done me a favor again
really if they even come. I mean they
I'll have to show it again is it?
This stupid little virgin [ __ ] keeps
harassing me right. This little virgin
and obviously I've got the thing where
the [ __ ] court kept they kept telling
me to report it. So I've got the I've
got the reference number as well.
Yeah. So I've been like well it's been reported.
So, I mean, you can't really say it's
not been reported, can you now fake? You
know what I mean?
But I mean, he's he's not harassing.
He's just shown himself up. I mean, I
don't go on the channel anymore, so he's
wasting his time. Like I said, I've not
been on it for over a week, and I will
never go on it ever again.
Oh, I've got everything. I've got a
whole harassment folder.
I've got a harassment folder with 161
things in it. Videos, call logs. I've
got everything, mate. Every little thing I've got.
And if they want to try and say, "Well,
why didn't you report it?" Well, there's
a crime reference number there. It's
been reported multiple times
because that's what the court told me to do. So,
so that's that 160 uh
16 161 things.
Anyways, I don't give a [ __ ] We're not
talking about this anymore. I'm not
going on the channel and anyone that
brings it up is just going to get
blocked. So, anyone that brings it over
to this channel is going to get blocked
because I don't go on it anymore. I will
never go on that channel again. Just
like that Red Star channel. So anyone
that brings it over here is [ __ ] stoing
because I'm not going on that channel ever again.
So he can be a keyboard warrior all he
wants. That's fine. I'm not interested. Simple.
He can be a harder keyboard warrior. He
can be the biggest hard keyboard warrior
going for the rest of his life. I'm not
interested. I'm never going on it ever
again. So I'm not going to see anything.
So, the only way you're going to get
through to me is
well, unless you come at the [ __ ]
door or something. I'm not going to see anything. So,
I won't see anything unless you come in
the [ __ ] door. So, yeah.
The only the only thing I'll say is what
I've been saying forever is he needs to
get laid. Simple. That's that. Yeah.
When will I go out approaching again?
Not for a while. Not for a while.
No, I won't be doing it for a while.
I might try and meet that number that replied. Yeah, Yeah.
Yeah. It won't be for a while to be
honest. I just don't care about it anymore.
I'm not interested, you know.
I'm not interested anymore, mate. One second. >> [sighs]
>> Yeah. Lost. Oh, lost.
No, that's USA. Is he
said thank you?
You said thank you.
What a loser, mate. What?
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro. I'm [ __ ] Virgin. Oh [ __ ]
What a loser.
What a [ __ ] loser, mate.
jumping out of windows. What a loser.
Oh, Steven, do you watch porn? >> [laughter]
>> What the [ __ ]
That's some That's some one on here, bro. It [clears throat] greasy.
What have you called, bro?
What have you caused? H
What have you caused me?
What the [ __ ] bro?
These people need to get a life.
They need to get a life on here.
>> [clears throat]
>> Just [ __ ] Jamie Thompson keeps
[ __ ] stalking me as well. Steven Howard,
I keep getting these weird calls.
[ __ ] weird, is it, bro?
So [ __ ] weird. Was
you trying to message Adam?
Was you trying to message Adam, bro?
That's not nice of you, bro. Yeah,
another jealous loser that ain't got a
life. Just like most of these on here. [snorts] Yep.
[ __ ] weirdos, man. Of
course she uses filters.
I know that. You know that.
I don't know who took it.
I don't know.
probably the person she was with. [sighs]
[ __ ] hell, mate.
That story was mad in it. Steven Howard,
do you want my number?
Virgin boy was raging when he saw that
approach. Absolutely raging. Yeah.
Oh my god. [sighs and gasps] I've got a
feeling I'm going to have the [ __ ] from
them wings, you know. [sighs and gasps] Oh gosh.
Not [snorts] good.
Yeah, I reckon so greasy.
Was you trying to message Adam Grezy?
Don't stop messaging his family and
stuff, bro. He's a cool dude. You know,
the only person that deserved that was
the Massachusetts witch.
The Massachusetts witch. We
catch my drift. Oh gosh. [clears throat]
well, you can find him on Facebook.
You can find them on Facebook. Grezy.
Just type Adam Thomas Brighton. Yeah. [snorts] Get a
I've been to Brighton loads of times.
Not for a night out though.
Never been there for a night out. Yeah. [snorts]
I've never [ __ ] been um never been
drinking there. Don't think I've ever drunk there.
black. Well, he's actually mixed race, but yeah.
What do you think the worst accent is in England?
It's got [clears throat] to be the bra
one, isn't it? Oh gosh.
Who's Stephen George?
The [ __ ] is that?
Don't message his family though, man. Please.
He hasn't done anything wrong. I mean,
he is a posh stockup [ __ ] but I mean, it doesn't, you know, Yeah.
You know, there's some uh Reddit
accounts, right, that was made 13 years
ago and they haven't been seen for 13
years agree. I guess they just gave up
on Reddit now.
>> Did she? That's good for her.
Yeah. Well, she's not allowed to.
>> Monty's got caught on the 27th, doesn't he?
It's the 27th, isn't it, Grezy? What you
This is 27 Gy. Yeah.
Well, he's got caught, don't he? He has
got caught, doesn't he, Grezy? >> [snorts]
>> He's got caught Very greasy.
Who the [ __ ] is Lady Z?
No, no, I'm I'm not going to sleep.
He's going Is he going?
Imagine he goes to prison though,
imagine he goes to prison, bro. Oh my
god. [ __ ] that.
He won't last in prison.
Oh, [ __ ] I almost just shut my underpants. [ __ ] hell.
Almost just shut my bloody underpants. Oh [snorts]
yeah, I still got that video where that
where that one in Nottingham gave me a
[ __ ] It was lush. Greasy. Absolutely lush.
Nope. Not interested. >> [snorts]
>> I don't know what I'm doing.
Why [snorts] would I be going out this week? Nah.
Well, maybe I'll ask if that uh number
wants to meet if they want to meet then.
Yeah. But like going out drinking. Nah.
No. [ __ ] that.
Won't be out for a while.
Weather's [ __ ] People are [ __ ] It's just
Yeah. Can't be asked.
[ __ ] Am I going out for bro?
I ain't going out drinking. Nah. >> [snorts] >> No,
I had a really bad hangover as well on Friday.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
Nothing lasts forever.
Does it Grezy? A
go now gets so boring, bro.
It gets boring.
It's It gets boring, bro. It's the same
[ __ ] every time. If you don't stick to
beer, the hangovers are bad.
You know, I'm definitely definitely
going to be leaving the country. I
definitely definitely definitely am.
Time for something different now. Ain't it grievy?
No, it's boring, bro. It is boring.
It's boring, bro.
What do you think, Grezy? >> [snorts]
>> The women are all the same. The people are [ __ ]
The [ __ ] hangovers are bad. [snorts] Yeah.
Why do you always ask if I'm going to go
out anyways, Bob? Why do you always ask that? Huh? [snorts]
It's also window as well, so it's [ __ ] >> [snorts]
>> What? I'm not buying any more presents.
I bought my mom agg boots and that's it.
I'm not buying anything else. [gasps] [snorts]
I'm not buying any more stuff. No,
it's about me this year, Grezy. Me.
I only care about myself.
It's [snorts] about me. Me
me me me me me me me me me me me me me me.
Okay with you, boss. Grezy,
it's about me me.
Okay with you, boss.
I'll never do Christmas braver again. No,
you don't get no thanks for it.
Is that right, Grezy?
Is this the thanks I get?
I see. I'll probably be out again.
It's not about mood. I don't I'm not
asked about it anymore. I'm not bothered
I don't care about it because it's
always going to be the same old here.
So, I just go out when I want to go out.
So, unless this person wants to meet, I
probably won't go out until December,
mid December, maybe. So,
because it'll always be the same here,
is it? So, there's no point going out every week.
There's literally no [ __ ] I could do
it as well if I want. I can afford it,
but it's just there's just really no point.
I want to save some money, raise some
money and [snorts] leave England as well
cuz you know uh uh uh yolo and that you
so [snorts] yeah
it's boring bro
I don't even feel like clubbing anymore
like when I go Well, I want to be in by
like 12, 1 the latest. I don't want to
go out until 7 8:00 in the morning
anymore. Been there, done it, worn the t-shirt, you know?
I want to go traveling. So, that's
[snorts] what I want to do. So,
obviously I need to save some money and
[ __ ] do some stuff, whatever. [snorts]
Um, and yeah, [sighs] [snorts]
I don't care about these [ __ ] anymore, bro.
I don't give a flying [ __ ]
I really don't care. They're all the
same anyways, so I don't give a [ __ ]
None of them are different. So yeah,
who cares about them? Isn't that right,
Grezy? As long as you've got a nice KFC
and [snorts] a warm cozy bed, you're laughing.
Isn't that right, Captain?
[sighs and gasps] Oh gosh.
Isn't that right, Greasy?
I like the Nottingham [ __ ] That was nice. Greasy.
But I kicked her out of the hotel room
when I came. Greasy.
Yeah, I kicked her out of the hotel
room. That's when I went to Nottingham with Ant-Man. Yeah,
I remember that. Yeah,
I went there the Saturday, come back the Monday.
I stayed another night, didn't I?
Good times, bro. Good times. [snorts]
So, I booked a hotel and Yeah.
[snorts] Uh, it's fun. Ain't it crazy? It's fun. [ __ ] Greavvesy.
Why do you always think about [ __ ] Greavvesy,
why do you love [ __ ] Greavves
obsessed with blowjobers and sex. [clears throat]
What is it with you greasy in [ __ ] Huh?
Yeah, I got a [ __ ] in Nottingham. Do
you remember that, Greavvesy? It was lush. Absolutely lush.
>> [clears throat] >> Yep. that virgin >> [snorts]
>> The red one
is a troll Man, >> [laughter]
>> Grim is such a troll.
You're such a Oh, gosh darn it.
You're such a troll, aren't you?
Aren't you, Grezy?
Oh gosh darn it.
So I'm going to have to live without
milk now. Is it Greavvesy?
I'll be able to do it, won't I, Grezy?
Yeah, I'll just have to try to live
without the milk now.
Do you think I look like my mama? Oh gosh.
Did you see that cam that said there's
loads of uh history for Peter Belly in
Elephant and Castle?
There's lots of history.
You don't get it, do you, Grezy?
What? They look like me. Yep. [snorts]
So what? We look like we're related. Greasy.
That feels horrible,
Gravesy. It feels really, really horrible.
Why did she abandon me?
My mommy's never called me a bastard.
This is my mommy. That's my
isn't it Grey
Peter Belly can't get attached anymore. Grey [laughter]
Peter really can't get attached anymore
because he's already found his mama. [laughter]
That [clears throat] account. Do you remember Greavvesy?
She wanted to keep it a secret.
Do you remember an account coming and
said it, Greavvesy? You remembering it?
I wonder who that is. It's the same
person that keeps doing it. Yeah.
How are we going to change our [ __ ]
situ? It's the same person doing it.
Creepsy, you do realize that, is it?
Just different accounts.
So what? You reckon she looks like me
more than Laney does?
Why does she look like me so much?
Greasy, that's weird. H
Greasy, that's really strange. H [laughter] she
[clears throat] crazy.
I don't even know where I came out of
these things from.
Yeah, cuz Laney doesn't look like me. Really? H
She had lost boobies. Greavvesy. Yep.
Yep. Lost boobies. Greavesy. A
just that account said Grezy that in
April will be 3 years since you met your mama.
3 years in April since you met your
mama. Time flies.
That's what I said.
You're not my mama. Go away.
A lot of history
for Peter Belly and anything and Castle Grezy.
because he's already found his mama.
Griez, are you actually fat in real life?
Grieves, are you actually fat in real life? Really?
All right, captain.
Oh, bless you, Greavvesy. It's all
right, though. It's winter,
Grevy. It's okay, though. It's winter,
you know. So,
in go to the gym in January.
in January, just save some money and go
to the gym. Just save money until like
March. That's what I'm going to do. Go
gym and save money until March. And yeah,
would I do some reacting to
No. No, I [ __ ] wouldn't.
Yeah, just go to the gym in January
until Feb until Feb March and save some money, bro. Yeah.
Well, bless you then.
Well, bless you, Grezy. It's okay for
now because it's winter, in it. So
you you don't find that funny, is it,
Greavves? What I told you earlier about
mass tag Brady went to B and Q and some women dropped
paint and it went everywhere and it went
on him. He was pissed off about it. I I
thought it was funny me.
I thought it was funny. me. Grezy. Oh,
that's my mama.
Yep, that's my mama.
You must know Yep.
Yeah, she's my mama.
What's so funny about that?
She's got lovely boobies as well. I've seen them.
She's not the same age as me. She's a
year and a half older than me.
She's not the same age. She's a year and
half year and a [snorts]
year and a half older.
Nope. That's my mama.
And she's got lovely boobies as well. 14 Maxwell.
I know. I've hooked up with her.
And her boobies are full of milk. So, yep.
Nope. [snorts] That's my mama.
No, she's a year and a half older than me. So, yeah. Yep.
That's cute. Is it graves day?
That's really cute, Grezy. That
that's my mama.
What do you like my mama 14 Maxwell?
She came on kissing me,
stroking my face.
She's my mama.
I don't like her, Greasy. But she'll
always be my mama, you know.
And I don't believe like blood
thickening the water, but you know, your
mum is your mama, is it, Grezy? Um, I
don't have any DVDs actually.
I can't help who my mom is. Why?
Why are you asking? Oh, bro.
I was um I'm just on this
flask checking the [ __ ] scores when I
put that 120 on the double both teams to score
and yeah when I won it was such a lush
feeling bro when it come double both
teams to score was lush absolutely lush
it was lush bro
120 to 380 was lush.
Is that right? Grievously lush Grey.
Why did my mommy come on kissing my mouth? Grezy,
I didn't think mas were supposed to do that. Grezy
Why is my mama
kissing me grieving? Huh? Oh gosh. Grievy.
Grievesy. Why did my mommy
start kissing me and stuff
crazy. I'm bloody talking to you.
Crazy. I'm bloody talking to y'all. Oh gosh.
I said, "Why was she Why did she come on
to me kissing my lips?
I didn't know mommies do that." Grievy
I don't think you're supposed to do that
with your babies and stuff, your children. You see Uh
yeah, when I won that um football match
on when I won the football belt on a Tuesday,
remember Steven Howard when I put 120 on
it and it returned 380?
That was lush.
That was [ __ ] lost.
That was actually lost, man.
That was a couple of months ago, was it?
I need to do another one
at some point.
Do you think my mom is pretty grievy?
Uh, no it wasn't. It was September.
No, it was September, I think. Cuz it
was still kind of warm outside.
And I was wearing shorts. No, it was September.
Do you think my mommy's beautiful, Grey?
No, it was September.
Well, you like my mama, Grezy.
What do you like about my mama? Really?
Would you would you go on a date with her? Greasy. Why?
You can get to know each other and stuff.
Yeah, but she
Yeah, but you could be you could be a
good couple and stuffy.
I wish I had 500 pound on that double.
Both teams just lost even hour that day,
man. [ __ ] hell.
Wish I had 500 bloody pound on it.
Yeah, she uses filters though. Greavves
USA is he uses filters.
Have you ever used an electric bike,
Greavesy? I have. They're quite fast.
You like uh
you like USA is greasy.
Is that right, Grezy? I think he likes her.
You like my mama?
I don't know where I found I find these
people from, Grezy. Oh,
I found her on the street. You see,
I found USA Izzy on the street actually.
Grezy, I found her on the on the street.
Is that cute?
Oh [ __ ] Was it heavy?
Must have been heavy. No. [ __ ] hell.
You remember that solissa I went on a date with?
She had big boobies as well, Grezy.
but she disappeared.
She left me all alone.
Oh, that's so cute.
Left me all alone. Oh gosh. Greasy,
you like it when I say that. Greasy.
I think you've got a crush on my mama.
Oh, do you like Adam?
Do you like Adam?
Yeah, Adam's a cute fella.
Yeah, he's a cute fellow, isn't he?
That's why he blocked.
I said, "I really like you, Adam." Yeah.
And then he blocked me.
Yeah. He's a cool fellow, Adam.
I can't believe he's got a white brother. Wow. Listen,
I really want you, but I don't think you want me.
>> Yeah, he does.
I agree with you. I'm going to I'm going
to link you something. Yeah. One sec. [laughter]
I'm going to upload this and link you it. Excuse.
Excuse my laughing in the background though. Yeah,
it's okay to like Adam. I like Adam as
well. He's a cool dude.
Adam's family or anything like that,
bro. [ __ ] that. Nah.
No. He's He's a cool guy.
laughing all day. Yeah, I'm going to
send you a greasy.
No, don't message me his family, bro.
He's He's He hasn't done anything to us.
Seriously, man. He's caught.
USA Izzy deserved it, Grezy. She started
it with me, so I finished it, you know.
Well, I'm going to send you this. One
second. Let it um upload. One sec.
Right. I'm going to post it. Yeah. One sec.
That made me [ __ ] howled all day, bro.
Bro, that just made me [ __ ] how bro.
You can hear it in it, bro. [ __ ] That
had me howing, bro.
I was dead.
I was dead. Like when he went to the guy
and said, "Excuse me, mate. Just woman
just [ __ ] just like got [ __ ]
spread drop paint all over me."
Oh, do you know who the guy is then, Greavesy?
Yeah, he's a YouTuber.
Yeah, I was laughing my off.
Ah, you know who he is then?
Oh, bless you.
You know who # Brady is?
No, he doesn't. He does traveling videos.
Did you hear me laugh in the background? Greasy. >> [laughter]
>> He said, "Excuse me, mate. Someone has
just knocked a [ __ ] in a plane and
it's kind over me." [laughter]
You would have been fuming it, creepsy.
You would have been fuming, would you?
He contacted Adam.
I mean, it's a waste of time really
because he's just harassing them. If
he's doing that stuff, Scooby, he's just
harassing them really. It's not going to
bother me. If he goes on my channel,
then what's he going to say? Oh, what?
You getting my [ __ ]
I mean, he can, but he's just going to
be harassing them.
He doesn't realize him contacting them
is him harassing them. So
he's a sad bastard though to be honest.
Like you remember when he was pretending
to be USA Izzy for 3 months.
I mean he's a sad fat low-life bastard.
I mean that's nothing.
I mean that's nothing compared to what
he's done in the past, bro. He literally
pretended to be somebody for 3 months
talking to himself. He literally was
speaking to himself for 3 months. Yeah,
that that's that's actually minor, bro. Very minor.
All he's doing is harassing him to be honest.
So, I mean, if he wants to do that, let
him crack on. The weirdo.
And that's who that account was
messaging my sister on Instagram.
Yeah, there's an account my sister had
to block. It kept stalking me and I got
rid of it. Then it kept like messaging
my sister. My sister blocked it in the
end. It's a [ __ ] loser, bro. That was
proper proper loser.
Leave Adam alone.
I know, bro. I know. It's a madness.
You know what makes me laugh, Scooby? Right. Oh, [ __ ]
Is that they they tried to call me a
virgin even though I proved I've had sex.
They they called me a virgin. Yeah, I've
proved I've had sex multiple times.
Multiple times. I've proved I've had sex
multiple [ __ ] times, mate.
But then when I call nons legs a virgin,
everyone's like, "Oh, we can't be a
virgin. He's got a girlfriend." But then
when people call me a virgin, no one
says nothing. I mean, people on here
love nonses, so
it's it is what it is, lad. Yep. So,
you like Adam, don't you, Greasy?
I like Adam. You like Adam? Adam's a cool dude.
He's a cool dude. Adam.
I know that, bro. I already know that.
That's what I've been saying for [ __ ] years. Yeah,
that pain thing was funny, ain't it,
Grey? This room is just [ __ ] not pain. [laughter] Oh, bless.
Oh, I can't stop fighting. Oh gosh. Oh gosh,
I can't stop fighting. I think it was
them bloody wings. Gosh,
hope I don't poo myself. Oh gosh. [ __ ] sake.
No, [clears throat] I had KFC earlier.
Put the picture up now. Stop giving him
chances. Put the picture up. [ __ ] him, bro.
[ __ ] him. He's the one that's been
stalking my [ __ ] sister on Instagram.
The sad bastard.
Yeah, do it.
It's so [snorts] obvious it's V.
This is what I mean with these people on
this gre on this community grieves you.
You get rid of one of the [ __ ]
right? And then another one comes.
See, that's what I mean with this
community. You get rid of one, you're
like, "Oh, okay. We got rid of one now.
They've been defeated. And then another one comes.
You get rid of them, then another one comes."
Have you noticed that? Jesus Christ. [snorts] Yep.
I bet he's going to regret meeting me
now. It grieves Adam.
Yeah. He's going to be like, "Fucking hell." [snorts]
Because if people start messaging him
from this community, he's going to
think, "What the fuck?" Obviously,
cuz apparently V. Yeah, he's a sad that
V. Sad sad bastard.
He's a sad bastard.
They shouldn't contact him or he's
family, man. He's a cool guy.
[snorts] See what I mean? Griev I don't
just [ __ ] with people for no reason,
bro. I wouldn't [ __ ] with people for no
reason. USA Izzy deserved it.
And she's lucky it was just her family
that that that got contacted. I didn't I
didn't go there and kill her, bro.
Seriously. Like, you think it's a joke,
but it isn't a joke.
You know, you think it's funny. It's not
even funny, bro.
It's not even funny. It's not even
You know, it's not funny, Grezy. It's
not funny. It's not funny.
I don't message people's family randomly, bro.
Is he still saying M as well? That V. He
needs They need to think of some new comebacks.
Grezy. Yeah, we need, you know, when you
said we need new meat and content. Yeah,
we need new comebacks as well, bro.
These [ __ ] repeating people still
using the same [ __ ] Shitty little
[ __ ] projecting insults.
They need to think of some new um new
sayings as well.
See on this con on this right we've got
we always bring up new
things and if we do say that if we say
old things it's not every day
it's like maybe once a week these people
repeat themselves every day
do you remember when Monty man said that
the first time I was dead you must
remember that ain't it that video these
people repeat themselves every day and
I'm getting sick of
Do you remember?
No, but seriously, they do need to think
of some new insults. It's getting boring now, bro.
No, for real, bro. It is getting boring now. [snorts] You know,
would you agree, Grezy? They need to
think of some better comebacks now.
Would you agree,
Grezy? Would you agree they need to
think of some new comebacks now, bro?
It's boring. This whole month of [ __ ]
big nose. It's boring now, bro. Think of
something original, you know? Original, bro.
It's [ __ ] boring, bro. That's the
same repeating people in it. Yep. fantasist.
The law a owns six properties. [laughter]
Owns He owns six properties.
Oh, that's funny, bro. [laughter]
He owns six properties.
Imagine that, bro.
No, it doesn't because it's repeating.
Did you see Monty? Monty do that video
on V earlier, Grezy. Yeah.
Yeah. Did you see it? I saw it.
Did you see it, bro?
You're sub to Monty, aren't you, Grezy?
[snorts] Let me go and see some Mark's
channel. I've not I don't I haven't been
on his channel for couple months.
I used to watch Suicide Mark a lot back
in 2016, 2017.
Those were the days where
those were the days.
You remember when he used to gamble?
But he used to gamble.
Do you remember when Mark used to gamble?
Yeah. Well, even 2018,
do you remember that time when he went
all the way to Kent for that woman?
Oh, this must have been back in 2018, 2019.
He was on all day, bro. He was on
YouTube all day and he went to Kent.
Oh, do you remember
Yeah, he went. It was Kenny went.
[ __ ] hell. How many videos does he
post a day, bro? Jeez. What?
You like suicide, Mark? Light your graves there.
But all of his content is just the same [ __ ]
If I never had T m au fist oda syndrome,
I would have worked all my life.
I think he's taking a piss, bro.
[snorts] I think his videos are trolling. Yep.
Yeah, that video was a low life, bro.
Proper proper low life.
He was messaging my sister. Yeah. Saying
that if I don't stop, he's going to come
to my house and do this and do that and
do this and do that. Bro, he's a [ __ ] low life.
Why is there so many low lives on this community?
Rey's got a crush on Adam, don't you?
No, Adam's a cool guy.
Leave him alone, bro. He's a cool guy.
No, Fraser was trolling me though.
Fraser was actually trolling me.
He never come back since, did he? That Fraser.
I wonder what happened to him. Greasy, that Fraser
Yeah, I met Fraser and he switched on me.
Um, Grezy, he said, "You done me dirty."
That's what he said.
And then he started trying to grab me and stuff.
He said, "You done me dirty."
That's what he said. is how you die. You
dumb me dirty.
What do you reckon he was going to do to me? Grievesy,
I think he planned to beat me up. Yeah,
but then he got a bit nervous.
What do you think?
What do you think, Grezy?
No, he wouldn't have went for a pine,
bro. He led me to that to an alleyway.
Then he tried to like tried to grab me in that.
He's like, you did me dirty. Nah, bro.
No, it wouldn't have been a pint, bro.
Trust me. I don't know. I don't know
what would have happened.
I think he wanted to do something, but
he was too nervous. No.
He never came back since, did he?
You blaming virgin. Yep.
You reckon he remembers who I am?
Yeah. Me and him done cocaine together.
We was laughing our ass off, bro.
Me and him was laughing our ass off.
I remember [clears throat] how he was
laughing our ass off. Do you remember that video now? Slow. [laughter]
Yeah, that's funny, man.
Yeah. And you fancy Adam Grezy.
And I think you fancy my mommy as well.
I think you've got a soft soft spot for my mommy.
Don't you, Grezy?
Well, I haven't done it for four years.
I've only tried it twice.
[snorts] It just makes you very
confident and horny.
I've already tried it twice and that was
four years ago, bro.
Oh gosh. Do you have a soft spot for my
mama, Greavvesy? I think you like my mommy.
I like my mama.
I think she's cute.
Uh, is there a better picture of my mama?
That's my mommy.
Yep. That's my mama. Whoa.
My mommy's got lovely hair.
Yep. I met my mommy on the street.
That's my mom.
I know. I got to suck them and squeeze them. Scooby. Yep.
I said to her, "You got nice boobs." And
she was like,
she was like, "Thank you. My ex said that, too."
And then she come on kissing me, Scooby.
And she told me that I'd be her 25th and stuff.
Ask Grezy. He can confirm it.
She said, "How many people have you
slept with?" I said, "Three." I just
said a random number.
I said, "What about you?" And then she
said, "You'll be my 25th." And then she
said, "The slower the better, Scooby."
Which was quite scary at first, you know. Yeah,
she had big boobies.
Do you like them, Grezy? Do you like the boobies, Greavesy? Oh gosh.
They're not the biggest boobies I've had, though.
I've had bigger ones,
believe it or not.
Mr. B, remember Fraser? Mr. B.
Yeah, I got to squeeze them and suck on them, Scooby.
Uncle Bad Touch had a go on them.
Yeah, Uncle Bad Touch had a go on them.
Well, I've had bigger
I've had bigger ones. Um,
yeah, I've had bigger ones.
She was wearing a Calvin Klein boss bra
Scooby and she pulled her top up and
they come dangling out
[snorts] and they they came dangling
out. She was wearing a Kelvin Klein top.
I was like, "What are you doing, mama?
That's really rude."
It's not lucky me cuz she abandoned me,
Scooby, and left me all alone.
It ended really badly. No, it's not
lucky. It was actually really scary.
So, no, it isn't lucky.
Yeah, it kept me fed, but then I wanted more
and then she abandoned me and stuff and
blocked me and made up stories
and load of lies.
Then I had to message all of her family
and [ __ ] with her
and then she went to the police about me, Scooby. So
yeah, it was really scary.
See, I got fed and then I wanted some
more food, grievy,
and then obviously I lost the vitamins.
So it's like I can tell you exactly what it's like.
If you've got a routine of going to the gym,
right, and then you suddenly you don't
go to the gym, you can become really depressed.
Um, you can have like uh withdrawal
symptoms. So, you can actually go into
manic depression. I'm not even joking,
by the way. It's true. You can actually
go into manic depression
if you're if you got like a routine and
then you stop. And that's obviously when
you stop getting vitamins as well. So
when I stopped getting the vitamins,
yeah, it was really quite a bad time actually. Yep.
Yeah, I went back for seconds, but then
she abandoned me. Grievy, what's the
point of having children if you don't want them?
If you was just going to whisk me
straight into the care system. You know,
and it's not even just sex. Like just
being kissed and being fed is enough,
greasy, you know, just being kissed and
being fed. Obviously, if you don't get
that, you know,
I just I said, "Why did you even have me
if you was just going to put me into care?"
What was the point? You know,
I've still got that approaching video
where I met my mama, Scooby. Yep. My mama.
That's so cute. I didn't think I would
have met my mommy on the street though, Greavvesy.
I didn't think I was going to meet my
mama on the street.
That was really weird.
That was very strange.
It's like taking a baby away from its mama.
That's what I always used to say. Taking
a baby away from its mama. Grezy,
do you like the little voices? Grezy. Yep. Try them.
Now I want more.
Yeah, but Grey, why can't the other women do
like other women that I've been with?
Cuz they had kind of like um
they had boobies as well. Greavvesy. So
why wasn't they why weren't them women
good enough then? Greavvesy. Huh?
You would have thought if you found
someone else, right, that will feed you,
it will be the same. No, Grezy,
I had to try to meet other women to get
my vitamins. Grievesy,
do you remember when I was going on
dates and stuff?
What? You're pissing yourself? It's not
funny. It's quite serious. Grezy,
it's quite a serious matter.
Why are you laughing?
But yeah, I went out to try and find
other women to get my vitamins, Grezy. And yeah,
I sucked a lot of boobies that year,
Grezy. Oh, well, I actually sucked a lot
of boobies in that April. Grievesy,
the the same month where I met my mama.
I actually sucked a lot of boobies that
month, believe it or not.
Yep. Cuz I used to go out and stuff and approach. So,
but the vitamins didn't didn't seem the same.
They weren't the same vitamins.
I don't know. They didn't taste the same, you know.
The one that come on to me, I sucked her
boobies. The one in Nottingham.
Yeah, but they just I don't know.
Why didn't it Why didn't it taste the same, Grezy?
Huh? Cuz it's all milk, isn't it,
Greasy? So, why wouldn't it have been the same?
And even when
I'd get kisses and stuff,
I was like, "Ew,
go away. That's yucky."
I also kissed a lot as well in that
month, Grezy. But it was yucky. It was yuck,
Grezy. It was yucky.
No, but what I'm saying is when I met
other women that had boobies and I
suckled on the other breasticles, it
wasn't the same.
It just didn't it didn't uh give me the same vitamins.
Weirdo Jamie Thompson keeps stalking me.
He keeps calling me. Leave me alone, you weirdo.
You [ __ ] stalker. Anyways, Greavvesy,
what I'm saying is it didn't um
it didn't taste the same for some reason.
I'm not sure why.
There were quite big breasticles.
What was that all about?
Go away. You're not my mama.
Do you remember when I used to tell the
dates about my mama, Greavvesy? They
used to think I was quite mad.
I used to tell other people about her.
at my mama. Yeah.
Yep. They used to They used to think I was bonkers.
They used to think I was bloody mad. Wednesday. Yeah. Breasticles.
Breasticles. The solicitor had big breasticles. Grezy
Who the [ __ ] calls them breasticles?
That is weird, bro.
Now I want more.
Remember that one, Greasy. Now I want more.
See, the 19year-old was good. She was
good at sucking my willie and stuff,
but there was not enough milky.
That's why I was never really satisfied.
I was always looking for bigger boobies
to latch on to
Greezy cuz she didn't really have any
boobies and stuff.
I tried but there was not enough milk. So
I was disappointed.
So when I used to go to like the weather
spoons with her and stuff, I was looking
always looking at other
potential Peter Belly candidates. They'd
be Peter Belly candidates. Uh Greasy. Yep. Well, yes.
But if you don't get the milk from your
mom, Reezy, it's not the same,
Greavesy. You need to get it from your
mama. Otherwise, the vitamins is not the same.
So obviously if I get it from her, it's
the same cuz with the same blood. So if
I go to another woman and I get the
milk, it's not the same. It's not uh you
know I mean it's not it's not the same.
So it doesn't do anything.
It needs to be from your actual mama previously. So yeah,
my ex said that too.
Well, I'm saying you got big boobies.
Do you think if you saw USA is his
boobies, Grezy, do you reckon it would
make you hard?
But would it make you hard, Grezy?
Whisked straight into the care system. Huh? Whoa.
See, if you were say Izzy didn't betray
me, I could have bought her some UGG
boots. Greasy, like I bought Laneie some mug boots.
Who is this penny account?
Let's have a little look.
Oh, it's some fake account.
Oh, it could have been a it could have
been a potential candidate
for maybe Peter.
Sorry, I was only having a little look.
Oh, yeah. It could have been a potential
uh candidate for maybe Peter, if you
catch my drift, Grezy. But nope, it's
just a fake account. Oh gosh. Never mind. Search continues. Uh Imagine
USA is his boobs if if she gets pregnant. Greavesy.
Whoa. They'd be really big
one day, Greavvesy.
Could you imagine? Oh my god.
That would be quite quite humongous. Wooy, what?
Why are you you being sick, Grizzy?
Why is that disgusting?
They would get really big, wouldn't they?
Why is it yuck?
All I'm saying is they'd be big bigger.
Why is it yucky? It's natural, you know.
Why is it yucky? Why? Why? Yeah,
I think pregnancy is quite cool, Grezy.
When someone's belly gets big and stuff,
I think it's quite cool, Greavesy.
Why would it be yucky about the boobs
being pregnant? Greasy.
Why is that disgusting?
Why is that? I think it's quite quite cute.
When I get married, I want Grezy to be
my best man.
Okay with you, boss.
Grievy. Okay with you, boss.
If you be my best man at my my wedding. Oh gosh. Oh,
you can be my best man at my wedding and stuff.
King will come as well.
Why did you say yuck? Why did you say
yuck to USA Izzy's boobs?
If she got pregnant, Grezy,
it'd be full of milk.
I'd save money on milk for my cornflakes
and my cups of teas in the mornings.
Sick of bloody wasting money on milk. Gosh.
So, we'd have free milk for 9 months. Yum.
We would need We won't need milk for 9 months.
I wonder how much money we save.
We put them in the cornflakes and stuff.
We would save a lot of money on milk.
How much? We'd save maybe 2530
a month. So we'd be saving money on milk,
which so let's say £30 a month
for 9 months, right? Bargain.
Nope. No, it's not.
Why is it nasty if if she got pregnant,
Grezy with the boobs and stuff?
What I said is there to get bigger.
No, it's not a sketch.
I need my vitamins, Grezy. If there's a
big difference, I need my vitamins
and kisses and stuff.
That is just a stupid thing what they do
on Little Britain. Oh gosh.
My mom is so good to me. Grezy
say Izzy is an abuser.
You know, if you had a baby with her,
she'd probably abused a kid, Greavvesy.
She'd probably bullied a child. I
wouldn't trust her around children, bro.
Would you trust her around the kid?
No way. She'd probably bully the baby.
I wouldn't trust her around a baby.
Would you, Grezy?
No. Narcissist shouldn't be around kids.
She'd probably try to control the baby and stuff. Oh gosh.
I think you're mocking me. Uh, Grezy, I
don't think you like me. I think you're
just mocking me.
You're making fun out of me.
Why do you keep making fun out of me?
Why do you keep making fun of me, Grezy? Stop it. Oh,
what are you doing over there? Mama.
She wanted a dick as soon as I
approached her. Greasy.
approached her. Greavesy, who the [ __ ] does that?
But if you're looking for sex, Greaves,
you get a bloody bolican.
If you was only looking for sex,
you'd get a bunch of white knights after
like the KKK.
You know what that means?
No, it's not.
You'd get you'd get a bunch of white
knights after you like the KKK with the
torches and stuff
if you only wanted sex.
Isn't that right, Grevdy? A
That's so cute.
She messaged me straight away as well
the next day, Greavvesy
saying we should meet up on Tuesday and stuff.
She wanted to meet me really fast. Greavvesy,
that's strange, isn't it?
See, Greavves is not into casual sex,
are you, Greavvesy?
You're not into casual sex, are you?
I'm surprised a woman would be into that
to be honest because I don't think I'd
be into that.
I mean like having sex and never seeing
the person again. I think that's pretty
like boring, bro. I mean, you can have
sex the first time meeting someone.
Yeah, but I mean to not see again. I
mean, that's a bit like [ __ ] what the
[ __ ] It's a bit boring, isn't it, Reevesy?
That is a bit boring, eh?
Oh, she wanted me to wear a condom at first. Greasy.
Yep. She wanted me to wear a condom at
first. What kind of [ __ ] is that?
At first? Yeah.
Why would you want someone somebody to
wear a condom? You won't even be able to
feel the sex at first.
She wanted me to wear a condom at first
and I legitimately lost them.
So, I had to uh say I lost them and
stuff and in the end. Yeah. But I don't
know why you'd want sex with a condom.
No, but I don't feel Yeah, but you don't
feel anything with a condom.
>> Yes, but you don't feel anything with a condom.
I had them, but I actually lost them.
Yeah, true story. I actually lost the condoms.
Must have fell out when I sat down somewhere.
I actually lost the condoms, bro.
Yeah, not even joking.
Yeah, but you can't feel anything with the condoms, Scooby.
Yeah, you can't feel anything with condoms.
I Why would you want to stop babies?
Babies are cute.
That's really, really cute.
Don't know why you'd want to stop
babies. Babies are cute.
I love boppers.
Dear Grezy, they're cute babies.
King was a baby once.
Yeah, she wanted to use condoms. I don't
know what was her problem.
Yep. Nons legs is a virgin as well.
Nons legs. Timmy bomb. The free virgins.
The free [ __ ] virgins. Yep.
Yeah. Well, can't you take some pills or something?
No, you could have took some pills
to stop pregnancy and stuff, you know.
Yeah, exactly. I I I've Yeah, most of
the one night stands I've had were condomless.
The one I had on my birthday was condomless.
I had a one night stand on my birthday.
I just [ __ ] her.
Her name was Maddie Grezy.
I said [snorts] I was we was going to go
get your nails done and stuff.
I I sold her a dream, then I disappeared.
It was lovely,
lovely, lovely result.
But whenever you get these one night
stands, you can't even come anyways cuz
you never know when you're going to get
laid. So you masturbate once or twice
and then when you actually finally get
it, you can't even come.
Well, you can, but it takes very
it takes a long time and you have to
finish off yourself more often than not
because you've masturbated a lot
throughout the day.
No, listen to what I said.
Oh, never mind.
I can't be bothered.
You mistook everything I said. Never
mind. [clears throat]
What an idiot.
What a [ __ ] idiot.
I can't stop farting, Grezy. It's them bloody wings. Lord. Lord.
I can't stop farting and it stinks. Quezy.
Oh [snorts] gosh darn it. Oh gosh.
Oh gosh darn it.
Do you want to join? Uh, Timmy, do you
Oh, Steven Howard. Do you like Do you
like The Rock?
Do you like The Rock, Steven Howard?
One second. I'll put a link up.
I was watching The Rock earlier.
The Rock is
a silly goose.
No, he's a wrestler. Well, he was a
wrestler. He's retired now.
I watch them and they don't they get
rejected nine times out of 10.
They don't get bad things. they get rejected.
I I've been watching them a lot
recently. I watched them earlier
and they get rejected even in America.
What the [ __ ] bro?
I do. I watch uh Ed Matthews.
Yes, I watch Ed
and he gets rejected, which doesn't even
make any sense, but yeah,
bro, go and watch most of their videos.
They get rejected, bro. Well, he does. I
don't know about the other one. I don't
watch the other one, bro.
Go and watch these live streams. There's
a channel called Ed Plug
and he constantly gets rejected. Uh
I watch it. I watch him, bro. I watch
the other one.
They don't get the odd rejection, bro.
They get rejected multiple times.
multiple times. They It seems they get
the same [ __ ] as I get. Well, they he I
don't know about the other one.
They get Instagrams and stuff. Yeah,
I've been I was watching him all day on Friday
when I was hung over
and Saturday as well.
They definitely definitely get rejected, bro.
Definitely get rejected.
Yeah, I watch clips. Yeah.
So, but yeah, I watch Ed. Yeah. >> [snorts]
>> Oh, what? Numbers don't mean anything
either. I get loads of numbers, but just
getting them to [ __ ] meet you. Yeah.
But yeah, I've seen him get rejected
multiple times. Multiple times.
I've seen him get rejected. He He's gone
to America as well.
I've seen American videos.
Oh, it's [ __ ] mental, isn't it?
No, it's the other way around.
He probably gets like 20% of women. From
what I've seen,
he probably gets like 20%.
which is still good. 20 30%.
Trust me, I've seen a lot of his stuff, bro.
I've seen a lot of his stuff.
Yeah, I watch I've watched a lot of his
[ __ ] bro. I think I've seen I've seen
all of the clips now. I think
No, they don't. I mean, he's got their Instagrams.
He's got Instagrams and stuff. He's got
numbers and Instagrams. Yeah. Um,
no, they're they're not clips, bro.
There's like they're like 3 4 hours.
Some of these some of these videos are
like 2 three hours.
They're like 2 three hours long, mate.
They're not little clips. They're hours long.
He went to Liverpool as well. He went to Liverpool.
and it was like two hours long.
I was watching it. They're not clips,
they're live streams.
People will clip a whole live stream
that he's done.
Yeah, they're not clips. They're hours.
When he does a live stream, someone will
put it on YouTube. So,
he doesn't he doesn't get 70% of women, bro.
He really really doesn't. That's why I'm
shocked because I've been watching a guy
and he it seems like he does.
He's dealing with similar [ __ ] like me,
which doesn't even make sense cuz
he's got money and he's got followers.
What the [ __ ] bro? And he's still getting rejected. Yeah,
I did see that. Yeah, he got her Instagram.
I've watched all of his [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, I've seen his [ __ ]
I've seen his [ __ ] Yeah, there's
channels, bro. And
Oh, no. I didn't see that one then.
Oh, I didn't see that one. I've seen the
American ones. I seen the Cardiff one. Yeah.
Yeah, I've seen them ones.
No, no, no. There's four lives on this
channel. They're two and a half, three hours long.
You know, there's full lives.
There's full lives on um on this channel. Yeah.
I'll have to download kick and follow
him then. Is it okay? I'll have to
download that tomorrow and see.
I'll have to have a look, man. I'll
download it tomorrow and see.
I'll sub to him. Yeah. Yeah, man. What's up
I watch Brady.
Yeah, I watch # Brady.
But I don't get these people that go up
to Edia and say, "Oh, can I get a
picture? Can I get a picture?"
I mean, there's so many idiots in this
world, bro. I mean, if you see someone
that you idolize, bro, you just try to
speak to them.
You even see it in America as well, bro.
They're [ __ ] idiots.
But he can't get most women that he approaches.
So despite what people are telling you,
and like I said, I've watched a lot of
his [ __ ] anyways, bro. I've watched a
lot of his [ __ ]
There's ones where he's he's he's gotten
into fights with women and [ __ ] and
they've tried attacking him. I've seen a
lot of his [ __ ] bro. I've seen a lot of
I've seen a lot of his [ __ ] bro.
No, he isn't, bro. Because there's ones
where he will try to start a
conversation and they'll just be [ __ ]
They'll just be complete [ __ ]
Like I said, I've watched a lot of his
[ __ ] bro. I've seen a lot of his [ __ ]
He can probably get like Yeah, he can
probably get 30% of people, but
that's about it, bro. I've watched a lot
of his [ __ ] So, yeah. It's mad.
It's not more than f Okay, I'm not going
to go back and forth and argue with you,
bro. I've watched his stuff. Yeah, on
Friday I spent all day watching his stuff.
Okay, bro. I'm not going to sit here and
argue with you, bro. Whatever. I've been
watching the guy. I think I'm sub to his
channel, bro, cuz I watch some of his
stuff because I like watching [ __ ] like that, bro.
I'm not going to sit here and argue,
bro. I was watching the guy literally all day.
Literally. Literally all day. I was home
alone as well on Saturday. So, I was
watching some Friday and I was watching some Saturday. So, so yeah, [ __ ]
Right. Let me download this app.
I'm downloading this app. All right,
I'll do it tomorrow. I downloaded it.
Yeah, I've got the app anyway, so I will
update it tomorrow, bro. And follow. [sighs] Yeah, bro.
I can't believe people go up to him
screaming in his face for a picture like
men. There's so many idiots in the in
this world, bro. There's so many
absolute idiots in the West. Absolute idiots.
Have you seen it, bro? I've like I said,
I don't know who's behind these
accounts. I've seen [ __ ] some of the
I've seen some of the side men.
I've seen Cal Freezy.
I used to live next to them. I tried
talking to Cal Freezy.
He spoke for a little bit. But I see
these guys, bro.
They literally get in his face saying,
"Can I take a picture? Can I take a
picture?" I'm thinking, bro, I mean,
this is these people are [ __ ] idiots. Absolute idiots
in it. Absolute
[ __ ] idiots, bro.
Don't watch [ __ ] Tik Tok in this
[ __ ] Is it?
No, no, no. You don't. The side men are
not dead, bro.
The side the side men are dead. They're,
bro. They're millionaires,
bro. They are millionaires. How are they dead?
No, bro. But what I'm saying is if
people like someone, they like someone.
But these people are going up saying,
"Can I take a picture?" It's [ __ ]
weird, bro. And they're grown ass men.
Side men are not dead
compared to Ed, bro. What the [ __ ] You know,
they're [ __ ] millionaires, bro. Millionaires.
Yeah, man. [snorts]
A lot a lot of these people in the West
are [ __ ] idiots though, bro. Absolute idiots.
They are [ __ ] idiots.
You can't idiot. So
yeah. And that Ed and that Ed Matthews
will will die one time, bro. In the end.
Yeah. He'll die out soon.
They all die out soon. It's not just the side men.
Yeah, Ed will die out soon as well.
One day. Well, not soon, but
yeah, one day. It happens to everyone.
You remember there's like um Yeah,
there's channels, you know, you've seen it yourself,
but the smaller [snorts] channels are
better anyways, to be fair. Yeah. Madness.
Yeah, that's fine, bro. I don't mind
five people watching, bro.
That's fine, man. That's fine.
Still public, bro. Um, manga.
Yeah. Disgusting, huh?
Nah, my approaching days are done, lad.
My approaching days are done.
My approaching days are done, matey. [ __ ] that.
Can't give up. Well, I have. [snorts]
So, I can because I have.
Nah, bro. I only send it when I feel
like going out drinking.
Only when I feel like going out drinking
because it's just a waste of time. It's
just the same [ __ ]
It's just the same [ __ ] So, I only
really do it when I got when I fancy
going out drinking
really when I'm bored
cuz it's just always the same old. So, I
don't really bother with it.
You know how it be.
Yeah, I just can't be bothered dealing
with women's [ __ ]
The mind games, the lies, the games, the
attitude. I just can't be bothered with it, bro. You know,
that's What's that?
You know what I mean, bro? Yeah, man.
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] about them,
bro. I just can't be bothered to do it.
I know it will never change.
I'm not as That's why I don't do it
because it's just the same old [ __ ]
That's what I'm trying to say to you.
I don't give a [ __ ] That's what I mean.
Like when I went out on Thursday, I knew
it weren't going to change.
I'm not ass, bro. I don't care anymore.
I know there's no hope trying to find
someone in this country.
And I know when I go out,
I'm playing at my own risk.
I don't give a [ __ ] I know that, you
know. I know it will never change, bro.
That's why it doesn't annoy me.
No, it won't change.
It's not negativity. It's reality. It won't change.
It It won't change, bro. That's just how
it is. It's not negativity. It's
reality. I'm not going to sit here and
pretend that the next time you go out is
going to be any different because it's
not. That would be lying.
You go out cuz you go out. You try cuz
you're out. And that's that. But deep
down, it's never going to change.
It will never change because I'm going
by my experiences that it won't change.
It's not about what you manifest. It's
about your experiences.
It will never change. That's how it how it is.
And I don't really care. Simple. Like
that's it. I'm not crying. I'm not winging.
I've accepted it. So that's that. [snorts] Yeah. Only
one or three things ever will ever
happen when you go out and you try.
I have a boyfriend.
Uh not interested. Give you their
number, lead you on, and play games. The end.
That's literally all that will ever happen.
Nothing else, bro. Nothing else.
nothing else would ever happen.
I mean, we know that now after [ __ ] 5
years, you know what I mean? Jesus Christ. So, yeah,
but it is what it is, eh?
It doesn't get me depressed. It doesn't bother me, you know.
Well, it's never just happened for me
cuz that Well, I mean, dating apps don't work.
So, I mean, well, dating apps don't work.
And if I didn't approach, I'd be a
virgin. So, just just letting you know
that. by the way, that dating apps don't work.
Never met anyone through friends,
women don't approach, and if I didn't
approach, I'd be a virgin.
So, uh, yeah, read into that what you will,
just to help you out a little bit.
Tell me what you think of that. So, Yeah.
Yeah. I'd be I'd be a virgin
if I didn't approach. I would have never
been on a date if I didn't approach.
Well, saying that, dating apps.
Yeah. One nighter.
You can't you can't even get a
conversation out of the [ __ ] let alone
a one nighter. Jesus Christ.
I've not had sex in probably about except escorts. But
for no, it was actually
[snorts and gasps]
Yeah, maybe 6 months.
And that was somebody that I already knew. So,
how long ago was that?
How long ago was that?
I mean, you can't even get a date
nowadays. So, I mean, me saying that me
going out, it's never going to change.
Wait, wait, hold on. You You said it was
18 years ago.
Not trying to be funny, mate, but that
might have something to do with it. That
it was 18 years ago.
That's probably got something to do with it.
Not going to lie to you.
You said 18 years ago, bro. There wasn't
even Facebook 18 years ago.
Yeah. And no wonder you found someone 18 years ago.
I'm not surprised to be honest with you.
Now it's completely different.
Everyone's on TikTok. Everyone's on Instagram.
No one's interested.
18 [ __ ] years ago. Well, I'll put it
this way. My dad died 15 years ago.
And that was a very, very, very long
time. And that's well Facebook was made
in 2007 I think but people didn't know
about it in until 2009. We didn't start
hearing about it till 2009.
Until about 2009. That's when we started
hearing about it.
So brother dating games even changed in
the past 3 years.
Like even if I when I went out three years ago,
I could get like dates and it' still be
hard, but I could still get stuff. Now
you can't get nothing.
Like [ __ ] all.
That's how bad it is. Like literally,
you can't get anything, mate. Like, I've
not been on a date since April, and I've
been out a lot since April.
Like, not even a date. So, when I got 10 numbers, uh,
and I didn't get a date, I was like,
"Oh, yeah, this is impossible. Okay, now
I don't care, bro. Like, if I go out,
this is what I'm going to expect." Cuz,
yeah, 3 years ago, it was different. It
It was different. It was still hard,
don't get me wrong. I think it's always been
hard. It's not the immigrants. It's just
Tik Tok [ __ ]
It's it's something to do with Tik Tok,
bro. Cuz even 3 years ago, it wasn't as
bad. It was still bad.
It was still bad, but not like this.
Not for me anyways. It wasn't as bad as
it is now. Now it's like, yeah, you
can't even get a date.
You try to speak to someone, it's
straight away, I'm I'm not interested.
I've got a boyfriend. Straight away.
That's That's all you ever get. So So
18 years. Wow.
I'm 28. So I was 10.
See, [snorts] if I if I approached 18
years ago, I probably wouldn't get rejected.
No, they don't have a boyfriend.
No, they don't have a boyfriend. They're
chatting [ __ ] mate. Most most women are
single, believe it or not. I would say
I would say seven times out of 10,
they're chatting [ __ ]
They're chatting absolute wank.
Seven times out of 10, they're chatting [ __ ]
They don't have a boyfriend.
They're talking [ __ ]
talking absolute [ __ ] People that
have a boyfriend just walk away.
I mean, they don't sit there and talk to
someone then just to say they've got a
boyfriend. They're full of [ __ ] And
believe it or not, there's loads of
single people out there. Most of the
people I know are single.
I know people in relationships.
They don't have a boyfriend. They don't
And we're not I'm not going to get into
this conversation anyways, bro, about
whether they've got boyfriend or not. I
know that seven times out of 10 they're
chatting [ __ ] Probably even more to be
honest. And that's that. So
no, they definitely definitely don't
have a boyfriend.
Definitely definitely definitely don't.
They're just chatting [ __ ] most of the
time. And I don't even care anyways.
Does it matter whether they do or they don't?
I mean, does does it really matter?
No, it doesn't. So,
that's that. Anyways, it doesn't really
matter, does it? Whether they do or they don't. Yep.
It sucks, isn't it? But that's just the
way it is. So,
get used to it or leave. So yeah,
the boyfriend thing has been the most
[ __ ] excuse for the longest time. I
mean, everyone knows that. Literally
And it's not about boyfriends either.
This is what I was trying to explain to
this transgender in Scotland. It's not
about boyfriends or not boyfriends.
It's not even about that. It's not one
thing. I don't know why we seem to think
that it's one thing. It's about them
giving their numbers, leading people on,
playing games, having attitude. It's not
just that. It's not one thing. It's not
one thing that they do. Cuz if that was
the case, then we'd go out and we'd hear
nothing but I've got a boyfriend and we
wouldn't get any numbers. It's not even
just about that.
You know, it's not one thing.
Yeah. I speak to some transgender in um
Scotland just like a friend. It's not
just about the boyfriend [ __ ]
Like they give their numbers and
literally lead you the [ __ ] on. Like
that's what they do, bro. It's not just
about the boyfriend thing. So yeah.
So yeah, it's not like I said, it's not
one thing, lad.
L1, you need to grow up.
Yeah, you need to grow up.
Yeah, that's what I think you need to
do. I think you need to grow up.
Yeah, you need to grow up, lad.
It's boring now, lad. Very, very boring.
So, yeah, it's not about uh whether they
say they got boyfriends or not.
Yeah, you need to grow up, mate.
You need to grow up. It's boring. Very boring.
But they don't have boyfriends because
most men are single. So, how do all of
these women claim they've got boyfriends
that are out clubbing till early hours
in the morning, but their boyfriends are
never with them? So what are their
boyfriends doing? Sat at home having a wank.
The porn. Really, bro?
Really? Really, bro? Really?
So they're in a club the early hours in
the morning, but apparently they got boyfriends.
Mate, most men are single. It's either
more men are single or it's the same.
Trust me, bro. I've got a lot of
friends. I know a lot of people that
have got no connections to each other
and a lot of people are single.
A lot of people are single.
It's rare to be single. No, it's not
rare to be single. Most people I meet
are single. Even women that I've got
numbers from. Trust me, most people are
single. or it's the same. Or it could
just be the same. Maybe it's the same. I
don't know why I'm saying most. Maybe
it's 50/50 to be honest. So,
oh, that incel word. That's boring.
Yeah, that incel that that's very very
boring. That word. Very overused. Very
So, I mean, it's I'd say it's 50/50 to
be honest. I wouldn't say most people.
No, I think it's 50/50. But them women
that are saying that they've got
boyfriends, seven times out of 10, if
not more, they're talking [ __ ] They're
absolutely chatting [ __ ] Because even
you meet, right, even when you meet people
that come over here and study abroad,
they apparently claim they've got
boyfriends, which doesn't, and I'm not
even having this conversation. I know
they're chatting [ __ ] Like, if you want
to believe them, that's that's on you, bro. So,
it's not that rare.
It's not that rare. Single people that
have never had a relationship is very
No, it's not that rare. Not really.
It's not that rare.
It isn't that rare, mate.
Anyways, we're not having this
conversation. I know they're talking
[ __ ] If you don't think they are, then
that's on you, bro. I don't really care.
We're not having this conversation. I
know they're full of [ __ ] So, I mean, I
don't understand the point of this conversation,
you know? It's that they're they're talking [ __ ]
Trust me, bro.
I would say out of them people that say
they got boyfriends, three out of 10
actually don't do.
Most people I know are [ __ ] single.
No, I I know. I know, mate. I I've met a
lot of women. I've met more women than
you. Trust me, I fully much [snorts] know.
I definitely definitely definitely
definitely definitely know
that all of these people that claim
they've got boyfriends wouldn't be out
slagging it until [ __ ] 7:00 in the
morning while their boyfriend's at home
having a wank. It's common sense.
Anybody would know that. But if you want
to think that they've got boyfriends,
good for you, bro. It's we just agree to disagree. So
they're full of [ __ ]
So [clears throat] yeah, and I don't
really give a [ __ ] Anyways,
you want to believe them, believe them.
I don't care, man.
Anyways, we're moving on now. Moving on
from this boring conversation. Um,
moving on from this
boring conversation cuz I've got a
feeling a couple of these people are
white knights to be honest with you.
Okay, bro. I don't know anything. I'm a
28-year-old. I've never been with any
women. I don't know anything. I don't
leave the house. You're right and I'm
wrong. I mean, if that's what you want
to hear, bro, I'll tell you. I don't
know anything. Never been with a woman.
Don't know how women work. I'm just a
dumb 28-year-old that don't leave the
house. Happy? I mean, that's how like
all of these conversations will always
end. If you don't agree with them,
they're just going to keep going on and
on and on and on and on. So, you're
right, bro. I'm 28, never been with a
woman. I don't understand anything.
Thick as [ __ ] Never never left where I
live. I don't know absolutely anything.
So, it'd be it'd be it'd be it'd be
interesting to learn these things.
Yeah. Okay. And you and you trying to
say that nine times out of 10 women
that say they've got boyfriends do is
nuts because they're full of [ __ ] No.
Women that go out. No. No. Women that go
out club until early hours of the
morning don't have boyfriends. It's
common sense. Anyone that's not a white
knight would know that. And we're not
going to keep having this conversation.
I'm not going to believe you, bro. Yeah.
Bro, I'm a virgin. I don't know
anything. You clearly know more than me.
So, I'm not I'm not in this conversation, bro.
Bro, I don't know anything about women.
I'm a virgin. And you know this stuff.
Every single woman that says she's got a
boyfriend has a boyfriend. None of them
are lying. You're completely right. I
don't know what I'm talking about. Honestly,
you're completely completely right.
You're completely completely completely
right. I don't know anything.
>> Yep. I know. I've never been with a
woman. I'm a virgin. What's it like
being with a woman? I've never been with
one before. I'm a virgin.
Is it good? I've never been with a woman
before. I'm a virgin. Never had sex.
Never kissed. What's it like? Is it
good? I never had sex. Hey,
bro. Defeatist attitude. I'm agreeing
with you, bro. I'm I'm agreeing with
you. What the [ __ ] I'm literally
agreeing with you, mate.
It's How How could it be defeist when
I'm literally agreeing with you? All
women that say they've got boyfriends
are completely telling the truth. None
of them lead people on.
No, none of them do any of that stuff.
Nah, of course. Of course not.
I'll tell you a story, Stephen Howard. Um,
Um, I uh
approached uh a couple of weeks ago this
woman from Amsterdam and we was talking
and uh she said that uh can you give me some recommendations?
And she gave me some recommendations.
Um yes, I have been in a relationship.
Try again. And uh she was like, "Oh, oh,
we should exchange numbers." She says,
"Oh, I don't I don't exchange numbers
because I've got a boyfriend." But yet,
she said she would if she sees me later,
she'd have a drink with me. Have a drink
with me when you've got a boyfriend.
Really make it make sense.
I know, bro. They're so boring. They
need to get a life. They really, really
do need to get a life.
But I'm off anyways uh today for a
couple of weeks, bro. So, don't say I
didn't tell you.
Yeah. Yeah. You need to get a life.
Golden goat. Just like a lot of other
people in here. You seriously need to
get a life.
How does what work out? Steven Howard.
Uh, well, it works out because um
they're talking [ __ ]
Yeah, you get a life, sad bastard.
See you later.
There's no point arguing with white
knights, bro. Waste of time. It's a
waste of everyone's time.
Waste of everybody's time. literally is. Yeah.
She said that she she said, "Can you
give me some recommendations
like clubs and stuff?" Cuz she was only
visiting. So I said, "Go here. Go here.
Go here." She wrote them down. So I
can't exchange numbers because I've got
a boyfriend. But yeah, if she sees me
later, she'll have a drink. Now, why
would you want to have a drink with
somebody when you got a boyfriend in another country? Strange.
But I didn't say anything about it
because it's not my place to put these
people in their place.
Do you understand? Like I don't A lot of
these women have got attitude problems,
but it's not for me to put them in their
place until they disrespect me. You
know, a lot of them have got attitude
problems. They need telling about
themselves. But me, I'm not going to do
it unless one's rude to me.
It's not my place to do that.
You know what I'm saying? It's not my
But if they get rude to me, then I will
happily put them in in their place. But
until then, I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
But these people in the chat, they don't
know anything about women. Stephen
Howard, trust me, I approached 50 women
literally two weeks ago. Trust me, these
people don't know anything about women.
The truth is, women are entitled and
have a really, really bad attitude, most
of them. And none of them are honest as
well. They're all compulsive liars. 5050.
Trust me, Steven Howard, I know, mate. I
was out for several hours talking to them.
They're all they literally are they've
all got attitude problems and anyone
that tells you otherwise, bro,
um they're just white nighting, bro. So So
Timmy, you said that you got 20 to last
you a month.
That's what you said. You said that you
got 20 to last you a month.
I mean, every every woman in the West is the same.
Every westernized woman is the same. It
doesn't matter if it's America, Canada, Australia.
They're all They're all the same.
Westernized women are all the same.
All women are the same. from the west.
It doesn't doesn't matter where whether
it's [ __ ] London or [ __ ]
Manchester or [ __ ] Liverpool. They're
all they're all the same, bro. Like just
in the West, they're all they're all the same, bro.
Doesn't matter about the [ __ ] city,
you know what I mean? They're all full
of [ __ ] They all play games.
I'll go when I'm ready.
Simple. I'll go when I'm ready, bro.
And if they're not stuck up, they all
lead you. They just lead you on. So
if they're not stuck up, they just play
games with you.
So it's Yeah,
I've only been to Liverpool once and the
women were [ __ ] there as well. From
what I remember,
there were also [ __ ] in Liverpool as well.
Yeah, I've only been Liverpool once.
I've been to Manchester like 10 times.
I don't like any woman in the West. I
think they're all stuck up [ __ ]
But each to their own, lad. Each to their own.
I approach because I just do it because
it's something to do when I'm bored. I
don't actually like think it's going to change.
I know all women are the same.
But if I'm going to go out drinking then [ __ ]
why the [ __ ] not.
I don't know man. Maybe 23 24.
She was a [ __ ] as well.
Let's put her up. Yeah, she was a [ __ ] as well.
No, this is USA. Is he?
Yeah, there's Izzy and then there's USA.
Izzy. There's two Izzy's.
Nope, not my exes.
Just people that I had a one night stand with.
Not my exes. I weren't in a relationship
with them. Just people that I had a one
night stand with.
She was a [ __ ] as well.
I ended up messaging her family and
[ __ ] I had to call the police on me
like four times, five times. Nope.
I can't even remember what her nipples
look like to be fair. But anyways,
we need to stop talking about this [ __ ]
bro. Cuz you know Nons is going to be
wanking off over it.
He'll be like play playing with his
little flaccid little dick cuz he can't
get hard. This is why he's still a
[ __ ] virgin. But you just know that
he's going to be trying to like play
with his little dick over this.
We need to behave to be honest.
Yeah, she she was a [ __ ] I messaged her
family and [ __ ]
She deserved it. But Adam, don't leave
Adam alone, man. Don't message Adam. Adam's
a good chap.
Adam's a good fella. No messes Adam,
man. Leave him and his family alone.
What do you mean the narrative has changed?
Why? Why is that?
Why? Why? Why has it changed, bro? How
How's it changed?
It hasn't changed. Yeah. Well,
>> yeah. I I [ __ ] messaged her family
and everything on the packet cuz she
started being a [ __ ]
She started being an entitled little
[ __ ] And I gave her so many
opportunities as well to apologize. So,
I thought, "Fuck it. I'm going to
message this cunt's family, bro."
And if you ask me now, do I regret it?
Nah, I don't regret it.
No, I don't. Even now, I'm old. I'm
older now. I still don't regret it.
I said this to my mom as well. Um
when I was um when we fed out and stuff
and we was meeting, I said, "I don't
regret it. I can tell you all the things
that I regret. I don't regret. My dad
just started messaging me back and [ __ ]
threatening me, basically.
I said that your daughter's a little slag
and she's got like given an STD before
and you need to sort your little [ __ ]
slaggy daughter out and that. Nothing I
said was false, by the way. I didn't
make up any stuff.
She started being a [ __ ] So yeah, she
deserved everything she got basically.
Lucky I didn't go there the first time
and kill her, bro.
Seriously. Yeah. Seriously. Yeah.
Yeah, the madness, bro. She deserved it,
though. She She actually did deserve it.
She deserved it, bro.
She deserved it.
She deserve it for me to cut. [clears throat] Um,
led me on
basically uh led me on
um lovebombeds me, led me on and then
uh hooked up with me. Then when I went
to Messenger again, she blocked me and I
was like, "Oh, wow. Can't believe this."
Got my friend to Messenger. And then she
started making up stories about me.
And then I've I I actually bought
another phone. Cost me 60 quid, by the
way. She still owes me. Saying, "Hold
on, why the [ __ ] are you talking shit?" Yeah.
And then um
she was just basically saying, "Oh, uh
I'm sorry. I'm just not interested." I
was like, "No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
One second. Yeah, you lied to my friend.
You [ __ ] lovebombed me." And yeah, it
just kind of escalated from there, bro.
Then I said like, "Can you just
apologize and then we'll just leave it?"
And you weren't having none of it at
all. So I was like, "Okay, well, I'll
get you one way."
Yeah, I met her in real life. Yeah, obviously.
See, all of these women are very big
until they meet their match.
They're big until they meet their match.
Very big until they meet their match.
You know, they're not too far away from
a Peter belly, mate. Yeah.
They're very big until they meet their
match. These women.
No, she was visiting here and then she went back.
It's like this one. I'll tell you
another story about a narcissist. Right now,
this is similar to her. You with these
narcissists, they can never defend
themselves. They always have to get
other people to do it for them. There
was somebody that I was speaking to on
um Reddit and we moved on to Instagram and um
we we moved it to Instagram, right? And
then all of a sudden, this was on
Reddit. This was another country. She started ignoring.
I messaged again and again and then they
started ignoring and they were doing it
on purpose, like proper being a [ __ ] on
purpose. Then I messaged again and
again. And I said, "Listen, if you keep
ignoring me, I'm going to keep calling
you until you block me. I won't going to
stop until they block me." And then kept
ignoring and ignoring and ignoring, bro,
I went on their picture. I spammed their
whole page, bro. I spammed their whole
[ __ ] page. And then she blocked me.
But not only did she block me, she
blocked me and then put my profile
as her story, knowing damn well other
people was going to message me. So I'm
thinking, one second. So, you blocked
me, which is what I wanted, but then
you've put me on your story knowing damn
well other people are going to message
me when you have blocked me. What a coward.
This is what I'm saying. They can't they
can't stand up to themselves. These
cowards, they're big and they're big and
narcissistic until they meet their
match. That's what I'm saying with these women.
I spam their whole page, bro. D.
Yeah, you need to stop the M thing, bro. It's boring.
Again, different insults, different comebacks.
No, it was someone else.
It doesn't matter if I met her for 4
hours. She started being a [ __ ] I could
have met her for 10 minutes. She started
being a [ __ ] [ __ ] So, I gave it back.
And I don't still have her picture. Her
picture is just on this um account.
So you need to stop the M [ __ ] Stop
repeating yourself, you [ __ ] virgin.
Go get laid,
skin virgin. Um, so yeah. So
that's what happens. Basically, they're
all big until they meet their match. These narcissists,
these narcissistic women are very big
until they meet their match.
That's sick, bro. Very sick in the head. Yeah. So, yeah,
they're just [ __ ] isn't it?
I'm still yet to meet a woman that's not the same.
They say all women aren't the same. I'm
still yet to find one.
Maybe next year I'll find one that's not
all the same. This will be the sixth year now. Next year.
Every woman you meet says the same, acts
the same, has the same mannerisms, but
they're not all the same.
It makes it hard to believe, don't it? I
mean, they seem very robotic, don't they, lad?
And it's not even like she wrote um
Yeah, I [ __ ] with her cuz she deserved
it. Like, simple as that.
So, and I booked to go the first time,
but the person I was kind of meeting
begged me not to go. So, I was like,
"Don't go. Don't go. Don't go." I was
going to [ __ ] her up, bro. I swear to God,
I got half the money back,
even though it was half, but she was
like begging me not to go and [ __ ] bro.
The madness. Yeah.
So then I called up tried to get some of
the money back. It was bad, bro. Bad.
And these women really really They are
all the same, bro.
They are all the same, bro. They
definitely are all the same. I don't
know how people can say they're not all
the same. They really, really are.
She gave up the [ __ ] but it wasn't the point.
I think I'll just shut myself. This war
women aren't all the same.
[snorts] No, they definitely definitely
are all the same.
Say all the same stuff, have the same
excuses, have the same mannerisms, lead
people on the same way.
I don't know.
They do a lot of the same stuff for
people that aren't the same.
They act a lot like one another. And at
the end of the day, I always say to to
myself that if I found somebody that was
exactly the same as me, I'd be very
worried. But they all seem to act the same way.
It's clear as they they're NPCs.
They all literally act the same way.
You know what I'm saying? They they literally do
they really really do do act the same
way for people that aren't
that aren't all the same. You know,
a lot of them go on dates to waste
people's time as well. On the packet,
I The last day I went on, we was holding
hands for hours, tried to kiss her, she
moved away. I'm thinking, "What the fuck?"
Vibing, well, holding hands. So, like,
you can even go on dates with like
someone and they'll just waste your time.
That I think that was April. Yeah.
March or April. No, I think that one was But yeah.
Yeah, that one was April. Really?
Holding someone's hands is simp behavior.
No, no, no, no, no, no. A lot of them
will go on dates just to waste your time.
No, no, no, no. Bro, believe it or not,
as as ridiculous as it sounds, they will
some of these people will go on a date
to waste your time and their time. I
know it doesn't make sense, but they do.
I I could tell you another one if you
want. You wouldn't even believe it. So,
I could tell you another one. You
wouldn't even believe it.
I mean, they're just they're just bad experiences.
Okay, I'll tell you one.
Obviously, everyone's heard this before.
This was I've only been on three dates this year.
I went on I went out a bank holiday. It
was Friday. Yeah, it was a bank holiday.
So this woman's approached me saying,
"Oh yeah, you're attractive. You're good looking.
Talking to them, got their number."
Friends was being a bit of a [ __ ]
So I messaged them the next day and then
we were talking back and forth. Oh, this
is going well. They're not stuck up.
They're not being rude. We're getting
somewhere here. And then we arranged to
meet on Thursday. So, they traveled an hour away.
Um, and then we met. So, I was like,
"Okay, look my best, act normal,
obviously, as we always do." And then
after half hour, we was drinking, just
talking about normal stuff, play things
we've done. And then they've turned
around and said that they don't feel the
vibe. And then cuz I said, "Oh, when
when should we meet again after
leaving?" And they said, "Oh, um, they
don't feel the vibe." And I'm thinking,
"Wait, what do these people possibly
want?" Like, you can look your best, act
normal, and you're saying that you don't
feel the vibe, which is strange because
this person was 33 and they were like
just below average looking.
That's not normal, bro. That's No, no,
no, no, no. That That's not normal.
That is That is not normal. Somebody to
travel an hour away just to say just to
say within 20 30 minutes, you don't feel
the vibe. Bro, that's not that's not
normal. Especially when that person has
approached you as well. They actually
approached me. So, I mean, and the fact
that they're 33, so they're actually
losing their value. So they're actually
like they're actually
like like hitting the wall sort of
thing. So I mean that just goes to show
you the the the insane standards, the in
the unrealistic standards that they've got
when a 33y old
who's average looking thinks they're
better than you.
That's uh that's a problem, bro.
And I didn't like them either. That's
the thing. It's It's not about that I
like them. It's a taste of, "Oh [ __ ]
these guys are coming up to me, bro."
They were like, "Fuck, if they were uh
if they were 50
if if average people that are 33
thinking they're better than you, then
what chance do you really have?"
Well, no. How could have I been with
them long term? They live in America, bro.
Well, why didn't you click? Well, no,
but that doesn't make any sense why you
didn't click because
the conversation was fine.
So, then there's got to be a reason why
two people don't click. There's got, you
know, everything happens for a reason.
You know, the conversation and I didn't
even like them either. It's just a
figure of thing is that
what what do you want? What more do they
want? And then I thought to myself, "Oh
[ __ ] well, there's actually no point in
going on any dates now because they've
just got these unrealistic expectations
because it doesn't make sense. You can't give up. Um,
you can't give up on the first
um sign of disappointment." And that's
what I think these people do. And you
don't realize that quickly if you click
or you don't click either. It
[clears throat] wasn't long enough.
Well, there is a reason because there's
a re there would be a reason why two
people don't click. You don't just don't
click. There's always a reason why you
don't click. It's like when someone
says, "Oh, it's not going to work.
There's a reason why it doesn't work.
There's always a reason, you know." So, yeah.
So, and and it was also the fact that it
was in with like and it was the fact
that it was in like 20 30 minutes. If it
was within 3 or 4 hours, then I could
understand it. But you don't know if you
click with somebody or not within 30 minutes.
If it was like four or five hours on a
second date, then I'd be like, "Okay,
fair enough." But not within 20, 30
minutes. Especially when you've
approached that person. It's like me
approaching a woman and then saying
within 30 sec 30 minutes, oh, I don't
feel it. It wouldn't make sense. It
doesn't make sense. I mean, I know
they're wasting my time. I know they're
full of [ __ ] And I don't care what
anyone says. Not to sound bigheaded,
like I'm not trying to sound bigheaded,
but I know about women. I've met
thousands of women. Th absolutely thousands.
So, and none of them are good. So,
but no, it wouldn't have worked, Scooby,
because they live in America. But it's
not the point of whether it would work
or not. It's how they went about it.
Well, what why why do women do the
things that they do? Why do women talk
to people and lead them on if they've
got no intention of meeting them?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. It's not
about looking at about It's not about
looking at it reasonly, right? These Why
Why do these women text people if
they're just going to lead people on?
No, no, no. That nothing they do makes
sense. So, I don't need to look at it reasonable, you know?
So, I mean, they they done it because
they probably was bored and had nothing
else to do. I mean, it's you you can't
say whether you click or you don't click
within 30 minutes. It doesn't make sense.
It's just they've got unrealistic
expectations. That's that.
So, I mean, there's women that will lead
people on and never meet them. Why do
they do that?
There's women that will waste their time
texting people just to never meet them.
It doesn't make sense, does it? So,
just like they lead people on purpose,
why do they lead people on?
You know, it's like
that's that, bro.
So when you've got a 33y old average
woman that thinks they're better than you,
you're down bad, bro. That's all I can say.
And then you think to yourself, what is
it they're looking for? So
I know what these women are like.
They're [ __ ] bro.
I mean, you can say that all women are
different all you like,
but women will always prove they're all
the same. You can say what you can say
one thing, but they will always show
another that they're all the same. So,
they will always prove to be all the same.
So, I mean, it doesn't really matter
what you say to be honest, lad.
So they're all the same.
That's that in the west anyways.
In the west anyways.
So that's that. So yeah,
go on a lovely date.
Yes, I am.
I should have to go Thailand. I should
be able to find someone here,
but I can't.
No one's interested here. Hello.
I don't really care anyways, bro.
They're all [ __ ] westernized scum, aren't they?
I hate their attitude. Even when they're
not giving me attitude,
I hate their attitude, bro.
these westernized [ __ ] [ __ ]
women, bro. I really hate their attitude.
And I feel like I'm lowering myself
talking to them. That's how bad it is.
Like you feel like you're lowering yourself
talking to them because of what how
they're like. You get what I mean?
Because none of them are genuine and
they're all full of [ __ ] You're
actually disrespecting yourself by
trying with them.
And you know what I find so mad is how
they will ignore a normal nice message,
but then as soon as you write a negative
one, they're there.
I've noticed that. I've noticed that on
a dating app uh about a week ago,
I matched with this person. So I matched
with them. This is a weird. It weren't a
random person. I I actually matched with
them. So I messaged them, no reply. This
was on Hinge. So they didn't reply.
So then I said to them, "I hate women."
Bam. Straight away on the message trying
to justify why they didn't reply. So
that tells me that they're a narcissist
even though I don't really know the person because
bear with me. They've ignored a normal
nice message yet as soon as you've sent
a rude one, they've replied back trying
to victimize themsel. See, they think
they're very smart by what they're
doing, but they're not. By by trying to
victimize themsel, they're trying to,
how do I say it? Like, it's hard to
explain. They're trying to victimize themsel by
saying how they were going to reply even
though they had no intentions. They all
do this. They They are literally all the
same. This is what I'm trying to say to
you. They are all the same.
They really, really are.
I I met an Italian one before. She was
trying to justify why she didn't reply.
And as soon as you write that normal as
uh negative message,
bam, they they reply straight away.
Like you could you couldn't make it up.
Yet their normal nice messages get
ignored. Yet they matched with you on
the dating app. They liked you on the
dating app. It doesn't even make any sense. So
that is like
why do they reply to negativity and
ignore normal nice messages when they've
matched you on a [ __ ] dating app? [ __ ] mad.
Yeah, if you I' I've done tests like this before
um where I'd get 10 numbers
and they would maybe
maybe like I can't remember exactly what it was.
I basically messaged all the numbers I had.
I'm not believing anything. I'm knowing
there's nothing to be positive about,
bro. I'm being real. I'm not positive.
I'm not negative. I'm just a realist.
I'm not a uh
I'm not a I'm not negative. I'm not
positive. I'm just a realist.
That should be my middle name. I'm being real.
They do. As soon as you're rude, they reply.
They do reply straight away when you're
rude. But normal messages, they don't,
which then contradicts the whole thing
that they go for positivity.
It just contradicts everything.
As soon as you're negative, they're there.
There's no posit. Yeah, I am thinking
positive thoughts. I'm leaving.
And there was this Italian one before. I
remember she was a proper narcissist
trying to say, "Oh, I was going to reply
and I didn't feel the connection." I was
like, "Connection? This wasn't even a
romantic thing." I was like, I was I was
a tour guide. I I tell a story 11. I was
a I was being this person's tour guide
for about 40 minutes, right? I I'll tell
you. and said, "Oh, let me buy you a key
ring." No, no, no, no, no. I got their
number. Now, bear in mind, I didn't like
them. I didn't think we was going to get
together. So, then they've gone back to
Italy, right? So, then I've messaged
them. Didn't even get a response, which
is a bit which is a bit [ __ ] isn't it?
L1. I mean, it wasn't someone you were
speaking to for 5 or 10 minutes. I mean, I could
you could have at least responded,
you know? I mean, it's uh
it's crazy. And then they tried to
victimize themsel as usual saying that,
"Oh, I would have responded sooner."
Really? You You would have responded
sooner. Really, mate? Would have you? I
mean, I was thinking to myself, it's
been 3 months and the only reason you
replied is because I've wrote a negative message.
But again, have to be the victim. See,
it's mad these [ __ ] bro. They're crazy.
Yeah. And then she's talking about, "Oh,
I didn't feel I said there wasn't no
connection there. You live in a different country.
It's just they're always trying to victimize themsel.
They really are [ __ ] The more you
think about it, they really, really are [ __ ]
I hope to be proven wrong one day. I
really do. I really hope to be pro I
want to be proven wrong, but no one can.
So, she tried to victimize herself. I've
got the message there. I remember it
because she was never going to respond.
So, why are you writing saying, "Oh, I
would have responded sooner." You was
never going to respond
ever. It's been 3 months. You weren't
going to respond. Stop trying to
victimize yourself. I don't know what it
is with these people.
They think you're an idiot. That's what
it is. these [ __ ] right? They think
you're a [ __ ] just like every other
s. And then when somebody actually gives
them a challenge, they they play victim. Is it?
>> No. Is that so? Yeah.
Do you think all women are the same,
Steven Howard? I I definitely think
they're the same. Do you?
I 100% think they're all the same,
to be honest. Yeah,
pretty much. Yeah,
I think they're all the same
cuz the stuff they do is very similar to each other.
You know what I'm saying?
Which obviously men don't do, only women do it.
Well, I've never met one that's
different. They've always been all the
same to me. for the [ __ ] leading on, ghosting, excuses, etc., etc.
I mean, there's some
I mean, no, they're they're all they're
all full of [ __ ] They are all full of
Generally are all full of [ __ ]
And obviously, it's women because no men
do what they do. That's facts. That's
not me being gay. That's facts. So
therefore, it is them that's all the same. It is
it is women that are all the same.
See, I've never met a man that was a narcissist.
Well, actually, I have. Virgin boy is a
narcissist, but maybe only a couple.
Virgin boy is a narcissist. Um,
there is a few one, but mainly it's
women that are narcissist. I mean, that
tells you something. Steven Howard, when
Yeah, that's what I mean. They're all
the same because of Tik Tok, cuz the
[ __ ] that they watch. Yeah, they're all the same.
But most most narcissists are women. So,
why are mo why are most narcissists
women? Maybe you should ask that Lex
that that Lex therapy is why are most
why is it that most narcissists are women?
I'd love to see his response to that.
Why are most Yeah.
Yeah. I used to say to Virgin Boy all
the time, "All women are the same." He
says, "You don't know all women." I
said, "I know more [ __ ] women than
you." And I'm still saying it [ __ ]
Yeah. 11 years later.
I know more [ __ ] women than you and
they're all the [ __ ] same.
I used I used to say it a lot, mate. To Virgin Boy.
Yeah. I used to say I know more [ __ ]
women than you. Cuz I [ __ ] do, mate.
Cuz I [ __ ] well do know more women than you.
I do know more women than you
and they are all the same. I won't even
saying it to be awkward. I won't even
saying it to be difficult, bro. You know, you know
I was watching something about stray
cats earlier. It reminded me of Virgin
Boy. He's a little stray cat.
The little copycat.
And the stray cat was talking. Oh,
that's him. He's a little copycat. Little striker.
Yeah, he's a little copycat.
He's a little copycat,
isn't he? Ste, he's a little copycat.
He's copying. He's a copycat.
He's a [ __ ] copycat.
Is he a little copycat? Little copycat. He's
He's a little stray cat. He's a little
ginger straight straight cat.
He said Chev was attractive.
He said that she's attractive. Steven Howard,
you said that [laughter] she's attractive.
He said that she's attractive, Steven Howard.
He said she's attractive.
I can't get over that, bro.
He said that you can't deny she's attractive.
He's a little copycat.
He's a little stray cat,
isn't he? He's a copycat.
Yeah. What he wants to do is bloody well
fit in. Fit in with the crowd,
bro. That is so weird. You know, man,
whether you find someone attractive or
not, you'd really call someone gay.
You'd actually call someone gay for not
for not liking a certain woman.
Bro, that's weird.
But if you don't find a certain woman
attractive, that makes you gay. That
means you automatically like [ __ ]
That's [ __ ] weird, bro.
What is it with this [ __ ]
What is it with this [ __ ] Sher Cole, man?
What is it with this bloody Cheryl Cole?
I've had enough of this. Why?
I'm not gay. Little copycat.
Why does he say that? If you don't find
shovel co attractive, you're gay though. Steven Howard,
why did he say that to me? I'm not gay, bro.
Well, I don't [ __ ] like men. What the
What is it with him and bloody Shevel Cole?
couldn't believe you what he was saying to me.
No, but he says if you if you don't find
her attractive, you're gay.
Well, that's what he said to me. I said
I'm not gay.
He said that's homo vibes. Little copycat. Scooby,
someone said to me that if I don't find
Cheryl Co attractive, I'm gay.
I'm not gay. I just don't find her attractive.
I just don't find Cole attractive. I'm not gay.
[ __ ] Virgin boy said I was gay.
I'm not gay. I've been with women and stuff.
No, but he said that if I don't find
Cheryl car attractive, I'm gay. I think
he was just being a little copycat.
I think he was just trying to fit in
with the crowd. Scooby trying to fit in
like a little copycat. Like a little stray cat.
Yeah, I like big boobies.
I like big boobies. me. Yeah,
I don't I'm not gay, bro. I just don't
find her attractive. Doesn't mean I like dick.
What the [ __ ]
Yeah, he's a copycat, man. He's an absolute copycat.
Why? Why is he copying? Huh? [ __ ] eight.
[ __ ] eight copycats.
Wait until his [ __ ] dad dies. Steven
Howard, I'm going to I'm going to throw a party.
Watch when he's [ __ ] dad dies, mate.
It will be soon. I'll buy the most
expensive bottle of champagne, mate,
and I'll celebrate, mate. Trust me. Oh,
I'll do a YouTube barbecue when his dad
dies, mate. Oh,
[sighs and gasps] let's hope his dad
dies before my mom dies. But then he
might not tell people his dad's dead.
Yeah, he likes to make fun out of dead
relatives. Watch when his dad dies.
I'll have a party.
Watch, mate. You [ __ ] watch.
Yeah, you watch.
Yeah. You know why he does all of this
stuff grassing and stuff and doesn't
meet anyone? Stephen Howard is because
I'm not a kid. If I wasn't a grown man,
he'd happily meet me
um and try to like intimidate me and
argue with me. If I was 17 or maybe 18,
I noticed that. And then when I finally
turned into like 20, he didn't want it no more
cuz he knew that he can't talk down to a
grown man. He can do it to a kid, but he
can't do it to a grown man.
And that's basically when he decided
that, you know, he'll [ __ ] with people
online. And then when [ __ ] with
people online didn't work, right?
Um then obviously it's the boys in blue.
It's the boys in blue, mate. It's the
[ __ ] boys in blue.
Cuz think about it, right?
He's saying that he didn't meet me
because of my behavior, right?
Steven Howard, but he's the one sat on
YouTube every day stalking me, posting
about me. His whole life has been
obsessed with me, but he stopped meeting
me because of my behavior.
That doesn't make any sense.
He stopped meeting me,
right? Because of my behavior.
Yeah, he's the one on YouTube obsessed
with me every day. But don't forget, he
stopped meeting me because of my behavior. Strange.
That is very, very, very strange, isn't it?
Is it getting worse, Stephen Howard?
Like I said, I'm not on the channel,
bro. I don't go on the channel, lad. I
don't see any of it. I I would No, I
don't go on the channel. I'm never going
on that channel ever again.
I'm never going on that Virgin channel.
I don't go on Virgin's channels, mate.
Really, I don't go on it. I don't go on
that Red Star channel
because they're never going to meet you.
They're never going to say anything to
your face. So, there's no point reading
what they're writing,
going back and forth with a keyboard
warrior. It's pointless. I I don't go on
it, bro. Like I said, I really don't.
I'll never I'll never go on it ever again.
Nope. I only go on Monty's
cuz Monty's quite funny.
Yeah, I seriously don't go on it. Cuz
what this virgin wants is people to keep
going back and forth with him on videos.
He wants people to keep giving him
attention via videos.
He wants you to read stuff and then go
back and forth and back and forth and
back and forth and back and forth cuz
he's a keyboard warrior and I'm not
doing that. So there you go. You understand, bro? So, uh,
sad bastard. Really sad bastard. Really, mate. Really sad.
Yeah, I don't speak to Monty anymore.
Monty don't speak to me. It's good,
isn't it? Steven Howard.
It's quite good that, huh?
I feel hungry again.
Yeah, I'll never speak to him again,
though. He's a snake.
That's my mama.
That's my mommy with her chubby little cheeks.
That's my little mama.
By the way, I don't have these pictures.
Basically, when I go on this email, the
pictures are already on this device. So,
I don't have these pictures saved.
They're just on the when you go on edit avatar.
I have loads of pictures. I've got some
of the virgin as well,
the skin virgin. Um, I've got her. I've
got me. Yeah, they're not saved. I just
saved on hell on this account. Yeah.
I want to have a big session on
roulette. Steven Howard£500 versus
But I can't do it, bro.
I can't afford it nowadays to be risking
that kind of money.
No, bro. He's going to break my [ __ ]
phone. [ __ ] off. You're going to broke
You're going to break my [ __ ] screen.
[ __ ] off, man.
What? 500 versus Rouette. Steven Howard,
we might win like 10k.
Yeah, we could have been at 10 20k. Why? Why?
Yeah, but do you reckon I could win?
Stephen, I would
Yeah, he can do that all he wants. No one cares.
He can make a report all he wants. No
one gives a [ __ ]
That's fine. I've got plenty of evidence
on him anyways. So, he can report all he
wants. No one cares.
I didn't do anything that can get me
arrested. So that's not a problem. You
can report all he wants. Yep. Oh [ __ ]
Yeah, that's not a problem at all,
matey. He can report all he wants.
Oh, [ __ ] He's a loser, ain't it?
Running to the police over YouTube. What a loser.
What a loser, man. He's obsessed, isn't
he? He's so obsessed with me.
But remember, he stopped meeting me
because of my behavior.
I've got all your videos, all your
harassment, bro. You can call the police
all you want. They won't even come out
anyways. And if they do, trust me, bro,
it will be the last thing they do
anyways. I've got all of your [ __ ] And
this has got all your [ __ ] [ __ ] as well
that's been sent to the barrista. So, I
got all your lives, all your harassment.
I've got everything. your skin virgin
[ __ ] So, keep reporting.
Get the old bill out, matey.
I've got everything, bro. I've literally
got everything on a folder. I don't know
how many times I have to say this.
Everything on a folder.
161 different things, bro.
his voice, his face, calling,
screenshots, community posts, videos, blackmail,
you name it, bro. You name it, I've got it.
Stop trying to be a victim, you silly
little virgin, cuz you can't back yourself up.
[ __ ] What an absolute loser.
You got more, bro? Send it my way. If
you've got more, send it. I've got 161 different things.
So, the more the marrier, bro. I've
already got enough, but send it anyways.
Yeah, [ __ ] it, bro.
You know what I mean?
Reporting to the police that you're
coming on YouTube like you're some kind
of big man.
[ __ ] skint virgin trying to [ __ ]
come on here. Join the [ __ ] panels.
I've got evidence where he's tried to
join the panels as well. [ __ ] skin
little virgin. Skin little low life. Yeah.
Skint lowife virgin. Yep. Bless you.
S little bastard.
Anything you got, bro? Just send me it.
I've got more than enough stuff anyways,
so it's not a problem. So, yeah.
Yeah. Go on, bro.
What a loser.
Do you know the good thing when you live
in another country from someone Scooby?
You can do what you want.
You don't know the amount of [ __ ] I done
to that USA is bro. Message her family,
friends. I royally [ __ ] with her, bro.
If she lived here or I or I lived there,
I'd probably be in prison.
I for sure would be in court. That's the
good thing about it, bro. when you live
in another country.
I mean, they can't do anything. I mean,
they can call the police, but the police
are not going to do anything.
Trust me, unless Yeah. They they never
do anything. So,
that's a good thing. If they live in
another country, you can do what you want.
Like, if I get a number from a tourist
and they don't reply, I just send them my dick.
And uh obviously they can't do anything.
They can't do anything about it.
And this Jamie Thompson needs to stop
calling me the fat weirdo.
Fat freak. This Jamie Thompson little
weirdo that pretends he's got a wife
keeps stalking me as well. [ __ ] weirdo.
Fat bastard. [clears throat]
Fat jealous bastard ain't got no life.
Yeah, Peter Griffin. Fat ugly bastard,
bro. Stalks me every day. Don't know why
these people are so obsessed with me.
It's creepy, Scooby. It's really creepy.
It gives me the EB jebies. Yep.
Yeah, his real name is Jamie Thompson.
Anyway, I'm go
and I'll uh I'll see you in two weeks.
Anyways, I'll see you in about a week
and a half, two weeks. Yeah, cuz I'm
coming off this for a bit. So, yeah. See you. Bye-bye.