Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Just wanted to see if it's the same
people in YouTube. Hopefully not. I I
just want to be talking to myself, you know?
That's what I want to be doing. Yeah.
All I want to be doing is talking to everybody self.
No one else.
[ __ ] Yeah. I don't want to be talking
to anyone else. I just want to be
talking to myself. That's okay. [ __ ] Yep.
So far so good. No one's joining. That's
good. I don't want anyone to join. I
just want to be talk.
Like I said, I just want to be talking to myself.
I don't want to be talking to anyone else. That's good.
had some absolutely [ __ ]
lush food today. And I mean [ __ ] lush.
I should have recorded it, but I never
Yo, I had some Brazilian food today,
bro. It was [ __ ] lang.
Oh my [ __ ] god, bro. Brazilian food
is up there, bro. Oh my [ __ ] god. It
was banging. Absolutely banging.
I would have would have recorded it, but
I was with my mom. Yeah,
it was nice.
Nice Brazilian food.
Brazilian food is nice. It's like pork,
lamb, it's everything. It's literally
everything. Only thing I didn't see was
turkey and they bring it fresh. Uh um basically
it's like a macaroni cheese
as like it's like a buffet thing. You go
up and get the buffet and then they
bring meat to you on like a skewer. So
pork loin, pork belly, lamb, beef,
chicken, [ __ ] everything, bro.
Everything. Sausage, everything.
And you choose like which one you want.
It's [ __ ] good, bro. That's my first
time having Brazilian. It was banging.
It's definitely up there, bro. Pork
loin, pork belly, chicken wings, lamb,
beef, you name it. They They had it,
bro. They had it
and they bring it to you as well. It's [ __ ] good. Lush. Yeah.
Yeah. It was lost.
Yeah, it's good.
I recommend it, man. Definitely.
Cuz when you go to like a like an
Indian, they don't do beef
and like maybe Chinese won't do lamb and
vice versa, but here they do everything.
Gam as well, they had gammon.
Gammon. Oh man, it's [ __ ] gorgeous.
And it only cost Yeah. £24 each.
£24 something each.
Bog him mate. [ __ ] bargain. Really?
No, it wasn't, mate. Not for what I got.
Not for what I got. I got tons and tons
and tons of meat.
24 is too much for all that meat. No, it
ain't, mate. And you could stay there
for two hours as well if you wanted to.
But all of that different meat, £24 is
Indian was [ __ ] 40 something the other day. Yeah.
Oh, Greg, you would have loved it.
You would have loved this Brazilian
restaurant I went to today. I was with
my mom. I didn't record it, but they had
gin, pork belly, pork loin, lamb, beef, [ __ ] everything.
[ __ ] everything. Any meat you you
could think of, they had it. and they'd
bring it to you like fresh
um and then they bring it to you like fresh
um like they they put it in in like on a
skewer as well. So they'd cook it in
like um some oven and bring it out
straight to you. Bro, you would you'd
love it. You you would love it. I knew
it was going to be good as well cuz I
got some Brazilian friends
and they recommended Brazilian food
before but I just never went. That's nice. Yeah.
Yeah. Literally. Yeah. That's that was it. Yeah.
And he's got a dentist tomorrow. Griezy. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, good for him, bro. No one cares.
He's a loser.
But yeah, they they they carve it in
front of you. Yeah.
Yeah. I won't be out this week.
I can kind of try and meet this woman
this week. She text back again yesterday, Grezy.
I don't know.
I could do it.
Save some money, bro. I really need to
start saving some money.
Not cuz I don't have money. I've got I
can [ __ ] go out. But it's more of um
I do it every every year for like two
months, two or three months. I always do
it no matter how much money I get. But
maybe depends how bored I am. If I'm
bored, then I will. Maybe.
I don't [ __ ]
I don't know when I'd be wanting to go
out drinking again, bro. After [ __ ]
last week, I had a nasty hangover.
I had a nasty [ __ ] hangover, bro.
I thought I was going to die, bro. I
actually thought I was going to die.
It's kind of dead, isn't it?
It's kind of dead going out drinking
now, is it, Grezy?
You only live once, Grezy. You only live once.
I don't even know who the [ __ ] that is.
You need to do some traveling, Greasy,
before you get really old, lad.
You need to go to some places before you
[ __ ] get too old.
And that's not even me taking a piss. I'm
I'm actually being serious, bro. I'm not
even taking the piss when I'm saying it 100%. Oh, [ __ ]
There's a lot of stalkers on this community, Scooby.
A lot of [ __ ] stalkers on here.
A lot of [ __ ] stalkers, mate. A lot of stalkers.
that Jamie Thompson being one of the
biggest [ __ ] stalkers.
[ __ ] stalker, man.
He's a [ __ ] stalker, Scooby. He's
getting my number out. Yeah, I'm getting
calls like every [ __ ] day, bro.
Every [ __ ] second of every day, bro.
It's [ __ ] weird. They're [ __ ]
stalkers. It's not even funny, bro.
They're absolute. You know what they
remind me a bit? They remind me of Reddit uh
moderators. Some of these people on here, bro.
They remind me of Reddit mods. Yep.
Reddit mods. Not even joking. [ __ ] weird, bro.
I got a [ __ ] email from a [ __ ] um fostering agency.
He's a weirdo, bro. He's a [ __ ]
weirdo, bro. He's gave my [ __ ] number
out to and [ __ ] But I'm not changing
my number. No way.
I'm not changing my number.
Stalking in it, bro.
Stalking weirdos on here, man. Stalking weirdos.
That's why I wasn't on yesterday. I'll
just come on and off when I please, to be honest.
I see that Smokeoky B was on earlier.
Another low life.
Another [ __ ] low life. Hey.
It's sad, isn't it, bro? Really sad.
The people are sad. Yep. One second.
What do you think, Greavves? Did you go
out drinking this week or uh
that not okay with me, boss?
Not okay with you, boss. Nah.
No drinking for Peter Belly.
Oh, Greasy. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Uh, I forgot to tell you. There was an
Instagram real. Yeah. And it was this
guy talking about narcissists. You would
have absolutely loved it. He was saying
basically, yeah, if you've done someone
wrong, right, you've cheated on them or
you've used them or whatever and
you uh you block them and then you try
to put the script on the other side and
make it seem like they were the ones
that done wrong and then you just go
about your life normally without giving
an explanation. You've got mental
problems. Like he he worded it so good.
Oh yeah, I forgot there was something I
had to tell you. I actually recorded it
as well. I might actually um show you it.
And I was I was watching it. I was like,
"Yeah, USA all over." Literally, bro,
like USA all over again, bro. Yeah. I'm
going to put it up. You're going to love it. One second.
I was thinking, bro, if my mom had done
that, Grezy, you know,
I'm putting up right now, Captain. One second.
Is that all right with you, Captain
Grezy? Is that okay with you, Captain? Captain. Captain,
is that all right with you, Captain?
You like that, didn't you? Thank you, Captain. Oh,
right. It's loaded.
Yep. This is USA, is he? One second. Hold up. right?
There you go, Captain.
What do you think? Graves eight.
Rezy, what do you think? Goodbye. M
Crazy. Did you watch it?
Not for me. I could take a nail off of
YouTube. Most of these people can't.
It's not even addictive. I'm just bored
and yeah, I'm about to go sleep in a
bit. It's not No, it's not just It's not
addictive at all. Why would it be
addictive? It's the same spasticated
people every day, self-projecting,
ain't got a life.
So, no, not really. Most of the people
are just haters that talk about
themselves. There's nothing addicting about it.
Yep. I went to a Brazilian restaurant.
Yeah, a Brazilian restaurant.
And I don't know what I'm doing
this week. I'm not drinking.
They're just weirdos on here. I need to
go to the dentist tomorrow.
Uh yeah, I ain't drinking this week. [ __ ] that. Nah,
not this week. M.
Not this week. Matey. doing. Oh, [ __ ]
It's such a waste of time, is it? Going out drinking,
isn't it? Just such a waste of bloody time. Yes, it is.
What's the time?
It's waste of time, bro.
You already know the answer to that. So
I don't know why you're asking
why you're asking questions you already
know the answers to. To be fair,
you know that I don't. So I don't know
why you're asking.
Must be trolling, lad. Wow.
Lost 1,900 pound. [ __ ] that, bro.
What the [ __ ]
That is mad.
I should have booked a holiday, bro.
That's mad. What the [ __ ]
Yeah, that's USA is he? That is greasy.
That's USA is he? That's definitely
definitely USA is he isn't it?
Yeah, that's defo USA is he that is
No, that is definitely definitely USA is 100%.
Yeah, I'll keep it up, bro.
No, that's definitely USA. Easy.
What casino? Uh, what casino was it? [ __ ]
Yeah, I've lost 2K on roulette before.
Only once though. I've only lost 2K once,
but I had loads of money, so Yeah.
Where is it?
[ __ ] What location?
Yeah, that's USA is in it, Grezy. Well,
see if this person wants to meet up and
go on a date,
then I obviously I'll go out this week,
but if not, then I probably won't go out this week.
Um, so yeah,
they were texting back.
It's just pointless though, isn't it
really? Going out drinking this country, bro. Cuz
it never changes.
It never changes. Your [ __ ] Tik
Tockers are getting rejected.
People that are Tik Tokers have got more
money than me then. I mean, yeah. Yeah.
I've never got I've never been to a
casino in Manchester.
Yeah. You save a lot of money as well.
Yep. And you also save a lot of money.
Yeah. Save a lot of money. Yeah.
Like I said, you should say from January until March. Basically
say from January until March or like or
like midFeb maybe, you know. It's good, man.
I do it every year me. Yeah.
something like that, bro. Yeah.
Can't believe you lost, 1900.
But yeah, Bob, why are you asking
questions that you know the answers to?
You know that it will always be the same here.
Just like I know it will always be the same here. Yeah.
Do you know this? Just like me,
1900. [ __ ] hell, bro. You mad.
I could never lose that kind of money now. Never. [ __ ] never.
That's a madness. Yeah. Um
130 football bet. I don't gamble that
much. Oh [ __ ]
And I ain't playing roulette in almost a month, so
don't gamble that much
cuz I can't stand losing. But I'll
probably put £150 on two teams at some point.
Sometimes I do have thoughts of going
big on roulette online, but
just faults. They're not even urges.
Yeah, they're faults, not urges. So I
just don't to be fair. Nah.
Been there, done that.
Been there, done that. Want a t-shirt, matey. [ __ ]
Balls are itchy. So yeah, that's that.
But yeah, if this person doesn't meet,
I'm going to say to him, let's meet
maybe tomorrow, the next day. Um meet in
um meet on Saturday. And if they don't meet, then
that's me in it.
Never done the lottery in my life.
And on scratch cars, I've won a little
bit. Yeah. Not much though.
No, I think I've won like
20 pound on a scratch card. Oh, [ __ ]
I'm definitely definitely
And I need to find a day where it's when
it's not raining to go out.
It's just kind of pointless going out in
this country because it would always be
the same here.
It would always be the same
like with the women and stuff. So
it always be the same here. So start
But yeah, I haven't had a date since April. So,
I don't know why you'd think I'd have
any dates lined up.
It will always be the same. Sorry. Yep.
Yeah. You can't even get laid. It sucks, isn't it?
It will never change. So yeah,
I start it.
People on Reddit say that you'll meet
someone though, Bob.
I'm kind of hoping this person doesn't
want to meet me this week so I can save money cuz
save money means more money to do other
things in a different country, not this
[ __ ] [ __ ] country where nothing ever changes.
You know, if I stayed in here for the
past two, three months, I'd be loaded,
bro. [ __ ] loaded. I would
actually be loaded, bro. Not even joking.
Went out last week, the week before, the
week before that. [ __ ] would have
been loaded, bro. [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. This person who was messaging me
back, they're like, "Ty, you know."
Well, I haven't messaged her asking her
to go out.
I hope she says no. I really hope she
says no, bro.
So, it gives me an excuse to stay in.
That's what I want to do. I want to stay
in, bro. I don't want to [ __ ] go out.
Obviously, if someone wants to meet you,
then it's different story, you know.
Obviously, then you'll go out in it.
I haven't messaged her yet
about going out.
I just say I'm going to be around Saturday.
Join me. basically.
Then I think I won't go out until Yeah. mid December.
Probably mid December. Yeah. Because
there's just no point, bro.
There's just there's just no point.
There's really no point.
No, I'm not.
Because it's always going to be the same
thing. I'm not interested. I have a
boyfriend. People leading you on.
But it's all right once in a while if
you're really, really bad.
And there's literally nothing else to
do. But other than that,
there's really no point. I had a really
bad hangover last week, you know,
really bad hangover.
Yeah, it's bad.
[ __ ] bad, bro. The headaches and So yeah.
Yeah. That's why I'm leaving the country.
That's why I'm leaving.
That's why I'm actually leaving.
That's what you need to do. You need to
save money and you need to leave. That's
what you need to do. Jesus Christ. Yeah.
Never getting anywhere here, are we,
mate? We're never getting anywhere here.
and the fact that Tik Tockers get
rejected as well. Tik Tockers that have
got more followers than me, people that
actually famous. So, I mean, what chance
does a normal person have?
No chance. Absolutely no chance.
Absolutely [ __ ] no chance. Yep. No fire. Yeah.
What do you think's going to happen,
Bob? One day you're going to go out and
it's all of a sudden going to be different.
Is that what you think? One day you go
out and all of a sudden it's going to be different.
Is that what you really think, bro?
Is that what you really really think?
It will never change. It will never
Um, no I don't.
It will never change, bro. So,
and it's toxic as well. So,
that's another thing. you get banned for
trying to speak to people as well. It's
just all toxic [ __ ] Um toxic [ __ ]
people don't need
in their life basically. So
yeah, toxic [ __ ] people don't need.
I don't even get m
You know, you need to leave.
You need to leave.
There's some guy that lives up the road
and um he said he's going to Thailand in
two weeks cuz he hates it here. I said,
"Oh yeah, that's the same as that man.
He's going for two months. He's going to
Thailand for two months.
[ __ ] don't blame him, mate. Don't blame him.
Do not blame him at all.
No, I don't blame him at all, mate.
Where are you? >> Yeah.
No one's bloody interested, Bob.
No one's bloody interested.
And then the other number didn't reply.
I've been with a M. You say Izzy was a M
in real life. So I've been with Mas. Um,
so many numbers from the past three
times I've gone out, bro. Like 24 numbers. Mad. About 24.
24 [ __ ] numbers, bro. Madness. What's matter? Yep. That So yeah.
So yeah, basically
going to make myself a coke in a minute. Yeah.
Let me back up my thing. Oh, wait.
Sorry, bro. It's just [ __ ] catchy. That's all.
Tatchy as [ __ ]
I'll be washing up in a kitchen. Yeah.
And I'll be [ __ ] saying Virgin boy.
[ __ ] I'm mad.
[ __ ] is wrong with me, bro?
[ __ ] issues or some [ __ ]
I need to go and piss one sec.
Who that bloody is that bloody who that bloody skin? Oh,
no. Because dropping your standards don't work.
No one's bloody interested.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. No one.
No one's bloody interested, Bob.
What are you up to this week, Captain?
Nice cold punt. CocaCola. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm not going out this week unless
she she wants to meet.
I need a nice detox after that [ __ ]
that mad one.
That just came wrong.
I told you, but this is something that
[ __ ] comes out. You know, you
want them some salted popcorn.
Is that okay with you, boss?
Is that okay with you, Captain?
Yeah, that's one of the only things I
don't like is um sweet popcorn. I can't
stand it, bro. I don't like sweet
popcorn for some reason. I don't like it.
I like salted. Oh,
that's another thing. The Brazilian
place, they never had um
normal Pepsi. They had Pepsi Max or had
to get lemonade.
Yeah. Had to get a lemonade grievy. Okay
with you, boss.
Lemonade was still nice. you. Oh, like I
said, I'm going to go back to that
Brazilian place and I'm going to record
it this time. Whoozie. Oh, mate.
For £24, you definitely got your money's worth.
Definitely definitely got your money's worth. [ __ ] hell.
What do you think, Greg?
Should I go out drinking this week or
not or not? Nah.
What do you think, Captain?
Nah, I don't think it's a good idea, matey.
What? Why would you say nah, we
just prefer, you know, chilling in with
a cup of [ __ ]
Why would you say no, Captain?
Well, it is not good going out drinking greasy.
Why not graves the not good going out?
You save money as well. Is it?
It's good to save money. It's always
nice to save money.
I'll be out again like I said um December
unless this number wants to meet then December. I think
okay with you boss
the okay with you boss
okay with you captain
I was just really bored on Thursday for some
Don't normally get them days, man. I was [ __ ] bored. Nah, bro.
No, cuz I need to leave this country and
if I keep going out wasting money,
it's going to take me longer to do it. So,
I mean, it's the same [ __ ] I mean, what
what content do you want to see?
It's always the same old [ __ ]
I mean, it is generally the same old
[ __ ] every time you go out.
I mean, it's just the same thing
in in it is always the same [ __ ] Sorry. What? Yeah.
Go out. Get drunk.
Here. I've got a boyfriend.
Get numbers that lead you on.
The end. Isn't it greasy? The end.
Isn't that Isn't that a thing, Grezy? The end.
See, I can't even go to the pictures cuz
there's nothing on Grezy.
There's nothing on at the pictures. Um, no.
Well, that's never going to happen. So,
you know, that's never going to happen. So, I mean,
I've been out more than anyone in the
world. I've tried more than anyone in
the world. It's never going to happen in
the country. So, yeah.
It's never going to change.
I've been out a million times. It's
never going to be any different. So,
it's never ever going to be any different.
Is it crazy? Never
will never change. So
think of how many times I've been out in
the past four years. Had it ever happened?
The last times I've gone out in the past
four years. Has it happened? No. So
why would it happen the next time you go
out? Think about it logically.
It's true though, isn't it? Why would it
happen the next time you go out?
I think that makes sense, mate. Wow.
No thank you.
No thank you, bro. I'd rather keep
myself dignity and my pride.
You can if you want. No,
I would never disrespect myself like that.
Putting up with their [ __ ] I only do it
for a laugh.
No. If I was a virgin, maybe if I was
like nons, if I was like a virgin like him,
then I would No. Nah, nah,
I'm good, bro.
I'm leaving. I'm leaving England, bro.
I know what I'm doing, bro.
I only go out and try for the sake of
trying when I got nothing else to do.
Why would I Why would I go out every day approaching
when I know that they're all the same
and it's always going to be the same?
It's okay if you're really bored and
there's nothing else to do. then just do
it for a laugh in it. But
it will literally never change. Like I
told you, I've got 24 numbers in the
past month and I haven't even got a
single date yet. So I mean
it will never change. It will never ever change. So all right.
I didn't go, bro. I was bullshitting.
I will be gone or that I will be gone. [ __ ] sake.
Will be I will be gone.
Yeah, Bob says that I should go out every week.
I've already been out three weeks in a row
and it's just the same [ __ ] It never
changes. Never never changes.
Yeah, it never changes.
So, this is a waste of time here.
I got my haircut.
My ass at some point
getting long but out.
Yeah, 100%. I know it is
going to be to go out every day and try
bombber. I don't really know. Well, I
didn't know it was bomb, but I know
they're trolling obviously, bro.
Remember these people are older than me,
by the way.
Remember that these people are older
than me, Big Les. Yep.
No, Big L, I was just saying that I've
got 24 numbers the past three times I've
gone out and not a single date. Well,
this person's been speaking to me, so
I'm going to invite them out this week.
And obviously if they want to meet then
I'll meet. I don't mind. But if not then
I won't be going out because I had a
really bad hangover last week and I want
to kind of save some money as well. So
that's it. But if they want to meet then
I'll meet and it was guaranteed. I don't
mind meeting you know problem. Yeah.
You say you try hard. You don't try
hard. Would be doing it every day than
you can. Moan.
Oh, bro. Just stop it.
Just just just stop it. Everybody knows
I've tried more than anyone in the
world. I mean, just just stop it, bro.
It's it's embarrassing. Just stop it.
Just just stop.
Just just stop it.
Stop it. Good. Yeah.
and [ __ ] um
you wouldn't think right you got a bunch
of 30 40 year olds sat on YouTube every
day trolling would you pathetic
Absolutely pathetic, matey.
Yeah, that's nice, bro.
Shame he didn't owe me when I went to
Manchester two times.
Shame he didn't owe me them two times, did he?
Shame he didn't owe me when he ran off
of YouTube for a year when he got doxed.
He didn't owe me them three times, did
he? No. Still using the word own. Bro,
you need to you need to grow up. You
people on here seriously seriously need
to grow up. You're like double my age
sat on the internet trolling. It's sad
as [ __ ] How you even think it's normal
is is mad.
It's [ __ ] pathetic.
You got some fat [ __ ] called [ __ ]
Jamie Thompson [ __ ] stalking me every
day. What a weirdo. Only you people
would think this is normal.
Got serious serious serious issues.
Serious serious issues. We need to talk
about it, man. Why Why do you do this
[ __ ] every day on YouTube? Can you answer me?
Was you bullied at school?
Is it because your skin?
Like why why do you do this [ __ ] every day?
I'm generally curious why they do it
every day. Uh Big Les.
Why they do this [ __ ] every day? It's
sad, bro. Really sad.
I think I generally think these people
are bullied, bro. I'm not even joking. I
generally think they were bullied
their whole life.
I generally think so, you know.
Yeah, I [ __ ] do.
It's [ __ ] sad.
I get calls all day from random numbers,
big le because of this Jamie Thompson.
Does he want to bum me or something, bro? Like,
does he does he want me to spread it
open or something? He's a weirdo, bro.
[ __ ] got these random ass numbers calling me. [ __ ] mad.
But I know, bro. It's just people that
hate their life.
So there's people that just hate themselves.
Proper proper stalker, bro. He's a We
got some [ __ ] virgin in out of London
constantly stalking me. And I don't even
go on the channel anymore.
I don't go on the channel anymore. I
haven't been on the channel for two
weeks and I'm never going on the channel
ever again, Big Les. Because there's no
point going back and forth with a
keyboard warrior that's never going to meet you.
Back and forth with a keyboard warrior
that will never meet you.
You know what I mean? There's no point.
It's immature. It's what children do, you know?
But yeah, that JB Thompson's definitely
a stalker. Definitely a stalker, bro.
Proper proper stalker. I think he's got autism.
Yeah, probably got probably got autism
to be fair. Oh, [ __ ]
Nice detox. Can't beat a nice detox. No,
really can't make it.
Oh, it's four. Well, Franklin
You'll never lose it.
So yeah, when are you people going to
grow up anyways and get a life on here?
Yeah. And get a job.
So, who who did that remind you of? Um,
when that man was talking about people
that do that in a video, Greavvesy, who
who did that remind you of?
Who Who did that remind you of?
When am I going to get a job? When you
I'll get a job when you get a job. Maybe
I already have a job.
How do you know?
Maybe I already have a job. How do you know?
You know, you don't know what I do. You
don't know me, kid.
You don't know anything about me
other than my name and what I look like.
Maybe I do work every day.
Maybe I was at work today. Maybe I was
at that I was at work yesterday. How do you know?
You don't [ __ ] know. Nothing good.
Well, duh. I mean, that's just what will
always happen. Big L.
I mean, yeah. The guy's obsessed.
He could actually be spending his time
finding someone to have sex with and
then he could lose his virginity.
But if he wants to stalk me all day,
that's fine, bro. I don't go on the
channel anyways. I'll never go on the
channel ever again. People can do what
they want to do. He won't be the first
and he won't be the last, mate.
And they tried to call me obsessed. Nah,
mate. Nah. So anyways, how do you know I
wasn't at work today? Maybe I was at
work today. You don't know. You don't
know me. You didn't answer the question.
No. That reminded me of USA. Izzy. That
was definitely USA. Izzy.
No. That was definitely USA. Izzy,
that was definitely USA. Izzy. Yep.
Him, Red Star, Jamie Thompson. They're
all little stalkers, bro.
They're all little lowife stalkers. Yeah.
And a few others as well. Yeah. Smokey
be another one.
You listing all the thing that you don't have.
smart enough, Terry. I'm smarter than you
and I can afford a new pair of trainers
and you can't.
Anyways, I'm going to ban you. I'm going
to put you on time out
cuz you're boring as [ __ ]
So, yeah. Uh I had a Brazil I had some
Brazilian food earlier, Steven Howard.
Yeah. I had some nice Brazilian food.
I just got my haircut, brother.
Look at that hair. Jesus.
Look at that [ __ ] hair, man. Oh [ __ ] Oh man. Oh,
you all right, Captain?
All right. Top 10. Top 10 pump.
Yeah. When he was talking, that reminded
me of USA. Is he? Yeah.
But yeah, anyways, um, Big L, that's why
you don't meet someone with autism.
That's why you don't meet someone with autism.
You know, [ __ ] off. Don't leave you
alone. You can't get rid of the [ __ ] you know? [ __ ] weird mad.
I said to this American
All I can make you laugh, Grezy. Yeah,
I can make you laugh.
You're that tied with USA, bro.
I should have got the [ __ ] pregnant
because that way she wouldn't be able to
run up her [ __ ] mouth. She wouldn't
be able to be cocky, would she, Greasy?
Think about it, right? If she if she
tried to get rude, right? If she say
that the [ __ ] was pregnant and then she
tried to get rude and she tried to be a
narcissist. Squeezy, all I had to say,
I was thinking of this the other day,
all I'd have to say is listen, [ __ ]
I spunked up you and you done absolutely
nothing about it and you're pregnant and
you're carrying my baby, so shut up.
and you'll do nothing.
That's how you can own these narcissists.
You get them pregnant.
Then they can't say anything.
Then they can't say anything back.
You know what I mean? Then they can't
say anything back. You always
You should do that.
I'm a funny [ __ ] Oh no, Grezy.
Why do you think I will never Why do you
think I don't eat people out, Grezy?
Because they can never use it against me.
They can never say that they dominated me. Greasy.
Wherever you get a woman pregnant and
stuff, you can say that you spunked up
them and now they're pregnant and you
can laugh about it.
And then what could their response be? Nothing.
You know, nothing.
Then they'll be [ __ ] Grezy. They
won't be able to laugh then, will they?
They won't be laughing them if they've
got a [ __ ] baby in their stomach.
Greasy, would I?
It won't be so funny then, will it? [ __ ] [ __ ]
ain't it, Greasy? [ __ ] [ __ ]
Oh, I love it, mate. [ __ ] love it. Lovely.
Yeah. I said to this American, "Can I
get you pregnant?" And then she blocked me.
You need to get a woman pregnant, Bob.
So then they can't they can't mouth off
cuz you you have one over on them.
If you get someone pregnant, you have
one over on them. You see,
isn't that right, M? Yeah, defin M. Yeah.
Yeah. She blocked me even though she
said that she'd suck my willie.
That's what I find with weird with these
women is they change, don't they,
Greasy? They change.
Here today, gone tomorrow. They change.
Yeah. The next person I have sex with,
I'm going to get them pregnant with you
to teach them a lesson.
That's what I'm going to do. I want to
teach them a lesson.
Is that okay with you, boss?
Right, let's go. Um
Yeah, this is what I don't understand, bro.
Yeah, it's weird how they randomly go.
Funny, ain't it?
I think you'd have luck in America with
your accent. [ __ ] that.
America's even worse.
If you if you approach someone in America, bro,
they'll just straight up say
they'll straight up [ __ ] say that um
this is what they say. They say um
they say basically
that they don't have social media.
I'll do it for you. Greasy boss.
I'll do it for you, boss. You want You can't.
America's the same.
Do you remember?
So, Antman, how's the approaching going?
How's the drinking going? Like, how's it
Ah, they all got boyfriends.
I'll never forget that, bro. The way you said it.
They all got boyfriends. I said, "Calm down."
I said, "Calm down. You're You know,
you're going to cause a scene here."
He didn't give a [ __ ]
Scooby, what do you think would happen
if I go out on Saturday approaching Scooby?
Maybe Greavves, this person beats me
this week, I can get attached again.
Grievy, what do you think?
You reckon maybe I'll be able to get
attached again now?
Yeah, I think I get depressed, bro, in
the winter. I'm like really not
depressed as in like um
not depressed as in like killing myself
or that or stay in bed, but I feel
weird, bro. And it's not anxiety either.
I don't have anxiety. It was It's just
weird. It's like a weird feeling, bro.
I felt like this even when I had the house.
I think it's just this country. It just
makes everyone depressed. It's a depressing country.
It's a depressing place to be in it.
It's depressing as [ __ ] bro.
It's like you always doubt yourself
and you think you're worse than you
actually are. Like, you doubt yourself. And
I think of like bad experiences I've had
with women and [ __ ]
And and I feel isolated now. See, back
in the old house, I didn't feel isolated
cuz I always had company, which is why I
didn't go out as much, which is why I
probably go out now more because
obviously I don't have um
um anyone basically here, do I? So I'm
kind of isolated
and I always go to the I always go to
the cinema in the winter grievy and it
always reminds me of USA Izzy.
I don't know why it's weird, bro. That
always comes up, you know,
when I'm depressed and stuff. But
hopefully this person will meet me this
week and maybe I can get attached again. Greavesy,
what do you think, Greavves? I could get
attached again. No.
What do you think, Reevesy?
Maybe I could get attached again or what?
You reckon I could get attached?
You reckon, G? You reckon I can get attached?
Yeah, but my
Yeah, but Yeah, but my
Yeah, but my mama doesn't want me.
She abandoned me. So,
yeah, but do you remember that account
that come in the other day, Greasy?
There's a lot of history for Peter Belly
in Elephant and Castle.
This account keeps mocking me. It keeps
following me wherever I go.
Like if you're not on YouTube, nothing
happens. But as soon as you come back,
he's there, bro. I don't know who it is.
There's a lot of there's a lot of um
history for Peter Belly
in Elephant and Castle. Do you get it, Grezy?
[ __ ] hell. Oh gosh.
So what happened in elephant in castle gre
Yeah. Well, how do you know these things? Huh?
already found his
Yeah, but you shouldn't remember this stuff.
Yeah, that was someone else.
No, she never said that. She said, "I
really want you, but I don't think you want me."
And I said, "I do."
That's the one that sucked my togery.
That's the one that sucked my toger.
No, what happened was I I see this
person in the corner
and I was like, "Oh, let me go over and
speak to her." It was in the O'Neals. It
was in the O'Neal's W Street review. Actually,
remember it was in the O'Neals. He was a
blonde little thing. And then she said,
"Oh, she was from um Georgia."
I said, "Oh, nice."
And then she said that her name was
Emily and stuff. And then we was talking
and I got her number and then she was like,
she was like kissing me and stuff. And
then she was like, "I really want you,
but I don't think you want me."
I said, "I do, but everybody's looking."
One second. So, I ordered myself a little drink.
And then the bartender was looking,
order myself a little drink. Bartender
was looking and then I took her to the
alleyway and then she sucked my greasy.
Well, I don't think you want me.
That's funny, bro.
Who even said something like that?
We always used to hit up that place every Thursday.
Nope. It wasn't a dream, mate. It was
very much real life.
It was very much real life.
very much real life, mate.
I don't make up stories like the Virgin
Steen Howard. You know that
I don't make up stories like the Skint Virgin.
Oh, I just bit my [ __ ] lip. Ah.
Have you ever done that, Graves? Oh,
I was watching the Little Britain thing yesterday.
Yeah, I was dead wrong.
I'm looking for somebody with the name
of Linda Williams.
Um, how old? Um, anywhere between 37 and
38 because as you know I can't afford to
be picky at this age.
I love that.
Are you Are you sure the film's been made? No.
No. But it's the film that I would like
to see today.
That I would like to see today.
Well, I don't think you're going to be
able to see it. It's okay. I'll just wait.
You'll you'll wait.
Yeah. Until it's been made.
What a lovely site. Yeah.
Yeah. That black guy talking about that
reminded me of USA is he because that's
what she done to me. She [ __ ] me over
and left me wondering. Grievy.
Yeah, that's exactly what she done. And
he's right. Like they go on with their
life and meet new people and stuff.
Yeah, it's bad, isn't it, bro? Really, really bad.
It is bad to be fair, bro. And people
that have got that people that do that
have got mental problems
with he's quite right that anyone that
does that has got mental problems.
It's true they do have little problems in it.
Far, bro. That far.
That far, bro.
What do you think, Greasy?
Like I I I know cuz I argued with
someone before some woman, right? This
was ages ago. I remember telling you
about this and I found out she got
abused by her like her parent and stuff.
And I didn't realize I didn't realize
when I said I said to her I'm going to
beat her up and that not realizing that
she had a um
um a history of abuse. I didn't even
know that until and then I said oh I was
on the buck back. I was like [ __ ] I feel
bad you know bro like I felt bad. I like
made it um made it my mission to
basically say sorry to her and [ __ ] It
was bad bro. Really bad. So I can't lie
I'd have a guilty conscience if I was to
do anything like that, you know. So
I felt bad, bro. So anyone that does
that is [ __ ] up, bro. Anyone that does
that is [ __ ] up.
Cuz even remember that time I went to
the toilet and never come back. Grezy,
I still justified why I done it. I never
ran away like a coward and I literally
ditched them. So
it is cowardly. It is cowardly, bro. It
was done on purpose as well,
Grezy. It was very much done on purpose. You know,
I know how people can Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ]
Grievy, that Lex guy replied, by the
way. Oh, he replied on Instagram. I
didn't tell you. What did he say? Um,
one second. I've got it here.
Okay. Where is it?
Where is it now? Hold on. Conversation loaded. One sec.
No, he didn't call me that. He said
I said to him, "Oi."
He said, "Question mark." I said, "I
heard you're right night. Explain this.
Why are most narcissist women?" He said,
"Tik Tok 7:30. Feel free to join." I
said, "Why not have a one v one
discussion here and now?" He said, "You
think I have time for a one-on-one all
day and you're the only one, lot?" I
said, "You do realize white nighting
will never get you laid, bro." He
responded, "Good job I'm not doing that
then, isn't it? Goodbye." Never called
me a [ __ ] misogynist, did he? No. No.
Cuz he knew not to go there, Grezy.
You know, he knew not to go there with me.
Cuz I I would have [ __ ] him up. I
would have [ __ ] him up, mate. You know
what I'm like, Grezy. You know what I'm like. Yeah. Oh yeah.
Trying to get me on TikTok. I don't want
to go on that [ __ ] [ __ ]
That's where all these [ __ ] NPC women
go. You know why they're NPCs? these
women cuz they all they all watch the
same [ __ ] They all go on Tik Tok. They
all go on Instagram. That's why they're
all the same. He said, "Yeah, Ant-Man
said that you know women in in Thailand,
they even speak like, bro, what the
hell, bro?" But you know, that proper
like westernized. And he always says to
them, "There's nothing Asian about you."
Ant-Man says to them, "There's literally
nothing Asian about you." cuz they they
they say rah and stuff, you know how
they're like proper westernized
[ __ ] you know? And he says there's
nothing Asian about you.
That mean there's nothing Asian about you.
No, I'm all right. Just having my little popcorn, you know.
Yeah, there's nothing Asian about these
women. A lot of women in Thailand,
there's nothing Asian about them.
There's nothing Asian about these women.
A lot of these women we
like Jinky Izzy.
I like Jinky Izzy. She She licked my ass. Yep.
Do you like Jinky? Is he greasy? Grezy, remember
you can't let these [ __ ] women win.
Remember that account that keeps coming
on saying that. Grezy, don't let these
[ __ ] women win. Peter Belly,
don't let these [ __ ] women win.
Don't let these [ __ ] women win. Oh,
bro, that's funny.
That's funny. Is it Grezy?
Don't let these hunting women win.
I don't want Oh gosh,
you do like it when I say that. Oh gosh. Oh [ __ ]
What did you just do here? Mister H. Oh god,
I found some more Coca-Cola.
Grezy, can you go downstairs and get me
some more Coca-Cola, please, boss?
Thank you, Captain. I'm cozy. I'm
playing my little game. I don't want to
go back downstairs.
Peter Belly can't get attached anymore.
Because he's already found his mama.
I know she does, but she's all the way in Manchester.
She sucked Peter Belly's dick very nicely.
That was a lovely sight.
Licked my ass. Sucked my willie.
What more could you ask for?
I can't believe she licks my butt. Jesus Christ.
Yes, it [ __ ] is far, mate. Manchester
is not far. Nah, it's [ __ ] around the
corner, is it? Not far. No, not far,
mate. Nah, just round the [ __ ] go.
Just around the corner, man.
It is [ __ ] far, mate.
I'll take the virgin with me.
Be his first time getting laid in it. Steven Howard.
You reckon I should go and see um
Chinese is he greasy?
Remember when I said, "Oh, mean you
should have a baby." She's like, "Oh,
would you be able to support the baby?"
I said, "Yeah,
I need to find someone to have a baby
with. I need to have one over on them,
Grezy. I don't want them to win. I don't
want these [ __ ] women to win, Grezy.
Don't let them [ __ ] women win.
Women win. Is that why
them [ __ ] were laughing at us?
Is it a real person behind that Bob
account? Was it?
Is it a real person or no?
You've seen the account, haven't it, Bob?
Is it a real Is it a real person or is it automated? H
going to be a lonely winter for me.
I haven't got my mommy to cuddle anymore
greasy, do I?
You know what? Sometimes I wish I was never born.
It's not very nice, is it? Your mama abandoning you.
You would never know, Grey, unless it
ever happened to you.
People like that should be in prison.
They shouldn't be They shouldn't be
allowed to have kids if they're just
going to abandon them.
No, there's another Bob account. And
they keep saying to me, "Don't let these
[ __ ] wimpy women win Peter Belly.
Don't let them win."
I don't know who it is.
They shouldn't be allowed. Kids,
you know what my new name is going to
be? Grooy the narcissist destroyer.
cuz I absolutely destroy these narcissists. Oh god,
I need to buy a new phone at some point.
This phone is blocked. There's a phone
that's £300. Then there's a phone for four. £450, but
the £300 one I've had before
when I used to do Uber and it works fine. So,
maybe I'll just get that one. But I do
need to get a phone.
I definitely need to get a [ __ ] madness.
I use a fold, but they block this fold.
No more folds for me, Grezy, lad.
No more [ __ ] folds for me. [ __ ] man,
how they justify them prices. I shall never know.
Don't get me wrong, the folds are good.
They're really good. They never slow down, but £1,800. Really?
£1,800 for a [ __ ] phone? Really, bro?
When I can get a when I can buy a phone for £450
and go on holiday with the rest of their
money, [ __ ] nob brainer, bro. Yeah. [ __ ] stupidness.
It's stupid. It really is stupid.
Need a GoPro. I used to have a Nikon.
I used to have a I used to have a Nikon camera. Yep. I just
so I guess Joseph Ferrar is a goner
in I guess he's a goner, huh? Yeah.
But he it's okay for him to go on Lord
J's channel and he lies all the time. Yeah, bro.
He's just a biased non-lover
just like a lot of people in here.
They're just biased nons lovers. Yeah.
But it's okay for him to go on a lies
chat that lies about everything. Lies
about having six properties.
Lies that he's going to go on Jaden's
door. He doesn't. So, it's okay for him
to lie, but it's not okay for me to
say I was going to go somewhere and then go.
[ __ ] hell, bro. [ __ ] madness.
There is a [ __ ] madness in it, bud.
Yeah, he's [ __ ] he he he's [ __ ]
skint [ __ ] skint flint. Stephen
Albert, I know this. You know this. He's
skinting skin flint. Just like the virgin.
But for some reason they [ __ ] lie. I
don't know why they need to lie. Skint
and a [ __ ] skin flint.
Steven Howard. So you know you've got
you know you've got a skin flint. Right.
So you've got a skin flint. Yeah. They are skintlin.
They're even skint bloody skin flint mate.
Oh look. USA. Izzy
USA Izzy Chinese Izzy messaged me back
straight away saying, "Dear, how are
you? I'm in Blackpool."
So tempting, isn't it, bro?
But so far away.
But I know she'll give me a lovely
[ __ ] you know. Greavesy
[ __ ] She's back in Blackpool for
[ __ ] sake. Is she ever coming back to [ __ ] London?
[ __ ] in hell, man.
Is she ever coming back to London?
[ __ ] black wall. Yeah.
Imagine that. Greasy Peter Belly getting
a nice little [ __ ] by the sea. I'll
do a video on it. Make another porno if
you want, boss.
That'll get the virgin raging, won't it?
That'll get the virgin [ __ ] raging.
You know what do you think of that greasy?
You know, a new porno. Did you like the
other porno, Grezy?
Did you like the other porno?
Yeah. Did you like it?
No. But did you did you like did you
like watching the [ __ ] though?
Did you like watching the [ __ ]
Do you remember that guy that was trying
to say, "Oh,
you're pissing me off.
You're pissing me off. I want to throw
you off the train." Yeah, if you [ __ ]
tried it, he would have got his [ __ ]
head smashed in. See, you love this
content for some reason, Grezy. You seem
to love this content.
Yeah, he would have got [ __ ] up, bro.
He would have got seriously hurt.
But my dick is so big, Grezy, it doesn't
even fit properly in a lot of people's mouth.
Yeah, I'd like to see him try that, bro.
Yeah, I'd like to see it, bro. Really?
I'd like to see that. Yeah.
Yeah. My dick is so big. It doesn't It
doesn't really fit in people's mouth too well, Greasy.
You know, it kind of goes halfway in and
then Yeah, that's how fat it is. It's quite big.
>> It's quite big in my little my little Pekka. Yeah.
Yeah. I should have got that [ __ ]
pregnant, but then you'd have one over.
You can laugh about how you came in them
and they done nothing and how they're [ __ ] now
and how they're [ __ ] now, bro. You know,
no one said anything, did they? On the
train. I told her I said to her, "You're
a loser." How is some fat ugly [ __ ]
with glasses trying to call me a loser?
It's Do you know what it is? It's the
people that are calling you
these things, bro. It's the people that
are calling you these things.
You know, you get people on here trying
to say you're a loser when they're sat
on YouTube don't even leave their
[ __ ] house. Ain't got a pot to piss
in. It's the people that are calling you
losers, bro. They're losers themselves.
Just like the virgin. He's the biggest loser going.
Big virgin loser.
that needs to get [ __ ] laid, you know. But
they'll [ __ ] never lose it though. I was right
option away from it. Mama grieves.
What do you think of that gui taking a
bumpion away from its mama? Mhm. Yep.
Too many entitled [ __ ] in this
country that need to mind their own [ __ ] business.
You know what I mean?
I actually got to be in Blackpool though.
I want her to [ __ ] I want her to lick my ass again.
Greasy. She says that she does this job
now to pay her debts off.
That's cute, isn't it? A
How cute is that?
That's very cute, isn't it? Greasy. Yeah.
Go out and get someone pregnant for a laugh.
That's funny, is it? Stephen H. You
should go out and get someone pregnant
for a laugh.
They wouldn't be so [ __ ] big then,
would they? No. No, mate.
Wouldn't be so [ __ ]
Wouldn't be so cocky then. Yep. No, no.
Got to fill up this glass in a minute.
I'm feeling thirsty again. Oh gosh.
I still need to go to Wales and get that
uh kebab, don't I, Gregy? That I said I
was going to get. I still ain't got
round to doing that. No. Yeah.
So, are you sure you say he was my mommy then? music. You sure? Well,
we do need to go to Thailand.
That's what the plan is. We actually do
need to go. So, yeah.
And the plan is that we're speaking to
one of these numbers and if they agree
to meet then we'll be out this week. If
not then I won't be out for a little while. So yeah.
Um so that's
like I keep saying I need a detox. Bro,
that hangover was bad.
That hangover was [ __ ] bad, bro. The
other day it was bad.
It was really, really bad.
I thought I was going to die, bro. Seriously,
I need to save some money as well. So,
like I say, if this person wants to
meet, then I'll meet them. But if not,
then I'm just going to chill. So, yeah.
No point going out, wasting money,
getting a haircut, wasting time, wasting
money just to hear a friend.
I need to go to Thailand. I will
actually need to go eventually. But all jokes aside,
the flights are like £800. So once we
book the flights, we have to save like
for a couple months and
have some spending money over there and
that. I need to buy a phone first.
That's what I need to do.
Yeah. Go from there.
No, we was talking uh yesterday and the other day. Yeah.
So, I'll invite her out on Saturday just
saying that I'm going to go out even
when I'm not. And then we'll see what she says.
Even the guy from up the road going to
Thailand in two weeks. He said he hates
it here. He's going to Thailand for two months.
Sounds like Antman that it.
But other than that,
we're [ __ ] 24 numbers in
and we haven't even got a single date. So
a single day. So sucks, isn't it? Oh well.
I can't go in two weeks, bro. I've got
stuff to do.
I can't go, bro. I can't go that
quickly. I need to buy a phone and all
sorts. I can't.
Not this [ __ ] I can't.
I can't, bro.
cuz I'm going to book it for like two
months and save some money for two three
months to be able to have spending money.
I can't do it as quick as that.
And I need to get a phone as well cuz
phone's blocked. So I have some things I
need to do first.
Yeah, he going for two months. He's been there before.
Yeah, he's been there before.
He said he loves it there.
He loves it there.
He [ __ ] would.
Yeah, but he's not going to wait, is he?
I know who he is, but he's not going to
wait. Yeah, obviously he's not going to
wait, is he? For me, so
don't worry, we'll be going, bro. We'll be going.
A USA is he
is it normal greasy that I think about
USA is when I'm depressed.
Is that normal grievy?
You know you think of the bad times and stuff.
What do you think? A
yeah, that was very horrible of her.
Yeah, it's really bad, isn't it?
No explanation, no nothing.
just played a victim. Yeah.
I didn't give a [ __ ]
How rude is that?
How [ __ ] rude?
supposed to love me, you know,
do you remember when her dad was trying
to defend her? Uh we
[ __ ] her [ __ ] dad was trying to tell
me I had issues.
Her dad was saying to me, Greavvesy,
that I had issues.
That I had issues, bro. [ __ ] hell.
That's rich, isn't it? Very, very rich.
All right, Captain.
You all right, Captain? Captain C,
you were right. Captain C. Yeah,
I should go and see USA. Izzy.
USA. Izzy. Chinese. Izzy. What else is
Chinese? Izzy. Greasy.
Maybe she misses my Pekka.
What do you think, Grezy?
She's still messaging me back straight away.
Grezy, there was this black guy saying
that uh it's a shame women have got um
these unrealistic expectations because
they're missing out on good guys. I was
watching these videos 11 minutes
long and he said it's a shame because
they're missing out on normal guys
because of their unrealistic standards.
Would you agree with him? Greavvesy,
can I link you the video and you watch
it and tell me what you think? Give me some feedback.
It's only 11 minutes. You can just skip
through bits. I want you to give your
honest opinion on it. Captain, why?
Okay. What if What if I play it on the TV?
Those guys get the Punani.
He makes me He made me die. He says the
guys that are good-looking are the ones
that get the Punani. busy.
They're the ones who get the goods.
They're the ones that get the goodies.
Okay, I'll play it. All right, Captain,
stop mocking me.
Stop mocking me.
Why do you keep mocking me?
You all right, Captain? Sorry about
there. We go.
Where is it?
Where the [ __ ] is it? Hold on.
Oh, here we go.
>> Can you shut the door?
>> Check, change, and get back to you. Black Friday.
>> What's going on, guys? Back at you guys.
Um, for this presentation, guys, I just
want to talk about if women
were so shallow.
If women wasn't shallow,
the dating scene be a lot easier for
guys like us. Dudes who've been written
off, dudes who've been labeled
unattractive. And the thing is, >> yeah,
>> a lot of the dudes that women feel are unattractive
are not even deemed as hitt. It's just
that a lot of these women, especially nowadays,
they just have unrealistic expectations
when it come to men. Um,
if women wasn't so shallow, man, I swear
they would be a they would open
themselves up to some good dudes because
a lot of the dudes that women feel I can
turn it up. I can turn it up,
>> you know, because they have all of these
unrealistic expectations when it come to men. Um,
if women wasn't so shallow, man, I swear
they would meet some really good guys
because it's a lot of decent guys out
here who would make good boyfriends.
They would make good husbands, but women
will not give them a chance because
they're unrealistic and they're just
crazy. They're just they're just stupid and shallow,
you know? They're just overly shallow.
These women nowadays are just overly
shallow. add this to a grieving.
>> You know, this is why, you know, you
have a lot of guys who are just, you
know, they just they just got a big X on
their head. Women have just exed a lot
of dudes out and it's because of the unrealistic standards.
>> Is your right?
>> The unrealistic expectations. Um,
I'm telling you guys like, um, I was
just thinking to myself like if women
wasn't so shallow, they would really
meet some good dudes cuz it's a lot of
good guys out here, you know? But women
just they so caught up in what a man
looks like and what he can provide from
a financial aspect to where they don't
care about who the man is. You know,
they don't care about is this dude a
decent person? Does this dude have
morals? You know, would this dude, you
know, would this dude be a good example,
you know, for children? Would he be a
good would he be a good husband?
You know, women don't think about these
things, man. And it's because they're
just unrealistic and just super shallow. Um,
I'm telling you guys, um,
>> is he right, Greg Zy?
>> I'm just telling you guys, like
these women, man, I'm telling you, they
the standards are just unrealistic, man.
And you know, you got a lot of dudes who
just been totally disqualified from the
dating arena all because they don't meet certain standards.
I mean, it's sad, man. I mean, this this
just doesn't make any sense.
>> I wish women wasn't so shallow because I
feel like if women wasn't so shallow,
a lot of dudes who not able to get a
shot would be able to get a shot
due to the shallow nature of women. You
got a lot of dudes who will never have a
shot at having a girlfriend, having a
family, nothing. Because these women
today are just overly shallow.
They're overly shallow. And it's like as
a man, it it's gotten to a point where
you got to be on a certain level,
you know, to even get play from females.
It's like if you don't have celebrity
status, if you don't have big money, and
I'm not talking about nine-to-five
money, I'm talking about CEO money. If
you're not uh looking like one of these
runway model dudes, it's over for you.
When it come to females, like I, you
know, I I just think to myself like if
women wasn't so shallow, man, a lot of
us that's in these positions wouldn't be
in this position. We wouldn't be going
through what we going through if these
women wasn't so shallow. A lot of us are suffering
because these women have these
unrealistic standards when it come to guys.
I mean, it's ridiculous, man. Like, it's
like women, they want a man to be dag on near perfect,
you know? And it's like and and and you
know the crazy here's the kicker. This
is where the shallowess gets so crazy. A
dude could be a bad dude, but if he
looks good, nothing else matters. A guy
could really be a horrible person, but
if the woman is attracted to him, it
doesn't matter if he's a horrible
person. You know, I mean, Jeremy Meeks
is a perfect example. Like if you look
really good at the women, it doesn't
matter if you're a terrible person or not.
>> They gonna still give you the the the
punani. They gonna still bust it open
for you. But I just think to myself,
>> if women was supposed
out here suffering with no [ __ ]
>> you wouldn't have dudes out here who 30
something, 40 something years old with no family.
That's why I say the shallowess nowadays
is just on steroids, man. It is on
steroids. And as
>> Yeah. Well, you want you get the point
anyways. You get the point.
Yeah, you get the point.
So, you actually agree with him, Greavesy.
You actually agree? Yeah. Heat.
Yeah. And even Tik Tockers are [ __ ]
You can see it with me in it, Grezy. You
can see it with me, huh?
Yeah. You can see it with me cuz what
what are you going by? Like my
experiences or what?
Well, you going by my experiences, Grezy. Yeah.
Yeah. It literally has to be celebrity status.
But saying that though, even these big
Tik Tockers get rejected.
Even that Ed Matthews, I was watching
him. He gets rejected,
you know, and he's [ __ ] he's like
he's got loads of followers like he's
famous and [ __ ] and even he gets
rejected. So, what chance does a normal
guy have? None. So,
what do you mean I don't do myself any
favors with what?
In regards to what? Huitt.
Don't do myself any favors.
What with like women I met? Well, USA
[ __ ] me over, Beezy. She actually did
[ __ ] me over. What did you want me to
do? She was trying to bully me and I
stood up for myself.
Yep. I stood up for myself.
That [ __ ] time. I stood up for
myself, you know.
I wasn't going to take her abuse, you know. Yep.
Was I supposed to take it or something? Grievesy.
H. Well, I supposed to take the abuse. [ __ ] off.
Gosh. Gosh darn it. Gosh.
[ __ ] Franklin. I need a [ __ ] escort. [ __ ] him.
I need a bloody escort.
[ __ ] that car. He can wait. I [ __ ]
need one more than him.
I don't do myself any favors.
You're a funny [ __ ]
There must be a time where you remember.
I've not done myself any favors, Greg.
There's got to be a time you remember.
There's got to be.
Unless you're making it up. Wait for it. Lovely. Lovely piss. All right.
You sure can't.
Good. [ __ ] off, Jay.
Right. [ __ ] you. I just saw you
subscribe to my channel and here's what
I'm going to say to you. Yeah. Unless
you want to talk about
something to do with you. One second. Oops.
Something to do with
you sucking this right here. You can
[ __ ] off. Not interested.
Oh, I love that. I thought that was funny.
No, I'm not okay. I'm very upset.
Oh, I got
No, I'm not okay. I'm really sad actually
because it it will not it will be April
soon. And you know what what when what
April is, don't you agree with Zy Jane,
Steven Howard, even the skin version of
the Out London Beds?
You know, we all know we all we all know
what April is, don't we, Greezy? What
month that that um that that means Oh.
It's the month I met my mama Jane if you
didn't know. Oh, I'm under my little
blankie. I'm under my little blankie
because my bedding is not dry. My bed my gosh. Oh gosh.
Gosh, my bedding is not dry. My bedding
is not dry. Greasy.
So, I've had to use the electric blankie for today. The blankie.
Is that all right with you?
Ah, I miss my mama. Jane,
isn't my mommy so beautiful?
Do you like my mama,
Jane? That's my mama.
No, it's not ridiculous. It's actually really true.
I'm under my blankie cuz my dry. It's
not ridiculous. This is the truth. Our
bedding is not dry. So, I'm under my blanket.
I'm under my little blankie.
Yep. I'm under my blankie.
It's not ridiculous. It's the truth.
Under my little blankie.
You should be drying tomorrow.
That's my mama. Jane. It's not
ridiculous. It's the truth.
Why is he ridiculous?
That's my mother.
She abandoned me three years ago. You
must know. You must know the truth.
Oh, why does Timmy keep uploading
videos? Squeezy. I just refreshed his
channel and he's just uploaded another video.
He gambles every day that Timmy don't he
said that he had a free piss up. I can't
believe this Timmy [ __ ] drinks every
day. That's mad.
That is mad.
Who who who's a dude that can't get laid?
No, that's my mama in the photo in the photo.
No, that's my mama in the photo. Who
can't get laid?
What? Timothy Elrajano.
What about Timothy Elijano? Huh?
That's not a dude. That's my mama. You [ __ ]
Give me a free outrage.
You sucked a lot of willies lately,
Jane. Do you remember when you said you
wanted to suck my willie? You taught.
You well taught.
You [ __ ] Welsh Tart.
Yeah, I saw it.
I can't believe he goes I I can't
believe he drinks every day. How does he
afford it? I guess he [ __ ] um
I guess he just uh
um just drinks cans in it, I'm guessing.
It's all right in the summer. You can go
out a couple of times a week in the
summer, but in the winter really? Nah.
Can't do that. Me, bro.
Side job. He doesn't have a [ __ ] job.
He's never worked in his life.
He don't have a side job, bro. He's [ __ ] skin.
Jimmy's [ __ ] skint, mate.
No, bro. Timmy's [ __ ] skint.
You don't have a side job.
Cut to class.
Nah, you skint mate. Just like L J
in a s in the summer. I guess you could
go out on like a Wednesday. Yeah,
in the summer you could probably go out
like a Wednesday, Saturday. Yeah, you
can go out a couple of times. I used to
when I had loads of money in the summer,
I was out all the time, bro. Spending
£700 on days out and [ __ ] Yeah,
you do all sorts of mad [ __ ] bro.
Especially in the summer is [ __ ] hot.
I used to all the time, bro, in the summer. Yeah,
I spent 700 pound on a night out before Janie kins. Yeah.
It's all right, man.
Yeah, I went out last week, Jane. I had
a really bad hangover.
I spent 700
in the past few weeks I've gone out I've spent 300s
300 300 300
cuz I always get an escort at the end of
the night. Well, last week last week I
spent 100 with the food, but that was
with food so it wasn't that bad. £100 I spent. Yeah.
What do you mean? Why? Because I was [ __ ] horny.
If I If I stayed in the past two months,
I would have been [ __ ] loaded.
I would be loaded, bro.
But I'm not drinking for a bit now anyways, Jane. Nope. Nip n
what? How much do you spend on a night
out? £100 for a night out is not a lot. D.
It's normally about £80 when I go out drinking,
but I've spent 500s. I spent 500 not so long ago.
Don't ask me how I bloody do it, but it it happens. It's um
You think £100 for a night out is a lot?
Yeah. I mean, if you stick to Guinness, you won't.
If you stick to Guinness, you won't. But
if you drink rum, you will because they
water down the rum. But if you're if you
stick to Guinness, then yeah,
it's probably about 60 70,
maybe less. depends what you're drinking
because they can't water down Guinness.
They can water down rum. So when you
drink rum, you just get it down you
quickly because it they water it.
Whereas if you drink beer, Yeah. you
It's probably about 60 70 you'd spend. Yeah.
So I spent 100 with food last week, so
it wasn't too bad. £100 with food. Yeah.
You just need to stay away from the
spirits cuz they water it down.
I I told you I tell you what I drunk
last week. I drunk Guinness and then I
had four cocktails and that was it. That
was the end.
Two of the cocktails was 16. Then it was 32.
But that was it. That was the end. There
was no drinking more after that, bro. I
was [ __ ] Yeah, I had two Guinnesses.
No, I had two Guinnesses, one Corona,
and four cocktails. Yeah,
that was the end.
It was 32 for two cocktails after the
happy hour, but it was the end, bro. You
couldn't drink any more than that. So,
yeah, about 100 with the food. So yeah,
>> you don't need to drink before you go
out. All you do is drink Guinness. All
you do is stick to Guinness. Cuz if if
Guinness is a pound a pint, you're not
going to be having more than five Guinnesses.
Yep. It was in Liverpool Street.
Yep. The h the happy hour ended,
but the cocktails were full of rum and
it wasn't watered down. It was like Ray
and Nephew and [ __ ]
Yeah, cuz it was it was it it it's happy
hour until 8.
I know. I've had I've had cocktails in Wales.
I had a Florida cocktail in Wales.
It's 2 for 16 until 8:00 and then it
goes to 32. But either way, you have two
of them um cocktails. You're not
drinking anymore after that anyways. So,
I don't think it was too bad.
And it's not £10, it's actually 14. It's
like 134 in Wales cuz I know cuz I've
been there. I had cocktails there.
Yeah, but I still spent I still spent
£100 with the food. So,
and I had a good night for £100 with the
food, so I didn't mind
cuz I knew it'd be the last. Yeah,
but if we're not talking cocktails and
we're drinking Guinness, we're talking
Guinnesses. Yeah. Okay. It might be £8
for a pint of Guinness, but like I said,
you're not having more than what? Six.
I need to go to Wales, Jane. I need to
get the chicken don kebab. You can't
There's a chicken don kebab in Wales and
they don't have it in London. So, I'll
probably be going there um very soon.
I'll probably just pop on the train and
just go to Wales and have some chicken
ticker. Don't know. Yeah.
I'm going to get a chicken ticker on a
kebab. It's my favorite. They don't have it here,
but they have it in Wales.
But I don't really like it cuz when you
go to Wales, they've all got blood. They
all say they've got bloody boyfriends.
Jane, all of these women, they say
they've got bloody boyfriends.
That's what they say. They've all got
bloody boyfriends. And I've bloody had
enough of it.
I've had a bloody enough of it.
We all got bloody boyfriends.
I've had a bastard enough of it.
No, they're not. They're all stuck up
and there's also loads of fights that
happen as well
last time I was there. So yeah. Yeah. [ __ ] hell.
There was a fight with a bouncer and um
some drunk guy. I've got the video still.
It was that square bit in Cardiff by the Five Guys.
You know where the Five Guys is in Cardiff?
Uh, it's called something square. Yeah.
Yeah, I might go to Wales next week.
Yeah. If you if you want to join, Jane,
would would you want to join?
Do you want to join me?
No, I'm joking. I would never meet you.
I'm probably going to go to Wales and
I'm going to go to Bristol.
Nah, there's no maybe. You're full of
[ __ ] You never meet.
You just talk a big game on the phone,
but you never actually meet.
Nah, you never got to meet. You're just
a troll. I wouldn't meet you anyways,
mate. You put all my business on YouTube.
You would never meet. You would never meet ever.
You're full of [ __ ]
You'll never meet ever.
You do remember that time when when
lockdown was going on and I was in
Bristol and you said that you was going
to pick me up.
You're so full of [ __ ] Really? Really?
You're going to meet? Really? And we
will never meet, mate.
All you do is troll with Mark. It's so obvious. Yeah,
the same as Chase. He doesn't meet you
when you go to card. If he doesn't meet
you, if I ever see that guy, bro, I'm
going to knock him out, bro. I swear to God.
If I ever see that chase, I will [ __ ]
uppercut the [ __ ] bro. Straight up his
nose. If I ever see that [ __ ] ever again,
if I ever see that [ __ ] Sorry, not ever
again. If I ever see that [ __ ] Yeah.
Why don't you meet me anyways, Jane?
Huh? Why don't you meet?
Why don't you come and meet me if I go
to Wales? Why don't you come? Huh?
Let's arrange it.
You owe me an apology.
You owe me an apology anyways.
Why don't you come out with me? It'll be
easier to get in with two people
because you need to you need to say
sorry for what you and other women have
done to me.
You know, you need to apologize.
You need to bow down to the king, which is me. Yeah.
So, are you going to come out or not?
So, I'm going to go next Saturday. You
going to come out or not? What?
Nope. I won't put anything on YouTube.
Nothing at all. No videos, no nothing.
Maybe just a chicken ticker video for um
Grezy. I won't put anything on YouTube. No, not me. So yeah.
Yeah, them calls were really nice. I
can't believe you said you was going to
suck my willie.
Oh my god.
You're crazy. You are.
You said that you was going to suck my bell end. That's crazy.
You did say that.
You did say that you was going to suck my willie.
Yeah, you did.
Yeah, that's what you said.
Oh, I haven't had a [ __ ] for ages, Jane. Nope.
Not for a while.
My friend used to come around and give
me a [ __ ] but I stopped talking to her.
I was saying to Grey that I've got a
really big dick, so it doesn't really
like fit in people's mouth,
you know? It doesn't fit in people's
mouth um so much. Yeah.
It doesn't fit into people's mouths.
like all the way only like half. I don't know why. Yeah,
you know how it be. I need to check my
little emails. One second. Oh, it's on this b. Oh gosh. Yeah. Heat. Yeah, Jane. So, yeah.
I'm not sure. I don't speak to him. He's
a He's a weirdo.
I don't speak to that weirdo. Why? That's the heat. Yeah. No, you
No, he's weird.
I don't speak to him anymore cuz he's
weird. He's just a weird fella. Oh gosh. Yeah.
Yeah. I saw Slug's video. Scooby. Yep.
Let's meet up next week, Jane,
and go live on YouTube and laugh at everyone. Oh gosh.
Why don't let's meet up next week and go live. Jane,
I'm never going to forgive you, Jane. Never.
You have to apologize on behalf of you
and every single woman. And then you
need to suck my willie.
And if you don't do that, I can't forgive you.
USA needs to do it as well. Yep.
You just need to say sorry
for all of the trolling and the [ __ ] Yep.
for all of the bollocks.
Why are you saying ew? Sucking Willy's
is not ew. It's absolutely lovely.
It's absolutely ace.
Why is it you?
Why is it you? It's It's lovely.
I've had lots of [ __ ] in my time,
Jane, and I think they're absolutely lush.
I don't think they're here at all. Yeah,
we could go gambling as well, Jane. Yep.
Who her? That's my mama.
Yep. I met her 3 years ago, but in April
will be 3 years.
That's my mama.
Yep. We hooked up together.
She let me suck on her boobies as well.
Jane, I haven't been the same ever since
she abandoned me, to be honest.
I've never been the same since.
Yep. It's been quite sad. Been quite nasty.
She abandoned me
again. She left me and abandoned me.
She left me all alone.
It's horrible, isn't it?
What do you mean? did something very wrong.
No, she did abandon me.
She left me
and went back to the United States.
She did abandon me.
Makes me cry thinking about it.
No, it did actually happen.
She abandoned me.
She's a narcissist.
She is a horrible little narcissist
who's got mental problems. Yep.
Just like you, Jamie.
So, are we meeting next week or what?
Are you going to be a let down?
We need to we need to show LJ and show
LT who's boss.
She had really nice boobies. Jane,
I got lots of milk and vitamins from them. Yep.
Taking a baby away from its mama.
Yep. She had really milky boobies. Shane.
That's my mama. Yeah.
So, what do you want to do?
You coming out or what? Jaden Edcom.
Oh, she's in a relationship. That's why.
No wonder she's blocked me. Okay,
I was speaking to this person in America.
None of these women are different.
They're all the bloody same.
Jay, they're all the bloody same. These women
I've had off.
[ __ ] off, Jane.
I'm going to have to block you now.
You're trolling. I'm going to have to block you.
If you're not willing to suck, dick, I'm not interested. Simple. That's that.
I don't even know why you cover my [ __ ]
You're just a troll.
That's who you are. You're just a [ __ ] troll.
You shouldn't you shouldn't keep winding
me up cuz I'll just come on your door.
You don't know what I'm like. I'll just
come on your [ __ ] door, mate. Do your
[ __ ] windows in.
I'm not ever going to forgive you until you apologize
and suck my dick.
That's the only time.
So, we'll never be friends.
We'll never be mates until that happens. So,
same as USA is he
needs to apologize
and suck dick.
That's what she needs to do.
I would do it though. saying,
"Who's that bloody virgin ploner?"
But I would do it.
You silly [ __ ] Don't get sloppy with
me, you silly [ __ ] Ah. Yep.
Yeah. You can dare me to
need to suck Willie.
Do you like sucking Willie, Jane? Huh?
My mate lives in Bristol. So,
yeah, my mate lives in Bristol. Jane
All right, Jane. Is Bristol Is Bristol near London?
Would you say it's near London? Bristol kind of
Yeah. So it's near London though. Yep.
Nothing's going on in my world. I still
can't get a jet. I still can't get a
date. I still can't get sex. And it's
really sad. So, I'm off to Thailand, Jane.
Yeah, I'm off to Thailand.
Yeah. What's good about Bristol? It's
the outskirts of London. Jane Yep. No,
I want it to be just me and you. I like
it that way.
I like it that way.
Go to bed in a minute.
I'm going to go to bed now. All right.
See you later.