Just checking to see if it's the same
people. You know what I'm like.
Just wanting to see if it's the same
people in your brain. Got a lie. Oh, still day.
You have a headache to be honest.
You want to see if it's the same people.
Can't get off it.
Hopefully not. I want to be talking to myself.
I like I like talking to myself. I do it
a lot. I don't like people coming on my live stream, you know,
cuz all of these people have got jobs.
They've got lives. So they say that. Yeah.
So hopefully I'll rejoin and just be me
talking to myself.
That would be
talking to yourself, you know. Oh, six
people already. I hope no one types.
I hope no one types. I'll be like, you
still on [ __ ] YouTube know that. You
know what I'm like, mate. Yeah,
I keep getting [ __ ] attacked by a
[ __ ] cat. Every time I go to that
house, he keeps [ __ ] mirroring me. He
wouldn't leave me alone. Cat little
puppy cat. It's ginger.
They catch ginger.
[ __ ] need some pills.
Bagging little copycat.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] it's Ginger.
I named it. I've named the cat a name.
Not going to tell you what the name is,
but I've named it.
Yeah, it keeps like [ __ ] hitting me
with it. Oh,
I said [ __ ] off. Leave me alone, you little copycat. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, I say leave me alone, you little copycat.
Always hating cats, me dogs. I like
cats. They copy each other.
They got mind of their own. Little cat. Little copycat.
The little copycat. Copycat.
Every time I go to the house, the
[ __ ] cat goes at me. [ __ ] weird.
Leave me alone, you stupid cat. I don't
find sh attractive. I'm not a copycat.
I'm not I'm not insecure about my
sexuality. I don't need to copy people.
It's never been in It's never been in me
to to want to do that.
So leave me alone, you stupid cat.
Yeah, don't leave me alone, bro. Every
time I go to the [ __ ] house, I'm
going to stop going there. I don't even
know why she has a bloody cat. It's [ __ ] ginger.
He's giving me the evils as well. All
cuz I don't find attractive because I've
got a copycat.
They won't leave me alone as soon as I
go in the [ __ ] house. Leave me the
[ __ ] alone, stupid cat.
[ __ ] stupid eyes. It's Ginger.
I'm not sure if it's a [ __ ] boy or a
girl to be honest.
I'm not sure.
Is it a boy or a girl? I guess I not sure. Wait. Yeah.
By the way, I'm changing my number. So,
uh, David Thompson, you won't come to
stalk me anymore.
My WhatsApp number is delivered to my
other number. I'm going to change my
other number to be honest.
Leave me alone, you fat stalker.
Leave me alone. Stop taking your failies
out of me just cuz you're fat and ugly
and depressed. Leave me alone, you fat, ugly stalker.
Ronald P was right about you B.
Ronald [ __ ] P was right about you. It was
You fat loser.
Yeah, it's just a call. My WhatsApp
number is different, but I'm going to
change my number anyways. Yeah, loser got
a [ __ ] life. I ain't got no wife. I
ain't got no nothing. You're full of [ __ ] mate,
to sit under your job doing what you do
every bloody day. Clear as day to anyone
that's not disabled, you got nothing.
Because people people know these things,
you know? [ __ ] got these stupid
bloody things calling me and messaging
me. Leave me alone.
You know, it's not my fault I'm better
looking than you and I'm younger than
you. Leave me the [ __ ] alone.
Taking out your failures on me because
Oh, what is it? You see someone that's
younger and better looking than you. Oh,
we'll take our failures out on him. No,
leave me alone. Let's take out on the
guy that's better looking and younger
because they've got a chance in life.
[ __ ] me. You know that's not fair
though, is it? Not bloody welfare.
No, but seriously, you need to stop
taking out your life failures on other
people. Not my fault. You're fat and
ugly and you ain't got a life.
Stalker. [ __ ] stalking bastard.
Little low life.
Like I say, this is Reddit moderators all over.
Some people in this community, sad.
Yeah, bro. No one cares about you.
You're a keyboard warrior. Shut up. You
can't join a panel. Shut up. You're boring.
You're boring, mister. Hiding behind a
100 different accounts that can't join a
panel. Well, you're boring. Just Just
stop it now. Like I said, come back to
me when you've got the balls to join the panel.
>> Then we can talk about it. Not a
problem. Until then, just stop embarrassing yourself.
Just just stop embarrassing yourself.
You must be the only You
maybe you must be one of the only people
that can hide behind 100 accounts but
scared to join a panel. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, you said this all before. It's boring.
Yeah, no one cares. You can't join a
panel. So, no, no, no one cares what you
say. You need better in you need better um triggering tactics.
[ __ ] hell. Getting old, mate. It's
boring now. Like I said, when you can
join a panel and stop repeating
yourself, come back to me.
But you can't.
That's all you've got
or haven't tasted
behind 101 different accounts but scared
to join a panel. Imagine that. E
sad. Really, really sad. Loser.
What what do you actually have in your
life right when you have to hide behind
101 accounts trying to troll on YouTube?
Nothing. You literally have nothing. And
you're older than me as well. That's
another thing. The funny thing is with
these people is they're actually older
than me. I'm 28. And I would say a lot
of these people are probably double my
age, sat on YouTube, no money, no life,
don't even leave their house. Sad.
Really, really, really, really is sad.
you know, you you actually pity these people.
But anyways, back to what I was saying.
Um, I'll be changing my number anyways,
so it's not a problem at all. So, yeah.
Proper proper stalkers on this
community, is it? [ __ ] hell. Proper
proper stalkers. It's not my fault I'm
younger and better looking than you. Jesus Christ. [ __ ] me.
Dusty Show is one sad [ __ ]
in his 30s, 40s, ain't got no life but
trolling behind fake accounts. What a loser.
And that's why you go at me as well when
I say these things cuz I hit a nerve.
Cuz everything I say, everything I say
about you is the truth. That's why it
hit a That's why it hits a nerve. That's
why you start writing stuff because you
know what I'm saying is the truth. And
I'll say it to you on panel as well.
Yeah, I'll always be alone. Bro, just
stop it. Everyone's seen me with more
women than you've had hot dinners. Mate,
you are alone in your 40s. Lonely man on
YouTube behind 100 accounts trolling
because you ain't got nothing. Just just
just look at what Okay. Okay. Right.
Let's just take a step back and look at
what you people do every day on YouTube.
Yeah. hiding behind the 101 different
accounts, trolling simply because you
have nothing. That's just look at what
you people do. You know, your YouTube
activity gives you away. Sad, lonely,
bitter old virgin men. It's [ __ ]
obvious. You, Jamie Thompson, Red Star,
this is all you have because you're
simply fat and ugly. It's It's not even
me trying to [ __ ] be rude. It's the
truth. Cuz if he wasn't any of these
things, you'd get off of YouTube and you
would get a [ __ ] life. But you can't
even take one day off of YouTube. So
it's obvious what I'm saying about you
is the truth. No job, no life, no money, fat, middle-aged.
It's the truth. What I say about you
people on here, that's why you don't
like it. I hit a nerve because it's the
truth. You what you say about me is not
the truth. It's just self-projecting and
repeating. So, I don't really give a
[ __ ] what you write because it's just self projecting.
We all know right now that if you people
come on panel,
you'd all be fat and ugly. So, I mean,
that's why you won't join. You can't
talk. So, just, you know, same thing really,
bro. You people are fat and ugly. It
would not take much for people to be
better looking than you.
Did I say that I'm good-look? I said I'm
better looking than you. I have I've had
more women than you have. I've had sex
more times than you have. You still a
virgin. You red star virgin boy. Yeah.
All virgins. Absolute virgins. It's like
when you [ __ ] you know when you when
you when you see them people on a
scooter them noobs them [ __ ] what
they called e scooters. You're like you
absolute virgins. that that's what you
say. Yeah, you've said this before.
You're going to stop repeating yourself.
Women hate you as well. That's why
you're single and you're virgin again.
Stop taking out your failures on me.
Stop taking your failures out of me, lad.
Yeah, my family hate me. Yeah. Okay.
You've said all of this before. Stop
repeating yourself. It's not going to
change the fact that women hate you and
the fact that your family hate you. You
keep self projecting is not going to
make your life any better, lad. So, it's pointless.
Yeah. I mean, I was at my sisters
yesterday. I see my sister all the time.
See my mom all the time. Okay, bro. My
family hate me. Congratulations. You
keep telling yourself that. That's not
going to change the fact that you're a
virgin and your family hate you. You can
say it a million times. It's not going
to change Dusty Showbiz's reality. The
loser on YouTube behind 101 accounts
being a little keyboard warrior. That's
not going to change that, bro. So, you
can say whatever you want. Women Women
have been hating you. At least I can say
I've actually pulled women and I've
actually had sex. Unlike you, some
middle-aged little virgin loser, single,
single behind little YouTube accounts.
You know what I'm saying about you is
the truth as well. There's nothing you can say.
So just stop. Like it's the truth. Women
hate you. You're single. You've never
been inside a woman. Just like Red Star.
Just like Virgin Boy. You all absolute virgins.
So bro, I don't give a [ __ ] Honestly, I don't care.
Behind 101 accounts cuz you've got
nothing. Got nothing but YouTube. Like I
said, bro. Like I said, you're one of
these little bully victims that every
time you try to leave your house, you
get slapped up for being so ugly. That's
why you spend all your life on YouTube.
I've got 20 left to last me a month.
What the [ __ ] Self projecting. Talking
about yourself again. Yeah, bro. I've
got 20 to last me a month.
Oh, you called me out. Yeah, I got 20
pound. Yeah, exactly.
Oh, bro, literally the last time I went
out, I spent too much of your benefit
money. Stop embarrassing yourself. It's
really, really embarrassing now, bro. Stop it.
£20. You must think we've all got your
life, don't we? You must think that
everyone's on £300 a month like Dusty
Show is the little YouTube virgin. You
must actually think that's you, bro. You
must actually think that is you.
You think everyone's got your 300 pound
a month virgin life on YouTube? [ __ ] it.
You can't take me serious, bro. You
can't even join a panel. You're that
scared of joining a panel and you're
telling me that you can't take me
serious. Bro, I literally told you that
you will never tell me where you are
because you know what's good for you.
And you're trying to tell me that you
can't take me serious. Bro, I've got
more money than you would ever have.
Believe that boy.
You can't take me serious. Yet you're
scared to join a panel and say where you
are. Please stop it. It's embarrassing
now, bro. You can't even join a panel.
You virgin. You're that scared to join a
panel and you're trying to tell me that
you can't [ __ ] If I come across you,
you bro, you're a keyboard warrior. Like
I said to you the other day, I will
happily come and slap you up today. And
every single time I tell you about this,
virgin boy. And women hate you, you ugly
bastard. You ugly virgin. At least I've
been inside women. Unlike you, virgin.
You can't even talk to a woman. You
little YouTube [ __ ] keyboard warrior
virgin. You can't even beat me cuz you
know I smack your teeth down your
throat. That's why you keep saying, "Oh,
if I come across you in my travels, bro,
I would happily come and smack your
teeth down your throat." 100% today.
Triggered. See, this is what I mean,
bro. You're you're a little virgin.
You're just a little YouTube virgin. A
repeating little [ __ ] That's what
you are, bro. You're a repeating little
[ __ ] little bully victim virgin. Get
on my level, bro. You're a spasticated
little [ __ ] little virgin. Just like
Red Star. Just like Virgin Boy.
Repeating little autistic bastard.
Virgin. That's what you are, bro.
You skint [ __ ] little autistic and
I'm saying this to you now and I'll meet
you anywhere today, bro. Autistic little
skint [ __ ] that women hate. That's why
you're still a virgin. And I'm wanting
to say it to your face. This is what I'm saying, bro.
You know what I mean, bro?
So that's that. Stop repeating yourself,
man. It's boring.
So yeah, stop repeating.
It's rigged. Have you got anything
original, bro? Come on. [ __ ] boring.
Have a timeout.
[ __ ] boring as [ __ ] man.
These people don't want to get me in the
[ __ ] mood, so I swear to God. Question people.
Please allow it, bro. Just just leave
it. Please just leave it.
Just please leave it, bro.
Please just leave it, man.
Please, bro. Swear these people are
trying to bait me. I swear to God, bro.
Just woke up today just chilling, bro.
And these people are trying to bait me.
Bait me. Bait me. Bait me. Bait me. Bait
me. Bait me. Bait me, bro. Baiting me.
Baiting me. Baiting me. Baiting me.
Baiting me, bro.
What I'm trying to say.
If I react, no one's going to like it.
Yeah, there's a sand.
If I start something, bro, I will finish
it, bro. Trust me, I'm not in a mood.
So, just leave it, bro. Allow it. This
has been all I Oh, supposed to go
dentist. I didn't wake up. One sec.
Just stop baiting me, bro. Please just
leave me alone. What?
Repeating regurgitated [ __ ] over and
over and over and over and over again.
just chilling, bro. And people I don't
know why people are just
stop it. Just allow it, man. You know, [ __ ] sake.
yeah, they're all stalkers.
They're all stalking little losers on
here, bro. So, everyone knows that, man.
That's their life, isn't it? Sad little
low life people.
Did you just realize that?
Yeah, they're all stalkers, bro. I told
you this. They're all fat, ugly little
low lives. They ain't got a life.
So what, bro? We all know about them.
Fat, ugly life losers that come on here
and project. And I rattle them every
time I say this stuff because it's the
truth. They're fat, ugly little low
lives coming on here creating negativity
every day because they've been bullied
their whole life. That's what they do on
here, bro. They wait us.
Sorry, I'm just talking to someone.
They need to make up their mind, bro.
Honestly, which one is it? [ __ ] hell.
Heads or tails? Damn.
You don't want me to go on this phone
today, bro. Trust me. So, just leave me.
Just stop trying to wind people up. You
know, life is, you know, hard enough and
stuff. And you're trying, you've been
trying to bait me since since I woke up
this morning, you know, since I've woke
up this bloody morning, you know. It was
raining. I didn't go to the dentist and
stuff. No, not really. I'm not going to
get into it. But, bro, I'm just
chilling. Like, don't
try to bait someone. Like, I'm just
like, you know what I'm saying? Life is
hard enough because if I get on that
phone, you're not going to like it. So,
just stop it and just leave people
alone. And trust me, I will finish it,
bro. You know what I'm trying to say?
You know, I'll just start on every
[ __ ] [ __ ] and it's not and and I
don't want to do that, bro. I don't know
what what it is. You know,
stop trying to bait people. It's [ __ ]
mad. I need to change my number as well.
It's nothing to do with YouTube. I need
to change my number as well. That's
another thing because of these stalkers on YouTube. Yeah, bro.
Sad little bastards on there, bro. But
isn't anything to do with people on
YouTube, but I need to change my number.
So yeah, you need to you need to figure
out like are you heads or you tails?
Which one is it? Because you can't keep
switching like this. You know what I'm
trying to say?
That's basically what we need. We need
to know like you heads tails which one
and stick to it because yeah
it's always drama and drama and drama
and drama and drama.
I'm not trying to sound tough.
I'm not trying to sound tough at all. I
just want people to [ __ ] leave me
alone to be honest.
Do you think you're tough being a
keyboard warrior every day on YouTube
stalking people thinking that you're
good at trolling? Because it's [ __ ]
sad to be honest.
I mean, do you people think that you're
bullying people when you're just coming
on here every day self- projecting
when you're just talking about yourselves?
Like, do do you actually think that
you're bullying people when you're just
self- projecting every day?
That's my question, too. But no, I I I
don't sound tough and I'm not trying to sound tough.
Autistic community, that's what it is.
This is an autistic community. So
means we need words anyways.
It's not even anything to do with anyone
on YouTube anyways. So yeah.
That's that, isn't it?
It's just constant constant drama when
people are bored
every single time. It's constant drama
when people are bored. And I can't be
dealing with it, bro. Why do people want
such like a drama life? Like, don't
people just want like an easy life with
no drama? I thought that would be the
way to be honest.
It would just start making me bring up
stuff from a long long long long time ago
cuz obviously I'm a grown man now. So,
you know, it' be a different [ __ ]
story. People are very hesitant to start
with people that are grown men because
we all know that people, you know, pick
their targets very carefully. So, so
I think you lot are a bunch of [ __ ]
nerds. You know what I get with this
community? You're all like Well, you
like most of you, you're just [ __ ] nerds.
Just nerds with no life to be honest. I
think that's I don't think that's
hating. Like I've seen like
some of the comments like alerted us.
They're proper proper nerds on here.
I don't know what I would say, bro. [ __ ]
me. Yeah, I'd actually say most of the
people in this community are [ __ ] virgins.
Absolute virgins. I'm not even joking.
You're never ever going to say anything
to anyone's face. So, I don't know why
you just don't leave people alone. I
don't understand it. Again, it's nothing
to do with people on YouTube. Why?
Cuz I can't keep doing this back and
forth back up back and forth [ __ ] You
know what I mean? You can make up your
mind, you know?
I'm not involved. I don't want to be
involved of a of a drama life where
people want drama cuz they're bored,
you know? I mean, [ __ ] [ __ ] that, you Madness, bro.
They're going to try and [ __ ] you
know, blackmail people and [ __ ] It's a
madness. It's actually a madness.
Absolute madness, bro.
It's just the same old boring,
repetitive, regurgitated [ __ ] Your
heads or tails, which one is it? You
know what I'm saying?
Make more [ __ ] sense. Whatever, man. Oh yeah.
Been all day, bro. This ass Yeah.
Sorry about that. Lord knows. So yeah.
So anyways, when are you people going to
get off YouTube and get a life?
That's all I need to ask you.
Going to get off YouTube and get yourselves alive.
We stop selfjecting.
Come on, man. It's getting old now.
Dusty showers, when you going to get off
of YouTube and get a life, you need one.
Desperately, desperately need one.
Desperately need one. Yes. So yeah,
you need to make up your [ __ ] mind, bro. Basically,
say sorry to YouTube. Is that all you
got, bro? Like same, repeat, and [ __ ]
You need to come up with some better
comebacks. Then I could actually laugh
at it. You need to think of some new
things to say. So yeah,
that's starting it basically.
What a fear a minute. See what's
let me know anyways
excuses over and over and over again. Yes.
free time as well, bro. Yeah. Stop basically. >> Yeah.
Shame people weren't this way when they
were taking up your money. Is it? Ah,
it's a shame people didn't feel that
same way when they were taking all your
money, isn't it? Strange.
Keep me out of your shitty drama, please.
You might be bored with your lives and
need drama, want drama. That's on you,
bro. Do not involve me [ __ ] with your
[ __ ] you know. [ __ ] that.
every [ __ ] month. It is every [ __ ]
month or every 3 weeks. It's some
[ __ ] that comes out of nowhere. It's
always some bollocks, some [ __ ]
[ __ ] make up your [ __ ] mind.
You know what I'm saying?
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] every [ __ ] time, you know.
Trust me, bro.
Madness. I'm [ __ ] mad.
Oh, thought that was a message from
Yeah. Anyways, I'll be back. Right.