Mr. Bloody got back to [ __ ]
matey. That's what it [ __ ] needs to do. [ __ ] hell. knee back.
I need to get a [ __ ] new phone, man.
I was looking.
[ __ ] out of stock. Out of stock. Out
of stock. Hurry up. We need you back in
stock, mate. That's what we [ __ ] need.
We need you back in stock [snorts]
and a Look,
do you feel?
Yeah, bro. There's this phone. It's It's
[ __ ] £460. I want to buy it, but it's
not in stock. And there's another one
that's £500, so I might buy that one.
Cuz obviously my phone's blocked. So I
need to buy a phony, don't I? Yes.
Pixel 10. How much was that?
I need like a decent Samsung
cuz Yeah. annoyingly I need to get out
of the way.
No, I'm not paying £900 for a phone. [ __ ] that.
I'll pay £500, but it's not worth it.
900 is not worth it.
Not worth it at all.
No, that's not worth it. Sure
you can get a decent one for £500. Decent phone. Yeah,
that's still too much for a phone. Even
[ __ ] £500 is But I'll pay £500.
Yeah, I'll pay500.
I'm not cheap,
but far I'm [ __ ] cheap. I ain't say
cheap. My [ __ ] jeans are £200. My
trainers are £200.
I'd know all about I'd know all about
not being cheap, matey.
I'm not cheap either, matey.
But that's ridiculous. If the fold was
£1,000, then I would pay. If the fold
was £1,000, then that's the only time I
think I would pay it.
Other than that,
[ __ ] Rice ain't cheap. Of course he's
[ __ ] cheap, bro. He doesn't own one
pair of designer clothes.
What the [ __ ] That's mad.
No, that's [ __ ] No, it's [ __ ]
The guy is not cheap,
bro. He doesn't have a designer clothes.
He doesn't even get his haircut. [ __ ]
you mean he's not cheap?
Of course he's cheap.
course she's cheap. The [ __ ]
I'm not crying about £900. I I I would
pay £1,000 if it was a fold,
but other than that,
no, it's not worth it.
I don't know. [ __ ] knows. [ __ ] no.
one. It wasn't a It was £1,250
for the phone, but we had a deal on it.
Yeah. So, you're telling me I don't do
cheap? I do [ __ ] dear, right? And for
designer clothes, I walk around in
Gucci, mate. What are you talking about?
You don't. No, you [ __ ] don't. I'm
with No, you don't. Show Show us your
wardrobe. Show us your wardrobe. What?
>> Show us your wardrobe. Go on. You don't
you own You don't have
>> That's kind of like Wait a minute.
That's kind of like immature in there.
Show my wardrobe. That's like baby play.
Yeah, it is.
>> Not really.
>> No, you you look you moourn about
spending all that money, right, on a
[ __ ] phone, right? But you spend more
money, right, on a [ __ ] takeaway,
like a kebab.
>> Well, I spend £900 on a on takeaways
over the month. I don't think so.
Well, you you went into the restaurant
the other day and how much you pay for
that? About 70 quid?
>> No, like 30.
>> Well, you're telling me that stuff that
they were cooking in front of you now
that cost 30 quid.
>> Oh, that was £25 actually.
>> 25? What? 25 quid for all that? >> Yep.
>> [ __ ] hell.
>> So why what you think it was 70? Why
would it be 70?
>> Cuz it looks like a pass line.
No, I wasn't in central London. So, so
why why did you get a new phone anyways?
Do you need one?
>> Why' I get a new phone? Because I had
one phone for 3 years of my life, right?
And I was nothing wrong with it. So, I
needed a new upgrade. So, I bought the
Pixel 10 and I got contract on it,
right? It's not contract. It's basically
what it is. I can use as much air time,
as much minutes as possible forever only
for like 50 odd pound a month.
>> So, did Cody write it for you?
Well, no. We went in half.
>> What? Half and half.
>> She has She hasn't got a phone. She
hasn't got a phone anymore.
>> So, you share phones?
>> Well, yeah.
>> For now.
>> Really? What the [ __ ]
>> You don't realize how much [ __ ] You
don't realize her charge port went in
her phone. She hasn't got a number and
she's not she's not giving her number
out. But the fact is, yeah, she um she
uh nobody's got nothing of hers no more
now off YouTube. So that's good. And
this phone is dear as [ __ ] mate. It's
worth every penny.
>> What's so good about it?
>> It's a Pixel [ __ ] 10. It's like a PC.
I had a Pixel 6 and I was good. This is brilliant.
>> You know, you know the best phone is
Samsung F, isn't it?
I looked at that and he said there's a
problem and there's a a floor in there.
>> That's what I'm using right now.
>> Yeah, it's a floor in there. I I don't I
used to like Samsung's but I went off. I
went to the Pixel and even a guy in his
shop. He said if if my phone come he was
with a different company was uh Apple.
He said if Apple went down tomorrow he
said the best phone he would go for
would be the Pixel 10. He said because
they are amazing.
>> Yeah. I hate Apple.
>> I don't like Apple. I think it's load of [ __ ]
>> There's [ __ ] in it.
>> Yeah. And you're And you're skinned, by the way.
>> I'm skinn. How do you wear that one out? [laughter]
>> I'm joking. What happened? What's
happened to Mongolan? I haven't seen him for days.
>> I don't I don't talk to him, bro. I
don't talk to him.
>> I thought I thought you were friends then.
>> No, I haven't spoke to him for ages, bro.
He he be
>> he doesn't come on my channel and I
don't go on his channel. You know,
>> his contract is running out in a couple
of days. So, he's been taken off Kay's
uh phone now. So, he he'd have to go and
get a new thing now.
>> How's he how's he going to How's he
going to manage that?
>> Exactly. He has no money anyway. That's good [ __ ]
>> He said that he bought his his phone. It was £400.
>> No, he didn't.
He didn't know.
>> No, Kay did.
>> Oh, didn't know that.
>> He's a liar. >> Yeah,
>> that's what he said in it. Yeah. [ __ ]
>> So, his contract is run out now. We paid
for him to get off here. >> Oh,
makes sense, man.
>> Yeah. He's going to prison sooner
anyway, so he's going to get bummed by black.
>> When is it [ __ ] uh 27th in it?
>> 27th. Yeah.
Do you think he's actually going to get sent down?
>> Well, think about it logically, right?
You're a smart guy. Yeah, you're a smart
guy, right? He ain't going to have tag
cuz he's coming all the way to Plymouth,
right? And to be honest, if he's coming
all the way to Plymouth, right, on the
same day, you have to have that tag
fitted in your place. So, he has to go
all the way from Plymouth all the way
back to his location. But the fact is
he's not going to have tags. So, that's
out the window. The only thing he could
have is community service or a fine. >> Yeah.
>> But if that's if that's if he doesn't
have a fine or a community service, he's
definitely going to be bummed in jail. >> Yeah.
>> Because on the day that you have tag,
you have to be at your house in an hour.
Yeah. So he ain't going to make it all
the way for the He's not going to be on
tag. So that's out the window.
>> Yeah. He has to go the court's in
Plymouth, is it? Yeah. So,
>> that's long, bro. That's [ __ ] long.
>> Yeah, but I think he's going to Well, if
if it goes in his favor, he'll either
have a fine or I reckon he will
basically uh have community service. And
I think he [ __ ] that up anyway. >> Yeah.
>> He thought he was going to get away with
it, isn't it?
>> No, he won't get away with that. That's
>> He thought he was going to it.
>> No, he's dying. He's there's something
wrong with him, isn't it?
>> He's not normal. >> Yeah.
>> You know, he's shifting, you know, PJ,
he's shifting two grand, right, a month,
right? What the [ __ ] is he doing with
his two grand? >> Yeah, it's true.
>> What is he got? He doesn't put no money
away for his for his kids for every
year. Like a like a trust fund. He could
at least put like 50 quid away for Prim
and Lola every month. Yeah. make a trust
fund for him and he brags about, oh, I'm
going to give 200 quid for my kids for
Christmas. Like, what the [ __ ]
>> Yeah, he bought 200 um trainers, isn't it?
>> So, he'd rather pay 200 for a pair of
tra trainers, but he can't put 50 quid
away a month away for his uh for his two
kids. That's 100 quid. What's 100 quid
out to his money in two month in a month? >> Nothing.
>> It's nothing, is it? He's a bad father, mate. >> Yep.
I just don't get it. Like, he's got all
that money. He's single. He hasn't got
no responsibilities, nothing. He's
living in a [ __ ] hostel or whatever.
HMV. He should have money coming out his
[ __ ] ass, mate. >> Yeah.
Does he get two grand a month?
>> Yeah, of course he does. Well, Kaye
said, "How much does he have a month, Kaye?"
>> Nearly two grand. Yeah. There you go.
So, he's a single guy. Yeah. So he
should have money coming off his
pockets, mate. He should The world is a
zoyster rather spending on [ __ ] drugs,
>> weed, you know. He should be walking
around in like Gucci and [ __ ] like that.
>> Yeah. And money and that.
>> Yeah, exactly. And he's walking around
in boss [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Hey, boss is all right, man. It's not that bad.
>> I wouldn't be seen in her to be fair.
>> You don't like You don't like boss?
>> Nah, I I don't like [ __ ] like that, mate.
What do you do? Do you like Tommy Hilfiger?
>> No, I like I don't mind Tommy. I don't
mind like uh like I don't know. I I like
Gucci and [ __ ] like that. I like
>> Someone said ask you about Someone said
ask you about your 13 grand.
>> Well, tell him to mind his own [ __ ] business.
>> Yeah, mind your own business.
>> That's the difference on this internet.
Everybody's telling everybody their
business and no one's going to know
about my business anymore.
So you you get like two grand a month.
>> Well, I get money, but I me and Kayie
shares it. It's it's basically we
partnership. So whatever I get Yes. It's
it's it's a partnership thing. Does that make sense?
>> Yeah. Obviously.
>> Yeah. So, you know, he should be [ __ ]
mate. He should be You know what? He
should be riding around in like a
[ __ ] really smart car. Like, you know
what I mean? >> Yeah.
Are you going to get a car?
>> I don't know, man. It's pointless
driving in London, is it?
>> So, I was looking up a London the other
day, actually. The the most things get
stolen in London is bikes and phones.
>> Yeah. Uh phones actually motorbikes.
Yeah, it's happened to me. Need to be careful.
>> Yeah. To be fair, I've seen some rough
areas in London or to be fair.
>> Yeah. So, yeah.
>> Yeah. I I
What's Lester like? >> What?
>> What's Lester like? Is it rough?
>> Yeah, there's kids walking around with machetes, mate. >> Mad.
>> They they broke mine and Kay's door
down. Four people machetis trying to kill us.
>> What the [ __ ] You're chatting [ __ ]
>> Yeah, they No, I'm not chatting [ __ ]
It's the truth. The C was involved. They
literally kicked the door off the
engines, mate. And I was a fire door
>> over YouTube.
>> Yep. It was
five great guys did it. Paid somebody to do it.
>> They won't get away with it because
they've got what they need. They found
it. They found who the They found the
people on camera. So they hanging up together now.
>> They're constant.
>> Do you know what I don't get about this
internet? Yeah. These people weasels on
the internet. Yeah. calling you skin,
can't get a girlfriend. To be fair, I've
been watching you for a while. You have
more women than need [ __ ] [ __ ] on
the internet, mate. They're [ __ ]
dribblers in their mother's basement.
>> They just they just self project.
Yeah, jealous. I've been listening to
you for a while. Jealous, mate. They
just jealous because you get funny and
they don't, mate.
>> They're fat, ugly people, in it. >> Yeah.
>> You know, they they sit on the internet
from the time they wake up time they go
to bed, do it.
>> Yeah. It's sad, mate. You know what I
mean? You haven't got no jobs, nothing,
mate. You know, it's it's an
embarrassment. Even them commenting in the beginning. >> Yeah.
>> You all right, mate? All these people are dribblers.
>> You still You still drink?
>> I don't drink, mate. I haven't been
drinking. How long you been together, Kaye?
>> Four months, mate. I'm charged to drop.
>> That's good.
>> Yeah, it is, mate. I put loads of weight
on now. I have I'm really good, mate. [ __ ] me.
Yeah, I drunk last week, bro. I had a
really bad hangover, but it was really bad. No,
>> I don't want to go down that road again, bro. I
>> know it was it was I was drinking
cocktails, bro. It [ __ ] me the next
day, bro. Really bad.
>> Yeah, I can't be I can't be asked that
[ __ ] mate. My body can't take it. I I
drunk like 9 liters of [ __ ] ramen in
a few days, mate. That That killed me.
>> Have you ever had Have you ever had cocktails?
>> I'm not really into cocktails. Yeah,
>> I'm not really into all that, mate.
Anyway, I'm going to have my food cuz
I'm having I'm Bab.
>> All right, man. See you.
>> All right, you speak in a bit.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Y everyone. Yep.
It's a madness.
I'm going to get this £500 phone. I think
I am in you. Yeah. No. No sir.
I need to get a new phone cuz this
phone's blocked. So eventually Yeah.
Joseph Ferrar has a 200 pound phone.
Nah, mate. I can't be having Can't be
having a 200 pound phone.
They're too shitty in it.
Cheap shitty things.
No, [ __ ] that.
think she's wearing. Yeah,
I see that. Ah,
that [ __ ] uh
that Hugh don't come on my um
on my lives anymore, does he? Do you
remember that Hugh guy?
Yeah, that little rat.
Little snaky rat. Whenever they get
caught out, they never come back, do they? No. >> [cough]
>> nail biting is so addicting, bro. Yeah.
Oh, it's not You're [ __ ]
your [ __ ] skin and a [ __ ] skin. Flynn.
>> [clears throat and cough] [clears throat] >> Yeah.
>> Where the [ __ ] is Grezy when you need a
[ __ ] Where the [ __ ] is he, mate?
Good old greasy. Bye-bye, weirdo.
Nope. Got to buy a new phone. £500.
Yeah, I'm going to buy a new phone cuz
my phone's blocked.
need a new phone
because my phone's blocked.
This phone's been blocked for ages and
I need to find a new phone.
Obviously, this phone's blocked. So, you
can't use it. You can only use on Wi-Fi. Yes.
No, I just chilled out.
Yeah, I chilled out.
Yeah, not didn't do much at all.
Still talking to that number. So
hopefully they meet me. Hopefully, eh,
that'll be a Yeah,
>> mate. When I'm as fat as you, I worry about it. Nah,
you need to stop trying to troll Bob,
you're really bad at it. And mate, when
I'm when I'm when I'm nearly 1% of what
you are like, Martin, I'll stop worrying, mate.
I mean, you people in this community are
[ __ ] obese. You have no right to talk
about other people.
You're [ __ ] fat, ugly mongos. Worry
about yourselves before trying to judge
others. Thank you
again. Self projecting.
Bye-bye, [ __ ] [ __ ] sake.
[ __ ] Mongs on this community, aren't
they, bro? [ __ ] proper proper Mongs.
Self projecting Mongs. Oh my [ __ ] god, bro.
Need to get a life. Honestly, need to
get a [ __ ] life, bro.
Just stop this [ __ ]
Skin. Skin. Skin.
It's boring now, bro. Boring.
What do you mean it seems long? Well,
I'm not drinking for a little bit, am I? So, yeah, obviously
depressing and skin that you people in
this community self projecting.
These people in this community, bro, are
[ __ ] fat, ugly, depressed people with
no life. They literally are, bro. I
swear to God, they're proper proper
[ __ ] fat, ugly, sad, depressed people.
It's quite sad to see, to be honest.
No, I haven't asked them to meet yet.
Not yet. I wrote it off. You're good.
Maybe I'll ask him some more.
I kind of don't want to go out drinking
though. That's the thing for a long time. Uh [clears throat]
Doesn't matter where they're from, bro.
Doesn't matter where they're from.
How could these fat ugly people try and
say that someone else is packing on the pounds?
These fat ugly people are talking about
people packing on pounds.
Really, bro? Really
doing good, bro. Doing good. Uh,
I need to buy a new phone cuz this
phone's blocked. So, uh, looking at some phones.
Looking at some phones to buy. Turn right. Yeah.
Steen. Now, we're looking at some mobiles.
Looking at this one here. It's £500,
bro. I might get this one. And then
there's one that's 4 60.
Uh, but it's not in stock. So, I might
wait for that one. Depends.
I need to buy a phone because this one's blocked.
So, obviously when I go traveling, I
can't use this phone obviously. So yeah, that's
Yeah. Well, this one's £500. It looks good, bro.
I can't have a [ __ ] phone.
150,200. I can't have them phones, bro.
They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
This one's good.
Joseph Ferrar's got a 200lb phone. Wow. Heat.
One second, bro.
It says eight.
Yep. It says 8 GB of RAM,
which is enough. I I remember I had a
phone before. It had like 2 GB of RAM,
bro. It was [ __ ] It was [ __ ] [ __ ]
Really, really [ __ ]
No, it's not crap. How can a 500 phone
be crap, bro? It's not crap.
There's no way a phone that costs
anywhere from £4500
is going to be slow. There's no way,
bro. I had a 300 pound before phone
the one that you saw and that wasn't
that wasn't crap. That was good.
It was just like normal. That's like
£250 now. That phone. Yeah. Yeah,
this Bob is such a bad troll, bro.
It's Samsung obviously, bro.
Cuz that one before that was £400,
that's 250 now. That's like£250 now. And
that weren't slow.
So, a [ __ ] £500 phone, there's no way
it's going to be slower. You know,
the folds are the best, but they're too too expensive.
Way [ __ ] too expensive, bro. Yeah.
Samson's good, bro. I don't know what
the [ __ ] I don't know what the [ __ ]
you're talking about.
just some of the things that you say.
Yeah, but a phone's not going to
obviously be slow. A 500 lb Yeah, but a
500 lb phone is not going to be slow.
No, it's not. It's not. Uh,
it's not possible, right?
I haven't ate today. I'm not even
hungry, you know. Yeah,
I ain't even [ __ ] hungry.
No, I want this. I want the S25 Plus,
but it's [ __ ] out of stock. It's 460,
Hopefully, it goes back in stock tomorrow.
In stock tomorrow. I'll buy it.
Then I'll just [ __ ] buy it. Yeah.
That's a good phone, bro. It was 750, but
C's out of [ __ ] stock.
It's already Black Friday, you [ __ ]
Well, it's not Black Friday, but there's
already sales on.
That's what I'm saying. There's already sales on.
These phones are like £800.
some [ __ ] like 800 pound of that.
They're like 800 [ __ ] pound. [ __ ] knows.
This boat I'm looking at is £750 down
to400 and something. Yep.
Yes, it is.
Yes, but the the phone Yeah, but I'm
saying phones are on offer now. It
doesn't matter if it's Wednesday,
there's phones on offer right now. So
yes, but there's phones on offer now.
That's what I'm saying. Boring.
Go away. We're not giving you attention,
you sad bastard.
Bye-bye. No one cares.
You're not getting attention. You sad
fat ugly bastard. Anyways, um
yes, but uh not that kind of offer.
[snorts] Yeah, V's just wanting
attention because he's a sad fat ugly
freak. He ain't getting any attention on
his channel. He's not getting a voice in
this channel either.
So, well, we'll see what what what it's
saying Friday, what the phones are
and go from there basically. Yeah. [clears throat] Heat.
Yeah, it's boring, bro. It's the same
[ __ ] with these repeaters, bro, in this community.
Sad act [ __ ] bro. Same [ __ ] with them.
I wonder when they're going to get alive. Yes,
I've got Amazon. Yes. Why?
Yeah, I think the folds are like 1,600 now. 1,00 Yeah. Chinese phone.
Stop reading stupid
is another one that gets bullied just
like uh Dusty showers.
All these people get bullied in real
life. Steven Howard, they're a bit like Reddit moderators.
This community reminds me a lot of um
yeah, Reddit moderators. Yeah, bro. definitely there.
this phone, but it needs to uh come back
and stock. It's a S24 Plus,
so I'll wait for it. Yeah.
Hopefully, it comes back in stock
tomorrow at 460.
eight today, bro.
Just don't feel like eating.
Some bacon at I had some bacon earlier.
Maybe I should eat, but I don't know what.
No, you can provide your own content if
you get a life.
Nah, if you got a life, you'd be able to
provide your own content.
No, I don't know why.
I'm just not hungry to be fair.
I don't know why.
Yeah. If you got your if you got a life,
Bob, then uh you know, you can create
your own content.
Isn't that right, uh Steven Howard?
So you get to live and
No, I know. I'm just saying that if you
had your own life, you'd be able to make
your own content.
That's what I'm saying. That's what I'm saying, though. Yeah,
that B is such a sad bastard.
He's he's another Pat Mustard. Proper
fat, ugly bully victim. Ain't got
nothing in life.
Speaking to yourself for [ __ ] what,
three months? Jesus Christ. [sighs]
That is mad, bro.
Let me see.
He is a proper proper keyboard warrior.
Proper proper sad.
But the thing is with these people in
real life, yeah, they never say
anything. They never even look at you.
They would they wouldn't say anything to
anyone's face. They wouldn't look at
anyone the wrong way. These people on
here, believe it or not,
they're [ __ ] absolute spastics in
real life, bro. Little you you could
like touch them, bro, and they'd fall
over these people on here. Like, it's
it's not even a joke, bro. I swear to God.
It's a [ __ ] uh some madness. Yeah,
I might go get some food, bro.
You're too skinned to do it. How much do
you have? How much money do you have now?
What is the day today? It better not be
[ __ ] Oh, yeah. We're good.
Yeah, we're good. Good, bro.
We already have coke. Yeah, I'm going to
go get some food. I think
that's not skin.
What you think having 200 pound is skin?
£200 until when? Ah,
bro, it's not skin.
Oh, bless you. You got £200.
There's There's [ __ ] kids in Africa,
mate, that don't have anything.
So, what if you got £200? What? You
What? You're not going to survive on on 200?
Really, bro? Come on, man.
You really think that's Yeah.
So why can't you do that?
What the [ __ ] did you do with all your money? That's hardness.
Yeah, but how though? Cuz I went out
last week, the week before that, the
week before that, and I've still got money.
So, how have you done all that money, bro?
H, you could be worse. You could you
could be me having to [ __ ] fork out
£500 for a [ __ ] phone.
Can't you get a [ __ ] um
Can't you get a uh advance loan?
Yeah, I bought Uggs as well this month.
That was 165.
So, next month I should be good, bro. I
should be really good. Got my jeans, got
my trainers, got my phone. I would have
bought a phone by then. So, I'll be good, bro. Yeah.
Oh, that last week, week before that,
that's crazy, bro.
I used escorts twice as well.
Do you think 200 to last 11 days is skin Steven Howard? Nah.
Oh, bless you. How are you ever going to survive, eh?
I'm being sarcastic, by the way.
Oh, bless you. Bless. [laughter]
Not really. Why?
Why not? [ __ ]
[ __ ] me, bro.
Well, if you needed a [ __ ]
you'd be fat, wouldn't you?
When did I last have a [ __ ]
I got two this month. I think I used
escorts twice this month. Jesus Christ.
If only I stayed in. Eh.
If only I had [ __ ] stayed in.
I think I'm going to have t I think I
think I'm going to have tandoori
chicken. I think. Yeah.
Tandoori chicken and
rice. Yeah, basically that's what I
think I'm going to have.
I've already won, bro.
I've traveled. I've [ __ ] women. I've
traveled everywhere. But you seem to
dismiss all them things.
I've won loads and loads and loads of
times, but it just gets dismissed.
Isn't that right, Steven Howard?
Been seen having sex, been seen with the
most women, been seen here, been seen there.
But, um, people still at like I haven't
done anything. So, I mean,
come on now, man. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
My leg's [ __ ] itchy.
But then you still,
but even then you still dismiss everything. So [ __ ] So,
don't understand the [ __ ] point of it
to be honest.
That B needs a life.
You can just tell you you could just
tell he's been bullied, bro.
That V. You can just tell that he's been
bullied, bro. So obvious.
Nope. Cuz I know it will never change.
She's Asian, by the way. I was speaking
to her earlier, Steven Howard. Yeah,
that's another thing because I was
planning on going out for a couple of
weeks cuz I've already been out drinking
and [ __ ] So, I was planning not to go
out for a bit.
This is hard one, is it? Then
I need to get my haircut and [ __ ]
and know I haven't asked her yet. We
we've been talking and that but sake
this puts me in a position, bro. Cuz
then if I go out then I'm going to have
to spend money and that's the thing.
Then all the other [ __ ] gets delayed.
But I mean I guess it's not that bad, is it? Just
that's the problem with all of this
[ __ ] bro. It's [ __ ]
all expensive, is it? [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, [sighs and gasps]
we just talking about [ __ ] horror
movies and [ __ ] Yeah.
You want to ask me first? I doubt it. I doubt. Yeah.
Let's hope this phone goes back and stop tomorrow.
Fingers crossed. Yay.
She didn't say I just said I went to the
cinema the other day. I just lied to her
saying I went to the cinema. Obviously
haven't been to the cinema, but I just
said I did. So
yeah, I bought them ugly as well. They were 165.
See, I bought a lot of [ __ ] bro.
I bought the trainers and the [ __ ]
jeans. Oh, [ __ ]
So, hopefully I can get a phone on this
[ __ ] uh Black Friday. Yes.
I mean, I approached her, so
I guess she is. Yeah.
But I don't really want to drink this
week. I mean, I said I weren't going to
drink this week anyways, and I So,
[ __ ] sake, man.
>> I mean, all of the women I speak to are
women I've approached, so Yeah.
When should I go out drinking again, Stephen?
I reckon hund I reckon mid December, bro.
I reckon this
I reckon mid December Okay.
I think I think mid December, bro.
Definitely mid December.
So, I need to spend my money on
I've been out a lot as well.
Yeah, I go out more in the summer, but I
don't normally really go out anymore. I
don't know what's gone into me the past couple weeks,
but I need to obviously buy a phone. I
need to save some money as well cuz I am
actually leaving. I am definitely
leaving this country, bro. 100% I am.
But obviously, I I'll invite this person
out. If they want to go out, then
obviously I'll go out. I don't mind. But
other than that, I need to really stop
for a bit. Then I won't be able to do
other things. And yeah.
So yeah, man. Basically,
I don't like the summer. I prefer the
winter, but I go out drinking more in
the Yeah. Then we have load We'll have
most of December just saving money. It
will be lush. Just saving money. A lot
of that December
will be good. Yeah.
Yeah, man. It'll be sick.
Try some football bets as well.
No, I think like the 15th of December. Yeah.
Yeah. I think the 15th
so bloody, bro. I'm going to have to buy
this phone as well. So,
[ __ ] sake, man.
I don't want that [ __ ] football [ __ ] win. [sighs]
[ __ ] hell, bro.
[ __ ] [ __ ] it.
But yeah, I'm going to have um the rest
of this month off unless the person
wants to meet
like I said. Yeah.
>> I don't know, bro.
But no one's really going to be out much
now because of that cuz obviously um
when I went out it was it was dead. So
it will start from December. Then then
um then then
uh obviously you save money January and
then you save money February. [laughter]
So we'll have some time to save some money.
Yeah, we'll have some good time to save
some money as well.
because obviously people don't go out.
You have the whole of January to save
money. You have the whole of January at
the very least the very least
midFebruary. So that's good.
So my thing is save money now until like
mid December. Just go ham and then
that'll be it until [ __ ] yeah February.
Even if it's the start or something,
bro, that hangover was [ __ ] rank. It
was [ __ ] stinking, bro. That hangover.
Virgin boy knows
people [ __ ] dismissing my struggles.
Sake, I'm going to get some um tandoori
chicken and ricey. Is that okay with you, boss?
Yeah. And I was just saying to everyone,
I need to buy a new phone. I sold this
phone for £500, Grezy. I'm thinking of buying it.
What What phone What phone do you have
again, Greavvesy? How much did your phone cost?
Cuz this phone's blocked in it. So, yeah,
we were basically saying Yeah.
What about your little mobile? Oh,
listen then. It really was £300.
Oh, is it brand new? Oh, bless. More bless.
Where did you get it from?
Yeah, there's this one I want. It's It's
actually 459, but it's out of stock. I'm
hoping it gets back in stock soon so I
can buy it. [ __ ] You know,
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
Where did you buy it from? Greavves.
Did you get it new or did you get
refurbed? Oh, you got it refurbed. Yeah,
but the thing with that is Yeah, but the
thing is if you get refurbed and [ __ ]
Oh, years ago.
But the thing with that is it's the
battery. I can't have a dodgy battery.
That's like one of the only reasons why
I'd buy them new is cuz I can't risk
having a dodgy battery.
That's mad. All them years. Wow.
How much RAM is it?
Wow, that's mad.
Yeah, I want this [ __ ]
That's the thing though. It's the battery. £300.
Is 8 gig is 8 gig is 8 gig RAM uh good enough? Grezy,
is it good enough? 8 gig RAM, I supposing
8 gig. Is that is that good enough?
The RAM's very important. Steven said
it's not, but I think it's all right. No. Yeah,
I think that's that's enough. No.
Well, that phone I bought for £400 is now 250.
And that worked fine.
That Samsung worked completely fine. It
was a lot faster than the Fold, but it worked fine.
Yeah, that worked fine.
That was 249.
I paid £400 for it. Yeah.
>> What do you think, Weezy? >> [snorts]
>> What do you think of 8 GB RAM? Whereas
do you think that's bad?
Yeah, it's £500. This [ __ ] phone.
I want this S24 Plus, but it's it was
750. Now it's 4 60, but it's um
it's out of stock. But like I said, it needs to. Yeah, basically.
No, seriously, Greavves. Is it actually good? H
I remember my um one of the tenants.
Yeah, he had £150 phone boos. He was
[ __ ] You couldn't even use it.
You couldn't even use it. It was so [ __ ]
Nope. You couldn't even use it, bro. It
was bad. Really, really bad.
It was [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
Yeah, the folds are the best. The folds
I like folds. Greasy.
Do the folds.
No, he doesn't.
So what it's not actually good really
eight 8 GB of RAM is not good really.
Oh, you told him. Yeah, man.
Just get some food.