Greaves is going to [ __ ] love this.
Just [ __ ] uh voice noted that [ __ ] Lex. Yeah.
Yeah. Greasy is going to love me for
this. I really want to one on debate
with him because he ain't going to win
against me, mate. He is really really
not going to win against me. I don't
want to go on no [ __ ] Tik Tocky, bro.
I want to have a one-on-one with you
right here, right now. Let's have a little debate.
And I was basically telling him how like
it's mad how you defend women when like
[ __ ] most of them are [ __ ] narcissists.
Um, and I was saying to him basically
comparing is not a valid argument, you
know, and I'll explain it further if you
want to if if you want me to. Um,
so that's that basically. Yeah.
We'll see what he has to say.
I sent him a um 2 minute 27 second voice note. Yeah.
I don't get dudes like him, bro. I don't
I really don't get dudes like him
defending women when most of them are
[ __ ] narcissists. That's a mad thing.
So, I'd love I'd love him to reply back.
I would love for him to reply back. Bro,
>> that is insane. I said to him that
basically that I went out last Thursday and
all that ever happens is these women
pretend that they've got boyfriends or
they say they're not interested or
whatever, which isn't the problem. I was
basically telling him that the problem
is is that these narcissistic women like
to lead people on and play games and
then you've got people like you [ __ ]
defending them. I don't know why you're
defending them when they're clearly most
of them are narcissists if not all of
them. It's [ __ ] obvious, you know,
the leading on the piss taken. And I was
saying to him as well that um comparing
right is not a valid argument. And I'll
explain why if you if you know if you
want to get into it, you know, cuz they
are narcissists. They are narcissistic
[ __ ] And I said to him before you want
to start throwing out names, I'm not a
white knight. I'm not a s. I'm not an
incel. And I'm not a virgin. So I've got
no reason to lie about anything. I've
got no reason to say something that I
don't fully believe, you know,
because it's the truth. It is. They are narcissists. narcissistic
lying [ __ ] That is what they are.
And I'm I'm not being I'm not lying when
I'm saying it. They are literally all
the [ __ ] same. So that's that. You know,
that's the thing, Grezy. I don't care
about people that pretend they've got
boyfriends or people that are honest. I
generally don't care. But they're not,
though. That's the problem with it,
Greavvesy, is that they're not honest.
They're narcissists. When you speak to
one, you feel like you've spoke to a
million other of the same people before,
but people that again are not all the
same. This is what I don't understand, bro.
You know, they're not honest. They're [ __ ] bullshitters.
You know, it pissed me off yesterday
because it's like, how many more years
are you going to keep giving these
people the benefit of the doubt, Grezy?
How how many more years how many more
times do you have to go out and keep
thinking that there are good people out
there when there isn't? There generally is not.
That was my last bit of hope for
Thursday. And then they just acted like a [ __ ]
I'm not going out today. I'm not going
out tomorrow. Simple.
So, and I'll also explain to him, right,
before you want to sit there and try and
say that they're not all the same,
here's one thing, right? Do you know
what different means? Yeah. This is what
I'm going to say to him as well. If he
responds back, I'm going to be like, do
you know the definition of somebody
being different? Yeah. Because, right,
me, I'm different than
every other man. No one acts the same as
me. No one says the same stuff. You will
not meet a man that's similar to me
because I am different. You understand?
These women are not different, right?
They are all the same. And I told them
that I am completely unbiased.
So, and what reason do I have to lie?
What am I a virgin? Don't think so. You
know, I'm just sick of their toxic [ __ ]
People can be sick of their toxic
[ __ ] and and and complete and be
completely unbiased, you know,
Greavvesy. People can be sick of it.
People can be not scared to say what
they think without having to be labeled
as a [ __ ] name. Do you understand, bro?
You do you understand what I'm [ __ ]
saying? Now, I met this guy right on but
I'm I met this guy on uh
Thursday, right? Just like building
connections and stuff. And I messaged
him and I met him, right? and he's fine talking normally
and like we'll meet up for a drink and
whatever. Not in a gay way obviously.
Now you just said that women aren't all
the same. So why is it that no man acts
the same way as they do, right? As like
obviously men do other things that make
them bad, whatever, but I'm saying that
surely to God if you would be meeting
people that that are men are the same.
Oh my god. Stop calling me, you [ __ ]
stalking little fat ugly bastard. The
Jamie Thompson. This fat ugly.
Let me [ __ ] turn my
[ __ ] sim off. Fat ugly [ __ ]
Turn my sim off. I'm changing my number
soon. Anyways, get a life you fat ugly
bastard. Anyways, um, as I was saying,
Grezy, yeah, that's that's that
basically. Um, yeah. So, this guy seems
completely cool. So, you if if women
weren't all the same, then men would be
doing the same thing. Men that you come
across would be doing the same thing
because that's the only gender that you
can compare it to. They are obviously
all the same.
Think about it, right? You know, when
you when you've had like bad times
before, right? and you've had to like
get stuff off your chest. Do you not
find it funny how it's only men friends
that are there for you, never women,
because they're narcissists? Have you
have Have you Have you Have you not noticed that? You know,
so my problem is their toxic behavior
and leading on. You know, I don't give a
[ __ ] about people saying they have a
boyfriend or not. That will always be
the same [ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] about that.
It's mad. And then you got people like
him defending them. It's weird. It is
honestly weird, bro. It [ __ ] is mad.
But I'll be interested to see what he
writes back. I'll keep you updated.
It's [ __ ] up, bro.
He'll get ruined, bro. If he wants to
have a debate with me, I'll ruin him,
bro. I will ruin him. Trust me.
You know, I don't know how people can
defend them. I really really don't know.
And they always give off like
victimizing vibes. Like they always sit
like for example griev I can't explain
it. Like oh um yeah I felt pressured
into giving my number. They always have
to be the victim but I can't explain it.
They always have to
um try to victimize themsel. Can't
explain it. I can't explain what I'm
It's a vibe that they give off. They
always have to be the victim,
you know? They have to be the victim
every single time. It's madness, bro.
[ __ ] madness. It really is [ __ ] mad. Yeah.
Right. Think about it. Someone say that
they felt pressured to give their number, right?
But they're texting you every day asking questions.
Doesn't make sense, does it?
Games, victimizing, narcissism. That's
all you deal with with these women, bro.
It's boring now. Very, very boring. So,
very, very, very, very boring.
And then you got some [ __ ] skint in Kent
trying to sit there and still say
they're not all the same. What the [ __ ]
I've not met all women, but I've met
more women than you. And every single
time I meet women, they are all the
same. So what, bro? So [ __ ] what?
You know, explain that one. [ __ ] idiot.
Madness, bro. Absolute madness.
Also, another one on Reddit earlier
Grezy was trying to blame me for recording.
They said, "Oh, you shouldn't record your approaches."
Now, what's wrong with me recording my
bad experiences? What's wrong with
documenting the [ __ ] that I have to go
through with these [ __ ] I don't see a
problem with recording audio. What's a
problem with recording audio?
Is there such a problem with that?
I don't know what's what what's wrong
with me recording audio in a public
place. What's what's the problem with that?
It's like they look for any little thing
that they can find just to put the blame
on to you. It's pathetic, bro. It's
[ __ ] pathetic because if you didn't
record, right, these approaches,
Greavvesy, no one would believe you. The
few people that are unbiased out there
wouldn't believe you.
you you no one would believe you. You'd
be like the the boy who cried wolf. If
you sat there and said, "Oh, well, you
know, and say you you turn around and
said, "Oh, every time I try to speak to
someone, they pretend they've got
boyfriends." Then they're going to turn
around and say to you, "Oh, well, it
could be the way you're acting." No, no,
no, no, no, no. And obviously that's
what the the videos are to prove that,
you know, that you act normal and these
women are stuck up and they don't like
it, so they try to put the blame onto
you. Then I turn around and say to him,
"Okay, well, what about the 99% of
approaches that haven't recorded? The 99
99% of them aren't recorded. So what
about them ones then?" It's constant
excuses to justify their shitty behavior.
And I've had enough of it,
you know. I've had enough of it, bro.
You know, and it has wound me up today.
And it wound me up yesterday as well.
And it doesn't wind me up anymore
because really but it did. Uh and it's
like the whole Groovy. It's like the
whole women don't owe you anything. Why
do you Where do you think that comes
from, bro? Where do you think that come
from? That women don't owe you anything.
It's from It's to justify their shitty behavior.
That's what it is. It's not because it
it's used. It's because whenever they do
something shitty and someone complains
about it, they try to get out of it by
saying, "Oh, well, they don't owe you
anything anyways." Doesn't justify what they do. [ __ ] madness.
It's a way to try to cover up what they
do by saying that they don't owe you
anything. Hence why you never hear men
don't owe you anything. Have you Have
you found it funny, G? How you never You
will never hear men don't owe you
anything for the exact reason why I'm
explaining. It's just made to cover up
women's shitty behavior, narcissistic behavior. [snorts]
For example, you spend two hours with
someone and they don't even reply back,
right? Let's just say that, you know,
you you know, you was nice to someone
and they and they didn't even reply
back. They didn't have the decency to
reply back. They'll be like, "Oh, well,
they don't owe you anything." I mean,
yeah, technically they don't [ __ ]
have to reply back, but it would be a
bit nice, wouldn't it? It'd be a bit
nice. It would only take five seconds of
your day to just write something back,
you know? You know, I mean I mean No,
really. Come on now. What? Five seconds
of your day just to be a bit bit polite.
No. No. [ __ ] madness, bro. Madness.
The double standards is is insane.
It is insane, bro. And this guy is a
[ __ ] idiot. So, yeah. Hopefully he
gets back to me.
I'm talking about them, bro. I'm not
talking about them having boyfriends or
them, you know.
I'm talking about what they do. That's
what I'm doing. I My problem is what
they do. That's the conversation I want
to have with him is what they do.
I don't give a [ __ ] about not having sex
or people saying they're not interested.
I don't give a [ __ ] I'm talking about
this toxic [ __ ] that they do, i.e.
leading on the narcissism. You know,
my my first message to him, Greavesy,
was why are most narcissists women and
not men? And he didn't really reply, did
he? He kind of shhat it. He shhat his
pants a little bit. When I first
messaged him, he shhat his pants. I have
the messages right here. Um, you know,
he can't have a one-on-one. Probably
what he wants me to do is join his
TikTok so all these little minions can
go at me. But with a one-on-one, it will [ __ ] it,
you know? And that's the thing, bro. And
they're never honest as well. They're
never honest. Um, these these these
women, they're never ever honest. And by
honest I mean like you won't meet
someone and they'll just say oh that
like it's always the same leading on
every time. Time wasting leading on.
They are all the [ __ ] same bro. That
would be [ __ ] Yeah.
I'll have an audience if he lets me join
the Tik Tok, right?
I'll join it. Just me and him. I'll join
it. I I'll see you later. He said I'll
join it and then record the whole thing. So,
it's annoying, bro. It is annoying.
He's not going to win against me, bro.
And if he wants to try to compare me to
other people, then he's going to get
wrecked with that one as well,
cuz I've got evidence of what they've
done, you know, on messages and
whatever. So other people's experiences
don't change that.
So it's like what, bro? You want to
compare other people? What? Because
someone might have got lucky on a dating
app. Because someone might got lucky.
because someone met someone through
social media. It's not comparable to
people that are trying [ __ ] nowadays.
It's not at all comparable. Idiots
[ __ ] It's lazy as well. very lazy.
Well, I don't normally record their
faces, but I did the other day. All right.
But there should be no problem with recording audio.
Most most channels record their faces,
Greasy. When when people approach, most
of the time they record their faces. So,
how is audio such a problem? And it's
because it's showing women in a bad
light. They don't like it. That's what
it is. It's nothing to do with you
recording. It's your proving what they
are like. Because even when when you
approach them, a lot of them are just stuck up.
Yeah. And not only him, a lot of other
people do it as well. Yeah. Yeah, I was
watching him yesterday. A lot of other people.
Yeah, I was watching him yesterday and
he was getting the same [ __ ] as well
again. Wow. Someone like him's even
getting the same [ __ ]
Imagine that. Eh, but
I don't compare myself to him. I still
think that, you know, the odd time I go
out and try it might be different.
Even though that guy's getting the same
[ __ ] and he looks fully white and he's
[ __ ] famous, but I still like to
think that, you know,
I my luck will be different than he's
see I don't compare
because I will still go with a mind with
the mindset of well that's him not me as
mad as that sounds you know
so I don't even compare any anyway you
But yeah, he's not the only one that's
done it, bro. There's loads of channels
that record their faces. They have a
problem with you recording audio. But yeah,
but the funny thing is, Grezy, is that
they'll have no problem walking into a
shopping center where their faces are
recorded, where they're walking around,
then it's all recorded.
They'll have no problem with that.
probably being recorded in toilets, but
you show them in a bad light and you
show them to be stuck up, they're
chasing you with actors, mate.
And let's face it, mate, if you was a
gay guy approaching men, recording men,
no one would have a problem with it. So,
it's the fact that it's showing women
what they are, and people don't like it.
So, the only thing that they can come
they can come up with is, "Oh, well,
you're recording. You're recording."
[ __ ] insane, bro.
It's tiring, bro. You How many times do
you have to keep going out, you know, in
hopes to find someone that ain't all the
same, that's not a narcissist?
How many more times? How many more times? Eh,
grievy. It's It's pathetic at this point.
You'll meet someone,
right? You'll give them the benefit of
the doubt and then they just do the same thing again.
They just do exactly the same thing again, you know. [ __ ] madness. Oh well.
So it looks like Grezy, if you go out approaching America,
it's worse than here. I knew it. I knew
it, you know. I didn't even I didn't
even need to watch Ed Matthews to know
that because I met so many Americans. I
met so many Americans, bro. Um,
obviously living in London, I I used to
meet [ __ ] so many of them every week.
And people used to say like, "Oh yeah,
but the problem is here is that, you
know, they hear the accent all the time
that they were trying to make it seem
like, oh, the reason why it'll be easy
in America is because there's not as
many English people.
Um, so obviously the accent, obviously
here they'll hear the accent, but no,
they're westernized [ __ ] bro. Stuck
up. Stuck up westernized. Even in
America, bro, an accent, they're not
going to get with you because of your
accent. You know, you've seen you've
seen this Ed Matthews. He has an accent.
He's got followers.
Um, you know, he's got money. People
know who he is. And he still can't get anything.
So, no one's going to shag you just
because you got a different accent.
So, what do you think, bro? What What do
you think? You're just going to go to
New York City and
all of these women are going to be
different because you're British? [ __ ] off, bro. Nah. Never. Maybe.
The only way it would be different,
Greavvesy, is you could only tell from
by a very, very long time. So, what I'm
saying is it could be different if you
stay there long enough, like, and I'm
talking a year, a year and a half. I
don't mean you're just going to go there
and then you're going to get women. You
might have met someone if you stay there
long enough, like a year and a half maybe,
you know, but you're not just going to
go to a country and then someone's going
to be like, "Oh, you're from England."
And then get with you. That's what they
make out. I'm sure you've heard stuff
like that before, bro.
Yeah. I don't know who that is, but
American people the worst.
They are the [ __ ] worst.
Worst people ever, bro.
People on Reddit say if you go to
America, you you you'll find someone
because the accent,
you know, [ __ ] Absolute [ __ ] bro.
You might have more luck. Yeah, maybe
two years down the line, but not
straight away. No way.
They're westernized. They're [ __ ]
It's the same as England [ __ ]
Same as [ __ ] with Thailand's getting
like it now as well. Look at that
problem. Look at that issue I had with
that escort Grezy yesterday. The whole
conversation took about an hour. I'm
thinking, "What the fuck?" She's a
[ __ ] as well.
And then when I told her about herself,
she started being all right. She's like,
"Oh, who do you live with? How far do
you live?" Like then she was like, but
it took me telling her about herself and
I'm thinking, what the [ __ ]
I said to her, why are you being a
[ __ ] Why are you acting like such a
[ __ ] for? So I had to tell her about
herself before she started acting normal again.
[ __ ] mad. It's so toxic, you know.
Greasy, you told him that he dismisses
my struggles in it. You asked him why he
kept dismissing my struggles, in it, Grezy. Yeah.
Yeah, that's what you was asking him, was it?
But a lot of people do that. A lot of
people dismiss your struggles.
It doesn't suit them.
Where the [ __ ] does did this Lex guy
even come from?
What the hell? mad. Oh, yeah. So, um,
you're going to get the popcorn out
later where I go on Tik Tok and have a
debate with this guy. Yeah, get the
popcorn out. I'm eating popcorn right now actually. Salted popcorn.
[ __ ] madness come. You right. [clears throat]
Could be a boring day today. do nothing.
You like the food video yesterday,
it was lush.
It was lushy.
You like it?
Yeah, I'm trying to think what
restaurant I can go to next.
Yeah, I me I messaged that next guy,
bro. Oh. Oh, Z. I I messaged that um Le Sky
again. I'm going to destroy this [ __ ]
because he's full of [ __ ]
I said to him that [ __ ] um that
they're narcissist and that and they
just lead people on for their own entertainment.
Um, I'd love to have a debate with him
and comparing people to other people is
not a valid argument
and then explain why if you actually
respond back. He's an idiot, bro. And I
told him as well that I'm not um I'm not
I'm not a white knight. I'm not a s. I'm
not an incel. I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
I'm saying to him that we're sick of
their [ __ ] People can be sick of their
[ __ ] without being labeled as anything,
mate. You do realize that
if you can set me up with a woman, well,
that's going to be a bit hard because
the guy doesn't get no women, hence why
he's a white knight.
So, yeah, people could be sick of their
[ __ ] without being labeled as anything.
Cuz I am I am sick of that [ __ ] bro.
Time and time and time and time and time
and time and time and time again.
So like how many more years you have to
keep giving these people the benefit of
the doubt before you lose before you run
out of patience
and just give up. So yeah.
Yeah. They they say a lot of things. Oh,
I was on Reddit just now or I was ask
and um I showed this um person my
approaches and you know what she turned
around and said? She says, "Oh um why
have you got a c I'd recommend you not
having a camera in their face?" I'm
thinking firstly, a camera wasn't in
their face. Secondly, um what's wrong
with me recording the audio? I mean, I'm
I'm I'm I'm trying to prove my
experiences and what happens, you know,
to disclaim all of the things that you
tried to say on Reddit and now all of a
sudden there's a problem with recording audio.
There's a problem with recording audio.
Okay. So, what about 99% of the
approaches that aren't recorded?
It's any excuse. It's pathetic, bro. It
really, really, really, really is
pathetic. Then I show them a load of my
screenshots where, you know, they've
played games and um led me on and then
she's all of a sudden working now and
she can't get back to me until later.
What do you know, Greavvesy? [ __ ]
[ __ ] bro. You know, blaming you recording.
How else are you going to prove that the
the [ __ ] [ __ ] are stuck up in this
country if you don't record it?
You know that is that is insane, bro.
Yeah, they'll blame your beard,
blame your haircut, but it's sad that it is excuse
yet they claim that they're equal yet
they claim equality.
You know, they they they it's like the
whole owing people anything. Do you know
I was just telling Rudy about this you
want it when they say that women don't
owe you anything. That's just an excuse
to cover up their shitty behavior. Do
you do realize that? You do realize that
saying is to try to justify every shitty
little thing that they do.
Um sad really that that that's the world
that we live in. But yeah,
so that's your excuse, right? So if you
meet somebody for a couple of hours,
right, and they don't even have the
decency to reply, that's because they
don't owe you anything. Oh, [ __ ]
really. You know, that's that that's the
excuse that you're going to come out with.
So because they don't owe you anything,
that justifies them not wasting what 5
seconds of their time replying back.
Really, bro? [ __ ] well. Really?
But the irony is if you was if you was
in um I I've actually had this before.
If you if you're in Morrison's right and
you don't say thank you or whatever,
people have have have the ass about it.
So make it make sense. You know, if you
if you don't say thank you or whatever
like that, people go
people people go mad.
But when a woman does something shitty,
she don't owe you anything. My son, make
it make [ __ ] sense, bro. Make it make [ __ ] sense.
It's really bad, bro. It's used in the
wrong context as well. That's that.
It's so crazy what people have to put up with.
It's really, really bad.
Really, really, really, really bad. It's
depressing, bro. So, I won't be out this
I won't be out this week. No.
Yeah, that's a good um that's a good
point. Yeah, I'll use that.
They use it to justify their shitty behavior.
That's why that's why they use that to
justify them being stuck up um [ __ ]
with unrealistic expectations. That's,
you know, that's what it is. And and and
it is anything to suit their narrative
because you never hear it about men.
Have you ever heard a man don't owe you
anything? Never. never ever ever,
you know, you've never ever ever ever.
So, but yeah, I'll use that um I'll use
that boss one. Yeah, that's a good
analogy, right? Because if you're going
out pursuing people and they're leading
you on and they're and they're acting
[ __ ] toxic, right? Then if they don't
owe you anything, then yeah, it's the
same way then. Yeah.
It's stupid, bro. And the fact that it's
only used when it's to do with women as
well. That's the problem with it is they
never say it about men. They only say it
about women, which proves they're
[ __ ] sexist to begin with.
You never hear about men not owing
anyone anything. Never. You can go all
You go on the internet, right, and
you'll never ever hear it. But when you
complain about women, oh, they don't owe you anything.
Really, bro? Come on.
How Virgin Boy says they're not all the
same is is [ __ ] beyond me. I don't
give a [ __ ] if that lanky little [ __ ] is
older than me, mate. I've got more life
experience than he would ever have.
You know how that lanky little virgin
[ __ ] can try and say that they're not
all the [ __ ] same in his little
virgin bedset. In his little skin virgin
bedset is beyond me, bro. Yeah. Madness.
It's so bad, bro.
Yep. He's a proper proper copycat.
He's a proper copycat.
People have different types of people, you guys.
that they go for like but he says that
you're gay. He says if you don't find
Sherco attractive you're gay. That is
copying. If you go on the student room
form or any kind of thing people always
used to say that to each other. It was
the trend. It used to be about Beyonce.
They had one with Beyonce as well. That is copying.
Yeah. Copying the crowd because you
don't want to feel left out. You're a
copycat. It doesn't make you look big.
It makes you look like a copycat that's
got no mind of your own. Yeah. Copycat.
Proper proper copycat, bro. Proper proper copycat.
So if I find someone not attractive,
that looks average, that's got no tits,
that makes me gay.
Really, bro? Really, bro? Really?
Someone that's got no ass, no [ __ ]
tits. That makes me gay because I don't
find that attractive.
What a loser, mate. He's never going to
get laid. He's going to die a virgin.
Proper proper. Going to die a virgin, bro.
You're gay. Yeah.
I didn't know that makes people gay
though. If you don't find a celebrity attractive,
I thought being gay means you like dick. Copycat. Little copycat.
Every time I go to my sisters or or
Yeah. I get this cat. She's got a cat
and he keeps attacking me
saying and it just reminds me of him. [snorts] Oh, copycat. Copycat version. Yeah. Oh.
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
What happened to What happened to like
different types of women?
I mean, what happened to that grievy? You know,
I've seen better looking people walking
down the [ __ ] street than her.
But you're But if you don't find these
people attractive, no problem.
No problems. No problem.
If you if you don't find someone that's
better looking than her attractive,
that's fine. You're not gay. But if you
don't find her attractive, you're gay
because of the name. It's all to do with
Think about it, right? It's all to do
with the name.
No, I'm not getting pork fried rice.
[ __ ] that. Uh,
it's the name, is it? You little copycat. Little copycat. No copycat.
No, but I'd nail your sister. You [ __ ] weirdo.
No, but I would I'd nail yours.
When am I going to find someone that's
not a complete narcissistic time waster
that plays games? And I thought I was
immature. You know what? Sask. I thought
I was I I for all of these years thought
that I was the immature one.
I always thought I was immature like
laughing at stuff, but nothing is more
immature compared to these women, bro. Narcissistic women.
You have none of these problems with
men. Not in a gay way. I mean men that
you come across in a friendly way, you
have none of these problems. But they
will sit there until they're blue in the
face and tell you women are not all the same.
I was speaking to that guy from Reden um
earlier, bro. He seems like a cool guy.
I sure need to ask him if he banged that
fatty. Now, you don't get any of these
problems with these men that are your
friends or people that you meet. You get
none of these problems. But they tell
you that all women aren't the same,
right? So, let's see what Lex Therapy
has to say about that.
I'll go on a TikTok later with a nice
Chinese and I will split him in half,
bro. Trust me, he won't win against me.
He won't win against me.
Trust me, he won't.
And I've got evidence as well.
I [ __ ] hate them, Mr. B. They're all
Yeah, I was going to try and meet this
Taiwan on Saturday. Didn't even really
like her that much, but you know, it was
something to do. See, even it's not even
the fact that you like people and you
can't get laid. It's just them and what they do.
It's toxic. It is so toxic, you know.
So, um that's that.
I'm definitely getting a Samsung Galaxy
Fold 8 when it comes out next year. I'm
not going to get the seven. I could buy
the seven, but nah, there's not going to
be no difference between [ __ ]
a year difference. So, I'm going to get
the eight. Should be out in July.
Yeah, he's a virgin. Nonsense is a
virgin. Bomb's a virgin.
Yeah, there's loads of virgins.
Absolute virgins we call him on this
channel. Absolute virgins.
You're an absolute virgin. You like that
one, Mr. B?
Yeah. And that Jamie Thompson's a virgin
as well. That fat ugly freak if you've seen him.
Bomb's a virgin. Nons legs is a virgin. Yep. Yeah.
Yeah. Bomb's a complete virgin.
Bomb has kids, though. No, he doesn't.
No, he doesn't have kids. That was made
up. No, he doesn't. Have you Have you
seen these kids? Have you met these
kids? What's their names? What do they look like?
Really? What What do these kids look
like? What's their names? Where do they live? Bro,
tell us. Tell everyone. We want to know,
bro. What do these kids look like?
What's their names? Are they all right?
Where do they live?
So you don't know he's got kids then. So
there you go. No. Yeah.
N is a virgin. That's why we call him
virgin boy. But we call him a copycat.
He's a little copycat.
I'm going to ask my sister, right, if we
can rename the cat um after his name.
It's just so many similarities every
every time, right?
Yeah. Nongs is a virgin as well.
It's not just Timmy Eldridge. It's NonGS
is a virgin as well. And bomb. Um every
time, right, I go to my sisters, the the
cat attacks me, Mr. B,
and it tries like hitting me and stuff
and it keeps like meowing and stuff.
He's because I don't like Sher Cole.
The cat's calling me gay and stuff. So
that's why I don't go much anymore
because the cat like go for me and
stuff. And he says if I don't like um
come I'm I'm gay because he's a little
copycat. Yeah. He's got a disabled bird
that he's never had sex with. Yeah.
Yeah. A disabled girl that he's never
had sex with. Yes. We've been over this
a million times and I'm not doing it
again. Right. It's funny how I don't see
you defending me when he calls me a
virgin even though I put a porno up
there. [ __ ] off you little nons lover.
Yeah, I don't see you on them community
post when I used to go that channel
talking about how how the porno that I
put up the women's beds that I was
sleeping in. You [ __ ] little nonslover.
You [ __ ] little nonslver. [ __ ] out of here, bro.
Yeah, I have never seen you in any of
these community posts, so don't [ __ ]
sit here and try and tell me because
he's got a disabled gal, he's not a
virgin. [ __ ] suck my dick, you [ __ ] non-slber.
I hate biased people in this community, Mark.
I hate biased people on this [ __ ] community.
Does my nothing, bro. [ __ ] does my
nothing. So someone that's got a
disabled girlfriend can not be a virgin.
There's no way they can be a virgin.
There's no way in hell that they can be
a virgin. There's no way. Even though
they sit on YouTube all day stalking
someone stalks people sloppy seconds,
there's no way that person can be a virgin.
But somebody that's proved they've had
sex can be a virgin. Someone's someone
that's put a porno on YouTube can be a
virgin. Yeah. [ __ ] illiterate [ __ ]
simpletons. [ __ ] off you little
non-slubbers, bro. Get off of my
channel. Go back to your [ __ ] boyfriend's channel.
Boyfriend's channel, bro. [ __ ] mad.
Yeah, I've never had a shag. Well, I've
already put a porno out there. So,
again, go back to your boyfriend's
channel since you love nons so much.
Yeah, even though I proved I've had sex.
Nons lovers. Hen was right about these
people. They're nonsvers on here. Joe F.
You know this guy right here, they love
nonsense. You know what you you you you
you'll laugh about, right, is that these
people, right, will have a problem with
me and Monty. And I don't even like
Monty because of like [ __ ] that that
we've said and stuff. They've done it to
Monty, but an actual pedophile, an actual pedo, right?
An actual pedo that they'll have no
problems with. Don't you find that mad or ask?
Don't you think that's a bit mad?
Uh, what did I prove? I proved I've had
sex many times, which you have seen many
times. Like I said, go back to your boyfriend's channel.
This is what I mean with these little
[ __ ] biased nons, bro. Han was right
about them. Yeah,
it's true though, Mr. B. It's true. It's
true. It is honestly true. It's mad.
They actually love nonsense on here,
bro. They actually do. They actually love them.
Actually do. I proved I've had sex many,
many, many times and you still sit there
and call me a virgin. That doesn't even
make any sense. The conversation doesn't
even make any sense. But somebody
because they've got a disabled
girlfriend can't possibly be a virgin.
Okay, bro. Okay, whatever you say.
You know, it's mad.
You're little nods lovers. That's what
you are. You little nods lovers.
You know, that's what makes me think
it's jealousy. That's what makes me
think like it is jealousy on here,
Greavesy. Because all of these people,
right, are saying that they've got a
problem with you because of things that
you've said. Yeah.
things that you've said, right? Yeah.
But when someone's an actual pedophile,
they don't have no problems with it.
This is what I mean. They're nons
lovers. They're nonsers on here, bro.
I'm telling you, they're proper proper pedos.
They're pedo lovers.
They're proper proper pedos on here, bro.
You can tell they're proper pedophiles. Proper pedos.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Pure and untouched.
Yeah. You keep saying yourself that,
man. Go back to your boyfriend's channel.
The one that's had sex with his disabled
girlfriend apparently. Okay, bro. Whatever.
Even when you prove these little
[ __ ] that you got more money than
them and you've banged more women than
them, they still talk [ __ ] It's madness.
Even when you prove that you've got more
money than them, you prove that you're
better looking than them, you prove that
you've had sex and they haven't, they
still talk [ __ ] [ __ ] mad, isn't it?
Yeah. No worries.
Yeah, I'll show the screenshots of the
Taiwan. The Taiwan what she done
yesterday as well
trying to take the piss.
But all women aren't the same. Remember,
all women are not the same.
Only a virgin would say that.
[ __ ] non legs are zas and red star.
Two absolute virgins.
Absolute virgins. [laughter]
They're absolute virgins, mate.
He says, "You know full well that I've
had sex. I know full to the belly that
you're still a virgin." This is why I
call you one, because you are one. And I
know you're better than you know
yourself. And you've never had sex and
you're still a virgin. And you can show
a disabled girl all you want. You will
die a virgin.
Why do you not believe escort stories?
Think about it. Ras, right? If you was
meeting someone and they told you that
they had sex with an escort, you would
you believe it? I mean, I would believe
it. No one, no one else ever disbelieved
it but him because he is the virgin. So,
he was not going to be happy until he
had confirmation that you're a virgin
like him. That's what they do, mate.
That's what autistic people do.
You know, who the [ __ ] doesn't believe a
[ __ ] someone's got a [ __ ] escort?
It's just it I've never known anyone to
lie about using an escort. That's
[ __ ] mad. You absolute virgin.
That man, who the [ __ ] lying about you a
[ __ ] escort, man?
He's make up all of these excuses that
escorts ask for ID and stuff.
I think it's Pat Mustard.
Whoever it is, is a fat ugly bastard.
Have you seen his fingers when he was
showing his uh when he was showing his
all benefit money? Did you see them fat fingers?
If you look carefully, bro, you'll see
them big [ __ ] cumbling sausage
fingers. Another one. Fat and ugly. Oh
my [ __ ] god. I can see why they do
what they do now every day. Cuz they're
fat, ugly disabled people that ain't got a life.
And you see these [ __ ] cumbling
sausage fingers. Fat ugly bastard.
I told you everything that I say about
these people on here is right, bro. I
was right about bomb.
I mean, I don't go on their channels anymore.
I don't go on these uh I don't go on
their channels anymore. I haven't been
on them for a couple of weeks. Will
never go on it ever again. Do you know
why or ask? I don't go on virgin channels.
My channel was a no virgin zone. So, I
don't go on virgin channels, mate.
Keyboard warriors. We will never go on
it ever again.
I will never ever go on it ever again. Never.
Is Peter Belly smart, matey? Yeah.
There go that virgin channel.
Oh, so he's seen he's seen the message. Grezy. Uh, no reply.
He said it 10 minutes ago. No reply.
He's not so big after all, is he?
I message him again.
Let's have a debate about this. Question mark.
Oh, he's just Oh, he's just seen it
again. So, he must still be on a
Well, we don't think you're going to be
able to to see it because it's not been made yet.
Are you sure the film exists?
Are you sure the film exists? Squeezy,
are you sure the film exists?
Basically telling them my experiences
and how women lead people on and they're toxic narcissists.
Um, and that I'm unbiased and I've got
no reason to say something if I don't
believe it. I'm not an incel. I'm not a
white knight. I'm not a s. I'm completely unbiased.
I don't think you're going to be able to
see the film, Grezy, because it doesn't exist.
That's okay. I'll just wait.
You'll you'll you'll wait. Yes. Until
it's been made. Oh, bro. I think that
I'm looking for a woman with the name
uh Lindsay Williams.
Any any age range? Uh just anywhere from
37 to 38 because at my age you can't be
picky. You You see?
Oh, that was funny, bro. I'm looking Do
you remember that one? I'm looking for
um a birthday present for a man who's 60
five who he hates cats and dogs.
He's bloody ignoring me now.
He's bloody ignoring me now, matey. >> [snorts] >> Yeah,
Monty man's getting sent down um on the
on the 27th.
What do you think about that? He's
getting [laughter] sent down.
Oh, now he's gone quiet. Now Lex's gone
They're all big until they meet their match,
aren't they, Greasy? They're all big,
these [ __ ] until until Peter Benny
comes their way, is it?
Yeah, they're all well and big until
they meet their match.
What do you think about that, Grimsy?
So, what you're telling me? Yeah, if
Monty gets sent down, it's over the same
website you can watch Little Britain on, Greasy. [laughter] Nah,
it was It was YouTube, was it? It was It
was all YouTube, was it?
Like the like the like the platform, wasn't it? Yeah,
I'll [ __ ] your mom.
I won't do [ __ ] all, but I'll [ __ ] your mom.
Why don't you go back to [ __ ] Nons's
channel? Go back to your boyfriend's
channel, you little nonsleg lover. Go
back to your boyfriend's channel, you
little [ __ ] and go and suck his
You little weasel. Go back on your
little boyfriend's channel.
on your little nonskin boyfriend channel.
We don't want your kind here.
Stay alive. Ah,
go back to your boyfriend channel.
Yeah, but Grey, he's not um
he's not um he's not in court over
YouTube, is he?
He's not going to call over YouTube, is he? [laughter]
I don't think it was. Was it?
It's like some writing thing.
It's [laughter] some It's some writing thing though. Mom. Ah.
So what? The same website you can watch Spongebob on. [laughter]
What? The same website you can watch
Spongebob on. [laughter]
[snorts and clears throat] Really greasy.
It's always [ __ ] YouTube, isn't it? [laughter]
It's always YouTube.
[ __ ] hell. Mad. Yeah.
I've almost finished my popcorn
because he's already remember.
So why is [ __ ] Lex backed out now,
the [ __ ] idiot?
But you know all of these accounts
coming in mocking me greasy right I
brought it on myself in it because if I
didn't say about this mama stuff and
whatever they wouldn't have known about
it would they
just copying things that I've said in it
they're just copying things that I've
said in it really
Yeah, cuz think about it. If you didn't
say any of these things, they wouldn't
they wouldn't have anything to say in it. Really?
It's like when Ant-Man says that he's in
Thailand and these women are given attitude, right?
He says that there's nothing Asian about
them. When they're westernizing that and
they give attitude, he says he says to
them, "There's nothing Asian about you."
And I'll like copy it because it's
funny. I'll be a little copycat.
Yeah. I'll be like, um, there's nothing
Asian about you.
There's nothing Asian about you. That's
a good one, though, isn't it? Yeah.
He says that he says as soon as a woman
can get her hands on a smartphone,
Greavesy, it's bad because they become westernized.
He says in Thailand even the women there
were talking like bruh and stuff like proper westernized.
That's the worst thing that happened to
society is [ __ ] Tik Tok and
Instagram. They're all NPCs.
They're all [ __ ] NPCs, is it?
Oh, okay. He's replied back saying, "I
don't think you realize it's never been
a debate, but sure. I'm on TikTok all
the time. You're more than welcome to request.
Okay, I'm going to go on there at like 5:00 p.m.
Okay. 5:00 p.m. Oh, so now he's saying
it's not a debate. So now he's [ __ ]
it. Okay, I I I'll join at about 5:00 p.m. Yeah.
So now he's saying that it's not a debate.
So he shhat his knickers.
So now we shhat his [ __ ] underpants. Copycat. [ __ ] copycat.
A stray cat. Every time I see cat, it
just makes me think of him. He's a little copycat.
He's a little copycat. Wants to fit in
with the crowd. That's him. We wanted to
fit in. That's cute, isn't it?
I just asked him, "Man, will you be
live?" He's a little copycat.
He's a little copycat. He's a little
I hate cats.
What about you, Grezy? I hate [ __ ]
cats, man. You
I hate cats. You're a little copycat.
He's a little copycat. So, why did Nons
say, "If I don't find Sher Cole
attractive, I'm gay." Greavves. Is it
because he wanted to fit in?
He wanted to fit in with the crowd.
He wanted to fit in, didn't he?
Sad little bastard. Yeah.
Bless him then if he didn't want to feel
left out. We he might have just not
wanted to feel left out.
Oh, that's cute. Is it?
Yeah, it's cute.
He didn't want to feel left out. A little copycat. Little copycat. [laughter]
I will I I'll wait
until it's been made. Madness.
He hates cats and dogs.
Do you remember? Do you remember
Margaret? I don't have any arms and legs.
Can you come down and help us with this customer?
Can you come down, Margaret? I don't
have any arms or legs.
Remember that one? Yeah.
I'll just start by saying I've got a
bone to pick with you.
I've got a bloody bone to pick with you, mate. Yep.
I've got a t-bone to pick with you. >> [laughter]
>> Oh, bless. He didn't want to feel left out.
So, you think that's cute, Grezy? He
said that if I don't find Chev
attractive, I'm gay. He didn't want to
feel left out. Bless him. Oh,
you think that's quite sweet? He didn't
want to feel that he wanted to fit in
with the crowd,
you know. It must be it must be you know
hard being new
know to like a college or a school and
you know anything to fit in you know
anything to fit in with a crowd. [laughter]
He's a little copycat.
He's a cat with green eyes. [laughter]
What a loser.
Oh, he said 7:30 p.m.
his time, isn't it? So, he's 5 hours, right?
But don't forget, he's probably like 5
hours behind us, isn't he? He said 7:30,
which will be like [ __ ] 10:30.
Oh, he's from the UK. Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay. See you there. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Okay. See you there, Captain.
I just wrote to him saying, "I'll see
you there, Captain.
I've got a [ __ ] bone to pick with
him, you know.
Get the popcorn ready, Rosie,
and the McDonald's Coke. I've had a
bloody enough of this [ __ ] you know.
I've had a bloody enough of this bastard. Little copy. Little copycat.
That's how they That's what they do in it
because cat do you know where they you
know cats they copy?
Did you not know that with cats, right? They copy.
Yeah, I know. He's Yeah, now he's met
me. He's met his match, isn't it? He's
met his match.
>> That's what cats do. They copy each other.
Have you ever seen that? They copy each other.
They copy each other. Oh, you're a copycat.
You bloody copycat.
I hate cats.
I hate [ __ ] cats. You little copycat.
You little copy cat.
You like cats, is it?
Little stray cats. >> Yeah. [ __ ] virgin.
Yeah. I said, "Okay, see you there, Captain.
Who do you reckon is going to win? Me or him?" Grievesy.
And I'm going to say, "I've had a bloody
enough of these women, these [ __ ] women."
No, I won't say [ __ ] I'll be like,
I've had a bloody enough of these women
leading people on,
you know, and I keep hearing about your
name every time I go live.
I think I've got Tik Tok, actually. I know.
Yeah, I think I've got Tik Tok.
I'm going to eat him alive
cuz I've had a bloody enough of it.
I've had a [ __ ] I've had enough with this [ __ ] defending women. Little copycat.
Okay, I'll say to him, um, yeah, I've
got a bone to pick with you. I hear that
you like defending women for the sake of
defending women, and I'm going to tell
him about my experiences. Yeah. [snorts]
Yeah, I need to go pee pee. Oh, where do
I pee, Greasy?
Where do I pee? You know where I pee. Oh gosh, no.
Oh, the sink.
In the sink. Oh, no. Lost. Oh, lovely.
You know when you just when when you
have to go to when you have to pee
before you go to bed we usually it's
lovely isn't it? Yeah.
We have to go wee wee. [laughter] You bloody.
You're a little copycat.
You little copycat.
So would you say that is copying then Greavesy?
If you say that you don't find Sher Co
attractive, you're gay. Is that copying?
It's copying, isn't it? >> [laughter]
>> Yeah, I used to peek um on the carpets.
So, is it actually copying then music?
Why is it copying? [clears throat]
[laughter] What makes you say it's coffee?
[laughter] What makes you say it's been a copycat?
Why is it being a copycat? a bit.
Thy show is like she's definitely
attractive. Definitely a
little your little copycat.
Yeah, definitely is. Yeah. Of course,
someone just sound like a copycat statement. [laughter] Yeah.
Yeah. He's a little copycat. You don't
want to feel left out.
You don't want to feel left out.
The little virgin. Yeah.
Cuz it's not even like they said, "Oh, I
find her attractive." They literally
said that you're gay if you don't find her attractive.
Yeah. I've been with more women than
this country will ever be. Obviously,
he's still a virgin. So, that's not
saying much, but you know what I mean.
Used to do Beyonce. Yeah.
It's just a little copycat.
Just a little copycat.
A copycat statement. Gy. [laughter]
That's a good one. That one. It just
sounds like a copycat statement. [laughter]
Oh, I like that one. I like that one. [laughter]
A copycat statement. Bloody hell. [laughter] Copycat. Little copycat.
It's the namely it's the name. It's not
the person. It's the name. [laughter]
Yeah. They said that you're homo. You
give off gay vibes if you don't find her attractive.
>> I didn't know I was gay. It's news to
me. I didn't know I like dick. No,
I've never ever I never knew I liked it,
mate, until I had it confirmed to me by
a little out London virgin
on the ground a month.
I didn't know that. I didn't know that, mate.
I wish he could come and type on there
and and and tell us why he feel the need
to be a copycat.
You know why you feel the need to copy?
Tell me easy. [laughter]
It just sounds like a copycat saving. [laughter]
What is that? Okay.
And your point is Yeah.
[ __ ] hate cats. I do.
No, I've never liked cats.
Oh, what are you having for dinner today, Reevesy? I'm having
I don't know what I'm having, bro.
Maybe a Chinese. Yeah.
[snorts] Triple H said that his birthday
is in January.
Oh, that's cute, isn't it?
Oh, what are you going to have a takeaway later?
Yeah, Trip H didn't come back last
night, did he? No.
Imagine your birthday being in January.
What would you even do on your birthday
if your birthday's in January? you
I don't know what do you do January
I mean you got for a drink I guess but
no one will be out would I
well you only live once Greaves I'm
getting one today takeaway but I'm not sure what
maybe yeah probably Chinese to be
Do you like the month January, Grezy?
Yeah. Do you like the month January? Really?
Why is that? Because it's like cold and
there's nothing to do. Yeah.
What about February? Do you like
February is okay.
But you know, Valent um Valentine's
Day is February.
The day to make fun out of people that
ain't wanted by no one. Greasy. Let's
poke fun out of the men that ain't
chosen by nobody, you know. Yeah. Yeah. basically.
So, you still watch that N Matthews
then, don't you? Um, Greasy,
he gets kicked out the parties and
stuff. Have you seen He gets kicked out the parties? Yeah. Yeah,
I get what you mean. Yeah.
Well, bless you then, Rosie. Bless you.
Franklin's on his little quad bike. Grezy. Oh,
what do you think of that?
Yeah. These are these little quad bikes.
Stick his middle finger up. Yep.
No bless you then.
I don't know whe to have a Chinese today
or something else. Squeezy. Do doctor [snorts]
I don't really fancy KFC G You see? Yeah. Oh gosh.
Why am I the only channel that you go
on, Greavves? I think you're just mocking me.
I think you just come on here to mock me.
Oh, you're not mocking me, are you? Huh?
Please don't tell me you're mocking me.
What what do you reckon would happen if
I went to Italy, Greavves, and I tried
to date in Italy? Nah,
no chance, is it?
No chance, matey.
What would you honestly say the hardest
country is, Greasy, to date in? I'd say Italy.
I'd say Italy or France. What would you say?
Yeah. Like hard, isn't it?
Nah, bro. It's hard. They're stuck up Italians.
They're [ __ ] They're like the
worst women I've met. I think Italians,
they've all been [ __ ] They've all been [ __ ] [ __ ]
All the Italian women I've ever met have
been [ __ ] [ __ ] Absolute [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
I said to Antman, "What do you think
will happen if I go out approaching in a
club?" And he says, "Well, you'll
probably meet people that say they've
got boyfriends or they're not looking to
date yet they're in a nightclub. Just
the same old really.
Is he lying? Greasy.
I'm getting a fold eight next summer, so
I'm going to save £100 every month. Grievy,
is that okay with you, boss?
If I save £100 every month, I'm going to
buy the iPhone soon,
but then I'm going to save £100 a month
for next year's fold.
Okay, with you, boss.
Yeah, I just save £100 a month.
Should be good by then.
Is that okay with you, Captain?
Cuz you're obviously my financial
advisor, aren't you?
You're my financial advisor, aren't you, Grezy?
So, again, I need to run it by you.
So what I can get I can get this I can
get the fold eight next year.
It'll be about 15,600 pound. Is that okay?
Grezy. Yeah. Okay.
Thank you boss.
Do you remember Grezy? That not okay
with me boss. That's not okay with me
That's not okay with me boss.
I'm running out of [ __ ] streamyard
minutes here, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, they're doing monthly. Yeah,
but I'll need to delete my I'll need to
delete the account on here and make
another one because if you keep making ones
if you keep making new emails, bro, they
say that you got too many destinations
and then you won't be able to go live again
unless you delete um so obviously I'm
using my mom's email.
So after this one, I'll have to delete
the destination and make a new email. If
I don't delete the destination, I can't
go live on here again. What happens? [ __ ]
If that makes sense. So yeah.
Okay with you, boss.
I'll never ever see you again.
Yo, not invitations better be on, lad,
cuz I'm going to put this [ __ ] in his place later.
So, do you reckon this phone will still
work in 4 years? Grezy,
this Samsung fold
that I've got. I think it will, you know. Yep.
4 years. The battery still seems healthy.
I've had it a Yeah, I think almost a
year now. Grieves. I've had it
almost a year. Yeah.
Still seems fast.
The screen is just a bit [ __ ] Yeah,
the screen's a bit [ __ ]
You reckon it will still work in four years? [ __ ] flagship
I'll be back later.