I just woke up. [ __ ] you up. Peace.
Oh my god.
mate, Gary guess you never guess who messaged me
yesterday wanted to
[ __ ] wanted to come over that
19year-old. They all come at once, don't
they, bro? You messaged me again.
Oh my goodness.
None of them can, mate. They all come
running back. Yeah, I got a Janipino
pizza. I was waiting [ __ ] two hours
for the [ __ ] The delivery driver kept cancelling it,
bro. Yeah, you can't be a nice jalapeno.
Filipinos. Yeah, I woke up. I went to
sleep. I woke up, bro. I was trying to
get rid of the [ __ ]
um Yeah, I sleep with the hangover off.
It kind of work to be
fair. Yeah, they always come back to
Peter Benny, don't they? Where is
that? Let go of Peter
Belly. The house wasn't too far above.
They kept C. It wasn't too far. It was
like 10 minutes away, but there was no
delivery driver, so they just gave me
another one for
free. Which, let's be fair, who's going
to eat two [ __ ] pizzas? Yeah, I was
in the mood yesterday, man. I was like,
what do I get,
bro? Chinese Indian or like a pizza? And
I had a pizza for ages, so I just had a pizza.
No bad [ __ ] McDonald's coke.
Oh, time do you call this, man? What
time do you call this, buddy? coming
So, I don't know if it
does. Yeah, especially when you're that
Virgin's area. Hey Gary. Hey. Hey
Gary. I bet it's no fun, is it? Almost
being 30 and still a virgin. E
Gary. Hey buddy.
I was on Lord Days
earlier. They were self
conjecting. Nah, bro. Don't little
self-reflectors. That's what I call
that. the self-reflecting side of YouTube.
Skin that your
skin is not good for your mental health,
lad. It's not good for your mental
health talking about yourself like that, bro. Is
it? It's not good to talk about yourself
like that. I might get a banana milkshake for
McDonald's. I ain't had a milkshake for ages, man.
You're going to [ __ ] die
of you virgin
virgin. You [ __ ] virgin.
Yeah, the milkshakes come all like slushy, don't
they? Yeah. I'm not going to get a
milkshake, man. I got a dry
mouth. Got to see this American today,
bro. Oh, man.
Not some madness, but it's kind of late.
So, I mean,
perhaps be a bit
different. It might be better today cuz
it's it's late. So,
I don't know, man. I'm [ __ ] [ __ ]
bro. There we go. Oh yeah, man. Sorry
about that. Oh [ __ ]
You know, do you not understand that
that's why you drink on Thursdays? You
drink on Thursdays, buddy? Because you
might meet a woman on um you might meet
a woman on a Thursday and then you go
out the Saturday, you
see? And then you'll be prepared for the
Saturday. If you go out Friday, you'll
still be [ __ ] Saturday because of the
drinking. So, when you go out Thursdays,
it gives you like two days to
recover. It gives you a good two days to
recover, you see?
And you're not
[ __ ] When you go out Friday, you try
to go out Saturday, you're too
[ __ ] [ __ ] hanging,
bro. [ __ ] [ __ ] [Music] virgin. Yeah.
[ __ ] She called that guy. Peter
B. She can't get those. Why is Peter
Benny going to be getting more [ __ ] Huh?
That'll piss the virgin off. Is that right,
Gary? That'll piss the virgin off.
The virgin's not awake at this time. So
uh can't stop me.
Just finish off, bro.
I just got pissed, bro. One sec.
Oh, I'm [ __ ] hungry, man.
So maybe Peter from America might not be
off the cards, bro.
Oh, it's not good for your mental health,
lad. It's not Yeah, I'm [ __ ] bro. I'm
still hanging, bro, for [ __ ] But I'll
be all right,
though. I'll be okay, man. By by the
time the tomorrow hits, I'll be all
right. I just ordered a McDonald's
milkshake. That's why, Ben, you go out
drinking on That's why you go out
drinking on Wednesday or you go out
drinking on Thursday in case you meet
someone and you have to meet them
Saturday. If you go out drinking on
Friday, you'll be [ __ ] on Sat You'll
still be [ __ ] on Saturday, man. See,
I'm not stupid, man. I had a Japino
pizza. Oh yeah, I could raise a
baby. Yeah, I got to see this American today.
That 19year-old messaged
me. Ben, that 19year-old messaged me.
It's like when they come, they all come
at once. I noticed that, bro, with these
[ __ ] When one comes, they all come at
once. They're proper [ __ ] up, man. I
swear. I've not had a banana milkshake for
ages. Literally. Yeah, like
buses. Yeah, it was [ __ ] Ben. Man, I
went out on Thursday, right? I went to
this club. All I got was, "Oh, I've got
a boyfriend. I've got a boyfriend. I've
got a boyfriend." Like four times, bro.
I didn't get nothing. And then as soon
as I went out the street and done one, I
got somewhere. It's a madness, isn't it?
I was with them for like an hour, bro.
And I have to meet them again today.
It's a madness.
It's such a
madness. It's mad how it works, eh? It's
the complete opposite to what people tell
you. Yeah, I did. Do I about like four,
bro? I swear to
God. Yeah, my nose is [ __ ] because of
that [ __ ] fan that need to turn off.
Okay with you,
boss. Oh, that means you should go out
cold approaching with me, buddy. Yeah. [ __ ]
hell. I'm still kind of hanging though.
I'll be I'll I'll be all right
later. Yeah, the 19year-old wanted to come over
then. She was asking if she could come
over. I'm sure she's got [ __ ] bipolar,
bro. Uh, you know, no one ever lets go
of Peter Benny fully, you know. Nah.
They do with Virgin Sea
though. They do with Virgin
Sea. Yeah, you can,
man. I'm [ __ ] bro. I swear I'm
[ __ ] It's not even a joke.
man. Say what you want. Oh, you you
asked if I
could. Yeah, I could raise a baby
Ben. There's this French one I'm meeting
very soon as well, Ben. And I was going
to name the baby baby
Pierre from Paris with his little frog baby girl.
Then what's your opinion on that? I' I'd
stick him in a French uh in a in a in a
frog baby grow with a little class on
and stick him up the Eiffel Tower. Ah,
what a lovely
site. What a lovely
site, Ben. What a lovely
site, you know. That's a lovely site, Ben.
Yeah, I remember I went out with my
friend J last Friday. He said, "I can't
go any further. I'm [ __ ]
mate." From drinking the night before.
He said, "No, I'm
fucked." No, I don't want to fall in
love. I just want a baby.
Ben, bro. Oh. H.
Uh because I think it would be cute and
I would get more benefits.
Ben, you can't. I need a milkshake. [ __ ] Yeah,
mate. Your little ways, baby.
Oh yeah. Hopefully it doesn't taste like
[ __ ] today. It shouldn't do cuz um uh
it's quite late so hopefully it's not that
busy. Yeah. I've not had a banana
milkshake for [ __ ] ages, man. That's
my favorite one. I don't like the um chocolate
one. My mom likes the chocolate one, but
I I think It's too
bitter. I think it's too bitter
me. Bless you,
mate. Bless you. [Music] That's the
level. Oh [ __ ]
bro. I I I kind of thought that you all
was going to come back. I did and I
didn't at the same time. I don't
know like two minds you
No. Everything's safe. Oh
[ __ ] Run this.
play. Come on.
on. Hope you don't tell me to [ __ ] die.
Lovely lovely jalapeno pizza for papa. Oh,
But yeah, nothing surprising me anymore.
The only thing that would realistically
surprise me, mate, is if he actually
lost his replay, lost his virginity.
That's that's the only thing that would actually surprise
me. Yeah, he finally loses his virginity.
He really pops that
[ __ ] When he pops that [ __ ] finally gets
laid. I think he would do the world of good getting
laid. I think that would do the world of
good if he if he actually lost his virginity.
Do you think be a much nicer person,
much happier, more
compet, you know what I'm saying? Yeah.
[ __ ] Catching the
cold. I don't Come on,
man. Give me this [ __ ] milkshake.
shorts. That's what I'll be wearing tomorrow is
Jalapenos. Probably some fresh cut
jalapenos. I just really fancy the
pizza. Like a really jarapillo pizza. I
like pizza, but I have to be in the mood for
it. That's good after drinking. It's
good before drinking as well. I'd
probably say peach is one of the best things. And
curry really good,
man. I was even going to get a Chinese
curry, an Indian curry or pizza.
You're going to [ __ ] die virgin.
Oh, you're a [ __ ] [ __ ]
virgin. You're going to [ __ ]
die. You're going to [ __ ] die. diabate.
I caught my [ __ ] finger. Talk.
Why is it taking so long,
man? Can't be that [ __ ] busy at
[ __ ] 1:00 in the [ __ ] morning.
There's no way that busy at 1:00 in the [ __ ] morning, mate. No [Music]
way. See how much drinking [ __ ] you up, lad. Okay, heat.
Yeah, she came back, man. She missed
Peter Belly's dick in
it. That's what it was,
Ben. Miss Peter Belly's dick. Come
on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come
on. How long would it take, mate? It's a
[ __ ] milkshake. [ __ ] sake, man.
Anyone chat? Anyone texting? No.
Well, I'm going in a minute cuz no one's
typing. Oh, man. Oh,
[ __ ] want to be that [ __ ] virgin. Virgin
SH be that Virgin
S. Don't be that little [ __ ] virgin
then. That little
virgin. That's what no matter how bad
life may seem, right, life could always
be worse. You could be like that Orington
virgin. Could be like that Orington
virgin. I really suck
then. Couldn't imagine being 30 and
still I couldn't imagine it. I really
Well, I'm out of here anyway. See you later.