[ __ ] absolute losers, mate. You
[ __ ] dropped me. You didn't even let
me [ __ ] talk and then you [ __ ]
muted me, you [ __ ] idiot.
What the [ __ ] bro?
Madness. They didn't even let me [ __ ]
speak to that [ __ ] stupid Scottish
They just [ __ ] labeled you the same
[ __ ] names, bro, and then [ __ ]
muted you. Mad.
Mad. [ __ ] mad, bro. Bro, it wasn't a
good effort. They They didn't let me
talk. She just literally spoke over me.
Like literally spoke over me, you know?
So, there was no point in it,
you know. So they literally just shouted
over me, bro, at one point. So I would
have ate her alive if she would let me
talk. I would have ate her alive. I'd
said, "Listen, yeah, you're using the
word [ __ ] incel and misogyny again
because you're losing. That's the only
way you can think you can win an
argument, bro. They just kick people.
That's you know what I'm saying?" Yeah.
I want I want to know that [ __ ]
woman's [ __ ] Instagram. I want to
know that woman's Instagram. I'll have a
one-on-one with [ __ ] her, bro. But
get her on my live stream right now,
bro. And I won't kick anyone. I won't
kick any [ __ ] Get on my [ __ ] live
stream now. The [ __ ] stupid Scottish
car. Yeah, I couldn't even get a [ __ ]
word in, you know. And that just goes to
show I've won the fact that you had to
mute me and talk over me, [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
And they're trying to say that's that
they're idiots. They're absolute [ __ ]
well idiots, bro. That's that's that's
what they [ __ ] are. Yeah.
Yeah. Tell me uh Tik Tok. I'll message
her, bro, if you you if you can find her.
Yeah. And I was going to say the women
women that what women go through. Yeah.
Because of the men that you continuously
keep going for. If you would let me
[ __ ] finish, [ __ ] idiot.
Yeah. Yeah. What you have to put up with
for the because of the men that you keep
going for, idiot.
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. I would have
[ __ ] ate her apart, bro. If she
wasn't talking over me. Mad. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, I got her. I got her. I got her.
One second. I just went I just went on
his podcast. One sec.
Is it going to let me message her?
Right. Yeah. Hold on, hold on, hold on,
hold on. Yeah, I've got her. I've got
her. I've got her, bro. But I don't
think it's going to let me message her.
Let me try and find her on Instagram. Little coward
talking over me. The stupid little
[ __ ] Yeah, I'm going to message her, bro.
Yeah, let me try and find her Instagram.
I've got a Tik Tocky, but I don't think
it will let me message her.
Message her, bro. Come on. Let's have
it. Come on.
Yeah, I'll just whip her ass, bro. Yeah.
They say it was never a debate, mate.
She was talking over me, bro. She was
[ __ ] talking over me.
She was [ __ ] talking over me.
Yeah. No, it's not even about
experiences, bro. I'll tell her about
herself. Answer me some things then, you
[ __ ] stupid idiot.
>> There's her [ __ ] Instagram. Go. Let
me try and find her on Instagram, bro.
That's annoying me, bro. One sec. Yeah.
Would you say I beat them, Grezy?
Would you say that I beat them?
trying to say that's not leading someone
on. And you saw all the little [ __ ]
simps trying to say, "Oh, they changed
their mind. They changed their mind."
Oh, bro, my point proven even [ __ ]
more, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, but she kept [ __ ] talking over me.
Yeah, I made some decent points, but
they they wouldn't let me talk in the end.
[ __ ] bro. Absolute [ __ ]
Yeah. And I would say to her, I would
and I I would say I would say, listen,
listen. I would say, listen, you talk
about going through [ __ ] with men, right?
Yeah. And I was going to say to her,
"Yes, you do. The men that you choose."
Yeah. I'll put her in a [ __ ] place,
bro. One second. Where is this [ __ ] Instagram?
Yeah, it's private. It's private. It is
private. Let me try and see if I can
find her on um Instagram.
What's her name again?
>> Kitty. Yeah, she might have Instagram.
She don't even have Instagram. So, you
come you come on a [ __ ] thing, right?
Talk over people, right? Talk over
people and think that you've won. Yeah.
And you don't even let someone say
anything back. You stupid little feminist [ __ ]
Yeah. Where is it, bro? Where is it?
She needs to accept. I need to I can't
message her, bro.
Yeah, I know her username. I've got her
username. I don't know if she's got
Instagram, though. Let me see.
I've got I've got her on Tik Tok, but
it's not letting me message her.
Rainy day and rain.
You can tell she's a proper proper feminist.
So, everyone that makes valid points hates women.
Yeah. Okay. So, we cuz we don't suck up
to women, we hate women. Is that is that
your logic? Yeah.
Yeah. I've got it, bro. I can't Yeah,
she ain't got Instagram, so I can't
message her. What a coward. What a [ __ ] coward.
Yeah, don't forget the S as well.
Nah, she's a coward, bro. She's a [ __ ] coward.
I would have absolutely [ __ ] I would
have I would I would have wrecked them,
bro. Trust me, I would have wrecked her.
Oh, what women have to go through. I I
can tell you why you women go for that.
It's because of the men that you so
habited keep seeking out and then
generalizing all men based on the men
that you go for. Yeah, trust me. She's
not going to want one-on-one with me,
bro. You know, that guy had more of a
chance of winning.
And then he was trying to backtrack what he said. Yeah. So,
yeah. Get get her on YouTube. Try to get
her on YouTube. She's more than welcome to join.
She's more than welcome to join, bro.
Get her on it. She can join. She's more
than welcome here. No kicking, no
[ __ ] no nothing. We don't kick on
my channel, bro. If somebody wants a
debate, whether I win or lose.
No, we were just on TikTok
arguing with Lex.
Yeah. And did you see all of their
little squeezes? Oh, she uh uh
did you hear
did you hear uh
Did you hear the little simps? Oh, maybe
she changed her mind.
Yeah, they were all making excuses, bro.
Yeah. What? You change your mind. And
they were trying to say, "Oh, that's not
leading someone on. That's not leading
someone on." How is that not leading
someone on? I used it as an example. So,
what you giving your number to someone,
right, and constantly texting them,
asking them questions back, that's not
leading someone on. So what the [ __ ] is it?
>> You know, he could he couldn't answer
it. He knows, bro. He lost. How the [ __ ]
is that not leading someone on?
Yeah. The whole they don't owe you
anything is is a is a lame attempt to
cover up their shitty behavior. He also
couldn't say anything to that either.
No, I want that [ __ ] kitty, bro. I
want that kitty.
That's who I want, bro. Yeah.
message I want.
So she's just come she's just somebody
that comes in right [ __ ] runs up her
[ __ ] mouth knowing you can't defend
yourself. What a loser. And
[clears throat] you think you're [ __ ] right.
Oh my god. Listen, Kira. Yeah. Send her
my way, mate. Send her my [ __ ] way
any day of the week. Come on. You and
her versus me. And I And it was
twoon-one. And they were still [ __ ] She
was still shouting over me. She was
So, I'm mute. I'm muted. Okay.
Yeah, I've got a Tik Tok, but she's You
can't message her.
Coward. Absolute [ __ ] coward.
She is a coward, bro. Yeah,
I'm I said I said to Lex, the first
thing I said was I'm none of these names.
Do you actually think I beat them though, Grezy?
and he was trying to like Yeah, he can't
have like he he he would have he would
have lost more. Trust me, how is he
going to win against someone that's met
more women than anyone in the world?
Think about it, bro. You're talking to
someone like me. Yeah. How are you going to win?
You know, where's this [ __ ] kitty, bro?
Yeah, I had to raise my voice because
she was shouting over me, bro. And then
he kept muting. I didn't even realize I
was on muted at one point. Yeah. Madness.
She Oh, intel misogynist. And I said,
oh, yeah. Is that is what how women get
treated? Women get treated by the men
that they choose to go for. Yeah. I'll
give you a couple of examples.
Yeah. If you want.
What do you think, Grezy? Do you think
she Do you think she stands a chance
against me oneon-one? I don't think so.
Trying to say that. I was just using
that as an example. That Taiwan. Yeah.
It was just an example. Oh, they're not
leading you on. Maybe they changed their mind.
Huh? Really? Change change their mind.
What? A lot of people change their
[ __ ] mind, don't they, mate? Don't
they? Yeah. Yeah.
Why do you [snorts] think she wouldn't
beat me, Grezy? Why not?
I need to find a way to message her, bro.
Right. I'm going to I'm going to I'm
going to um I'm going to voice note him
saying that um yeah, it was a good
debate uh you know conversation, but in
future you shouldn't allow people on if
you're just going to kick people when
you're losing the argument, you know,
and then have to resort to shouting over
someone um because it's it's ridiculous.
What's the point? What's the point of
letting someone up, right?
having a normal [ __ ]
you know, a chat then a chat and then
you're just going to shout over someone
and kick them like please send her my
way. Please, please send her my way and
I will and I will show you everything
that I write back. I mean, some people's
agreeing with me as well.
I don't know how many people's agreeing
with me, but
maybe they changed their mind. See what
I'm saying? It's always excuses. Yeah.
If you'd let me if you'd let me in
there, I would have explained. They
always make excuses,
you know. That was my that that was one
of the problems, you know. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. One sec.
That's why I wrote to him. I want to
have a chat with Kitty. Yeah. And then
you shouted over me and then you kicked
me. What the [ __ ]
He knew I who I was straight away in it.
I want to talk to that kitty.
She doesn't have Instagram. She's a
coward. She's a [ __ ] coward, mate.
Proper coward, isn't it?
I think that guy's gay, you know.
Yeah, I think that guy is [ __ ] gay.
I actually think he's gay, bro. He's
defin I think he's gay. Ain't he
kitty, mate? I want that kitty.
Yeah, that guy's definitely gay.
Of course he's gay, bro. You can tell
he's gay. You're not. Can't you tell gay
people's mannerisms? That's why probably
why he's so up women's asses because
he's never had to deal with them his
whole [ __ ] life. Yeah.
No, that's pissed me off, bro. That
really has pissed me off.
Yeah, I can't even defend myself, mate.
Uh oh, that's funny, bro. Oh, man. So,
don't forget people, I am a misogynist
because I said that someone's led me on.
That makes someone a misogynist.
Oh my god. What? Cuz stating the obvious
makes you misogynist. Really? Really, mate? Yeah.
Yeah. We need to somehow get through to
that kitty, mate.
Yeah, they denied it. Yeah, they were.
It's the same excuses. Oh, um, yeah,
maybe they've changed their mind. How is
that not leading you on? And then I
explained to him if you was not leading
somebody on, you would have stated you
would have stated your intentions. You
would have stated your intentions right
within, you know, the the first or
second message. You didn't. So, you was
leading someone [ __ ] on. You know,
it's [ __ ] obvious. You know, leave
her alone. No, I won't leave her alone.
She wanted to come in and stick her nose
in. Yeah. and shout over people because
that's the only way these people can win
a [ __ ] win a [ __ ] chat, whatever
you want to call it, argument, you know.
So, you you started it. I'll finish it.
No, I didn't say that. No, no, I didn't
say that. You're twisting my words now.
Do you see anything to suit your
narrative? Yeah. You you're you're
you're twisting my words now. Yeah.
Yeah. I said I bullied somebody into
into giving their number. No, definitely
definitely definitely definitely not.
See, they're making up stuff now. No,
I'm not threatening her. Tell her to
come here and we'll have a debate and
I'll and I will answer her questions,
right? Instead of shouting over, right,
instead of shouting over someone, right,
ask me the questions and I'll answer them
and I will answer them, you know? No
problem. We will have a we'll have a
chat because you don't like the word
debate. you don't like that and I'll
answer your questions. You had some
questions, but you didn't let me answer
them because you shouted over me. I'll
explain to you why women get treated
badly and all of these things and I and
I'll explain it to you and I will
explain it to you if you want me to, but
there's no point asking me something
then shouting over me, though I can't
answer the [ __ ] question.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. I said that she said that she
felt pressured into giving her number at
the very last message to victimize
herself. If you had let me right finish
properly. She said that she felt
pressured to victimize herself.
Duh. You know
Yeah. Exactly. You you mate, you can say
whatever you want. You lost the argument
and you know it. That's why you had to
kick me out. You can say whatever you
want. You kicked me out because you knew
what I was saying was true. Cuz let me
tell you something right now. Yeah. If
if someone's on my Streamyard and I know
I'm right, best believe no one's getting
kicked. Best believe no one's getting
kicked. Yeah. You made it 231 and you
had to shout over me because you knew I
was too intelligent for both of you.
That's what it was. 231. And guess what?
You still shouted over me.
Yeah. still shouted over me. Yeah, you
still shouted over me. If I need to do a
video, right, I will do a video and link
it to Lex and and you know since you
don't you want to kick people out
because you can't win against them,
right? That's I'll make a video for you
if you want and you can send it to your
little minion because you don't like a
you don't like you don't like having
chats that you can't that you can't win,
can you? No. No. you know, so if if you
if you need to do that and I I will explain
what you've said and I'll answer it. And
that's what I was trying to answer it,
but you kept talking over me.
You had to make it a 2v1 and you still lost.
And you still lost. Triggered. Not at
all, mate. I'm not the one kicking
people. You kicked me. I got kicked.
Yeah, they paid to kick me. Exactly.
Because they knew that what I was saying
was the truth, right? They knew what I
was saying was the was facts. That's why
you had to kick me.
Yeah. They were bored. Yeah. I'm boring.
Really? Really? I don't think so. I
really, really, really don't think so.
Yeah. I was bought. Why? Because it's
facts. and and and all of these excuses,
these same excuses over and over and
over and over and over again, people
changing their mind, ret. They said they
felt pressured into giving their number
at the very last message to victimize
themsel because if they could if they
didn't say that, they would not be a victim. Yeah.
I'm going to do a video to both of these people.
Yeah, women reject me. Exactly. This is
what I'm saying, Greavvesy. You can't
have a debate with these people because
every single time you prove them wrong
and you tell them about women's shitty
behavior, it's straight. Oh, women
rejected you. Women rejected you. They
have no they have no argument. This is
what I'm trying to say. They're so
uneducated that they don't even have an
argument. Like you, we're talking about
one thing, right? And how a woman's done
something shitty and it's straight away,
oh, women rejected you, women. It's like
you just just stick to the topic, bro.
Stick stick to what we're talking about.
You know, they can't stick to it. They
resort to making stuff up because they
knew they weren't they weren't going to
win. That's what it was, bro. Yeah.
So strange. Very, very, very strange.
I [ __ ] whoop their ass and you know
it, Greasy. I whoop their ass and you
know it. Yeah. And you [ __ ] know I
whooped their ass as well.
And you [ __ ] know it, mate. Mate, we
was just on [ __ ] Tik Tok to be
arguing with these bunch of [ __ ]
We were just arguing with these bunch of [ __ ]
Yeah, I had [ __ ] two of the [ __ ] on
me, you know?
I had two of the [ __ ] on me and I still
stood my [ __ ] ground. I don't give a Yeah,
I bet you thought, "What the fuck?"
When when you when you saw me on there,
uh, Grevy, you were thinking, "What the
[ __ ] is it?" You didn't think I was
going to go on there, [laughter] it
Where the [ __ ] was virgin boy? Where was
the skin virgin? He was [ __ ] there.
Where was the [ __ ] skin copycat?
Virgin boy be all right. Where the [ __ ]
was he? The skin virgin. Oh, mate. Why
do you want me to do this video to Lex later? Greasy. Yeah.
I'm going to do this video. I'm going to
title it Lex and Kitty since they're so
rude and don't let people [ __ ]
finish. You know,
they don't let people finish. Yeah. [laughter] Easy.
But where was the [ __ ] skin virgin?
Where was the virgin? Greasy. I thought
he was going to show up. Used to love
these kind of debates and [ __ ]
Greavves. Where was the [ __ ] virgin?
Virgin boy then. The copycat.
Oh, looks like [ __ ] cats. Where was
the [ __ ] copycat?
Where's the little copycat? Where's copycat? Where copycat?
Where's the little copy?
H I'm a dangerous nasty man. Mate,
listen. You lost the argument. You got
wrecked. Now this Lex, I don't know how
long he's been going for, but he met his
match with me. He met his match with me,
right? He completely met his [ __ ]
match with me, mate. Did he? Let's be
real here. He met his [ __ ] match with me.
Yeah. And now you're saying about people
changing their mind. [laughter]
Really? What? Somebody just randomly
changed their mind off the week leading
someone on. Really? [ __ ] hell, mate.
Yeah. What? What do they do? Do they
change their mind suddenly? What? What?
Someone that feels
pressured to give in their number. Yeah.
But will talk to somebody every day for
a week. Really, mate? Really? Really? Yeah.
Yeah. Pair of [ __ ] [ __ ] That's what
them two are. Pair of [ __ ] [ __ ]
Easy. Yeah. He's gay as well. He is
actually gay. That guy, I'm telling you,
he's gay. I know gay people. So, yeah.
No, it's not that they changed their
mind. It's they're using it as an
excuse. People are perfectly able to
change their mind. But these people
weren't changing the their mind. They
were leading you on on purpose. Yeah,
that's the big difference. It's not them
changing their mind. People change their
mind all the time. But I don't think
somebody has spoke to someone and led
someone on for a [ __ ] week and then
decided to just change their mind. It's
excuse after excuse after excuse with these people,
you know, and that's what my argument
was basically. That's my my my argument, you know.
So that's that.
Why do I disgust you? Because it's the truth.
No one cares about what what I said I
wanted to to do to kids. Stop changing the subject.
Yeah, exactly. They can't make up their mind.
Yeah, she lasted a week, mate. Again,
this is all stuff, Sarah. When you're
proven wrong, you got proven wrong and
you [ __ ] know it. Yeah, simple.
Yeah, simple. Making excuses for women
leading people on and then have to
attack the messenger. I mean, for [ __ ]
sake, mate. Seriously. So, yeah,
I know, man. They live in the past.
Yeah, it's a madness. I can't believe
Greavvesy, they're trying to deny the
fact that this person has led me on. I I
I just It's like that whole that just
tells you all you need to know, bro,
when you know you got a lot of people
sat there attacking you just because
someone's led you on. I mean, they've
led you on. It was an example. I didn't
give a [ __ ] about it, but it was just an
example that I was stating they led you
on. It's whatever. No one cares. It's
just I was using it as an example, you
know. But you seem to completely dismiss
it and make up stuff. How is that not
leading someone on, Grezy? How can you
tell me how that's not leading someone
on? Do you know what leading someone on means?
It's they are obviously leading you the
[ __ ] on. If somebody if somebody
genuinely felt pressured into giving you
their number, they wouldn't have
replied, let alone replied for a week.
Think about it, bro. Absolutely think
about what you're saying. But they but
they don't. They don't. And then they
say that you're Oh, well, you got
rejected. What? Well, you got rejected.
That that they think that's winning the argument.
You know, that's not winning an
argument, bro. You know what I mean?
It's an example that I don't really care
about, but you know, it's an example
nonetheless to to to to throw out there, you know?
And I was trying to say that yes,
men, men are shallow. Women are more
shallow than men. Women are more shallow
than men. No, it's not factual. The fact
is the person led me on and you're
making excuses. That's not factual. They
led you on. That's facts. Why is it such
a problem for you to admit that? Because
Greasy, if a man leads someone on,
that's that everyone would admit it.
Everyone be like, "Oh, well, the guy led
you on." Um, men and women do it. They
lead people on. Why can't they just
accept the fact that a woman has led you
on? You you you see the madness in that.
We all can say a man's led someone on as
men lead people on.
But why are they struggling to
acknowledge the fact that this person
has led you on? I don't I don't
understand. It's like they don't want to
It's like they're so um
so scared to to take any offense. It's It's mad.
It's like they they they they look for
any excuse to put the blame back onto
you, even with that one example.
Uh so what if they did? Oh, so now
you're saying, "So what if they did?"
Well, it's them being a [ __ ] Someone
that leads somebody on is toxic and a
[ __ ] So they are a toxic [ __ ] Simple.
That's what you said. So what? They're
toxic and they're a [ __ ] And it's not
so what if they did. They [ __ ] did.
There's no so what about it.
So it's it's they did because they're
toxic and they were [ __ ] And you and
then he's he goes to say about how women are uh
like or men not shallow. But the thing
is men will admit they're shallow.
They'll be like, "Oh, I go for ass. I go
for tits. I go for this. I go for this
kind of woman." But women, no. We go for personality.
We We go for personality. We do, mate.
We don't go for looks. No. No. We don't
we don't reject that guy because he's
got blue eyes and not green eyes. Not
us. No, we go for personality, my boy.
You know, and that guy up the road. Oh,
he's got a beard. So, I don't want I
don't want to go near that. But women go
for personality. They don't they don't
they don't they literally don't, right?
They they they don't go for anything
physical, Grezy. Do you know what I'm
saying? It's it's [ __ ] madness. She
didn't lead you on. you spoke for a week
and and you expected more. Okay, let's
rewind back again to their last message
again. So, they said that I quote, "I
felt pressured into giving my number."
That's what they said. This person has
been texting me every day for a week.
People that feel pressured into giving
their number does not text everyone
someone every day for a week. They are
leading you on. Do you need a dictionary
for this? I mean, what the [ __ ] would it
take to get through to you people? I
mean, I expected more because they said
that they were going to [ __ ] meet me,
you [ __ ] idiots. Oh, you want me to
explain that? Have you come from Tik Tok?
I would explain that if you want me to.
You know, I don't need to block people.
I don't need to do I I will I will
explain that if you want me to. Have you
Have you just come from Tik Tok?
I mean, I I I'll explain it to you. Oh,
calling me an ins, mate. I'm a big boy.
I can take it. I'm a [ __ ] big boy.
Look. Look. I'm I'm a big boy. I can
take it, mate. Yeah. You calling me
names to try to win the argument is not
going to it's not going to bother me,
mate. It's not going to bother me. I'm
I'm a big boy. You can call me
misogynist. You can call me a [ __ ]
whatever you want to call me, mate. It's
not going to it's not going to bother me
because you need to understand that
people can very much have an opinion.
Yeah. And not be labeled as any of these
things. You understand that? Yeah.
And I can explain that American if you
want me to. I can explain that American
if you want me to. Yeah. If you want.
Yeah. Okay. Are you you from Tik Tok,
right? Okay. One one second. Let me
check this account. Okay. One sec.
That's how I'll be able to answer you,
but you can't answer me, mate. But you
can't answer me. That's the funny thing.
I'll explain it to you. Okay. Let me
I'll explain it to you. I'll explain it.
I'll explain it to you. Okay. So, I met
this person, right? It was about 3 years
ago now in April. Approached them on the
street. Since you asked me, I won't
ignore or dismiss anything that you've
said, right? So, okay, here we go.
Right. So, met this person on the
street. They've offered me their number.
So, they've actually offered me their
number, which is unusual because we
normally ask for their number. Some
woman uh from America, I'll explain it
to you outside Eminem shop uh in
Leicester Square. I don't know if you
know where that is. Um, but yeah,
throwing it out there. So, met her on
Thursday and she was completely
lovebombing the [ __ ] out of me, saying,
"Oh, you're cute. Come to America, see
me, retit." All this love bombing. So,
it weren't a, you know, you've met
someone once for 4 hours. You've said
[ __ ] drunk and they [ __ ] off and
you've never seen them again. This was
very calculated and this was very done
on purpose. Anyways, met them on a
Thursday, hooked up with them on a
Tuesday, done what we had to do,
whatever. Loads of love bombing. Went on
for days. Sober, mind you. It was very,
very sober. So, they were very
calculated with what they were doing.
They must have thought right when they
saw me that Here's another one. But they
met their match, mate. They met their
match. Bit like Lex who's met his
[clears throat] match now with [ __ ]
me, right? So, met her, right? done the business and
then she has uh blocked me. I remember I
had I was in another house and I'm
thinking right this this person's
blocked me. Now again they didn't say
you know it was it was great time um you
know if you ever come to America we can
we can be friends and she was telling me
she was she invited me over to come to
America um Mantis. So you know you're
saying about it being 4 hours he was
inviting me to come to her country. She
was very much lovebombing the [ __ ] out
of me and saying about how yeah you
should come to America t. So she went
back to America, blocked me and I've had
to [ __ ] get my friend to message her.
She didn't say, "Oh yeah, nice meeting you,
you know, come to America, show you
around as a friend." Just just a polite
thing. Just anything polite. No,
straight to blocking. Right. So, I said
to my friend like, "I don't want to have
to ask you to do this, but could you
message me this girl?" Because for some
reason, she's [ __ ] blocked me, right?
Which I don't know why she's [ __ ]
blocked me. So, he's messaged her and
she was making up excuses. Oh, uh yeah,
he uh he grabbed me, he done this, he
done that, he done this, he done that.
And I messaged her saying I had to buy a
new phone, by the way. I'll be invoicing
you the 70 quid. So, I've had to buy a
new [ __ ] phone saying, "Hold on a
minute. What the [ __ ] is going on here?
Why are you lying to my friends saying
this, that, and the other? I want an
explanation. Let's go on the phone right
here, right now. And what what is your
Well, it wasn't actually me doing that,
actually. It was actually me basically
pouring out my heart to them on on voice
notes saying, "I thought we was good.
What's going on?" You know, basically a
love poem. It was basically a love poem.
I don't know what I'm talking about. So,
I play I tried playing the nice guy here
to get an explanation. And what they
done was they blocked me, right? I said,
"No, let's just talk on the phone. Hold
on. Let's just let's just get this over
and done with like what's what is going
on here? Why why are you making up
stories?" Blocked me.
And yeah, from then she just I was like
and then I said to her basically, "Can
you apologize, right? Can can can you
just apologize?" And they turn they
weren't having it at all at all. I said,
"Listen, can you please apologize? Yeah,
I don't like the fact that you think you
can make up stories about people." And
the thing that annoyed me was people on
YouTube that found her. She was
responding back to them saying, "Keep me
updated." I said, "Listen now, right?
You're pissing me off now. I'll keep you
updated. I will come to your [ __ ]
country and I will keep you [ __ ]
updated if you want." Yeah. If that's
what you really want, I will keep you
updated. And I said, "Just apologize and
leave it at that." She wouldn't
apologize. So, I messaged all her
family, bro. I messaged all her family.
I, bro, I booked to go there and my
friend kind of more than a friend who I
was seeing. She begged me not to go,
bro. She stopped me, bro. She stopped
me. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I booked it. I can
show you the booking if you don't
believe me. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I [ __ ]
messaged all her [ __ ] family. You
want to [ __ ] with me, you little
[ __ ] Yeah. Yeah. So, it's okay for
them to try to mock somebody they see as
vulnerable, but they play the victim and
someone gives it back to them. Yeah. She
would have got [ __ ] up, bro. I was
speaking to a friend um
about a couple months ago and she was
really really really trying to trying to
bait me to go there, bro. Trust me.
Trust me. Yeah. Don't be a [ __ ] She was entitled
little narcissistic little [ __ ] So I've
had my like fair shares with narcissist. Yeah.
So that's it, bro. And then she played
the victim. But what if I wasn't this,
bro? What if I wasn't this? Then what? I
wouldn't have been able to defend
myself, would I?
Yeah. It doesn't matter how long I've
known them for. Bro, hear me out here.
Yeah. Can I just say something to you?
Yeah. You can agree, you can disagree.
You've not just met someone for four or
five hours, bro. It's not that. Listen,
you go into a bar, right? Like that one
that gave me a [ __ ] in the alleyway.
You've met someone drunk, you're talking
[ __ ] and you hook up and then they've
gone. That's four or five hours that
people just do. This was calculated.
Yeah, it was very very calculated. And
the way they went about it was wrong.
Yeah, they brought it all on themselves.
Yeah, they they brought it on their
[ __ ] selves. Yeah, you've not just
stumbled across someone drunk for four
or five hours and started talking [ __ ]
It was very very very very calculated.
And guess what? She's a [ __ ] anyways. So
yeah, [ __ ] her. Yeah, she met her
[ __ ] match with me, mate. Yeah,
in it, Grezy.
You know what I mean?
Defending narcissists now. Well, okay.
Let me ask you this. Okay. Okay, Grezy.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Right. Why couldn't
have you just wrote, you know, it was
nice meeting you, you know, let's just
allow it. Why? Why couldn't you just do
the decent thing? Why couldn't you just
do the decent thing? And do you know
what these people are going to say now,
Grezy? Because they don't owe you anything.
Do you know what I'm saying, bro? Why
can't you just do the decent thing? I
was speaking to uh him for about was it
5 10 minutes and then this woman from
Scotland come in and started shouting
over me saying, "Oh, you're an incel.
You're a misogynist." No, no, no. like
she was talking over me and even two
three 2 v one they still going to beat me. Yeah.
Yeah. It was this woman from Scotland
coming in shouting over me and then
kicking me. That's the only way they can
win is is is is shouting over and kicking.
Mad. [ __ ] mad, bro. So yeah,
she's lucky I didn't go over there and
kill her, mate. Yeah. Seriously.
Seriously. Yeah. M Mantis, she's very
lucky I didn't go over there and [ __ ] kill her,
you know. Greasy will tell you that as well.
Yeah, it was good. Yeah, it was annoying
when that woman was shouting over me.
I'm going to have to do a video now to
to them and hopefully she can send he
can send this to her cuz you're not right.
I can say it cuz I just [ __ ] did.
I can say it because I just [ __ ] did. Yeah. Simple.
Yeah. He caught me off guard a couple of
years ago. Do you want to Do you want to
see two Okay. Do you want to see two
videos where I stuck it on a black
bouncer a couple of weeks ago and he
shhat his pants? Do you want to see Do
you want to see uh Do you want to see a
video where I stuck it on four people
the other day and they done nothing
about it, mate? Do you want to see that
video as well? Do you want to see Do you
want to see a new updated video? Yeah.
Where they all shat their pants and
[ __ ] crumbled? Yeah. Do you want to
see that, mate? Do you want to see that
video? I'm sure you'd love to see an
updated video, mate. Yeah. I' I'm sure
you'd love to see it. You know, I'm sure
you'd love to see it, mate. Yeah. [ __ ] idiot.
Yeah, bro. The the guy caught me off
guard two years ago. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
Yeah. Go collect your silver medal, bro.
Yeah. He literally
he literally caught me off guard two
years ago, bro. Yeah. Two years ago.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Get with the times,
bro. Get with the times. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Anyone
can catch someone off guard when they're
bigger than them. Anyone can do that.
Anybody can do that. Anybody can do
Yeah. Yeah. The guy was bigger than me.
It was 2 years ago. He caught me off
guard. Stop it, bro.
Why was the bouncer lucky that night?
So, that's that.
You need to stop saying the word
triggered, bro. You need to think of
some new things. It's boring. You seem
really triggered. You need to stop that.
It's boring now. The repeating, bro. Stop repeating.
They say that it's not a debate, Grezy.
Yet a woman comes and jumps in and
starts shouting down your throat. But
it's not a debate, is it not?
Yep. He was working. And that's not an
excuse because the four other people
that I stuck it on wasn't working. So
don't try and use that as an excuse. Oh,
he was working. He was working. Mate,
don't even try and use that excuse
because if you want to use that excuse,
I get you. I I tell you something right
now, bro. I will show you where I've
stuck it on four people, two men and two
women that weren't working. So stop.
Don't even try to use that excuse.
Right? And I'd done the very
professional thing and said to him, "If
you want to meet me after work, I will
take your number." Yeah. Do not even try
using that as an excuse. Do not even try Yeah.
Know what I mean? Do not even try using
that excuse cuz it's not going to wash.
That excuse ain't going to wash. Yeah.
So don't even try to say, "Oh, he, you
know, uh, Risy's job." That is not going
to wash in the washing machine. It's not
going to wash. Yeah. Because what about
them four other people that done
absolutely nothing who I told about
themselves that wasn't at work. Yeah.
What about them?
Stop it, bro. Stop it. Stop it. Because
if that guy at work beat me up, you
wouldn't be saying, "Oh, oh, it doesn't
count because he's at work." Is that
right, Greavvesy? Is that right?
Remember the guy? Do you remember the
bus driver, Greavvesy? Right. You
remember the bus um driver Greavvesy a
couple of years back when I when I used
to go to the Admirals back when I used
to gamble and he was running up his
mouth at fetish baby Peter. Do you
remember? Do you remember that Greavesy
when they were when um he was running up
his mouth to baby Peter which I was a
baby at the time. We didn't say oh whoa
he's a coward because he's at work. You
can't hit him. But as soon as they take
it out well the guy's not gonna lose his
job. The guy's not gonna lose his job.
Yeah, we have seen Greavves on countless
countless occasions where bounces have
knocked people out. You know what I'm
saying, bro? You know what I'm saying?
It wasn't, "Oh, well, he's at work. He
knows you can't hit him." See, it it's
whatever suits their narrative. They're
[ __ ] idiots, bro. They're [ __ ]
idiots. These these not are going to
drive me to to ordering a McDonald's,
Grezy. I'm going to order a McDonald's
in a minute. I had I had fish and chips
earlier. It cost me 20 pound. Well, I
I'll order a [ __ ] McDonald's [ __ ]
if I have to.
So, yeah. Basically, they say things to
suit their narrative. They said nothing
about that bus driver. Yeah. I said the
same thing to LT. Yeah. Grievy. LT
thought I was trying to wind him up. But
I wasn't I wasn't trying to wind him up.
I was being serious. Right. You're
saying Grievy, answer me. Just answer me
this. You're saying about how Right.
You're saying about how, you know, you
can't hit people because they're at
work. So, what about that bus driver
running up his mouth then? Okay. Okay
then. So, what about the bus driver
running up his mouth in Morphing Star?
What? So, I I wouldn't be able to hit
him then cuz he's at work. You see,
these people are full of [ __ ]
excuses. You know, watch when I do this
video later to Lex. I'm going to title
it Lex and Kitty. Yeah. The [ __ ]
courage the cowardly [ __ ] dogs.
That's what I'm going to do, bro.
Yeah. The bus driver. It was basically
when I used to get the bus to Admirals
when I was back at the old house, lad.
Yeah. Yeah. She was lucky I didn't go to
America and kill her. Yeah.
Basically, I was on a bus and he was
running up his mouth to me. And where it
was like years ago, I was a lot younger.
I was a bit like hesitant to say
anything back. No, I don't think No, he
didn't offer me out, but he was running
his mouth. And obviously, when I was a
lot younger, and I'm not as strong as I
used to be, like mentally as well, not
just physically, I didn't really say anything.
Um, so but no one was saying, "Oh, well
the guy's a coward because he knows that
if you know if you hit him, he's going
to lose his job." So it's whatever suits
their narrative. That's what I'm saying
with people on here. You know,
this is what I mean, bro. And who cares
about the black bouncer, bro? [ __ ] him.
There was four people that wasn't at
work that got me that night, bro. There
was there was two men with two women,
and I told them all about themselves. So
what was the excuse for that one?
Yeah, it's excuses with these people
every time, bro. Every [ __ ] time.
Yeah. So, that bus driver was a coward
then because if I run up my mouth to
him, you're just going to sit there and
say, "Oh, well, he couldn't hit me
because he's at work."
They mocked me. They made me walk away.
Bro, you're seeing things. Yeah, you
need to go to Spec Savers, bro. You're
seeing things. cuz I literally told them
to [ __ ] off back to Newcastle. This is
what I'm saying. They make up stuff.
This is exactly why with these people I
don't post content because they make up
stuff. Bro, I clearly told them to [ __ ]
off back to where I land. Yeah, if you
watch the video properly. You constantly
constantly make excuses. This is what I
mean with these people. Listen. Okay.
How about this one, Mantis? How about
you meet me tomorrow then? How about you
meet me tomorrow and I smash your teeth
down your throat? I'll smack your teeth
down your throat. How about you meet me
tomorrow then? Yeah. Why didn't they get
up? Why did they sit down, bro? I boy
the guy off. My train is worth more than
your whole outfit, bro. They No one made
me walk away. No bouncer and no person,
bro. Just like you. You will never do
anything to me either, bro. I told them
to [ __ ] back to where they come from.
You think anyone could ever tell me
that? Anyways, little boy, meet me
tomorrow, bro. Meet me tomorrow and I'll
smack your teeth down your throat, [ __ ]
in your mouth, and and laugh at you. You
little [ __ ] bro. I I I own that black
bouncer and I own them four people. I
told them to [ __ ] off and mind their own
[ __ ] business. Yeah. And they were
swearing on that [ __ ] video as well.
You're a [ __ ] little [ __ ] You make
excuses. Yeah. All you do is sit there
and make excuses every time you take a
fat [ __ ] L. Yeah, that's what you do.
You sit there and you make excuses. Oh,
the guy was at work. The guy was at
work. The guy was at work. The guy was
at work, bro. The guy was at work, [laughter]
bro. Uni people laughed at me. Yeah.
Okay, bro. You keep you keep telling
yourself that. Everyone's seen the
video, bro. Everybody has seen the
video. So, whatever you're thinking
happened in your head, you can keep
writing it. I told them to [ __ ] back to
where they come from. I think you're
getting me and them confused. You're
constantly full of excuses. Oh, the guy
didn't want to lose his job. This is
what I mean with you people on here,
bro. You are complete and utter [ __ ]
Even when you lose, you still pretend
that you've won, bro. Listen, listen,
listen, listen. If they were a real man,
when I told them to mind their own
business and [ __ ] off back to where they
come from, bro, they didn't even stand
up, bro. They literally didn't even
stand up. [laughter]
I told them to mind their own business
and [ __ ] off. And they didn't even stand
up. They didn't even stand up when I was
standing the whole time. Stop it, little
boy. It's embarrassing now. It's
embarrassing. I told them to [ __ ] back
to Newcastle where they come from and
how my traders are worth more than their
whole outfit. They didn't stand up once.
They did not stand up once, mate. Yeah.
When we all know a real man would stand
up and get in your face. You're an
idiot, mate. You're an idiot. You
constantly make excuses. Oh, he couldn't
do anything because he's at work. Oh,
because a bouncer is at work. Yet, we
see multiple times where a bouncer has
beaten people up. Oh, he's at work. Oh,
he's at work. Oh, he's at work. And then
when they're not at work, you still make
excuses. Oh, well, he can't do anything
because he's at work. [laughter]
You're a [ __ ] bro. Oh, it's at work.
You're a [ __ ] [ __ ] To be honest
with you, I I would have I should have
known. Yeah, you was going to use that work excuse.
Oh, we can't hit you. He took an L. So,
let's just say that he's at work. You're
a little [ __ ] man. You're a [ __ ]
little [ __ ] Suck my dick, you little
You little [ __ ] You're a little
fatty. [ __ ] LJ and [ __ ] your mom, bro.
Your mom's a little [ __ ] Come and do
something to me, bro. You know where I
live. Come on, big man. Show everyone
what a big man you are. Your mom is a
little [ __ ] who gets [ __ ] shafted
right up her little [ __ ] and you're
going to do nothing. And we're not
talking about LJ. We're talking about
your mom, bro. Yeah, bro. Bounces slap
people all the time. They You've seen
what happened in Cardiff. You Oh, bro.
It's not even about slapping, bro. No,
no, no. To be fair, it's not even about
slapping, bro. The guy stood there like
a pedigree dog. Like a pedigree dog,
bro. He sat there like a pedigree dog.
We're not even talking about violence,
bro. He sat there like a dog, bro. Like
he he he didn't even say anything, but
he can't do anything because that work.
This is what I mean, bro. Every time
these people take an L, they're full of
excuses. They are full of excuses, bro.
They are full. If that guy was a man,
Yeah. If that guy was a man, he would
have turned around and gave it back to
me. He didn't need to hit me. He didn't
need to do anything.
you know, or he could have said, "I'm
meeting you. You know, I'll meet you
after work." These little [ __ ] on
here, they constantly make excuses. Even
when they take L's. Yeah, bro. It's Bro,
Indigo, it's excuses with these people.
Yeah, it is excuses with these people.
It would always be excuses with these people.
I just gave you an example, bro. It's
excuses, bro. We know this. Yeah.
Yeah, my life will always be better than
yours, bro. You're probably some [ __ ]
middle-aged fat ugly man that ain't got
no life. You know what I mean? Some fat,
ugly man trying to judge other people on
the internet, bro. Allow it, please.
Yeah, just just allow it, bro. I'm an L,
bro. You're probably some fat ugly man,
bro. Stop it. It's embarrassing.
Anyways, you can [ __ ] off now. You can get banned.
[ __ ] repeating little bastard. Yeah,
they always make excuses. This is what
I'm saying, Indigo. That's why I never
post no content. I'll meet my match,
bro. Yeah, that's never good. Who Who
Who's my match, bro? Who's my match?
There's no one that's that's my match.
Why would I be in prison? What? Okay.
Okay. Let's Let's talk about this
sensibly. Why would I be in prison?
What? Because I said a few things that
you didn't like. Because you can't win
an argument against me. Cuz I whooped your ass.
What? What? in it cuz I whooped your ass
in an argument. That's why I should be
in prison. I'm not sure that's how that works.
Why should Why would Why should I be in
prison? I don't have any convictions.
I've never been to prison. Why? Why
should I be in prison? What? Because
someone's beat you in an argument. Since
you don't like the word debate.
[ __ ] off, man.
Yeah, cuz that guy's repeated. Yeah, but
he's not having a debate. He's repeating
himself. He's not coming on the Hangouts
having a debate with me. Do you want to
come in and have a debate with me? You
want me to put the link up and any of
you can join if you want,
you know? I mean, I can put the link up
and no one will get Do you want to talk?
Do you really really want to talk? Oh,
guess what he done, Greavvesy?
You never guess what Lex's done? Oh, no.
I'm going to put the link up. [laughter]
Oh no. Oh no. Oh, Lex, you blocked me.
Oh no. All I said to him was, "Let me
back in. I want to chat with Kitty. Was
unfair to shout over me then kick me."
And then he's blocked me. Oh gosh darn
it. You know, so you you put you you Oh
my god. So you put up a a a link for
people to join and now you've just
blocked me on Instagram.
Well, I'm going to do this video and
hopefully it gets to him to him.
What the [ __ ] He actually blocked me.
What a what a coward, bro.
Wow. So, I can't even get through to
that woman now.
What the actual [ __ ]
What was the point of even joining them?
What was the point of even [ __ ] joining?
What was the point of even joining, bro?
I don't see the point of even joining.
So, he's blocked me.
What the [ __ ] was the point in that, bro?
What was the point of that? What in the?
So he he must block people. Yeah.
So I don't know how I'm going to get
through to this kitty to be honest with you.
Yep. They muted me and then they shouted.
No, I feel like I need to get I need to
get the last word, bro. N Grezy, I'm not
going to stop now, bro. I'm not going to
stop. You know what I'm like, bro. You
should have got me into this. You know
what I'm like, Grezy. You know what? I'm
like, so what was the whole point of
this whole thing?
Like I I want to have a debate and if I
lose, I lose. That's fine. I'm not going
to kick anyone.
So what what my impression is is that he's
a gay guy that just defends women for
the sake of it and that kitty's his best
friend and they can't actually win an
argument without shouting over people.
Without shouting over people.
That's that's basically what I' I've
gathered from this, you know, is that
he's he's a gay guy that just defends
women and she's her she's his best friend. H
I don't understand it.
Yeah, but what's the longest video that
you can do?
I don't know why she don't just come on here.
She is a coward, bro. She is a coward.
Anyone that needs to talk over someone
and keep mutin is a coward, bro. Is a [ __ ] coward. Yeah,
you're [ __ ] we caught you. You
[ __ ] caught you. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, [ __ ] shouting over me, you
I never said there's a problem with that.
Um, I never said there was a problem
with that. I never said there was a
problem if he if he was gay. I I I said
that he was gay because he comes across
very feminine. I don't give a [ __ ] if
he's gay, but he comes across as gay cuz
he comes across very fe feminine and I
know loads of gay people. So,
who said there was a problem with
someone being gay?
Yeah, I'm not I'm not worth your her
time, but yet you shouted over me for
about five minutes, but I'm not worth
your time. Okay. Okay. So, maybe maybe
maybe in future if someone's not worth
your time. Best not joining a panel
shouting over someone and not not let
the other person speak. Maybe may may
maybe maybe maybe in future avoid that, you know.
So yeah, she's a coward. Proper coward.
Proper proper coward. Bro,
we need to get through to this kitty. I
I I don't want to bully. I just want
like a debate. I can answer you why
women go through [ __ ] I I had the
answers, but they wouldn't they wouldn't
let me talk. They wouldn't let me talk though, Grezy.
I don't do the same to others. When did
I once shout over somebody
on that panel, Greezy? When did I once
shout over somebody on that panel?
I could tell you exactly why women go
through [ __ ] I had the answers. I had
the answers right there in black and
white, but you you didn't want to hear
it, so you shouted over me. This kitty,
let me tell you what this kitty is. I'll
tell you what this kitty is, Grezy. She
is someone I I'll explain it to you,
right? This kitty
is someone right that goes for men that
cheat on her, abuse her, horrible
people. And women like her are attracted
to these kind of men. They generally
pick these kind of men to go for. And
then when they go for these men and they
get cheated on or beat up or whatever,
they generalize all men, right? That's
why. And they and then they play victim.
But they're the ones that are going with
these men time and time and time and
time and time and time again. That's why
she's a [ __ ] feminist, you know. Yeah.
That women like her, I I I know what
they do, bro. They generalize all men on
the men that they go for that they then
complain about. I know it. I've seen it
all before, bro. You're talking to
someone like you're talking to me.
You're talking to me, Grezy.
You know, I know I know these things.
They go for men that cheat on them and
beat them up. They like these kind of
men. They choose these kinds of men. You
know, we've seen it all before. And then
they generalize men being all like that.
That the men that they go for. How does
that even make sense?
Yeah. Yeah, I was talking about an
American woman, Sarah.
No, no, no, no, no. You don't know what
men are like. You know what men are like
that you go for. No, no, no, no, no.
It's the men that you choose. It's the
men that you go for. All of the decent
other men, you reject them and you're
not interested. No. It's not what men
are like. It's the men that you go for,
that you pick. Not that you come across.
It's the men that you pick. And that's
what I was going to say to her.
Yeah. It's not that you know what men
are like. It's the men that you go for
are like. The men that you choose are
like. Yeah. Yeah. Big big difference. Big difference.
Big [ __ ] difference. There's a big
big big difference.
Yeah. Big difference, mate. So, yeah.
What do you mean make it make sense?
What do you mean make it make sense,
bro? I've just told you, right? She's
saying about Oh, oh, what women go
through, what women go through, what
women go through. Yes. because of the
men that they choose that cheat on them
and abuse them. They are that they
choose to get with these men and then
complain about these men then keep going
back to them. So, I've made it make
absolute sense. I've made it make
absolute sense. How does that not make
sense, dummy? They go for men that cheat
on them and abuse them, moan about them,
then keep going for these men. You make
it make sense. You make it make sense.
You can't moan and winge about men being
this, that, and the other. Yet, you keep
constantly going back to these people
and then you moaning. You need to make
it make sense because I've made it make
absolute sense. You need to make it make
sense. Yeah. No, they do not lie and
pretend to be like, "Get the [ __ ] out of
here. You know what these men are about.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. You know
what these men are about. Stop talking
shit." Yes. Yes. You go for drug dealers
and you go for cheaters and you
continuously go back to them. Yes. Yes.
You Yes, it is absolutely right. So what
you're telling me, you don't know what
these guys are about. It's [ __ ] It
is absolute [ __ ] Cuz every single
time, right, a woman, right, listen,
Grezy, this is how you know they're full
of [ __ ] Cuz every single time these
women have said to me in the past, "Oh,
you're sweet, you're this, you're that.
They found some excuse not to get with
you because you're not a drug dealer.
Cuz you're not a woman beater. They go
for these men. Bro, do not let them tell
you otherwise. They know what these men
are like. Yeah. So, what it is, Grezy,
when these women say they can't find
someone, right, it's men that don't beat
them up, drug dealers, people that treat
them like [ __ ] people that are not big
Tik Tockers. When we say we can't find
someone, right? When we said we can't
find someone, right, we generally can't
find someone. No, women are the ones
that are deluded. Yeah. Yeah. You are
the ones that are deluded. Yeah.
Right. Do you not find it a bit strange,
Grezy, how there is men in prison and
most of them have got girlfriends? You
ever watched the prison documentary?
Stop repeating. Um, have you ever
watched the prison documentary, Greasy?
You'll find that
most of these men in prison have got girlfriends.
Strange. Most of them have got
girlfriends and they're actually having
children whilst they're in prison. Have
you ever not Have you not seen that, Grezy?
Mate, listen. Stop trying to reverse the
psychology. Um, Abby, it's not going to
work. Listen, listen, Abby. reversing
the psychology and trying to victimize
women is not going to work. So, there's
no point even doing that on my channel.
You know, you're you're you're twisting
things now. When I'm stating facts,
right, you're you're twisting things.
It's not going to work on this channel. So, yeah.
No, no, no. We're not talking about
people that are raping you. We're not
talking about people that are raping.
We're talking about drug dealers and
abusers and you do go for their men. You
generally generally generally do go for
their men, right? Okay. Okay. Okay. Let
me give you an example, Grey. What
happened with that woman that I met 3
weeks ago? Do you remember what she said
to me on Snapchat?
I'll give you a good example. And again,
I don't care, but we'll use it as well.
Do you remember what she said to me on Snapchat?
You got a good memory. Do you remember
what she said to me on Snapchat?
Please, please tell me if you remember
cuz this will this will fit in right
again. Again, don't care, but we'll just
use this as a vlog. Do you remember what
she said to me on Snapchat?
She turned around and said to me that,
"Thanks for coming up to me. You're very
sweet. You made my day. You're a very
kind, nice person." And reta t. So she's
seen me for what I was yet made 101
excuses why not to give me a chance.
That goes to show that they only want
drug dealers and men that abuse them.
It's it is the truth. It generally
generally generally is the truth. Again
I don't care but we'll just use that as
an example since we're going by my
experiences. You would have thought that
Greavves if somebody was these things
somebody would give them a chance
because that's what they would want. Do
do you understand Grezy? Wouldn't you
want a sweet woman that's made all day
and ret would Would Would Would Would
Would Would Would Would Would Wouldn't
you want to give that person a chance?
But they don't because they only want
drug dealers and people that abuse them.
So, they wouldn't give you a chance. But
then they they they say that they don't
know what these men are like.
Apparently, they don't know what these
men are like. It's [ __ ] Of course
they know what they're like, Grezy. Of
course they know what they're [ __ ] like,
you know? Of course they know what they
[ __ ] what they're like, bro. madness.
But listen, Greavves, in future, bro, if
you're going to recommend me anyone,
please make sure they're not just going
to kick people when they're getting
their ass whooped,
you know? Please don't, you know, in
future just Yeah. So, they definitely
definitely do know what these men are
like. They definitely do know what these
men are like that they keep going back to.
They definitely definitely do know what
they're like and what they're capable of.
They don't want nice, normal people that
aren't drug dealers, that aren't
abusers. Am I lying, Grezy? Am I lying?
Am I lying, Grezy? You know, cuz there's
no way, Grezy, that all of these women
have just gone for all of these abusive
men, drug dealers. Um, you know, there
there's no way there's no coincidence
that that's just happened. Am I am I
lying, Grezy? I think I've got a valid
point. Grievy tells me if I'm wrong.
Grezy tells me if I'm right, he's not a yes man
is why we keep you on it. There's no
coincidence that they just keep going
for the same guy. Think about it. That
person on Snapchat, what they wrote was
everything that you would want in someone, you know?
No. A lot of them don't have money.
So, is my dad a drug dealer? My dad's
dead. So, I mean, no, maybe
I was dropped. No, I I I was kicked. No,
Yeah. So, that woman, Indigo, was saying
that I was sweet and I was this and I
was that, yet she was making every
excuse not to give me a chance. Doesn't
that contradict everything that they
say? Again, I don't give a [ __ ] about
it, but does that not contradict
everything that they're saying? how they
want a sweet man and you know a down to
you know the thing is indigo it doesn't
ring right because when they come across
down to earth normal people they're not
interested they they generally are they
generally are not interested
yeah they kicked me from the um uh Tik
Tok thing yeah they kicked me from the
Tik Tok stream
So yeah, that's mad.
So no, they choose these men. They're
very aware of what these men are like.
Don't get it twisted,
which is fine. You know, people can go
for who they like, but don't moan and
say all men are the same because of the
men that you are choosing, that you keep
going back to, you know.
That's that's that
you go for who the [ __ ] you want, but
don't moan about all men being the same.
So, it's the men that they go for. Yeah,
can't believe Lex blocked me. That's mad.
I'm moaning about women don't want When
have I ever moaned about women don't
want me? I don't give a [ __ ] about
women. They're all toxic [ __ ] that
aren't the same.
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] about every
man being single or not. I don't compare
myself to other people. I don't give a [ __ ]
I don't give a [ __ ] about other men. I
don't compare myself to other people. I
don't give a [ __ ] No, it's nothing to
agree on or not. It's it's it's
completely pointless comparing yourself
to other people. When have I moaned
about women don't want me? I don't want
them. They're [ __ ] toxic [ __ ]
and they're all the same,
you know? No, I didn't moan that. She
said, "I know women are all the same.
They're toxic [ __ ] I don't want them
[ __ ] narcissistic dickheads." That's
the whole reason if I was if I wanted
women, right, on ser on a serious thing,
I wouldn't be joining Lex's [ __ ]
panel telling him about women.
So, I don't [ __ ] want them
narcissistic evil [ __ ]
Yeah. No, I said I don't want a woman.
Yeah, cuz they're evil. They're evil
[ __ ] Toxic little [ __ ]
Timewasting little nasty [ __ ] that lead
people on. That's exactly what they are.
I don't give a [ __ ] Simple.
I was stating what they do. I was
stating what these [ __ ] women do.
Yeah. I was stating,
"Yeah, he teaches men." Yeah, but he got
his ass whooped by me single-handedly.
How did that make sense?
I whooped his ass, bro. You have to admit. Mad.
It's mad. I know that women are toxic [ __ ]
No, I wasn't crying over her because I
didn't even like her. I was using it as
an example. This is what I'm saying. You
don't even have an argument. All you do,
right, every time you're proven wrong,
you always say, "Oh, women don't want
you and you're crying." They've got no
argument. This is exactly what I'm
saying, Grezy, right? You will give them
an example even of somebody that you
don't like. And then they'll say, "Oh,
well, you're crying because they don't
want you when they're proven wrong."
It's [ __ ] madness. It's [ __ ]
madness. Every time they're proven
wrong, they resort to, "Oh, women
rejected you and you're crying." They've
got no argument. This is what I'm
saying, bro. Why do you think that I got
kicked? Why do you think that I got
kicked? Because they've got no argument,
bro. If you went on, if you saw the
chat, bro. Yeah. If you saw the chat,
right, if you if you saw the chat,
right, bro, you would see that they were
pretty much saying the same thing.
Didn't you read the chat was basically
saying the same thing, you know? You know,
[ __ ] women. They're toxic little
[ __ ] I hate them, bro.
I do hate them.
No, I completely whooped his ass. I
completely whooped his ass. Mate, if I
didn't whoop his ass, you wouldn't have
kicked you wouldn't have kicked me. You
wouldn't He wouldn't have kicked me. If
I didn't whoop his ass, he wouldn't have
kicked me. He would have left me in
there, mate. The fact that he had to add
someone else that had to shout over me
proves that he lost. Yeah, it was a 231
and he had to shout over me.
I mean that proves that you lost. You
know what I'm saying? You lost, bro. You
know, and you know 231 shouted over me
and kicked me
and you think that you've won. Okay, man.
I don't I Bro, they're [ __ ]
[ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] about
women. They're all [ __ ] Anyways,
they're just [ __ ] stupid little
[ __ ] [ __ ] them.
[ __ ] them, bro.
Yeah. Yeah, you are the loser. Yeah,
I didn't let them talk. Uh, no. Again,
if you listen properly, right, if you
listen properly, you would hear that the
Scottish woman was shouting over me. Yeah.
Yeah. Because they don't want me. You
can keep saying that, mate. Every time
that you get proven wrong, you're just
going to say that you got rejected. You
got no argument. This is exactly what
I'm saying. You're losing the argument.
Every time I'm pointing out a woman's
shitty behavior, you say, "Oh, they
rejected you." It shows that you're
losing. Every time they do this, Grevy,
it shows that you're winning. If they
keep saying the same thing over and over
and over again, you're winning. You can
predict their answers. Every answer,
right, that they're given, I've said
that they're going to give it. Every
time a woman is proven wrong, they come
out with the most stupidest things. Oh,
they rejected you and you're crying
about it. That's what they do. Every
time they're proven wrong, the excuses
are mad, bro. Yeah. Well, you must be
getting mad cuz you're still typing.
Yeah. No, I wasn't in. Well, tell her to
come on here now then. Tell her to come
on here now. Tell that kiltw wearing
[ __ ] to come on here now. Yeah.
Tell that [ __ ] kiltw wearing [ __ ] now
to come on here. Yeah. And no one's
going to get blocked. Tell that kiltw
wearing [ __ ] that Scottish [ __ ] to come
on here now then. Yeah. Come on. Come
on. If that's really the case, tell her
to come on here now then. Yeah.
Tell that [ __ ] that [ __ ] Scotland
[ __ ] Gy to come on here now. Come on.
Tell that pipe sucking [ __ ] kiltw
wearing dick sucking fat stupid little
[ __ ] Yeah. To come on here now then.
What? What? Come on now then. Come on.
What are you waiting for?
Exactly, bro. Exactly.
Yeah. She's got better things to do. Yet
she's on Tik Tok. Yeah. Listening to a
gay [ __ ] white knight.
What? Listening to a gay white knight.
Oh, she's got better things to do.
Please, bro. Come on. Come on. [ __ ]
Scottish little [ __ ]
Yeah, she got her [ __ ] ass handed to her. Bro,
why don't one of you come on here? Why
don't you come on here? Well, I want I
want to have a debate with someone now,
Greavves. I'm actually in the mood. I'm
actually in the mood now.
I'm not dating. I'm not dating. Yeah,
I'd answer you. I'd answer you the
question if you want me to. I'll answer
you the question if you want me to, but
you're just going to talk over me. I'd
explain to you why I got that woman's
number and why I wanted to meet her.
But you're just going to talk over people. So,
I couldn't Well, come in and let's have
a debate then. Okay. I'll put the link
up. All right, Captain. [clears throat] One second.
There you go, Captain.
So yeah, I don't date I don't date women.
So what are you going to come in or not?
I want to have a debate with one of
these [ __ ] Come on. Let's have a
debate. Let's have a debate. Come on.
This cunt's got me in a [ __ ] mood. Come on.
Please. Come on. Come on. Let's just
Let's just have a chat. No shouting. No
kicking. I won't kick no one. Even if I
lose, I won't kick. I'm not kicking
anyone. Just come, please.
Cuz I'm not talking to accounts. I want
to actually have a debate,
you know? I I don't want to talk to I'm
not going to if you're not going to join
I'm not going to keep responding to
these [ __ ] accounts.