Why the [ __ ] would anyone do that, bro?
They're so disabled.
Why would anybody do that?
Proper proper disabled on here, isn't it?
Proper proper disabled,
bro. They're proper proper disabled.
I swear to God.
Yeah, they're proper proper disabled, bro.
Put the link up again. Proper proper
disabled. Why would anyone do that when
it was about to be lush content? [ __ ]
disabled on here, bro.
There's about to be some lush content
and then they'll put a nude up to stop
the whole thing. That's their disabilities.
Proper disabled, is it?
Disabled [ __ ] on there, bro.
Anyways, that's the link. Yeah. Here
we go. I got to get a McDonald's
at some point.
They're so disabled. Why would they put
a nude up when we're just about to have
people potentially join? It doesn't make
any sense. They're so disabled, bro.
Like, who would even do that? Yeah. when
people are just about to join. Breezy,
that's so disabled, isn't it? Like
there's content on here. Yeah, there's
content about to be had on here, right?
There could be people potentially
joining and we can get into it and then
they're putting a nude up. What the
[ __ ] Knowing that there's going to be like content.
No, it doesn't let me do it anymore. It
doesn't let me cover the screen. I don't
know how. I can't do it anymore. It
don't let me do it, bro.
No, I need to ask Rey, who do you
actually think won? 100%. Well, not
100%, but who do you actually think won?
Cuz I I don't think I can celebrate just
yet, cuz I don't think I completely won, did I?
I can't believe Lex blocked me.
I can't believe he blocked me, bro.
Can't believe that [ __ ] blocked me, lad.
What the [ __ ]
See, I put a link up. Anyone can join
and have a debate with me if they want.
I just can't believe like Yeah.
Yeah. You're not coming in, you little
[ __ ] trying to put nudes up.
You're not coming in either, you fat
loser. Jamie Thompson, you can get a
life. You're not putting another nude
up. Is there anyone on here that
actually wants to have a debate? You know,
yeah, but you you to be fair, you
thought they were going to beat me, is
it? What I don't understand, Grezy, is
it's similar to what I was saying. I
okay I've explained to you right about
this person in Thailand. Now, if anyone
wants to know, you know that I don't
like Thai women, right? When I went out
on Thursday, right? Um, I basically uh
just don't approach this cuz I went out.
Now, you know, I don't really like Thai
women. Just approached this person. I
thought, "No, if it's someone to meet,
it's better than nothing." Me again,
giving them the benefit of the doubt.
So, if they wanted to meet, then it's
better than nothing cuz I wouldn't have
to deal with toxicity. It was my way of
giving women the benefit of the doubt
again. I don't give a [ __ ] But I could
use it as an example of where they have
led you on because they have led you on.
But it was, you know, it was I don't
give a [ __ ] bro. You know what I'm saying?
It was silly to be fair, especially when
they all they done was shout over me,
you know? But again, it seems that they
like to be in control. Grezy, how about
this, Grezy? me, him, and her on a
podcast on YouTube. H they would never
do that. You know why, Greg? Because
they wouldn't be able to kick people.
They wouldn't be able to ban people. So,
they'd lose that power. So, they would
never do it. They would never do it. You
know how you see podcast for it? Yeah.
Where it says, "Whatever you want to
say, say it. Swear if you want, we'll
get into this [ __ ] right now." Yeah.
You know what I'm saying?
Have you seen them kind of podcasts
where anything goes? Whereas they will
never do that, you know. Yeah.
Well, anyways, get Kitty on here, man. I
want to talk to Kitty.
I want to talk to Kitty. Me?
Yeah. On YouTube, whatever. Yeah. YouTube. Yeah.
Yeah. I would have ate her alive. That
[ __ ] Scottish woman. I would have
absolutely ate her, mate. You know that
in it, Greg. I would have ate her, bro.
I would have ate her for breakfast,
dinner, and supper. Meaning, who's live? Nah.
So, anyways, why do women go for men
that abuse you? Oh, she doesn't want to
talk to me. Well, she wasn't saying that
when she was shouting over me, saying, "Incel
women go through. Incel, incel, incel."
Of course, she wouldn't want to [ __ ]
talk to me. I'd completely destroy her.
Why would she want to talk to me? She's
a loser. Anyways, Greasy, make sure if
you ever um
if you um ever
want me to argue with these people
again, make sure they're on YouTube.
and they don't just kick people when they're losing,
you know, and make sure that it's
YouTube and it's not they'll kick you
when you know they they're losing cuz
what's the fun in that, you know?
There's no fun in that, Grezy, if
they're just going to kick people and they're losing.
But make sure it's on you. Make sure
it's definitely definitely on YouTube
or real life.
you know, real life would be good as well. Yeah.
It's mad they say they can't find
normal, decent men.
Cuz I know that.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] They're lying when
they say they can't find normal nice
men. Yeah, there's a lot of creeps.
Yeah, there's a lot of people that are
like that. Yeah, I'm not. Don't get me
wrong, there is. But there is people
that are genuine. And when I have
approached these women, I have been
genuine in the past when I was dating.
So them saying they can't find normal
people is [ __ ] you know?
So it's it's [ __ ] when they're
saying they can't find normal people,
it's [ __ ] They go for these abusive
men, these drug dealers. Don't don't let
them tell you otherwise, mate. Do not
let them tell you otherwise because they
wouldn't go back to them. As simple as
that. They wouldn't go back to them.
Anyways, if you're not going to join um
Streamyards, then I'm not going to keep
going back and forth with these stupid
accounts that are typing.
Is that fair, Grezy?
There's no point me reading out
comments. If someone wants to debate,
they can they can join.
Yeah. Yeah. You keep saying that.
Anyways, so and you know what? I don't
even like talking about this to be
honest, bro. It's so toxic. It's toxic.
It's depressing. So, unless you've got
anything to say on the [ __ ] um Streamyards
um then I'm not interested. Simple. That's that. Yeah,
the link is up. Let me put the link up again.
So, anyone wants to join, they can join. Come on.
I want to ask you a couple of questions
and you can ask me questions. No talking over. Yeah.
I want a I want a nice debate now. You
know, these [ __ ] have got me in the
mood. Greasy. I want a [ __ ] debate.
I want a [ __ ] debate. Now I can't
even get through to Lex anymore because
he's blocked me.
Don't know why he blocked me.
Bit rude, isn't it?
He couldn't answer the whole um
Nope. You're not coming in and sending
nudes. I know who you are. [ __ ] off.
Um what was I saying now? You're not
coming into Why are you coming in trying
to put up nudes? So, are you that
disabled or something? Like, we're
trying to have a content stream. We're
trying to have people come in and have a
debate with us and you're trying to put
up nudes. Like, are you a [ __ ] or
something? Like, it's not even it's not
I'm not even saying this to be funny.
I'm being serious right now. You can see
we're trying to have a debate
and you're you're coming in putting up
nudes. Are you disabled or something,
bro? Like, serious, man.
So, are you going to come in mobin and
say this stuff directly to me?
Yeah. You wonder why I'm alone. Really?
I mean, we've been through this before.
We've we've been through this.
We've already been through this. So, are
you going to come up and have a talk or what?
So, you going to come in
Are you going to come in and have a
debate or what? Are you just going to
keep repeating yourself?
Hello. What's going on?
Hello. We're not talking about Greavves
now. We're talking about me and you. Yeah.
Yeah. Whatever. Are you going to come in
and have a talk? We're not talking about
Greavesy now. [ __ ] Greavesy.
I'll time him out for 5 minutes if you want.
So, you're not you're not joining? No
one wants to join?
No. The link's there.
Grievy, why are these people not joining?
Oh, Lex, Lex. Oh, Lex. Lex. Women
changed their mind. Lex. Oh, Lex. Lex.
Oh, Lex. That guy is being horrible to
me. Ban him, Lex. Ban him. Oh. Oh, Lex.
Lex. I'll give you £50, Lexi. Ban him,
Lexi. Ban him. Ban him. Ban him. He's
telling the truth, Lexi. Oh, Lexi. Lexi.
Lexi. Burn him. Lexi. Oh, he's 2v one,
Lexi. And he's still being you. Oh,
Lexi. Lexi. Lexi. Burn him. Burn him.
He's hit the nail on the head. Lexi.
Burn him. Burn him. Lex. Lex. Lex. Lex.
He's stating the truth. Burn him. We
need Lex. Get another woman in to shout
over him. Lex. Get him. Lex. Get him.
You tell him, son. Come on, Lex. Don't
like it when I do it, do you?
Do you? Do you? Oh, Lex. Lex is a good
man. Lex is a very good man. Oh, Lex.
Lex is a good man. Oh, bless Lex. The
guy that tries to educate men, but he's
not educating himself. He's so educated
that he lost an argument against me. And
I turn another woman into shout over me.
But Lex is so educated.
Lex. Lex. Lex. Lex, Lex, you're so educating.
Oh, Lex. Oh, Lex, can I suck your dick,
Lex? Oh, Lexie,
stop it. It's embarrassing, bro. It's embarrassing.
Oh, Lex is an educated man, but he
couldn't even win an argument against
Peter Berry. He couldn't even win an
argument against Peter B.
Lex. Oh, so my name is Lex, everybody.
And oh, I sound a bit like a girl, but
um I'm not gay, I promise you. Um yeah,
so I really really think that it's men
that are the problem and not women. No,
women, they don't do anything wrong.
Women do. Oh, I've had my nails painted
today. Grievesy, do you like them? Um,
so I generally generally think the world
would be a better place without without
men. I generally think it is it is it is
men that are the problem. Um, you know,
when it comes to dating, nothing to do
with women. Oh, no, love. They're perfect.
Join us. Join us. Join us. Join us on
our our little adventure.
You all right, Grey?
Where do you live, son? Do you want to
go on a date? We can talk about how bad
how bad how bad men are. Even though I'm
a [ __ ] man myself. Yeah, I'm I'm a
big puddter, but you know, you know, I'm
a big puddter, but I'll happily take you
on a date.
It's It It is madness. It is. It is
generally [ __ ] madness to be honest.
Oh, was that you? Yeah. Come back. Oh, I
thought it was a fake you. Join again.
Join again. Join again. Join again. Oh,
one I thought it was a fake Q. My bad.
Sorry. One second.
Hold on. Hold on. Yeah. Yeah, I thought
it was a fake. One sec. One sec.
I thought it was a fake. My bad.
Sorry, there's a lot of people that
tried to put nudes up. Was that you?
Yeah. Okay, join again. I'll let you in.
Come on, love. Let's talk about how bad
men are and how innocent women are.
Women are. Men are bad, aren't they?
Very, very bad. We We It's not a debate.
It's not a debate. Even though if you
beat me, I'm going to kick you out, but
it's not a debate because if you say
that word, I'm calling the [ __ ] bomb
squad. I'm calling the bomb squad on
you, right? It's not a debate. Just two
people chatting. Okay.
>> Yeah, I'm all good. You don't
>> You're right, C. You're all right, Captain.
>> Yeah, I mean, I'm not the one make I
mean, I feel like
>> So, why why do you keep sucking this Lex's dick?
>> So, sorry. Just to clarify, it's two
hours now since you got booted. You're
still winging on about it. I I just you
know what I just can't I can't believe
it. I just can't believe why you'd let
someone on a podcast and then ban them
when you're losing. It just it's
>> a podcast.
>> It's well whatever it is a stream.
Whatever it doesn't matter what it is. I
mean you've let you've let me in. You've
spoke to me. You've added someone on to
shout over me then kick me. I mean that
what is the point of that?
>> I mean firstly the person you spoke to I
don't speak for the either of these
people. They're their own people. I
support the stream clearly,
>> but I don't speak for them. But have you
ever you've obviously never been to
watch it before?
>> No, I I got I got into it through Grevy.
He told me about um told me about him.
>> If you
>> I've been speaking to him on Instagram. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, if you had watched it before,
you would understand that it's a it
isn't a debate. And you before you mock
that you obviously you're going to talk
about that in a minute.
>> I [ __ ] am. You know you know
>> the reason. >> Yeah.
>> The reason they stress that so much is
because it is genuinely supposed to be
an educational space. It's not for
clicks. It's not for views. It's for
there are some people that are part of
that platform now that were really
heavily redpilled that are now not and
they are really invested in helping
other people do the same. That is all.
So there are also moderators. I'm sure
you have moderators.
>> I I actually don't have moderators to be fair.
>> Fair enough. Okay. It's a it's a big
plat. Some people do, some people don't.
Whatever. One of the people you spoke to
is a moderator. That's why she came up
in the box. >> Yeah.
>> There's people in
>> Let Lex supports women. That's what his platform is.
>> But but the problem is you said that
it's education, but all she done was
shout over me and didn't give me a
chance to talk. How is that education?
That sounds more of a debate to me. No,
>> you can't think back to anything you
said that was problematic at all.
No, I was talking about how a woman led
me on and I was sharing my experiences.
What was problem problematic about that?
Do you want me to lie or what? I mean,
>> no. Um, I mean, you're in like you've
got your experience from your point of
view. Do you want to know why people
said that there were so many red flags
involved in what you said?
>> I would love to know. Yeah.
So I know your narrative is very much
that I haven't seen these messages so
you know I can't comment to what was
said but the way you described that that happened. You
said that you took spoke to somebody you
met them in a bar. You then spoke to
them over the week and you were led to
believe you started you prefixed this
conversation with that this woman owed
you something because she'd been talking
to you all week. That's not how it goes.
>> Right. And I and I specified that the
you saying about how people don't owe
you anything is to try to justify a
woman's shitty behavior because we never
ever hear about men not owing anyone
anything. You can't, right, keep using,
oh, a woman doesn't owe you anything
every time she does something shitty. It
doesn't wash. No, no, no, no, no.
Anything. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
One second. One second. You're using it
in the wrong context. Right. If
someone's lying in bed saying, "Oh, I've
got no money." No, no, no, no, no. You
can say that. You can't say that
somebody doesn't owe you anything when a
woman does something shitty. And it is
only when a woman does it. We never hear about
>> the relationship transactional. And
that's not if you want a successful
relationship, it cannot be transactional.
>> So if somebody Okay. Okay. So if
somebody doesn't owe you anything, why
would they be leading somebody on for a
week? What sense? What what what
connection does that have it? You're
using it in the wrong context. That's
what I'm trying to say. You're using it
in the wrong context.
>> You said she owed you something at the
start of the
No, I said she led me on. When did I say
that somebody owed me something? So the
things you were saying it's it was very much like
>> I've spoke to her this many times so
therefore she owes me a shag and that is
not how it works.
>> What I never said somebody owes me a shag.
>> No but that is how you made it sound and
that is why people
>> So me okay so me saying okay so me
saying so me saying somebody is leading
me on me stating facts equals me wanting
a shag. Can you explain that one please?
That doesn't make sense. the way you
described it like it was like therefore
I did this, she did this, therefore this
should have been what happened. What
else would you think someone talking to
you she you used her complimenting you
as uh her an example of how she led you on?
>> Women celebrate people. Women c I tell
my female friends that they look fit
because they often do like and they
women mean a compliment as a compliment.
There's not a hidden agenda. >> Okay,
>> some women are not. There's going to be
problematic women just like there's
problematic men. There will be people
that treat people like [ __ ] There will
be women that treat people like [ __ ]
There is no denying that happens. Like
some women can be shitty.
>> There's no doubt about that. But this whole
>> narrative of oh she spoke to okay let me
askation she's going to sleep with you
>> so what would you say right okay no one
said anything about sleeping you're
making stuff up
>> so you're not you're who said anything
you want then
>> I've how okay I'll explain it again yeah
because some of you wanted to speak talk
over me okay so they gave me their
number they've messaged me back and
forth asking me questions for a week.
Okay. So, if somebody wasn't needing
somebody on, they would say within the
first or second or third message, "It
was nice meeting you. I don't want
anything further rare." Or they just
wouldn't reply. Anything more than that
is leading somebody [ __ ] on. It's
obvious. It's common sense, right? And
let me let me just ask you this. Let me
just ask you this. Would you be saying
the same thing if I was gay and a man
was doing it? No, you wouldn't. No, you
[ __ ] wouldn't. And I'll be and I'll
be willing to I'll be willing to test
that I would be willing I would be
willing to test that theory out as well
to be honest.
>> I mean you can test whatever theory
>> how how how was she how was she leading
me on because she was saying about meeting it.
>> So how is that how does that
>> Okay. What Okay. What does leading
someone Okay. Okay. Explain to me what
leading someone on means then. Let's
let's hear what you what you think leading
>> you messages saying I can't wait till we
do this this and this. as if you were
going to be in a relationship or you
were going to have sex or it was going
to be a casual thing.
>> Why does it need to be sex with someone
leading someone under?
>> Why does why this the conversation keeps
going back to sex?
>> Why does it keep going back to sex?
>> I used three examples. You picked the
sex one out.
>> Okay. So Okay. So, okay. Okay. So, a
woman that has no intentions of meeting
you but keep texting you and saying
she's going to meet you is not leading
you on. Okay. Thank you. Okay. Fair
enough. Whatever you say.
>> People are friends, right? Like
friendship exist. Oh my god.
>> You're just going to keep justifying
everything they do. Like it's just a
waste of time. It really really is,
mate. If somebody wasn't leading you on,
they would tell you straight they're not
interested. It's it's anything more.
They're leading you on. Or to be fair or
or if they stated their intentions from the getgo.
>> Sorry. Is is there is a woman never
allowed to have friends if ever again if
they or so I have lots of people. I have
friends that are male. I'm married. I
have friends that are male and female and I
>> am I not allowed to have those male friends now?
>> Well, she didn't state that she wanted
she didn't state that she wanted to be
friends until after seven days when
she'd already let me on.
>> She didn't know and you didn't know she
didn't know. Okay. Okay then.
>> But honestly,
people don't know. She didn't like you
might not have known. You might have
changed your mind after a week. Why is it a
>> never ever changed my mind in my life
unless I've met the person?
>> That's weak. That is weak. That is very
>> I mean,
you realize you say quite a lot of
problematic things, right?
>> And you realize you keep making excuses
for [ __ ] women. I'm sick of it. I'm
[ __ ] sick of it. We never ever hear
Okay. Why do we never hear these
excuses? Okay. Why do we never Why do we
>> You have used so many [ __ ]
problematic words in the time I've been
here. Maybe you just said a few of them
and you just thought, "Fuck me. I'm out here."
>> No, I never. I've got the whole I've got
the whole conversation. So now you're
making up stuff again. So you're trying
to have a debate with me, but you've
making up stuff the whole time. You're
talking about sex when no one said
anything about sex. Okay, let me ask you
this question. Okay, so let me ask you
this question. Yeah. No, I don't think I
made Matthews at L. So, at the end of
the day, right, why do we never hear
about men not owing anyone anything?
I've never heard it in my life. Can you
Why have we never heard it?
>> You're on YouTube banging on about it
now. Sort your [ __ ] out. Do it yourself.
You know what I'm saying?
>> Women don't need to do your work for
you. We don't We're talking about our
rights. Go talk about your own [ __ ]
rights. It was international.
>> But we're talking about We're talking
about double standards. We're talking
>> No. No. We're saying
>> and listen, Autumn, you need to remove
your You need to remove your filters,
you fat ugly bastard. Autumn, you need
to remove your filters. And another
thing is Yeah. And another thing I don't
understand is why do these women keep
moaning that they can't find someone but
keep going to these same drug dealers,
the same abusers every single time.
There's no coincidence. There's no
coincidence that they just keep going
for the same men. It's no coincidence.
>> Who are all these women that are going
>> loads of loads of women? You want me to
You want me to name you every single
one? You want me to name you every single one?
>> No. No. You You're saying
that women all do this and your mad
example that people are in prison with
girlfriends. They might have been in a
relationship before they went to prison.
>> Yes. But they go for drug dealers. They
go for abusers and they go for these
toxic men. There's no They moan. They
moan about men to meet a drug dealer.
>> They moan realistic.
>> They moan about men, right? But it's the
men that they choose that they like and
then they generalize like me. I'll tell
you why I generalize women because I've
never been shown I I'll explain it. I'll
explain I have I I will tell you why I
generalize women cuz I've gave them the
benefit of the doubt for years and they
all seem to be the [ __ ] same. Now
women, they choose these men that they
keep banging. They they will literally
go for these men. They don't come across
these men. They go for these men. And
yeah, okay, there might be loads of
creeps and loads of bad men, but there
is genuine people that try with them and
they're not interested. Just shut up and
stop moaning about [ __ ] men cuz we're
sick of hearing it.
>> So why Sorry. Your issue seems to be
that people Yeah. From what you've said,
they sound like bad choices. Like I I
don't know why someone would want to get
involved with someone like that. However,
>> well, you Well, you should know you're a woman. suggesting,
>> "No, I'm happily married and honestly,
and none of those things you've said
even stack up close to the [ __ ] hot man
my husband is, so let's not do that."
Um, and do you know what? You banged on
quite a lot about how they say it's their personality.
I'm very lucky. My husband's fit and has
a great personality. But people mean
that. Women do mean that. like you will
any relationship that has longevity has
to have more than physical attraction.
And they do mean that. They know that.
Like if you're having an issue and it's
people saying they want someone with a
different personality, they don't like
your personality. That's all.
>> Yeah. But but did you hear about the
Tinder experiment that told Lex?
>> Um no, I don't think I did.
>> Okay. Okay. So, basically, right, there
was this thing where they put uh a
profile of an average guy um on Tinder.
I think it was Tinder. It was Tinder.
And he was trying to get like a woman
and that. And he was struggling. No
matter what he was trying, he was
struggling. And then they done a picture
they made a profile of a better looking
guy and he was telling these women that
they that he was a sex end of that bit.
>> So, that very much contradicts and I've
done my own experiments on this as well.
I've done my experiments as well.
>> How many women are we talking?
>> Quite a few, mate. Quite a few.
>> You said you were away and find the
source as a record.
>> So, it's definitely definitely a
physical thing. Even though women never
>> the last two [ __ ] hours you've been winging on.
>> I mean, duh. No, I haven't. But so why
is that then? So why why so why is that
then? Why is that?
>> I don't know. I'd like to hear more
about it. So I'm
>> And did you hear about the person now?
Did you hear did you hear about the
person that I met three weeks ago as
well? That was another example. >> Yeah,
>> I've asked you for more information
about a study that you've quoted ideal
in fact because if we both want to
anecdote off, we can do that and but it
make no difference because I could make
it up and you can make it up. Like it
doesn't matter. We can both say and we
can have a [ __ ] life off Olympics or we
can say this has happened to me. Let's
just deal in fact. So come on, where's
this Tinder study?
I I'll show you it if you want. I'll put
it up on YouTube.
>> I will do I will do after this live
show. I will do
>> it now. Like
>> I'm not doing I'm not doing it right
now. I'm I'll have to find it. I'll find
it. I will find it for you. I'm not
doing it right now. I'll find it for you.
>> I can Google cuz actually I can multitask.
>> I'll find it for you. It's on my phone.
I'll find it for you. It's not a problem
at all, mate. I've put enough [ __ ] on
this channel. You I don't think you
realize I've put a lot I've put a lot of
videos and [ __ ] on this channel where
women have led people on and stuff where
women have led people on. Yeah. So,
>> so Tinder experiment
>> and I'll show you some more boards.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. >> Experiment.
>> And I'll do even more experiments if you
want me to. >> Yeah.
>> I don't What? You're going to get your
own [ __ ] lab out and do some experiments?
>> I would. I will do. I [ __ ] will do. Yeah.
>> The problem is
you're the test and you're hugely
problematic. No one's going to want to
say yes to you. But but again again
again it's a very physical thing because
when you pretend to be a a child
predator and you're better looking these
women have no problem. Contradicts the
whole they go for personality is my
whole point. It's [ __ ] Yeah. And
this is what I was saying to Lex, right?
Yes, men are shallow. We never said that
men are shallow, but women will reject a
guy for having blue eyes and not green
eyes. They're the most shallow people
out there, mate. They are. They
generally are. And I have no problem proving it.
>> No. No one's saying that people don't
have types. Like, no one's saying that. >> yeah,
>> no one's arguing that. You find people
attracted for different reasons.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no. But women have
got unrealistic expectations and they will literally
>> I've told you what I think they want.
>> Mr. Eternally single, you know what
women want? Yeah.
>> Um, how many women have I met over the
years? I don't think you I don't think
you really know, do you?
>> Women have stuck though, have they?
>> Okay. I have met none of So I have not
met any of these women more than once.
>> So okay. Okay. So you
>> you hadn't I I don't know.
>> So if I So if I So if I was in one
>> now is
>> So if I was in one or two relationships,
does that automatically mean I would
know all about every single woman then?
I don't get I don't catch your logic
with that. Explain a bit more with that
one, please. So do I need to be in two
or three relationships to to I don't I
don't understand. Have you had a long-term relationship?
>> No. Do I need one?
>> I mean, it sort of suggests there's a
bit of a problem. How old are you?
>> Yeah. Women have got unrealistic
standards that And I will prove this to
you. Yeah. And I will prove it to you.
>> Sometimes a [ __ ] person just can't get a
partner. Like you
>> Okay. Well, explain these. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Explain the drug dealers and the
women Explain the drug dealers and the
women beaters. Explain them. Explain how
these people have women. Can you explain it?
>> Most experienced domestic violence. I'm
explaining it. You just couldn't let me
finish, which I imagine you don't let
any women finish, whether that's in bed or talking.
>> Wasn't the Wasn't the Wasn't the last
woman shouting over me, then kicked me.
Or did you just miss that bit before I
let you finish?
>> Okay. She shouted over me. She shouted
over me as [ __ ]
>> She shouted over me and I got kicked out.
>> Yeah, everyone saw that. Okay, continue.
>> Um I mean, okay, cool. That's what you think. Um,
>> no. That's what I know. I was the
reality. You were
>> Okay. So, hold on. She wasn't shouting
over me. So, she wasn't shouting over
>> at you.
>> No, she was shouting over me. So, I couldn't talk.
>> You were saying predatory things. She
was shouting at you. Yeah.
>> What the [ __ ]
>> Okay, whatever. Continue. Anyways,
>> most people that experience domestic
violence, the person does not show
themselves as someone that is domest is
a violent person when they start the
relationship. That is a fact. You can
look it up. >> Really?
>> What do you mean? Really? I can facts.
>> There's no way these women can go
through go for drug deal and abusive
men. There's no way they can keep going
back to them. There's no way. There's no
>> I'm sorry, man. There's no way.
>> The problem is once you're in that
relationship, you do you understand how
they work? Have you done much research into
>> No, I'm stupid. I don't know anything.
>> I didn't call you stupid. I'm not
telling you that. I don't know anything.
No, I don't I don't know anything.
>> And just for future reference, calling
whilst we're doing this, when you're
saying things like I'm not stupid,
that's an abless thing, which is a
problematic thing, like some of the
things you said, calling gay people
[ __ ] and things like that. Those are
things that will make women not like you
and decent humans not like you.
>> Well, let me tell you something. Women
have got a really stinking bad attitude
and I' I can prove that on some of my approaching videos.
>> Excuse you calling people. So what do
you think about their accountability?
>> What do you think about their stinking attitudes?
>> Because we never hear about I'm not homophobic.
>> You were calling people [ __ ] think slur.
>> Okay, now you're saying about me and
whatever, but I have met so many women
with disgusting, horrible, entitled
attitude. Let's talk about that cuz we
don't touch on that enough times. You
want to try and blame See, the thing is
with you people, right, you like to try
and blame the man for everything. That's
what you That's Yes, you do. Okay, then
why are you sat there saying about what
I've said when we all know that women
are [ __ ] They are absolute
[ __ ] and I will prove it. If I have
to put up if I need to put up every
single one of this screenshot again, >> calling
>> a man.
>> Yeah, I will do it.
>> Person a [ __ ] or you calling you said
you called someone a [ __ ] like you you
or a [ __ ]
>> Was them people them people were slating
me. Them people were slating me.
>> Doesn't matter.
>> Yes, it does matter. Yes, it does matter
because those people are not those
communities that you're slagging off.
So, you're just using other communities
that are marginalized to offend other
people. And that's
>> Terry, listen. Terry, Terry, Terry,
listen. Yeah. Don't make me come to
again and and and fight you again, you
sad little bastard. >> Yeah.
>> So, you asked about why do they go back
to people that are domestically violent. >> Yes.
>> The way that works is it starts off
slow. And I'm not saying men haven't
experienced domestic violence before you
ask that. There is cases of it. There
are. It's significantly different um in
numbers, but it it's it does happen. And
I'm not deterring anything from that.
It's [ __ ] Whoever it happens,
>> get owned, mate. The only thing that
gets owned is you, Terry. You [ __ ]
broke little [ __ ] [ __ ] And yet
another thing is so I'm more than happy
to put these messages up where these
women are being [ __ ] which
contradicts the whole oh women want
somebody that's a good person. They're
not good people. I can prove they're not
good people. And if I have to put every
single meal in the
>> If I have to put every single message up
of these [ __ ] women up, I will do
it. Don't try and say they want someone
with a positive attitude. They are [ __ ]
>> But is it possible any of these women
have watched some of your content in the meantime?
>> No, there's not. And do you want me to
put all of this stuff up and prove you
wrong? I will happily do it again. I'll
happily do it again. I mean, you
constantly I mean, even from the start,
you won't even admit when a woman's
leading someone on for [ __ ] sake.
You've got a million and one excuses for
them. It's pathetic.
>> If she led you on, I don't give a [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Yeah, I don't. But stop defending
them, [ __ ] They're [ __ ] That's
it. Is it?
>> She might. Honestly, you might have just
>> her off with your personality or she
might speak to you. I can't speak for
>> What about the women that have got
stinking dirty attitudes? What about
them women that apparently go for
personality? What about them stinking
dirty women? What about them? Come on.
>> You're saying that women No, no, no, no.
You're just saying I don't even
>> You're saying women go for personality.
What about these stuck up women that
have got no personality? What about
them? Let's touch them. these women
stuck up. I have got people, listen
mate, I have got people where I've tried
to speak to them and they've been stuck
up straight away. Make it make sense
when you're saying women personality
makes sense. So like so you're backing
out now. Really? Yeah.
>> No. How are you? I'm still happy to talk
about this. So tell me how are they
stuck up? What what are they saying that makes them
>> their attitude? Their attitude.
>> Okay. Is that
>> There's no point explaining it cuz
you're just going to keep you're just
going to keep defending them. So there's
no point. You've got your way of
thinking. Women don't leave people on.
They go for personal and I will show
everything that they have done. >> Yeah.
>> I'm the one that's backed out and you're
like, I know I'm never going to change
that your mind. You're just going to
keep them. You're an absolute idiot.
Women don't go for personality. They're
more stuck up and shallow than men.
You're delusional. You're delusional. If
you really want to keep on this channel,
I'll put everything up. I don't care.
>> Yeah. Go on then. Put it. I I
I can only tell you what the facts say,
what the government reports say on
things that have happened and I can only
obviously tell you about my own experience
>> and I can tell you about my experiences
as well and I can tell you about mine
and I can tell you about mine as well. I
mean I can show mine as well.
>> Blame all these women. >> Yeah.
>> But you and say that women keep picking
the wrong men yet you seem to be picking
people like that don't work out. Like,
have you thought maybe you're an issue
in this factor?
>> I mean, there's videos where I've
literally said one word to someone and
they've been stuck up. So, not really. No,
>> but what was the word?
>> Um, hi, how are you? Um, you look nice
today. Yeah, really like don't don't get
me putting all of this stuff up.
>> I'm asking for context.
>> Yeah, I'm asking. So, was this on a
dating app? Was this via message? Is it
>> in real life? No, I don't I don't I
don't meet people on dating apps. I just
meet people in well I meet people in
real life. Yeah.
>> So do you know what's going on in that
person's life that day and that they
might not want to talk to someone?
>> Yeah. But the problem is they're moaning
that they can't find men. That's that's
that's the problem. And and the thing is
And the thing is one second I don't
know. And it doesn't even matter because
they're never honest anyways. They don't
sit there and say oh they don't want to
speak to someone. They lead people on
and play games. So whatever's going on
in their life doesn't justify it. And
when you see these screenshots, you will
know, won't you?
>> Your screen What could possibly have to
be absolutely wild to change my mind?
>> What could be going right through
someone's mind or in their life where
they have to just constantly lead people
on and take the piss? I mean, I've had
people blatantly troll me over WhatsApp.
What's going on, bro? But like blatantly
done it as well. Yeah.
>> What do you mean troll you?
>> What I mean they've they've literally
trolled me. What do you mean? What do
you mean? What do I mean? You don't know
what trolling means?
>> How is that to do? I do, but how is that
to do with women? Like, I don't I don't understand.
>> Because it was the women that was trolling me
>> about what?
>> About, you know, when I've got their
number and stuff trolling me, saying
that they were going to meet and then
they never. What's possibly going on in
their life, bro, that's making them do
that? Is someone Is someone putting a
gun up to their head making them do this
every day? Do you know much about
flight, fright, freezing, thorn?
>> Go on.
>> So, I don't know how much you look into
any of this stuff. One in three women
has been sexually assaulted,
>> right? Yeah, I I know about that.
>> As a trauma response, various things can
happen. You will either f freeze, fight
your flight, or sometimes there's a
thorn. And the thorn is where you
go into a self-p protection mode and you sort of
I don't know you try to deescalate the
situation is the best way I could
describe it. So people and this is not
me saying this is you just to be very
clear but if they've gone through a
traumatic experience recently and
they're in those throws and they just
freeze and they just are too scared to
say no and I'm not saying it's because
they're scared of you. They might be too
scared because the last person that they
said no to beat the [ __ ] out of them or
raped them. So
>> there might be reasons for it. One in three women
>> can't be harmed that often. You if you
know women in your life,
>> you must know like most women you know
will be able to tell you about an
experience that's happened to them. And
and it's not this man is a [ __ ] man or
he doesn't earn enough money or he's not
look. It is they've been from a it
starts in school from a teacher saying
something dodgy to you. Like I can only
tell you one thing that like my teacher
said to me which was I used to go to a
swimming pool and he would say to me as
a 14year-old girl in front of the whole
class, I didn't recognize you with your
clothes on today Sarah. as if that isn't
really [ __ ] problematic.
That's that wasn't even the first
experience. And that was not even like I
barely remember that. That's just
because it it's so often that these
things happen to from going out having
your ass grabbed all the time like to
>> the if you say you if I if I go into a
live like Lex is
>> do you know how many death threats I get
after kicking muting someone that day? Maybe three, >> right?
>> From men. Here's but here's here's the
thing to report to the police because
they escalate so much. So this isn't
just someone saying like I don't know I
I've got a thick skin like I don't
really give a [ __ ] about most things but
this is people that escalate and it gets
to the point where it's sinister and
that's a day. So
>> if you think I'm really lucky like my I
have a husband and sons and they are I
the men I know in my life are brilliant
but then all the men in the world.
>> So what you're saying is then why are
they leading people on over messages? I
know what you're saying. No, no, I know
what you're saying. You're saying that
you know they're they're you know they
can't trust people because of you know
what you've said. But that doesn't
justify them leading people on. That's
got nothing to do with anything. You
you're failing to to stick to the
subject. And and before before you you
talk, when they do come ac
I can give you an example. Um 3 weeks
ago where I've met someone and they
messaged me on Snapchat. We was going
back and forth for two. Now bear in mind
I don't care anymore. I don't expect
anything. Now they turned around and
said to me about how you're this, you're
that. good everything that somebody
would want to be with, but they're not
interested. So, at the end of the day,
it's even when they come across people
that are not like that, they're not
interested. So, they can't moan. And
also, it doesn't mean And also, so when
they come across someone that's not like
all of these men that they're that
they're claiming, then they're still not
interested. So, what what what's what
what do you want? It doesn't make sense.
So, have you ever sense asked? No. I'm
So, have you ever after this has
happened asked what? Like, have you ever
asked what went wrong with
>> the last one? I didn't. No, they they
turned around and said to me that you're
sweet. You're this. Thanks for coming up
to me that day. Reed. Now, this is an
example. Now, they were saying all of
these things. Now, surely to God, you
would give someone a chance. I mean, I
would if I'm if I if someone's come up
to me and they're all of these things, I
would I would give them a chance. They
haven't. I don't don't care, but I'm
saying if I was to put myself in their
shoes, wouldn't they want that?
Especially if someone's come up to them,
>> but so what?
>> But why?
>> So, what was the right thing for her to
do in that situation?
>> What was the right thing?
>> Obviously, not interested in you
anymore. Whether she was or wasn't, I
can't speak for her. you can't speak for
her it. What was the right thing to do
at the point she didn't want to be with
you? What was the right thing?
>> Uh not respond back or respond back
saying uh yeah it was nice to meet you
reta t and that's that that's it. And
also um please do not complain that you
can't find a normal nice guy.
>> That's that's what does me. They do.
Women do. They generally generally
generally do. They generally moan and
winge and complain and but yeah, to
answer your question, just
>> reply once or twice and that's it. And
then just say then
>> she didn't know until she'd spoken to
you for a few days. Like just because
she didn't immediately say no.
>> Okay. I mean, know what?
>> No. Know what?
>> Know what exactly?
>> If something was going to grow out of
it, like she doesn't know. You don't
know. You only time tells you that. Like
if she didn't know,
>> but there was no but there was no time. >> Sorry.
>> There was no time. You didn't you didn't even
>> led you on for
>> I mean, you know, I'm not saying she led
me on, but I was I said that's that
would have been the right thing to do.
I'm saying that she's saying that I'm
all of these things. Now, I'm saying
that if I found a woman, cuz very much
what I do all of these years is I'm
trying to find a woman that's not toxic,
that's not all of these things, but they
all seem to be the same. No matter what
people say, women always prove they're
the same. You can say something
different. [ __ ] Henry up the road can
say something different, but they will
always prove that they're all the same.
So, if I ever if I very much come across
somebody that wasn't all the same, I'd
be [ __ ] happy. Especially if they've
come to me, but she for some reason said that.
So, it's crazy, isn't it?
>> Do you ever reflect on some of the stuff
you posted online and regret it? Because
there's some pretty bad stuff on there. >> No.
>> Right. Okay. So,
>> I don't
>> in the nicest possible sense. How do you
expect to attract a nice person when
you're threatening violence constantly?
I You did threaten Kitty. I came into it
here and you said, and it wasn't the
American one. I The whole No, no, no. Don't.
>> Yes, it was.
>> You did it about both of them because
you said she's lucky I didn't go to
Scotland. So, you were definitely not
talking about the American one.
>> No, it was No, it was America. It was
definitely the American. I would admit
it. I would admit if it was her, I would
admit it. Why would I deny it?
>> Why is it okay to threaten to kill women
or men? Like, why is it okay?
>> Because Because the American was was a
[ __ ] Simple as that, is it? It's
that's how it [ __ ] They don't
deserve to be dead. You're a [ __ ]
You don't deserve to be dead. Like you,
the things you've posted, I've been in
here and all you've done is talk about
how you've used really offensive
language about minority groups. You've
talked about how you've beaten the [ __ ]
out of people or that you will beat the
[ __ ] out of people and [ __ ] in their
mouths. What sort of woman do you think
is going to find that attractive also
attract a nice don't forget
>> right and and I'll explain it to you is
that these women because of these
experiences have made me like this now
before the before you say anything now I
generally believe if anyone went through
what I went through right some somebody
would have killed someone and I would
love to know what you would be like if
you had to deal with the same [ __ ] I've
had with women
>> no idea my life.
>> You ain't been through worse than me.
So, you're trying to Okay, so what
you're trying to say
>> have a [ __ ] life.
>> Can I Can I Okay, let let me talk. Let
me talk. Right. Let me just say something. Right.
>> I'm saying these things about women
because of my experiences with them time
and time and time again. It's warranted.
All of the things that I've said is is
completely warranted. They have been
nasty. They have been [ __ ] Something
that you keep dismissing as usual
because it doesn't suit you.
>> Saying some women aren't [ __ ] There's
some women that I think are massive [ __ ] but
>> And there's no And there's no nice women
out there. So that's
>> also untrue. I know a lot of women.
>> How How old are you? >> 43.
>> I'm 28. And I can guarantee you I've got
more life experience than you have.
>> Oh my god, you are so
>> I promise you. Oh, trust me. I promise
>> Saying this and then you never back it up. Okay.
>> Do you want me to tell you a bit about
me so we can decide who's worse off? And
I can tell you I've met more women than
you have. Believe you me, mate. I might
be I might I might be I might be [ __ ]
I might be might be bloody, you know, 20
years your senior, but trust me,
>> whoever thinks it's funny to be 43,
hopefully you'll get to 43 one day. It's
hardly a slam to go, "Oh, you're 43." Um,
>> are you from Manchester? >> No.
>> Well, where are you from?
>> The North. And I'm not giving you any
more than that because you've clearly
threatened people before. So, that would
be insane of me to give you any more
information like that about myself. >> Okay.
>> Um, I have a condition where my joints
dislocate every single day. I have to
staple my own skin back together every
every two or three days and put the
joint back in the place. So, um,
and most of the [ __ ] experiences I've
had of that is when male doctors have
been really dismissive. I've been
resuscitated because I've lost so much
blood from endometriosis.
>> Is that doing a chan? Sorry. Sorry.
>> It's okay. I mean, I presumed like you
wouldn't probably listen anyway.
>> No, listen. Go on.
>> Right. So, I have
>> like one of the like most minimal things
that has happened like that that that
happens every day. My life is putting my
joints back in and having to go to
hospital for that. I still try and live
like quite a full life, but I've had abusive
um stepparents. I've had there's a lot
I've been through and you can't decide
to that you know or have had a [ __ ]
life than me. Most people are carrying
trauma in their life. I I don't think
like I don't think
>> Yeah. And you don't know my experiences
with women. So before judging what
people have said, you might want to walk
try and walk a mile in their shoe.
That's same to you then. How can any of
them have done it? In the same way that
I can't blame I can't blame my husband
for the man that assaulted me.
>> You can't blame every woman. >> Okay.
>> No women are blaming every man. They're
saying can the man doing this? Stand up
for to the other men.
>> Wait, women are not blaming every man.
Are you sure about that? Cuz I've seen
many many times where women generalize all men.
Okay. Now, let me let me let me just um
tell you this. Yeah. Why do you think I
don't go out anymore trying to speak to women?
>> You said you did on Monday. >> Yeah.
>> No, it was last Thursday. Okay. And and
I explain it. And that was the first
time in a very long time. Do you know
why I don't go out and speak to women? >> No.
>> Because they're all the [ __ ] same.
>> I learned that. I put up with this [ __ ]
for years and years and years and I
thought this is [ __ ] late. This is
toxic, mate. That's why I don't bother.
And why I went out on Thursday? I went
out drinking. I actually went out
drinking for a laugh. I done it for a
laugh. You think I'm going to bother
with people that are all the same?
>> No, bro.
>> You're spending so much time talking
about it and being angry about it
>> because I went on Lex's channel earlier.
I went on I don't keep all that I don't
keep trying. I could be out today if I
wanted to. I could be out tomorrow. Why
am I not? I've got money. I've got the
money to do it. Ask yourself, why am I
not out every day at every because
they're all the same. And and let me
tell you something with this with this
Taiwan one I was telling you about for
last week, Sarah. I was giving them the
benefit of the doubt. You know, I don't
particularly find Tai people, you know,
attractive, but I I don't mind going out
having a laugh, you know, on on a
Saturday and not having to deal with any
toxic [ __ ] but again, they always prove
to be the same bullshiters. So, no one
cares anymore, you know?
>> I mean, what I mean, what's an end to
this conversation that's going to
satisfy you? Because like, I'm not going
to say all women are [ __ ] They're not. Like,
>> you don't need to, but every woman I
generally believe they're all the same.
>> And when when I'm proven wrong,
>> you think I know it. I like whoever that
is in the comments. I I I don't know who
you're on about. I've been married to
someone since I was 25
and I'm 43. I don't know who you're talking about.
>> Um, you know,
>> so yeah. Um, I mean that's I mean I've
given women years of benefit of the
doubt and they always prove they're the
same. Every single time they say Do you
know what I find so funny Sarah? How you
say that they're all different, right?
>> But they say the same stuff.
>> People are different. But they're saying
the same stuff as every red bill bro
that there is out there.
>> Bro, but but can they back up what
they're saying? Cuz I can back up what
I'm saying. They can't know though, can
they? I'm guessing whoever these people are.
>> Who? We government reports on what men
are doing to women. South Africa had to
have a day today where women left the
workforce and economy in protest because
so many women are being killed by their
partners and by feel bad for them
>> and women are [ __ ] so I don't feel bad
for them. So that's that. I mean you
>> that's where I'm out. I mean what's the
point? Like you if you think everyone
deserves that enjoy
>> when I'm pro listen when I'm proven
wrong by a woman I'll come back and I'll apologize. Simple.
>> So that's that. So that's simple as
that. See the thing is greasy right or
whoever this woman can say what she
wants all she wants. But my experiences
are my experiences. So that's that's that. Um
then that's literally it to be fair. So
that's it. I don't give a [ __ ] if she's
got a lovely [ __ ] voice. You can die
of cancer. [ __ ] women. They're
Who is that? Puna.
Puna. Kitty in the calavan. Go now up
the sides now.
Is that corner?
It is in the cupad.
You [ __ ] Welsh monk.
Ka it has to call the woman in the
cupad. [ __ ] Welsh [ __ ]
[ __ ] pair of [ __ ]
Pair of [ __ ] Kitty in the Caliban.
Listen mate, you don't want it with me
because I'm going I'm I'm going to be
going to Cardiff soon
to get a chicken tickon, mate. And I
will smash your [ __ ] face in. Think
about it, bro. Look of look at uh look at um
get a shave. Yeah, good one. How about
you suck my dick?
No, listen. I'm going to be going to
Cardiff soon cuz I need to go hit back
to my place, bro. I'll smash your face
in. Yeah. Didn't you see me the other
day with them [ __ ]
Uno in the caliban.
[ __ ] [ __ ] Pair of [ __ ]
Absolute pair of [ __ ] Yeah.
So that's that.
All women aren't the same. They [ __ ]
well are all the [ __ ] same. [ __ ] off, mate. Yeah.
Yeah. Get a shave. Uh
they're just going to keep it is a good
debate, but I think the thing is greasy,
right? Honestly, honest opinion there.
No [ __ ] It was a good debate, but
it's always going to be a thing of this, bro.
That they're saying one thing,
your experiences are always going to
prove different. So, it's going to be a
case of just two people are just going
to disagree. Um, and that's just how
it's always always going to be. So, you
know, that's the way it will always be.
We can have debates, we could talk every
day, but they can say one thing, your
experiences will always be different
with women. So, it's that's just how it
is, I think. You know, and and it is
good to let people on here and and and
stuff and, you know, but that's how it
is always going to be because one of the
things she said was about how women go
for personality and they go for nice
people. But the thing is, we all know
what women are like. We've I've shown
what they've done. I've shown my
approaches and what they're like and
whatever. So, it's always going to be
it's never going to be a case where we
agree and then we just like walk out.
Honestly, like all seriousness, you know,
because your experiences will always be different
no matter what they say. Like, okay, so
say for example, I'm speaking to this
woman. What's today? Today, Friday. So,
let's just say I decide to go out
tomorrow and start speaking to women. Griezy,
what do you think is going to happen?
What do you think will happen? So, I
mean, I'm not contradicting myself
because I generally don't try. I went
out last Thursday cuz I was bred out my
head for whatever reason and then that
put me off again, you know. It put me
off, bro. It's put me off for like 2
months even going out drinking before.
So, at the end of the day, So, at the
end of the day, mate, um, you know, um,
yeah, Bethany, good one. I've looked
smacked multiple times. Whatever. You
can keep trying to blame me. I don't
care. But you know the thing is I mean
it's put me off for seven eight weeks before.
Um so at the end of the day bro I mean I
can't when your experiences is different
to someone. You might think I'm being
awkward. You might think that I'm being
awkward and I'm being difficult but I
promise you I'm not. You know it might
come across I'm being difficult but I'm
not because this woman is saying one
thing. my experiences are saying other,
right? Or showing other and the fact
that you've gone out so many times,
giving these women the benefit of the
doubt to prove that they're different,
but none of them can. You know, you've
seen all the places I've been to. I
mean, you're the you're older than me
and I've been to more places than you.
I've traveled way more than you probably
ever will. Not a dig, obviously. Like,
I'm just saying in in in relation to
this, do you understand? in relation to
trying to find someone that's different,
which is how I got all of them WhatsApp
messages. So, whatever someone says, so
whatever someone says, Grezy, your
experiences will always show otherwise.
So, that's my that's my opinion on that.
And it might seem I'm coming across as
awkward, but I'm not, bro. I promise you I'm not.
you know, talking about how they go for
personality yet. They are [ __ ]
you know. I've never been beyond Belgium.
Really? I've never been beyond Belgium.
So, it's not up for her. It's not up for
me. It's not up for you. It's up for
these women to prove that they are
different. But they can't. And the thing
is, Grezy, she might go on this exposure
page and say, "Oh, you know, you've said
this, you've said that, you've said
this, you've said all of that." But what
these people fail to realize is they're
not in your shoes. They don't know what
you've experienced with women. They
don't know how many times that you've
given these women the benefit of the
doubt only for them to [ __ ] you over
again. Even, you know, even people that
you're not interested in. And you know,
as the old saying goes, there's only so much
someone can take. And I generally think,
Greavves, you laugh at this [ __ ] right?
And you think it's a bit mad. Anyone
else would have killed someone by now,
bro. If they were me, well, they would
have either given up or they would have
killed themselves. Hating on me. Yeah.
I've probably got more patience than a
lot of the [ __ ] population dealing
with their [ __ ] their lies, their
leading on the toxicity, their attitude.
you know, even people that I was not
texting. Literally, when I went out
three weeks ago on an approaching
session, the amount of attitude I had to
deal with with these women, bro, like
time and time and time and time and time
again. Um, it contradicts everything
they're saying. That's my whole point,
bro. That is my whole point. Do you understand? Yeah.
you know, and then they and then and and
and again, Grezy, like I said, it's it's
all right, but it's always it's always
going to be a case of, you know, your
experiences. You know what women are
like. It doesn't matter what anyone
tells you. What are they going to tell
you, bro? I mean, [ __ ] hell. Like,
they can't even admit when someone's led
someone on. They're always going to
defend women. Why they do it, I don't know.
It's very unhealthy, bro. They need to
ban social media.
So, I mean,
it just contradicts everything that they say, basically.
and and and everyone gets blamed all
because women have got unrealistic expectations.
You know, that's that's the thing.
Everyone gets the blame. Oh, you're
this, you're that, you're negative,
you're this. And it's all because women
have got unrealistic standards and they
think they're better than everyone. And
and I know cuz I've experienced this,
you know, and I don't want you telling
me one thing and I don't want me me
telling you another. I want to be proven
different by these women. I want to be.
No, it's not easy to get in a
relationship with apps. Not if you're
not a woman. It's not, mate. Not if it's
not a woman. Right. I think we're going
round and round around in circles now. I
think we should just just leave this
now. You've had your opinion. I've had
mine. I know my experiences. I know
exactly what I've been through and
what's going to continue to happen. So,
I think we should just leave it now.
We're not We're not getting anywhere.
And and the maddest thing is I I just
wanted to end but end end with this is
saying that don't forget I've still
given them the benefit of the doubt.
Grievesy despite having these arguments
I've still gone out given these women
the benefit of the doubt and they always
prove that they're the same. So it
doesn't it doesn't matter. It's you've
still given them the benefit of the
doubt. You know time and and and stuff.
These women are all the same. And I
wouldn't say it if I didn't believe it.
I would not. Um, you wants a woman who
grooms himself. Um, I groom myself every
time I've gone out, has a job, got a
job, got a good upbringing. A good up.
Right. We're going around in circles
now. I think it's best to just agree to
disagree. I think we're just going to go
round and round in circles and just
leave it at that cuz we're just having
the same argument over and over and over
again. We're not going anywhere. So, you
think what you want. I know what I've
experienced and agree to disagree. I
think that's just the best with that
one. So, if you want to think women go
for these things and whatever, that's
your life, bro. I know what I've
experienced. Um, so that's that's that.
I think that's the best way to be honest. So,
um, anyways, I think we'll just move on
from that now, Griezley. Um, if that's
all right. if that's all right with you, boss.
Because we're just going round and round
in circles now.
So, I mean, everyone see me looks max,
looks my best, and they're just going to
keep defending women. So, you're never
going to get anywhere. Just just just
ignore it now. They're always going to
nitpick and keep defending women. And if
you've got any kind of um sense that
that's going to happen, you you run a
mile. Unless you're going to actually
find someone that's not biased, there's
no point arguing with them. Um,
yeah, there's plenty of people like that
in the world now. So, there's there's no
point. So, they will say one thing,
women will prove another. So, so we're
just going around and around in circles
and they're always just going to keep
defending women. So, we're just wasting
all of our time.
So, yeah. So, that's that.
It's sad really though
cuz you know Yeah. Well, we're not going
to get into it anyways. I'm I'm leaving it now.
So, yeah, that's that. I think we made
pretty much good points.
So, yeah, they're always going to like
you. I could literally write put up all
of my approaches, me looking my best cuz
I've got another channel by the way, you
don't know. and they would still sit
there and defend women. So, there's no
point being in this whole argument.
There's no point being there's no um
there's no point because they're always
going to find a way to defend women. So,
my dad drank himself to death. Una,
you're not going to you're not going to,
you know, get a rise out of me, bro.
You're a fat old ugly man. You don't
know anything about my life. You don't
know anything about my dad. So, I mean,
no one in my family has got multiple
dads. Again, Luna, you're a fat old man.
Yeah. You You don't know anything about anyone's life.
But yeah, what did you say? You just
need to groom and look after yourself,
and that will get you women.
Oh, go, you need to get some life
experience. You're talking to someone like me.
Yeah. Okay, I'm the problem. Whatever.
You've made your point. I'm not going to
agree with you. You're not going to
bully me into agreeing with you. I know
what I've experienced and I've got my
videos and my messages. Simple. So, that's that.
I mean, I could give these people my
other channel of where I've looked my
best approach, but they're just going to
keep defending women. And you don't want
people that are just going to keep
defending women because it's pointless.
There's no point. They're always going
to lick women's asses. And these women
have got stinking attitudes as well. Add
bad attitude. And all I can keep
thinking about um Breezy is when this
woman was on here talking about how they
go for personality. Their attitude is
disgusting. You know, 3 weeks ago, bro,
when I went out approaching, their
attitude was disgusting. So that's kind
of why I went out like I went a bit high
rate. I went a bit high rate, bro. Like
their attitude was dile, bro. A lot of
these women. But then you've got a woman
trying to say to you that these women go for personality.
It contradicts everything she's saying.
That's why I raised my voice a bit. You
understand, bro? Yeah.
>> Yeah. It's madness, bro.
It's mad. They're always going to keep defending women.
I don't know what it is with them keep
defending women. You'll show them
everything that women do and they'll
still dismiss it. That's why I find so mad.
Okay, whatever. Whatever. Go Chan.
You're a fat old ugly keyboard. No one cares.
Yeah. More going for you. Okay. Anyways,
we're moving on now. Does anyone else
want to join?
We're moving on now anyways.
Moving on now anyways, but it's pointless.
Yep. We're just ignoring it now. Anyways,
I've shown my experiences. I've shown
women's attitude. If they want to
dismiss it, that's up to them, bro. I
don't really give a [ __ ]
And you're not coming in. You fat ugly
bastard. Lord Juna,
you're not going to get a reaction. Stop
it. It's boring now. Go crawl back under
the rock that you [ __ ] come from.
It's boring now. You're I'm not Monty or
Timmy. You need to You need to
understand this, Gona. I'm not Monty man
or Timmy. Stop it.
Like that's me telling you stop it. It's
embarrassing. I'm not Monty or Timmy. Yeah.
Anyways, you wanted a link. Join.
Yep. You're talking about my appearance.
Come on. Go. Come in and show us your face.
Go. I tell you what. Yeah. Why don't you
come in and show us your face?
Come on, bro. What are you scared of?
You ain't got anxiety, have you?
Come on, bro. You spoke about my
appearance. That's cool. That's cool.
That's cool. Come in and show us your
face. Come on, bro. What you got to
lose? Come on, bro. Talked about my
appearance, bro. I'm not letting that
fat ginger farey little projector on
Jay. Let Okay, let me let me let me tell
you something, Jane. Yeah, because you
might not believe me.
I don't go on anyone's channel on here.
Yeah, I don't go on no one's channel. L
J's, Virgin Boys, um, Red Star, all I
don't go on any of these people's
channel. I don't and I haven't for
weeks, weeks. I just go live on my
channel. If people come on here, they
come on here. I don't go on their channels.
And you know why I don't go on their
channels. So simple.
Yeah. So, you're speaking about my
appearance, Gona, but you're not coming
in. What? What? You're not a keyboard
warrior, are you, Jane? He's not coming
in. You're wasting your time.
How do I know they've been posting about
me? I don't know. They've been posting
about me. And guess what, Autumn? You
look like a [ __ ] impala,
mate. You wouldn't You know, all of
these women that get raped, you would
never have to worry about getting raped.
Go figure it out.
I don't know. know they're posting about
me. I'm assuming they're posting about
me because they're obsessed.
But I can tell you I have not been on
any of them channels in weeks and I'll
never go on it ever again
because I'm not an idiot.
You never have to worry about someone
[ __ ] raping you, mate.
Yeah, I was begging you. Yeah, I was
telling you to come in. Yeah, cuz I had
to talk about you.
I don't go on their channels, mate.
I don't go on their channels.
Autumn's an Oompa Loompa.
Bro, I don't like you either. You
[ __ ] fat [ __ ]
You [ __ ] fat bastard.
Yeah, you [ __ ] mad this
28 there. Okay, anyways, is anyone
wanting to join?
Is anyone wanting to join?
Come in, man.
Why don't you take your field? Guess
what? Guess what? Guess what? Yeah. I
ain't been to the Barbies for ages,
Autumn. Ages. But guess what? You can
never come here without any filters. You
could never come on live stream right
now without any filters.
How's about that one?
You can't [ __ ]
join without using filters. I've just
got a long beard, bro. I'm calm, bro. I
don't mind. I don't mind showing my
face. Looking a bit homeless right now
cuz I'm hibernating.
That's fine, bro. Show the beard off.
But guess what? Juna can't join, show
his face. Autumn can't join, show his
face. Isn't that madness? And look, I'm
I'm giving you the benefit of the doubt, bro. Look,
how can I talk about anyone's looks? Cuz
I mean I can show my I can show my face.
I mean I'm showing my face. So I can
talk about anyone's looks if I want to
because I'm showing my face. Yeah.
You need to [ __ ] off and get raped, you silly [ __ ]
That's what you need to do. [ __ ] off and
get raped, you silly [ __ ]
That's what you need to do, [ __ ]
Yeah, my hair's long, bro. I can
probably butt it up to be fair.
Yeah, you've pissed me off today. These
people have pissed me off cuz I hate
talking about it cuz women are scum of
the earth. So when you have someone
right on your live stream trying to
groom you. Yeah. Trying to [ __ ] groom
you. Trying to tell you that women are
different. [ __ ] eat a dick [ __ ] You
know what I mean?
Yeah. She didn't reject me. Go. We've
already been over this. You're boring.
You're boring, bro. You're a fat, bro.
Listen. Listen. Listen, Duna, right?
Look. Look at me, bro. Right now. Yeah.
You're telling me you're not better
looking than this? I haven't been to the
barbers for a long time. And you can't
come in and show your face, bro. Think.
Look at this hair. Goona. No woman's
rejected me. And anyways, I'll be in
Cardiff soon anyways, bro. So, you can
say all of this stuff to my face. I'm
sure you've seen the most two recent
videos. Listen, I'll be in Cardiff soon
anyways, so I'll I'll be sure to go
live. Don't worry about it, buddy. Make
sure you don't run away, though. Yeah.
Yeah. So, come in and show your face then.
Yeah. Come in and show your face.
[ __ ] off, you [ __ ] [ __ ] You're
not coming in for eyes. [ __ ] off. So, yeah.
Look at that beard, bro. Jeez.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that,
Gona. Like I said, I'll be in Cardiff
soon anyways in the kebab place. So,
yeah, I'll be in Cardiff soon anyways,
bro. Let's see how big you are a couple
of years later, bro. Yeah. You remember
when I first went to Wales, bro? You
would All I'd have to do Yeah. Is knock
you straight in your nose, bro? It be
It'll be over, bro. It will be over. It
will be over, bro. With a tally bam
beard, bro. just whack you one in your
face. Like you won't even be able to
stand up, bro. You'll be [ __ ]
Why are you not coming in, Gona?
What? You're not better looking than a
homeless person. You little mug. Stick
to trying to bully Timmy, bro. Stick to
trying to bully disabled people. Yeah,
stick to Stick to trying to bully
disabled people. Yeah, stick to trying.
stick to uh
really disabled people.
Never had a girlfriend. Have had a
girlfriend. Drinks alone. Guy with my
friends all the time. Eats alone. Ate
with my friends. M. You know, £1,100 a
month income. No, that's not true
though. Is it Gona? You don't know how
much money I've got.
£1,100 a month income.
Bro, did you see what I've just bought
the past two months?
You don't know how much money people have.
That's the irony of it. You don't know
how much money people have. How much
money do I have, bro? You don't know anything.
You literally do not know anything. How
am I wearing 200 pound jeans and you're
telling me that I'm on £1,100 a month?
How have I got jeans worth more than
your whole wardrobe and you're trying to
tell me I'm on £1,100 a month? You see
how that doesn't make any sense?
How does that make any sense when
someone has got jeans
that is worth more than your wardrobe,
bro? That's how skint you are. And
you're telling me that I get £,100 a month?
Okay, bro. Yeah. Okay.
When was the last time I was on £1,100 a
month? Stop it.
Stop it, bro. Just just just stop it.
So yeah. Yeah. I want to bet. Okay, bro.
I want to bet. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay, bro. I want to bet.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, bro.
How much did I win? So, you think
winning what? A couple of hundred pound,
bro. Do you know how much money I've
spent the past month? The amount of [ __ ]
I bought the past month. Okay, bro.
Yeah, there were birthday present for
mom. Yeah. Catalog, h Yeah, good one,
bro. Catalog. Yeah, you people really
are [ __ ] idiots.
You people really are idiots, mate.
I need to get a McDonald's in a minute.
I'm hungry, mate. Had fish and chips earlier.
Look at that beard. Jesus Christ. I'm
growing it, mate.
I'm growing it.
Yeah, mate. I've got more than you would
ever have, Gona. More than you would
ever have. More than you would ever
have. Tell Hey, I also went to your area
last time, Terry, and you didn't come
out. Tell him about that. Autumn, this
Terry told me to come to his area. We
had a little
push and shove, we call it the first
time. This [ __ ] told me to go to his
area. Went to his area. He didn't come
out. The little [ __ ] house didn't come
out. Tell him about that. Let all the
nut ladies know about your actions.
Let them all know about your actions, mate. I'm obese.
Definitely not obese.
Must be self- projecting there. Anyways,
um yeah, tell make sure you tell the
ladies about that.
Yeah, how you didn't come out, you
little [ __ ] Oh, sorry. I shouldn't
say [ __ ] Stare will come in and tell herself again. Oh yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I look ill. Thank you.
At least I don't have to worry about
getting raped like you.
It's okay for today, though, bro. Like
we can talk about this [ __ ] today, but
tomorrow we're not talking about this again
cuz it's unhealthy and it's unhealthy
for everyone to be honest. So we all
know women are the same. We all know
their [ __ ] So we don't need to keep
having people try to convince me
otherwise and me trying to get other
people to believe something
to make them understand. We're getting
nowhere. It's it's unhealthy, you know.
You know, it's uh it's very very unhealthy.
Very very very unhealthy. No,
we need to stop, bro. So,
yeah. James said she wanted to suck my
dick. She's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
I get pip. You don't know what I get.
Terry, you don't know anything about my
life. Stop talking.
We need to stop, bro. I don't go out
anymore trying because women are all the
same. I'm not. If I was actively going
out trying, right, and moaning about it,
then people can give me grief. But I'm
not. I stopped because I know what
they're like. I know they're all the
same. I know they're all [ __ ]
That's why I stopped. That's why I gave
up. I made a conscious decision to give
up. You know what I'm saying? So, I
don't know why we're we're going on
about this. I gave up to get away from
this and we're still talking about it.
You know, if I was out twice a week or
every week, then you can say, "Oh, well,
you're going but but we're not anymore."
So, you know,
on Reddit need to stop as well.
Yeah. Yeah. So, that's the thing, bro.
You need to stop um
clearly depressed. I'm not depressed at
all. I'm just hibernating. me depressed. Yeah. So,
uh No, I don't. I went out last
Thursday, bro, because I was bored. I
went out because I was bored. Yeah. I
went out because I was genuinely [ __ ] bored
and I didn't want to stay in. And then
it put me off again, you know? And that
was the first time in ages, a long time,
because women are all the same. I don't
need to keep trying to make people
understand. I don't give a [ __ ] you
know? So that's that, bro. I don't give a [ __ ]
So, they are all the same. I don't need
an old woman, a young woman, a man
trying to [ __ ] convince me otherwise.
I know what they're like.
They are all the same. What the [ __ ] is
the whole conversation? What's the point of it?
No, I'm definitely definitely not
depressed. Definitely definitely not
Definitely definitely not depressed, mate.
No, definitely definitely not.
Definitely definitely not. So yeah,
do you know what right I if this person
right come on here and said I don't like
what you said about kids kids I would
say you know what you win this is my
problem you're you know no I'm just
hibernating bro I'm just growing my
beard it's winter that's why I ain't
going to the barbers definitely
definitely not depressed
Then I'll be like, "Oh, okay. Well, I
mean, kids are innocent. Babies are
innocent, but they're [ __ ] innocent
people, bro. But women are not
innocent." That's what grinds my gears
the whole time of having this debate is
you think that you know what they're
like. You like know what they're like.
And by you, I mean me. So that's the
[ __ ] that annoys me, bro. Is you know
what these stuck up [ __ ] women are
like. Time wasters. Why are people
trying to tell you otherwise
when you've given them multiple chances
to prove that they're that they're that
they're not all the same? But they are
all the same. I don't understand the
whole point of the [ __ ] conversation.
Everyone's got different lives,
you know. Everyone's got different
lives, you know, and you know,
everyone's in different positions.
You've gave women more than multiple.
And you know why I haven't gone to the
barbers? I tell you why, Guna. I'm
leaving. I'm leaving England, bro. For
real. For real. I'm leaving. I mean, I
can still get my haircut and stuff. I
can still go out, but I'd rather save my
money now and get out of here.
I'd rather save my money and leave.
Still need to sort out a phone. And I'm
leaving, bro. Yeah, I'm leaving, bro.
100%. I'm gone. So,
yeah, I'm leaving.
Yeah, I'm just saving money, bro. Do
this a couple of times a year. Yeah,
saving money and I'm leaving.
Who was that? Was that the [ __ ] Orington virgin?
I'm going Thailand.
Going Thailand with my mate.
I'm leaving. I'm out of it, bro.
Uh, you know that I like kids.
Definitely definitely don't like kids.
See, what makes me laugh is right. There
is an actual nons on this community that
no one goes for. This is what makes me
laugh. That's that's what makes me
really really die about these people,
you know. And listen, you want to talk about USA?
She was the one running to the police
multiple times. You forgot to add that
in there that the [ __ ] went running to
the police. Yeah. Yeah. She went running
to the police. Yeah. I'm meeting
Ant-Man, bro. He's friends over there
now as well.
Yeah. So, the thing is, mate, you you
forgot to add that the [ __ ] would run
into the police. Yeah.
Know what I'm saying?
So, yeah, I'm out of it anyways, bro. That's that.
Well, [ __ ] it. What are you going to do?
Stay in this country with stuck up
women, shitty weather, um, shitty
people, bro. Let [ __ ] it. 16 hour
flight. Who cares? So be it. So be it, mate.
It's not worth it here, bro. These stuck
up [ __ ] women, shitty weather, other
men waiting around for everything.
So what if I contacted all her family
and friends? [ __ ] her, bro.
And her friend was trying to give it
big, saying, "Oh, you know, if you come
here and that, I'll get seven of my
cousins to shoot you." Yeah. Really,
[ __ ] Really? The one that I was on the
phone to for [ __ ] 5 hours. Really?
Really, bro? Yeah. So yeah,
I think yeah, we we can't do this because
it's just pointless, you know, like you
know what women are like. They are all
the same. What's the whole point of the
debate? I don't really understand what
are they trying to make you believe something different
when you have gave women the benefit of
the doubt to prove that they're
different but they prove that they're
all the same. So the whole thing doesn't
even make sense.
You want the link? Okay.
So yeah, one second man.
So that's where we're at basically.
Nice knowing a chan is still stalking me.
Yeah, that's lovely. That is
No, they're not. They're [ __ ]
Nah, they're [ __ ] [ __ ] I hope
they all get raped. Hate them.
Probably shouldn't say that, but I hope
they all get raped. All of them dirty bastards.
Dirty stinky bastards. [ __ ] them. They
shall get raped.
That, bro. That's what I think. They
will [ __ ] get raped and die, bro. So, yeah.
That's where we're at in it. Yeah.
Only people that say that about women or
people that don't have women.
I doubt you've been laid since having
your child, Goona, to be honest with you.
Yeah, women are [ __ ] and I'm
completely unbiased. Not a white knight,
not a s, not an incel. And I have no
reason to lie. They are complete
[ __ ] Like that is an un that's as
unbiased as you get. People don't need
to be labeled as something in order to
have an opinion. You know, just because
someone has an opinion, it doesn't mean
they're something. But they are proper
proper. I mean, that's why I don't go out.
That's why I don't go out and try
because they are all the same.
Like going out drinking, you know what I
mean? Because they are all the same. I
ain't contradicting anything I'm saying.
That's why I gave up with them. They are
literally all the same.
And even when I'm out just taking a piss
and not even really trying, they are
literally all the same.
So I'm not contradicting anything I'm saying.
Yeah, I did say that.
I did say that. They're [ __ ] Yeah, I did.
Yeah, anyone's an incel that doesn't
suck up to women. Anyone that doesn't
suck up to women is an incel apparently.
Yeah. And what they do is vile as well.
Them leading people on, them being
[ __ ] them being [ __ ] that's vile
as well. So [ __ ] them. So yeah, [ __ ]
them. They deserve it. So yeah.
Yeah. Okay, bro.
Yeah. Whatever you say.
Yeah, they're vile as well.
So, new day tomorrow. Anyways, we need
to stop talking about this now. Anyways,
it's very unhealthy.
Yep. You keep telling yourself that,
Bethany. You keep telling yourself that. >> Hello.
>> What do you want, you slag?
>> Excuse me.
>> You heard?
Who are you speaking to?
>> I'm speaking to you. And do you know
what? I'll be going to Cardiff soon
anyways. And if you've got a problem
with it in Gona Chan, I'll show you
exactly where I am.
>> Yeah, fine. Good.
>> I will 100% I will.
>> Good. I I'd wipe the floor out.
>> Yeah. Really? Would you really, mate? I
went to my mate, even your boyfriend
shot it [ __ ] how many times for me?
How many times did I have to go to his
[ __ ] area and he shatters his pants?
My chain. My chain. [ __ ] off, mate.
>> All right, let's Okay, not not that that
concerns me anymore, but just to put
that into context, you literally
arranged to meet a fake Mark.
>> A fake Mark? Was it really? What? When
he was live streaming, mate, I was
literally in Victoria Park for three
hours on two different occasions.
>> I promise you.
>> Okay, whatever. Okay, I'm not his
biggest fan at the moment, but I can
promise you that did not happen.
>> Well, I can tell you it did happen,
mate, because I know exactly where I was
for three hours on two occasions.
>> Yeah, because you were a dick and you
arranged to meet a fake
>> Listen, you you're in denial, Jane.
You're in denial. You really are in
>> Listen, all I wanted to say is that lady
that came up was so polite. She was so
respectful to you.
She decent and like you were so out of
order in the way you
>> I wasn't out of order. I wasn't out of
>> No, you weren't.
>> No, I wasn't.
>> She literally was trying to help you and
you were so disrespectful to her.
Like, what the [ __ ] is wrong with you?
>> She can't help She can't help me.
>> Yeah, you're beyond help
>> because I'm telling her my experiences
with women. So whatever she's saying
doesn't doesn't mean anything.
>> Yeah. But she was being decent with you
and you didn't allow anyone on the panel
to back her up. And
>> no one was no one tried to come but
Laur's not coming in.
>> Oh my god. I I said in the chat so many
times, dropped the link. And you
>> Yeah, I was too busy talking.
>> No, you you chose to ignore it.
>> It's funny, isn't it?
No, it actually wasn't.
>> I think it was.
>> I actually felt like she was a really
lovely lady and she was trying to help
you and you got aggressive and yeah, I
didn't I didn't see the need for her.
>> You know, >> what
>> you said? Yeah, whatever.
>> Okay. So, you were out of order that.
>> Yeah, it's funny.
>> No, I didn't think it was.
>> Women are [ __ ] though. I don't You
know what? I blame Grezy for this. You
know, he got me into this [ __ ] today.
>> He's an like he's an enabler because he
was in the chat saying like, "Oh, how
much fun this is." I don't think it's
funny when you have a respectful lady
trying to speak to you properly and
you've got some [ __ ] nesbit in the chat.
>> You on I I don't think that's funny.
>> No, I don't. I don't.
>> It's unhealthy. I mean, the whole thing
we're never going to get anywhere. I've
got my experiences. That's the end of
that, ain't it? What's there left to
say? There's nothing left to say. You know
>> what is the whole point of it? We're
just going back and forth, back and
forth. You want to think women are
innocent and they don't do anything
wrong. That's on you, bro. Like, what the [ __ ]
>> Do you know? Actually, I would never say
that because as like a woman,
I can be equally as bad as any type of
man. Blah blah blah.
>> Okay. Okay. Let me ask you Okay, let me
ask you this then, I'm not Oh, here we
go. One second. Let me kick out Jane for
a second. Right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Let
me let me ask this. I said she was a
decent respectful person. So you can't
get through to be but don't act like
people haven't been clipped. Okay. Okay.
So what do you want me to do? Rezy.
Okay. Let me ask you this question then.
Right. You're saying that you can't get
through to me. Okay.
What how many times have I showed you my
approaching videos, my messages where
people have led me on? People have an
attitude time and time and time and time
and time and time again and it does not
get through to you people. What has not
gotten through to me? You tell me what
has not gotten through to me.
That's like I have spent God knows how
long trying to show you what these women
have done and you just completely
dismiss everything. What What How are my
opinions going to change, bro? If I've
not been shown any different, what what
do you want me to suddenly start
thinking differently? You got to
understand again, right? I have met more
women than probably most people in the
world. Why am I Why would my opinions
change? Why? It It doesn't even make sense.
Why would my opinions change when I've
never been? It's It doesn't make sense.
What? It don't make no sense at all. You know,
you know what? What's the opinions is
supposed to be, bro? What opinions are
supposed to change? How many times have
you gave these women the benefit of the
doubt? How many times?
So, we're just going round and round and
round in circles. Yeah. Met more women
than anyone in the world. This guy is
absolutely crazy. I might be only 28,
but I've done a lot of traveling, mate.
And I used to approach every day.
Believe you me, I have traveled. I have
met more than I have met more women than
anyone in the world. And they are all
[ __ ] Yeah, they have. Yeah, they are.
I mean, I'm 28. Do you know the [ __ ]
I've done in the past 5 years? I haven't
had to work in 5 years, mate. So, you
don't know my life. So, I mean, why
would my opinions change? So, Greavesy.
So, after speaking to that woman, what
am I supposed to think? Oh, yeah. Women
aren't bad now. Yeah. Yeah. So, I've
just I've just spoke to this woman from
up north. One second, Jane. And what are
my opinions supposed to be? What now?
What what are my opinions supposed to be?
That this hasn't happened. That that
hasn't happened. That this hasn't
happened. That that hasn't happened.
What What opinions are supposed to change,
you know, but why? What opinion? I don't
I don't understand it, you know. Um,
no. I don't think most men are single. I
think it's about I think it's about evens.
It's about evens. And what I meant by
that is why I brought that up, Greavves,
is people would always say, "Oh, well,
there's other men in relationships.
There's other people and there's other
people." And the thing is, there's a lot
of single people out there.
You need to start with attitude.
Exactly. We're going around and around
in circles. So, whatever you prove these
people, they're just going to keep
dismissing it. This is why I stopped
uploading things, you know?
So, everything I show you, you're going
to dismiss, which is why it's best off
just ending the conversation.
You're going to defend all the women
that have led me on, that's done me
wrong, and I'm not going to think your
way. So stop trying to bully me into
thinking your way. I'm not doing it. So
just leave it at that, bro. We'll just
end the conversation. No woman can show
they're different. I don't want to hear
your [ __ ] End the story. I don't want
to hear it. That's that, bro. I don't
want to hear about how women are good. I
don't want to hear it. I have spent
thousands and thousands of pounds of
time giving them the benefit of the
doubt. I don't want to hear it. I'm not
interested. Simple. I am not interested.
They have had several chances to prove
me wrong and they haven't. I'm not
interested. Simple, bro. I really,
really aren't interested. Simple.
You know, all women are the same. I
believe it. That's why I don't bother
with them. Let someone think what they
let someone have their own experiences.
Stop trying to bully someone into
thinking your way. You know, it's
annoying, bro. It is [ __ ] annoying
and I'm not doing this. I'm not doing
this again after tomorrow. It's [ __ ]
pointless, you know,
cuz the whole thing don't make sense. It
does not make sense at all, you know? Done.
>> [ __ ] annoying, bro. >> Yo.
>> All right.
>> Yeah. Good for him, man. He can get laid
with a fat ugly woman with an STD. No
one cares. [ __ ] off.
>> Yeah. Sorry. >> Hello.
>> So, what other Hello, we can hear you.
Yeah. So, what other opinions are
supposed to change, Greavesy? Go on.
>> Why do you keep listening to this
greasy? Who is this grievy person? You know
>> just someone
>> is greasy oxo. >> No,
>> I kind of blame you, you know, Greasy
for this today because this is very very unhealthy. >> Yes,
>> Sarah, come back on. Let's have a let's
have a chat with Jane. Yeah, bring bring
some other people into the hangouts. I
don't like being in the hangouts on me and we
>> Yeah, cuz you're a [ __ ] slag.
>> You remember when you said you wanted
You remember when you said you wanted to
stuck my Willie?
>> Can I just say like that's so tacky?
That's so like
>> you're vile, mate. That's kind of like
desperation that you would say that because
>> you're the one saying how you wanted to
suck people's dick
>> because actually like for all the way
you've treated me, I've still like tried
to be okay with you.
>> Yeah, but why are you talking about
sucking people's dick? That's gross.
>> That happened about six years ago.
>> Yeah, but why did you say that? cuz I
didn't know you.
>> The thing is, the thing is, Sarah, the
whole thing doesn't make any sense.
The whole thing doesn't make I don't
really understand the point of it.
You're saying women aren't all the same.
Women will always prove they're all the
same to me. So, it's like I don't
understand the whole point of it really.
Do you know?
>> Do you want me to be honest with you? >> Yeah.
actually think Do you know the lady who
was on earlier?
>> Where did she come from? Like how how
>> Tik Tok.
>> Oh, okay. Do you know I actually thought
she was so polite. She was so respectful
towards you. Even when you were saying
things she didn't agree with,
she was still so decent. And you just
totally kept on trying to disrespect
that. And yeah, I thought that was bad form.
>> I don't know why people just defend
women the way they do.
>> Sad to be.
>> Okay. In fairness, like I'm a girl's
girl. I'm always going to back a woman,
but if a woman's wrong, like, no, I'm
not going to do that. But that that lady literally was >> think
about it, right, Grezy? Yeah. About that
woman leading me on this whole that
whole conversation that whole
conversation took about an hour.
>> What? That lady led you on?
>> No, someone else. You know that one from Thailand?
>> That took about It took about an hour.
It took about an hour. The whole thing
>> It's greasy. So,
>> you know. No.
>> Do you want my opinion? >> Yeah.
>> They're all [ __ ] I'm never going back
on that [ __ ] Tik Tok.
>> I love Tik Tok.
>> I hate women. They're [ __ ]
But maybe it's not the fact that women
are [ __ ] Maybe it's the way you treat women.
>> Maybe. Just maybe. Yeah.
>> Yeah. But let's be real
>> and let's look at like my situation on here. 95%
of the problems I've had on here with
trolling and things like that is because
I spoke to you. We had a private phone
conversation which you played live
to everyone and from that day forward
I've been trolled relentless.
>> So it's like what do you expect?
>> Yeah, you're right. I'm the big bad
wolf. Women are innocent. I know. It's so bad. >> Yeah.
>> I'm just I'm just going to agree with
these people now, Grezy, because I feel
like they want you to disagree with them
like Sarah and other people. I just generally think
they they just want people to agree with
them at this point.
>> Like literally you you played a record
you put out a live.
>> So what?
>> Okay. But what I'm trying to say is like
that's bad form. So how can you plant
everything on women when like you created it? >> Okay.
And even despite the fact you did that,
I still kind of was like dumb enough to
be like, "Okay, maybe he's got his
problems, blah, blah, blah." But
literally, like you just burn yourself
every opportunity you get. Like
that lady earlier was so polite, so
respectful to you, and you you were just
[ __ ] rude to her. Yeah,
but like well women are rude,
>> but maybe that's that's the aura you
give off and that's what they respond back to.
>> Yep. Whatever.
>> Okay. Well,
you've got so much to say to other
women, but I'm
>> because there's no point. I don't
understand the whole point of this whole
this whole argument like this whole
discussion because when people show you
women doing wrong you just dismiss it.
So there's no point of the whole thing.
>> But no one
>> I don't understand the whole point. Like
people can show these people approaches
grievy of women being stuck up. You can
show women leading you on and they just
dismiss it. So
>> what's the point of this whole thing? But no,
>> think about it.
>> But no woman has actually done you wrong.
>> Yes, they have.
>> Yes, they have multiple. Yes, they have.
>> You've confronted women who have chose
not to be part of something and you take
you take that as a as a wrong thing.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Okay. >> No.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Yeah.
>> PJ, seriously, engage your brain.
Listen, you can approach 100 women and
maybe out of 100 women, 95 of them
wouldn't be interested for their own personal reasons.
>> I can't listen to these excuses. I
really can't, bro. I want to stop
talking about this. I really, really,
really want to stop talking about this.
I don't want to keep talking about
women. It's [ __ ] toxic, bro. You
know, Greavvesy, I blame you for this
today. You know, I really, really blame
you for this, you know. I really, really do.
I don't want to talk about these
[ __ ] these [ __ ] [ __ ] I'm sick
of them. This excuses, the [ __ ]
I've had enough of it, bro. You know,
when you constantly are hearing people
make excuses for these [ __ ] time
and time and time again, bro, it's
[ __ ] annoying. It's been all day,
bro. Yes, women are perfect. They don't
know any better. They don't lead people
on. Okay, whatever. Like, do you want
people to agree with you? I don't get it.
It's the same. I don't want know what
these people want. Honestly, I don't
know what these people want.
You show them things, they dismiss it.
What do these people want? I don't get
it, bro. It's mad.
You brought all these [ __ ] to my channel, Gresy.
You brought all these bloody [ __ ] to my
channel, didn't you?
You always make excuses for them. It's
just better to just leave it at that,
bro. They're never going to stop
defending women. They're never going to
stop making excuses for women. So what,
bro? It's [ __ ] mad.
>> Right, I'm going to order McDonald's now.
It's just depressing. And that's why
it's wound me up today. And I never get
wound up. I never get wound up anymore.
You know what I'm like, Grezy. It's just
this whole thing is winding me up, bro.
I Why did I delete all of them videos?
Why did I delete all of that [ __ ]
No. When you're constantly, you know,
your experiences, right? And these
people are trying to tell you otherwise.
They're trying to make you believe that
women are not like this when you have
got your own experiences. Imagine how
that feels, bro. Like, imagine how
annoying that is. No, no, no, no, no,
bro. It's annoying. It's not Reddit. No,
it's these people stra [ __ ] you know
the people on here earlier. You know
what's the goal here?
What? Women are not innocent. Women are
not good people. You're wasting your
time. You know, just like I've wasted my
time thinking that they were all
different. They are all the same. They
are [ __ ] I hate them. I hope they all
get raped. [ __ ] off. If that means you
will stop giving me advice, get [ __ ]
[ __ ] off. They can get raped.
If that stops you, if that stops me
getting advice, good. [ __ ] off. I don't want it.
Leave me the [ __ ] alone. It's annoying,
bro. I gave up to get away from this
[ __ ] You know, I might not be in
Thailand yet, but I gave up to get away from them.
I don't want to hear about how they're
not all the same and how they not lead a
I don't want to hear it. I don't care.
[ __ ] off. You know,
seriously, bro. It's mad
trying to sit there and tell me they're
not all the same when they [ __ ] are.
It's annoying, bro.
So that's that.
[ __ ] leave me alone.
You know what I mean? Just leave me the
[ __ ] alone, bro.
Why are they so adamant to try to change your mind
when you've given these women the
benefit of the doubt time and time and
time again? Why are they trying to
change your mind? I don't get it. It's weird.
Well, I'm going to order this McDonald's now.
Cuz what about all of them approaches
that I've I've put up, Greavvesy, and
all of the messages? Do they not suit you?
They just don't suit you, do they?
What is it? Do these things not suit you or
does it does it not suit you or what?
Well, I put approaches up, haven't I?
No, I'm not putting a link up. [ __ ] off.
Why do I think what way? Uh,
I don't know, man. Maybe because of my
experiences. It's the same argument.
It's the same argument, bro. It's the
same argument. I used to have it with my
mom as well.
It's the same argument. People are just
going to keep dismissing your struggles
and the same thing happens again and
again and again. I'm tired of it. I am
No, it clearly doesn't it doesn't suit a
lot of people. They just dismiss it.
So now they actually dismiss it.
Yeah. Victim mindset. No, it's not a
victim mindset. It's a reality mindset.
No, I'm saying that this whole thing is unhealthy.
I'm saying it's unhealthy, mate. You know,
it's not a victim mindset. It's a reality mindset.
I would be out today if I thought
different. I'd be out tomorrow if I felt
different. But I'm not
cuz they're all the same.
These women generally are all the same.
So that's that. Yeah. So, yeah.
And then she said, "Oh, look at all of
the things you've said. Why have you
said these things?" And then you just go
round and round in circles again.
You can see how it's unhealthy, can't you?
Sick of these people keep making excuses for women.
[ __ ] annoying. I don't want to hear
it, you know.
[ __ ] annoying as [ __ ] it is, bro.
So, I used to have it with the skid
virgin. One second, Jane. I used Come back, Jane.
I used to have it with the skinned
virgin in the bedset.
Nah non flags.
What the [ __ ] do you want, you [ __ ]
>> All right, first of all, don't speak to
me like a piece of [ __ ]
>> Do what I want.
>> And second of all, don't endorse your
chat. Speak to me like a prick either.
>> Nonslegs Iva. Not not Timmy.
Oh yeah, Timmy. Timmy as well.
Are you listening? >> No.
>> Well, good. You should.
You proper made a prick of yourself tonight.
>> Not at all.
>> Yeah, you did with that lady. And
>> not at all.
>> Okay. And and just to say because to
your chat, I'm not typing back to you
all. You are so [ __ ] beneath me. You
>> not at all Greavvesy. Not at all.
>> And you are so bashing your way typing
your hat. Who gives a [ __ ] Nobody does.
>> Not at all.
>> So anyway,
>> why don't you shut up, you prick?
>> Why don't you?
>> Well, I don't want to.
>> Okay. Well, [ __ ] happens. You
>> Why are you such a [ __ ]
>> Because you treat women so disrespectfully.
>> Completely dismissing all the things
that women do to me. Same argument.
>> Oh, no.
>> I can't deal with this, bro. It's the
same argument. I I can't be dealing with
this in my head. It's the same argument,
Greavvesy. Isn't it the same argument?
Dismiss all the things they've done. Go
back to defending them. Bro, it is annoying, bro.
If she don't stop, I'm going to talk
about her kids. I'm going to talk about
her kids if she doesn't stop. I'm going
to talk about her disabled kids if she doesn't stop.
Please don't drive me to talking about
the kids again, bro.
Please, you're winding me up. You know,
I had this problem with my mom as well
like a month ago.
You know, I had this problem with my mom
a month ago. I said, "You're [ __ ]
annoying me now." You know, stop
dismissing my struggles. [ __ ] off, bro.
I was exploding. It's annoying. Stop
dismissing my struggles. It's [ __ ] annoying.
No, you don't understand. It's annoying,
bro. It's [ __ ] annoying.
Have you ever heard Have you ever heard
The Boy Who Cried Wolf?
Oh, Tony's live.
Have you ever heard about the boy who cried wolf?
That's what you feel like in this
conversation. It's annoying, bro. You
ever You ever seen the tale of the boy
who cried wolf? Look out before you go to bed.
That's what you feel like with this.
Everything that they do gets dismissed.
It's annoying, bro. [ __ ] annoying.
God, it is so annoying, you know.
you for this greasy today.
I'm not doing this again. I'm not doing Yeah.
This wasn't healthy today, bro.
You have a bunch of people on this
[ __ ] YouTube dismissing your struggles.
I don't know what the goal is. What are
they trying to make me change my opinions on?
How can your opinions change?
I had it with my mother as well. She's
another one that dismisses your struggles.
They dismiss people's struggles.
It's [ __ ] annoying.
[ __ ] annoying, bro. And I'm not
feeling like the boy cried wolf. It's annoying. [ __ ] that. You know,
I don't give a [ __ ] about women. I'm
just sick of people trying to convince
me that they're not all the same when
they blatantly are. I don't see the
point of the whole thing.
To be bullied into thinking their way.
I'm not being bullied into thinking their way.
Why don't a woman prove you that she's
different instead of you [ __ ] yapping on
all the time about how they're not all
the same when they are all the [ __ ] same.
I gave up to get away from it, you know.
Well, my food should be here in now anyways.
I feel like smacking someone's face, bro.
I just got this food. I feel like going
out and smacking someone's face, bro.
I'm not doing this again, bro.
I'm not doing this again, Grezy. Yeah,
I'm not doing this again. I snatched the
[ __ ] food off the [ __ ] delivery driver.
Yeah, it's not funny, bro. I feel like
smashing someone's face in. I feel like
going out and smacking someone's face
in, bro. It's not even a joke.
See how annoying it is. It's not
healthy, bro. I hate it. the [ __ ] that
you [ __ ] caused today, you know.
Lord, man, it's so annoying because I've
had the same conversation multiple times.
I got to make chicken sandwich meal. By the way,
I don't want to do this anymore.
When people are trying to tell you,
that they're not all the [ __ ] same
when they are all the [ __ ] same. Why
are they trying to bully you into
thinking their way?
I hate it. I know my experiences.
I don't go out and try because of them.
And then you've got these people [ __ ]
trying to tell you
And then you dismiss people's struggles as well.
You literally dismiss people's
struggles, which is annoying cuz I've
had this conversation with my mom before
and it's very, very, very annoying.
Very, very annoying.
It's like there's one person in the
argument. It's like there's one person
in the argument and it's very [ __ ] infuriating. Yeah,
they dismiss everything that they do.
Why do they keep dismissing everything
that they do?
These little rape victims, you know,
these little [ __ ] rape victims. Why
do they keep dismissing everything these
little rape victims do?
You know, maybe I should do a video
about that. Why do they keep dismissing
everything that these [ __ ] do?
[ __ ] hell, boys. Yeah.
Defending women every time.
And I'll just go out and do something.
It's not even funny, mate.
I'll just go out and just do something him
and you'll never see me then, bro. It's
not funny. It ain't funny, bro. It's [ __ ] annoying,
you know? I'll just go outside and just
smash someone's face in you won't be laughing then.
[ __ ] I hate them. I hate them all. I
hope they all get raped.
If that means you will [ __ ] leave me
alone if I keep saying that. [ __ ] off
and stop [ __ ] trying to convince me
that they're not all different.
Yeah, they're all the same. [ __ ] off. [ __ ] annoying. Mad madness.
I had him with that copycat
sour for like two years.
Oh, you don't know all women. I know
more women than you. You [ __ ] skin
virgin. I said the same [ __ ] then and
I'm saying the same [ __ ] now. I don't know.
I don't know how many times I had to say
it to the virgin.
The skint little virgin.
Oh, I'm trying to make you see the good
in women. There's no good in women.
They're all little [ __ ] They can
go get raped. [ __ ] off. Said the same
thing then and I'm saying the same thing
now. [ __ ] off and leave me alone. Simple.
You little skinned virgin. You know
why is it with these people just leave
people alone you know [ __ ]
absolute [ __ ] mate
and then you got the champ mate I'll be
going kind of soon anyways mate so you
can say it all to my this. I'll be
letting that dollar kebab soon. Anyways,
that chicken tickle one.
See what you're really about, [ __ ]
What do you want me to do, bro? I don't
understand the whole point of the
conversation. Am I supposed to go out tomorrow
and try to find a woman that's
apparently different? How many times we
keep doing that, bro?
How many years are we going to keep
giving these women the benefit of the
doubt? What? Another 10 years? You want
to be in the same cycle for another 10?
They're clearly all the same. They're
clearly all the same scum, which is why
we gave up with them.
But your experiences don't seem to suit them. So
every thing that they do gets excused for,
you know. Well, yeah, cuz you pissed me
off now. Yeah, because he's pissed me
off. Simple. He's pissed me off these
little [ __ ] So, someone's got
someone's going to have to get, aren't
they? You know,
think about the first thing she said.
How is that leading someone up? They won't like
admit any wrongdoing that they do.
Any wrong thing a woman does, no one
admits it. I don't know what it is,
which I think it's it's the same thing I
said to Lex as well. Why are they so scared
to take any um
any fault that anything that they do? I
don't get it. I really really really
don't get it, mate.
We've got some old woman joining trying
to say how them talking to and and you
know the thing is the thing is right
uh is it's because
it is a woman. Okay. Okay. What? Okay.
What What do you reckon the conversation
would have been today if I said a man's
led me on? What do you think their
response would have been? Oh, uh, what?
He changed his mind and all of these
excuses that we're hearing about women.
Do you think it would have been the same
if I was a gay man?
I'm asking you a question.
So, if I was gay or I was bisexual and I
told everyone that this man has been
leading me on, what do you think
everyone would say? Do you think they'd
be making 101 excuses for this man? No,
they [ __ ] wouldn't. Like, as soon as
it's a [ __ ] woman, oh, well, uh well,
she doesn't owe you anything. Uh well, um
uh well, what what does a woman need to
do? like they they don't it they go on
like they're babies that they don't know
what they're doing
and I don't get it as simple as leading
someone on. They can't even admit it. I
[ __ ] don't get these people.
The [ __ ] led your ass on. End the story.
They're so scared to offend. So she must
be a feminist, isn't it? That this woman
today must be a feminist.
She must be a feminist.
They may Oh, and that that changed their
mind excuse. They've always got 101
different excuses from these women. And
I don't know why, you know, maybe I'm
going to do I'm going to do a video
about this, I reckon, because this needs addressing.
101 different excuses.
Like 101 Dalmatians.
You know, it might as well be cool
because it's like 101 different excuses.
But when it just contradicts itself, you know,
so and I'm not even going to ask your
opinion anymore, Greasy, because people
are just going to say, "Oh, you want
someone to agree with you or whatever."
But I want to know what the about these 101 excuses
they have for women. May maybe someone
else that watches your channel can tell me,
"Oh, they changed their mind." Or, "Oh,
they didn't lead you on." It's like
they're so like they could never ever
admit that. Oh, a woman's a narcissist
that's led you on. Oh, a woman's wasted
your time. They would never ever admit
it. Why? Why though? I don't understand
why. What could possibly stop them doing
exactly the same as what a man does? We
what what stops them from doing what
other men do? What what what stops them?
Why wouldn't they do it? You know,
because I'm sure men need people on
them. So why can't none of these women
leave people on them? Why not?
Cuz they were women. Is that what it is?
[ __ ] off, mate.
I swear, bro, if this was if they
wounded me up a bit more, I would have
[ __ ] went out and done something, bro.
It's the excuses.
101 different excuses. 101 Dalmatians. Yeah,
it's sad, bro. This is sad. And that's
what annoys me.
is having these arguments with people.
That's why, you know,
defending women. It's mad.
So toxic and unhealthy.
So what you do, do you want me to go out tomorrow drinking?
So what do you want me to do tomorrow
then? Do you want me to go out tomorrow and approach? Huh?
And try and find a woman that's not
different. I'm not doing it. I'm not
doing it. [ __ ] off. I'm not doing it.
Is that what you want me to do?
Oh, but a woman a woman's being nice or
like they know they know what they're doing.
So, it's like they get away with
everything. everything that they do,
they get away with it.
Because when I had this conversation
with my mom before, bro, I was shouting,
like literally shouting because it's it
is quite annoying, you know, when you're
trying to when you're trying to put your
point across and tell people your
experiences, right? But yet, no one will
have it. They'll completely dismiss it.
It's [ __ ] mental. It's [ __ ]
It's very, very annoying. As funny as it
sounds, it's very, very annoying.
You remember that one before? Um, the
one that I had going on a wild goose
chase, uh, Grezy,
I woke up one um, nighttime. I think it
was night time.
And um, a lady brought it up. She said,
"Oh, you had someone go." And no matter
how many times I told her what she had
done, she was not listening to it. She
just didn't suit her. I'm thinking, hold
on a minute. So you've started
something. I'm telling you why I have
done it and you keep dismissing it, you know?
So I don't I don't understand like
what's the whole
Can somebody explain to me why these
what is it with these 100 million one excuses?
Can you explain it Grievy? Can someone
else explain it?
We hear so many excuses for women. [ __ ]
me. So many excuses. They've changed
their mind. They didn't lead you on.
There were this, there were that. It's like,
what did that what did she say,
Grezy? This this this this 43year-old.
Oh, there's loads of women that get um
raped and one in three women get raped.
So, I've let her speak and I'm thinking,
okay, what's that got to do with them
leading people on?
Okay. So, if you get raped, right, does
that mean that's the reason why you
start leading people on and you start
being a [ __ ] because you've been raped?
How does that make sense? How does the
two have any connection to each other?
All it is is constant sugar coating and
excuses. And I'm sick of it, you know?
I'm not getting into any debates anymore, you know.
No more debates, constant excuses.
Then they tried to say, "Oh, well, yeah,
they don't know their abuses at first."
Well, that's not that can't be true
because Grezy, I've approached people
before. No one's gave me a chance and
I've never hit anyone. So, no, they do
choose these guys they go for. They
might not know. They might not be abusers.
They might not be abusers at first, but
they're never good people. The women
that these people go for are never good people.
They never they're never ever good
people. They know they're not good
people before going with them. So, they
might not be abusers at the start, but
they know that these these people that
they're going with, they know that
they're not good people. Don't let them
try and tell you that they don't know
[ __ ] at first, cuz it's a load of
It's a load of bollocks, mate. A load of
bollocks. They know that they're not good people.
So, don't give me that [ __ ]
It's wow me up today talking about this.
It's [ __ ] It has wow me up, bro.
It seems that your experiences don't
exist when you're a man, Grezy.
That's the way it feels, is it, Grezy?
It feels like they don't even exist, is it?
It It seems that they don't even exist. Mad.
So what you said that Groovy if I was
gay or bisexual and I was talking about
a man leading me on what they would you
reckon they'd call him for it?
They'd call him a prick. But with these
women it's every excuse under the sun.
Every excuse under the sun, the
Teletubby son. [ __ ] off, mate.
This conversation has took all day about
someone leading someone on Grezy. It's
literally took all day. Do you know that? So,
I mean, it's crazy, isn't it?
What's What's madness?
All cuz the person's got a [ __ ] and not
a dick. All because she's got a [ __ ] and
not a dick. This conversation has took
all [ __ ] day. You know, most of the
day, you know,
them trying to justify why they're
leading on them pretending that these
people change their minds. We've heard
it all before, you know.
All because they've got a [ __ ]
Yeah. Okay. Whatever. I've already told
this about I've already told this a million times.
Yeah. And we all know that if I was
talking about a man, you'd agree with
me. So get the [ __ ] out of here.
Yeah, occasional woman.
You're full of [ __ ] [ __ ] off, man.
You're full of [ __ ] [ __ ] We all know
that if this person had a dick, you'd be
calling them to [ __ ] Get the [ __ ] out
of here with your stupid excuses.
But what I'm saying, Tiger, is these
people constantly Right. Remember when I
put that video up and these women, right? Right.
Yeah. And these people were making excuses.
You saw the video just like today,
another story where someone's led me on.
Now they're saying that they haven't led
you on when they have. This has took all
day. But what I'm trying to say is that
if this person was a man, no one would
be making excuses.
So I mean that tells you everything that
you need to know. They've gotund one
excuses to defend women. I'm done with
them. I know women are [ __ ] They're all
the same. They're all evil. I don't want
to be told otherwise. I want to be shown
otherwise. And I haven't. I'm done with
it. I don't care anymore. You know, I'm
never going to be shown different, so
I'm never going to think different.
Leave me alone. Simple. I've given up to
get away from them. I don't want nothing
to do with these evil scumbags, and
that's my choice. Leave me to it. You
know, that's it. I've met Tiger more
women than you can imagine at 28 years
of age. It's not for me or you to say.
It's for these women to prove they're
different, and they can't. That's the
end of that, you know. It's that that's
what it is.
I don't go out approaching. I've already
answered this. I don't I went out
Thursday cuz I was bored and I done it
for a laugh. Yeah. When am I going to be
out again? Yeah. Think about it, bro.
Yeah. Okay. Whatever you say.
And that's my choice at the end of the
day, you know. It's toxic.
It's toxic. very very very very toxic.
These women are toxic [ __ ] is and I
can't be bothered with it, you know. I'm
I'm I'm sick of it.
They're clearly all the same. Clearly
clearly all the same. I've gained them
more than the benefit of the doubt.
Tiger, right? I went out last Thursday,
right? Uh, I don't know if you saw my
live stream, but I went out on Thursday
and I done a couple of obviously you saw
the approaches and
I have a um
I don't know. I got two numbers and only
one replied. Yeah.
Yeah. Whatever. So then then they led me
on and then basically even though I
didn't really like the person, I was
more than happy to meet them because
like it was just something to do and I
wanted to go out this week talking to me
and all of the sudden they come out with
a load of [ __ ] again. I'm done, bro.
[ __ ] this. You know what I'm saying? And
and that was just me giving the person
the benefit of the doubt. We know I'm
not really into like, you know, Asian
people and stuff. So even when you don't
care and you're just giving people the
benefit of the doubt, they're still
[ __ ] you over.
I'm not doing this [ __ ] anymore, bro.
I ain't doing it anymore, bro. You can,
you know, [ __ ] them. It's toxic. Very,
very, very, very, very, very toxic.
And then you have people that are 40
[ __ ] three-year-old women coming to
your [ __ ] trying to change your mind.
Why? Why? It should be up to these
people to to prove they're different. Very
toxic, bro. Very. It's not good, bro. It
really isn't good, you know.
Really good. Really good, bro. So,
why do I still have their numbers? What
do you want me to do? Delete their numbers?
It's just trolling, immaturity, [ __ ]
leading on. I'm not asked with it.
And we were saying tiger tiger how that
these women claim that all men are the
same, right? And they're all abusers and
t but they constantly end up with the
same stereotypical guy. And then these
people say, "Oh, well, they're not
abusers at first. They're not abusers at
first." Yeah, they might not be abusers
at first, but most of these women know
that these men are no good. They know
that these men are no good, but they
keep going back to them. So stop
generalizing men based on the people
that you are going for.
They might not be abusers at the start,
but you know they're no good. You know,
you know there's no good. There's no way
you've come across all of these good men
and they somehow end up being abusers.
Get out of here, mate. You're full of [ __ ]
right? And there's plenty of um genuine
people that want to date and get
married, but you reject them. So [ __ ]
off and stop moaning. You know, I've
heard it all before.
I've heard it all before.
You know, I've heard it all before.
That's what I say to them. It's like
some woman from 3 weeks ago, Tiger
Tiger, right? Saying, "Oh, thanks for
stopping me. You're sweet. You know,
very rare. You made my day, but I'm not
interested in meeting new people right
now." Didn't really care. But you would
think that that's something that
somebody would want. It's something that
you would want. It's something that I
would want. Why wouldn't you want
somebody that's all of them things? So
they just contradict themselves. So they
have these genuine people coming into
their life, but then they're using
excuses as to why they're not
interested, which I don't really care.
But then you would have thought that
they would want someone like that,
but they're not interested. So I mean,
that's strange. These are just examples,
by the way.
Yeah. So that I don't know what you can
do, bro. That's uh it's one of them.
Yeah. Women can be the same, too. But we
was basically talking about
I don't go out and try. When I go out,
it's because I'm bored. I I I stopped
going out for like 8 weeks, bro. Last
week was the first time in a while. When
I go out, it's because I just go out
and I try when I'm drunk because I I
mean, I don't know. I just do it.
There's no there's no reason. I just do
it. I don't have any hope that of these
women, you know. I know that they're all
the same. You know, I didn't go out
today. I'm not going out tomorrow.
And when I went out 3 weeks ago, Tiger,
you didn't see it cuz I didn't record
it. The attitude of these women, bro, is
mad. Like that's really what people have
got to go through in order to find
someone. That's No, it's not numbers
that don't that don't reply. No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. It's not about
numbers that don't reply. It's about
numbers that lead you on.
That's what it is. It's about numbers
that lead your ass on. I don't care
about people that don't reply. It's it I
mean, it's it's always going to be this
way, you know? It's never going to
change. I mean, I expect that. It's the
leading on. It's when people give you
false hope, right? And then you think,
"Oh, I've hit the nail on the head here.
Let's get a date." And then they prove
to be the same again. You know, this is
what I'm trying to say to you. How many
times are you going to keep doing this?
And their attitude stinks as well, bro.
Like even without the numbers, like
they've got bad bad attitude. They need
telling about themselves. I'm not doing
it. I'm not the one to do it. like a lot
of them three weeks ago was before last
week, bro. They literally need telling
about themselves. Some of these women,
I'm not going to do it because it's not
for me to do it. But just just throwing
it out there.
No, I don't go out and try to get
numbers, bro. I go out I go out because
I want to go out,
you know, and I don't expect anything.
But I'm thinking now really I don't want
to talk to them ever again, bro. They
are all the same, bro. And arguing today
about this was toxic.
Very toxic, bro. And I felt like going
out and beating someone up, bro. It's
not funny because feeling like the boy
who cried wolf is not nice. It's It's
annoying, bro. I've had it with my mom.
I've had it with these [ __ ]
You clearly think all women are
innocent. You clearly are going to keep
dismissing people's struggles. Agree to
disagree. What what we keep going on about, bro?
You're clearly going to keep doing it
and it's not healthy, so we're never
going to agree. So, just leave it. Get
on with your life, bro. You know,
you know what I mean?
The excuses they make for these women,
Tiger, is mad. And you know, they're
doing it on purpose. Anyone that leads
people on, right, is obviously doing it on purpose.
You know that. I know that. [ __ ]
Queen Mary knows that. But these people
will continuously make excuses for them.
And I don't get why they do it.
I was on TikTok earlier, right? I was
arguing with this uh woman with this guy
at first. We was having like a debate.
He lost. So then he had to add a woman
in. And then all she done was shout over
me. She couldn't even let me defend myself.
there. They just shouted over me, then
[ __ ] kicked me,
which caused this whole madness today. So,
so that's that in it.
I think I'm 25 numbers now, Tiger. No
date. I've only had three dates this uh
this year. It was April, by the way, or
March. I think it might have been March.
two in March, one in April.
So, I mean, and that hangover was really
bad last week. And then you need to like
think to yourself,
is it really worth this anymore?
You know, is it really really worth it?
Going out, dealing with their [ __ ]
their lies, the toxicity.
You spend money, [ __ ] get hangover.
Is it Is it for what, bro? You know what
you going to do, bro? What? Meet the
love of your life. I don't think so.
What is it, bro? What What are we doing?
You know, I don't get it. So, that's
Yeah. Shouting over, "Oh, women go
through this, women go through that." I
said, "If you had a better choice than
men, it wouldn't happen. Sorry.
It's very very toxic. There was one on
Reddit that disappeared. Grezy, I was
talking to her on Insta,
then she blocked me. Spoke to her on
Reddit. We was talking and then she
blocked me on that. Now I'm going to
have to tell her about herself later.
I'm going to tell her that she's a
disgusting, vile little narcissist.
That's what I'm going to tell her. Yeah,
toxic. Yeah, I know. Very toxic, is it?
It's better off not dealing with them,
bro. It really, really isn't. You know,
I'm going to tell her about herself.
She's a coward.
You'll notice this, Grezy, when you if
you ever speak to a woman, right?
They're one person one day and then
there's someone else the next day. You
you'll find this in time. You know how
we talk or you speak to any of your
friends on WhatsApp or whatever you do,
you'll notice that
it's always stable chat. But you'll
notice with a woman, even if it's her
last message, they completely switch.
The next day, they will completely
switch into another person.
So, it's bad, bad, bad.
This sucks, bro.
So that's where we're at.
>> No, I think he's still here. He's going
in two weeks.
But they don't have an argument.
[ __ ] I'm going to wake up with a [ __ ] headache.
Going to wake up with a [ __ ]
headache. I am.
And then you got Jane, right? And then
you got Jane. And I'm thinking the whole
time I've showed my approaches. I've
showed my messages. Why are we still
having this conversation? Did I?
>> Yeah, you was the root cause of the USA
thing as well.
Yeah, you was the root cause of the USA
Izzy thing, weren't you?
You was the root cause of that, too. Madness
trying to blame me.
Yeah. Even when you go out and you groom,
it's still the same thing. Why do I look
like this, bro? Cuz I'm not going
anywhere. I'm saving money. What am I
supposed to be doing? You know, >> Yep.
Yeah, they are [ __ ] bro.
Proper proper [ __ ]
[ __ ] hate women out there, bro.
I bet you're loving this, isn't it?
Timmy's live. Grezy
It's [ __ ] mad. Yeah, but you was
laughing, weren't you, Greasy?
O Grey, you don't know Cristiano
Ronaldo, do you?
I've just heard about this guy. I don't
know who he is.
No, I didn't know about him until yesterday.
I didn't know about this dude until yesterday.
Oh, is he any good?
Yeah, I've calmed down, bro. I just
don't want to have these debates again.
These women are evil. I don't want to
hear about it ever again, bro.
How do you know who Ronaldo is?
He got 668
million followers. [ __ ] you. Now that's
just on Instagram. Mad.
I don't know who he is.
You see on Instagram, I see this guy.
He's having a baby. Remember this guy?
No, obviously he's not having a baby
with the person that he's with. Yeah.
Yeah, that was so toxic today. That debate, bro.
Look at what you've caused today, bro.
Look at what you [ __ ] caused, Grezy.
They're not all like that. Yeah.
Is it the same website you can watch the
side men on?
Why did you keep saying that when I was
arguing with that woman?
That's a staple. I don't know what the goal is.
Yeah, I did send a voice though cuz I'm
sick of hearing about this little [ __ ] Yeah.
You was there waiting for me in it? You
didn't think I was going to come on.
Yeah. Crazy. Cuz them [ __ ] were
laughing at us.
Them [ __ ] were laughing at us
and I couldn't let it lie.
[ __ ] that, bro. Yeah, them [ __ ] were
laughing at us in it. Yeah,
them [ __ ] were laughing at us. Yeah,
if I had it my way, I'd remove everyone.
I would remove everyone, you know.
I'd remove everyone.
from England and it just be me here.
Yeah. No, it's just, you know what's
annoying about it is the people just
missing your struggles.
I just hate them dismissing your
struggles. It's horrible, you know. Yeah.
Do you remember Greavves? Do you want my opinion? Dell [ __ ]
Greavves. Do you remember that one? That
was time J [ __ ] perfectly. Do you
want my opinion, Zippy?
Uh-huh. They're all [ __ ]
Do you remember that one? Do you want my
opinion, Zippy? Uh. Uh-huh. They're all guns.
That is what he said, isn't it?
It's so lazy in there. Well,
do you remember Grezy? And you you fly master.
Yeah, I seen. Was that your hands when
you was holding the Black Ops 3
Greavesy? You've got some chubby fingers. Bless you.
Yeah, you got some chubby fingers, Greavvesy.
Yeah. Do you want me to do that one
morning? I'll record it. And you lying master [ __ ] Oh, bless.
I guess you want to find a woman soon,
don't you, Grezy? H
I guess you'll be looking for someone
soon, won't you?
I can go out tomorrow if you want, Grezy, but
they'll be all the same.
Let's see what football's playing
tomorrow. I'm not going out tomorrow, though.
There's some teams playing
Why do you have to force yourself, Grezy?
Yeah, football playing tomorrow. I'm not
going to bet on it, though.
You don't have to fool yourself.
Why do you need to force yourself to get
a woman? Grezy,
you can't live life alone. Yeah, bro.
It sucks. Women are all the same, is it? Yeah. Yep.
Ant-Man says, "You know what they're
like. You've known what they're like for years."
Is he right, Grezy?
He says, "Who cares what people say? You
know what they're like?" He's right
though, ain't it? Yep. Elephant church.
You all right, Captain?
All right, Captain. Yep. Oh, please. Yeah, mad. Yeah.
I can't believe you're older than me,
Greasy. That's mad.
Now I'm getting sleepy now.
How much money did you save this month, Grezy?
I think I would have been able to save 800. Maybe
this ain't bad to be fair. I went out a lot. Sir,
>> what about you, Captain?
You probably done more than me this
[ __ ] month, didn't you?
I was going to do football back
tomorrow, but don't see there being any point
like lumping and I got some money in it.
So, I must have you saved.
Well, bless you.
Well, your little £1,200.
Well, bless you then.
Yeah, I went out a few times as well to be fair. But,
well, I've got a bill. I've got Franklin
coming out and my other bill, but that's
not until next month. Franklin's only 15. So,
so I've saved 800.
But I bought Uggs as well. I don't think
I bought Uggs and I went for food and
went out and that. So,
I need to buy a phone though, obviously.
How much was your bill? Grey.
£250 [ __ ] pounds. What the [ __ ]
That's how much I'd be paying for a
phone though, to be fair. Oh, [ __ ] me.
You get a little bit of money every week
as well. Like I get £80 a week. So
that's why it seems like easier cuz
you know £80
in it. So like a couple of food in it.
I take it you don't get bloody weekly.
There's some good football on tomorrow
Steven Howard, but I won't be betting on it, bro. No. Pointless.
250 [ __ ] quid.
I bet when you when there's a chance to
get a budgeting loan out, Greavvesy, you
get it straight away, don't you? You get
the you get the budgeting loan straight
away, don't you, Grievy?
Yeah, I'm not doing it tomorrow. I can't
be [ __ ] bro.
I'll be doing nothing tomorrow.
Yeah, there's some good football playing tomorrow, bro.
Oh, I'm urging more.
We should put 500 pound on a double.
Both teams to score.
Oh, [ __ ] me, bro. Could you imagine? Nah. Nah, bro.
Oh, that version boy.
Okay. So, this one
if you put 120 on this, it returns 33 334,
which isn't that good, is it?
That's [ __ ] odd, bro. What the [ __ ]
Yeah, they're really bad odds.
Yeah, these are bad odds, bro. What the [ __ ]
Hold up, boy. Do
do you watch virgin boy? Little copycat.
Little copycat. Yeah, them odds are
[ __ ] bro. Really bad odds.
These odds are even worse.
100 to two 240. What the [ __ ]
Why are the odds so bad on these ones?
When I put 120, it returned. It returned 380 before virgin boy.
Oh, that virgin mark.
Oh, that virgin boy.
It's still there. Grezy,
we need to get Virgin boy. We need to
get Virgin boy laid. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. That's the league. [ __ ] The
odds are [ __ ]
Yeah. I don't know why the odds are so
[ __ ] on this.
What if I go out approaching tomorrow even Howard?
Do you think anything will happen?
Yeah, dude. 20 on like six teams.
20 pound on two teams. What's the point of that?
I think I might do a treble both score no draw.
Why would you do 20 pound on two teams?
That doesn't make sense.
So what you going to put 20 on it?
20. You're going to put 20 on two teams.
Why are the odds so [ __ ] on these um on
the football, bro?
The odds are [ __ ] [ __ ] in it. Why?
Let me see other bookies.
Why are the odds so [ __ ]
What about that bloody version?
Well, what about that bloody virgin Steven Howard? Yeah,
you should play online roulette. Steven Howard
Yeah, they have [ __ ] odds. Was
it? I don't go on the channel anymore, bro.
I don't go on Virgin's channels.
Yeah, I don't go on virgin's channels.
It's the best way, is it?
So, no virgin zone on my channel, mate.
[ __ ] Virgin boy.
You like Virgin boy?
He's a little copycat.
Isn't he right? Isn't that right, Steven
Howard? He's a little copy.
Isn't he my little copycat? So copycat.
He's a little copycat. Little copycat.
What do you think, Steven Howard?
It's a little copycat.
He's a little copycat.
He's a little cat.
Don't know. I'll probably be in bed all
day tomorrow, bro. I can't be bothered
to do anything.
What are you doing tomorrow? Made threats.
I don't even go on the virgin channel
anymore. So, I don't see anything, bro.
I don't go on that skin virgin channel.
Why are women all [ __ ] UK asylum? Why
are they all the same?
Why do people keep making excuses for
these women as well?
Getting into that debate ever again, bro. Never.
Yeah, I'm not going out ever again
drinking UK asylum cuz women are all the
same. So there's no point trying to meet anyone. Ah.
Ah. See you. Uh,
that was very toxic today. Greasy. Very toxic.
No. Not no cold approaching. No.
No. Cold approaching. No,
no thanks, bro. No thanks.
Nope. No cold approaching.
Yeah, but why? I'm not going to go out
drinking to not speak to anyone. And I
don't want to speak to women cuz they're
all the same. So, I'm [ __ ] Basically,
I'll just chill tomorrow.
It doesn't matter about breaks or not.
It's never going to change.
It's never going to change, bro.
It will never change in this country.
Doesn't matter what you are, who you are.
So, it doesn't really matter. You have
to leave England.
I have some I'm saving some money. So,
I'm saving money. Um, yeah.
Yeah, I'm saving money basically.
That's why I have a long beard and [ __ ]
Might do a little football bet tomorrow.
Yeah. Antman. Yeah. Loads of people are
going Thailand now.
The women are [ __ ] The women have
failed us in this country.
I hate them. Me, bro. I hate them.
They're all [ __ ]
the UK island. They're such [ __ ]
I really hate them, bro.
Oh, you don't like Thai food?
Thai food's nice, bro. And yeah, of
course they have KFC there, man. K. They
have KFC everywhere.
I just think they're [ __ ] I just hate them.
I really hate women, bro.
Yeah, it's not all fish. Yeah.
What I don't understand is why people
continuously make excuses for women.
When they lead people on, people make excuses.
I'm sick of it. The whole thing is
toxic. That's why I gave up
UK asylum. I gave up because it's just toxic.
Very, very, very toxic. It's not even
depressing anymore. It's just toxic.
If that's that's the word for it. It's toxic.
It's not depressing because you can't
even get depressed because you know, you
already know what it is. They're all the
same. But like, it's toxic if that makes sense.
I have got a lot of underlying hate and
bitterness towards women. I wonder why that is. H
Maybe because every single time you go
out and you give people the benefit of
the doubt, they [ __ ] you over again.
I could probably see why that is to be
honest with you. and rightfully
warranted as well. Rightfully warranted.
It's all warranted.
And the fact that you give these people
the benefit of the doubt time and time
again and they all prove they're the same. So,
you know, I still go out and
occasionally try when I'm bored out of
my head and they're always the same. So,
I don't get these people's argument really.
You have every right to be bitter and hate them.
you're you you've given them the benefit
of the doubt for years and years and
years and they've just [ __ ] you over.
So the the bitterness and hate is completely warranted.
If you don't know what that means,
you'll you'll be you'll think different
when you're shown different.
They are literally [ __ ] I do hate them, bro.
And the reason why I'm saying it today
is because it's brought it all up.
You know, if we didn't have this today,
I wouldn't have really said anything.
But it's these [ __ ] when you got
people trying to tell you when you know your experiences.
I [ __ ] hate him, bro.
When I wake up tomorrow, I don't want to
talk about it again.
I don't want to talk about them again,
bro. It's [ __ ] toxic, you know?
So, so toxic. That's that.
Now, I could go out drinking tomorrow UK
asylum and it would be the same thing. I
could tell you exactly what would
happen. I'd put a bet on it. I'd put
£500 on it. I could tell you exactly
what would happen.
Well, it won't. Well, you do realize
Thailand's not perfect.
You do realize Thailand's not perfect
anymore. It's It's better than here.
It's still way better than here, but you
know, it's kind of getting westernized
there as well.
Antman was telling me, but you can still
get women there. You can still get women
there. Don't get it wrong. But
it's not uh he said it's not like it was
like 10 years ago and [ __ ] But yeah,
you're never your perspective is never
going to change. Yeah. Because all you
would keep doing is keep meeting the same women
that look different.
Just different characters. Same [ __ ]
Isn't that right, Grezy?
You will meet the the you will meet
basically different characters doing the same [ __ ]
That's what you you'll meet
and then they only reply to negativity
and then it's so toxic mixed with the
alcohol. It never changes, bro. That's
why you're better off doing nothing.
You know, you're best off tomorrow just
staying in bed. in if you had to stay in
bed or go out drinking, I'd stay in bed and chill.
That's a lush. That's lush. Might sound
boring to you, bro, but boring is better
than toxicity, isn't it, Greasy?
I'd rather be bored
and a bit boring than have to deal with toxicness.
Isn't that right? So,
what do you think UK asylum?
Yeah, that's pissed me off today. That has, bro.
Made me want to go out and beat a woman up, bro.
Made me just want to kick them in their
[ __ ] I hate them so much, bro.
If I had USA Izzy in front of me today,
bro, oh mate, I'd have a field day, bro.
I'd punch her so hard in her tits that
she'd get breast cancer, bro. It's not
even a joke.
Yeah, it's not even a joke, bro. It's
not even a joke.
Give me one minute with a [ __ ] and I
tear them apart, bro. [ __ ] hate them [ __ ] [ __ ]
Greasy. I hate them.
Do you remember you know when I used to rent
Do you remember when I used to rent the
rooms? Yeah, Grezy. When these women
would message me, I'd say up. It's
double for you cuz you're a woman and
women are smelly. That's what I used to
say to them. Sometimes I used to say no women allowed.
Yeah, it used to be on Facebook uh
market. They used to message me. I said,
"Oh, it's actually 700 for you.
It's actually 700 for you cuz you're a woman
and you break people's hearts and stuff." Yeah.
There's going to be some more lost
content in it, Grezy.
Yeah, we need that Scottish kitty in here.
Anyone that don't think their way is an
incel. Anyone that don't think their way
had a £250 bill. What the [ __ ] Cle doesn't matter.
That is mad.
You missed it all. Why Steven? Now, do
you know this Samsung Galaxy Fold um 6
is very very fast?
It's a very very fast phone. Uh 12 Gigabytes Steven.
I'm not sure, bro. But it's very very
It's a very very fast phone. Too bad it's blocked.
Yeah, it's a good phone.
you can get the Samsung Galaxy Fold 7s refurbished for
600 and something pound,
but they're like 1,500 new. £1,550. [ __ ]
You should get it, Steven Howard. The £1,550 phone.
Why don't you get it? Why not?
Why not, bro?
What? You would never buy that phone for £1,550.
What if you won 20 grand? Would you then?
Would you pay if you won 20k? Yeah.
1550 for the phone.
Yeah, you can pay it then.
That phone is lush. Yeah. Uh,
it's going okay.
I had an argument with these [ __ ]
idiots earlier. about women trying to
convince me all women aren't the same
and [ __ ] when they [ __ ] are.
It got really heated and toxic.
Yeah, we started off
we started off on Tik Tok, didn't we, Grezy? Yeah.
Nah, they are definitely definitely all the same.
Nah, they're definitely all the same.
And I'm not interested in
in thinking otherwise because they can't show otherwise.
Nah, nah, they're definitely definitely
all the same.
Women are definitely all the same, bro.
And I'm not going to sit here and argue
with it. So there's no point. You have
your opinion. I have my opinion.
I think that's the best.
No, they definitely definitely are.
But we'll agree to disagree anyways. So yeah.
Yeah, women aren't all the same. They
just do all the same stuff, act the same
way, same mannerisms,
lead people on the same way, go for the
same scumbag men, but they're not all
the same. You tell him, my son. Isn't
that right, Grezy? There's nothing all
the same about that, is there? Yeah, right.
But like I said, agree to disagree. best
way I think.
Strange, isn't it?
Very, very strange.
I find that
they do a lot of the same stuff for
people that aren't all the same. I give them that
they are all the same scumbags.
I had another one lead me on from last week. Packet. Yeah.
I'm never dealing with them again, bro.
I'm chilling tomorrow.
Nah, I don't trust you.
Nope. I don't trust you at all.
Women are all the same. I don't trust you.
Nah-uh. My experiences show otherwise. I
don't trust you. Nope.
I don't trust you at all.
And it's not up for me to trust you.
It's up for them to show different and
they can't. So that's that. It doesn't
matter what me and you say, they have
proven multiple times that they're all
the same. So that says it really doesn't
matter what you say. It doesn't matter
what I say.
It matters about what they do and they
prove that they're all the same. So
that's that in it. Actions speak louder than words.
No, it's not different. any country is
just Yeah, we're having the same
argument over and over again, right?
We'll just leave it at that. See what I
mean, Grezy? It's just the same thing
over and over again.
Women are definitely all the same
scumbags. That's why I don't deal with them anymore.
Every time, the rare time you go out,
the very, very rare time you go out, you
realize why you stopped going out. How
mad is that?
Because they are all the same.
They are literally all the same.
You will literally go out, you will
literally stop going out for like 2 3 months
and be like, "Oh [ __ ] that's why I
stopped going out." Yeah.
No, women are definitely definitely all
the same, bro. Definitely all the same.
So, how many how many more years do I
have to keep giving them the benefit of
the doubt on the pack? Cuz I can't take
your word for it.
I can't I can't take your word for it, bro.
How many more years do I have to keep
giving these people the benefit of the
doubt? Cuz Grezy, that's a that's a good
question, isn't it?
How many more years do you have to keep
giving these people the benefit of the
doubt? For how many more years? You know
how many more years, bro? It's already
been five years.
How many more years do we have to keep
giving these [ __ ] the benefit of the
doubt? It's not fair, you know, just
taking your word for it.
Yeah. Well, that doesn't work. So, your
advice is rubbish.
Yeah, it was really bad today, Siri,
man. These people on [ __ ] Tik Tok,
they literally make up any excuse for
these women. It's very, very unhealthy.
I was going to knock the delivery driver
out, bro. It was [ __ ] with my head.
These people, they literally make up any
excuse to defend women. If you heard
earlier, bro, you would have heard it.
They literally do anything to defend women.
It's [ __ ] madness, bro. Any excuse.
You should You should have [ __ ] heard
the things that they were saying earlier.
It's so toxic.
He didn't do anything. It's these [ __ ]
that were pissing me off, bro.
These [ __ ] little rape victims that
were pissing me off. Indiana, I had to
say [ __ ] off and go get raped because
they wouldn't leave me alone, bro.
They kept coming and annoying me. They
kept coming on here and annoying me,
bro. I said [ __ ] get raped. A lot of
you and [ __ ] off. Yeah.
[ __ ] the lot of you. I hope you all [ __ ]
off and get raped. All you dirty little
[ __ ] And then they [ __ ] off. Yeah,
cuz they wouldn't leave me alone, bro.
Greavvesy caused all of this today.
Not what what they do is not normal either.
What they do is not normal either. But
we won't get into that because you just
dismiss you dismiss everything that they
do. So, well, I can say that. I hope
they all get raped. And I just said it
again. So, I can cuz I just did.
No opinions of what they do. See what I
mean, Smy? It's pointless because
everything they do, they will just keep
dismissing it. That's why there's no
point because they will just ignore
everything that they've done and keep
going for you. That's why I stopped
that's why I stopped arguing with my mom
about it as well. Cuz no matter whatever
you would tell these people, they would
just keep ignoring it. everything you
would show them, they'd keep ignoring it
time and time and time again, you know,
and it's so [ __ ] annoying, bro. Like,
I had the same thing with my mom. They
just ignore all the bad that they've
done to you. That's what they do, bro.
And it gets very, very annoying. Very,
very annoying, bro. When you're trying
to when you're trying to put your point
across and they just keep ignoring it.
It's so annoying, bro. It is. It really,
really, really, really, really is.
You know, you show them leading you on,
they make up excuses,
bro. Stop comparing me to other people. Yeah.
I'm I'm not interested in being compared
to other people. You should know this channel.
You know, bro, I don't compare myself to
others. So, that doesn't give me any
kind of hope. I don't compare myself to strangers.
So that's that's no good to me, good or bad.
But yeah, it gets very very annoying and
very very toxic when you're trying to
put your point across and people ignoring it.
Very very very very annoying.
So yeah, stop comparing me to strangers.
Again, another person that's dismissed
my struggles. What is it with you people
keep dismissing people's struggles? Do
you know what I'm going to do? I'm going
to go on Reddit. I'm going to go and I'm
going to act like a complete [ __ ] and
see if and see if we hear all of these
excuses. Do you know what I'm going to
do that tomorrow? I'm going to go on
Reddit and be the biggest [ __ ] ever
and see if they keep making excuses when
I say, "Oh, men keep leading me on. Men
keep doing this." If I act like a big
[ __ ] will we hear about the same
excuses that we've heard today?
You know, if I keep will they keep
making a million and one excuses for men
if I pretend I'm gay tomorrow. I'm going
to go on Reddit tomorrow and I'm going
to do it.
I don't compare myself to nobody.
I don't compare myself to anybody. Never
have, never will.
and rating yourself out of 1 to 10 is
not comparing either way. So, I'm going
to do that tomorrow, Greavves. I'm going
to go on Reddit and be a complete and
utter [ __ ] and see if Let's see if we
get the same excuses.
I want to see the same excuses tomorrow.
You know, all of these excuses we've
been hearing today about women leading
people on, I want to hear it tomorrow.
I'm going to be gay for the day. I'm
going to be a big [ __ ] That's what
I'm going to do. And I want to hear
these same excuses that they keep making
for these women as they will do tomorrow
for men. Yeah. We'll see.
Let's see if my struggles get dismissed.
And I might do it where I pretend to be a woman.
Let me What if I pretend to be a woman? tomorrow, Grezy?
And I start moaning and winging about
men. I wonder what people have to say about me.
No, don't tell me to relax. Why don't
you suck my dick? Why don't you come
here and suck my dick and I'll relax,
you little [ __ ] [ __ ] All right,
that one. You You pissed people off
today, you little [ __ ] [ __ ] on here.
Yeah, I'll relax when you come and you
suck my big dick.
I'll pretend to be gay tomorrow. Yeah.
And let's see if we hear these. Well,
when I Well, do you remember what
happened when I pretended to be a woman?
The excuses stopped. All of the excuses
All of the excuses stopped.
Yep. All of these excuses stopped. Why is that?
[ __ ] women, bro. I hope they all get
cancer and get raped. [ __ ] them, bro.
Absolutely [ __ ] that. You said I can't
say it, but I can
because I just did. I hope they get
[ __ ] raped and shafted by a dog. I
hate them, bro. Hate them little rape victims.
When I hear about one getting raped
again, I'm going to open a bottle of
champagne and [ __ ] have a dance.
Going to buy the most expensive bottle
of champagne and have a dance. [ __ ]
scumbags. I'm doing this gay experiment
tomorrow as well.
Yeah, I'm doing this experiment tomorrow
as well. I want to see if I hear the same excuses.
Maybe I should go around recording men.
No, thank you. I like my beard.
What if I start going around recording
men? Me chatting up men. Greavvesy,
will we hear about how it's creepy to record?
Hm. No, I don't think so.
But they're not sexist. Remember, Grezy,
They're not sexist.
No, of course they're not.
But they're not sexist. No.
They [ __ ] are sexist. They [ __ ] are.
[ __ ] [ __ ] Why all women get raped? Yeah,
I hate him. Yeah,
I do mean that.
So, I'm going to pretend to be gay
tomorrow and I'm going to moan about men.
So, what's people's money on Grezy?
Are they going to make excuses or are
they not going to make excuses? Cuz I
don't think they're going to make
excuses for these men.
I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm gay."
But um yeah, this guy keeps this man,
this man led me on.
And we'll see about I want to hear all
of these excuses tomorrow for these men
that they keep making for women.
They'll probably just say that he's a
dick. A [ __ ] that's led you on. I
bet you they all say that he's a
[ __ ] that's led you on. They'll make
excuses. I don't think they will, mate.
I don't think they will.
I wonder if over here the man doesn't
owe you anything.
Nah, they won't make excuses.
They won't make excuses for men. They
never make excuses for men. They only
make excuses for women. Nah. Nah.
They will say that he's a dick and move
on. That's probably what they'll say.
Grievy, what do you think they'll say?
They'll probably say that he's a dick
and move on.
I'm not getting their numbers, [ __ ]
I've already explained this multiple multiple times.
No, they'll probably say that he's a
dick. He's a [ __ ] and move on. They
will not make 101 dalmatation excuses
like they do for women.
You don't think it will make it will
make a difference? Because I've
pretended to be a woman before moaning
about men and trust me there was a
massive difference. There was a massive
massive difference. The It was a night
and day difference.
We never heard about men not owing you
anything. We didn't get called nasty
names. We didn't get attacked.
We didn't get a load of excuses. So
yeah, but I won't be going out drinking anymore. So
no, I think there will be a difference
cuz I've done an experiment before with women. So,
no, there will be a difference. They
make excuses just because they're women.
It's not because they think you're right
or they think you're wrong. They do it
because these people are women. So, they
always make excuses for women. Women
can't do any wrong in their eyes.
Yeah. Women can't do any wrong in their
eyes for some reason. I don't know why
they think that, but that's what people think.
But I won't be drinking again for a long time. So
So yeah, I'll be chilling in bed tomorrow anyways.
Yeah, nothing to do.
women are all the same.
How many more years are you going to
keep giving these women the benefit of
the doubt? It's been going on for years.
How many more years? 6 years, 12 years,
18 years? How many more years are we
going to keep giving these women the
benefit of the doubt? These stuck up
[ __ ] women. Toxic women. How many more years?
[ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that.
No. [ __ ] that [ __ ] I'm not doing that again.
You [ __ ] women.
Another 10 years. You can [ __ ] right
off, mate. If you think I'm doing this
for another 10 years, you can [ __ ] right off, mate.
You can [ __ ] to [ __ ] You can [ __ ] to Tim
Bach [ __ ] too.
It's not just London though. It's
London. It's Manchester. It's Bristol.
It's Liverpool. It's Nuke. It's [ __ ]
America. It's not London. It's everywhere.
It's everywhere in the West.
It's everywhere in the West. They're all
the same. Women are all [ __ ]
I watch Ed Matthews. He's when he goes
to America and they're all [ __ ]
there as well.
I watch Ed Matthews. He's in He goes to
America and they're all [ __ ] there
as well. Absolute [ __ ] there as
Same as Australia. They're all
westernized [ __ ] Doesn't matter
where you are in the West.
Anyways, we're not getting into him
anymore. Anyways, um and even these
escorts are [ __ ] as well. I had a
problem with an escort yesterday.
So, you're best off just doing nothing really.
You're best off doing nothing.
You're best off doing [ __ ] nothing really
cuz it will never change.
You're best off doing nothing.
Trust me, it will make your situation
[ __ ] uh worse.
Yeah, women definitely are all the same.
Long story. She was being a [ __ ]
So, that was two [ __ ] That
[ __ ] and that that Tai one that led me on.
I was like, "Oh, this is why I gave up
for two months." So, I'll give up for
like 2, three months, go out when I'm
bored and be like, "Oh, this is why I
gave up with women again." And then the
same thing continues and continues and
continues. Never ends. It will never
end. And it will never change. So,
you're just best off staying in your
bed. No toxicity, no wasting money. It
doesn't matter what she done. It wasn't
what she done, it was what she was
saying. She was being a [ __ ] So, Yeah,
they clearly are all the same.
No, she was being a [ __ ] It doesn't matter.
It's just better to stay in and not have
to deal with this [ __ ] ever again.
Just stay in. Stay for like 6 months and just leave.
Uh, I'm not going to get into it.
I'm not going to get into it. Well, I
don't need to say for 6 months. But I
mean, if anyone You might as well just
stay in bed. Just chill for 6 months and
leave. Be depressed for like 6 months.
No, she was being an awkward [ __ ]
I'm not going to get into it. So yeah,
he was being a [ __ ] So yeah.
Yeah, you could save up for like 6 months.
Just be depressed for like 6 months and
then just leave.
Beat staying here. Nope.
You could probably go given to save to be honest
and then just leave. You could save up
for 6 months and leave.
Yeah. But what I'm saying is these
escorts have got attitude problems.
A lot of these escorts have got attitude.
Yeah, actually a lot of these escorts
actually have attitude as well.
Very toxic. It's just toxic. The whole
thing is toxic. Going out, drinking,
dealing with women. It's toxic. That's
why I gave up cuz it's toxic.
All of it is toxic. It's negative and
That's why I don't bother.
I just watch like quiz shows now
on the TV. I just watch like quiz shows
and [ __ ] I don't Yeah, it's it's
pointless. It's toxic. It's negative.
You don't need that in your life.
It will never change here. Women have
proven what they're all about time and
time and time and time again. So,
just watch quiz shows and stuff. It's toxic.
No, I didn't.
No, I didn't. She was just being a [ __ ]
I could tell you the story, but I can't
be bothered to be honest. Yeah.
No, I didn't.
No, I can't be bothered telling the
story. It's too long. Well, I'm too tired. Sorry.
Okay. Well, I messaged that escort yesterday
and I said, "Are you in London?" Bear in
mind, I've met them four times, so they
know who I am. I've got their number.
And then they were like, "Um,
yeah." So, I said, "Why didn't you let
me know? you was in London the other
day. She said, "Oh, I've only just got
here." I said, "Oh, okay. Can I come see
you?" They like, "Oh, I'm living with
people, so it will be a bit hard."
And I'm thinking, "What?"
And there's like, "Yeah, I've been
seeing people. It' be a bit hard living
with people." I said, "Strange."
I said, "Can you come to me then?" And
they said, "Oh, we can't go to client's
houses." I can't go to client's houses
as it's a bit dangerous.
And I said, "What? You've literally met
me four times. What are you talking
about about it being dangerous?" And I
said, "And then she was just being like
a proper [ __ ] Like proper being
awkward." So in the end, I just told her
to [ __ ] off. And I've seen her like four
or five four or five times. I said
dangerous. I was like, "Bitch, you've
met me four times. What are you talking
about? You've just been an awkward dickhead."
And I said to her like, "What's going
into you lately? Why you being such a [ __ ]
But she was fine obviously before this.
I've saw her four times. So yeah, not interested.
She just being a [ __ ]
So I'm not interested. Simple.
Told her delete my delete my number. Just Brazilian.
Yeah, she was being a proper awkward [ __ ]
No, she doesn't have a pimp.
She doesn't have a pimp. She works for
herself. She doesn't have a pimp. She
was just being a [ __ ]
No, she was just being a [ __ ]
Games and [ __ ] I'm not interested
in games and [ __ ] which is why I
don't deal with people.
So they're just [ __ ] [ __ ] them.
Hate them, mate.
So I hate them, bro. I hate them. Yeah.
So, yeah, that's why I don't bother with them anymore.
I'd rather keep peace of mind than just
chill, you know?
These women are clearly all the same.
So, it makes sense. Just give it up.
Yeah, it's bad, isn't it?
All of the same attitude, the same mannerisms.
Mad, isn't it?
There'll be a new day tomorrow anyway,
so we won't have to talk about this again.
I can't believe I used to go out like
twice a week.
Look at all of these numbers I've got on
my phone as well. Bad.
I need to get rid of these numbers.
These ignoring [ __ ]
Nah, you need to stop the gay jokes.
It's boring, mate. Very, very boring.
Very, very boring. The gay jokes are
very boring now, bro.
Nah, you need to stop the gay jokes.
It's very boring.
Yeah, but she's just I've been with her four times.
Nah, stop. Stop it, bro. It's boring
now. It really is boring.
You You need to stop the gay jokes. It's
boring now, mate.
Um, but the thing is, I've seen this
escort four times
and she's being a [ __ ] So, I told her
about herself basically and then she
tried like backtracking.
Yeah, she's a [ __ ] bro. She's a proper
[ __ ] And I've seen her four times
as well. Four or five times.
And they actually know who I am as well.
They actually know who I am as well.
That's the worst thing about it. It's
not like they didn't know me.
So yeah, women are just not worth dealing with.
Nah, [ __ ] her, bro.
I'll be chilling tomorrow anyways.
I won't be out again for a very, very,
very, very long time.
You can't even get a date nowadays.
There's no hope in this country. How
people think there's hope for you is
beyond me. I mean, what are the odds, eh?
What are the [ __ ] odds?
What are the odds, eh?
One in a billion.
It's bad. It really is bad.
proper ignoring [ __ ] in it.
I have a boyfriend.
I have a boyfriend. Uh,
that's their favorite word.
It's not good for your mental health.
You know all this,
it's not good for your mental health.
It's really, really not good for your mental health.
Dating, you know,
constantly running into narcissists,
toxic people, madness, isn't it?
I got told I was gay because I don't
find Cheryl Co attractive.
Only that makes me gay. Does that make
me gay? Anyone?
I've never liked dick or anything, but I
got told because I don't find Sher Co
attractive I'm gay.
Yeah, it was some cat that told me
some random cat little copycat. Yeah.
Yeah. Some some someone told me that.
Yeah. I think he was just saying it to
fit in with the crowd though.
No, she [ __ ] isn't. She's [ __ ]
ugly. She's got no tits.
I mean, does that class does that class
as gay? If you don't find someone
attractive, I'm not entirely sure that's
what gay means.
I mean, I'm not entirely sure that's
I don't think she's hot. I think she's [ __ ] ugly.
Does that really make you gay? Really?
I must be gay then. Well, I didn't know
I was gay.
No, there's nothing special about her at all.
People just copy each other.
I didn't know not finding someone
attractive makes you gay.
So, if you don't find Cheryl Co
attractive, you're gay. Huh?
Strange. Sounds like a copycat statement.
That sounds like what a bunch of
copycats would say.
If I didn't know any better.
She's certainly not. She's very average
and she doesn't have any body.
So wait, if you don't like her, that
means you're gay. Really? So
she can't be So
you have to So she has to be your type.
So if she's not your type, that means you're gay.
I'm not sure that's what gay means to be honest. Really?
I'm not entirely sure that's what gay
means to be honest. Sounds like a copycat statement.
Copycat. Little copycat. You little
Binda. You little copycat.
What if she's just not your type?
What if you liked blonde people with big boobs?
boobs? Does that still make you gay?
Just throwing that out there.
You little copycat.
Little copycat. Bender. You little
You little copycat. No.
You don't copy that. You don't copycat.
You little copycat.
Yeah. If you don't find shovel co hot,
you're gay. You little copycat.
Bless you. Do you want to fit in with the crowd?
Bless you. Do you want to fit in?
Bless you then. If you want to fit in
with the crowd, you don't want to feel
left out, do you? It must be tough being new, you know?
I mean, like I said, you could like
blonde people with big boobs and blue eyes.
I mean, not attractive is not attractive to everyone.
But they say if you don't find Shel Co
attractive, you're gay.
Sounds like what a copycat would say. If
I didn't know any better.
What if you liked black women?
I'm not trying anything, bro. I'm
leaving England. End of.
I'm not trying anything to do with
women. I don't want nothing to do with them.
I hate them. And that's that. No,
the only time I'd have anything to do
with one if it's to do with me ruining their life.
I'd ruin a woman a woman's life, but
that's about it.
Try men. No thanks.
There was a woman I was going to [ __ ]
over Billy. I was going to take her to
the restaurant and make her pay,
but she clocked on, right? So, I just
stood her up anyways.
I'd love to [ __ ] up a woman's life, bro, really badly.
They deserve it. They're [ __ ] Absolute [ __ ]
There's no good ones out there, mate.
Take them from me. They don't exist.
You like Cheryl Carinder? You little copycat.
You a little copycat.
You little copycat.
Little copycat. You look copycat. No,
I need to work on my meow. You're a little copycat.
Yeah, [ __ ] you if you're a woman. Women
are [ __ ] [ __ ] you.
I hate women.
I hope someone comes in you and you gets
and then you get pregnant and your whole
life gets ruined. Scumbag.
I'd love it. That's what these women
need. They need their life ruining, [ __ ]
I should have [ __ ] that cunt's life up
in America, bro. I wish I wish I could I
knew what she was like. I would have
ruined her life.
I would have ruined her life, bro.
Really would have ruined her life.
All women, bro. All women.
Every single each and every one of them.
All of them. Yep.
And I hate I hate [ __ ] men as well. So, Yep.
I would go out and just [ __ ] a woman's
life up, but I don't have the energy,
mate. And I'm not a sado.
I would do it cuz I hate them that bad.
I'd make them pay for all of the [ __ ]
they put me through, bro. Especially that American.
I hate them so much, bro.
All women are bad. Yes, they are. Every
single woman is bad and I'm yet to be
proven wrong by them.
All women are definitely definitely bad.
They're all liars. None of them are
genuine. They're toxic.
There's all women are bad. 100% all
28 years and counting, bro. I'm 28.
I was 28 last month and I can tell you
they are all bad. Trust me.
So that's that. That's why I don't
bother with them.
I was really bored on the Thursday.
That's why I went out. I don't know. I'm
never bored, but that's me done for. Yeah,
that's that in it.
No, women are definitely all bad.
They are all bad.
Really, really are. They are all bad.
All [ __ ] All time wasters, all
full of excuses, same attitude.
Uh cuz I don't like men.
I mean, I don't like white knights and
white knights are men.
How about you just don't go with either
because you're not gay? Doesn't that
make more sense? I mean, you hate women,
right? That doesn't mean that you like
men. Doesn't it make more sense to go
with maybe neither because you're not
gay? Maybe. No. Straight to the being
gay, isn't it? Yeah. So, because you
hate women because what they're like,
that automatically means you want dick.
No, I don't like anyone.
I don't like white knights either.
Why? Why would I be gay just because I hate women?
No, I wouldn't date you.
You fat ugly [ __ ] Kaye. No.
Well, I'm happy by myself. Simple as that.
You really think all women aren't bad?
You're delusional if you think all women are bad.
Most of them are narcissists. Are you
[ __ ] for real?
Most of these women are narcissists.
What do you mean they're not all bad?
Are you mad in your head?
[ __ ] off, mate.
Get the [ __ ] out of here.
And why are you asking me if I would
date you? What a stupid question. No thanks.
Why would I date you?
Most women are narcissist.
All women aren't bad.
You're crazy if you think that.
You're really mad if you think all women aren't bad.
I've met more women than most people in
the world, bro. To be fair, I'm 20. I
might be 28, but I've met loads and
loads and loads of women.
Well, I'll put it this way. I've met
more than enough women.
I think that tells you, you know.
No, I wasn't begging for you. Definitely wasn't.
I'd never go anywhere near you. [ __ ] that. Yeah.
Yeah. You wish Yep.
What is that?
Yeah. Put the text up. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. [ __ ] off.
Do you want my opinion?
[ __ ] women. I hate women.
They're [ __ ] [ __ ] them.
[ __ ] women. I hate him.
I hope I hope they all die of cancer.
You know what I mean? Yep.
But they all die of cancer.
Nah, women are all the same. I'm not
asked. I'm happy by myself.
Thank you though.
And it's not what I think, it's what I know.
Going by my experiences, they're all [ __ ]
Yeah, they're scumbags. They're evil
Yeah, I am happy. I'm just tired.
I'm I'm buzzing, bro. I'm leaving soon.
Of course I'm happy.
I was a bit pissed off today cuz you [ __ ]
Yep. Whatever, Katie. We've heard it all before.
I've put my approaches up there. I've
put my messages up there.
Whatever you say. I'm I mean, I've
already shown my evidence and I'm not
going back and forth.
I've shown my messages. I've shown my
approaches. I've shown their attitude.
Take it or leave it. I'm not interested.
That's you, bro. You want to You want to
agree, that's on you. You want to
disagree, that's on you. I don't care.
I've got nothing left to prove.
So, that's that.
This is what I'm trying to say. You'll
be shown things
and you'll still dismiss them.
That's what's weird is you you'll be
shown evidence of what they do and then
you'll still argue it. You you you'll
show you'll be shown
black and white evidence and still
disagree with it. How the [ __ ] does that
even make sense?
How can people be shown black and white
evidence and still think they're right?
It's mad. It's like going to a courtroom
with evidence against you killing
someone and pleading not guilty. It
doesn't make any sense.
That is mad.
You get shown messages. You get shown
approaches and you still dismiss them.
Why do you dismiss people's struggles anyways?
Is there a reason why you do that? Genuine question.
Why do you keep dismissing people's struggles?
Anyone got any answer to that?
Why do you do that? Anyways,
you're saying that maybe it's not the women,
but I've literally put approaches on my
channel multiple times.
How is it not the women? What is there?
Is there something I'm missing?
Everyone makes excuses for these stuck
up entitled [ __ ] with unrealistic standards.
Everyone's tired of it now.
We're tired of it. Tired of it, bro.
Tired of it.
No, thank you.
I think I need to give up, which is what
I've done. That's what you need to do.
You need to give up, which is what I done.
They're never going to change these women.
So, no, you need to give up and leave,
which is what I'm doing.
Still dismissing people's struggles. Mad.
You dismiss people's struggles. It's weird.
Very, very weird why people do that.
Dismissing people's struggles.
Why do you do that? That's weird.
You shown You get shown things and you
dismiss them. How does that make sense? Huh?
I [ __ ] hate women. They're [ __ ]
You've seen my videos.
Talking about rejection again. I can't
be bothered with you, bro. I'm not even
answering your questions now.
You're just talking silliness now. So, never mind.
There's no getting through to you
people. So, there's no point.
You know, why do they dismiss all the
bad things women do? Billy Bundles,
maybe you can answer it because no one
seems to be answering it. You just keep
seem to keep dismissing everything I'm saying.
Why do you keep dismissing people's struggles?
I don't know how many times I've asked
I've asked this and it's still not been answered.
Is it because I'm a man or I'm genuinely
question why do you keep doing that?
making excuses and defending women.
Well, we'll find out tomorrow when I do
this experiment, won't we?
Any thoughts on the approaches or the
messages? No, just dismiss that. You're
literally dismissing everything I'm
saying, so I don't know why you keep typing.
It doesn't really make much sense.
You're dismissing things I'm saying and
you're making stuff up.
So, I don't know why you're still typing
to me to be honest.
They dismiss every bad thing women does. It's weird. M
still dismissing my struggles. Madness.
These people are [ __ ] sexist. They are, bro.
Oh, it's all good to someone. Yeah.
Sorry. I was talking to someone.
Yeah, I believe it when I see it. That's
what I say.
Yeah. So that's that. [ __ ] that, bro. I
hate women, bro. I hope they all [ __ ]
get raped. Honestly, I hate me. Literally,
I hope they will get raped. Me, bro.
[ __ ] scum of the earth. Yeah. So, man.
Yeah. Ant-Man was saying the same thing.
They say they want a nice guy, but they
always end up with these [ __ ]
Yeah. These women need to get raped.
They're [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. I hate
them. No sympathy for me either.
Hope they will get raped. They deserve it. Hunts. Yeah.
[ __ ] them, bro.
I hope they will get raped, Finder. I'm
not even joking.
I hope they all die cancer and get
raped. All of them. Yeah.
Yeah. That's where we're at basically.
What do you think of this [ __ ] Joe
Finder? It's [ __ ] mad, isn't it? But
yeah, I won't be doing nothing tomorrow.
Probably just be in bed. Not doing no
football bet, no nothing.
What? Tomorrow? I'm not I'm not drinking tomorrow.
I'm not going out tomorrow, bro.
I'm not going out tomorrow. I'm chilling, bro. Yeah.
I'm not going to drink alcohol in the
house. I'm not an alcoholic.
No, I'm good. Yeah.
No, I don't I don't drink that much. No. Yeah.
No. Well, maybe like 3 years ago.
I don't really drink that much anymore
unless I go out when I used to try to
meet women and [ __ ] but they're all the
same [ __ ] So
yeah, 3 years ago Yeah, love. Yep.
I hate women, man. I don't want to get raped.
That guy with a sniff. Don't know what
you're talking about, bro. Yeah, I'm here.
I've never been to a concert. Oh, yeah.
That was last No, it was the October
before that. Maybe it was last October.
Yeah, [ __ ] the [ __ ]
Yeah, she sucked my dick. She kept
wanting to [ __ ]
Yeah, she was Somalian.
She lives in um Shepherd's Bush.
Yeah, the somalian. Yeah,
bang the somian. Yeah, [ __ ]
Can you save? Can you live off £50 a
week for 6 months? I could do it. Yeah,
discipline. I could do it.
I could 100% live off 50 a week for 6
months. If I had to in order to go on
holiday, I would [ __ ] do it. I could
do it, mate. I'm a good saver. I could do it.
discipline. Yeah, I could do it.
I could do 50 a week. 100%, bro.
For 6 months, be depressed, and then leave. Yeah,
time flies, isn't it?
Yeah. Go Thailand. I I could do it, bro.
Yeah, I could do it.
Well, that's what you've got to do. I
mean, do you still go out? I don't
really go out on nights out anymore in this country
because it's just pointless for the
[ __ ] For the [ __ ] women, you
don't get anywhere
toxic. I mean, yeah, but that's that's
what you do if you want to save up for something.
Do you need to go on nights out? I
didn't go out yesterday. I'm not going out today.
There's no point.
There's literally no point in going out.
You go out to try to meet women and no
one's interested. So why why would you go out?
Well, I went out three weeks in a row,
you know, the past couple weeks, escorts
and stuff, but I wish I hadn't. I wish I
just saved the money, to be honest.
Yeah, I don't I don't really go out now.
I've got no money, but
there's no point cuz it would always be
the same here with the women, so no point.
You can get banned in places as well,
even for speaking to people. I got
banned for speaking to people. I got
banned in a place for speaking to people.
It's not the pints. Even if even even a
pint of Guinness is £8, but you don't
have more than like eight Guinnesses.
So all in all, it's all right. To be fair,
it's the rum that you don't want to
drink because they water it down. But
even if I go to a place where it's 8
pound a Guinness,
I only have a few and then I'm [ __ ]
the whole night. So, so yeah,
all you do is you pay to go to these
places just to see a bunch of
disinterested women. That's all you see,
just disinterested women.
that aren't interested.
What do you think would happen if I went
out approaching today?
out approaching today? Finder
Same old in it. Whoa.
Yeah, I would live off 50 pound a week for six
and then leave.
No, you It's not that you might get a
few numbers. You will get a few numbers.
No, you will get a few numbers. You will
always get numbers.
It sucks. You can't even get laid.
I was [ __ ] horny as [ __ ] yesterday as well.
It sucks. She can't even get laid. It's
depressing as [ __ ]
You can't even get laid here. It's mad. No,
no. You can't get laid. You can't do
nothing. You can't date. You can't have a family.
Sucks, isn't it? It really, really is a
horrible country, isn't it? Suck up women.
never changes. Mad is it? You can't even
get a date. Like I said, I haven't had a
date since April.
God knows how many times I've been out since April.
You might as well just not even try.
That's how bad it is.
I was speaking to some woman on Reddit. Um
the number uh I got a number.
The boyfriend thing it just gives you a headache.
Yeah. I was speaking to some woman on
Reddit on Instagram. Then she randomly
blocked me. I messaged on Instagram. I
said, "Why you blocked me?" She said, "I
don't really like talking on there."
That's who was talking
and all of a sudden she's blocked me on
there. It's weird how they switch, isn't it?
They're one person one day and then the
next day there's someone else.
I don't trust them as well. They're
liars. All women are lying bullshitters
as well. That's another thing. They're
absolute lying bullshitters.
I just don't like them, bro. I really,
really don't like them. Seriously, they
aren't evil, bro. They really, really are.
And it bothered me today cuz when you're
talking about it, you're thinking about
it. Like today when I had that argument,
when you're talking about it, you're
being reminded of it. Whereas most days,
we just kind of
Yeah. You're not reliving it. You know,
that's what you're doing here. You're reliving it.
Bad experiences and [ __ ]
Toxic. The amount of narcissists I've
had to deal with recently as well.
It's so bad. Really, really bad.
Horrible, bro. Horrible.
So, how would you get a sex life here?
You won't, will you, Finder Billy? Nope.
You won't get a sex life, will you? Nah. No chance.
Very very unlikely. No.
It's bad, isn't it?
Or people that actually want children and [ __ ] Very bad.
Yeah. You can't even get that. You You
can't even get a conversation out of the [ __ ]
let alone friends with benefits. You
can't even get that. No one's interested.
So, we won't be going outside and
humiliating ourselves. Yeah. You can't
even get that.
I don't think I've had sex with somebody that wasn't
Yeah. Probably about a year and a half ago. Yeah, you could.
Yeah. People go on like you can get sex
easy. You can barely even get a
conversation out someone, let alone sex. It's [ __ ]
Even sex is impossible to get. Like even
if you just wanted sex, there's people
out there that just wanted sex. Even that's impossible.
because the dating apps don't work and
if you try to speak to people, they're
not interested. So, as usual, so you
wouldn't even be able to get sex.
There'd be no way of getting laid.
Even if you just wanted sex, which is
mad when you think about it, is it? It
is actually mad when you think about that.
No sex life, no nothing.
Sad really, isn't it?
for people that have got a high sex
drive in it. Mine's not really that high anymore. Thank [ __ ]
but it used to be bad when it did. It
used to make me depressed like 5 years ago.
Not women that I slept with. Nope. Uh-uh. Nope.
So it used to be mad when I used to have
a high sex drive, but I don't have a sex
drive anymore really. So
yeah, I don't think I slept with any of
them. Oh, a lot of these women, they go
on dates to waste people's time as well.
That's another thing. I've had a I've
had some bad dates this this year. So,
there's no point even going on dates
either cuz they've all got unrealistic
expectations. But if you think about it,
the whole thing is just a waste of time.
The whole thing is just a waste of time
if you think about it.
It's just a whole waste of time if you
think about it. Cuz all that's going to
happen is you're going to go out, people
are going to pretend they got
boyfriends, give attitude,
or say they're not interested very
rudely, or give you their number and
lead you on.
Or if you're very, very, very lucky,
you'll get a date that
just goes on a date to waste time.
There's nothing good that can come from going out.
So yeah, I'm just going to stay in. Yeah.
So that's that. Nothing good can come
from it. It'll always be the same. Yeah.
It's not about mindset. In order for
your mindset to change, your experiences
need to change. And this [ __ ] with women
will never change.
Nah, [ __ ] that.
No, bro. Your experiences need to change.
That's how life works, you see. So,
no, last year I was depressed. I don't
even get I don't even get depressed anymore.
Last year I was [ __ ] depressed.
I mean, it's always been the same [ __ ] with women.
It's been the same for years,
bro. But that happened one time about 2 years ago.
Don't think it was last year. Maybe it
was. Bro, it happened one time. How
about the fact that I went out and got
10 numbers and I didn't even get a
single date? How about that? I'm on 26
numbers and not even a single date.
Yeah, it's not good, bro.
It's not good. It's disgusting. And
that's why I gave up for my own mental health.
Um, so yes,
it's disgusting. That's why I gave up
and I'm booking this trip as well. I
need to get a new phone.
Any thoughts on the 26 numbers and not a
single date? No. Completely slipped your
mind. Didn't suit you.
Anything being on the me getting numbers
last week and not getting anywhere?
Three weeks before that, not getting
anywhere. No, just completely didn't
suit you. No, just talk about something
that happened once last year. That'll do
it. Yeah, that suits you better. Yeah,
>> you dismiss people's struggles.
So there's no point of the whole thing.
There's no po point of this whole conversation.
cuz you constantly will just keep
dismissing people's struggles. And I'm
sick of repeating it. And I'm sick of repeating myself.
You know what I'm saying?
Not had a single date since April. We
are in It's almost December now.
I don't think I'm going to meet someone.
I don't know.
I mean, not a single date since April,
and I have approached God knows how many
women since April. I don't think I'm
going to find someone. I don't think I'm
going to meet someone.
To be honest with you, for some reason,
I do not think you're going to meet someone.
No, I definitely don't think you are. So yeah,
nah, all I know is I've not had a date since April
and that's that's the end of it. So I'm
talking this year I have not had a date since April.
So that's the end of that. Whatever
happened last year was last year. I have
not had a date since April and I'm not
willing to go out and try again. I'm not
dealing with their attitude, the
toxicness, the [ __ ] the mind games.
I'm not dealing with it. So, it's not my
problem anymore. Simple. So,
yeah, it's not good. It's really,
really, really not good.
you know, traveled up and down the
country since I was 22. That's terrible, bro.
I should be with someone right now.
Right this second, I should be with
someone at this age. I should have to
keep trying. I don't have the energy to
keep trying. I'm not disrespecting
myself to keep trying. I should be with
someone right now. So, really, it's not
good. It's disgusting.
Horrible. It's vile, bro. Vile.
So you should be with someone. Yeah.
Yep. And they've got attitude problems as well.
These women are very, very, very, very
nasty and rude.
I want to stop talking about it anyways,
bro. It's depressing. It is depressing
talking about it. I want to stop talking
about it now.
Oh, it's depressing.
I want to stop talking about these [ __ ]
You need to [ __ ] off and get raped. Stop
talking about them anymore.
It's [ __ ] depressing as [ __ ] That's So yeah. Um,
so yeah, I'm just saving now anyways.
Just being a boring [ __ ] now and just saving basically. Yeah.
You got to stop. No. No.
Yep. I've heard it all before.
That's what makes me laugh. You get
these women that say they go for
personality, yet these women are stuck
up. And yeah, I'm going to stop talking
about it anyways cuz we just go around in circles.
We just go around in circles, bro. And
yeah, I've I've given up to get away
from it. So, I don't need to talk about it anymore. Simple. [ __ ] them.
They're evil [ __ ] I hope they get
raped. [ __ ] them. Yeah, simple. Yeah.
I wish I never ever ever spoke to one in
my life, bro.
I [ __ ] hate him, bro. Really hate him
with a passion.
And if that [ __ ] in America was in front
of me, I'd smash her face in, bro.
I would absolutely smash the cunt's face in
like the bad experiences that I've had
for years isn't worth what I got. I
could have traveled the world, bro.
I could have actually traveled the world
with that money that I had and used to
get. It's not worth it. I could have
done so much better, you know?
That's how bad it is,
you know, other than dealing with their
behavior and [ __ ] and whatever,
you know, it's not worth it. It's not
worth it. The amount of times I used to
go out, [ __ ] hell, and have to come
back at 8:00 in the morning,
bro. It's disgusting, bro. Disgusting, you know.
Just leave them to it. They're just [ __ ] bro.
Yeah. So, I'll be chilling tomorrow anyways.
Watch a movie or something. Yeah.
People on Reddit say you can get sex
easy, Billy. They say you go on dating
apps to get sex.
They're [ __ ] idiots. It is.
Yeah, I'm too tired. I don't have the
energy. I like to be back in bed by
about 11 12.
Yeah, I don't have the energy for it now. Yeah.
Yeah. I used to be out until the light,
but now I don't have the energy for it.
I don't know. I just don't have the energy anymore. Yeah.
Yeah. I got a [ __ ] in the alleyway.
That was like [ __ ] a year and a half
ago, bro. Two years ago.
That's it's it's Do you know these
things, bro? They're one they're one in a lifetime.
You know, these things that we speak of
is one in a lifetime.
Blowjobing an alleyway, pulling off the
street. They will never happen again. Like me,
I'll probably never have sex ever again
with a normal person. Obviously, you
could have sex with an escal, but like
in terms of like a normal person, it's
very unlikely that you'll ever have sex again or
by the looks of it even get a date again.
Yeah, these are all one in a lifetime things.
someone offering you their number on the
street, someone giving you a [ __ ] in the alleyway.
These are all very, very rare things.
They're super, super rare things.
And it's only cuz I went out like a
million times, but they're super super super rare.
So, it weren't worth it in the end,
really, was it?
So yeah, very very very rare. Very rare.
I can't tell you the amount of times I
used to go out and [ __ ] get nothing.
Millions and millions and millions and
millions of times. Yeah.
dates that wasted my time. It really
wasn't worth it to be honest.
Yeah, but who do I have now? No one. I
don't even have a sex life now. So
it doesn't really matter, does it? I
should have a sex life now. I should be
with someone now.
But you don't. So
you should be with someone now with all
of the trying.
But you don't. And I'm not trying again.
So that's that in it.
Very very rare. I'll probably never have
sex again, bro. Unless it's an escort.
It's very very very unlikely. Like I was
saying, it's very unlikely.
It's very rare to meet someone now.
Very rare. Very, very, very rare.
That American that I pulled off the street was
one in a lifetime.
when they offered me their number and
they met up with me. It's very It's one
in a lifetime, bro. That one
I tried for like two years before that, I think.
Yeah, I gave up because of the leading on
is the bullshiting, the false hope, the
attitude and that.
Um, I remember when I went out
approaching 3 weeks ago, right? They
were so stuck up their attitude, their
bullshitting. And I was like, "What the
[ __ ] is this? Is what is this what you
got to go through to meet someone?" I
was only doing it to like [ __ ] around.
And I was like, "Oh [ __ ] is this what I
have to go through in order to find a
partner? [ __ ] this. I'm not doing this
[ __ ] again after today. I just done it
as a laugh. I don't know why I done it.
That's why I'd never do it again, bro.
Then I gave up for like I gave up for
like two months. Cuz I gave up for like Yeah.
Dealing with their attitude.
Dealing with their shitty attitude. So yeah. Yep.
So yeah, that's why I gave up.
I'm not dealing with that [ __ ] just in
order to find someone. [ __ ] that.
All stuck up [ __ ]
No, thank you, bro.
I'd rather be by myself.
Easier that way.
It a bit weird that you're never going
to have a sex life, but
so be it.
I don't even get escorts anymore. My sex
drivers die down that much. Doesn't
matter, mate. It's not going to change
my situation, is it? Thinking about other people.
I don't care about other people, bro.
I mean, there's this guy called Ed
Matthews, right? And he's uh he's
good-look and he's big on Tik Tok and he
can't even get anyone.
He's rich. He's got Tik Tok followers
and even he can't find anyone.
I mean, that really puts it into
perspective how hard it actually is. And
it shows that you've got absolutely no chance. Well,
well, I I would say it shows that you
got no chance, but I still don't like to
compare myself to other people.
But let's just say it's very shocking.
I still like to think that maybe I'm a
bit different than him.
Yeah, but she had a she's got a
boyfriend now, so that's [ __ ]
So, I can't use her anymore.
I don't have anyone now, bro.
I have no one.
Literally no one. So yeah.
Yeah, I think she found someone.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. And then
this is a guy that's
good-looking and [ __ ] Yeah. And even
he can't find anyone.
So most people will see that and think,
"What the fuck?"
Cuz if he can't find anyone being what he is,
you ain't got no chance, bro. You ain't
got no chance. No [ __ ] chance. No chance.
And he's done it in America as well. And
they're [ __ ] in America as well, bro. Cuz
I used to think, right, it was just the
American women in London cuz people used
to say, "Oh yeah, if you go to America,
they'll like the accent." And no, no,
no. It's [ __ ] They're even worse in America.
Cuz I used to go out in central London
on Thursdays and they'd always be Americans always.
But no, they're bad. even in uh
Yeah, they're bad.
And why would you even waste your time going out?
No one's interested, Billy. So, why are
you wasting your time and their time?
Cuz they're not interested in this
country. So why are you why would you uh
why would you waste your time? You know
this tire one that led me on is a [ __ ]
Just another time wasting [ __ ] that
leads people on. Boring.
They're boring as [ __ ] it.
Bors me, bro. Yep.
I got an American's number, sorry, a Manchester's number
a couple weeks ago. She seemed down to
earth and everything, but when I
messaged her, she never replied. Yeah.
Yeah, I hate him, bro. I hate him.
Yeah, I don't have a sex life these days.
No sex life.
Nope. Not for Peter B.
What I don't understand is they will
they will give you their number. They'll
reply to you just to say they're not
interested in the end.
And people will make excuses for them
how they haven't led people on and when
they constantly do.
That's what annoys me, bro,
is the leading on.
That's what annoys me. That's not even
what annoys me. What annoys me is the leading on.
Like you'll get a number that just leads
you on and then [ __ ] you over in the
end. That's why I stopped doing it, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, I got a lot of women's numbers as well,
but they're just not interested.
Yeah, but they don't they lead people on
because they're narcissists. They're narcissists, bro.
Can't even get sex these days. Billy
must be hard on the younger generation. Is it?
I hate it, bro.
Don't let women win.
I hate him, bro. I hate him.
I [ __ ] hate women, bro.
To the maximum.
When I went out with Monty, this woman
led me on.
Constantly leading people on.
[ __ ] them, bro. [ __ ] them.
You know what I might do? Yeah. If I go
out again in a very long time, I might
not even get numbers.
I might just stay with them.
Saying that though, really,
cuz I won't be going out again. So,
that's not going to happen. But that's
what I would do.
There was one I was speaking to from Glasgow, right?
She seemed all right. When I messaged
her, she never replied.
She seemed like down to earth and that,
but never replied.
Have you ever been to Nottingham?
Yep. I've had it as well.
Have you been to Nottingham?
I used to like Nottingham.
I used to go to Nottingham to drink.
I have Shepy. Where the [ __ ] is that? Oh, Ken.
Do you like Sher Cole? Billy,
you're from Kent.
I tell you where is good. Newcastle.
I've been to Newcastle a few times. That was good.
Yeah, this guy said to me that if I
don't like Sher Cole that I'm gay. Billy,
I called him a copycat.
Wants to fit in with the crowd.
Yeah, he says I'm gay.
A little copycat.
He's a little copycat.
Yeah. Do you remember when people used
to say that, Billy? Don't take offense
to it, man. They were just copying each
other. They didn't want to feel left out, you know?
Yeah. A lot of people used to say you're
gay if you don't like her.
But they're just copycats.
Copycat statement, is it? Yeah.
The most I've ever spent on a night out was 700.
Yeah, definitely. Definitely.
He didn't want to feel left out. He's a little copycat.
Yeah. He wanted to fit in with the crowd.
Yeah. He didn't want to feel left out in it.
What celebrity do you like?
I was drinking, gambling, hotels.
Wouldn't be able to do it nowadays. I
don't have as much money nowadays, but I
used to have a lot of money. like um
it was basically [ __ ]
hotels and drinking and gambling and
[ __ ] but I won £700 as well. £600.
I used to have a lot of money, matey. Yeah. Yep.
Yeah, man. It sucks that I'll probably
never have sex again the normal way.
Billy sucks, isn't it?
It does suck, isn't it?
So, I'm really into [ __ ] you see.
But, uh, good luck trying to find
someone to give you a [ __ ] Impossible. Sucks to
Yeah, I need to go to bed in a minute,
but I'm so tired.
No, no, no, no, no.
Well, I'm gone now. I'll be back tomorrow.