[ __ ] hell, bro. That was a long one
yesterday, wasn't it?
Jesus [ __ ] Christ, bro.
Just bloody woke up. Yeah,
I was going to do a football bet. I
can't be bothered
walking to the betting shop. [ __ ] that. Say something.
Yeah, I'll be chilling today in bed. [ __ ] that.
No point going out drinking. Women are
all the same. So, no point doing
anything like that.
It's such a depress depressing country in England.
how depressing this country is. It
annoys me, bro. Let's
buy it up. No.
[ __ ] madness yesterday, is it? [ __ ] bro.
There's no point doing a football mat
them odds because
you're more than likely not going to win
and I'm not lumping on the football. So
there's no point doing if we
not long woke up. I'm just chilling in bed today.
Same old is it?
Anything good in this country? Nah, I
don't think so, mate.
Anything good in this country?
Nah, nothing good.
Yeah, because they were winding me up.
Yeah, cuz yesterday they were winding me up.
Yeah, it's not nice feeling like the boy
who cried wolf. It's a horrible feeling, bro.
I had to say cuz they wouldn't leave me
alone. They kept coming back. I said,
"Fuck off and leave me alone." Simple.
But it was all justified. It's very very
very annoying being boy who cried wolf.
>> Very very very annoying.
It's a [ __ ] country, bro. [ __ ] weather,
[ __ ] people waiting around for everything. Uh
can't have sex.
Can't have a sex life. There's nothing
good about this country. I would have
done a football bet today if I was
closer to the betting shop, but I can't
be bothered to do a football bet. I was
going to do like a treble both teams to
score, no draw, but it's just pointless,
isn't it really?
I probably would have just done both
teams to score to be honest.
Maybe five teams, but pointless.
Yeah, it's actually pointless in it, bro.
Yeah, I looked up the odds yesterday for
double both teams to score. The odds are really bad.
[ __ ] So, the odds are really, really bad.
Nah, I might as well not do a little one
because I'm nowhere near bookies.
So, I might as well not do a little one.
I might as well not because I'm nowhere
near I'm nowhere near a betting shop.
Nah, I'll probably just stay in bed
today to be honest.
I'm not doing anything today.
Nah, I'm staying in bed today. I'm not
doing anything. It's depressing, bro.
Still depressing from yesterday having
to [ __ ] bring up your experiences.
It's [ __ ] depressing and toxic.
You know, I won't be doing anything today.
I just woke up. I just [ __ ] woke up.
I'm saving money, bro. It's the right
thing I'm doing. But I'm doing it.
That's why I look I look all like this,
bro. Probably why I'm going bob is I'm
saving as much money as I can
when I leave.
Look at me. What the [ __ ] bro?
Yeah. Can't be asked, bro. I'm not even
depressed either. I just can't be bothered.
I don't know. I might do a six both
teams as well.
[ __ ] those. Bro,
you all right, Captain?
You all right, Captain? Cory. Captain. Yeah.
No, I'm not doing anything today, bro.
I'm saving my pennies.
It's actually raining today.
Go out today and approach and get
rejected and deal with the same toxic
[ __ ] No thanks.
Oh yeah, that aim is a [ __ ] mto as
well. I think I'm Ed Matthews. How the
[ __ ] did I think I'm Ed Matthews? What
the [ __ ] I don't even talk like him.
What the [ __ ] I I met Matthews. What
the [ __ ] I'm pretty sure I've been
approaching I've been approaching before him.
What the [ __ ] am I I'm sure I've been
approaching before him.
I've been approaching since I got split
from the [ __ ] umbilical cord.
Since the umbilical cord got snipped.
That's what I've been approaching since. Cory. Yeah.
>> Have you seen how he gets uh Have you
seen how this guy gets rejected
and they think there's hope for us? This
guy gets rejected, right? But yet they
still think there's hope for us. Cory,
isn't that mad? But they still think
that there's hope for us.
How is there, bro? How is that hope for
us? I watch your stuff, bro, and it's
bad. It's bad how they act. Yeah. Okay.
So, I'm going to meet someone, right?
Yeah. This guy gets [ __ ] rejected and
[ __ ] as well. The guy has got
[ __ ] millions of followers. The guy's
got status, bro.
And he still gets rejected. What the
[ __ ] And they think that someone like
me's got a chance. What? [ __ ] off, bro.
I seen this guy in America, bro, and he
was put up with the same [ __ ] as what I
put up with. I was like, how does that
even make sense?
I thought they'd want people with loads
of followers and stuff. So, even then,
you still don't get anything.
I think unless you're a drug dealing
pedophile, no one's interested. I think
unless you sell crack to kids and you're
a nons, I don't think women are
interested, bro. Unless you're a
pedophile, to be honest with you. Unless
you're a [ __ ] nons that beats up kids
and sells crack to kids. I think that's
the only way you're going to get
someone, bro. You'll laugh at it.
Yep. Unless you're a scumbag pedophile
that sells crap to kids, I don't think
you got any hope.
Cuz I would say that Ed Matthews is more
he's more confident than me because he
approaches more well he approaches more
than me. So, I don't really do it
anymore. But that guy is good. I don't
know why he gets the same [ __ ] as well.
The second part.
What second part?
You need to sell crap crystal meth to
kids. They'll be all over you, bro.
Unless you sell crap to kids, they're not interested.
I thought the I thought the followers
would have done it.
I was on Tik Toky yesterday. uh Cory and
they were constantly making excuses.
They're not high standards, they're
unrealistic standards. There's a big difference.
There's a big difference between high
standards and unrealistic standards.
A woman would not get with you cuz
you've got green eyes and not blue eyes.
So, like as an example, they don't have
high standards. They've got unrealistic
standards. There's a big difference.
There's nothing wrong with having high standards.
So what what you're saying I'm a nons?
It doesn't matter. I'm not getting into
it, bro. I don't care. I'm not getting
into it. So that's that simple.
It's bad, bro. It's very, very toxic.
That's how it gets in the end, Cory.
It's not even depressing. It's toxic.
Very, very, very, very toxic.
It's not even depressing. It's toxic, you know.
Yeah, but what's the point of me
answering? There's no point of me
answering. What's What's it going to do
me answering then?
You know what these [ __ ] women are
like. So, what what do you want me to
Why do you want me to answer it?
And actually I'm not a nons mate. You
like nonses. You like nons legs.
You people in there love nons legs. You
love nonses. So mate, if I was a [ __ ]
nunch, you would love it. You love
nonsers on here. That's why you
constantly defend nons. They con Have
you noticed how they constantly defend
nons, Cory on here? Right. They tried to
say that me and Monty man, right, is a
nons, but actual nons like nonsle legs.
They love them. They sit there and make
excuses for them. They love nonsers on here.
They love nons on here, bro. Trust me.
No, no, no. They do. They absolutely love nons.
They love nons, bro. You say that these
people have got a problem with things
that you've said in the past, but they
they don't go for real nons
because they love nons themselves.
They're trying to deflect when they're
calling you a nons, right? It's like
when that [ __ ] right, calls me a
virgin. Even though I put a porno out
there, no one says anything. People keep
going at me. Yeah. When I call that [ __ ]
a virgin. Oh, he can't be he can't be a
virgin cuz he's got a girlfriend.
They do it like we've heard it all
before, bro. They're nons lovers.
They're absolute nonsloving little
[ __ ] That's what they are, bro.
Both score no draw. Both teams just score.
>> Okay, bro. Whatever. Yeah, I don't have
anything to offer. Okay, whatever. We've
heard it all before. Boring.
Yeah. Okay. Hey, whatever you say.
Boring. We've heard all of this before.
Boring. Boring. Boring.
I don't know, bro.
You know what makes me laugh through
this whole thing, Cory? Yesterday,
right? Do you know what annoyed me about
this whole thing yesterday is the fact
that I put videos up? I literally put
like several different videos up that
everyone has seen by the way that might
not be on there anymore and they're
still still talking [ __ ] even though I
put up videos of what these women are
like time and time and time and time
again. So it's like is there a point in
me being in the argument then if you're
just going to dismiss everyone's struggles?
Yeah. Okay, whatever, bro. Low value
man. Yeah, whatever. Anyways, um, so is
there a point in me even being in this
argument? Like I I I should have went
backstage because they literally dismiss
every bad thing that they do.
They literally dismiss anything that
they do. So is there any point of the
whole argument? That's that's why I
stopped it in the end
cuz any bad thing they do, they just
ignore it and dismiss it. So there's no
point you even being in having an
argument cuz any bad they do, they'll
just make excuses for them. So there's no point.
I don't know and I don't care. I put
videos up for a reason and I'm not
explaining myself. If you was too
ignorant to watch the videos, that's on
you. I'm not explaining myself and I'm
not repeating myself.
So that's that. Enough is enough.
You're just going to keep making excuses
for women and I'm not interested in
that. I'm not interested in people that do that.
So, I don't care. They're all [ __ ]
I hope they all get raped and that's it.
[ __ ] off and leave me alone.
I hope they all get cancelled and get
raped. Simple. [ __ ] them. So, that's that.
Bet you love that one. Is it Cory?
That's that. Sir. Sir,
I'm skint and lonely.
Why? Why would I be skint?
Okay, whatever you say, bro. Okay,
whatever. I'm going to block you in a
minute as well. You're boring.
Yes, you're boring. I'm skin. I'm skin.
How many times have you people on here
call people skin and you've been showed
otherwise? You want to maybe stop
embarrassing yourself now? The last one
being the trainers.
Again, we're not you. We're not you. We
don't all have your life. Again, like
I've said millions of times before, you
seem to think everyone's got your life.
Skin. You people are skins. And I'm on
YouTube. Yeah. Skin m again. Self projecting, right?
Right. I'm skinn, bro. You've been
shown. Okay. Yep. Whatever. So, why
don't you come in the hangouts and show your face, huh?
Because you're an ugly bastard. This is
what I mean. It's all self-p projection
with you people. No one cares about your
little self-p projection. The truth
don't hurt. You're talking about
yourself. You're only hurting yourself.
You people are fat and ugly. The truth's
only hurting yourselves because it's you
you're talking about. You you people are
skinned on YouTube. Skin little fat ugly
people that take your frustration out on other people
like this Darren. Some fat ugly [ __ ] in
these 40s depressed on YouTube. This is
what I'm saying. It's all self-p
projection with you people. You fat ugly
people have been coming on here for
donkeys years, mate.
Bro, you fat ugly people, right?
Autism, OCD, depression. That's
yourself. Self-p projection. Yeah. Keep
talking about yourself. Yeah. Yeah.
That's you. Stop looking in the mirror.
You're disabled. Yeah, that's you.
Uh-huh. That's you. Stop talking about yourself.
That's you. Stop talking bad about
yourself. If you keep talking about
yourself, I'm going to have to ban you
for 5 minutes. Stop picking on yourself.
Stop talking about your disabilities.
It's not nice talking about yourself like that.
Stop calling yourself all of them
things. I can't have someone keep
talking about themselves like that.
Don't call yourself disabled and
skinned. That's not nice.
That's not You You'll happily join the
panel, will you? Okay, I'll put a link
up for you then if you if you want to
join the panel.
Stop calling yourself disabled in skins.
You have been shown money multiple
times, thousands and thousands.
Mate, stop calling yourself disabled.
Stop picking on yourself. I'm gonna have
to time you out. I'm not going to have
someone keep bullying themselves on my channel.
Anyways, I'm going to put the link up
now. You want to join?
You need to stop calling yourself names.
It's horrible. You know,
they call people skint because they're
skint themselves. You know why? That's
why they constantly going about money
cuz they are skint. I'm on YouTube
saving I'm I'm saving money, Cory. I
literally do this like twice, three
times a year, no matter what money I
get. That's why I'm on YouTube. These
people literally have nothing. That's
why they want it every day. Skin, fat,
ugly people. Depressed coming on here
every day trying to bring other people
down. That's what they are, bro. That's
what they are.
They're fat, ugly, disabled little bully
victims. That's why they're on him every day.
I'm on here, bro, because [ __ ] I'm
I'm just saving money. Anyways, you coming on
you shy little m. That's why they come
here and bring hate because they're fat
and ugly. No hopers. So that's why they
come here, Cory, and bring hate on
people's channel because they're fat,
ugly, and hopeless. And that's why when
you say these things to them, it hits a
nerve. It triggers a nerve because
everything I say about them is the
truth. fat, ugly, skint nobodyies. Ask
yourself this question, bro. If they've
got all of this money, why they sat on
YouTube all day every day, bro? Because
they're fat, ugly, and skint. I just I
just told you why I'm on YouTube. I've
literally I think I I think that's true
in what I'm saying, bro. I mean, I've
done a lot the past couple weeks. I'm
just I'm just chilling and I want to
save money, bro. Like, and I just don't
want to do anything. But these people on
here because they're skint ugly fat
people with no life.
You know how many calls I get a [ __ ]
day because of this [ __ ] Jamie
Thompson? That reminds me. I need to
change my number, by the way. Remind me.
Yeah. No, that's that.
Yeah, that's not him.
I think that's that [ __ ] V.
Don't think he's coming on. I think
that's that [ __ ]
What's his name? Fantasy stories. That
[ __ ] Irish little m that got bullied
by Pat Mustard. Think so.
>> It'll be lonely this Christmas for the second mother.
>> It's the one that got bullied by Pat.
It's the bully victim. It's the Irish
bully victim. Oh no,
>> the bully victim. Hey,
>> it didn't bully you off for two years,
you Irish virgin.
He knew it. He can't even stay with me.
It's the bully victim. I knew it. It's
the Irish bully victim,
>> bro. You can't even stay on a hangout
with me, you [ __ ] Northern Irish
spasticated bastard. [ __ ] out of here,
bro. It's the Northern Irish bully
victim. Yeah, who got run up [ __ ]
YouTube by Pat Mustard. Go and [ __ ]
suck your mom's [ __ ] That's the only
[ __ ] that you'll ever get. You [ __ ]
Northern Irish virgin. You literally
can't even stay in a hangout with me,
you [ __ ] Northern Irish virgin. Women
hate you as well. That's why you're
still a virgin. Yeah, Mr. Lonely on
YouTube running away from Pat Mustard,
giving it all the big right for all of
that time. And then you ran away, you
[ __ ] Northern Irish little spacker.
Yeah, I swear to God, bro, if I was in
Ireland, I would call this [ __ ] out
today, bro. Yeah, this [ __ ] Northern
Irish [ __ ] little [ __ ] spasticated
little ma in his mommy's basement. You
ran away from fat bustard. You ran away
from fat bustard,
>> bro. How can anyone take you seriously?
>> You are lonely. You are lonely.
>> For PJ,
>> you are lonely. Yeah, >> PJ.
>> Well, at least I didn't get bullied on YouTube by
big losers. At least I didn't get run
off for you by Pat busted like you. You
northern Irish virgin.
>> You northern Irish little virgin. O,
listen. Speaking about women, WHERE'S YOUR WOMAN?
>> Where's your woman virgin boy?
>> Where's your woman? You skin. Where's
your woman? You skin virgin. You don't have one.
>> A TV dinner for Christmas.
>> You don't have one cuz you're a virgin.
>> You skin ugly bastard. Right. Put your
cover on. I need a laugh. Put your cover
>> Oh, I love you. You you you bully me up
on YouTube by Pat. You bully yourself.
Bullied as much as you bully yourself.
You can't even stay out with me.
>> You got bullied. You got bullied by Pat.
You got bullied by old man.
>> You get bullied. You got bullied by a
fat old man. He made you leave. You
don't bully someone like me. You don't
bully someone like me, mate.
>> It's going to be a lonely skin.
>> You got bullied by a fat old man and got
off of YouTube. You don't bully me,
mate. You got bullied by a fat old man.
You let a fat old man run you off of
YouTube. That's bullying. What you're
doing is not bullying.
>> You got bullied by a fat old man and
that's why you talk over me because you
know what I'm saying is the truth. You
know I hit the jackpot. That's why they
talk over you. The bomb used to do it as
well. This fat ugly Northern Irish
little virgin got run off of YouTube by
a fat old man. Yeah. trying to threaten
people with [ __ ] baseball bats. The
[ __ ] Irish skint little bunter little
[ __ ] right? You Everyone saw it.
Everyone saw this Irish little bunter
that woman hates single singleton little
virgin get run off of YouTube by a fat
old man. By a fat old man and he's still
coming on giving it the big. He's still
coming on giving it the big in his
mommy's basement with his shitty little
gay accent. And he's still giving it the
big. The Irish ma is still giving it the
big. This Irish, Northern Irish little
spacker is still giving it the big when
he's run off of YouTube by a fat old man
and he's still coming on with the
spasticated virgin voice giving it the
big. This is what I mean with these
people coming. They honestly, bro. Yeah,
you can't you can't win with these
people. Even when they take L's, they
pretend that they've won. He got bullied
by Pat. That mustard bullied him. How
many people right was after this [ __ ]
So yeah, bro, listen to you as well.
You're the one shouting over people. You
[ __ ] skinned Irish virgin. Your skin
large a skin. They are skin. All the
Irish on their skin. Large a skin. The
[ __ ] Northern Irish spazzed and got
bullied by Pat Musters. Absolutely
skint. Where's your woman? You ugly
bastard. You don't have one because
you're too ugly. Bro, I would love for
you, bro, to come to London. Yeah, I'm
near crying. No, I'm definitely not near
crying. You're the one talking over me, bro.
You got run off of YouTube by Pat
Mustard. Who do you really bully?
Who does your Northern Irish ugly ass
really bully when you got run off of
YouTube by Pat Mustard? You can't even talk properly,
bro. You can't even talk properly.
That's how bad it is. You got bullied by
Pat Mustard and you still come on here
thinking that you've won. That's where
that's where the simple tidbits comes from, bro.
Okay, come on. Come on and we'll discuss
it. Stop leaving. I don't know why you
keep leaving. And And you have to talk
over me cuz you know I'm right. You
[ __ ] Northern Irish virgin little
hunter skin little virgin. That's why
That's why you keep talking over me
because you know I've got you. You know
I've got you by the bulls. That's why
you talk over me, you little bully
victim. Do you think a fat old man could
ever bully me off of YouTube? You think
some fat old man could run me off of
YouTube and make me say, "Sorry, I'm not
so much of an Irish bully victim. Do you
think some new [ __ ] fat old man? Do
you think some fat old man can make me
run off of YouTube for two years like he
did you?" Skin pathetic virgin
stop trying to be the bomb. All right.
>> It's boring now. It's boring now.
>> Mother, what do you want,
>> bro? Stop calling yourself a bun. It's
not nice calling yourself that.
>> You are the mon. You're
>> You need to stop calling yourself a bun.
Stop bullying yourself as the mon.
People call you the
>> Stop bullying yourself. It's not calling
yourself. Okay, put your camera on right now.
>> But listen, you're panicking.
>> Put your camera on right now. Cut your
>> Are you offended by being called the
mon? Yes or no?
>> No, cuz you're talking about yourself.
Stop being called the I'm offended. I'm
>> Why would I not call you what you're doing
>> people again? Cuz he knows I'm right. He
knows exactly I'm right. Listen,
>> you asked me a question. You asked me a
question and I'm trying to answer it.
>> If you put your camera on, it will show
who the MTO is. You virgin boy who ran
away from Pat Mustard. So, put your camera on.
>> Are you finished?
>> Are you going to put your camera on?
>> See what I mean? Munter. You get two.
>> I'm asking Stop calling yourself a bun.
Stop talking about yourself like that.
You need to stop putting mate. You've
already got run off of YouTube by Pat
Mustard. Stop calling yourself ugly.
>> Hate being called the mon when women
call you mon as well.
>> Stop calling yourself a b. Stop calling
yourself. It's not nice to talk about
yourself like that. Why do you keep
calling yourself a bunch?
>> I'm pretty sure your mom called you the mon once.
>> Why are you calling yourself a bun? It's
not nice. Stop talking about your skin
self. Why? Can you show me £100?
>> Can you show me £100?
>> PJ, show me £5.
>> Show mate, you've been showing£55.
PJ, show me5. I showed you £5,000 and
you ran away.
>> No, you didn't.
>> We not pay that game again. I ran away fromility benefit.
>> You cannot afford to live by yourself.
People like myself pay taxp
on the street. You'd actually be home, >> bro.
But the thing
get more women than you. That's a fact.
>> People had more women than you. I've had
more women than you. You're a virgin.
And I've had more women than you. And
>> And I've had more women than you. And
you're still a virgin. We've never seen
you with a woman. We've never heard you
with a woman. We see me with a woman.
We've seen me with a woman. But we've
never seen you with a woman because
you're still a virgin. You're a woman. You respect
because you're still a virgin.
>> Because you're still a virgin. You are
lonely. You are lonely. And you ran away
from DJ High School.
>> You are Mr. Lonely. Mr. Lon that ran
away from Pat. Can we just Can we just
say right? Can we just say about how you
ran away from Pat Mustard? You little bully victim.
>> You're almost crying.
>> How did you let that man bully you? Are
you Irish? Are you Irish? Really?
>> Go here because I can't just set up. No,
I'm right. Run away, little [ __ ] Do as
I say, boy. Run away like you run away
from Pat Mustard.
>> Run away like you run away from Pat.
Do as you're told. Do as all the nons
as you're told, single boy that ran
away. You have a very, very small
chance. All right.
>> Yeah. Well, you're a single virgin. Who
cares what Virgin says again?
>> Byebye, mother. Bye-bye.
>> Yeah, run away, boy. Run away. Do as
you're told. But this guy apparently
bullies me, yet he keeps running away
from me. He keeps running away from me
when I keep stabbing an eye in him. And
he's saying that he's bullying me by
calling himself a m. Him calling himself
ugly is apparently him bullying me. Bro,
you're talking about yourself. If you
cut your camera on, you'll show everyone
your ugly face. Just like Bomb, you're
all fat, ugly people on here. We've seen
it time and time again with you fat,
ugly looking, depressed monsters, bomb,
[ __ ] Pat Mustard, or you know, loads
of other people. Graycat, you're all
fat, ugly, depressed, hopeless little
keyboard warriors. We've seen it time
and time and time again with you people.
Fat, ugly, skint, and depressed trying
to bring other people down. That's what
you do because your life's fat, ugly,
skint, hopeless. Bro, this guy ran away
for two [ __ ] years because of Pat
Mustard, where the guy's coming on here
saying that he bullies me. This Irish
little single mun is trying to say that
he bullies me. This Irish ugly little
clown that's never had a girlfriend is
trying to tell me that he bullies me in
his mommy's basement still a virgin
wanking into a [ __ ] sock every day.
Get out of here, bro.
And you notice how he talks over people
as well. Can I ask you a question? Why
has a M had more women than you then
since? Okay, you don't want to talk all
over people. Why is it that this M has
had more women than you then? Let me ask
you this question then. Right, you're
saying that I've Okay, let's let's let's
put this let's put the record straight,
right? You're saying that I moan and
wins or whatever. Why has a M had more
girls than you? Do you want me to put
all the videos back up again? All the
hotel videos, all the kissing videos.
Why has a M had more women than you?
That must mean you're extra [ __ ] ugly
then, isn't it? If a if an apparently a
ma how could a ma have had more women
than you? Someone that sits there and
complains and acts like an incel has had
more women than you. That says a lot
about you then, doesn't it, bro? That
says really a lot about you. You know?
Yeah. You [ __ ] stupid Northern Irish
little bully victim. Little skin
bastard. Yeah. And you know what? I've
got I've got a new name for this guy
now, bro. It's fantasy stories. Not
fantasy stories, fantasy stories. You
remember how many times he was trying to
say about he was going to go to
Manchester and he was going to meet Pat
Mustard. Mate, the guy is too skinn and
afraid to leave his beds. He's not going
anywhere, mate. Yeah, he is not going
anywhere. Fantasy stories is too scared
to go anywhere. That's his name now.
Fantasy stories. I was just thinking
about that. Pathetic, bro. Absolutely pathetic.
And yeah, I was I was asking on it. Who
the [ __ ] has a microwave vindaloo, bro?
Who goes to Iceland and have a microwave
vindaloo? Oh yeah, I know. Skint people.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah, sorry about that, bro.
M nearly crying, bro. I told you. Stop
calling yourself a M, bro. If I'm a M,
why is a M had more women than you, bro?
It just shows that you're talking about
yourself. You're trying to say that I'm
a M yet I've been with more women than
you, but I'm a Ma. But why has a M had
more women than you and you're still
lonely and a virgin? Answer that
question then. Nope. I haven't done any
bets. I don't have any plans today. So,
if I'm a MT, why is a MT had more girls
than you? It's a simple question. That
must mean you're ultra ugly and you're
the bun. You [ __ ] fantasy stories
Northern Irish little road. You know
what? You wouldn't last a day in London,
bro. You wouldn't last a day. You're
Northern Irish spasticated accent. You
would just get smashed up. You would You
honestly would get smashed up for
sounding like that, bro. You know that
ugly disabled voice and you ran away
from Pat Mustard. You got bullied off of
here by Pat Mustard and you still think
that you've won when you ran away from a
fat old man and no one says anything.
Like he bullied you. He called you out
and he made you leave YouTube like the
good little boy that you are. Stop it.
It's embarrassing now, bro. It's
embarrassing. If you walked around there
with that accent, you would get your ass
handed to you, bro. Irish people are not
strong. They're weaklings. They're
weaklings. Weak little [ __ ] skin
[ __ ] ugly disabled little leprechaorn
[ __ ] [ __ ] That's what they are.
Just like you, you [ __ ] ugly bastard.
Yeah, come to London anytime you want,
bro. I'll happily smash your face in.
But again, you would never show your
face because you're an ugly bastard.
Just like bomb. Just like all these
other people. You're fat, ugly, lonely
people. You're a bit like Red. You're a
bit like Reddit moderators. You know
that you got nothing. You know that
you're ugly. You know that your life's
losers. And that's why you come on here
trying to bring other people down to
your level. You're depressed, ugly,
lowife people. Am I lying, bro? No one's
getting blocked here. Am I lying about
what I'm saying about you? No, I'm not.
Fat, lonely, ugly people with no hope.
And that hits that hits a nerve because
what I'm saying is the truth. What I'm
saying about you people, I've got you
bang on the money. I know exactly what
you people are like on here, bro. Fat,
ugly, disabled, single, sexless, taking
your frustrations out on other people
that are better looking than you. We've
seen it all before. We've heard it all
before. We have seen it and we have
heard it all before. It's nothing new
here now, bro. You know,
if I was if I was in Ireland, I' I'd
meet you today, bro.
I'd meet you today. It's that accent,
bro. That [ __ ] disabled accent. It's so annoying.
You know, if I was in Ireland, bro, I'd
meet you today, bro. I'd meet you today.
I'd call you out today. You fantasy
stories. That's your name. Fantasy
stories. Not fantasy. Fantasy stories.
You're a fantasist. That's what you are.
A complete utter fantasist. You're not
about that life, mate. Just like your
little boyfriend L ain't about that
life. Why do you think he came to London
at 7:00 in the morning on a Sunday?
You're not about that life, mate. You're
not about that [ __ ] life.
You really, really aren't about that life.
Yeah. Just like that guy on the train
when he was giving it the mouth. I'd
love him to try and get my personal
space. Remember the last time I went out
drinking? I would have I would have
[ __ ] that guy up, bro. Next level.
When I was arguing with that woman on
the train and that Irish guy was like,
"Bro, that guy tried going anywhere in
my personal space. He got knocked the
[ __ ] out, bro.
[ __ ] the Irish, bro. They're weak.
[ __ ] weak. I don't know where this
reputation come from that they're
strong. They're not [ __ ] strong at
all. They're [ __ ] weaklings.
I'm going to go put a belt on in a bit." Anyways,
going to go for a walk.
Yeah, I'm about drinking today. Asylum. Nope.
No drinking for me, matey. I'm going to put Yeah. Nope.
Very, very, very long break. A break is
an understatement, bro. A very very very
very long break. I can't be asked with it anymore.
Same old women, same old [ __ ] same old [ __ ] people.
What's the point in going out, bro? What
is literally the point in going out?
They're all the same.
They all do the same things, act the
same way. Women are all the same, bro.
There's no point bothering with people
that are all the same. Yeah.
What's the point of bothering with
people that are all the same?
>> No, I could still do it.
I could still do it, but nah, they're
all the same.
We are not all the same, bro. So, you
don't need to you don't need to speak to
them. I got put off after last week. I
got led on by someone I didn't like yet again.
So, like I was saying yesterday, how
many times you have to keep giving these
people the benefit of the doubt. They're
clearly clearly all the same. So, I
don't know how many more times for how
many more years you have to keep trying
to find different women that don't
exist. It's a waste of it's a [ __ ]
waste of time. They are clearly all like
that. It's obvious that they're all the
same. I've proven it multiple times that
they're all the same and none of them
are decent. I don't know how many more
times I have to keep doing it.
They are generally generally all the
same. Generally I I know they're all the
same. As many as much as people try and
say they're not, they [ __ ] well are.
No, I'm not using escorts either. Nope.
No. I had a problem with an escort
yesterday uh the other day and I weren't
even really going to go see them. No, I
don't I'm not going to use escorts. I'll
just have nothing, bro. I don't give a [ __ ]
I'll just have nothing.
No, I don't even want escorts. I'll just have nothing.
Uh, long story, bro. But no, I won't go
for escorts. I'll just have nothing. I don't mind. No,
she's just being a [ __ ] She's just
being a [ __ ] I can't wait to get out of
this country, bro. Finally. I really
can't. [ __ ] women, weather, [ __ ]
people. It's so depressing being here,
bro. It really And it never changes. And
people always sit there and say to you,
"Oh, it changes. It changes." Nothing
ever changes. You could go out every
week, you'll still come across the same
women. It will never change. It will
never ever change. So, I don't know why
people sit there and still say, "Oh,
you'll meet someone." You never do. You
only meet the same women, the same
[ __ ] women everywhere you go with
the same attitude. Unless you're a pedophile
or you sell crack to kids, you're not
going to meet anyone.
Unless you're a pedophile that sells
crack to kids, no one's interested.
Simple. So, and it's not good for
anyone's mental health either. So,
why are you going out trying to find
someone that don't exist? It's a waste of time. Would
you not agree?
They love pedophiles as well. Yeah.
I don't know how people sit there and
say women aren't the same when they are.
I don't know why they say they're not
all the same when they literally are.
All the same [ __ ] trolling. And it
makes you miserable. I noticed my worst
when I was dealing with them. It It made
me miserable. It did. It made me
miserable. Despite all of these people
saying, "Oh, they're not all like that,
mate. There's good ones out there.
You'll find a good one." It made me
miserable. It did. It did. It really,
really, really did. It made me
miserable. Every single time you go out
again, you meet the same people with the
same attitude. You come across the same
[ __ ] men time and time and time
again. The same waiting around for
things. It's depressing. You're best off
doing nothing. You're literally just
best off doing nothing. That's the way I
see it, bro. And it's not healthy
nowadays. It's not depressing. It's just
toxic. Like that number that led me on
the other day. It's just toxic. And they
do it on purpose. And that's what was
winding me up yesterday, bro. Is that
you get these people that will sit there
and constantly keep making excuses for
them, right? When you know your
experiences with these [ __ ] you
know your experiences, right?
You know, you know your experiences with
them and they're still making excuses
for them. That's what was annoying me,
bro. That's the thing that was annoying me.
You're better off being a batty man. Why
does it always turn to gay jokes with
you people, right? You know, why why
trying to say how they they weren't
needing you on when they they were they
are. I don't know how many more messages
and how many more approaches you have to
put up and then you just end up feeling
like the boy who cried wolf. How about
you're better off just not bothering
with men or women? Why? Why is it always
the gay jokes with you people? Can I ask
that? How about you just don't like men
and you don't like women?
I just I mean that is a possibility. I
mean why does it always go to being gay?
I don't I genu genuine question. I'm I'm
I'm curious about why does it always go
to being gay? I never said I was going
to turn gay. When did I say I was I
never said I was going to turn gay. No,
I didn't. No, I [ __ ] didn't.
No, I [ __ ] did not.
So, that's that. I probably won't even
put a bet on today. I'll probably just
stay in bed.
Yeah, I'll probably just stay in bed to be honest.
I woke up in a bad mood as well because
of these [ __ ]
So, so yeah, I went out last Thursday.
That was the last time I went out.
No, I said I was going to go on Reddit
and pretend that I was gay to see that
if people would make excuses for men.
That's what I said. I said I was going
to pretend I was gay on Reddit to see if
these people was going to keep making
excuses for men like they do women.
That's what I said. Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no. But it's the women.
It's the bad experiences with women. It
gets you down. It gets you so down.
That's why I gave up with them. They're
no different. And and the thing and No,
no, no. What is annoying is feeling like
the boy who cried wolf. No matter what
you show, they keep completely ignore
it. It don't suit them. All because
they're women. So, what I actually said
was, I'm going to go on Reddit and
pretend I'm gay, right? And see if we
hear about, oh, men don't know you think
anything. Oh, uh, maybe he changed his
mind. Let's see if you hear all of these
excuses for men that they do women.
No. The answer is no.
That's how I feel like the boy cried
wolf. And it's very, very, very
annoying. Very, very, very, very [ __ ]
It's so horrible feeling like you're not
listened to and you ignored. My mom's
done it as well, right? I remember one
time I woke up, I think it might have
been a month ago, and there must have
sort of the thing where I had that
person going on on a wild goose chase,
right? The one that was being a [ __ ]
being passive aggressive, being a
[ __ ] right? And no matter what I
told her, I done it because of this
reason. completely ignored it. It was
like I was not even involved in the
conversation because anything that these
women do will completely get dismissed.
So there's no point. There's no point.
Any bad thing that they do, people just
ignore it and keep making excuses for
them time and time again, you know, time
and time again. And it got to the point
where I started raising my voice, right?
Because it's like anything they do, they
ignore it. any bad thing these women do,
they ignore it and keep making excuses
for them. And it's so [ __ ] annoying.
And I said to my mom as well, I don't
want to I I I don't want to Are you
listening to what I'm saying or you just
completely dismissing what I'm saying as
usual? I'm trying to tell you what
happened between me and my mom and you
just keep ignoring it as usual.
Do you know what? I think I need to go
to the doctors and see um about my
voice, right? to see if my voice is
properly because people seem to keep
dismissing everything I'm saying. So, I
don't understand. Everything I'm saying
seems to keep getting dismissed. So,
maybe maybe my voice is on mute or
something, Grezy, because there must be a problem,
you know, and it got so annoying. People
keep defending them and dismissing and
dismissing and dismissing, you know?
It's horrible, bro. It's [ __ ]
horrible. A woman could literally rape a
child and they'd be like, "Nah, the baby
had a bad personality." I'm I'm
convinced they do anything to defend
women, bro. They [ __ ] well do. They
[ __ ] well do. And then the and the
whole the whole conversation, right, the
whole way through the conversation,
you're thinking to yourself, "Hold on,
you've put messages up, you've put
approaches up. Why are we still having this conversation?"
I'm thinking, "What? What? Why are we
still having this convo?
You put approaches up and you've put
messages up. Why are we still having this conversation?
You know what I'm saying? What you're
thinking, what the [ __ ] Why? Why are we
still even having a conversation?
Dismissing people's struggles as usual.
Yep. Well, they would get away with it.
That's what I'm saying. They get away
with everything. They seem to get away
with everything else. So, so yeah,
but I won't be going out today.
Speak to a professional who can help. No
thoughts on the women leading me on.
Nah, I'm the one that needs professional
help. That's very manipulative, isn't
it? I need professional help. So, you
kind of dis just just dismissed
everything I said then. So, you just
completely dismissed everything I've
said. Thank you for that. It wouldn't be
the first time I'm telling you about
women that's [ __ ] me over time and
time again, and you're telling me to get
professional help. I give up. I
completely completely give up.
I I give up. I completely give up, bro.
No. Nothing happened. I'm still pissed
off from yesterday, bro.
So, women have [ __ ] me over, but I'm
the one that needs to get professional help.
I wonder if they were telling me they
tell me to get professional help if I was gay.
We still need to do this experiment.
So, women have [ __ ] me over and done
me wrong, but I should get professional help.
Doesn't really make a lot of sense to
me. Seems like a a a way to victimize
women again. All of these things seems
to be ways to victimize women. You understand,
right? But I don't need professional
help. I'm trying to tell you about my
experiences with women that you keep dismissing.
This is so annoying that you keep
ignoring, bro. I I swear to God, later
today, bro. Later today, I'm done with
this now. We're not talking about this
anymore. There's no point to this. You
just keep dismissing everything. So
there's no point. You're you keep Why
are you telling someone to get
professional help when I've told you
women have done me over and you've had
no opinions on that? Why do they make
excuses for these women? I wish somebody
could could could could please answer me
why they constantly keep making excuses
for women. Is there is there a website,
Grey, that I could find on and and get
the answers to this?
cuz they dismiss everything that they do.
Yes. Right. But I don't need
professional help. Why are you talking
about professional help?
You know, we're just going around. This
is what makes me miserable, Grezy. This
right here is what makes me miserable.
This is what makes me down. This same
conversation over and over and over and
over and over again with the women.
That's what's getting me down, bro. You
know, that's what gets me down. You know
the same conversation getting dismissed.
That's what's getting me down, bro. You
know, I was fine before yesterday. I was
fine before yesterday, bro. Completely
fine. Yeah, I was completely fine, bro.
Any thoughts on the women leading me on?
Nope. Completely dismissed that.
See, you keep dismissing and ignoring
all the bad things they do. Why do you
keep doing that? I'm asking you why are
you doing something over and over again
and you keep ignoring me? Do you know
what I'm saying? You keep ignoring me
over and over. Why do you keep making
excuses for them? I don't know how many
times I've asked the same question. Why
do you keep dismissing my struggles? Why
do you keep making excuses for them? How
many times Gy did I ask this question
yesterday? How many times did I ask this
question yesterday and not one person answered it?
Why do you keep defending them just cuz
they're women? It's a simple question.
I I've asked my mom this question. Got
dismissed. Moved on to YouTube. Got
Have I not got a voice or something? Can
you hear me properly? Am I muted or something?
You know, you constantly make excuses
for them and victimize them. Why? I'm
asking you why you're doing it.
You know, I'm asking you why you're
doing it. Why do you keep making
excuses? How many excuses did we hear
yesterday on the podcast, Grezy? Oh,
they might have changed their mind. Bro,
did you see all of the little simps?
No, it isn't. No, it isn't. No, it
isn't. No, it isn't. Okay, then. So, if
it's everything that I have said is
justified. Everything I've said about
these women are justified.
Yeah. Everything that I have said is
justified. It doesn't mean I need
professional help. It's me retaliating
to them. Anyways, we're moving on now.
Anyways, so I'm not getting into this
conversation anymore. Anyways, go
dismiss some of the struggles on another channel. You know,
yeah. Did you see all of the little
simps? Did you see all of the little
You know, you're lucky I didn't beat
that [ __ ] delivery driver up
yesterday. I was going to smash his face
in, bro. An innocent person cuz you
don't know how annoying it is. You don't
know how annoying it is, bro. Keep being
ignored, being dismissed. It's [ __ ] annoying.
Oh, did you like that? Oh, Lex. Oh. Oh.
Hey, babe. Well, did you like that? Yeah.
Well, you are dismissing my struggles
because you because you wouldn't be
telling somebody to get professional
help. If you was telling people if you
weren't dismissing people's struggles,
you wouldn't be telling people to get
professional help because you would
realize that all of the things that
they've said is justified. So, you are
dismissing struggles. You really, really
are. How many videos have I put up on
this channel of approaches? How many
messages have I put up on this channel?
Yet, you go on like you've not been
shown anything. But you're not
dismissing people's struggles. Yes, you
are. Yes, you [ __ ] are.
You definitely definitely are dismissing
people's struggles. How many messages
have I put up? How many approaches have
I put up? So, how are you not dismissing
struggles? Of course, you're dismissing people's struggles.
It's not about luck. It's not about
luck. It's them. They're the problem. They're [ __ ]
It's them. They're the problem. And it's
not about having no luck. It's what
they've done. Again, dismissed
everything. Right, we're moving on now.
We're done with this conversation. We're
going around and around in circles.
Anyways, Grez, I think we've said what
we've said now. We just keep going round
and round and round and round and round
in circles. And I don't want to ruin
another day. We're just having the same
argument over and over and over and over
again. Have it in your head. Women are
perfect. Women don't do no wrong. You're
right. I agree with you. I'm a
28-year-old that has no life. Never met
a woman. I don't know what I'm talking
about. Are you happy? Because it seems
like you're not you're never going to be
happy until you bully someone into
agreeing to you into agreeing right into
agreeing what you want. It's like you
want to bully someone into thinking your
way, which is not good because every
single time you go out and you meet
women, they are all the same.
So, it's clear you want someone to agree
with you cuz we keep having the same
conversation over and over and over and
over again. You know, you're talking
about people having no luck and
whatever, mate. Right. We're having the
same argument. We're ending it now
anyways. So, we're not ruining another
day of this. We're not I'm not ruining
another day, bro.
You want to keep thinking women are
perfect and innocent. Okay, whatever.
I'm not interested, bro. I don't care.
That is a lot of [ __ ] I've shown on my
channel with these approaches and no one
seems to be bothered by it. No one seems
to be phased by it,
but they say they don't dismiss people's struggles. Okay.
I wanted to beat that delivery driver up yesterday, Grezy.
I really wanted to smash his face in
some random person, bro, cuz that's how
they get you on here, bro. That's
literally how they get you on here when
they keep dismissing people's struggles
time and time and time and time again.
It's very, very annoying. And you laugh
at it, bro. But when it happens to you,
you'll know how annoying it is.
You know, they literally dismiss
everything that they do. They it they
generally generally do. They generally
generally do it.
They generally generally miss dismiss people's struggles.
Yeah. I don't think I'm going to put a football on.
No, I was going to put 20 times on a
football, but I can't be asked.
Wasn't I fine yesterday, Greasy, before
I joined that podcast?
You know, it's not good for your mental
health. It's really It's not healthy.
It's really, really, really, really not healthy, bro.
I gave up for a reason, you know? I gave
up for a [ __ ] reason,
you know? That's that's that. You know,
it's not healthy because they're
dismissing your struggles. And when
someone has got the experiences that
I've had and you keep going back and
forth, it's not good. You know,
you know how many more years you have to
keep giving these women the benefit of
the doubt? Another question has still
not been answered. Still not been
>> Yeah, man. It's mad. Yeah. Madness, bro.
Yeah, Jamie Thompson still stalking me
again. This is what I mean, bro. They're
[ __ ] mongos on here, bro.
Proper proper stalkers. Proper proper autistic stalkers.
Why does this fat guy keep stalking me?
Does he want my bum or something?
Why does this fat Why does this fat
weirdo keep stalking me, bro?
This fat little bastard.
This fat ugly stalker. Why is he so
obsessed with me? He's He's worse than
Pat Mustard. This [ __ ] fat ugly gaylord.
Why does this fat stalker keep stalking
me every day? [ __ ] wife my [ __ ] ass.
Stand all stalking little fat ugly low
life. low life, ugly bully victims. This
is what I mean with these people. It's
like what I said, bro. They take it out
on you cuz you're better looking than
them. It's like what Ronald Pump said,
you're better looking than them. You got
more money than them and it kills them.
It's true. They spend how many hours of
the day, right, stalking someone on
YouTube that they don't know. It's
having better looks than these people.
What it is with these people, right,
like Jamie Thompson, they're fat, ugly,
smelly little rats that don't leave
their house. They're failures. They come
across someone that's younger, better
looking, they look up to them. Oh, we
want to bring this person down to our
level. That's what they do. It's funny,
but it's true. They hate any They go for
the better looking, the younger than
them because they hate that you're
better than them. That's where all of
this stalking comes from. Stalking non-stop.
And they've also pretended to be women
as well. They've also pretended to be women.
Yeah, they've actually this person
grieves you has actually pretended to be a woman.
So you message them. They've actually
pretended to be a woman. So you message
them. This guy ain't got no wife. He's
fat, ugly, and disabled. I would go as
far saying this guy's worse than Pat
Mustard. Fat, ugly autism. That's why
it's the same atmosphere. They pretended
to be a woman as well, Grezy.
That's autism. They ain't got no wife.
Don't believe any of what they say,
mate. They ain't got none of these
things. Trust me, they [ __ ] well don't.
You [ __ ] fat ugly bastard.
>> Why do you keep stalking me, you fat ugly bastard?
>> Um, it's pretty fun. Why are you
>> Why Why do you keep Why do you keep
stalking me, you fat?
>> Why do you keep Why do you keep I don't
I don't want to [ __ ] you. I don't want
you. So, can you stop stalking me, please?
>> If I didn't have a wife. Explain that.
>> You don't have a wife. You don't have a
wife. You little stalker. Mate, tell
everyone on YouTube what you do all day
every day. You stalking fat ugly mess.
>> I mean, I'm
>> You ain't got a wife, mate. You ain't
got a wife, mate. Listen, do you want me
to show everyone the miss calls?
>> Can you show them the email I sent you
yesterday? It clearly That's a document from the
>> I don't check your emails, you fat, ugly spat.
>> You do check my emails,
>> you [ __ ] No, I [ __ ] don't. You're
a weirdo. Listen. Listen. It's not my
fault. It's not my fault. I'm better
looking than you.
>> You see my new life in America that you
>> No, I don't go on your channel.
Actually, I don't go on your channel. >> Emails.
>> I don't go on your channel. I don't go
>> Everything I have that you will never
have what a fat a fat belly and an ugly face.
>> Wait, hold on. Hold on. You've got
everything. One second. One. You've got
everything that I want.
Half your age.
>> Okay. Okay. You've got everything that I
want. Yet you stalk me all day on YouTube.
>> Yeah, I know. I got No, no, no. I do it
while I'm getting paid for work.
>> Put your camera on my work.
>> Put your camera on. Put your camera on.
>> Why do you want to see my camera?
You're fat, old, and ugly. I assure you
I don't want anything that you want. I
assure you I don't want to be fat and
ugly like you. I don't want to be fat
and ugly like you. I assure you that.
>> Get a woman.
>> You can't get a woman. You can't get a
woman. That's why you're stalking me,
you fat bastard. You're sat on YouTube
stalking me every day. You fat bastard.
You lonely fat bastard. Little freak.
Yeah, you fat ugly bastard.
>> Go on. I I've sent you everything from
my cars to my [ __ ]
>> No. No. But you sit on YouTube all day
stalking me. Something's not right,
Jamie. Something's not right,
>> Jamie. Something's not right here. It's
like with the virgin. It's like with
nonslegs. You have everything that I
want, but you waste your life on me.
It's not making sense.
>> Getting paid.
>> It's not making sense.
>> I have built bots that have [ __ ] with your life.
>> No. No, it hasn't, mate. What you've
done? I've laughed at it the whole time.
You've not [ __ ] with my head. You've
>> How does it feel that I'm younger and
better looking than you? I bet it kills
you, doesn't it?
>> How does it feel that I'm better looking
than you and younger
>> and I'm not overweight? How does that
feel, Jamie? How's that feel?
>> You're a breath. It brings
>> How does that feel that I'm better
looking than you? from all your videos.
There's no escape.
>> Yeah. Okay. So, how does it feel that
I'm better looking? How does it feel
that I'm better looking than you or
younger than you? I bet that must hurt
you. I bet that hurt you.
>> Like the elephant man and I would still
have more luck with women than you.
>> But you don't know. But you don't have
luck with women. But you don't. But you
don't. You're still a virgin. But you
don't know because someone that's
happily married doesn't stalk people day
on YouTube. So it doesn't add up. Jamie,
you never had a relationship.
>> Just like Just like the virgin had a relationship between
>> Just like the virgin. Just like the skin
>> Are you going to let people talk
>> anything about that? You
>> right. Right. Okay. You and the skinn
virgin have got everything I want, but
you spend all your life STALKING ME.
IT'S NOT ADDING UP. SOMETHING'S not
adding up. Jamie, come on. You claim to
be smart. You claim to be a married man,
but you're stalking me every day.
Something's not adding up. Something is
>> Something is not adding up here.
>> And these bots are going to keep saying
>> they're not bots. They're you. They're >> Videos.
>> Hey, I wonder if Let me Let me tell you
something as well. Um I've turned my SIM
card off, by the way. So, you're not
going to get through to me that way.
>> Get your number again. That's
>> You will never get No, you won't. No,
>> All I have to do is It's funny. I love
it how obsessed you You won't get my
number again. What's my number?
What is it?
>> Listen, you're so Do you remember when
you tried getting me to go to Scotland?
Mate, I'm too intelligent for you. You
can't even go there. >> Funny.
>> You can't even go there with someone
like me. You can't even go there with
someone like me. You can't even troll. You fat.
>> What the [ __ ] You were talking.
>> You [ __ ] fat slob.
>> Two days and you were like,
>> "See you later. Bye-bye now.
Bye-bye now." Yeah.
[ __ ] fat slob.
What a [ __ ] fat slob, bro.
You fat Yeah, he's a fat bastard, bro. Fat bastard.
No life in it. He's got He's got
everything I want. Yeah, he's the one
stalking me all day on YouTube. Make it
make sense. Make it make [ __ ] sense.
Pretending that you're married.
Yeah. Okay, bro. [ __ ] idiot. [ __ ] stalker.
Proper proper stalker in it. Proper
stalker. That [ __ ] Proper proper
stalker. I got owned. No, I didn't,
mate. But guess what, Kayie? You got
owned at birth. You fat ugly bastard.
I got owned. How did I get owned?
You [ __ ] fat ugly bastard. [ __ ] off,
man. You little slag.
You [ __ ] ugly bastard.
[ __ ] off, mate. Bye-bye.
How did I get owned, bro? No one owns
me, mate. No one owns me.
How did that fat clown me? What? By
being a [ __ ] stalker. Ah, bro. How's
that owning me? Huh? By being a little stalker.
Fat ugly bastard.
But you ain't got my number now anyway.
So there's no way there's no way you can
do anything. And I don't go on your
virgin channel. And like I said, it's a
no virgin zone. I don't go on Nons's
channel cuz he's a virgin. I don't go on
your channel. I don't go on virgin channels.
That's that's a policy that I have.
Sorry. It's a no virgin zone.
I don't have virgins on here. I don't go
on virgin channels. I don't make the
rules, mate. I don't make the [ __ ] you know. Yep.
Sad little stalker.
[ __ ] mad. You got to laugh for it, Grezy.
Sad little stalker. I clearly have
something that these people want.
Clearly, bro. Clearly, mate. I've
clearly got something that they want,
Tory. To have these these many people
dedicated to you. I mean, you got to be
doing something right. You got to be
doing something right, bro. To have
these people obsessed with you the way
they are. And they don't even know you
as well. I mean, you got to be doing
something right to be fair. So, big up me, bro.
Do you remember yesterday you was like,
"Oh, it's the same website you can watch
the Sidemen on.
It's the same website you can watch the Sidemen on."
Yeah, they're jealous of something.
Definitely jealous of something because
for people to put all of this time into
someone they're better than, it doesn't
really make sense, does it? I mean,
they're obviously jealous of something,
whatever that is, because they wouldn't
spend all this time doing this. Probably
cuz you're younger and better looking
than them. Probably
>> younger, better looking. You can go out
and do what you want. Um, so that's what
it comes to with these people. They're
jealous of Definitely jealous of
something considering they like actual nons.
Yeah, 100% bro. 100%. Yeah.
People on Reddit say that you're going
to meet someone.
Well, I'm going to need to do this
football b at some point. I think I'm
going to do I think I'm going to do six teams.
That's a bit much though, is it?
Six teams. [ __ ] hell. Imagine that. Greasy.
I'm going to do
maybe five teams.
I think six is a bit I need like five
both teams to score.
What do you think of that one, Captain Greavvesy?
Maybe or four. What do you think, Captain?
Four, five or six teams.
I think five in it. Yeah.
Stick like 30 pound on four teams in it.
Well, I'm going to go in it cuz I need
to do this football bit, mate.
Well, I just put 30 pound on four teams in it. >> Yeah.
Why did you li Why did you say that's
the same website you can watch the
Sideman on yesterday when I was arguing
with that stupid Northern [ __ ]
I'm going to do a lush. I'm just going
to do a both teams to score. I'm going
to do both score, no draw cuz that's
they're harder in it.
They're [ __ ] harder. They are. What's
the date today?
It's my birthday in a couple of months. Grievy,
it's my birthday in 3 months. What you buy me?
Yeah, it's my birthday in February.
What are you buying me?
What are you buying me, son?
>> So, what? £30 on four teams? Yeah.
What do you think about that? 30 on four teams.
I think that's a good amount now.
Is that a good amount? 30 on four teams.
Yeah, I'm going to do 30 on four. Yeah.
Should be a good return, isn't it?
Well, I'm going to go and I'll be back
late today. 20 seconds. 20 seconds.
>> Oh my god, it looks [ __ ] minging out there, bro.
It looks [ __ ] minging out there.
It looks minging out there, Greavves.
They absolutely minging.
Okay, I'll see you in a bit. Anyways,
got do this [ __ ] football bet.