No, there's no point
be going on my other channel as well.
Anyways, 10 minutes to score and they
couldn't even score a goal. [ __ ] off.
[ __ ] isn't it?
Absolutely [ __ ] Even when you lower
the stake, exactly the same effect.
Exactly the same effect. Well, at least
we've done big stakes and low stakes.
Yep. [ __ ] Absolutely [ __ ] They
had 11 minutes to [ __ ] score and they
didn't score a goal. It's [ __ ]
bollocks, mate. And they both had
[ __ ] red cards as well. [ __ ] off, you
[ __ ] silly little [ __ ] That's £50 as
well, by the way. Huh?
But gamble money you can afford to lose,
they say. Gamble money that you can af
you can afford to lose, they say.
M so they say. So secular not says what?
£50. £50, bro. Really? [ __ ] off you
silly little [ __ ]
[ __ ] off you silly dirty little stinky little [ __ ]
You suck my [ __ ] big fat dick. You
silly [ __ ] [ __ ] off. [ __ ] annoying
it is, bro. So annoying. It's so
I don't know how anyone else's bets
went. I feel like going outside and
smashing someone's head in again, bro. I
swear to God. It's [ __ ] annoying, is it?
It is annoying as [ __ ]
I want to go outside and just [ __ ] do
something in. Bro, you don't even
understand. And I want to really hurt someone.
It's not even a joke.
It is so annoying.
So [ __ ] annoying. It's got nothing to
[clears throat] do with money that you
can afford to lose or you can't afford
to lose. It's so [ __ ] annoying. End
of story. End of story. Annoying.
[ __ ] suck my dick, silly [ __ ]
I feel like really hurting someone, bro.
You don't understand. Really really hurting someone.
Like seriously hurting someone.
We reduced the steak as well. Still
annoying. It's still annoying.
It's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
It puts you off your food and
everything. I won't even eat again today
now. I don't think. No, I don't think
I'll even eat again today now.
It puts you off your food and
everything. It puts you off wanting to do anything.
That's the whole um that's the whole um
thing about it, is it? Um
what's it called? Yeah.
It puts you off wanting to do anything.
It isolates you. That's what it does.
Well, it does me anyways. I don't know
about anyone else.
And that was £50. And it wasn't even
roulette. That's not a good sign to be honest.
No, that's not a good sign to be honest.
That's really bad, bro.
What's this comment say? One second. Wait
one second. Hold on. What is this comment?
How he thinks he can comment on anyone
is beyond me. Look at the state of it.
Okay, Autumn, like I told you yesterday,
same thing, right? Put a picture up without filters.
Yeah. Look at the state of it. What?
Because I haven't been to the barbers
for a while. Okay. Put a picture up
without filters and then come back to me
and tell me how I can't say this and how
I can't say that about that. You may
listen. And you're [ __ ] stinking.
Yeah. About how I can think I can
comment. I can comment on your
appearance. Yeah. You're [ __ ]
stinking. You're an ugly fat [ __ ] that
has to use filters.
Yeah. You're an ugly fat [ __ ] that uses
filters. So I can I can comment on your
you as much as I want. Yeah. You are
ugly. Red Star is ugly. Yeah. You all
little [ __ ] [ __ ] little keyboard
warriors. You know, I was thinking about
this as well before the football. I'm
coming off of this. Um, I'm coming off
of this place, bro. I really, really,
really had to think about it. I'm coming
off. It's the same atmosphere every day.
The same repeating people, low life
stalking people. I'm coming off of it.
And also, I don't like the fact that
like my mom watches my channel as well.
It's like kind of weird. So, I'll be
coming off this and I'll be going back
to my other channel. Simple as that.
Leave these little lowife little nerds,
right, that create the same atmosphere
every day because they've got autism to
it, basically. Yeah. [snorts]
Look at the state of you, Autumn, you
[ __ ] fat [ __ ] Yeah. Go and put a
picture up without filters, you [ __ ]
fat little [ __ ]
You fat, stupid, slaggy little [ __ ]
hoe. [ __ ] off, man. [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
Sat here arguing with people I don't
know. [ __ ] little low lives. I'm
coming off this [ __ ] tomorrow, bro. So
don't say I didn't warn you that. Yeah.
Yeah. The football bet didn't win UK asylum.
All these little fat, ugly, depressed
people that ain't got no life trying to
talk about other people. Really, bro?
This is what is just all this community
is is a bunch of fat, ugly losers that
ain't got no life trying to talk about other people.
Fat, ugly, spasticated people that talk
about other people that they don't know
that's got a better life than them, bro.
Come on. Really? Look at these people,
man. You know, and I'll prove it again
tomorrow when I'm off here and these
people are still on YouTube as usual.
You'll be the judge because they ain't
got a lie. Simple. I started
one second. Someone missing.
Yeah, nobody leaves, bro. I'll come off.
This is what I mean with these people,
bro. They're just fat, ugly, low lives.
That's why you have to come off this
[ __ ] for a couple of weeks. All it is
with these people in this community,
they're fat, ugly, and bullied. Listen
to what I'm saying, right? These people
like Ricky Millington, all of these
people, they're very fat, very ugly,
depressed people. Don't even leave their
house, bro. Trust me, I know about these
people. They're fat, ugly, skinned
people that ain't got hope in life. So,
they see someone younger, better
looking, and they and it kills them.
That's where all of this stuff comes
from. That's where all of this comes.
They're fat, ugly, hopeless people. And
that's what they are, bro. Laugh off you
want, but I'm I'm right, bro. Every
everything I've said about these people
on here, these fat, ugly, depressed
nerds that can't get off of YouTube.
Everything I've said is right about
them, bro. They're big fat ugly losers
trying to bring other people down to
their level. Jamie Thompson, Ricky
Milindon, little virgins. Most of them
are virgins. Yeah, they're no hope fat
ugly bastards. That's what they are.
Yeah, remember I said that as well when
I'm not on here tomorrow cuz I know
everything. These people ain't got no
life. These people ain't got no money.
It's so obvious for what they do on here
every day. It's so obvious. They're sad,
pathetic, [clears throat] ugly, jealous
people with no life. Yeah. Get that
tattooed on you, bro. Yeah, I know. I
know this, bro. Yeah, it's the truth
what I'm saying.
They're fat, ugly, jealous little nerds.
Think about it, bro. They're obsessed
with people that they don't even know. Yeah.
Yeah. They're jealous of people that
they don't even know, bro. The scenes on
it. People that they don't even know.
I feel like going out and killing someone, bro.
I'm going back on my other channel
anyways. No one knows about it.
Get away from these fat, ugly nerds for
a couple of weeks. Yeah,
bro. They hate because they're fat,
ugly, jealous losers. Bedbound,
depressed benefit bums. do not
understand. They're fat, ugly people
that don't fit into society. Do you not
understand, bro? Yeah.
They they pick on a guy that's better
looking. Oh, wow. Someone they go for
the better looking younger. Anyone
that's better looking than them. Have
you noticed how everyone gravitates
towards me, Siri? You will see, right?
You will see. Yeah. That they gravitate towards me
because you're better looking than them.
It's like what Ronald Pump said, you've
got something that they want. People do
not spend all day on the internet on
people that they're better than. Nobody
does it. You've got something that they
want that they're jealous of. They can
call you all the names under the [ __ ]
sun, but they wouldn't be stalking you
every day if they were truly better than
you. Do not understand. Yeah. They are
jealous of something big time. Yeah.
Maybe you're too disabled to understand
this. and you know whatever. But yeah,
younger than them, better looking than
them, more money than them, better life
than them, more confidence than them. I
mean, that's and it kills them because
they're fat, ugly people that ain't got
no life. Simple. Every everyone knows
it, you know? So,
yeah, I feel like going outside and
[ __ ] [ __ ] just stabbing someone,
bro. It's not even funny.
And it's not about the money. It was
£50. See, it's never about the money. I
knew it, bro. I knew it was never about
the money. And this is football, by the
way. This is football, by the way.
Football. Football. It's annoying.
Yeah. Which is what I just said to my
mom. It's [ __ ] annoying, bro. You know,
that's why I stopped. Truth be told. You
know when you ask people that, oh, why
don't you play Fishing Frenzy anymore?
Yeah. I done a bet on a community post
like uh on a community why don't you
like bet anymore and stuff because I'd
end up killing someone like in the end
bro so it's not it's not worth it for me
I would end up killing someone that's
why I stopped that's one of the reason
what like you say oh you don't do any
gambling videos and what anymore why do
you think bro you know so anyways Yeah,
it's bad, is it, bro? Bad.
They had like 11 minutes to score as
well. Nothing. Absolutely nothing.
I probably just nipped to the shop to be honest.
I care. I care because I don't like
losing. So I care. I care because I
don't like losing. I don't like losing.
Simple as that. So I care.
I'll probably just nip to the shop to be
honest and get like some chicken or
something something like that. Um
it's on my community post if you want to see it.
So I'll be I'll be coming off this
anyways. I'll be going on my other
channel where there's content.
I don't like these little nerds, these
little disabled nerds on here as well.
No, it was free.
You can look it up if you want. It's on
the on the channel. Yeah,
no, it's not going to be chicken. It's
got to be tandoori, chicken, and well,
what else am I supposed to [ __ ] get?
I could get Chinese, but I don't
I could get Chinese. I don't know, bro.
Yeah, I don't cook the rice, though.
That's made me want to kill someone, bro.
Could you imagine you was out drinking
waiting for like the scars to come in?
You'd end up [ __ ] glassing some
prick. You'd end up glassing some prick.
I would end up glassing some [ __ ] with
like a Guinness glass. Yeah, I probably
would end up glassing someone.
I don't know. Maybe the alcohol would
calm me down a bit. Maybe. So
depressing stuff in it, bro. Depressing. depressing stuff,
but it's a form of entertainment. So they say,
the only reason I'm not doing anything
is cuz this is my house, bro. Otherwise,
I probably would smash up the whole
house to be honest if it was my house.
Not my house, though. So that's that.
Yeah, I feel like smashing up the whole
house, bro. But if it was my house, I
would have. You saw what I used to do
with the mugs and [ __ ] because it's
annoying, bro. It's [ __ ] annoying,
is it? It's so annoying. [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
>> Well, duh. It's not my house. So,
>> if it was my house, mate, you would know about it.
>> Yeah. You don't need to be broke or lose
a lot of money for it to affect you.
Not at all.
Yeah. You've already said this before
and you're the only one that thinks that you nerd.
I don't give a [ __ ] about the neighbor.
I'm not scared of the neighbor. I'm not
scared of no one. And the only reason I
didn't do anything is because it's my
mom's house. Believe you me, I'm not
scared of anyone, mate.
But we won't get to that silly point in
this argument again cuz even when you're
shown wrong, you still make up stuff. So
we won't get into that again. Part This
is part of it being an autistic
community because it's full of disabled
nerds that ain't got a life. Disabled. Yep.
Right. Let's have a look on what I can eat today.
the [ __ ] it was about, mate. I'm not
scared of no [ __ ]
You would know if you know the
circumstances, you would know that. But
why? Whatever. Anyways,
I feel like I've got like a demon in my
body, bro. Like a baby in my body when I
lose. It's like a demon in your body.
Like, it might sound funny to you. Hot
noodle for one, mate. Maybe you, but not
me. I'm getting a nice takeaway. Autistic community.
It's like a demon. It's like a baby
demon in your body
and it's like it controls your whole mind.
You might sound funny to you. I'd laugh
about it as well. It's so It's like you
it feel like you feel like you've been
raped. You actually feel so degraded.
You feel like you've been raped. I'm not
even saying it to be disgusting, bro.
No, I said I swear to God. It feels like
you you've been abused.
It sounds mad, but it's it's the truth. Yeah.
Form of entertainment. My ass.
My [ __ ] ass. Form of entertainment. Yep.
Feels like you've been raped.
That just sounds so mad. Um [sighs] Yep.
I got two out of three. Only need one
team to score. And as usual, they [ __ ] me over. Same old. No,
it wasn't Darlington. It was Spymore. No.
Madness, bro. [ __ ] madness.
Yep. Why it wasn't
So, same old. I'm coming off the
internet anyways tomorrow for a bit. I'm
I'm going on my Well, I'm going on my
other channel and [ __ ]
You need to take a break from these
little stalking little lowife nerds on
here. They've got no life, bro. [ __ ]
no life. They really have got no life.
These fat ugly muners on here, bro. Um,
you can order from that Brazilian.
No, I'm not doing that.
I don't know. Um something
get delude to be fair. [ __ ] it.
That's kind of [ __ ] savings up now cuz
I won't going to get another takeaway today.
Not [ __ ] obviously I have money but you
know what I mean. Yeah, I'm going to get takeaway. Um
I want to go to one I've not had before.
Is it going to be all right with me? Of
course it's going to be all right with
me. I ain't no [ __ ] skint virgin,
mate. I'm out of London.
I'm not no [ __ ] skin virgin, am I?
What? Where is this [ __ ]
go? Oh, look. There's a Madras.
There's a KMA, which is Virgin Boys.
And then there's a Vindeloo.
And obviously I get
the lamb one.
But this will be it. I need to start cooking my right. Um,
cheese and chili on strange.
I'm not going to get any n cheese and
chili now. Why is stuff with
green chili and coriander on top?
It doesn't have that. You don't have
cheese on there. One second. I'm going
to go somewhere else that does.
had enough of this [ __ ] I have had
enough of it, man. I had a [ __ ]
enough of it.
But there was one where if you spend a
load of money, you get a you get loads
of stuff for like £20 skin virgin. Um,
chicken ticker £810.
That's a bit pricey, is it?
No, they don't have window.
No. One second. Let me see if the office
is still on the one sec. Nope. One sec.
There was a deal where you could get
loads of stuff for like 20 pound.
It's gone now though. We got loads of
[ __ ] for like 20 last time. Um,
let me try this one.
Chicken ticker£4. Wait, but it needs to
have none. I fancy a non today. Uh,
a lot of these places don't have
Oh, here we go. Jeez, man.
So yeah, I'm gone tomorrow anyways for a little bit.
Yeah, I'll buy a tandoori chicken. That's it. Uh yeah,
hopefully this place has been um Yeah.
You can go watch um
you can watch the Skint Virgin, can't you?
Is that the only rice they've got is boiled rice.
They're all doing it.
30 pound cheese man chicken ticker tandoori chicken.
There we go.
Still lo it but it
I don't know.
Yeah, I ordered it anyways.
do that skin plonker.
I think so.
I think so, mate. Yeah.
Yeah, it cost £29.
stuff. I need to start eating in from tomorrow. Yeah,
that sucks, bro. That football bet is it?
That sucks. That [ __ ] football bet. [ __ ] bro.
It's bad, isn't it?
See, I don't regret not going for two because
um because of um
the odds are [ __ ] in it. The odds were
really [ __ ] on two. So Yep.
Dodge was [ __ ] anyway, so I wouldn't
have done too.
Start it up.
went on Red Star's channel, man. They're
just little virgins on there. They're
just little old freaky nerds that ain't
got a life.
I just went on there today, bro. First
time in like 3 weeks.
Know what I mean? They're
just [ __ ] old fat ugly [snorts]
nerds. Hopeless little nerds ain't got a
life. Think about it, bro. How many How
long has these people been on here doing
this now? These fat, ugly little nerds, depressed people. H answer Ready
No, it's that guy that ran away from Pat
Mustard. Do you remember?
They're such fat, ugly nerds. They
always twist stories. I told them about
the escort thing, right? And they just
twist stories. I got rejected. They
always twist stories. They're that
disabled on here. Proper proper disabled
people on here, bro. Jealous, disabled,
hopeless people that ain't got no life
at all. That's what they are.
So, you're going to have to find someone
else tomorrow cuz I won't be live for a
long time, bro. Yeah.
Nah, I don't like these little nerds on
here. These little stalking fat, ugly
nerds. They ain't got a life. I don't
like entertaining these little spastics.
I don't like the fact that my mom
watches my channel either.
Yeah, I just don't like it to be honest, bro. So,
and the whole thing yesterday was really
unhealthy as well. So, yeah,
I won't be out for a while. Nothing.
Imagine I put £500 on just slow and
[ __ ] Kitty Minister
would have been about maybe 1,400 maybe. Yeah.
Who's really going to do that? Come on.
I bought the [ __ ] uh Uggs as well.
165, went there. Yeah,
but if I went out today, I would have
spent more than 50 [ __ ] pound.
So that's the only reason why I done it. Obviously.
Yeah. And 30 is just a takeaway and I've
just bought a takeaway. So what's what's your point?
Right. And £29 is just a takeaway that
I've just bought. So what's your point?
Okay. We we don't see it the way that
you see it.
I don't see it the way you see it.
That applies to people that haven't got any money. Oh yeah.
So that's it. Well, duh.
But if you went out today, do you know
the way I always used to see it? If if
you went out today, you would have been
spending what with a haircut,
maybe 130, 150 just to deal with toxic
women and be depressed.
So that's one way to look at it.
Yeah, that's one way to look at it.
That's one good way to look at that.
You wanted to like feel better about You
wanted to feel better about it, you know? Yeah.
It's too [ __ ] cold to get my haircut.
I'm not talking about
Hurry up, food. I'm hungry as [ __ ] man.
I got a tandoori chicken. Poor lady.
I only got one rice, so there was no
point getting another rice.
Yeah. So, if you went out, you would
have spent more money just getting [ __ ]
from women. So
I think that's the only way you can
actually feel better
about it, you know.
So I think that's the only way, you know.
Yeah, I'm not anyways. I'm not
interested in it anymore.
Did anyone copy that bet, by the way?
It was a good bet.
I don't know how I used to do the
roulette mood swings. Oh my god. When I
used to play that [ __ ] Jesus Christ. No
wonder why I got kicked out. [ __ ]
hell, bro. I was so bad when I used to
play that roulette. Yeah.
Would you ever put £500 on a football bet? Indigo. Nah.
Would you? Nah.
No, you could do, but it's a risk. Get it. >> Yeah.
So many times I wish I had more on it.
You know, when I put like 120 on two
teams, I wish I had more in it.
I wish I had more when I
come on food. I'm starving
boy. Is virgin boy excited? Virgin boy.
is [ __ ] skin
is a [ __ ] [ __ ] mate. Yeah.
She's just a [ __ ] in it.
Oh, she's a [ __ ] isn't it? I mean, same
old. Is there anything else that you need to
to be aware of?
It's just the same old Yeah,
I thought Penny Spenny more was going to [ __ ] score.
This is such a nerdy autistic little
loser community, isn't it?
I mean, not people from my side, but
people from like the other side, Red
Star. They're proper proper life's
losers, isn't it? You look at these
people and you think, "R man, in their 40s,
no life, stable, predictum,
[ __ ] mad, is it?" You look at these
people and you think, "What the [ __ ]
Hurry up, food. I'm [ __ ] starving. Yeah.
Well, one team [ __ ] me up and I wanted
to go outside and kill people.
Yeah. Now I've just ordered an Indian.
Don't laugh. It's not funny, bro. It's annoying. Yeah.
[ __ ] bastard, bro.
They ain't got a life on here. These
little nerds, mate.
Yeah, they're such little nerds on this
community, in it, bro. They're such little
sad little nerds. Red Star [ __ ] sucks
nerdy fat ugly people, bro. Why be
wasting these time? Why are we even
wasting our time on it, bro?
Sad ugly people that ain't got a life. You know,
that one on Reddit didn't reply back
when I told her about herself. Feel
cowards in it. They're cowards. Toxic
Come on, I'm hungry. Why? Yeah, they
It's mad, bro. Is it?
Yeah, she blocked me on Reddit. She was
speaking to me on Instagram, then
blocked me randomly. Why do they do
that? Sey like switched the next day.
You'll speak to someone, right, and then
they'll be like,
you say good night, they say good night,
you say good night back, and then the
next day they completely switch.
It's like then they're just a narcissist.
I think it's where they're so fake and
phony, they can't keep it up for for for
that long. They can't keep it up for
very long because they're so fake. They
can only keep that act up for so long.
What do you think, Grezy? I think maybe
that's what that is
where they're so fake
that they can't keep it up for that
long, you know.
I don't want to talk about it anymore.
Anyways, I know why I brought it up.
They are all the same, bro. All the same.
Did you hear Oreo man? Did you hear Oreo
man, bro? All the same in it.
Can this food hurry up? I'm [ __ ] hungry, bro.
I just got a notification that Monty's gone live.
Even he don't go live anymore unless he
does games cuz it's just the same [ __ ]
with these little Mongols on here. These
sad effect people. Yeah.
I'm [ __ ] hungry, bro. Up.
I went by Vindeloo. So the virgin can't take skin virgin.
Yeah, bro. You skin [ __ ] virgin
He's still got USA. Is he on his
profile? What What an absolute virgin.
Such an absolute virgin.
Have you seen it? He's an absolute
virgin. I don't want to be too loud, bro.
What an absolute virgin. You know what
I'm like, bro. It
I'll say how I see it. An absolute virgin.
Do I have one? Virgin boy, bro. Virgin boy.
Come on. We're working on your order.
How long have you been [ __ ] saying
that, you bastards? I'm [ __ ] hungry.
>> So, I spent like 80 something pound
today just on food and a [ __ ] football bet. Imagine that. Yeah.
Oh, that virgin.
on that virgin.
>> I lost 130 on a football bet a couple
weeks ago, but I'm still well up.
Somewhere along the line I am.
I know that for a fact.
Imagine I didn't imagine I didn't buy
the UGs and I didn't do the football bet.
I'm going to have to go big on roulette
at some point, you know.
Bless you, Greavvesy, if you saved five
550 this month. Bless you.
Well, it looks like mine's going to be
closer to seven now because of that. It
was eight, but now it's seven.
I'm really hungry now. believe there.
Can't wait to eat this ticker. Shove it
down my throat.
What do you think of online roulette
s? Good old roulette, eh lady.
Laney. I bought lady chicken. She
doesn't know yet.
They're little nerds on here, bro.
Little nerds, aren't they?
Yeah, that's what they were saying to me
though. No, Grezy.
What's your opinion on that?
Yeah, they changed their mind. Yeah,
that's strange how they can change their
mind yet they haven't even met you. That
doesn't even make sense.
Cuz I can tell you I've never changed my mind.
I've never arranged to meet someone.
Yeah, I've ordered some food
Indian and I've ordered you a tandoori
chicken. Well, I've already Well, I've
already ordered you it.
Can you try and have some?
Well, I can't eat it.
I got a bindaloo and some naan. No, it's
for you. the fine. Why? Come back.
for years. Years in it. Oh, you're not
taking him back.
He's jealous, isn't it? Huh?
Who is it?
So, what did she say about the Uggs again?
>> Yeah, but how did Rena say that? Doesn't
make any sense. Who's got the problem
with the Uggs?
>> And what else does she say?
They don't like you having hugs. He
doesn't Why don't you like you having
the hugs? Why? Why are you not allowed >> What?
That's sick. Who said that? Yeah.
>> You need to tell me if she says
something about me cuz I'll go there and
I'll stop, bro. You know what I'm like.
You know what I'm like, mate. You know
what I'm like?
>> Couple of weeks ago, you remember? >> Yes. Yeah. >> Yeah.
I don't know.
But he me and >> Yeah.
I think uh you [ __ ] need to stop living
in the past. No, two stop.
This is what >> Yeah.
>> So, you need to stop talking about me
cuz I'll go to a gaff bro and start a
load of [ __ ] Charlie, he's not
>> I'll go to him and I'll do it in front
of him as well. I'll do it in front of
both of them. I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
I'm not scared of none of them. Just
leave me out of your [ __ ] You know what I'm saying?
Nothing from uh
>> is there I'm not speaking to Shining again though.
>> No, I'm not speaking to her again after No.
No. You don't pick and choose when stuff
when you want to create drama. It don't
work that way.
It's done in the old house as well. Yeah.
Yeah. I was going to some voice not the
other day cuz they were piss pissing me off.
So both of them shing and Yeah.
I don't know. Yeah.
What if you lose?
>> Yeah, but you might Yeah, but you might lose.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Why are you looking at me? >> Yeah. box there.
Sorry about that.
Where is this food, man?
Come on. Food. I'm [ __ ] hungry.
We need to stop this [ __ ] takeaway malarkey greasy.
We'll have no money left. We'll be like
the skin virgin.
We'll be like a skinton, wouldn't we?
Lads, we have a takeaway every day. He
said we had a takeaway every day. Where
we are skin plunker?
Where we are a virgin can. What do you
think we a virgin bastard?
Where is he?
Come on. I'm [ __ ] hungry, man.
Your skin plonker.
Do you ever grieve a copycat? Copycat statement. Copycat. [laughter]
You're funny as [ __ ] Was it a copycat statement? Little copycat.
You look yellow copycat.
You little copycat >> greasy.
So is it a copycat statement? Really?
Yeah. Sorry, I need to read what you
were saying about the change in your
mind. One second. Let me scroll up. If
you're talking a good amount of time for
a week plus, it's not a mistake. But
like I said, Lex is the type who will do
anything they can to defend women for
the sake of it. Yeah, I was. Yeah, of
course it's not a mistake. They do it on purpose.
How people don't just change their mind.
You little copycat.
Why did he say you're gay if you don't
find Cheryl Co attractive? Steven
Howard, that's so weird, bro. What a
weird thing to say,
Grey. That's a weird thing to say that is little copycat. Loser.
Absolute loser. He's ran through the
police again. The loser.
What a [ __ ] obsessed loser. Losers.
No one's getting a spanner.
Look at that. Autumn. How he thinks he
can comment on anyone is beyond me. Look
at the state of it. Yet you're the one. Uh
yeah. How he thinks he can come. This is
what I'm always saying. He projected
ugliness onto others. Uh, no, that's
you. You're the one sat on there every
day calling me big nose. Again,
projection virgin boy. Yet, he calls
everyone else a virgin. Um, yes, I'm
[clears throat] calling you a virgin
because you are a virgin along with bomb
along with other people. He's never had
a girlfriend. Yes, I have had a
girlfriend. I try again. Yeah. Calls me
a virgin. You are a virgin. and my
girlfriend disabled despite we've been
together for two years. Literally, he's
a weak projector.
This f this virgin's mad. I'm calling
you a virgin because you are a virgin
because I know you better than you know
your [ __ ] self.
That's me projecting. How could I be
projecting when I've proven I've had
sex? If I'm calling you a virgin because
you're the biggest virgin going, how is
that me projecting when I proved I've
had sex? Do you not understand the
definition of projection, virgin boy?
You're saying that I'm projecting by
calling you a virgin, but I've proved
I've had sex. So therefore, how could I be projecting? You know,
mate, you've got a disabled girlfriend.
It's not a flex. And guess what? You
don't have sex with her. You're the one
in your little shitty beds sit every day
stalking me cuz you're a low life little
virgin. And you know that I hit a nerve
every time I say this because it's the
truth. You're a lowife little skint
virgin. That's the whole point of this
whole YouTube thing. Just like Jamie
Thompson, you all skint lowife little
virgins and your YouTube activity gives
you away completely because if you
wasn't any of these things, you wouldn't
be on here doing this every day.
You wouldn't be on here doing this every
day if you wasn't.
You're the biggest virgin going. You're
the biggest virgin going. You're not
allowed to have sex with disabled people.
You can't have sex with disabled people.
You could have been together for 15
years, but you're still a virgin. You
know what I'm trying to say, mate?
Anyways, I'm done with this nonsy weirdo community
um for a bit. Anyways, so after today
I'll stay alive and that you know a bit whatever.
Still not out for delivery. What the [ __ ]
Yeah, this little skint virgin is is is
a is the ultimate projector.
This little skint virgin. You project
your ugliness onto me every day, virgin
boy. Go going around with your ugly rat
face trying to say that I've got a big
nose because you're the ugly [ __ ] that
could only attract disabled. That's you.
You virgin. That's virgin boy. That's you.
But there's no point arguing with these
people because yeah, they just want to
go around in circles cuz they're
insecure, ugly people that ain't got a life.
You've been with someone for 4 years,
but you've never had sex with them. And
I'm willing to put my life on it that
you're a virgin. I've explained how
you're a virgin a million times.
You know, mate,
you [ __ ] skinned virgin.
And all has to use filters to fat Oompa
Loompa. You can tell she's a fat
Ompompa. Look at her forehead, bro. Look
at her forehead.
when I tell her to come on my live. Look
at that forehead.
And lo and behold, the skin virgin is
always around the women. What is it with
that skinned virgin? Whenever [ __ ]
you know you see women around, you
always see the skin ugly rat face virgin.
I bet you'd like to see a [ __ ]
collaboration, wouldn't you, Steven
Howard? I'd be like, you absolute
virgin. And we can we can see you can
actually shout the shout the loudest.
Can't we mate?
Right. You know
I've I've never had a girlfriend. I've
been with more women than you, virgin
boy. I've been with more women than you.
You've never even had sex. You skin [ __ ]
You know, weak projector. That's you.
You're the one on your little virgin gay
little insecure virgin channel doing
videos about me because you're a little
low life. Your little jealous low life
is what I'm saying the tr not the truth
mate. The only one that's ugly is you.
Have you seen your ugly face? Now I
don't know right how you know you you
know you do this. You are the ugliest
thing I have ever seen in my life. You
look like a drenched rat. That's why you
come on here because you're jealous.
You're a jealous low-life little virgin.
That's what you are.
You know that you're ugly and you know
that I'm better looking than you and
that's why you do this whole YouTube
thing every day. Do you understand?
Because you're an ugly ugly bastard
virgin. That's what you are.
[ __ ] skin virgin.
You're You know what I'm saying? You You
know you're in a You're an insecure
little virgin. You tell me someone
that's in a happy relationship that does
this every day, mate. It proves that you
don't get sex. For someone to sit here
every day doing this, it proves that
they don't get sex. It proves that
they've got no life. Am I lying? Tell me
I'm lying, bro. I'm not lying.
I'm not projecting my ugliness. You are
a [ __ ] ugly [ __ ] Have you seen your
face? You rat looking bastard. You rat
looking bastard. You ugly bastard. How
many times do you come on here talking
about my [ __ ] nose? You [ __ ] rat
looking bastard with greasy hair. You
[ __ ] ugly [ __ ] Get a life.
You know, and I'm saying all of these
things to you right now. You little
skint low life. You little skint
narcissistic low life with no money and
no house that you own. [ __ ] get a
life. That's That's like one of the last
things I'm [ __ ] saying, bro.
Still [ __ ] still haven't still not
out for delivery, bruh. What the [ __ ]
It must be the chicken that's taking too long. Yeah.
Well, I agree with you. You know the
[ __ ] thing about this community, bro.
Yeah. It's the same atmosphere.
It's the same atmosphere, isn't it?
You know this is the same atmosphere we Yeah.
It says the average cost for a single
adult in the UK is £70 for two adults.
That's £40 a week. Yeah. What you Yo,
[ __ ] it up.
Damn, man. Was it? Oh, [ __ ] Yeah.
On it way. It's on its way. It's on its Grizzy.
It's on its way. It's on its way. It's
Yeah. I wonder what that skin plunk is
having footy today. Greavves.
When is that skin virgin going to get a
life? He's never going to pop that V
card if he keeps if he keeps on like this.
What do you think that boy?
He's never ever gonna get laid. He's
going to die virgin. He's going to die
virgin. He's not going to die. Skip
Oh, I love cheese and crack. I love
cheese crack. Uh cheese crackers with
Oh, cheese crackers with [ __ ] um
Yeah, cheese crackers with butter. Oh, I
used to eat that so much, bro, when I was younger.
Saying I've never had a girlfriend. I
have had a [ __ ] girlfriend, you
[ __ ] skint rat looking [ __ ] And I've
been with more women than you. You skint
rat looking [ __ ] virgin [ __ ]
You like that content, don't you, Greavvesy?
More than you. You [ __ ] skint [ __ ]
You like that content, Grezy?
You know, I might [ __ ] what what's
his name? Sid from [ __ ] Star Wars.
Had more girls than you. You skin rat
looking insecure little virgin. See your
channel, that little virgin channel that
you've got, it proves that you're
insecure and you're a unhappy
ugly little man. Yeah,
this skint plunker.
Do you like that? You skint plunker.
You [ __ ] skint flank.
you like that.
Need a skimp ploner.
Steven Howard. Who's the skimp plonka?
Who's the skint bloner? H.
When is that ugly rat looking bastard
going to get a life?
We're going to have a bet on this.
Stephen Albert, when's that [ __ ] rat
looking ugly virgin going to get a life?
When is that [ __ ] ugly face going to
get himself alive?
That [ __ ] ugly virgin face. That ugly
creepy virgin, right? Do you know that
autumn, right? You know that autumn? She
was like, "Oh, how can you talk about
anyone right when I mean, have you seen
the state of him? I mean, I can talk
about you because you use filters. You
never guess who [ __ ] commented. That
[ __ ] crazy virgin trying to get
sexual material so he can wank his
little piny little flaccid dick again
cuz he's a virgin. You know,
you know that [ __ ] virgin [ __ ]
pops out of anywhere. That [ __ ] skinned virgin.
Is that right, Steven Howard? Wherever
the women are, the virgin's there with
his little flaccid little autistic skin
dick. I know you like my I know you like
my little comebacks, mate.
Go away. No one wants you. You skinned
virgin and I'll say it to your face as
well. I'll call you a [ __ ] skinned
virgin over a Guinness and you can't get
lagged. You're a virgin.
You know what I'm like, mate. I need to
keep the volume down a bit. I'd make
[ __ ] jokes. I'll be like, "When are
you going to lose it, you [ __ ] skin
virgin?" Give him the side eye, mate.
Bey loves me, mate.
Okay. Should be here soon.
I need a curry to calm down, mate.
I just don't know how I'm going to be a
31y old virgin. Never had it. I just
can't believe it.
[ __ ] virgin. You are a [ __ ]
virgin. You skint [ __ ] living in Kent.
You are a [ __ ] virgin. You and your
ugly nad. And your mom [ __ ] starved
you and you done nothing about it. You
little [ __ ] She starved you. You done
nothing. You little [ __ ] You've been
abused by your mom. You little [ __ ]
virgin. You know what I'm like, mate.
You know what I'm like? Like you [ __ ]
skink [ __ ] Don't [ __ ] come to London
and stop projecting your virginity onto
me, you know.
[ __ ] stupid. He's an idiot, bro. He
is. Don't [ __ ] get that trade into
London, right? Projecting that [ __ ]
virginity of yours onto what? She skin,
you know, trying to [ __ ] say about
Aisha. You didn't [ __ ] Aisha. She
rejected you. She wanted £300 for
trainers and you went nowhere near her.
You had nowhere near that girl. Your
[ __ ] skin virgin coming to London
with your virgin self, walking like a
virgin, acting like a virgin cuz you're
a big virgin trying to call other people
what you are because you deep down are a
virgin. When you look up and down,
you see yourself. You see the big
virgin, the virgin that got starved by
you mama kind of virgin. We made we made
a song about this, bro.
We made a song about this earlier, but
you missed it.
No, I'm [ __ ] lie, mate.
Oh, [ __ ] Tommy. He's a plunker, mate.
He's a plunker.
Don't come to my city. Start projecting
your virginity, you little [ __ ] You
little lanky [ __ ]
You're nothing to do with London. And
also, let me tell you something as well.
You know, uh, Chadwell Heath is actually
London. Actually, Rockford is London and
Chadwell Heath's buff before London. You
do realize that if you look it up, it
actually is London, not some [ __ ]
[ __ ] in Kent, some little virgin area
that if you [ __ ] live, mate, you'd
probably have mental health problems.
Not that little [ __ ] shitty little
virgin area full of virgins. I know.
I've been there. It's that it's it's the
home of virgins. You saw me there,
didn't you, Griezy?
You saw me in I I called it Little India.
I called it Little India me.
Do you not remember when I went there? Uh
was it year before I lost? Must have
been year before I lost. That [ __ ]
skin virgin area full of absolute
virgins. You know all about virgins. Was
he the biggest virgin himself? He know
all about what he is. Cuz he's the
virgin, mate. He's a [ __ ] skin virgin.
Oh, you're right. I was just talking
about the skin virgin.
I need to calm down now, bro. I'm
getting more hungry. I need to keep my
volume down. Just waiting for my lovely food now.
Oh mate, he he's a [ __ ] skin virgin.
We were just saying when is he going to lose it?
I'll give him a hug when he finally gets
laid and he's no longer that virgin from
Kent. I'll say congratulations,
you're no longer a virgin.
Your channel got banned, bro, for
putting my porno up.
Imagine that. Your your channel got
banned. I ordered some uh Lush Indian.
Oh, by the way, have you ever used this
before? This is very nice. It came with my trainers. Yeah,
we're talking about the skin virgin. The Orington virgin.
The the little virgin the grand a month.
We're talking about the skin boy.
You [ __ ] know, mate.
You [ __ ] know. We're talking about
[ __ ] skin virgin.
It's skin boy. You know what I'm saying?
You can't have a binderoo
because you're not strong and Turkish
like me. Only big strong Turkish men.
Only big strong Turkish men can pull
women. They're not far white little
virgins like you with little dicks. I'm
such a wind up, isn't it?
It's so nice to spray, bro. It is nice
to be fair.
They're not They're not for little
virgins like you, mate. Oh, man.
Big big big virgin. Big big thick skin
So yeah, Chadwell Heath and Romford is
is actually London to be honest. [ __ ]
Kent ain't London. [ __ ] little Kent
wanker. [ __ ] come to my city with
your [ __ ] virgin body, with your ugly
virgin, shitty little no muscle body,
with your [ __ ] no muscles, with your
skint legs and try and call me what you
are, the virgin. [ __ ] off, mate. Glad to
see you try and do it now, son.
I don't like it. I don't like it.
Don't like it. Not going to have some
skin little dick virgin try and come to
my city, right? No, I'm not going to
have I've had it up to here with this
lanky rat [ __ ] looking little virgin
that can't attract anything normal. No,
I won't keep it down. I've had enough of
this ugly little skin virgin, you know,
to last me a bloody lifetime.
You know, who does he think he is with
his ugly body, with his no muscle virgin
self coming to my city, right? The
little lanky little police informant,
little cowardly little shitag. Who does
he think he is, mate? When he gets a
good old ass whooping now, don't don't ever
think that these two are about it, mate.
You never think that Red Star and Virgin
are about it. They have to run to the
Popo because they got their ass a good
whooping. Don't Don't ever ever let them
try and tell you otherwise. They run to
the boys in blue, mate, because they got
their ass a good old whooping. Peter
Belly, they them two virgins, them
absolute virgins can't handle me so
badly that they have to go to the police
because they can't handle me. I own them
in every aspect of life. They have to
call the police and and that's and
that's the last resort, you know, [ __ ] losers.
[snorts] Virgins. Anyways, uh this food
should be coming soon. So, yeah.
Come on. But I'm [ __ ] starving, bro.
But no last coffee. I think it was a few
days ago, is it?
Sorry about that. I get a bit like that,
you know, sometimes,
you know. Sorry about that. Sorry. Once
I have my little food, I'll sleep like a
little baby. Yeah. I'm all right. I'm
all right. I'm all right, bro. I'm all You know,
just don't like virgins,
you know. You know, I just don't like
virgins, mate. You know, I've always hated virgins. Skint virgins.
Try not to uh meet me, try not to miss
me too much from tomorrow, though. Yeah.
It'll only be for like a week or two
weeks or three weeks, bro. You know, you
have to take a break off this sometimes
because it's the same atmosphere.
And you lose brain cells because they're
so disabled on here. So, you have to you
have to take, you know, some time off.
Oh, come on. Food. Dude, I'm really hungry.
We What are you having for tea today?
What are you having, bro?
You're almost 20 minutes [ __ ] late
for this bloody [ __ ] food.
Come on, bro.
Stop laughing, man.
You're going to have a take out though,
aren't you, Greasy? You going to have a little takeout?
>> [clears throat]
>> W expecting that ma.
Yeah, but you're obviously going to get
something, aren't you, in the end?
Waiting for this food, bro. I'm so hungry.
See, it's for big strong Turkish men
that can grow beards,
not some [ __ ] little rat face looking virgin [laughter]
that can't grow a beard. You [ __ ]
ugly [ __ ] And you'll see in a minute
when it arrives.
We'll do a tester.
We'll do a tester again.
>> Yeah. Come on, guys. Seriously, I'm hungry.
I'm gaining on It's all these cummies I
keep eating and these chicken. I can't
help myself in the winter, Grezy.
They're so yummy. Where is my food? Oh,
I don't think that's it.
I can't help myself with these
takeaways. Is he
Yeah, he did, mate.
>> I look a bit like Chebeca, don't I? We
one second, bro.
I love this phone so much. I look a bit
like Chewca, don't I?
I look a bit like Chew Becca now from Star Wars. Oh god. M
Yeah, I haven't had a shower for days to be fair.
Where is his food, bro?
It's on its way.
But where is it, bro?
Going to have a glass of coke.
We're going to have a glass of coke for now, please. Mom.
Mama, would you like a cup of tea?
The food's going to be here soon and
you're going to have your tandoori chicken.
>> Yeah, you are. Cuz I bought it. It cost
a lot of money. Huh?
So, you wouldn't go without food.
M. I can't eat the ticker and the
[ __ ] thing. I've got some naan coming as well.
You know, you silly goose.
Another one, Grey. [laughter]
Where's that golden bird?
Where's [screaming] that skin?
Where's the island skin?
Not calling everyone a virgin. I'm
calling you a virgin. You're the biggest virgin going.
You're the virgin. You're the all time
Also got a nice bottle of Coke Greg. Yeah,
nice fresh bottle of Coke, you know.
Yeah, delivery is better to deliver for Yeah.
Oh, you put everything there, mama.
there it is. The mama.
Oh, hey, man. Thank you, Captain.
The guy actually sounded English as well. More
more. The food's here. Mom, the food's
here. Do you want some chicken? But mom,
what do you mean?
I bought it specially for you, mama.
I bought it specially for your little kitty.
Got 30 worth of stuff in there, mate. London version. [laughter]
Leave me alone.
Well, I'm waiting to charge it up.
We'll just tell Lady
Laney, your chicken, Mark. Your tandoori
chicken's right there. One second.
Let's get my charger.
I gave my mom a chicken. Is that cute, Grezy?
I need to go pee. I hate that, you know,
when you're just about to eat.
One second, mama.
That little boy scream.
I'm having a pee.
Oh, I got Oh, another thing. more.
>> You can have a bit of naan bread, too.
How is your chicken, mama?
>> Oh, one second, mama.
>> I got some popping and I got some.
>> Oh, mate. Look at that cheese.
A tiny bit. Oh,
he was hungry, man. Yeah. time. Captain
lights and full. Huh? >> Yeah. What's that?
say that probably m
one second captains now.
Look at this. What's wrong? M now this out.
You don't believe I'm from London and
you think I'm from Kent, right? One second.
I'm clearly I'm from London. I must version that face. One second.
Is that lamp? Yeah, this
Do you believe I'm from London? Do you?
You don't believe I'm from London, do you?
We're not We're not convergent.
We're not convers that can only attract disabled.
I'm a big strong Turkish man.
I'm going to skip version.
I'm not some skinny little virgin look
like a rat.
You see me running for that [ __ ] drink, mate.
Do you see me running for that drink?
Yeah. Women W women don't treat me good.
It's a two-way thing.
If they want people to treat them
better, they should start treating other
people better than bullshiters.
I'm not from
some K version virgin one second. I'm not.
Do you reckon you could take the screw?
Do you reckon you could take it? Then you can't.
I'll be a bit disappointed if you were
like a virgin in Kent.
No one cares. No one cares. I've showed
my approaches. I showed my messages
which you dismissed. So, no one cares.
We're not talking about it anymore.
Yeah. Another one that dismisses my struggles. Remember
I said there's no point of the debate
cuz they just dismiss your struggles.
So there's no kind of there's no point
of any debate
cuz they just dismiss your struggles.
You don't dismiss you you you don't
exist in the argument. So it's
pointless. You're best off saying
nothing. You know
what about the approaching videos? What
about the messages that led me on? What
about those ones, Kaye?
What about those women that treated me
badly? You seem to dismiss them ones, didn't you?
I guess they didn't suit her, Grezy.
Yeah, you don't exist in the argument.
You You don't exist in the argument, so
there's no point. You're basically not a
participant because they just dismissed
your struggles. So it's pointless pointless conversation.
Yeah, exactly. But exactly.
I'm begging for sex. And now now Katie's
resorting to making stuff up. Begging
for sex. See, baking stuff up again. I'm
not I'm not having this conversation.
I'm I'm done with it. We had this yesterday.
I'm not getting into this debate
cuz I don't exist in it according to these people.
But it wasn't just him though, Grezy. It
was people that was commenting as well like Kitty.
Oh, best Kitty from Scotland. Do you
feel bad for Kitty?
What about all of the Right. Okay. have
the same conversation and then so uh did you um
so Kitty is innocent.
Everyone should feel sorry for Kitty
even though Grezy
she chose these men. The other men that
they go, they choose these men they go for.
They choose them. They choose these men.
Don't let them tell you otherwise. They
don't know what they're like.
They choose them, man. [snorts]
No, they choose them. They definitely
Yeah, they definitely choose that. They
know what these men are about.
They know what these men are about.
It's no coincidence. Trust me.
They go for men that that are [ __ ]
and then B. They get treated like [ __ ]
I know some bad ones
in the back [ __ ]
Yeah. And also she's made it so people
can't messenger. Howard. So she's made
it so people can't even private
messenger. [ __ ] coward. No.
Yeah. I think it's very cowardly
when you're not going to let someone
else say anything back. To be fair, it's
a bit coward. Yeah. [ __ ] bad.
But to be fair, it's not just him. It's
a lot of people that just defend women.
Look at Virgin Boy. He defends women and
women don't like him. He's still a
virgin. Think of it. Have you seen the
years that we've been on YouTube being
the virgin? Who's been with more women?
I have. And he still defends them
because they don't like him. And he
think he thinks by defending them
they'll like him.
But women don't like his ugly ass.
That's why he's still a virgin. Yeah.
Yeah. Exactly. Yeah. Yeah,
>> they changed their mind. They changed
>> They don't owe you anything.
>> And they couldn't answer questions when
I asked why are none of these things
used when men do these things. Did you
notice they couldn't answer it briefly?
Did you notice that they couldn't answer
it? They couldn't answer that part. I
said, "Okay, well, why don't you say the
same when men do these things?" And
they're going to answer it, man. [clears throat]
And then you got Katie dismissing my struggles.
Loads of people dismiss my struggles, don't they?
They love this mission. People struggle
for whatever reason. I don't know. But they
like for example, right? I put up approaching videos.
I put up messages. I put these things up
for a reason. And then somebody will
just come on my live stream talking
about absolute nonsense when I've just
put a load of [ __ ] up. What what I've
gone through. You know what I mean?
But that virgin thing was it was just a
joke though. Like I said, I'm not going
back and forth with some little autistic keyboard warrior.
Is that all right with you, Greezy?
I'm not going back and forth with some
insecure low life. That's why you don't
see me on here, bro.
I mean, I'm not going I'm not going back
and forth with some creepy little insecure
little keyboard warrior low life. You
like that one, bro? Yeah.
Yeah. He They dismiss people's struggles. Yeah.
That's the real Katie, by the way. She
dismissed my struggles as well. Yeah.
But Katie also dismissed my struggles.
I don't know why. So,
like I said, there's no point in being
in the debate.
There's no point being on the debate.
Then, if they're just going to dismiss
what you say, it's pointless.
They just miss your struggles. I feel
like they do. Yeah.
They Yeah. It's like anything you show
them, they ignore it.
They'll ignore every bad thing that
they've done and then go for you again.
But Gy, what's weird is that you'll show
what I keep saying to you, bro, is that
you will show them black and white
evidence. Like black and white evidence.
Not just me and you arguing.
Not just me and you arguing, right?
I'm right. You're right. I'm right.
You're wrong. Whoever
you will show them black and white
evidence and they will still nod their
head like a dog and pretend it never
happened with madness.
But I'm done now, bro. [ __ ]
I just filled up my second coat cuz my
mouth is a bit dry.
So now, do you believe I'm from London, Grezy?
Now, do you believe I'm not a Kent virgin?
There's rumors going around that you
thought I was from London.
Oh, sorry. Kent. I'm not from Kent. I'm
a big strong Turkish man. I ain't no virgin.
What do you think to that?
Yeah. Virgin by Get Get Virgin by Auma
wh else you're at it. Get the Virgin AMA. Oh gosh,
I'm stuffed. Uzzy. Yeah,
you ask Lexia. Why was he dismissing my
struggles, isn't it?
You ask him why why why was he
dismissing my struggles, isn't it, Grezy? Yeah.
dismissing my struggles.
Yeah, they do do that, bro. A lot of
them do that. They do it on here as
well. Like I said, you can show them a
woman leading you on. You can show a
woman ghosting you. You can show a woman
[ __ ] you over
and they would still pretend they never saw it.
Idiots, bro. And you know what's more
scary, Grezy, is more people do it than
don't do it. That's the most scariest thing.
more people defend them for being women
than than people that don't.
That's the scary thing.
I can tell you I've been on dates, bro,
and I've never changed my mind before
going on a date. Never ever I change my
mind. People don't just change their
People, like you said, people don't just
change their mind. Yeah. Yeah,
they seem to they they have it in their
head that a woman can't lead people on.
They they have it in their head, Gregy,
that women can't do any wrong just
because they're a woman. Mad.
Yeah. Like what you said, basically. Oh gosh. Mom,
I'm stuffed. Mama,
I'm going to sleep in a bit. Yeah, I'm tired now.
Can Are you going to put me in the oven
and make a stuffed lamb? Mama,
what? Why are you sitting all by yourself, mama?
No, you're disgusting.
Stop saying stuff like that, you gross bastard. That's gross.
You know who my mama is.
That's my mama. [snorts] Forget about my
mama. [ __ ] off.
That's not my mama. Mama,
go downstairs and give me that spoon.
Mama, who said that? Huh?
Sit back down and give me that spoon.
You are nice, mama.
I proved I was from London the way I ate
that curry. See, if I was from Kent, I'd
struggle with the curry. You know,
I ain't no [ __ ] tent virgin.
I ain't no [ __ ] tent virgin, mate.
[snorts] I ain't no [ __ ] virgin.
I ain't from Oh,
[ __ ] virgin for [ __ ] virgin.
That Jamie Thompson watch my ass. Sorry,
gay boy. I don't swing that way.
Indigo, these people give me the EBGBs.
They're so obsessed with me.
You got some [ __ ] skin virgin living
in a village obsessed with me. Then you
got Red Star. Then you got all these
silly accounts. Then you've got Jamie
Thompson. Why are these people Why do
they want my ass so much?
They They should be living their best
life. If I'm all of these nasty things
that they keep saying I am,
wouldn't they be living their best life
and forget about Peter Belly? They're so
obsessed with Peter Belly. It's a joke.
An absolute joke, mate.
They don't leave me alone.
They skint virgins. Skint virgin.
Just looking on this right here.
Look at that ugly face.
Two ugly faces.
I'm not going to tell you what I'm on.
I'm not going to tell you. I'm not going
to tell you. Oh, look at that ugly face.
Two ugly bastards.
[ __ ] ugly face virgin
pretending to be a woman who doesn't
want you. That's you. Britney don't want
you. You little cell projector.
No, people don't want you. You virgin.
God, he is so obsessed. He needs to get laid.
God, he needs to get laid, man. He's
such a virgin.
When is this virgin going to get laid?
When is he going to lose his veon and
stop being such a keyboard warrior, ugly
virgin? When is he really going to stop,
mate? When's he seriously going to sort
that ugly face out and stop coming
online and talking [ __ ] about people
that are better looking than him, mate?
When you got to sort that ugly face out
and get laid and stop taking out of the
world that you're an ugly virgin,
when are you going to stop this?
It's not my fault. I'm better looking
than you and I'm not a skinned virgin
like you. Now leave me alone, you creepy bastard.
Go away, you virgin. You like my basketball shorts?
We need to wind down, mate. I'm getting
a bit, you know.
When does he really He needs to mate.
I'm I've actually tried helping him so
many times. Steven Howard, it's the
face. It's the ugly face. That's why
you're a virgin. It's the ugly face. The
ugly face. You know what I'm saying?
That's what That's what it is, mate.
When's he going to get laid? I don't
want to see him be a 31y old virgin.
When's he going to get laid? When's he
going to lose it? It's not healthy,
mate. You know,
he got laid.
Have you noticed he's so jealous? Like
if you go on that channel, right? This
skint little jealous ugly bastard with
the ugly face. If you go on every single
post, he goes mad when I meet women. Why
is he such a jealous virgin? It's not my
fault you can only date that don't sleep with you.
[ __ ] hell. He needs to lose his vod
and mind his own business. The scruffy little virgin.
You're going to get bollocking now, mate. Who's that?
Why is he so obsessive? Because he can't
get women cuz he's ugly virgin.
I love to have it out with this virgin,
you know, face to face.
Stop taking out on the world. I'm better
looking than you and you're an ugly [ __ ]
that could only get down. It's not my
fault. It's not my fault you're an ugly
[ __ ] It's not my fault I pulled [ __ ]
USA and these women. It's because I'm
not an ugly [ __ ] like you. I've tried
telling you this multiple times, mate.
Odd's an understatement, bro. Virgin boy.
He calls me the incel. Yeah, he's the
one that can only get with Down syndrome
women. He's so He's so undesirable that
he can only get with Down syndromes. So,
when he's talking about incel, he's
talking about his virgin self. He's
looking in the mirror again.
He must be looking in the mirror again.
He [snorts] must see the incel virgin
that can only date down syndromes. If
you've seen all of the women I've been
with, they've never been down syndrome.
Like he's girlfriend. Have you noticed that, mate?
You know, mate,
need to get laid, mate. You need to
seriously need to s that ugly face,
you ugly [ __ ]
No, I'm joking. But I'm not really doing YouTube videos.
[snorts] I'm only joking, bro. I'm not
wasting my time on the skin little virgin
skin little obsessed autistic virgins.
But what I will say to you people who's watching this
probably h well even if you got autism
yourself, never meet someone with autism.
They become very jealous and obsessed
with you and they don't leave you alone.
never meet, especially if they're an
ugly [ __ ] like him, you know. Make sure
you you don't meet people with autism, [ __ ] virgin.
You [snorts] understand? Yeah, virgins.
Your followers are absolute nerdy little virgins. Little virgin.
I can answer you. I don't understand why
Sean puts up loads of abuse about PJ.
Surely that will hurt his case and he's
just as bad. I can answer you, Ricky. >> [snorts]
>> I could answer your question because
he's mentally obsessed. Um, he's been
this way for years. He doesn't he
doesn't care about the the case. He's
mentally obsessed. So even if he calls
the police on people, right?
He's an obsessed little virgin. He's
been this way for years. So it doesn't
really matter about the case, bro. You
know, [snorts] he's he's he's so obsessed
that he can't help himself. He's an
obsessed little virgin.
So, I mean that's to answer your
question if if you wanted to know. Yeah.
He puts up abuse because he's a mentally
jealous, obsessed little virgin.
To answer your uh question, if you if
you wanted me to answer it for you,
people that are mentally obsessed don't care, bro. Yeah,
cuz think about it, right? If you called
you call the police on someone,
you call the you you you know I mean you
know you call the police on someone and
so you're supposed to not do anything,
right? So you're supposed to but where
he's a mentally obsessed little virgin,
he can't help himself.
Like there's some people that that can't help themselves.
They they can't help themselves. You see
>> that's uh
that's why basically you wanted to know. >> Yeah.
Uh cow is a little copycat. Little copycat.
He's a little copycat.
So he puts up abuse because he's a
mentally obsessed virgin.
That's why. Mentally obsessed little
geeky little virgin.
I don't know why you're talking about
[ __ ] bouncers and [ __ ] as well.
>> I came to your area. I had you run into
the police, you little virgin [ __ ]
I had you run into the police, you
little virgin [ __ ]
Stop sniffing around these women, you
little virgin. Why don't you reply to a
[ __ ] man, you skin little virgin.
You [ __ ] skint little virgin.
Look at all of these simps, bro. On
[ __ ] um Yeah.
Yeah. It's mad mentally obsessed virgin.
same nerds. Same fat ugly nerds that comment.
Same fat ugly people that ain't got a life.
Same fat ugly low lives that ain't got
no life. Do you know what? I might do a
video before I leave, bro, for a couple
of weeks. Obviously, I have to run it by Greasy first.
I had Rickster in it as well since you
wanted to ask a question. I'll answer
your question for you if if you want, mate.
And I have had a girlfriend and I've
been with more women than you or
whatever, you little virgin. Insecure
little virgin. And the more you do this
YouTube thing, the more it makes me
write about you, you little insecure
virgin. That's why all of my videos get thumbs up. [ __ ] virgin. One second. Hey baby. Oh little bastards.
And when I come back, I don't want to
see any of you people on YouTube.
I don't want to see any of you people on YouTube. Deal.
Never had a girlfriend. I've had a
>> I've had more women than you have.
>> You've You've only been with one single mom.
[ __ ] get on get off of YouTube and go
get laid, you [ __ ] little low life.
Go get laid, you little low life. Trust
you to be stalking around women again,
you little virgin. Every single time
there's a woman you you'll notice you'll
see this virgin around
sniffing around with his virgin little
erectile dysfunctional dick. Yeah.
[ __ ] madness, bro. Absolute madness.
Skin little virgin.
Then they think that they've won. Loser.
You're showing yourself up on YouTube.
You little sad. You little sad act. Yeah,
you s little bastards.
Ain't got a life.
Ain't got a life but you, Jake.
What a low life.
Ugly. I coni I'm convinced these people
right on here
are ugly 40 year olds that ain't got
anything better to do. Bro, I'm
convinced at this point with these
little low lives. You know what? [ __ ]
it. I'll do a little video before I leave.
Obviously, I have to run it uh um
have to run it by Grezy
first. I always have to run these
streams by Grezy. [snorts]
I'm calling you virgin cuz you are a [ __ ] virgin.
[ __ ] porno got banned. Porno got
banned cuz of you. You virgin.
Get alive, you little skimp bastard. Skint bastard.
I am actually convinced that they're
just fat ugly little low lives that
don't leave the house on £300 a month.
100% they are. 100% they [ __ ] well are, bro. You know,
it's so bad they don't even fit into a normal community.
No one wants them even on a normal
community. That's why they stalk on here every day.
They stalk people that are better
looking than them, that's younger than
them. That's what they do because they
hate the fact that they're them. They
hate the fact that they are them.
That's why they're on here. People
living their best life don't [ __ ] do
this. Any anyone would know that.
Anybody would know that, mate. Anybody
would know that. you know,
bit like Reddit uh moderators,
there's no point doing a video to these
little weirdos. They're not worth
They're not worth the time. Steven
Howard. These little low lives on here.
Depressed ugly low lives. Depressed
little low life people. Don't miss me
for too long, bro. Two weeks. Yeah,
maybe even more to be honest with you.
May maybe a very long time, bro. I'll
come live again.
Same atmosphere, same repeating people.
You You get it, don't you, Stephen
Howard? You get it.
Ain't got ain't got no life.
Dedicated to being obsessed with people
every day cuz they hate them. They hate
themselves. Should I say that? That they
hate themselves. We can we can agree to
that in it. Yeah.
cuz I'm just
He's having a wank. He's having a wank.
They're [ __ ] weirdos on here, mate.
But yeah, good question, Ricky.
But he does it because he's an obsessed little virgin.
Insecure, fragile ego little virgin.
That's why he's on here every day.
Because his life's [ __ ] He's with a
disabled the wolf that doesn't give him
sex. What else has he got to What else
has he got to do? The virgin One's up.
One second, lad.
Where is that [ __ ] virgin?
A [ __ ] virgin.
Where is that [ __ ] bird?
Why do people ignore on Instagram?
Do people ignore on Instagram? Steven Howard,
they ignore Instagram, in it.
Yeah. I ate the food. All of it, bro. >> [snorts] >> Yeah.
Why' they ban on Reddit?
Is it a power thing? Why does the Why
does the mods ban people?
Does it make them feel powerful or something?
That's why I stopped using it for ages,
Reddit, bro. Cuz they ban you for no
reason, is it?
Does it make them feel powerful? What do
you think of Steven Howard like banning people?
They fear different opinions. Yeah.
Oh, that [ __ ] skin virgin.
Oh, that skin [ __ ] virgin.
What are we going to do about the
football now, Steen? Now, I'm going to
have to give up gambling.
I'm going to have to give up gambling now, lad. Yep. Yeah.
How much you got left now, Steven
Howard? How much longer you got left?
How much money you got left?
What about Noble Fund?
Yeah, I think I've got about 700 and something pounds.
700 and something. Yeah, man. >> [snorts]
>> Maybe I I don't know.
What about other money?
What about other money do you have? Lucky you.
You got more than me, matey.
But you don't go out drinking, do you?
You don't go out drinking.
you know, buy designer jeans and stuff there. So,
Bing is virgin boy excited. Yeah.
Boy is virgin boy by sight. Yeah.
when will I get laid again?
Never. Oh, the escort was telling me
that she's in Stratford, by the way. She
messaged me saying I'm in Stratford, but
nah, I'm all right. Thanks. I'm not going.
I need to save some money now. Anyways,
I already spent 80 quid today.
Spent [ __ ] 80 quid.
[ __ ] hell, bro. So, no.
The Brazilian one that was giving me grief.
Do you remember Siri that was giving me grief?
Yeah, the one that was giving me grief.
Yeah, I won't get laid again ever
in this country.
Yeah, it won't be out this week. It
won't be out next week. Won't be out [ __ ] Yeah. [snorts]
Get laid. You can't even get a date.
How do I win money gambling? Siri,
how am I supposed to win money gambling? Huh?
How do you win money gambling, matey?
Yeah, but they tried to get out of
paying you in real casinos. Don't know.
No, I'm talking about roulette.
Yeah, you outgrow it. I guess
>> I'm more than happy staying in bed
snoozing, you know.
Oh gosh, what's wrong with this dodgy charger?
>> Yeah, I'm more than happy just staying
in bed chilling. No,
you can win online roulette though, can't you?
You can win on online roulette. I'm sure you can.
Who's that [ __ ] virgin?
Well, online or in passion. Oh gosh.
When do you reckon I'll get laid again? Steven Howard. No escorts. Never.
It makes you wonder what's the point of
being born with a dick if you don't need
to use it. Virgin skin virgin.
What do you mean one in a million?
People on Reddit say you can get sex easy.
Yeah, but people on Reddit say I can get
sex from apps and stuff.
That's what they say on Reddit. Oh my [ __ ] boy.
So, are you sure I would ever get sex
again? Steen Howard?
What's the point of having a dick if
you're not going to use it?
Pointless, isn't it?
When do you think I'm going to get sex
again? Big me over
like without escorts. I'm I'm in
England. I'm in England. I'm in England.
What do you think?
Cuz no one's bloody interested
in this country. No one's bloody
interested. And I've had enough of it
being led on and stuff.
But yeah, I need to go get some food tomorrow.
What makes you say probably 2027 though?
Cuz people on people on Reddit say that
you just go on dating apps.
They tell you to go on dating apps, but
they don't work. [snorts]
2027. What makes you say that?
>> Yeah. Lucky you, bro. I'll probably have
about a thousand and something.
You're beating me.
Oh, that's what I was doing.
But don't forget, I done stuff and [ __ ]
So, I need to do some food shopping tomorrow
cuz I need to save some money, bro. I
can't keep getting takeaways, you know.
So, Big Mioa What do you reckon would
have happened today if I went out approaching?
If I went out approaching today?
Yeah, I went out approaching.
I bought Ugg boots. I bought 200
trainers, 200 jeans. I still need to buy a phone. Yeah,
that's still out of stock. That phone,
you know, I was looking at that phone.
It's still out of stock. Yeah.
What do you think would have happened? Big meow. [snorts] Yeah.
I've gone out
drunk, got numbers, no one's interested.
So, I need to I'll still obviously spend
some money every Saturday. Like, I can
still go and go to like a restaurant
every Saturday or go cinema or do little
things like that. But,
I need to seriously save now, bro.
I [snorts] want to be back to 2K again.
And I want to have I want to be back to
£2,000 again, but I need to buy a phone
as well. But that can probably wait, you
know. Still got this one for now. Yep.
What stuff did you see me buy? Steen out
with the jeans and the trainers.
You saw me by the jeans and the
trainers, didn't you?
Yeah, the trainers and the jeans and [ __ ]
and the jeans.
Yeah, my trainers are put away nicely
under the thing.
I need to buy refurbished iPhone with a
new battery. You can buy a new battery.
So, I'll maybe do that next month or
whatever. I don't need to do anything
for now. I just need to chill.
Save up and chill.
Yeah, chill and save it. You can buy a
new battery on a refurbished phone when
you order it. So, I'll just buy a new battery
and I'll get a Samsung Galaxy Fold 8 next year. Yep.
Almost got three teams today, didn't I?
Steven Howard almost You know,
I wasn't to be honest. I wasn't going to
buy a used phone. Maybe I won't get it.
I I don't know what I'm
My mom's got a refurbished iPhone. And
it was £110
and it's quite good.
Yeah. But what do you want me to do? Pay
over £1,000 for a phone?
I'm not paying over £1,000 for a phone, bro.
Is that what you want me to do? Pay over
£1,000 for a phone?
I'm not doing that, matey.
Oh, the iPhone 17
Pro Max is 1,200. See, that's not even
that bad compared to the other ones.
Well, there's an iPhone 14 here and it's
£495 brand new. iPhone 16.
Just looking at the iPhones, the brand new iPhones.
There's some uh iPhones here.
I tell you what, I might
There's a I like the flip phones. Those
flip phones are like $8.49.
Well, there I you get a brand new iPhone.
You don't like the Samsung Galaxy flip? They're 849.
You don't like the flips. [snorts] Yeah.
Well, I don't know what phone I'm going
to get. I'm just going to save and when
there's one, I'll just buy one in it.
Well, I don't see the point in paying
big money for a phone, you know. No point. No.
It was yummy.
[snorts] It was yummy. We Oh gosh.
So you said you carried over 550 this month, Greavvesy. Oh, bless.
I've got about £800 to last me two weeks. Quezy,
is that bad?
Yeah, I've got about £800 to last me two weeks.
I might. What if I starve? What if I die of starvation? Greasy. Nah.
A 250 bill. You're [ __ ] bonkers. Yep.
Sure is. Captain
Grezy, are you all right? Captain.
All right, Captain.
You're right, Captain.
You like Shy.
You like coy cat?
You know you'll get sticky if you know
what you are. So greasy.
You like sh
you don't copycat.
You know copycat. Copycat.
What a copycat statement. Greavvesy,
you remember you said it sounded like a
copycat statement. You're [ __ ] bunk
as you are.
Don't know why people feel the need to copy.
Greasy, do you reckon if I went out
approaching today, I would have got a
date for next week? Do you think?
You reckon I would have got a date for next week?
Maybe if I went out today.
Yeah, I was just asking.
We can't let these [ __ ] women win though, Grezy.
Yeah, but we can't let these [ __ ] women win. Yeah. What's up?
Yeah, women are evil.
Evil [ __ ] in it, Grezy. Oh, boy.
Hold up boy Franklin. Frenchland. [snorts]
Yeah, but grievy that account keeps
coming in talking about women. Have you
seen it? That Siri account saying we're
[ __ ] P. How are we ever going to meet a woman?
>> Yeah, but we'll be talking about
something and it will just randomly come
in. Is it Greavves? You seeing it in it?
You've seen it though. Greasy. You've
It does though. Say it does.
It's mocking me, is it?
It's mocking me, isn't it, Grezy?
It's rude, isn't it?
Step, step, step, step, step, step, step, step.
Do you remember the [ __ ] video I put
up, Grezy? Everyone was waiting, weren't
they? Everybody was waiting, weren't they, Grezy?
Everybody was waiting. [snorts]
Everyone was waiting
and then bam, you got a notification in it. Oh [ __ ]
Will you be on YouTube tomorrow, Grezy?
You're on YouTube every bloody day, aren't you?
A bless you. [gasps]
Bless you, Grezy. Yeah.
Bless you in life. Bless you in life.
See, iPhones greasy. They only go up to £1,200
whereas Samsung's they go up to like £1,800.
Mad didn't it?
That's mad. Is it Greavvesy?
Guess you just gone live. Tony, I got a notification.
Did you get a little notification?
I'm not saying the name, but did you get
the same notification?
I need to go poo. Greasy,
is that okay with you?
If I go poo.
Okay with you.
Okay with you
if I go poo. If I go poo. It's okay with you. [snorts]
Is that okay with you? Captain,
can you please choose me a phone to get
Steven out? I really need a phone now. Seriously,
I can't make up my mind.
Can you pick me a phone to get
And how much is it going to be? Oh gosh. There's a
There's an iPhone 16e. 549.
It's not that bad, is it? iPhone 15. That's Yeah. You know,
I had a 40 tablet before.
I had a 40 tablet. It was okay.
We're talking back in 2013.
Yeah, I had a 40 tablet in 201 13.
It weren't that bad. It weren't that bad
for uh £40.
It It was an It weren't an Amazon one.
It was a um I bought it from Amazon. Come on. >> [snorts] >> Yeah,
I agree with you. I got a 50 tablet before.
and it was [snorts] quite good. Yep.
What the [ __ ]
What? It's not £200. You silly goose. >> [snorts] >> Yeah. Yep. [ __ ] >> [laughter]