Yep. So, yeah, I said I was going um
today, but I'm fresh start tomorrow. I'm
definitely definitely off tomorrow. And
you know what? I I want to talk about
these people in this community. These
little nonch lovers, these little fat,
ugly, bitter, hateful little weirdos. I
I I want I want to talk about these
people on here today, bro. Yeah. This is
going to be like a different live
stream. I want to talk about these people.
Yeah, I want to talk about these little
mongos on here when more people join.
So, yeah, I'm going to do that anyways
when more people join. I said I was
going to leave today, but I'm gone
tomorrow. Fresh start tomorrow. Yeah.
And you know what? I'm I'm going to ask
them some questions. That's all I'm
going to do is ask these people why they
do what they do every day.
you know, since um
Yeah, you are autis You have got autism.
You're [ __ ] thick. Yeah, that's you.
You're talking You're talking about yourself,
you [ __ ] fat, ugly scaler, little
[ __ ] [ __ ] mate. Come come back to
me when you come to London. When you
come to London, come back to me. Yeah.
And we'll talk. Stop being a keyboard
lawyer. Um, I just want to talk about
these people in this community to be
honest with you, bro. Well, most of
them. Anyways, I don't know if you
watched my video, right, Jay Widow. I
don't know if you watched my video, but
I'm [ __ ] I I just don't know what it
is. Are these people cuz apparently you
say that I don't know. Are you What is
it with you people? Are you fat? Are you
ugly? Are you jealous? Are you skinn?
Have you got no life? I want to know why
you do what you do every day. I'm
generally curious. I I want to know why
you do what you do. And I'm going to put
a link up when more people join. I'm
going to put put a link up. And I want
to know why you people do what you do every day.
Was you bullied at school? Are you fat?
Are you ugly? Are you housebound? Like
there's there's got to be something
behind it, you know. Talk to Big Peter
Belly, you know. Um I went on uh
one second, bro.
I went on um
Yeah. You don't destroy anyone. and you
can't destroy anyone behind the
keyboard. Anyways, I'm going to put the
link up in a bit. Anyways, so I put I
went on Virgin Boy's channel yesterday,
Jay Widow, and he's promoting grassing
and he got 13 thumbs up.
13 thumbs up. Yet these people on here
claim they hate grasses. When Monty's
talk about grass and he gets called a
grass, when I've mentioned the police
for some reason in the past, oh, you're
a grass. They claim that they hate
grasses and that they hate nonses. They
they hate pedophiles. That's two of the
biggest things that they say they hate
on here. Yet they were the pedophiles
grassing channel every single day. So
that is you. It's got to be jealousy
with these people on this community,
isn't it? It's got to be absolute
jealousy. Um and I and you know what? I
will put the link out, right? Did
everyone No, I didn't see it. I don't
follow anyone's channel and 50 is
nothing to me.
So, I mean, 50 pound is nothing to me.
So, why would you celebrate someone
losing 50 pound? I'm still thousands up.
So, no, I didn't see it. And weird to
celebrate someone losing 50 when in
reality I didn't even lose anything
anyways cuz I'm still thousands up. So,
try again. Anyways, um back to what I
was saying. Um so, um so why are you
jealous of something? Are you jealous
because people are younger than you or
better looking than you? I'll give you a
chance to defend yourself in a minute
when more people join. It's a Sunday
because you said that you don't like
nons and you said that you don't like
grasses, but you're on a grassing nons
channel all the time that promotes
grassing. So, are you jealous or because
at first I thought like um you know it
was because of um obviously things that
I've said in the past and and whatever
because that's what they said was the
reason was they were but this guy is an absolute nons.
Why would you celebrate someone losing
50 pound? Well, I'm still better looking
than these people. I'm I've still got
more money than these people. I've still
got more life experience than these
people. So, why would they celebrate
someone losing £50? I guess that just
shows how skinn they really are in it.
Celebrating losing 50 when I'm still
thousands up. Well, they really are fat,
ugly owners, aren't they? As I was
saying. So, um I'm thinking what it is
with these people is they're fat, ugly
people that've been bullied. I'm I'm
trying to come to an assumption now. Um,
you know, based on what I've
experienced, they're fat, ugly, and they
hate themselves, and they hate anyone
better looking than them. Now, I'm not
saying I'm good-looking. I'm not saying
I'm ugly. I'm saying from what I'm
seeing with these people that they're
they're fat, ugly people that are
jealous of something. based on all of
the things I've been scanning. It it it
has to be subject with these fat ugly
people every single day doing this. And
like I said, I will give them I'll give
them a chance. It's not what people said
about kids and it's not what people said
about women because they love grasses
and they love pedophiles. So you can't
use that excuse anymore.
What What is it, bro? It's it's a
genuine question. People are asking you
a question. What is it? Is it because
you're jealous that someone's younger
than you, better looking than you? I've
got more hope than [snorts] you. Is Is
that what it is? Is that Is that
generally what? It's not my fault. I'm
younger. I'm better looking than you.
You know, we're not talking about women.
We're not changing the subject. We're
talking about you people on YouTube. You
nonslovers. We're not talking about
women. So, [ __ ] women and [ __ ] you. Stop
changing the subject. We are talking
about you people on this community and
what you do. Yeah. We're not. And
Indigo, you need to stop trying to
troll. You're bad at it. You really,
really need to stop. You're bad. See,
the thing is like, you're so low IQ,
right? That you can't even troll.
Like, and again, when I'm telling you
about yourselves, you're you're changing
the subject, mate. I've [ __ ] more
women than you would ever have. Stop
self-projecting. This is exactly what
I'm saying with you fat, ugly people.
Yeah. You come across a community, you
hate your lives, and you hate anyone
that's better than you. This is exactly
what I'm saying. Yeah, Mr. B, I went on
this guy's channel yesterday, bro. The
first time in three weeks, and I got and
I saw 13 thumbs up, right, to somebody promoting grass.
What do they say to Monty? What do they
say to me? And what do they say to Timmy?
What do they say, bro? When police is
ever mentioned, you know it and I know
it. These people are fat, ugly, jealous
people that want to bring people down
behind their keyboard. It's [ __ ]
obvious now, bro. It's obvious. And like
I said, I will put the link out in a
minute. Don't worry, bro. Everyone can
have their say. I'm not Lex Therapy, you
know, has to ban people, has to talk
over people and ban people. I'm not him.
But it's obviously these fat, ugly low
lives are jealous of something. And I
always hit a nerve. You know, when you
get your tooth when have you ever had a
feeling and you got a nerve in your tooth?
I mean, bro.
Yeah, bro. Let me tell you something, F.
I [ __ ] more women than you would ever
have. No, no, no one's glossed on me.
It's the whole promoting glassing.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no. How many people follow this
guy? A lot of people. A lot of people
follow this guy, right? Why is this guy
not getting [ __ ] for mentioning police?
It's because they're nonsubbers. It's
obvious. It is obvious, mate. It is. It
is very obvious. You are fat, ugly
people that hate yourselves. That's why
I get so much [ __ ] because what I'm
saying about you is the truth. You can't
The truth hurts, bum. When I'm talking
about you. Yeah, the truth hurts. I have
you by the gonads. And if you don't know
what the gonads means, it's by the
bollocks. Tell him. And what? What is
that? Women don't [ __ ] Women don't let
you [ __ ] then, mate. I've had sex more
times than you. You're still a virgin.
Can you give the self projection a rest
for one day? Bro, it's boring. We've
seen you fat ugly people. Fat ugly life
autistic losers. We've seen you people.
We've seen you people when you turn your
camera on. You're big fat ugly life's
losers. And it's the truth. And that's
why you don't like it. You're fat, ugly
people that have failed in life. You're
much older than me. And your whole
mission is to try to bring other people
down because you hate yourselves. You
hate everything about yourselves,
bro. Upload anymore? What about the
women that I [ __ ] What about all of
the women that I [ __ ] when you were
still in your mommy's basement, scared
to leave your house again? Fat, ugly
hate haters. That's what you people are.
You're fat, ugly, rejected haters that
are nobodyies in life, and you're too
old to change it. How does it make you
feel that you're an old man? Old, ugly,
and hopeless. And rejected as well. How
does it make you feel, bro? How does
that make you feel? You know, fat, ugly
little lowife keyboard warriors [ __ ]
laying in their own [ __ ] every day.
Pathetic, bro. So, they're not 13 old
accounts, bro. They're not uh they're
not 13 old accounts, bro. You know,
they're not 13 old accounts. And people
mention it on here as well all the time.
It's just like that Joseph Far. I'll
tell him that he's a nonslover as well.
I'll tell him that he's a [ __ ]
nonslover as well. You know,
[ __ ] idiots promoting grassing, but
then when someone else talks about
police, oh, you a grass, you a grass,
you jealous, narcissistic, fat, ugly
people that have got no life. You want
me to keep hitting the nerve with the
hammer, bro? You want me to keep doing
it? Cuz it's true. What I'm saying about
you is true. It's the truth, bro. You
little fat, ugly, little low lives,
little [ __ ] rejected people, bro.
Just like that [ __ ] Damian Thompson,
right? Another one. Fat, ugly in his
40s, got no life. That's why he stalks
every day because he's a fat ugly old
man that hates that you're better
looking than him. It's all to do, these
tactics are all to try to make you feel
the way that these people do. Virgins,
fat, ugly, no money. How many times have
we been hearing this [ __ ] now for years
with these [ __ ] mongos of this
community, bro? How many years have we
been hearing it? And let let's not let's
not forget the fact that these people
come on it from the time they wake up to
the time they go to bed because they're
skint people that have got nothing in
their lives. They are nobodyies. They
have got nothing. No matter what they
try to portray to other people, they are
nobodyies with nothing. No jobs, no
money, no life, nothing.
I'm going to put the link up now and
I'll give you a chance to
uh give an explanation as to why
you such grassing nons lovers. Sad.
Talk about how they hate grassing and
and and you know what, Kevin Murphy, I'm
not going to go back and forth with you.
I was in your city. You made excuses.
Why are you coming on here trying to go
back and forth, back and forth, back and
forth? You claim to be about this,
right? You claim to be about that life,
but you're on YouTube willing to go back
and forth. Bro, everybody saw when I was
in Liverpool, everyone shut their mouth.
Why do you want to keep going back and
forth, bro? You autistic or something. I
mean, you do go on L J. He's like, "Bro,
if you was any kind of a man, you would
be in London calling me out, not typing
on YouTube, considering I've already
been to your city and you was nowhere to
be seen." Apparently, you was nowhere to
be [ __ ] seen when I was there for a
day and a half. So then, bye-bye, Virgin.
Oh, screenshot that. Bye-bye, you little
[ __ ] autistic virgin. Go get laid,
you [ __ ] skint rat looking bastard,
virgin. You can [ __ ] off. I've screen
recorded that as well. By the way, more
evidence for me. Go and [ __ ] off and get
laid, you ugly Kent virgin. [ __ ]
don't come to my city again. We don't
like virgins here. And you're not coming
in, LJ. And you get banned. So Kevin
Murphy, if you want to come in, you're
more than welcome to join if you want.
Right. If you want to join, LJ is not
coming in and Virgin Boy is not coming
in. Self projectors don't come in my um
streams. So Kevin, if you want to join,
you're more than welcome to join if you want.
Or anyone else that's like a normal
person that wants to have a debate and
not ask questions and stop talking over
people and repeating themselves like LJ.
I don't want anything to do with LJ or
his little virgin channel. Nope. He's
not coming in. So there's no point
telling me to let him in. He can [ __ ]
off and go get his own life and stop self-projecting.
Self-proing fat ugly [ __ ] If he's got
anything to say, he can come and say to
my face. He knows where I live. Kevin,
if you want to join, you you can join if you want.
You know, it's been a long time. If you
want to join, I will end it right here, right now.
Yeah. Come on. You claim How long have
we been going back and forth now with
this [ __ ] bro? Back and forth. Back.
But you still haven't come to London.
So, are you autistic like these people
or something? Like, I don't understand.
I feel sorry for the police though, Mr.
B. I actually feel sorry for the police.
I actually feel sorry for the police,
you know. I generally generally feel
sorry for the police.
You know, some [ __ ] woman could be
getting raped. Some women could be
getting mugged. Someone could be getting
their phone snatched. And they've got
some [ __ ] skin ugly rat looking
copycat virgin holding their [ __ ]
lion crying. Yeah, no wonder they didn't
come out. They're [ __ ] sick of you,
you ugly virgin.
You ugly skinned one, as Timmy would
say. Uh, do I like anyone on here? Yeah,
I I like some people on here. Yeah. Um,
uh, Chris seems okay. He goes on Lord J's Um,
I mean, if you want me to name random
accounts, Greavves is okay.
Um, there's a lot of other accounts, but
they used to um leave but but they they
don't come on here anymore. I used to
like Candid Man, but
yeah, he became biased with the whole
Monty thing and that and it made me it
made me go off him.
It made me really go off him, bro.
Stop stalking me, you [ __ ] Kent
virgin, and go get laid. You're never
going to lose out at this rate. You're
going to die a virgin. Don't die that
virgin. I'm not letting that [ __ ]
rest on my my [ __ ] conscience, you
know. [ __ ] that. The fact that you could
have actually experienced sex for much
of your life. Yeah, I didn't used to
mind candid man. So,
but um yeah, he's someone that thinks
he's smarter than he actually is.
And it was offputting to be fair. So,
anyway, is any of you going to come in
and and tell me why you do what you do every day
and put your cameras on? Come on.
giving someone 13 thumbs up for
promoting grassin. Jesus, they really
are nonslvers. No wonder why Joseph Far
likes him. He's a non-slub. He's another nonslber.
What the [ __ ] [ __ ] absolute ugly
autistic people that ain't got a life.
It's the same atmosphere on here. You
end up with a migra. You end up with a
[ __ ] migraine, bro.
And then you got little weirdos on here
trying to put up nudes because they're
[ __ ] disabled. Why would anyone
Yeah. 13 likes for promoting bloody
grassing. But these people in here say
they don't like grasses. The [ __ ]
biased little nonslubbers.
Oh, we don't like we don't like grasses.
You're a grass. You're a grass. You
know, used to say it to Monty man. Like
they actually like they're actual pedos
on this community, bro. They are actual pedophiles.
They are actual pedos.
Pedo Pattersons. That's what they are.
Pedo Pattersons. Proper pedos on this
community. It's a nons community.
People that ain't got a life. Sat at
home all day. No money, no future, completely hopeless, bro.
[ __ ] mongos. Little nons lovers.
They're absolute biased nons lovers, bro.
That's what they are. So, is anyone
going to join and explain why you do
what you do every day?
Fat ugly. Bro, if these people put their
camera on, you will see what they're
like. Just fat, ugly mongos on here.
Just fat, ugly, disabled little bongos.
Ain't got no life. Ain't got no money.
Ain't got [ __ ] all. They got nothing in
their lives, bro.
And then they're trying to put up nudes.
Disabled. So disabled. These people are
on this community.
I like people in here that are not
biased. And there's not many people.
There's not many people. You say that
you don't like nons. You say that you
don't like grasses.
You hate grasses, yet you call the
police on people yourself. You call the
police on people yourself. I was
thinking about this when I was making
the tea with you little bongos. Right.
When I was when I was making this, I was
thinking about you little bongos claim
how you hate grasses and tad.
But then you you grass on people
yourself and then you like people that
that talk about grassing [ __ ]
disabled, bro. I think they want to be
me as well. I think it's jealousy, bro.
I generally think it is jealousy on this
community, bro. I genally generally
think it is jealousy on this community.
Like, and I'm not claiming to be
anything, but look at what these people
are, bro. They're [ __ ] fat, ugly
people that ain't got a life. Anyone
that's a part of a normal society is
better than them. You know, that's what
it is. They're fat, ugly little people
that ain't got a life.
They say that they don't like you
because you've said stuff about people's
kids. You've said stuff about people's
kids. and they go on about grasses. But
yet, but yet,
but yet when someone talks about grass
and is a pedophile themselves, they have
no problem with it. Can you explain that
one then? [ __ ] I think they they're
just jealous of anyone that's better and
just better looking than them and
younger than them, I think. And have
hope as well. That's what I think it is.
Defoer. This charge is dodgy, bro. [ __ ]
is wrong with it? Yeah,
definitely definitely jealous.
Definitely definitely jealous or
something. People that are not jealous
that have a good life, don't do this.
Remember that. Get that tattooed on your
arm, bro. Get it tattooed on your arm.
Fat, ugly, jealous people, they got they
ain't got nothing. They gravitate
towards anyone that's better looking
than them and younger than them.
And you are better looking than these
people. And I will prove that I'm better
looking than these people if they put
the cameras on. So you are better
looking than these people. You are
younger than these people. I think
everybody knows that.
I think everybody knows that you're
younger and you're better looking than
these people. Whether you was the
ugliest person [ __ ] alive. So that's
where the jealousy comes into it. And
like and the age. The age is a big thing
as well. It's not just about looks. It's
also about age.
You can go out, you can approach, you
can make friends, you can drink. These
people are sat at home. [ __ ]
um B. Okay,
Kevin wants to come in now. This is the real one.
>> You have a big [ __ ] news, PG.
>> okay? Get alive, Virgin.
See, they're obsessed. But they say
they've got a better life than me. They
say that they've got a better life than
me, but they're constantly stalking me
every single day on YouTube. But they've
got a better life than me. Don't think so.
Uh, it's not Kevin, you [ __ ] spasticated bastard.
You [ __ ] [ __ ] You [ __ ] spacker.
It's obviously not Kevin, you [ __ ]
Get a life. You need to get a life as
well, mate. You're on him as soon as I go live.
Yes, it wasn't him. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
That's why I kicked him. You [ __ ]
[ __ ] weirdo. You [ __ ] [ __ ] It
wasn't even him, you [ __ ] Mong.
Yeah, it doesn't matter if you're sub to
me. Go get a life.
Yeah, I'm sub to loads of people. And
what, bro? And what? Go get a life. Get
off of YouTube and get a life.
Anyways, Kevin, are you coming in or what?
I think you realize in the end you
[ __ ] up. That's why you're trying to
join. Doesn't matter if it's Sunday,
you're on here every day of the week.
So you ain't got a life I think. But
surely to god you knew it was never
going to work with the police. Surely
surely to god you loser. You knew that
that weren't going to work. That's why
you're trying to come in. You knew that
the police thing was never going to work
in the long run. Maybe two or three
times. You knew it was never going to
work. So why even? But again, you're
obsessed. You're an obsessed little virgin. So
you knew it was never going to work in
the end. So why even bother? That's what
I don't understand. Why even bother?
You was never going to win. Never ever
Yeah, but you're doing nothing every
day. Yeah, but you're doing nothing every day.
But you're doing nothing every day. I've
traveled all over the country for the
past 3 years. I've done some traveling
for 3 years. You haven't. So I'm taking
a break. You're on YouTube every [ __ ]
day, you weirdo.
Absolute weirdos on here, man. Absolute
weirdos on here. So, yeah,
you have to post some content on your channel. Yeah.
So, yeah. Why do you want to come in
just to put nudes up? That's so weird.
You people need to get a life.
[ __ ] get a life, mate.
I can't handle the truth. Really? You
want to come in hangouts and tell me the truth?
Handle the truth.
Handle the truth. Nah.
Everything you say is the truth about
your lives. Any I can handle that. I
just don't like people talking about
themselves so badly.
You know, you people calling yourself a
ma, you people calling yourselves skin.
It's not nice to hear people talk about
themselves like that. You know, it's
horrible to see people put themselves
down like that. And that's what you do.
You put yourselves down. You bully
yourselves cuz you don't talk about me.
You don't know me. So,
um I mean, I put the link up for anyone
to want to actually join and have a
conversation, but no one's joining. I
can more than handle the truth. But your
truth is you projecting every day on
YouTube. That's not the truth. Well,
it's the truth about your lives. Not my
life. [clears throat] Your lives.
Why do you come in and put your cameras
on? Wouldn't do that, would you? No. No.
Would never do that, would you? I wonder
why. I wonder why you people would never
put your cameras on.
I ain't saying anything. That's for you
people to figure out.
Did that gray cat ever did come out from YouTube?
Is my life that great? Um, is my life
Uh, well, compared to these people's on
here, yeah, compared to these people on
YouTube, yeah, in reality,
it's just normal. In reality, my life is
nothing special. But to these people on
here, yeah, it is because like I said
again, you're younger than them. You're
better looking than them. You got more
of a life than them. Just because I'm
chilling out now. I'm chilling out now.
Uh I don't need to name anything great
in my life. We're not We're not talking about me.
We're talking about you people. You fat
ugly little low lives.
That's what we're talking about. So I
don't need to name you anything. What's
great in my life? I'm not here to answer
to you about my life. Don't you worry
about my life, bro.
I mean, I get to do what I want. I'm
young. I'm better looking than these
people on here. I'm not skipped like
these people. I mean, that's enough.
That is enough, mate. That is enough to
get these people rattled. Jamie
Thompson, all of these other stalkers, you know.
I don't know about everything that's
happening. I just know that you people
can't take a day off of YouTube.
Everyone knows that.
And I don't stream for 5 hours a day.
And it's November, by the way. So, okay.
So, if I want to be on [ __ ] sake. So, if
I want to be on YouTube saving money for
December, I do this every year. And I
want to save money. Okay. So, but I do
it maybe once or twice.
Once or twice a year, maybe three times
a year. But the problem is is that you
people, even when it's a hot summer's
day, I'll start on YouTube.
What's What's the reason for that? Every
summer when it is a boiling hot day,
these people are on YouTube. And I've
seen it because when I've come back from
the beats, these people are on YouTube
every single day.
But they're hating on other people.
Doesn't make any sense.
I don't know what's happening. I just
know. I don't watch anyone but Monty.
Uh I can complain about others cuz I
actually go out. I leave my h I actually
leave the house. I've got a life. I
mean, I've got a life. So what do you
mean I can't complain? I've got a life.
I actually go out and live my life. So
what do you mean I can't complain? I've
took weeks off of YouTube before. You
people can't take a day off YouTube. So,
I can complain. I can complain because
you people can't take a day off of
YouTube. And I have. So, I can complain.
I don't watch him. I'm only subbed him,
but I don't watch him.
My brain used to fry when I used to watch Lays.
It used to give me a headache. That's
why I stopped going on it. Same
repeating self-proing losers. Same chat,
same atmosphere. That's the one that
used to make my brain fry. That's why I
stopped going on it.
But um No, not Monty's. No. Yeah.
I don't think so, bro. People that are
on YouTube every day like you people are
don't have jobs and girlfriends. It's
obvious. Your YouTube activity says otherwise.
That's all I'm saying. You can say
you've got all of these things or
whatever, but your YouTube activity
completely [ __ ] you up.
It doesn't lie to you. So, you can have
this fantasist life all you want, but we
all know that you people have got
nothing. We all know deep down what you
people are. So you can say you got kids,
you can say you got jobs, you can say
you've got a girlfriend, but we all know
that you people are low lives. So you
pro your YouTube activity gives you
away, mate. Simple as that. So um
and also it's what you do. It's it's not
even that you're on here. It's what you
do on here as well. It shows they've got
no life. Um it's it's also what you do.
Uh, not just the fact that you're on
here as well. Um, it's what you actually
do on here as well. I think that's a a
big thing that boys actually what they
do. They don't just pop in for like an
hour and say, "Oh, what's going on? Oh,
I gambled today. Oh, no." They don't
come in every day for an hour and chat.
Um, they literally sit on YouTube all
day hating, bro. So, it's also what they
do. It's what they do on here. Stalking,
um, the harassing, the hating. These
people are not happy in their lives.
Don't let them try and tell you
otherwise, bro. They're not happy in
their lives. I mean, you could Yeah, you
could maybe come on YouTube for an hour
a day. But you will see if you go on
LJ's channel. I used to do this when I
was younger and I used to go out, even
if it was only two years ago. I'd go out
on a f Well, no, it was a Friday. He
used to go live. I used to go out
Thursday as well. I used to go out on a
Friday. Before I used to go out on a
Friday, I used to go on his live stream
for 5 minutes
completely. Had 10 [ __ ] on me. went out
would come back like late at night and
it would be the same people on YouTube.
It would be the same people typing away
typing away, but they say they've got
lives. But these people say that they've
got lives and I'd be out for like six I
would be like uh
I would be like six seven
eight hours I'd be gone and there'd
still be the same people but they want
to talk [ __ ] about other people. Big big
big big difference.
So it's what they do on here. It's what
it's what they actually do on here as well.
Not me. I don't stalk anyone.
Nope. Never heard of it.
I wasn't alone. And stop trying to
change the subject because you know that
I'm right. You people sit on YouTube all day hating. So yeah,
it's obvious these people are just fat,
ugly skinned people that ain't got a
life. And the reason I've been on
YouTube is because I'm saving money for
December. I was saying to my mom said uh
semi right uh past when did I go out?
Two weeks ago. Did I go out two weeks
ago? Yeah, I can afford to go out. No, I
didn't stalk USA. No, I didn't. I told
her about herself and I weren't going to
let her walk all over me. No, I didn't
stalk her. Um know the definition of
stalking. No, I didn't stalk her. And
that's what that's not what stalking
means. And I was basically saying so is
that you might as well save your money for December.
you might as well like save money for
not going out two, three weeks for the
even though I can obviously I can afford
to go out but you you're best off just
carrying that money over to the next
month to be fair
because of um
yeah he is upset proper proper obsessed
that is stalking what he's doing is
stalking what I done to USA Izzy was not
big big difference I don't stalk that
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
yeah definitely definitely definitely
Definitely definitely upset and now the
police are not interested. Well, duh.
You was never going to win in the end
with the police anyways.
Obviously, you little copycat. What did
you think was going to happen? Yeah,
they come out because you kept crying to
them playing the victim. Yeah. Then I
reckon my solicitors got on to the
police. I think to be honest with you,
um that's probably why they're not doing
anything to be honest because you you
you break the you break the court order.
You've already you've already voided the
court order by posting about me. It's
like a restraining order. If you've got
a restraining order against someone and
that the other person contacts them, it's void.
It becomes automatically void. What was
even the point of it? It's because you
are obsessed. That is part of obsession.
Getting the police involved and and all
of that, that is proper proper
obsession, bro. Proper proper obsession.
You know, weird.
[ __ ] weird, bro.
I was watching some copycat videos
earlier, actually. You know, it's a real
thing. It's basically a cat copies another cat.
Yeah. It's a real thing, you know, cuz
cats like copy each other, is it? You
know, when there's like a group of cats, [ __ ] madness.
And then you just ended up in Amsterdam
the first time you went abroad.
I'm not so sure if that's where people
firstly go to be fair. I don't think
I've ever known someone to go to
Amsterdam the first time, but a copycat.
My sister's boyfriend's been there a
couple of times, but not the first. Not
the first time. I think it was the third
or fourth. I don't think anyone goes
there the first time. Got to be 1% of people.
It's got to be 1%. I think it's got to
be 1% of people.
I'm the only one in my family that's
been to Amsterdam. No one else has been
to the Netherlands.
Yay. But you know, they It's not the
first place people go.
But somehow the copycat ended up there.
Somehow the copycat ended up there. [snorts] Little copycat. Little copy.
I hate cats. I love dogs. Some people
hate cats and dogs.
Yeah, he [ __ ] his own [ __ ] up because
the thing is is the thing is, bro, is
that it voids the order because he's
posting about me and where my solicitors
probably got on to them. Um,
you know, I shouldn't have [ __ ]
blamed the the police at first to be
fair because it's only what they've been
saying to them. But the thing is it's
you're never going to win in the long
run because the amount of [ __ ] that I've
got on this [ __ ]
Nah, it's not it that that candy man is.
So I don't understand it to be honest
why you'd even waste the police's time.
And I've got evidence as well. So
it's just madness, isn't it? He needs to
he needs to get laid. That's what he
needs to lose his virginity.
That's what he needs to do. That's why I
did when you finally lose it.
Ricky, why did you disappear when I put
up my approaching videos as well? You
went quiet. I put an approaching video
up uh was it two weeks ago? That's when
I last went out. You seem to disappear.
No, Dusty Showers is that candy man, bro.
I can smell that [ __ ] and Milo. I can
[snorts] smell him like burnt popcorn.
See, they're so disabled on here. They
give themselves away.
Dusty Showbiz. Yeah, he's under about a
million. He's He's that slim cognito
account as well. Proper proper sad
bastard. People that are double my age
trolling behind fake accounts.
They're [ __ ] sad, aren't they?
So, yeah. If you ask me who I like, um,
I'd say I even like that Triple H, even
though he was a bit of like a [ __ ]
stirer. I think he's all right. You
know, Triple H, Chris, Kieran. There is
people I like on here. I just think most
of them are just biased nons lovers.
Now I can't stop thinking about him.
Every time I see a cat, Siri, every time
I see a cat, now I can't. It just
reminds you of him because the copycat.
See, you got me out here now.
Like with a little
Yeah, he was cool with Monty, but then
he switched on Monty or something. Yeah,
that Hugh was cool, but then I caught
him talking [ __ ] about me. Bit like Ricky.
And then once they get caught talking
[ __ ] about you, they never come back.
Oh, speak of the devil.
Are you all right, Captain?
>> All right, bro.
>> Yeah, I was just talking about you. Did
you hear me?
>> I've just got on. Just come on there,
lad. I was on that Sea last night, you know.
>> Proper obsessed it.
>> He was live about [ __ ] about [ __ ]
3:00 this morning. So, I went in for a
bit. He was just on about when he met
you and that.
>> Oh my god. We've heard all of these
stories before. Triple H.
>> Crazy in a lad. It's repeat. It's
repeating, isn't it?
>> Why? Yeah. All right. He's a bit You
have to admit he's a bit of a copycat in it.
>> He's a strange one life, but he's
>> Yeah. But you know, Do you know what
that means? A copycat.
>> He's Do you know what he said? >> What?
>> He said that uh he has went to Chinatown
or something and um you stories
>> and you know what I commented?
>> I don't want anything to do with him. I
want the Virgin to leave me alone.
Triple H. I don't want to know him.
>> Yeah. O but do you know do you know what
it means a copycat?
>> Yeah, you're copying off someone else.
>> Well, have [laughter] you have you heard
about it before?
>> Yeah, thank you.
>> You having a nice roast today?
>> I don't know what I'm having. I might go for dinner.
>> Yeah, I had some chicken and chips, but
I'm going to have a Chinese later, bro.
>> I had a Chinese.
>> Oh, [ __ ] Did you see the football
better do, bro?
>> One goal won it.
>> [ __ ] Spenny more. The bastards, man.
Do you know how many shots on goal he
had as well? I should have scored that.
>> Yeah, 10. They had 10 minutes at a time as well.
>> He had [snorts] about 20 shots on goal
as well. Yeah.
>> Yeah, bro. I had a Yeah, I just put 50
pound on it, but I didn't win. Could
have done with that money, mate. You
know what I mean? 200
>> I was um I was uh I was waiting on City,
mate. Man, City [ __ ] I took City.
>> How much did you How much did you bet on it?
>> I had 20 quid. 20 quid, but they had uh >> Yeah,
>> he had Chelsea, Coventry, City,
and there was the other team.
>> My mom My mom My mom said, "Oh, I've
never heard of Spennymore. I've heard of
it. It's a It's a place in the
Northeast, isn't it?"
>> Yeah, there's a Yeah. Yeah,
>> I know. I I know that cuz I've been I've
been to the Northeast, is it? So, I know,
>> man. But [ __ ] um You've never been a
copycat, is it?
>> No, don't cop. No, no, I don't need you
copy me, lad.
>> So, when when are you on the drink again?
>> I'm not going to be on it till December
now, I think. Bro,
>> I was thinking I was thinking to keep an
offer as well.
>> You might do you know what it is, bro?
You might as well just save your like
money in November and then use it for
December, the most expensive month. It
makes sense, isn't it? To me,
>> just get flat out, lad. >> Huh?
>> And just get flat out.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Like mid December, like New
Year's or even even if you want to go
out New Year's Eve, is it [ __ ] I like
Boxing Day, mate.
Yeah, it's good, isn't it? Yeah.
>> I don't drink I don't drink Christmas
day and they like I don't bother at all.
>> No, there's no point in it.
>> [ __ ] have you dinner with that, man?
You stuffed down. I like
>> You know what's lovely? You know when
you go on a little a lovely date to a
steakhouse and you have a nice bit of wine?
>> Uh a glass of red with a steak. Lovely lad.
>> Bit bit of red or white wine. Yeah. It's
[ __ ] nice, isn't it, bro? All I
>> I hate cats, man. Do you? I hate cats.
>> Horrible little things, mate. I [laughter]
Well, I like dogs in it.
>> Have you still got your little dog like
>> No, it wasn't mine. It was my It was my
sisters. But he still come.
>> No, I need to get I want to get like a M
Frenchie. Like a Mel one. You know, like
um like a dotted one, you know, like a
Mel. It's like dot. It's like black and
white, isn't it?
>> I used to have a Frenchy me.
Got rid of
>> snow. Got
>> rid of it.
>> Having a bit me having a beer. We saw we
didn't know what it would be like around the band.
>> Kevin, who's Kevin?
>> Oh, you know that Kevin Murphy Scout?
>> Yeah, he's all right. Actually, he's
that scouter in he
>> Yeah, I've got I've got beef with him,
bro. You know you know the story in it.
>> No, I don't know what that about. I
don't really get involved in it, mate.
>> You going to go Liverpool again for a
night out? You liked it in it? And then
maybe mate, it was [ __ ] quality. It
was good. We live that was good.
>> It's good New Year's Eve, isn't it?
>> The hotel we stayed in was quite light.
>> Huh? Was Have you ever been one of them easy hotels?
>> Yeah, in Sheffield.
>> Yeah, they're tiny. I'm the man.
>> Yeah, they are to be fair, but they're
cheap, isn't it?
>> Yeah, they're cheap enough like I Who
did you go with yourself?
>> No, there's loads of us, lad.
>> Oh, yeah.
You spent a lot in it.
>> Spent about 300. Yeah, that was gambling.
>> Then is it? Yeah.
>> You spent lots on a night out before in it?
>> I've done a few. I' had a look here cuz
I play the g I'm going bandits and that
me. But I don't really bother with them
now. There's no like old school ones
blueprints. I don't really like them.
>> I was tempted to play like online
roulette the other day. Like a big
session, you know.
>> [ __ ] roulette, man. It's pointless. But
>> you can win a Hey,
>> you can win though, isn't it? It's
>> [ __ ] very rare win.
>> Yeah, nowadays.
>> Why? I I won 500. I won 500 from 100
like last box, but now
>> I was in the I went to betting shop
yesterday. I done me back, right? >> Yeah.
>> And the rope like there was um F machine
next to where I was filling me in that
and there's three zeros on the roulette table now.
>> Yeah, there is. There is. Yeah,
>> that's mad that.
>> Yeah, it is. And you've got people
there's someone playing it as well and I
thought like why the [ __ ] would you play
like a like what's got three zeros
playing the one that's got one zero like
the [ __ ] brain dead some people are
like yeah I mean I've played I've played
it but not like for a long long time but
if you if you go Lad Brooks I think it's
still one zero is it lad Brooks yeah
it's like a global one. Yeah, the global
one. Yeah. Yeah.
>> But that's a [ __ ] That is, isn't it?
You know, when it goes like [ __ ] 10
to one, it
had that happen a few times. You got
like a few quid on a number and it gives
you 10 to one.
>> Yeah. It's nice if it gives you 100 to
one, don't it?
>> I've had one a few times, have you?
>> No, I don't think I've not played it
that that much to be fair, bro.
>> For it to happen, is it? >> Yeah.
>> What's the like what's the what's the
what's the best chance of winning now? I
think the football in it.
>> Football's way forward, lad. Yeah, it
is. All right.
>> It isn't it? Yeah. I I want to do I'm
going to do a double both teams to score
again, bro, at some point. I'm going to
I want to put like 250 on it, bro.
>> [ __ ] Liverpool, man. He's I think he
should get sacked. That's lock me. Like
he's [ __ ] They've only won [ __ ]
three the last 11 games or something.
>> Do you know what you should do? You
should do three correct score. That's
That's massive money, is it? But trying
to get that.
>> It's massive money though, ain't it?
>> Looking ridiculous. Some coin. Yeah.
>> You have You've tried it before though, is it? >> N
I've had a few [ __ ] singles. Correct.
But I think Yeah, I fancy um today. I
fancy Arsenal to one m.
>> Yeah. How much will you put on it?
>> I don't know. I don't know if I'm
putting on to walk up or not.
>> Yeah, the book is far now from where I
live. You have It's like a 30 minute
walk. It's only [ __ ] It's about 10:15
for me. Like can't be ass.
>> Yeah, that's the Yeah. You don't do
online anymore, is it?
>> N can't. >> Yeah.
>> You was You was prolific, weren't you? Online?
>> I used to be wild. I've had a [ __ ] a
few bad losses online.
>> You remember when you used to go on the roulette?
>> You didn't play online as well. [laughter]
>> You're a crazy [ __ ] Sure.
>> Would you say I think you've played
roulette more than me in it?
>> Nah, I don't know. When he used to go, [laughter] >> uh,
>> when he used to go to the book, Yeah. He
used to only have a [ __ ] Well,
obviously when I was uh when I was
younger, I was wild on it, but then I
[ __ ] I chilled out. I didn't really
bother going like on splots in the book.
He's not allowed.
>> Yeah, as you get as you get older, you
don't do it as much, is it?
>> I strange that though, is it? It's weird. Yeah.
>> The same with the drink though, is it? I
bet three four years ago you used to
drink a lot more than you do now. I do
like a drink. Like, don't get us wrong,
but I'm not I don't like
>> I can get I can give or take, but when I
have a drink, I like to have a drink if
you know what I mean. Like I don't like good skin.
>> Especially when in the summer is it like
you could be in for like three weeks and
one day you'll just want to go out in it
one day randomly.
>> So, next year man, the summer I'll be
out more and
>> yeah, the World Cup next year in
be flat out.
Bless you then.
>> Bless you in life.
>> Um I've seen a clip that someone came in
your live. Someone called Sarah Russ
giving you advice or something, wasn't
it? I seen it on someone's channel.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You I think you was in your
nest calls when she when it happened,
didn't it? You was sleeping.
>> You sleeping, didn't it?
>> She was uh she was giving you some good advice like
>> Yeah, but she didn't understand like
some of the things that I was trying to
say as well.
Like they just miss Do you know what
that means? I feel like they just miss your struggles. >> Yeah.
>> Do you know what that means?
>> Yeah. I think Sean misses you as a
friend, me, lad.
>> I don't I don't want to [ __ ] I don't
want to know that skin version.
Why don't you go be his friend?
>> He just I watched I watched an hour of
him yesterday and he was just talking
about you when he has met and things
like I thought I thought myself I think
wants to go back and be your friend. You
don't even you don't even act this way
towards a [ __ ] woman you love. Triple
H. Do you know? Have you ever been in
love yet? You don't even act that way to
someone that you love. Is it lad?
>> I think you can you be his new friend?
>> No. Why?
>> Cuz he's a [ __ ] freak. [laughter]
>> Yeah, but you can go you could you could
have a drink together. You, him and
Monty. You remember Do you remember him
and Monty used to be friends?
>> Best friends in it. Yeah. They were
mates. You bother with that Monty now
>> I don't talk to him. I don't talk to
him, bro. Do you still watch him?
>> Nah, I don't. He's just just them games
in the bar.
>> You remember when I went to remember we
went to Birmingham? [laughter] >> Yeah,
>> yes, she was greasy. She seemed all
right when I watched the clips back there, lad.
>> You like Grezy?
>> Yeah, he's just on about Sarah there. I
know that there's an account here that
keeps coming in saying, "Oh, Peter, you
can't let these [ __ ] women win." I
think they're mocking me, is it?
>> Yeah, they are.
>> They're mocking me. [laughter] Yeah,
they're catchy saying, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Sean said he's had dates on that
um dating site, dating what they call
them, dating websites. And that Sean
said he's had dates.
>> Yeah. With a [ __ ] [ __ ] with spastics. Yeah.
You still you still want the apps?
>> Nah, I don't know.
>> You like You like the single life now.
You said it.
You like the single life now, isn't it? >> You
like the single life now, don't you? Oh,
>> bless you then.
Hey, [ __ ] hell.
>> So, what are you doing? What are you
doing next Saturday, you think?
M you want a drink? But I don't think
I'm going to bother. Like I'm going to I
might keep myself out. >> Huh?
>> I might keep myself out of boxing. Not
interested in a drink.
>> Yeah, that's what Yeah. Yeah.
>> You feel like [ __ ] for days. It's not where
>> But the last time I went out my head
Well, if you stick to beer, it's not
it's not as bad, is it? But sometimes
you get carried away in it and you just
go on. But if you stick to beer, you're
all right for the most part. Is it? I
like that star of prime and I think I
drink a lot of Guinness me.
>> I love Guinness, but I love Guinness.
>> I get a nice pint of Guinness or some
giant pints of it in there.
>> Yeah, if you go to like a nice brewer,
you know, nice pub. Yeah, it's it's good.
>> I got a pint in Weather Spoons there
with me breakfast and I took it back. It
was [ __ ] awful.
>> You took it back? It was awful, lad.
Really? One the worst paint. It was
vile. Like watered down in that. It's
[ __ ] awful. I can't drink.
>> Would they give you a money back?
>> No, I just change it. I got a um was me.
>> How How much was that? How much was that be
>> in there? But uh [snorts] the
it was the cool£28 or something in there. But
>> [ __ ] cheap, bro. That's so cheap.
>> Is about 320.
>> Yeah, it's cheap, isn't it? That's
really cheap, bro.
>> I tell you, I'm getting a bit worried
about [ __ ] £8 a pint.
>> You what, lad?
>> London's like £8 a pint now.
>> Yeah, it's [ __ ] expensive to live London life. >> Yeah.
>> Ridiculous, man.
>> You know where it originates from? Guinness. >> Ireland.
>> Yeah. Have you? How did you know?
>> I don't know. It's an Irish drink. It's what they
me and you should go to the factory. My >> m
They did. [snorts] Yeah.
>> Then he went in, he walked out. He was
[ __ ] pissed walking out. You know
where you get the samples? [laughter]
>> It's expensive though, is it?
>> I'm not sure, lad. I don't know what
it's like over there.
>> Well, he walked out pissed. [laughter]
>> I I
>> imagine that G walking into the Guinness
walking out pissed.
Hey, that seaside Max struggling now and
he's um he's on that drink all the time.
I've just seen a video he's put up
there. He's back on the drink again. He
wasing about um the rice he warmed up
and I said it wasn't the rice. It was the drink.
>> The drink. You can't Mark.
>> I don't I don't watch him, bro. We usually watch
>> I like watch a bit of seaside now and again. Like
>> they call him the fish man, isn't it?
>> I John Lavry calls him Big Junior. [laughter]
>> Yeah. You like LJ is it?
>> No, he's a Mong. [snorts] [laughter]
>> You used to like him though, don't it?
>> No, he used to be all right. He used to
be good crack to be honest at one point.
But then he's just a [ __ ]
>> I I used to like I used to like it when
you used to go in there and call him John. [snorts]
>> He's blocked me now and he I'm blocked. >> Wow. [snorts]
>> It gives Tim a bit of stick, doesn't he? That lavry. >> Yeah,
>> Mr. to be skimp bacon that go slug.
>> So when you go out drinking again
>> you going to do any you going to do any
approaches lad when you go out again?
>> No I don't I don't really go out that me
I go and drinking [ __ ] I like to play
darts and pool and that me bless you.
>> Do you bother with any sporting
activities like Peter?
>> Nah not really bro I have played before. So
>> you what are you going to do? Just go to
like a local pub or you going to go Newcastle?
Um not sure yet lad. Boxing day normally where every
normally go to uh go to Darham and that
on a boxing day good flat good s there and then
loads of pubs in Darham.
You you off work and that
>> why was it too tiring?
>> No I'm off work.
Oh, but you going work against mine. >> Mhm.
>> It's lo [ __ ]
Are you um [snorts]
Oh, is the phone all right? Is the phone
been all right still? Yeah.
>> It's been bang on, lad. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Go on.
>> Yeah. [ __ ] what you doing there, lad?
>> Just chilling out to be honest, bro. Yeah.
>> Post the link. Post the link in PD. Let
some [ __ ] in. [snorts and clears throat]
>> Okay. One sec. One second.
>> That Tim Eldridge get some stick, don't he?
>> Yeah. You like him though, ain't it?
>> Tim's all right, man. I don't mind him.
But I think he's getting it beyond help now. Like
>> they they all go for him in it.
>> Yeah. They got him like a [ __ ] fly
around [ __ ] aren't they?
>> Yeah. [ __ ] [laughter]
I hate coffee.
>> Yeah, I seen Monty man upload a few
videos. Um, wasn't that emailed another
fell or something? [laughter]
>> Did they? Let me see.
>> And now you took it off now. I was in last night.
See, it was like Scotty put
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No, it's still
there. It's still there. It's still
>> So, what is she cheating on him?
>> That way, I don't know.
>> Would you give her one that? Nasty viol
man. A lot of people rave about her.
She's stinking I think. Like
>> Yeah. These people don't leave their
house though in it. So
>> would you give do you like that Lisa?
>> Nah. Would you do you like her? >> No.
>> Would you let her give you a [ __ ]
>> No. The [ __ ]
Lavry likes her, don't he?
>> [ __ ] that, bro. Have you seen that autumn rose?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. She looks all right.
Yeah, me and her got war. I said that
she's a little she's a slag that uses
filters, isn't it?
>> She's Well, you like her. Yeah,
>> she looks all right. I think the one for you.
>> Maybe maybe you could try it with that
autumn, is it? >> Why?
>> Cuz she I don't know where she from. I
don't know where she's from, to be
honest. I I don't know. Obviously
England, is it? But but if she said to
you like, "Let's go on a date." Would
you do it?
>> Probably, lad. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Why not give it a whirl? Would it?
>> It was close to me, like obviously, but
like if she was [ __ ] London, I would be off.
>> What about if she was like Glasgow?
>> No. So far. [laughter]
>> Yeah. But it's still up your way, is it?
>> Oh, bless you. Bless you in your little northeast words.
your little nose sightings.
>> You live with your mom now. Have you got
your own place? >> Yeah.
>> Have you got your own place now? Are you your mom's?
>> No, I'm living in a tent. What? Like Monty man? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, I'm living. You and your little
northeast sayings. Do you like that? Grezy,
>> have you done
>> I find I find I find the northeast
dialect quite cute. Peter. >> Yeah.
>> Have you done cocaine since you done it
with Mike and Tim?
>> Nah. You tried it like you tried it a
year. Last time you done it was like a
year ago. No.
>> It was a while ago. Like I don't bother
with it now. Me give back.
>> You used to be bad on that, didn't you?
>> I used to like it like when you used to
go and drink and but I don't I don't
bother with it now. Me.
>> Did you Did you owe like dealers money and stuff?
>> No, I never used cash with me. I I
wasn't bad at it. Like I just I need to
get one on me.
>> Michael Michael does it in it. >> Oo. >> Yeah.
>> Is he bang on that?
>> Yeah. Do you remember?
>> No. I know he's done with you and Tim. I
don't know. He's bad. I
>> remember that phrase. [laughter]
>> Yeah. Yeah. Man, he tried to set you up, didn't he?
>> Yeah. Me, me and him though. When we
done when we done the cocaine, me and
him. Yeah. We was laughing our ass off, bro. It
>> know you done it with him.
>> Yeah. That's the last time I done it
with him four years ago. I think it was
about 3, four years ago.
>> Oh yeah,
I did it. He's the He used to laugh at
everything in it.
>> I couldn't like what?
>> Yeah, you used to you hate him.
>> I like him like that.
>> Bless you.
>> Bless you then.
You ever you ever been to Manchester for
for a night out? You said,
>> "No, I haven't been to Manchester, mate." No,
>> it's a good night out there.
>> I know a lot of people who say good
night, but well, I go once soon. Well,
I'll go, but I don't know when
I've ever had that. Yeah.
>> You remember when that bum was talking
about your shits, the weirdo?
>> No, I like that bomb, mate. I didn't
like him. I thought he was funny in me.
>> I think he was a [ __ ]
>> No, deep down I think you like the bomb me. No,
>> he was all right, man. He was a
>> You could have an aist.
>> Oh, yeah. He's full of [ __ ] all day
long. Yeah, [laughter]
>> he's a bull, you know.
>> You remember when he said, Do you
remember when he tried saying he had
kids in Spain and that?
>> Yeah. And then he had all this money,
but he had a pair of bad ass fluts on.
He lived above a cab. [laughter]
>> You know what, Chip Rates? I think
you're a pretty good [ __ ] I think we'll
get on just fine, you know. So, um,
>> you seem like a pretty good gun.
>> Can you upload the middle video?
>> Uh, I think I've still got it. Yeah,
>> if upload it. I want to watch that. I
can't really remember that. I think
>> I don't think No, I don't think I have
the video of where like I was I have the
video where I was staying. I was
>> walking around Middlesbor.
>> I don't have it anymore. That one, bro.
Yeah, that was ages ago. That was my
other phone, didn't it? Don't have it anymore.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah.
>> I went to the shopping center.
Yeah. How did you go to Boris? The center eye.
>> Yeah, it was [ __ ] It's a scary place,
bro. It is a scary place.
>> All right. All right.
>> Would you Would you Would you walk
around at night in Middlesbrough?
>> N. Yeah. Well, I have before. I've been
a few times for a drink, but it's rough as [ __ ]
>> I remember I dropped my phone in a car,
but the cab driver Yeah. He he he he
told me, "Oh, you dropped it." He gave
it back. Like the people there are nice.
Funny enough, though. The people there
are friendly, but I mean compared to
London, but the the place itself is [ __ ] >> I
>> cuz where I was staying, there was like
a landlord that um looks after like the
house and that and he was he was a cool guy, man.
>> It's a [ __ ] dumb borrow. Like that's
where Dawson lives, doesn't he? >> Yeah,
but like like people in Newcastle and
like Middlesbrough more nicer than
people, you know, London. London,
they're [ __ ] [ __ ] here, bro.
>> I hate people from London. You met
anyone from there? London. They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> I like I like you and where you're from. Chip rate.
>> Can I come and stay with you? >> Yeah. >> Really?
>> I'll try and get you a woman if you ever
come up this way. The roads again, lad.
>> I don't You don't need to try to get me
a woman. The woman come to me in
Newcastle. She preached.
>> Oh, yeah. You had a bit of in Newcastle, haven't you?
>> Yeah. And she said, "Oh, you're
handsome." And we started kissing and
she started biting my lip and that is it. [laughter]
>> Did you get on land?
>> Yeah, [snorts] we So what? So we could
when I come up here, we can meet some We
can meet people. We can go on a double date.
>> I has Peter Belly got a lot of uh
history in Elephant and Castle.
>> What's Elephant and Castle?
>> Oh, it's a place in London. I have a lot
of history in Elephant and Castle, Mr.
B. That's where I met my mama. The
American is my mama, isn't it?
>> Who USA is he?
>> Yeah, my that's my mama.
What do you think of that?
>> Do you still keep in contact with that?
Is he like PJ?
>> No, none of that.
>> Do you messages still or not?
>> What the original one?
>> Any of them? >> Nah.
>> You know, do you remember the USA? The
the family knows about me and that they
all know about me.
You wrote to one of the family. Are you
Who was that then?
>> Oh, it was Morgan, wasn't it? [ __ ] Morgan. [laughter]
>> Remember remember
>> who's seeing that Charles?
>> Yeah, I messaged the dad and the dad was
like, "You little shit."
>> He was like, "You little [ __ ] messaging
me." That's what he said. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Thank you.
>> Right. One minute. I'll be back. I need
to go downstairs two seconds.
>> All right then.
Oh, Triple H. Bless Triple H. So, his
little northeast dialect greasy. Bless him.
Is that cute? I think everyone likes Triple H.
Is that a lot? What happened in Elephant
and Castle? Grezy, [snorts]
I can't get attached anymore because
he's already found his mama.
Stop mocking me.
Stop because he's already found his mama. You know your mama. Yeah.
Imagine me and Triple H on the drink. Huh?
Yeah. When I was working, when I was
doing the deliveries, the deliveries, it
kept sending me to Elephant and Castle. >> [laughter]
>> Yeah, he kept sending me there.
[snorts] Oh gosh.
Why did you see me in Tony's yesterday,
Grezy? I wasn't trolling him, was I? [laughter]
I wasn't trolling him, was I? Nah, [snorts] >> [laughter]
>> What the [ __ ]
>> Yo. Hey.
>> I was saying uh I was saying that's
where I met my mama. Yeah.
>> You know what someone wrote? Yeah. They
said Peter B can't get attached anymore
because he's already found his mama.
These people are sad on hearing it, bro. [laughter]
Yeah. They're trolling me. They're like
mockabe cuz you know things that you
say. Yeah. They repeat the same things
you said. Is it on here?
>> Did you Did you like the look of that Morgan then?
>> No. What? I've not seen that.
How have you not how have you not seen her?
>> I've seen that child. I never thought of
that child on yesterday. I don't think
I've ever seen that Morgan mate.
>> That's my mama trip. You should try and
get with her. You might like you in it.
Did you write a child? >> Huh?
>> Did you write the Charles?
>> I wrote the [ __ ] lot of him. >> What? >> Huh?
>> What did you say to him? I just said to
her like, "You need to sort out your
[ __ ] daughter. You should have raised
your daughter properly."
>> Charles was a girlfriend.
>> Oh, no. With Charles. Oh, no. With him.
I said, "Uh, are you still with Morgan?"
He said, "Yeah." I said, "Oh, your
girlfriend's been cheating on you."
>> What did he say?
>> He started getting mad and that and I
messaged her ex as well and he said,
"Oh, if you come here, I'm going to kill
you in that." He was getting mad, bro.
Do you remember that, Damon? You know,
you remember that in the voice not?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Hi. Hi.
>> Well, you heard what he was saying. [laughter] >> Yeah.
>> Who was the root cause of all that?
>> You. [laughter]
>> What? All me.
>> So, where did you meet this Morgan at
>> outside the Eminem shop? I've still got
the approach. I recorded it.
>> What? Eminem World?
>> Yeah. In London.
>> You went there with Sean as well, didn't you?
>> Yeah. Yeah. It was basically outside it.
>> Just put all this behind you.
>> No, I don't want to know that virgin
wage. I don't want to know that [ __ ]
skin virgin. Is it? >> Yeah.
>> He'll never stop in it, I don't think. Is it? >> Nah.
>> He's taking a cart, isn't he? [laughter]
>> Will he ever Will he ever stop though?
>> Is he taking out a car? Nah,
>> he is Peter. He said last night on his
live you caught the 2029 or something.
>> What? Say the year again.
>> 2029 or something, I think. [laughter]
>> Yeah. What What kind of court date is that?
>> I know. I was thinking I thought that's for it. >> Huh?
>> He said he said on his live streaming.
Yes. last night he said yeah like he put
his life at risk putting posters about him
>> yeah well he tried to get my money
stopped so he deserved it [ __ ] silly little [ __ ]
do you remember the posters do you
remember when I agreed with him Triple H
do you remember that name and I kept
saying yeah I'm going to do the poster
I'm going to do the posters bro and no
one believed me no one believed me and
then the all of a sudden the videos come
up and it [laughter]
>> was posting to like the the houses and
stuff you like
>> yeah but I know you had is you she with
no evidence you well you can't really
post stuff like that a man killed that lad [laughter]
>> you're joking in it
>> n honestly you could also could
>> yeah well he shouldn't be trolling on
YouTube and trying to get people's money stopped
>> I know but there's trolling and then
there's you taking it over the top
>> yeah but he no but he he called the
benefits to try to get my money stopped
that's that's modern YouTube [laughter]
so that's more that's modern YouTube
then is it
>> he tried to walk Get your door money. >> Yeah.
>> So that's modern YouTube then.
>> [ __ ] hell, man.
>> I can't get over I can't get over the
Monty and Money Mike video. And Timmy,
do you remember when Timmy was shouting,
"I'm going to knock him out." Remember?
>> Yeah, it was a beauty.
>> Money Mike was like, "We're all going to
get nicked. We're going to get nicked." [laughter] >> Yeah.
>> What was that? But you know what made it
funny? That was over YouTube. That
madest YouTuber on me.
>> He said, "Do you want to go for a pint
or do you want to do it dirty?" I'll
never forget that. Do you want to go for a drink?
>> Yeah. Do you want to go for a drink or
do you want to do it bad? [laughter]
What have you said? Do it bad. Is it
wasn't that [snorts]
mas I think was think Mike was stick
enough for him.
Yeah, I'm going to knock him out. But
you know what? I I got Monty onto
YouTube. So, if I didn't get him on
here, this wouldn't be happening, isn't it?
>> Yeah. You've had an He's had an ad run
over this YouTube man. He's had a bit of
[ __ ] Annie over it.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> You remember the teen dating app?
>> Say that again.
>> You remember the teen dating app? Ah, it
was wild. That like [laughter]
>> you think it was done on purpose?
>> I don't think he's meant to show it, was
he? [clears throat] >> Huh?
>> I don't He's meant to show it, was he?
And then [ __ ] people spotted it.
>> Yeah. Did he dating app?
>> My bad.
>> Grey said I'm the root cause for many things.
>> He's right. Like he is Grezy. I he
causes a lot of trouble
>> to me. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Like most of LT's fights has been
because of me in it.
>> Yeah. You've caused London Taylor.
>> Yeah. But Grievy calls a lot of [ __ ] the
other day. He got me on this Tik Tok
here and it was winding me up, bro.
[ __ ] winding me up. These [ __ ] on Tik Tok.
>> Oh, you're on Tik Tok?
>> Yeah, I was on Tik Tok arguing with this
white knight and they [ __ ] kicked me.
The [ __ ] bastards.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. [laughter]
>> [ __ ] [ __ ] in it. >> Yeah.
Are you behind Tik Tok?
>> Oh, you're on TikTok? Yeah.
>> So, what's up? Wait, what's the exact
phone you got again? The Samsung what?
>> A25, I think.
>> A25. Okay, I'm going to type that. I'm
going to get the same one as you. I'm
going to be a copycat.
>> Okay. Is that right?
>> A25. Yeah. >> Mhm.
Can I be a little copycat and copy you? >> Yeah.
>> Are you sure? >> Yeah.
>> Are you in bed?
>> Laid in bed, lad. Just chilling right
out. All right. Having a nice chill out day today.
>> Oh, bless you then.
Yeah. Say, man. I'm I'm I'm tired. I'm
Yeah, I'm tired, bro.
>> Would you ever meet Tim Eldridge again?
No, he's a [ __ ] spacker.
>> He's a spacker, isn't it?
>> Would you meet Bino again?
>> Nah, bro. They're [ __ ] freaks. I'd
meet Toasty again, though. You remember
Toaster? You remember me and Toast on Roulette?
>> Have you got the video?
>> No, that was years old, bro.
>> [ __ ] hell. Yeah. Lovely. It was
lovely, though, wasn't it?
>> Yeah, it was good. That eye.
Do you ever use the word lovely? >> I
>> That was a lovely That was a lovely
video in the roulette.
>> Did you win?
>> Yeah, we won a couple of hundred. >> Yeah.
You remember when you said to me, "Can
you do them voices again?" You used to
like the voices in it.
I the wrong [ __ ] wild.
Right. Hey, well, I'm going to jump off
P. I'll if you're on late, I'll jump on
about that, bro. What happened? You used
to like the little voices, didn't you? >> Yeah. >> Hello.
What? No. Can anyone do it like me?
>> No one can do it like you, Peter.
>> You You can You can try, Triple.
>> You can You need to message me on
WhatsApp. We need to arrange this meet up, lad.
Oh, do us a favor. >> Yeah.
>> Unblock me in your chat. You blocked me ages ago.
>> Did I?
>> Yeah. I can't pay a title. It's not
coming up. So, you've blocked me.
>> One second.
>> One second. Uh,
>> now I need to find your [ __ ] channel. You can.
>> There's so many Triple H accounts. >> [laughter]
>> the [ __ ] side there.
>> I think I've got like 38 subscribers, I think.
>> And you comment on someone's video and
then I can click on it cuz there's so many ones.
>> Um, yeah. One minute.
>> Oh, I think I got you. Actually, I think
I do. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Okay. Try type now. Um,
join 5th of August 2020.
That's got to be you, in it.
Am I the root cause for a lot of things, Grezy?
So, how do I get over my mom abandoning
me then, Grezy?
How do I get over like being abandoned?
What do I have to do now? H hello,
you're back. I don't even know. Why did
I block you? What the [ __ ]
I didn't even realize I blocked you.
Why? Why did I block you?
Because he's already found his mama.
But let me put the link back up
because he's already found his mama.
Remember sign not Peter Belly's mama. Grezy
signal Peter Belly's mama. >> [snorts]
>> Do you've got the A25? Triple H. The A25,
he said the phone's been spot on. Greasy.
Grezy, there's a iPhone. The iPhone 16.
Is that is that still a good phone?
They're selling it for £700 in August.
This phone is This [ __ ] charger is dodgy, bro.
This is this iPhone 16 a decent phone.
iPhone XR. Oh, bless you then. Bless.
Bless you then.
Oh, bless. I'm on the Samsung G. I'm on
a Samsung Galaxy Fold
sick greasy and the phone is absolutely beautiful.
It's [ __ ] handsome. It's a handsome phone.
I think I can get the seven on contract
if I want to, but I don't want to.
I don't like contract phones.
This fold six greaves is absolutely lush.
It's a flagship.
Oh, what a cute thing to call it.
Greavvesy. A flagship phone.
Is that cute? Grieves your flagship. [snorts] A
I've never seen anyone with it.
I've never seen anyone with the Samsung
Galaxy Fold other than me.
I don't think I have. Have you? Nah. [laughter]
Nah, I don't think I have. They're
bloody lovely though.
They're bloody lovely.
Elephant and castle.
A lot of history for Peter Belly and
Elephant and Castle. Grezy,
did you see that? I said that. There's a
lot of history for Peter Belly and
Elephant in Castle.
I said to that account, why didn't she
tell me that she was my mommy? And the
account said she wanted to keep it a secret.
She wanted to keep it a secret, Greezy.
Is that true?
You wanted to keep me and my mommy a secret.
What? Like, oh,
a little copycat.
Yeah, I was going to do that. You know, little copycat.
Yeah, I was actually going to do that, you know,
you know, like you used to, Isabella. >> Okay.
I was going to do that on that video.
You know where I said you skint copycat
on my video? I was actually going to put
that as the avatar. I actually was.
Who's that? Greasy. [laughter]
I was going to [laughter] Who's that?
Yeah. What should we name it? What
[laughter] should we name it?
I'm dead, bro. I'm [laughter]
I'm going to change the avatar of that
video I done to this.
It's got green eyes as well. Oh, [laughter]
yeah. But who does it remind you of? What person? Copycat.
Why your face? You look copycat.
Yeah, but who who does it remind you of?
Like what what person on YouTube? [laughter] One second. >> [laughter]
>> I mean, I'll give you an example of a copycat grezy [laughter]
One second graves day.
I'm going to I'm going to show you. Yeah. Huh? No. [clears throat]
I've just changed my avatar on my um
photo by the way. [laughter]
Well, if you go on my video, right, you
can see I've changed the avatar. [laughter]
Look, look on my channel, I've changed
the I've changed the avatar.
Copy. They copy a cat.
What? Did you see it? Did you see it?
What did you see what I done?
Yeah, but what [laughter] does Yeah, but
what does what does a virgin copy with?
What does what does
what does Virgin Boy copy with?
Yeah, but how does he how does he copy? Huh? [snorts] Um, so uh
well I would agree with you. Did you do
you find car attractive?
Did you say you didn't or you didn't
like her? You like you like her or you don't.
Gay. Gay, mate. You can't deny she's
attractive. You're gay. You're [ __ ]
gay, mate. [ __ ] gay.
You're gay. You're [ __ ] gay. You
[ __ ] gay. Gay. Homo.
[ __ ] homo. You gay, Grezy, mate.
So, did you see me change the avatar, Grezy?
The avatar of the f of the video that I done.
Yeah, they they observe and then they
copy. That's what cats do. That's why
they That's why they're called copycats
because they observe and they copy.
So, do you want to see?
Oh, we're just talking about the copycat
Triple H. So, you know, Elephant and
Castle where I met my mama.
This is the um this is what it looks
like when you go to Elephant and Castle.
That's where I met my mama. Triple H.
You said you never seen my mama, have
you? Triple H.
My mama is the one on the right.
She's the one on the That's my mama.
What is going on with this bloody charger?
Yeah, that's my mommy on the one on the right.
As you can tell, we look like each
other. And that's where I met my mama. See?
Wait. No. No. That's not good enough.
That's not good enough. Greeny. One second.
That ain't good enough. >> [laughter]
>> That's [clears throat] better. That's
better. Yeah, I like that one. That
one's [laughter] better.
That one's better. You doing it. You
caught it early, didn't you? You caught
it early, mate. He said that's what he
was like. Would you believe? [laughter]
Would you believe it that this that this
cat went to college? Grezy observing,
you know. [laughter]
Would you believe that this cat actually
went to college and he was studying
and he [clears throat] was studying
landscaping? Would you believe it? Would
you had to believe it? Would you would
you believe that this cat went to
college? What are the eyes about? It's
looking at You can just tell, right?
It's looking [laughter]
It's just looking at the next thing it
can copy, isn't it, Grezy? Look, it's
it's paying attention. It's paying close
attention to the next thing that it can
copy. Isn't that right, Grezy?
[ __ ] copy that. [laughter]
That picture just makes me laugh. I
don't know why.
[ __ ] hell, bro. That is That is funny.
Yeah. Yeah. Anything in Castle is is
where my mommy took me back to to to
come on to me. Greavvesy. That's where
she came on to me.
That's where she came onto me.
I can make it worse if you want.
I can make it worse.
Oh, grezy. I'm going to get a beef chain
and I'm going to get a chicken fried rice.
Yeah. All right. Who's Who's this? Um Siri, who's that?
This cat went to college.
We No, I'm not getting pulled. [ __ ]
that. I'm not getting pulled in Chinese.
What? What's this? Greavves. Um, what's this? Siri. Yeah. [laughter]
Yeah, but it went to college. Yeah, but Yep.
So, why is it staring like that? Is it
looking for the next thing to copy?
Siri, is is it looking for the next
thing to copy? Huh?
Yeah. What was this Cheryl Cole thing
about? I don't know what his obsession is.
Can't deny she's attractive.
You can't deny she's attractive.
Sounds like a copycat statement.
Creepsy, you you said it as well though.
It sounded like a copycat statement.
So why why did he stop why did he stop
going to college?
Why did he stop going to college? Sui
sounds like a copycat. [laughter]
Huh? I said to I said I'm going to be a
copycat and copy your phone. Triple H. Oh, [laughter]
you can't you can't deny she's attractive.
You can't deny she's attractive.
Apparently, you're gay if you don't like her.
If you don't find her attractive, you're gay.
Meow. And Siri, what's this?
What did this remind you of?
Do you know what this is?
You should know London. [snorts]
No. But do you know what that is?
And who's that on the right? Say you [laughter]
My mama looks beautiful in that dress.
A My mom is really beautiful in that dress.
Isn't that true, Siri?
Oh, bless you.
Oh, I like this cat.
What was it? What was the cat doing in
the video? Greavvesy, did you see what
the cat was doing in the video? [laughter]
[ __ ] you see what that cat was doing?
It was copying.
>> Yeah, it was copying the man. [snorts] [laughter]
I can't stop laughing at that cat's
face. I can't stop laughing. Ah.
I had some I had I had three pieces of
chicken chips. Three pieces of chicken
and chips earlier. The chicken had just
come out. Greasy.
That's how I get my vitamins.
[snorts] No, I didn't.
Actually, my mommy's buying me a Chinese
today as a treat. Yeah,
I'd fry middle breast. I had fire and
middle breast and leg. Oh gosh.
I need to cut down on sugar because it's
bad for your mouth, Greasy. But I can't
stop eat I can't stop drinking sugar,
bro. Like Coke and stuff is addicting,
but I need to stop.
Yeah, Sig bought me some lovely chicken.
Why didn't it work out between me and Sig? Suri,
she bought me some chicken. She gave me
sex. She gave me her boobies.
Like why didn't it work out?
Should have worked out in it, Grezy. You
meet a woman that buys you
that buys you food
and gives you sex and stuff. What What
more could you want?
You know, the first time of meeting someone. [snorts]
Well, that should have worked out now
because that's quite nice for somebody
to do that,
you know. That's very nice.
I was fingerling her as well.
She was like, "Whatever we do, we're not
having sex. We can kiss and whatever,
but we're not having sex, right?"
And then all of a sudden she jumped on
my dick. Say you
all of a sudden she she wanted a dick.
It's mad, isn't it?
I'll never forget that day, bro. It was mad.
Then went upstairs and then she text me
saying, "No, where did you go?"
She wanted Peter Belly's Willie. Sori,
she wanted Peter Belly's Willie.
Is that right?
Yeah, but it should have worked out
between me and Siga. Shouldn't have it. Seori
should have worked out.
Yeah, it should have worked out. It
should have worked out now.
But what happened?
No, that's okay with me, boss. Meow.
But you have to you have to say meow if
you do that. No.
So, why didn't it work out? I could try
and get I could try and get back with
Sig if I wanted.
Look [laughter] at that cat's face. I
can't stop laughing at it.
Yeah, I could try and get back with her.
Say you what do you think?
At least I can I'll never have to talk
about that USA again. Isn't it? Find
someone new in it. Say
find a new person that will treat me
good, treat me right.
What do you mean no?
Why not? Slig was nice to me. Say you
why Sig was nice to me. Greavvesy. She
bought me chicken and gave me sex. [laughter]
See, I told you Greavvesy. This account
keeps mocking me.
Yeah, but her boobs was just as big as USA Izzy's.
Yeah, they were they were just as big.
Yeah, but they were just as big though,
if not bigger. I think they were the same size
to be honest. Yep.
Yeah, but it's better than nothing
though, is it? Yeah, but USA Izzy is not
that good looking either without the filters.
She's not good without the filters. But
it's all about the vitamins, isn't it, Greavvesy?
No, this is my mama
on the right.
It's not about the face. It's about the
vitamins. You idiot. I need vitamins. You know? Yep.
Same thing with that USA. Is he? I
looked at her. I was like, you look
different than your photos. I didn't say
that to her. And then I was like, "Uh,
well, the accent's quite the accent's
kind of cute." And and then she had like
big boobs as well, so I was like, "Oh,
[ __ ] it. I've got nothing better." So,
no, I've only got one real mama,
but she put me up. She put me into care. Nope.
Yep. She put me into care.
Yeah, but she was like a three or four
USA Izzy. But the accent made up for it
and the boobies. So that's why. Oh, it
was some one night stand I had. Triple
H. She bought me some chicken and gave me sex. Yeah.
Oh, USA. Izzy,
she weren't that bad. Sig weren't that
bad, bro. In real life, she wasn't that bad.
No, I think that I think the the copycat wanted uh
I think the copycat wanted USA is when
he saw me get USA's number. This was his face.
The jealous face. Look. So,
that was his face in it
when he saw the video. Do you remember
the video of me getting the number? I've
still got the video, by the way.
Uh, it's very rare that you have things
like that recorded, you know. [snorts]
[laughter] Yeah, he's a copycat.
I like the Albanian as well. She had big boobies.
She had big boobies. I'm comparing all
of the boobies I've had. Sui,
I think the biggest has got to be the
I think it's I don't know.
Maybe the Albanian one.
Maybe the Albanian one. I think Sig and
USA Izzies were the same size.
I'm sure they were.
I only get with women that have got boobies.
If they don't have boobies, I can't I
can't get with them. Say,
that's how you know bor women are so boring.
Yep. They were like brown. Like the
nipples were brown.
I said, "Can I see your boobs?" And then
she pulled her top up
and out they went and I couldn't help myself.
I dug in, um, Greasy. I dug in. That was my dessert.
Yeah. I got I got dinner and dessert,
but then a broken heart at the end of
it. So, wasn't really fair, was it?
Yeah, I got dessert.
Is that cute, Greavvesy?
Uh, we was making out. Is that cute,
Greavvesy? I went to the barbers that
day as well, Suri. I gave the barber a
lot of money. I got face wax and stuff.
I looked my absolute best. I thought I
was going to be getting into a relationship,
but nope. It was all a lie.
It was all a load of [ __ ]
I used to do it every week. Go to the
barbers, spend £50. I used to have the
money to do it, so I never really I used
to do it every week.
Mad when you think about it, is it?
But that's mad when I'd meet someone, you know.
I need to get my hair cut at some point.
Did you like any of the women that I got with Grezy?
The Manchester one was all right, but
she had no boobies.
She had absolutely no boobies, so I
couldn't really get attached.
No, she didn't have no boobies. That one?
No, she had no boobies. She said, "Oh,
I'm going to suck your dick." I said,
"Really?" So, I took my pants down.
Yeah, Autumn says that I think I'm Ed
Matthews. I think I'm bloody Ed
Matthews. How can I think I'm Ed
Matthews when I've been approaching
longer than him?
I don't think I'm that [ __ ] clown.
We're nothing alike.
I've been [ __ ] approaching longer
than he has.
I've had a buzz cup before.
Maybe in the summer I'll get one.
No, I'm not doing that because that that
would mean I'm a I'm a copycat.
Oh, the one from Finland. She's blonde.
Yeah, I think she had boobies as well.
So, she led me on. Led me on and sold me a dream. Yeah.
If I got a buzz cup, would that mean I'm
a copycat? Grezy,
I'm not a copycat. >> [snorts]
>> Nope. I'm not a copycat.
Think she had. Huh?
What are you on about?
Well, yeah. Well, she did have Yeah.
Obviously, I didn't sleep with her, so I
don't know. But she had boobies,
but she was another time waster.
Oh, she did have boobies. Some Yeah, she
had some boobies, but she was a time
waster. I actually thought she was
different, but just another time waster.
leading people on as always.
I can't believe how long that
conversation took the other day, Grezy.
All because they're
I just don't get these people.
So, if you look at all of these women on
my phone, they've all got boobies. Greasy.
Yeah. I don't think if women had
boobies, I don't think I would bother
with them. Like, I actually analyzed
them before I approached them.
You can see every single woman on my
phone have all got boobies.
most of them.
Otherwise, I don't
I don't bother
cuz why would I want to get with someone
if I can't get vitamins? It's pointless.
They've all pretty much I mean, some of
them don't because
if their face looked really good, I
would have just done it anyways. Depend.
It depends. It depends. But most of the
most of them on here do
cuz again I need vitamins. So
but yeah they do I mean there was some
flat chested ones on here
but that's because I couldn't see their
boobs and stuff. What's that? Yeah. [snorts]
Yeah. I think Ant-Man's an undercover hater.
Oh, that Taiwan's put her picture back
up. These women love playing these
games, you know. I'm sick of them.
I don't play their silly games anymore.
These women silly games.
I'm tired of it all to be fair, bro.
Like I'm I'm going to go out again
probably Boxing Day. I might go out
Boxing Day or New Year's Eve. One I
might just save the money until New
Year's Eve to be honest. What are we a
month and a bit away?
This seems the most logical thing to be honest.
It's [ __ ] boring, bro.
This is the one I met in Birmingham when
I was with Monty.
She's from Romania.
We would have been a good couple but again
they lead you on.
How can one man um very easy with
women's unrealistic standards nowadays?
Very very easy how one man can go out
and not get anything.
quite easily with women's unrealistic
standards nowadays due to uh white
knights and simps inflating their ego.
I think I said that right, didn't I,
Grezy? With no hiccups.
Uh quite easy when the the West is full
of stuck up women
that think they're better than everyone.
Quite easy. Would you would you would
you add and believe it? Quite easy.
This is what I mean with these people.
This is how you know they've got no life experience.
You know, you can actually tell people
on here that have actually got no life
experience. It's a bit like Reddit
because why someone would even write
something like that.
An Asian nons. Ew. A white knight. Ew. Wooy. Ew.
Ew, a s.
Ew. Women have self respect. They're not
going to get with a man who looks like
an who looks like a an Asian nons. Ew. A white knight.
You know the mad Oh, I'm sick of saying
this, Greasy. Do you know who the
maddest thing is? You know all of these people, right,
that defend women? Like, listen to me,
bro. You know what all of these people
that stick up for women?
I've had less women than you. And by
you, I mean me. That's how mad it is.
You know, all of these people that defend women
or people that don't get women. How mad is that?
You know, that's the maddest thing that
I don't get is that they don't get
women. Women don't like them. They've
had less women than you
and they still defend them. That's
something that I could I could never ever understand.
Could never never got it. Never understood it.
And the fact that they don't deal with
women because that the way they talk about women,
it's so obvious. The way they defend
them and stuff, they've just never been
with women. It's so obvious. Sad really.
Yep. Nothing to offer them. That self
projecting again. We're not interested
in self projectors.
Yeah. Talk about This is what I mean.
This is why I don't get into any debates anymore, Grezy.
because you can't show these people otherwise.
It's like I was saying before, even when
you show them black and white evidence,
they still simp over women. There's
there's no point in it. That's why I
will never get into any debates anymore.
Cuz even when you show what these women
are like to these little virgins, they
will still nod their head like a dog.
Nope. Nope. Nope.
Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. They'll just
They'll just They'll just nod nod their
head like a dog.
I might put a dog up. Mad.
These virgins are mad. And they don't
get what by right, Squeezy. Let me ask
you this. Right. Do don't you think I
should be defending women?
Brucey, do do you think I should be defending women?
I've been with more women than these
people. I've had sex more times than
these people. So why am I the one not defending women?
Because I'm not biased. Do you
understand? I'm not biased.
Either way you look at it, I'm not
biased. I'm not some loser that has to
lick women's asses because I don't get
women. That's so [ __ ] sad, bro.
They defend women just because they're women.
No, that's just you talking about
yourself now, bro. You're one of these
people that hate their life on YouTube.
No, that's you, bro. I've had more women
than you've had hot dinners. No, that's
definitely you. We were talking about
you people earlier. You fat, ugly people
who hate yourself that try to bring
other people down. We were talking about
you people at the start of the stream. I
don't think Greavesy was here, but yeah,
we was talking about you little fat ugly
weasels earlier trying to bring other
people down to your [ __ ] level.
Yeah, you fat ugly people that failed in
life. Yeah, we were talking about you
lot earlier, bro. You missed it.
You're fat, ugly people that hate your
lives and you come on here to try and feel better.
>> Pathetic. And you're older than me as well.
This charge is really dodgy, Greavvesy.
Yeah, I'd always be single. And you'll
always be a virgin.
And you will always be a virgin and
single. So I win. Meow.
And I and I'd always and and you would
always be a And you would always be a single virgin.
How does that make you feel?
I'll always be single, but you'll always
be a single virgin.
That's even worse, isn't it?
Let me see. Yeah.
How do I know? Yeah. Cuz I I I I wonder
why. Yeah. Cuz you're a virgin. That's
how I know why. Cuz you're a virgin.
I was a virgin once. When I was 16. I
know all [clears throat] the signs.
Why are you trying to call me a virgin?
Even though I proved I've had sex.
Yeah. What about when I've proved I've had sex?
Am I a virgin? Even though I proved I've had sex.
Autism. You people on here really really are disabled.
I feel bad, bro. Yeah. A cold approach
and I've had more women than you. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
Disabled. Fat ugly bastard. I'm going to
put the link up. Jo, let's have a laugh
at your ugly face. Come on.
Same atmosphere on this [ __ ] community. Same atmosphere.
My sister don't count, but your sister counts.
Mine don't count, but your sister counts. Yeah.
Oh, let me guess. You called me a virgin.
They call me a virgin even though I
prove I had sex.
How's that, man?
They call you a virgin even though you
proved you've had sex. That's mad. [snorts]
That's mad. Yeah, I've seen it. Anyways, [snorts] bye-bye, [ __ ]
You like my new picture, Triple H?
You like it? It's a copycat.
[snorts and clears throat]
I'm not getting a buzz cut. That's what copycats do.
That's what people do. They copy the crowd.
That's all copy get to do.
My hair is getting really long. Trip H.
It's annoying, bro. Do you want to see it?
Look at my hair and beard, bro.
I need to go to the barbers.
Look at that, bro. Dude, dude,
I had a shower earlier,
bro. I just got [ __ ] barbers, man.
What the [ __ ]
Well, they say you don't shave in
November. It's called no uh November, whatever. Yeah.
Yeah, that's what they say, bro. You
don't shave in November.
So, I didn't shave.
So, go away, you little s. You little
virgin. No simp virgins on my channel.
You like it?
You like it, Triple H?
You like it, bro? Yeah.
Do you like it, bro?
Good beard, is it?
That's why I can't get a woman. Go away,
you little s, little virgin.
I'm not getting into any more debates,
Grezy, with these little virgins.
I don't want debates with people that
dismiss people's struggles.
I pay £50, but I get my skin done, my
eyebrows, I get wax, I I get everything
done when I go.
Yeah. I pay like 50 for everything. I do
it like every six weeks
cuz I get like a face mask and stuff
done to my skin and that.
What's the plan? There is no plan. I'm
just chilling out today.
I won't be out until November. So, December
cuz there's little to no point going out
spending money in November when you need
Doesn't make any sense, you know?
Really? I need to come up north. Matey,
do you like my beard? Oh, man.
Look at that beard.
No, I'm going to book a holiday soon.
Oh my god. Look at that beard, bro. If I
had like a razor, I would just shave it.
I don't know. I won't shave it all,
actually, cuz you don't shave in
November, do you?
[ __ ] hell. What is that beard, bro?
That is mad.
Jesus [ __ ] Christ.
I can probably get a bun now.
I think I Well, not a bun, a top knot.
Yeah, I feel I have a top knot now.
Look for break.
Yeah, I could probably get like a top knot. Yeah, almost.
This charger is dodgy, bro.
It's dodgy the charger. I don't know
what's wrong with it.
I might leave it for another couple of months.
No, I can't, bro.
I need to go to barbers, bro.
Turkey. I need to go to the Turkish barbers.
Yeah, I got my haircut in Middlesbrough Triple H.
No, I don't know if No, I don't think I
got my haircut. I feel I got my haircut
I got my hair styled. I got my haircut
in Newcastle, though. I've had my
haircut in a lot of different cities.
Leads. I've had my haircut done in Leeds. um
Man I Manchester.
Yeah, I have.
I know. While I was in Manchester
out of my head, I don't know. Uh
yeah, loads of places really.
loads of places.
Birmingham, I think
Sheffield, I have
Liverpool. No, I don't think I have a Liverpool. Uh, Nottingham. No,
look at this hair, bro.
What the [ __ ]
It's getting itchy and horrible now.
>> Yeah, mad.
I look like a [ __ ] terrorist, don't I? touching.
Look at the cat copycat.
Look at a little copycat.
It looks like him as well, is it? I
think it's Wells Virgin boy's only friend.
That's what it is, mate.
There I was bur. But I don't want to be
your friend. Go away, you little virgin.
Go away, you little skimp virgin. I
don't want to know you.
Leave me alone, you skimp [ __ ]
Don't want to know you.
I can grow a beard. You can't grow a
You can't grow a beard, mate.
You can't grow a beard like me, mate.
It's horrible. It feels like pubic hair
on your face.
It's horrible, bro.
Yep. Yeah, bro. It's pretty Well, I wake
up at like 9:30, 10, but Yeah. Yeah, it
was horrible when my sleeping pattern
was like that, bro.
makes you depressed as well.
Yeah. Makes you um
Red Star. Red Star still stalking me.
I think that's that chase. That red stock
[ __ ] whoever it is a [ __ ] loser.
Do like my hair like this. Triple H.
You like it, bro?
[ __ ] beard. What the [ __ ]
Oh, I like that little cat. Yes,
dry little cat. Mr.
Oh, do you like my picture? Uh, Mr. B,
what do you think about it, bro? That's
the little That's the copycat.
You like that's the thing copycat. Yeah.
Yeah. It went to college
and then stopped attending. Yeah.
Then it stopped attending. Yeah,
look at that beard.
It needs to be cut. I bet Joseph Ferrar.
Now Joe F's been quiet, hasn't he? Jeff
Ra, he's been quiet. Joseph Ferrar.
He's been quiet. >> Yeah.
How long did it take you to save up all
that money, Mr. B?
that money, matey?
[ __ ] hell. Must took you like six months.
Bad. I remember I saved like three grand
in a month.
I used to get more money. I saved it
like I saved like 3.4K, bro.
In a month. Obviously. Huh?
Those were just like roulette wins and stuff. It
>> Yeah, man. Yeah. Anyways,
I'll be back later.