Yeah. One second.
Yo, this [ __ ] I just need to get one
thing straight. Yeah. When a few people
join. Yeah. Listen to this [ __ ] UK
biggest nonsense. No one needs to prove
themselves to you. I'm not showing you
no receipts. I'm not showing you
anything. I don't know why you wake up
thinking that people need to prove
themselves to you fat ugly people. No
one needs to prove themselves to you fat
ugly people. You [ __ ] m you [ __ ]
m. How many [ __ ] times have I come on
here asking you fat ugly people to show
your face, show your house, but you
can't do it. And then you think you're
going to ask me to prove things? You
cheeky [ __ ] [ __ ]
Who the [ __ ] do these people are ask
thinking they're going to ask you to
prove themselves to them? These little fat, >> [snorts]
>> ugly, biased [ __ ] retards. Madness.
These fat, ugly, disabled people. Who
the [ __ ] do they think people need to prove themselves?
People don't need to [ __ ] prove
themselves to use [ __ ] mongos.
[ __ ] the cheek on it, mate. The
[ __ ] cheek on it.
One second, lad. I'm going to go over
some of this cuz I know you're watching
me. One sec.
Absolute bully victim. And you can keep
putting my sister up that no one's
bothered. But I'm going to respond to
this that first thing, serious question.
But how do you put up with being bullied
day in day out? You people don't bully
no one. You bully yourselves. You've
been bullied since you come out your
mom's [ __ ] That's how I deal with it.
Knowing that you are the ones that are
actually being bullied every day, no one
else. Throw me£20 on a live stream, you
skin bully victim with two sisters. I am
not showing fat, ugly skin projectors
any money. I don't need to show you skin
ugly people any money because you ain't
got no money. You ain't got no money,
bro. That's your problem. I'm not
showing you money again. I'm not showing
any of you fat, disabled, hopeless
losers anything. I mean, I've asked you
multiple times to show your face and you
can't do it. So, stop asking me to show you things.
No, you're a virgin because your very
small penis has never entered the lips
of a vagina. Because no one wants to
sleep with Giza claiming pip while
living with his mommy, even though I've
proved I've had sex many times. Do you
see what I mean with these people?
They're so disabled. It's the same
disabled atmosphere. This is why people
don't bother with this anymore, with
these fat little ugly hopeless losers.
This is why people don't bother with
them anymore, bro. Fat ugly fat virgins.
And I hit a nerve every single time when
I'm saying about these people. Stop
taking it out on the world that you're
fat, ugly, hopeless. It's not my fault
I'm better looking than you. It's not my
fault I've got more money than you.
Don't take out on the world that are
people that are younger and better
looking than you. This [ __ ] account
is asking me to prove him things.
This fat, ugly, skint person is trying
to ask me to prove stuff to him,
you know, asking me to show receipts.
Mate, no one's showing you fat, ugly
people, nothing. You biased, ugly little
low lives, anything. So, I don't know
why you keep posting every day. You
really want to see receipts for my
clothes? Come in and show your face.
I'll drop the link. One second, cuz I
know you're watching me. Yeah, cuz you
stalk me. I'll put the link up. Show us
your ugly face and I'll show you the
receipts and I'll show you that 20 that
you want. That's fair, isn't it, Grezy?
That's very, very, very fair. You're
asking me to show you receipts because I
got stuff for my mommy's catalog. Bro,
why do you think we're all skint? Why do
you think we're all on £300 a month like
you? Why do you think everyone's got
your lives? I'm No, no, no. I'm I'm I'm
I'm actually serious, bro. What is it
with these fat ugly people thinking
everyone lives their fat, ugly, skint
lives? Am I lying, Grezy?
with with these fat ugly skinned people
on YouTube. Why does everyone Why do
they think everyone lives their life, bro? Come in
and have a
Come in and have a chat since you want
to see something so badly. What? Where's
this link? Hold on.
They're [ __ ] mongos. I'm going to do
a video I'm going to do a video on this [ __ ] bro.
I'm going to do a video on this little
[ __ ] Whoever the [ __ ] it is, if they
don't come in, no one needs to prove
themselves to you fat, ugly skin people.
I don't know why you think everyone has
to [ __ ] prove themselves to you fat
[ __ ] low lives skin on YouTube every
day. I don't know why you think people
have to prove themselves to the lowife
ugly people. Like you don't, bro, you're
so [ __ ] chair that you don't even fit into society.
You're [ __ ] losers. Why does anyone
need to prove themselves to you loser
people that don't prove anything?
They're absolute life's losers. No one
needs to prove themselves to you, bro.
No one needs to know your [ __ ] receipts. And no,
I don't like cats with it's basically nons.
They seem to think that everyone's
people need to prove themselves to to
these to you.
They seem to think, "What would you know
what women want, mate? You're [ __ ]
You probably never even seen a woman
[ __ ] naked in real life, let alone
[ __ ] being a [ __ ] virgin. People
don't need to show you receipts, mate.
They don't need to show you skint little
people anything. You skint disabled,
self-projected, anything. There you go.
The link's there. Join. The link's
there. So, join.
All right. You You know, you you want
people to prove this and that, this, and
that. Come and join and we'll start
we'll start proving stuff. You [ __ ]
little fat [ __ ] This is what I mean
with these people in this community,
bro. [ __ ] disabled. This is why I'm
coming off of it. You know, same
atmosphere, same fat [ __ ] people.
double f every day with these people.
They're [ __ ] mongos, bro. [ __ ]
absolute mongos. Why are you not coming in then?
Do you know
a sister that he puts up? He doesn't
even know my sister. He's putting a
wrong That isn't even my sister that
he's putting up. I don't give a [ __ ]
about that. It's I find it cheeky that
these fat ugly people think that you
need to prove yourselves to them. That's
what That's what I find very cheeky.
Triple H. I don't care about the sister
[ __ ] [ __ ] all that. I just think it's
cheeky that these fat, ugly, bully
victim virgins think that anyone needs
to prove themselves to them.
They What are they? [ __ ] Donald Trump
or some [ __ ] Are they [ __ ] Angelina
Jolie or something, bro?
Who are these people that you need to
prove yourself to? Bro,
what the [ __ ]
You start showing your face. You start showing cash.
You've been asked multiple multiple
times to show things and you can't
because you're fat, ugly losers,
mate. I'm leaving more than Timmy. Don't
worry about me, mate. I can take a day
off of YouTube, you people can't. I can
take a day off of YouTube and you people can't.
I mean, I can take a day off of YouTube,
you people can't. So, don't come on here
and try and take the piss out of me. I
don't know what Timmy does. I don't know
what Timmy doesn't do. I don't I don't
know how long Timmy can stay off of
YouTube. Well, I'm saying I can take a
day off of YouTube. You can't. So,
no, no, no. I It's not easy bait. I just
I just find it very strange how these
ugly people think that they can ask
people to prove themsel thing in. You
know what I mean?
I don't know why these fat ugly virgins
think that they can ask people to prove
them that people need to prove
themselves to them. These fat ugly
hopeless little low lives. And you know
what? Even if they get a reaction, their
lives are always going to be [ __ ] So I
don't even know why they would want a
reaction because it's not going to
change the fact that they're fat, ugly
virgins and they're going to be like
that for the rest of their life.
So is there really a point in all of
this? because he's never going to
[ __ ] change any [ __ ] thing. Yeah.
Asking people to prove stuff to you.
That is cheeky, bro. Very, very cheeky.
Jealous fat, ugly people that ain't got
no [ __ ] life.
That's what they are, bro. Fat, ugly
virgin skinned people that ain't got no
[ __ ] life. It's not my fault. I can um
Yeah, I will. I will. and you carry on
going on YouTube every day cuz you can't
take a day off of it.
This is what I mean. It's the same
atmosphere with these mongos on here,
bro. Same atmosphere with these mongos,
mate. My dreams are real. My trainers
are real. It's not my fault that we're
not all skin ugly like you fat people
talking about what women want. You've
never been with a woman. Most of you on
here were [ __ ] virgins. We've seen
you on Lar J's and what you do without a
team. Most of you people on here are
[ __ ] virgins trying to bring people
down to your level, mate. What would you
know what women want when you've never
been with a woman? You've never seen a
woman naked in real life? What would
some [ __ ] virgins know about women?
What would some [ __ ] little virgins
know about women when they've never been
with a woman?
These fat ugly losers that get bullied
every single day. Every day they get go
outside the house, they get bullied for
being ugly. They are life's losers, bro.
[ __ ] weirdos trying to ask me to
prove receipts to you. [ __ ] off, you
skinned virgin. I'm not proving nothing
to you little [ __ ] mongos.
[ __ ] off, [ __ ]
Why don't you start proving stuff?
Oh, I need your opinion on something,
Grezy. Greasy, and I want you to give me
your opinion. Please tell me you're still here.
Um, and I want your honest um, opinion on this.
It made me think of you. This is
something different, by the way. This
this this made me think of you.
Please come back. >> [sighs]
>> Yeah, they're [ __ ] bongos, bro. Don't
ask me to [ __ ] prove my jeans and
[ __ ] prove my trainers about mommy's
catalog. I'm not showing you [ __ ]
nothing, you skin ugly little low lives.
[ __ ] off, mate. Mommy's catalog. Why?
Cuz we're not all skin like you people.
Why Greavves? Come back.
I was just speaking to someone on Reddit
and I don't I don't entirely think this
is fair what this person saying.
I want your opinion on it though. Yeah,
they're putting the sisters and [ __ ] up.
Doesn't bother me. I don't give a
They're putting someone up that's not
even my sister. Triple H. They're trying
to say one person's my sister. That's
not even my sister. They don't even know
my third sister or second sister. I've
got a bro. I've got two sisters and they
don't know the other sister. They only
know one of them. They've been trying to
find her for years and they can't find
her. They don't know my other sister.
I've got two sisters. They don't know
the other one.
It's [ __ ] hilarious, bro. And they
don't They putting some random person up
that's not even my sister. [laughter]
You got to laugh at these retards, you
know? You got to laugh at them, bro. Yeah. [laughter]
That's not even
up. Almost stocks my [ __ ] channel
there, bro. Almost stalked my [ __ ]
main there. Trying to put a box up. Hold
on. Sorry about this, lads.
Yeah, that's not even my sister.
That is That's not even my sister.
links up. Is anyone wanted to join or? Yep. [ __ ]
Right. You coming in or
I would give a little while to breach.
Oh, I was on a fake account, right? And
I complimented this woman just to see
what she'd say, right? I said to her,
"Your fit ex." And this wasn't even on
my account. She corrected me with the
yaw. And I said, "Go suck your mom's
dick." You know,
and I said, "No." I said, "Your mom
sucks dick." Sorry. Then she said,
"Because I'm not." And this is a fake
account, by the way. She said, "Because
I'm not interested in you." Very
pathetic, babes. I said, I gave you one
compliment. Stop gassing yourself up. No
one's interested in you. Lower your ego
down a bit, hun. You're not anything.
Ignore all the virgin simps that say
otherwise. They'd [ __ ] anything with a vagina.
I think I think that was good, wasn't
it, Grezy? This is the attitude of these
women. And this was a fake account, by
the way. This was an example. I I'll
tell you why in a I'll tell you what I
mean in a minute, Grezy. Um, they're so
they actually think they're the [ __ ]
Did you just read what I just wrote
there? They're absolute [ __ ] but
apparently they're not all the same.
Anyways, I want to get on to my main
bit. So, basically, right, I was talking
to this person on Reddit, right?
Greavvesy gave them a bit of rundown
about what I've been experienced for
years and how I don't want to continue
it anymore. And do you know what a guy
said to me, Greavvesy? He said that I
was re weakminded.
And I said, "That's not really fair, is
it?" You know, if somebody doesn't want
to deal with toxic women and mind games
at 28 years of age, is it weak really?
Considering I've tried more than anyone
in the world, I think I' I've gave my
fair share and given it a go. And what
because I I I want to give up for ever a
very long time. That's considered weak. Really weak?
I don't think so, man. I mean that's
that's a personal choice, is it not? Um,
no, but he No, but he's saying basically
that if you if you want to give up,
right, because women play games and
they're toxic and stuff, you're considered weak.
I don't think that's being considered
weak, Greavves, is it? I don't know what
your what. So because you don't want to
deal with mind games and [ __ ] and
toxicity, that's weak. Really?
That's really weak.
Well, because you don't want to deal
with their [ __ ] anymore. I just I just
don't understand this whole thing,
Grezy. It's like you you can't be or say
something without being labeled as
anyone. Anything. It's either you're a
misogynist or you're or or you're an
incel. You can't just be somebody that's
tried, fed up with it, and [ __ ] it
off. You have to be labeled as something
weak, incel, [ __ ] misogynist. Why not
just be somebody that's had women and
know what they're like and be an
impartial party? No, you can't. Nope.
Nope. You're either misogynist or you're
a [ __ ] insult. And he was saying
about Greasy. He was saying about how
Oh, maybe it's because you're negative.
Oh my god. Is it Is it the same argument again?
Is it just the same argument again with
this [ __ ] mindset? This is another
thing, Greavesy. You can explain how the
mindset thing works time and time and
time and time again
time and time and time and time again
and they they just won't get it. I say
to them, "What do you think people are born negative?
Do you seem to think people are born
negative? That doesn't make sense. Why
is someone negative for no reason? Why
is someone positive for no reason?
It's very obvious that you think the way
because of your experiences. No. Is that
not logical, Grezy?
Is that is that not logical? Okay, let
me let me give you an example, right? If
I was to go out next Saturday and I was
to say, "Oh, I'm going to go out and
people are going to pretend they've got
boyfriends and the numbers I get are
going to lead me on and something's
going to happen." Would you say that's
negative or would you say that would be accurate?
Would you say that that's negative or
would you say it's accurate based on your experiences
your I mean or would you say it's a it's
a reasonable thing to expect?
Would you say okay no would you say
that's being negative or would you say
that's that is what is to be expected
because I don't know how
you expecting something that is more
than likely going to happen negative
maybe maybe maybe
I should do a video about this who who [ __ ] knows you know
who in their right mind at 28 8 years of
age would continuously go out and keep
dealing with their [ __ ] It's about
having pride for yourself as well,
Grezy. If you're constantly going out
there dealing with their [ __ ] what does
that say about you as a man? You got no
pride for yourself. You want to call it
weak, right? You must be really, really,
there must be something really wrong
with you if you was to go out and keep
dealing with that [ __ ]
You know, you got no respect for
yourself. Some a man that's got respect
for himself would just give up.
or you know try when they're drunk or
you know what I'm saying that's having
respect for yourself that's doing the
right thing you know
obviously unless you're a virgin or you
really want kids it's like it's you are
I look better than you and I absolutely
do know how to chat women so stop self
projecting stop trying to put other
people down to your level we we don't
care about you we're having a serious conversation
Um, yeah. Do you know what? I'm just not
going to acknowledge these self
projectors anymore. Anyways, I'm just
going to carry on with like the normal
comments. So, that's So, yeah. What do
you think about that, Grezy?
We don't care about you little negative
self projectors. We're not even going to
react to you people anymore. You're boring, mate.
I'm like the best looking in this community, bro.
And and and you're still talking [ __ ]
Just go have a word with yourself.
I don't know how to I don't know how to
say hi to I don't know how to chat up
women, mate. I've spoke to more women
than you've had hot dinners. I'm betting
more women than you've had hot dinners.
You got any like content, bro, or
anything like any anything new to say?
Or just same self-projecting disabled
[ __ ] Then you wonder why people don't
go live anymore. But then they wonder
why people don't go live anymore like
Monty, like other people or people take
bait. Because you're [ __ ] disabled.
We're bored of it now.
We're bored of the same self-p
projecting by the same losers. We're
bored of you, bro. Bored of you.
Bored of you self-projecting fat ugly people. [ __ ] mongos.
Yeah. So, it's not it's not weak-minded
to want to to want to give up. And I've
been through a lot of [ __ ] with these
women, Grezy. A lot of [ __ ] More than
anyone would ever go through in their
whole life. So, you wanted to give up,
you know, or give up for 3 months or
whatever. That's that's on you, bro. Um,
was it? Did he? I don't care. I don't
care about what any of you losers think.
I really don't care about what any of
you fat ugly people think. So that's a
waste of time. You're just negative ugly
people that ain't got a life. No one
cares about what you think. Your
opinions are not even classed as
opinions. But yeah, that's um if you
don't want to put up with their [ __ ]
Reeves, that's actually a good thing.
And the thing is, I've been through it
more than anyone anyone in the world.
You're Bordon. You can't even
spellboarding, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Bye-bye now. Get kicked.
Is there no normal people on it, bro?
Just fat, ugly, self-projecting mongos.
Have I tried dating apps? No. Never.
Never. Ever tried dating apps at 28
years of age. Never tried them. So
all that's the thing Greavvesy is that
it's not weak-minded.
That's not weak minded, bro. I went
through a lot of [ __ ] with, you know,
people, even people I had met and stuff.
Why is it weak minded? Because you don't
want to deal with their toxic [ __ ] It's mad.
And another thing is some and and
because people are women, Greavvesy,
they can't do anything wrong on purpose
because they're women automatically.
Yeah, he had a guy about Oh, did he?
Well, good for him. No, again, no one
cares what you people think. No one
cares what you people think. But you
know about the negative mindset, Grezy,
that's that will always go around in
circles. that will constantly constantly
go around in circles. That's been going
on for years, bro. That's been going on for years.
Wouldn't you? But the thing is,
Greavves, if you was to go out and you
was to expect the worst, then when it
happens, you're not disappointed, are
you? Why would you think
you're triggered tonight? Repeating.
You repeating bastards are so boring.
But then if you expected a worse and
then it happened, then you wouldn't be
you wouldn't be phased by it, would you?
Whereas if you're expecting something
good to happen when it ain't going to
happen, then you're going to be
disappointed. No, think about it.
They're telling you that you need to go
out and be positive. Okay, you can go
out and be positive. Okay, but the same
thing is will happen. You know it and I
know it. So then you're going to be disappointed
when I go out now.
When I go out now, Grezy, it don't bother me.
It rarely ever bothers me. Have you
noticed that when I go out the next day,
it's like, "Oh, same old shit." Because
you expect it. You get to a point where
something will happen and you expect it
to happen. It's to be expected. Um,
so or you just don't expect nothing,
you know, one of the two. But that's not
being weak-minded because you don't want
to deal with toxic women.
I think you'd be weak-minded if you met
one and one [ __ ] you over Grezy and
then you didn't want to do it ever again
and you was a virgin and maybe you could
be a bit but I wouldn't say you're weak minded. >> No,
maybe but not not when you've been
dealing with women and then women upon
women and you don't want and you know
and you know what they're like as well.
as well. Grezy,
these women have got really, really bad
attitude. So, you're just disrespecting yourself by um
by dealing with them, like I said,
because their attitude and [ __ ] So, you know,
and I'm not talking about going out
approaching greasy. I'm not approaching now for
Well, the thing is, Greg, I don't have
it in my head to approach. I only do it
when I'm drunk or bored out of my head
because there's nothing else to do.
Like I said, I I don't even use escorts now.
The only reason I tried the past couple
years is cuz of my sex drive. It's
because of my sex drive.
You know, women are bad people, bro. And
the only reason I kept and I kept doing
it is because probably I was horny.
Yeah, I agree with that. No, I agree
with it, bro. I agree with it.
Cuz they don't understand, right? When
they're saying that other guys have have
tried, Grezy, they haven't tried as much
as me. No one in this world has tried as
much as me.
Believe you me, I've been through it all, mate.
hangovers, traveling, badic. Bro, I've
been through everything with these
[ __ ] So, when you get somebody that
wants to try and make you try and make
it seem like you're weak-minded, that's offensive, bro.
To all of the people that they're
listening, maybe there is someone in the
world that's tried more than me. I can't
imagine it though. You know what I'm
saying, Greavves? I I generally can't
imagine somebody that's traveled
everywhere, every week, going to a new
city, approaching. I I don't know who
would have done it as much as me. There
are probably people out there, but I I I
don't know, bro.
I have that with a lot of their um and
that's why I'm an I'm an unbiased um I'm
I'm an unbiased party.
I'm an unbiased party if you know what that means.
You don't need to be a [ __ ]
to be an inso or anything bad to give your opinion. So
it's strange though because
they seem to think that you're like a virgin or
you know you they seem to like say that
you're a virgin or you can't get women
because you think this way but it's not
true. You know like get it's because
you've never had any good experiences.
So that's why you would think that way
you know like it's hard to explain it.
They they seem to think straight away
you're a virgin or you've never been
with a woman when that's not the case.
It's because we know what they're like.
I'm surprised so many people don't know
what they're like to be honest with you. Crazy.
And then like I said, every time you try
to give someone the benefit of the doubt
again, they do the same thing. So what
are you supposed to think?
I couldn't believe that podcast though,
bro. I couldn't believe that podcast, Grezy.
They were doing anything and everything
in their power to not blame that woman
for leading me on.
Lead just leading someone on, which
isn't the worst thing. It's bad. It's
pretty bad. But they were going on like
it was [ __ ] murder or something. All
because there were women.
[ __ ] madness. That is [ __ ] mad.
All cuz they're women. Nothing else. No other reason.
No other reason, Grezy. No other reason
but they're a woman.
It's sex, isn't it?
I was looking at that autumn
and it seems that she's got big boobies.
It's a shame, man, because if she wasn't
um on this community and we didn't
argue, then maybe she could have been my
mama. But I don't go for women on
YouTube, and I don't like her anyways.
But yeah, if she was like a nicer person
and she wasn't on YouTube, then she
could have been my new mama.
But nah, [clears throat]
she could have been my new mama. Groovy.
Mama, by the way, mama been hijacked.
Hijacked. I ain't heard that word in ages, mate.
Yeah, that autumn could have been my mama. Grezy,
is that cute?
Yeah. Did that make you laugh? Yeah. I
was looking on her pictures, right?
Obviously uses filters and stuff and it
seems that she's got like big boobs and
stuff. So, she could if she wasn't on
YouTube and she wasn't a [ __ ] she could
have been my mommy.
Did you What about What do you think of
that Instagram? That woman from
Instagram. See, they've all got the same attitude.
And this was just me joking around on a fake account.
I was testing this thing, right, to see
if um, you know, they they say something
back if they thought I looked different.
It wasn't even me and I just said it
just to say it, bro. And then look,
they've got attitude.
They've all got the same attitude for
people that aren't the same, man. In it,
we won't get into that again, but just
throwing out there. That's rude, you know.
Yeah, that autumn's got big big boobs.
That's the only thing I was looking at. Lucy.
Nah, she couldn't be my mama. We all
know who my mama is. You can't replace
your mama, bro. Yeah. Nah.
Well, we all know who my real mama is.
Ain't it, Grezy?
[snorts] Remember, Grezy, I love my mama
and my mama loves me. If you watch Tom
and Jerry, you know that, Grezy.
And my mama loves me.
See, Joe doesn't understand. It's not
that women have everything that we want.
It's not what we want. We don't want
them. They're rude. But obviously, the nutrients,
it's what we actually need, Greavvesy.
We need the nutrients,
obviously. Why do you think we don't
care about women that don't have boobs,
Greavvesy? Any women that don't have
boobs, have you seen me care about? No,
because obviously I need the nut I need
the vitamins and stuff, especially when
it's winter. In the summer I'm fine, you
know, and in the summer I'm completely fine.
Gez, I'm completely fine, you know,
cuz most people don't most people don't
care about boobs. They'll get with a
woman that's flatchested or whatever.
But obviously, I need my vitamins. So yeah.
Yeah, Autumn's got some big boobies from
what I saw.
Too bad she's not my mama. [snorts]
I was scrolling up and down on her
pictures to see maybe she could be a
prime candidate for baby Peter. Nah.
Nah. No good.
You like small boobs? Ew.
Oh, I hate small boobs.
No, it's not enough vitamins.
It's not enough, is it, Greavvesy? Small boobs.
Elephant and castle.
What? You didn't believe Greavves. There
was a place called that.
What? You like small boobs? Ew, [ __ ] that.
No, I don't like there's nothing to
feel. I like touching them when I kiss,
you know? I like the way they feel, Greasy.
But they have to be real. If they're not real, yuck.
Yuck. I hate fake boobs. I'd rather have
somebody with no boobs than fake boobs.
I hate fake boobs. They're disgusting.
I hate fake boobs, man. They're [ __ ]
how disgusting they are, bro.
USA is ones were completely real.
They felt real as well.
You know, I only like real boobs. Yeah,
fake boobs are [ __ ] vile, bro. A lot
of porn stars have it.
Yeah. USA had really soft boobies. Yeah,
they're nice when they're real. That's
the problem with escorts. They're not
always real. So, yeah.
Let me look at that autumn.
Let me see her again.
I don't care about the face. I don't
care about the face. It's just the
boobs, isn't it, Grezy?
She's quite fat though, isn't she? [snorts]
It looks like there'd be enough milk there. We
Yeah, they look big enough. [snorts] >> [snorts]
>> No, she's not my mama.
I think her boobies are bigger than my mama's. Grezy,
I think they're bigger. Grey,
I think them ones are bigger than my mummies.
She goes for men that cheats on her this autumn.
That's not my mama.
But why does she use filters this
autumn? Why does she use filters? Grezy,
I don't understand, Grezy. They say that
these men that they go for, right, are
great actors, but I'm not buying it.
What's your opinion on it? I'm not
buying that they don't know that these
men are not bad before going with them.
I'm not buying it.
I'm not buying that, bro. Because
I don't think that they're abusive at
first, like they just beat people up,
but I think they know what they're
they're about before getting in with them.
What what do you think Greavesy? Like
these women will claim they don't know
what these men are like, but I think
they do know what they're like before
getting it into them with them. I think
they do. Maybe not abusive. Maybe they
might not be abusive straight away, but
I generally believe that uh
Why don't you tell us what you think, Grezy? Cuz
if that was the case, more women would
be giving me a chance. Think about it. Greedy, right?
Is that your birthday? The 26th of August, Timmy.
That's a good birthday.
26th of August. This
on the link. Yeah,
that's a good birthday, isn't it? 26th
of August. Greasy.
That's a good birthday. It's a good
number and good month.
Yeah, that's a good birthday, lad.
What do you think?
Remember, Greavves, you need to latch on
to some new B to some new boobies.
But Greavvesy, they're not they're not
telling the truth when they say that
these men are good actors at first
because if that was the case, then women
would be getting with me.
Is that not right, Grezy? Right. These
these people say that, oh no, these
women are they don't know what these men
are like at first. But that's not true
then because if that was the case, then
they would be getting with me, some of
these women, if they were nice to start
off with. It's [ __ ] [ __ ] mate. Hello. >> Hello.
>> Can you hear me?
>> Can't hear him.
>> One sec. >> Hello.
See my potato head, lad.
Look at the size of that potato head.
Can you hear me? Oh, yeah. My phone's [ __ ]
I can't hear. My phone's [ __ ] bro. I
need to reset my phone, I think.
>> Can you not hear me?
>> I can't hear.
>> I was going to say Timmy Elder is lad is
um is a
>> bloody phone.
>> Timmy Elder is a mom's lad.
>> Latch on to some new boobies.
>> Sim John El is a bacon, lad.
>> Yeah, I couldn't hear him, bro.
My phone's [ __ ]
What did you say?
What would you do if Autumn become my
new mama? Grezy,
would you be jealous?
Can you hear me?
Yo, can you hear me?