You little copycat.
You little copycat. Little copycat man.
Copycat man. Yay! Copy that.
Bunch of [ __ ] copycats.
Not laughing today, are you, mate? You
won't be laughing today, will you? I'm
excellent. I won my first double both
teams to score no draw. I'm absolutely
I'm very okay. I'm marvelous. I'm
feeling all right, actually. I've always
wanted to win one of those. The bet won
Triple H. If you if you didn't know, I
told you to get on it. I told you to get
on it, mate. You didn't listen.
You know, it might only be £110, but
bro, I won my first double both teams to
score. I'm so happy. I'm so excited.
Oh, it's so nice.
Just £110 off of 20 pound, but it's
still money, you know. It still still
pays food and stuff. So,
Yeah. Bye-bye now. Fantasy stories. I
told you to get on it. But you wouldn't
listen, would you?
You wouldn't listen. Listen, I told you
to get on that [ __ ] bet, son.
Uh, and the normal the other bet I was
going to do. Yeah, it would have lost
because they didn't even score. So,
something told me to get on this bet today, bro.
Still good though. 110 off 20 pound,
bro. [ __ ] I've had loads of wins the
past few months. So take it by money's
money in it. So yeah. Oh man.
You know the thing with the both teams,
this guy always has your heart always
has your heart rate um your heart
racing, bro. Cuz any thing is with this,
bro, you can get [ __ ] at any second
with the both score no draw. It can [ __ ]
you at any minute. Any [ __ ] minute.
And they keep adding on [ __ ] extra
time. You get [ __ ] any minute, bro.
Because of uh
Yeah, it can [ __ ] can [ __ ] you, bro.
Yeah. Better than [ __ ] all in it, bro.
Along with all the other wins I've had.
So, yeah. I was just happy to win the
double. Both teams to score. No draw,
bro. I was happy. I didn't think I was
ever going to win any one of them, but
one second. I'll just [ __ ]
on that. Did Kitty Minister score? They
didn't, did they? So, I would have lost
that one. If I put 150 on that today, I
would have lost.
>> Yeah, I might get myself a curry.
No, they didn't even score, bro.
I might get myself a little curry, you
know. Hey, you all right? I'm good. I'm
good. I might get myself a little [ __ ]
But I had some uh steak today, but it
has to be chicken cuz obviously, you
know, winner winner chicken dinner, mate.
Uh, no, but I remember when you was a
[ __ ] and you're still a [ __ ] Bye-bye now.
No buggers on my channel, mate. Yeah.
No [ __ ] [ __ ] on my [ __ ]
channel, mate. You know what I'm like, don't you?
Yeah. Yeah, if I put that 150 on I would
have got [ __ ] bro.
Oh, you would have been [ __ ] Really
Don't know whe to get a chicken curry.
I'm not sure.
H Should I get a chicken Should I get a
chicken Should I get a chicken Should I
get a chicken uh curry?
Because it has to be chicken, you see.
Like I said, because we're doing a
chicken dinner, you see? It's got to be
It's got to be got to be that, mate.
It's got to [ __ ] be that, mate. It's
got to be that, mate. Yeah. Got to be
that. It got to be that, mate. It's got
It's got to be that. It's got
lovely, mate. Sorry, I haven't took my
medication today, mate.
I haven't took my medication. Sorry.
I'll take it a bit later. Sorry. I'm bit
I'm a bit a bit crazy. bit.
All right, let me have a look at these coming places. One second.
Yeah, but it has to be
to be a chicken one though. It has to be
a chicken one, don't it? Cuz we're the
chick. I told you copycats. You could be
having this today if if you bet on it.
You could be you could have been having
it. You could you could be having some
curry. If you if you
you could have you know you could have
had this chicken dinner. Not a certain
person cuz he he he too much of a virgin
a complete virgin to go near that kind
of curry. But you know I need I need to
be careful mate because you don't make
names every mate.
Okay, all seriousness though, uh,
I'm trying to think where to get this from.
I'm going to treat myself to a nice
takeaway. I I have to, don't I, mate? I
[laughter] treat myself to a nice
takeaway. It'd be rude not to,
Triple. It'd be very, very rude not to,
would it? Let's make sure I got the
right ones here, mate.
Yeah, it'd be very very [ __ ] rude not to. Okay. Um,
yeah, I'm going to get a chicken one.
Okay, one second, bro. Um,
we need to look at these cries.
All right, Triple H, what's the most
you'd ever put on a football bat?
I just I just didn't want to risk the
150. I would have lost anyways. I would
have lost 150 if I put the 150 on, bro.
I would have lost and I didn't want to
risk that kind of money, especially
around Christmas time, you know. You
don't really want to risk that kind of,
you know, bloody you Christmas time and
stuff, you know. Nah, bro.
They're [ __ ] hard to get in them bastards.
Yeah, they both score no draws. They're
[ __ ] They're [ __ ] hunts to get in,
bro. They are bastards to get in.
Most I've ever put I think is 130. Yeah,
but what's the most you'd put on it now
though? That's what I'm saying.
You couldn't do more than a double both
scardo draw, bro. You'd get [ __ ] You
would get [ __ ] Trust me,
I don't want it from that one though. I
want a different Indian.
You know what I'm saying? I've already
had that Indian before. I want to try a
different one. Oh, I don't want Roen
Josh. I don't want Roen Joss. [ __ ] off.
That's what the Virgin has. Yeah.
That's what the [ __ ] Skint virgin
has. Triple H. [ __ ] off. I'm not having
tick masala. [ __ ] off.
I'm not like you and that [ __ ] Skint virgin.
If they copy my bet, they could be able
to come tonight, you know?
Right. We need to uh [ __ ] sake. Um,
no. I don't want I don't want tandoori chicken.
Biryani. That's biryani.
Vegetarian. This is madras. How was that?
You all right, captain? My football bet won. Yay. Oh,
chicken. I want chicken.
Yeah, I won 110 on my little football bet. Oh gosh.
Yeah. Okay. Chicken. I like
some rice as well, please. Oh gosh. Oh
no. I don't want no dessert. I want a soft drink.
Oh gosh. [snorts] Um, one second. Oh,
you don't have any cola. Why do you have no cola? Um,
yeah. I just want a chicken curry to be fair.
Chicken. I'll show you the chicken
dishes. Vindaloo. Get our roast. Done.
I'm not that hungry, but I What? Winner
winner chicken dinner mate. You know I
won the football bet fair and square.
So now I'm having my little [ __ ] if
that's all right with you boss.
I can't even go out and get more coke
cuz [ __ ] um
yeah the shop's closed. So
right I'm ordering this curry anyways. Yeah.
I reckon if you're going to put 22 250
on something, you might as well go on
[ __ ] roulette. Now, if you're putting
that kind of money on,
I wouldn't do it, but I'm saying if you
were going to,
right, so I've ordered this food anyways.
I don't play them for break. I don't
play them anyways.
Bro, I don't play them.
I don't play him, lad.
I haven't played them for a very, very,
very long time. I wouldn't go on them. I
don't I don't play him.
I'm not Timmy, mate. I'm not Timmy
[ __ ] Aldridge. No, nobody really
plays him. And I can't go out this week
cuz I'm going out next week. So there'd
be no point going out
next week. This week, there's no point
going out next week with my sister. I
need to get my hair done. I've got some
stuff to do. So yeah.
All right, Timmy, you want to come and Yeah.
Yeah. I won £110 off 20 football bet.
It was [ __ ] lash, mate.
Imagine I had 80 on it. Nah, I don't
think like that. Me, bro.
I'm happy. I'm just happy with the 110,
bro. For my haircut and [ __ ] I'm I
don't care, honestly. I'm happy with anything. Serious.
But if I put that 120 on that today, I
would have been [ __ ] bro. I would
have got [ __ ]
I would have got [ __ ]
cuz Kitty Minister didn't score.
Darlington did, but I think they drew.
Yeah, they drew, mate.
I knew. I just had a feeling these I I
knew I knew this battle was going to win, bro.
I knew it. I had this feeling, bro.
Cuz I've been analyzing these teams,
bro. So, I I had a feeling it was going
to win. I just ordered a chicken
vindaloo to celebrate my little win.
Yeah, I am, bro. I need to go and get my
haircut as well. I'm going to get my
haircut next week, obviously. Or this
week. Next week.
Yeah, I've just ordered myself a little
curry. Uh, I want to double both teams
to score, no draw. Yay, my first one.
Yeah, I knew I but I wouldn't advise
doing it ever again. But it your heart
gets [ __ ] start racing on the 85th [ __ ] minute.
On the 85th minute because [ __ ] um
both teams either score to win either
team to win. Yeah,
because of um
Yeah, it can [ __ ] you at any moment. It
can [ __ ] you at any moment, bro. This
happened like three times before. So
yeah, I had I normally get lamb
vindaloo, but I got I got chicken this
time because obviously I won. So if you
copy the bet, if you copy the copycat
statement, you would have won.
You would have won if you copied a
copycat statement, you could be having
£110 in your pocket. Better than a
kicking a dick, you know. It's better
than a [ __ ] kicking the dick, mate. Yeah.
>> Yeah. [ __ ] sake. I'd get tickle as well,
but I don't I don't feel that hungry. I
just want to the vend.
Let's be honest. I'm just doing it to
piss off the virgin, aren't I?
Just I'm going to do a video on the on
the curry as well, if you don't mind.
Just to piss off the virgin.
Just Just to piss off the virgin, mate.
You know me. You know what I'm like,
Triple. You know what I'm like, mate.
You [ __ ] know what I'm like.
You know what I'm like, mate. Pissing
off that [ __ ] skid virgin. Know what
I'm like, mate.
You're not laughing now, are you, LJ?
You're not laughing now, are you? You
silly little [ __ ] You wouldn't be able
to pick a bet like that.
You wouldn't You wouldn't be able to
pick a little bet like that, would you?
You silly [ __ ] No. No, you wouldn't.
No. I I chose it. I I done it. I done it. Me.
Hopefully that coke's enough, bro.
If it's that bad, I'm after all the
McDonald's coke, lads.
I still play roulette. I play roulette
like every 3 months.
Every 3 months? Yeah.
Yeah. Both teams just go on either team
to win. Yeah. Oh gosh.
What's the joy?
You probably saw [ __ ] I bet you
[ __ ] Virgin boy was [ __ ] racing to
the [ __ ] boogies. He didn't want to
feel left out, did he?
He didn't want to feel left out, did he?
He probably [ __ ] went [ __ ]
running as fast as he [ __ ] could. You know,
[ __ ] running as fast as he [ __ ] could.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. Because Because he didn't want to
feel left out. All because he didn't
want to feel left out.
All because he didn't want to bloody
feel left out.
He He He didn't want to bloody feel left out, mate.
It's the fear of being left out. [laughter]
It's the fear of being left out. Your mates
Mickey just commented.
Thank you, Captain.
Nah, I don't think so, bro.
Don't think so.
Don't think so, matey.
They have to scan the barcode. I don't
think so, matey,
cuz I've got the original slip. So,
yeah. Don't think so, mate. [ __ ] copycats.
No, they don't because I've got the slip
so it's never going to happen.
So, that's not going to happen, mate.
But I deleted it just in case.
No, it's not going to happen because
I've got the slip.
So, no, I don't think so, bro.
Nope. Because I've got the slip. I've
got the original slip and me on camera
betting on it. Oh, it's not going to
work, matey. But thanks for telling me though.
Yeah, one greavesy. Yeah, I've just
ordered myself a chicken bindaloo to celebrate.
Yeah, thanks for telling me that.
Anyways, I deleted it just in case. [snorts] Yeah,
I told you to be a copycat.
I told you to be a copycat, mate.
Yeah, I should be all right anyways. So, yeah.
But yeah, thanks for letting me know anyways. Yeah.
Yeah, he should have, mate. You should
He should have [ __ ] I bet you Virgin
boy was probably running to the [ __ ]
bookies, isn't it? He was probably
running to the [ __ ] bookies, wasn't he, mate?
Yeah, he probably went running to the
[ __ ] bookies, mate. Right. Not
wanting to feel left out.
He's a little copycat. He's a little
copycat, mate. He's a little copycat. He copycat
wanted to fit in with the crowd.
>> No, that was my first both teams to
score. No draw, win.
>> Yeah. So, I don't always go with your
gut because I change and look, I won. So, yeah,
I'm I've ordered this. Um, I normally
have lamb vinderoo grievy, but because
I'm a winner, you know.
Well, that's all he can have because
he's too much of a virgin to have
anything hot. Yeah. I normally have a
lamb vindaloo, but I thought I'd have
chicken this time. Yeah.
Yeah. I thought I'd have chicken this time, bro.
because of um Well, yeah,
because uh with the with the chicken
dinner and that so you know,
happy I won that bet. It's not even a money, bro.
It's I'm just happy that I actually
picked a double both teams to score and it won.
It's not about the [ __ ] It's not
about the body. I was It's 110. It's
better than nothing but still, you know. Yeah.
I just had a feeling about them two
teams because there are goals in them
matches it. Uh where Yeah.
Come on. Still [ __ ]
saying to work on your order.
Yeah, bro. along with all the other wins
I've had the past two, three months. Yeah, bro. Yeah, obviously.
So, I would have saved this month over
£700. Greasy. That's good considering I
got jeans, trainers, and UGG boots,
isn't it? Virgin boy can't afford that.
He's too [ __ ] skinned. He's too
skinned to get a body jeans. That's why
he doesn't copy that
because he's too much of a skin fl. He's
too much of a skin p. Yeah.
130 and it lost. Yeah. 130
[ __ ] me up that time. Yeah.
Yeah. 130, bro. 130.
and I got fat.
Yeah, it was a couple of weeks ago, but
I'm still way up, so I didn't mind to be honest.
Yeah, I got [ __ ] bro. Properly
Properly properly properly [ __ ]
Should we do the 500 on on the both
teams to score sometime? Nah.
Nah. [ __ ] that, bro. Might I done that
today, I would have lost bloody kitty
kitty fiddler minister didn't score.
That's what I call them. Kitty fiddler minister.
That's what they're called. Kitty
fiddler minister. They're bloody
bastards. They are
greasy. They're [ __ ] bastards. They are.
I had to delete it quick cuz of what
Triple H told me. Ricky said, "I'm good
at the football bets." Thank you, Captain.
Oh, it's on its way now, Grezy. Thank you, Captain.
Uh, I'm not sure. I might just carry on
paying. I'm not too sure. Greavvesy,
what did you say? Oh, hey, did you watch
my video? It got two thumbs up. Hey, did
you watch my video, Greavvesy?
Oh, apparently that escort told me where
she was today, Greavvesy. I was like,
"Oh, now you're now you're licking ass.
Now you're not being a [ __ ]
anymore." I told her I was out of London.
Yeah, I literally just told her I was
out of [ __ ] London, mate.
I sure did.
[snorts] Yeah, that's boring, bro. That
joke's boring. Come up with some new jokes.
Yeah, true. Oh, I've completed what uh
phone I'm going to get 100% now, Greavvesy.
So, there was a Samsung phone that I
bought when I was doing Uber and it cost
me £400, but it's now £250.
It's good enough, you know, and I've
still got this phone for personal use.
So, that's that's the end.
You get it on a black. It's on It's 250.
I paid 400 for it, but it's £250,
so it's it works well enough. It's got a
good battery, so it's good enough.
They're not even called budget phones.
Budget phones are
budget phones are
like 120, 150.
They're not budget phones. They're just
moderate [ __ ] Androids, man.
Because I can. It's my money. I can do
what I want with it.
Simple as that.
It's my money. I can do what the [ __ ] I
want. Isn't that right, Grezy?
Yeah, it's £250.
It's the one I had at the old house.
Grievy, the phone works fine.
I Hey, bro. I don't even know why I'm
saying I'm into these flagship phones.
I'm not even into The only reason I like
this phone is because it's got a big
screen. I was lying in my little Leester
call yesterday and I was thinking, bro, [ __ ]
I'm only I only [ __ ] um
I only like this phone cuz it's got a big screen.
I like to lie down and watch things on this phone.
I want the football, mate. I want I want
to double both teams to score.
No draw. I'm so excited, Michael. I'm so
excited. I never ever thought I'd see
the day where I won one. Yeah,
I'm saving myself for next week though.
It's going to be a madness because
that's why I didn't want to that's why I
didn't want to gamble to 150 yesterday
cuz if I put 150 and I lost, I'd be
pissed off, bro. Pissed off.
He's a fy skint and a fuking skint flint.
Yeah, LJ won't be laughing now, will he?
Won't be laughing now, will you, mate?
No, you wouldn't. No, you [ __ ] wouldn't, mate.
You [ __ ] virgin.
I say as I [ __ ] look away, mate.
Yeah, he's he's a proper proper skin
virgin. Proper skin virgin.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro. I need another
filling, you know.
My orders being delivered. I got a
chicken one this time.
He has six. I didn't even know there was
such a thing.
There's so many projectors on this
community in it. So many uh
so many self projectors.
My video was so right about the women
thing. They do make excuses just cuz they're women.
It is true.
We need to move on from that now. Anyways, bro, cuz
it's just going to keep got it's just
going to keep going round and round in
circles in it.
That's the same old [ __ ] in it.
Same old [ __ ] [ __ ] in it. Yeah.
I wasn't talking bollocks though. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I wasn't
talking bollocks. No, I wasn't talking
bollocks. Listen, listen,
listen to what I'm saying, bro. This
dude's a filling. They say right about
they go for nice uh they think these
guys are nice guys at the start. This is
what they say. I have had people message
me saying, "Oh yeah, you're really
sweet. Thanks for coming and approaching me
t." Yeah, for some reason they won't
give you the chance. So if they're
really going for people that act nice at
the start that what they're trying to
make out, they don't go for these
certain people, then they would be going
for you. You'd be getting people all the
time wanting to go on dates with you.
So, it doesn't it doesn't add up with
what they're saying.
It doesn't add up with what they're
saying. They know what these men are about,
you know. They know what these men are
about, mate. So,
that's not that's not talking.
What? Double standards. Yeah. Yeah. The
double standard is ridiculous.
And it's not even like, oh, women are
stronger than men. It's not even that.
It's the the double standard is ridiculous.
You don't want to suck. You don't want
to eat a [ __ ] you're gay. If you want
to stop dealing with toxic women
and and you want to go your own way, you're weak-minded.
That doesn't know. That doesn't mean
someone's weak. That means someone's got
respect for themselves. Double standards.
And also I think another good point I
made as well Greavesy is that have you noticed
also also another thing is and it's not
even about eating [ __ ] It's it's how
about you want to eat How about you
would eat someone's [ __ ] How about you
would eat someone's [ __ ] if you was
with them? What about that one?
How about like if you if you if you if
you was with them or you was married,
what would would you still be gay then
if you didn't want to eat? And also
another thing, eating out random people
is not safe.
You know that vagina hygiene is worse
than dick hygiene, bro.
You know, especially if someone's
circumcised. So why you know it's nah,
bro. Nah, bro.
And another thing is, no, what I was
saying is the fact that Greavvesy, they
don't sit there and say that you're wrong.
They don't sit there and say that you're wrong
um three time. They don't sit there and
say that you're wrong um
seven times out of 10 and they're wrong
three times out of 10. They just think
they're never wrong.
They they think that they're never wrong
because how is it then all of them
screenshots, how can they all be right, bro?
They do make excuses. It's like what you
said. You you said it yourself. They
think women are angels.
They think that there's no way a woman
could [ __ ] someone over intentionally
because they've got a [ __ ] It sounds
vulgar, but true.
They they don't seem to think that it
could be in any woman to lead someone
on. It can't be. So yeah, they think
they're angels basically. Yeah, like
what you said. You said it yourself.
Well, yeah, you said it yourself.
Oh, that's my food, Captain.
Oh my god, it is cold out there, bro. [ __ ] Right.
>> Your name?
>> PJ. Peter.
>> Well, you've ordered it to the door. [laughter]
>> You've ordered it to the door.
>> Yeah, it's my mom.
>> You've ordered it to that door.
>> Okay. Thank you. Yeah. Right.
This is the way I'm going to celebrate
my little win. Oh, I'm so excited
to celebrate my little win.
And you [snorts] know why? Do you know
why? Because I'm an absolute burg.
One second, man.
Oh, that looks nice. That doesn't look
like watery or
I'm going to do a video. Yeah. Oh bra.
Well, I'm going to do a little video. Yeah.
>> [clears throat] >> Mhm.
I got a video, by the way.
It's coming up.
You little copycats. Why didn't you copy today?
The virgin was probably running to the
bookies. So you want to feel left out
cuz he's a little copycat. But he didn't
have nobody to put the bet on because he's done
because he's an absolute virgin.
He's an absolute virgin.
All time virgin. Hall of Famer virgin.
The [ __ ] virgin.
This is nice. Really?
Have you heard me have a drink yet?
Have you heard me have a sip of drink yet?
No, you haven't. And do you know why
that is, Grezy?
You should know why that is. I know why
that is. Why do you think that is?
Tell us. Come on. You should know.
You've been watching me for a long time now. No.
Why is that greasy? You should There we
go. You know, don't you? You know, mate,
you [ __ ] know. You already know the drill.
I've just done a video if you if you
want to say
I haven't had a chicken com in ages, but
will win a chicken dinner.
Steen Albert's not going to be too happy
about me within a sec. Is he greasy?
But all seriousness, listen to me, bro.
Do you agree on the part where
they are going for the same stereotypical guy
and they're not just [ __ ] um
and they're not just the [ __ ] that they
are going for the same guy over and over
again? But don't listen to oh they don't
know what they're like. It's [ __ ]
bro. It is bollock with these women.
It's not that they don't know what
they're like. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. Don't take that [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] Of course they know what
they're [ __ ] like, bro. They know
these men are no good.
[ __ ] off, man.
Do you know what a guy said to me? He
done a video or something. He was like,
"Oh, how are these people going to try
and call you negative? They've not
walked in your shoes. They've not lived
your life. How is another grown man
going to try and tell you your
experiences?" It's the truth, isn't it?
It's true, don't it? It is true. You know,
I'm going to send you the video. It's
the same black guy. I'm going to play
it. I'm going to play it. I'm going to
play it. Bro,
how much is this? It cost me uh It cost £16.
Yeah, it cost me £16. This curry
is that right busy
is so much better. This is still nice though.
So there you go. You're going to have to
wait a little while now, Grezy, for
another copycat statement.
I made a copycat statement, didn't I?
That's funny as [ __ ]
There's some There's lots of horror
films coming out next month. Music.
There's lots of horror films coming out. Yeah.
There's one called the Bade or something.
This is nice music. You don't see me like like J
Papas. I've got one papa.
I've got one papa do. I did all the
papadoms, but I wasn't that hungry. I
just wanted a vindaloo to celebrate, you
know, to comfort eat.
All right with you, Rosie. Mhm. Copy that.
So, what's the what did you say? What's
the cat doing now? Crazy. What's the cat
doing now? Is it still looking to copy?
>> Waiting for what?
Waiting for what though?
Yeah, it might be, mate. [laughter]
Triple H. I'm not being friends with no [ __ ] virgin.
I'm not being no I'm not being friends
with some absolute virgin
some [ __ ] skinned little rat face virgin
I only get with people that spice
I'm only friends with spicy peopley
you remember me and USA Izzy went for steak Grezy
H. Do you remember when we went for um
steak? Was that cute?
One second. I'll show you.
I loving some curry. Yeah,
it's good. This weather warms you up quite nicely.
Yeah, warms up quite lovely.
Do you remember me in USA as he went for
a lovely steak? That was so cute, wasn't it? Really?
I thought I'd found the one.
But it was all a lie.
All a hoax. Just hurry.
I wasn't that hungry. I just wanted to celebrate.
I had steak earlier. I had steak for my teeth.
Lady took me it.
Yeah. Lady took me it. It was all right.
I've had I've had better. Yeah, that
that's quite tasty to be honest.
Oh, that's quite tasty.
I missed the tenants cuz of me banis, you know.
That was absolutely lush.
They used to cook me bananas like this
with a little spider thing in it. Oh mate,
when I had that foot injury, [ __ ] hell, mate.
It was absolutely lost, bro. Yeah.
So, who's my mama now? Boozy.
There was one time we went to this Indian place
and he shout his pants. Well, he shhated
his pants the next day. So, we were at
the Indian right and you and me being
big bollocks having having a vindaloo.
He wanted a vindaloo. I said, "I don't think
you can have it.
I don't think
you you can hack it, lad.
I don't think so. And he he insisted. He
insisted and he ate it. I said, "Don't
say I don't warn you, mate." Then the
next day he called me up. I was in bed
[ __ ] on the toilet saying, "I've got
the shits. I've got the shits." I said,
"I [ __ ] told you. I [ __ ] told you,
mate. I [ __ ] told you." You know, he
would listen to me.
Yeah. Yeah, he won't listen to me.
They're not for people like him.
They're a big strong Turkish man like
me. I can put Americans and grow beards.
Is that crazy? Isn't that funny? [snorts]
So, who's my mama now anyways?
[snorts] Ah, lovely.
Why is this about [snorts]
signal bellies? Have you seen that coming?
That looks like that [ __ ] virgin. the
version of butter.
Let's get out of there.
Might treat myself to spoons tomorrow.
Why not? Why the [ __ ] not? You only live once, you know.
This co is going to be [ __ ] flat soon.
She don't want to know you. She don't
want to know you. She don't want to know
She don't want to know. She don't want
to know. Don't want to know.
I ate all the chicken.
I've had all the chicken.
There's no chicken left. Yeah.
Oh, I haven't any
What did Timmy say? Someone tried giving
him a [ __ ] and they bit his dick.
Yeah, it's the same repeating stories.
What is wrong with that virgin?
Does he not know when to give it a rest
when somebody don't want to know him anymore?
Doesn't he not know when
he's trying to film me? Oh, yeah.
What did you think of that? Yeah, I said
don't touch my phone.
Uh, okay. I'll tell you the sto gra.
Well, basically I went to um
this this restaurant and they said, "Do
you want ice for the coke or do you not
want ice for the coke?" This is how this
is how autistic and obsessed he is. So,
I'm thinking the cocoa is going to be
cold, isn't it? So, they they say, "Do
you want ice or do you not want ice?" I
said, "Okay, um, I don't want ice." So,
they brought it to the table and it was
[ __ ] warm. And I said, "Oh, can you
put a bit of ice in it because it is it
is warm. I didn't expect it to be warm."
And he's been going on about the same
thing for [ __ ] years.
He's been going on about the same thing
for [ __ ] 10 years.
Cuz normally it's cold, isn't it? Ice or
no ice? It was warm. Must have said,
"Okay, can you put some ice in it?" And
[ __ ] what, Virgin boy? How much baby?
So, who is my mom?
No, that's him, mate. That's him. It
come in, Mr. B. It's coming in. It's
coming in, mate. £110. Oh, I got it. I
got the thing.
Yeah. Come in, mate.
Yeah. See you next week. See you next Yeah, bro.
I might do a roulette video soon.
Um, you know, I might do a nice little
roulette video soon.
Okay with you, Greasy Boss. Obviously,
I've got my Greasy first.
I don't know why I say these things
because I don't listen to him anyways.
I don't listen to him [ __ ] anyways.
No matter what he says.
>> Yeah, I might do at some point, but
not not not saying that. Bye-bye, MongoD.
Bye, [ __ ] Bye, child. defends.
Absolute virgins on here.
I didn't know about that bar.
All right, though.
He needs to He needs to [ __ ] off. He's
obsessed. I don't want anything to do
with a little virgin.
You're not anything to do with a little virgin. [clears throat] [ __ ] virgin. Yeah. Yeah. Should
be right cashing that in tomorrow, ain't it?
I'm the one with the slip, matey.
If they don't pay me out, I'll smash the
[ __ ] shop up.
I'll smash the [ __ ] shop up, mate. Yeah.
Oh, I can't even play that without that
thing, can I? [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] I need to plug it in.
Why? It's the same stories. It's the
same boring repeating stories, bro.
Why do you listen to them? It's the same repeating.
Oh, it's just
Why? It's the same repeaters.
No, it can't be, bro. It can't be cuz
I've got the original slip.
And they're not trolls. They're
spastics. Bro, don't even call them
trolls. They're spastics.
Bro, they're not even trolls. They're spastics.
They ain't trolls.
Yeah, they're not even trolls. They're
[ __ ] spastics, lad.
I don't know why you call them trolls.
They're [ __ ] spastics.
That's what they are. Spastics.
Absolute spastics on here, bro.
Doubt it, bro. Doubt it.
They don't pay me. I'll smash the shop
up. Bro, you [ __ ] mad.
I knew someone had done that before.
They were cheating on this machines, right?
I can make you laugh. Trip R. Him and
the cashier was There was a thing going on.
Yeah, there was a thing going on, bro.
With the cashier.
With the cashier, bro. There was a thing going on
um with with the cashier in it
with winnings and they were like adding
credits more credits than they were
supposed to. And he went back, bro. He
smashed the shop. Well, he didn't go
back. He smashed the shop up cuz they
wouldn't pay him out. Police were
called. Triple H.
Police were called. Mad isn't it? These
place these places are not good. Triple
H. They're not good. these places, but
you think it's all funny.
But yeah, anyways, back to the stories.
Yeah, he needs to stop saying he needs
to stop telling the same stories. It's boring, bro.
It's boring as [ __ ]
Yeah, it it's [ __ ] boring as [ __ ] bro.
Same old repeating stories. [ __ ] hell.
It's [clears throat] so They're so
boring. Do you actually watch that
version, bro? Jesus. It's the same
boring repeating [ __ ]
Why do you watch that?
Why do you watch that, bro?
Oh, Trip Rates, I've caught you on that
Simon Wilson's channel. You watch Simon
Wilson, don't you?
That's another thing I forgot to bring
up. I've caught you on Simon Wilson's channel.
Gay boy. There's no such thing. He's got lied.
He's [ __ ] got lied.
Yeah, I've seen you on uh I've I've seen you.
I've seen you on these channels, bro. to
see you on the channel.
>> He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] mate.
I don't believe that he does these no
money challenges, bro. Well, he does,
but he's cheating. The America one, he
was cheating, bro.
That America one, he was cheating, bro.
Yeah, he was [ __ ] Yeah, cheating, is it?
Yeah, [ __ ] cheating, isn't it? Proper
cuz he used like subscriber help.
Yeah, I don't know about all the other
ones, but yeah, of course, bro. in
America. He was using subscriber help.
Yeah, he was using subscriber help.
which obviously is cheating.
It's cheating, bro. Obviously. Yep.
I get my little benefit allowance soon.
Triple H. my little benefit allowance.
Yeah, I I I get um benefits because I'm really anxious.
Got I've got crippling anxiety. Me?
Yeah, man. Crippling anxiety.
Really bad, bro. I can't leave the house
or anything. No, mate. Not me, mate. Not me.
No, they're not. No woman. No woman out
there is nice.
[ __ ] right off. You're trying to trick
me. Nah, there's no women that are nice
in this world, sadly, bro. Mm-
Yeah, you wish, mate. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, you [ __ ] wish.
You [ __ ] wish, matey.
That ain't happening.
These trolls have these people really
got no life in it.
Definitely definitely definitely
definitely definitely not. [snorts] You wish.
You wish, mate. You can't do it with the code.
And you can't just do it with the code.
you need a slip
and you and it will and it will prove
that you weren't in the shop making that
bet. So, it's not going to work anyways.
that just goes to show how skinned you
are as well that you're even making even
making comments like that. This just
goes to show that you're [ __ ] skinn.
Yeah, you wish matey. You [ __ ] wish. One second.
That little bastard. Little low lives.
That's what they are in there, ain't it? Virgins.
You can't even do that anyways. You need
a slip. You can't even just do it with the code.
No, it won't because I've got the slip.
No, it won't be because No, no, no, no,
no. It won't be
because they need to prove that they've
done it and they can't do that. It's not
going to work.
It's not going to work.
It's not going to work. It doesn't work like that.
doesn't work like that, matey. [snorts]
And uh yeah, that's that. So yeah. Yeah, mom.
And guess what? The book is here.
No, no, no, no, no. It doesn't happen,
bro. And stop talking about it. I'm not
talking about this either, bro. It's
pathetic. I'm not talking about this.
So, stop bringing it up because I'm not
talking about it.
It's pathetic. kicking his ball in as
well. It doesn't happen and I'm not
talking about it either. So, change the subject.
And guess what? The bookies here open at 7:00.
That's another joy about living in London.
Okay, bro. I'm not talking about this no more.
Okay, I'm not talking about this no
more. I don't want to talk about this no
more. It's boring, bro. It's not going to happen. Yep.
You already know, Greezy. 100%, bro.
Yeah. 7:00 in the morning.
Yeah, they're open 7 in the morning here.
Good luck, matey. Oh, man.
Never your mind. Yeah.
Yeah, I'll just I'll wait. Grezy,
bro, these people are not These people
can't even leave their [ __ ] house for
[ __ ] sake. Jesus Christ. You could go
[ __ ] midday and nothing would happen.
These people are scared to leave their [ __ ] house.
That's funny, is it? Greasy. Yeah.
Anyways, we're moving on from this now.
We're not talking about this anymore.
So, uh, yeah, we're not talking about this anymore.
>> Gabby was definitely definitely a virgin
since you put his name up. Did you see
him on lodge? Did you see him on Lord
Jay's the other day?
Did you see him on [ __ ] Lord Jay's
the other day with [ __ ] uh Autumn?
Oh my god. He's definitely a virgin.
Definitely definitely definitely a virgin.
Have you seen him, bro? What he was
saying and [ __ ]
Yeah, you can't you can't you can't cash
in my bet. So, bye-bye. But anyways,
[ __ ] Mongos. These people are [ __ ]
disabled on here.
Yeah, proper, bro. He's a proper virgin.
Wall is a is a proper proper virgin.
Okay, I don't care, bro. I'm not talking
about this no more. Whatever.
Okay, bro. Whatever.
Whatever you say. Whatever. They're
going to cash in my bet. Okay. Whatever.
We've said this a million times. We'll
see you tomorrow, won't we?
It's not possible, but Okay.
Bro, I've got the winning slip. They
don't have the winning slip.
That's that. And if they don't have the
winning And if they don't have the
winning slip, they're going to have to
prove that they've placed a bet. They
can't prove that they've placed a bet on
that terminal. It's not going to work.
But whatever you say,
whatever you say, bro.
If you lose, if Yeah. If you lose,
right? If you lose the the the the [ __ ] um
if you lose the bet,
right? If you lose the bet, right?
They're going to if you lose the slip,
they're going to be like, "Well, yeah,
there you go." So, someone completely
out of London
has lost the slip and they've come into
a shop miles away. I don't think so, bro.
I don't think so. So, yeah. Yeah,
these people are they [ __ ] losers in
it. Absolute losers, bro. Skittle fat ugly losers.
No lives. That's what they are here.
So, why has the [ __ ] uh Xbox
subscript um sub subscription gone up to £22? [clears throat]
Yeah, they can't do it, bro. I've just
looked it up.
No, they can't do it, bro. I knew that's
how it work cuz my sister's boyfriend
lost lost the slip before.
Yeah, it's not going to work, bro.
Not going to work.
I knew it.
Tomorrow. No, I'm chilling, bro. No.
Yeah, you should have copied the bet,
man. Why didn't you copy the bet we
would have been 90 quid up?
[ __ ] little copycat. Little copycat.
Yeah, it's not going to work.
Not going to work, bro.
You a little copycat. >> [snorts] >> Yeah,
I'm quitting the garden soon anyways.
I'll just be doing 20 pound on the
football. What did you think of when I
was putting £120 on the football bet? Squeezy,
what about when I was putting that much
on the bets? What did you think, little copycat?
[ __ ] This [ __ ] Reddit, man.
Yeah, I won't be doing that again, bro.
I will not be doing that again. Yeah.
Okay. Well, what if you Okay. Okay. So,
what if you was on the ground a month,
right, and you wanted to go to America?
How would you do it?
You would have to try and win some
money, isn't it?
There's two ways you can do it. You'd
have to either live off 50 a week for
like 6 months or [ __ ]
gamble and you could get in the [ __ ]
But with that, you could end up [ __ ]
If you was to do that, yeah, the [ __ ]
You get [ __ ] if you do that. And then
if you lose, you're [ __ ]
Then you might have to sell things. So,
I don't know how people I don't know
cuz if you lose, you lose all your money.
Well, [ __ ] imagine that, bro. Imagine that.
These people can't even leave their house, bro. Yeah.
So, what would you do, Grezy? Would you
have to gamble in order to do it or what?
Say you needed five grand and you get a
grand a month. How you how how would you
get five grand? You'd have to win the money, though.
And then if you lose, you're [ __ ]
And you're [ __ ] then.
You would be [ __ ] completely. Yeah.
What with like with Izzy and stuff? Triple H.
Oh yeah. Do you remember Do you remember
the DJ San Andreas days?
No, you can't.
Yeah. Do you remember? Do do you
remember when Izzy used to come in? She
was a player. A player at heart.
Somebody said to me, "Did you touch
Isabelli's boobies, Greavvesy? That's
just immature, is it?" Nah, that's just immature.
Do you think it's funny, is it?
No, bro. That's immature.
That's immature, bro. It
Yeah, that's immature.
Did you touch the belly's boobies?
I'll start going out approaching soon.
um from next week maybe.
Do you not think it's unfair though, Greavesy?
Do you not think it's really really really unfair,
you know, trying to find a partner,
trying to have a sex life, having to
deal with all of that [ __ ] I think
it's really unfair. Me,
what do you think? I think it's really, really unfair. Yeah,
you should It shouldn't be that way.
Shouldn't be that way, bro. Just to try
and find someone.
It was um PS
three, I think. No, PS4. It was PS4.
It was PS4, bro. Oh,
bro. I want to stream Smackdown versus
Raw 2009. That's the best game ever. But
I don't know how you can stream it. I
don't think you can even use it on PS4.
It's an old old old old old Smackdown
game, bro. I can show you all the
glitches and everything.
It's called Smackdown First as well,
2009. That's my favorite one. Favorite
And my second favorite [clears throat]
one is 2010. And then after that I
didn't play him.
What's your favorite Smackdown?
2009 was the best.
I could even go out this week if I
wanted to cuz I said I was going to go out December.
I'm not going out in November. Waste of
money. Waste of time. Waste of money.
It's a waste of money going out in November.
November. Reevesy, January, waste of
money. February, waste of money.
January, February, and November.
Complete waste of money and time going out.
Would you agree?
Yeah. 2007. I don't think I had that.
No, I think I did. That's the one with
Triple H on the [ __ ] cover in it.
That's my Yeah,
January waste of money. February waste
of money. November waste of money.
November is a waste of money because you
get into November,
December is the next month. So, you're
going to need money for December, New
Year's Eve, Christmas. So, you're
wasting money in November.
It doesn't make sense. It doesn't make
sense at all. And then you could have
used that money for December. Then you
can save from January again.
Waste of time, bro. I went out when I
went out. It was [ __ ]
Yeah. December's the month.
December's the month, boy. Trust me.
That's when the money starts [ __ ]
going in it. Would you agree?
November waste of time.
It is a waste of time
and next year.
I don't want to go out until like March.
But I say that I say that Greavvesy. I
don't want to go out until March. But I
always end up I only last until midFeb.
I stay in January. It's really cold,
isn't it? But then I I only last until like midFebruary.
Still a month and a half, ain't it?
But really, you should not.
Maybe end of February, maybe.
You shouldn't really go out from until March, really.
But you never go out, do you, Greasy?
You never go out.
I'm definitely definitely definitely
100% going on holiday next year. 100 fucking%. Bro,
I was thinking April time. Greavvesy. I
was thinking April time. Okay with you, boss.
Is that okay with you, boss?
If I go on holiday in April, boss,
that's when my mama used to go on on
holiday. But it was it was cheaper then.
It was cheaper. It's cheaper to go out
in April than it is summer. But that's
why I think that's why my mama used to go
my mama used to go away in April. Greasy
by this account. Gre um Triple 8 said to
me that Peter Benny can't get attached
anymore because he's already found his mama.
There's so many [ __ ] immature people
in this community, you know,
because he's already found.
Is there anything in the pictures? Let
me have a little look. Nope.
I can't believe the escort was messaging me.
It makes sense just to stick to escorts,
really, doesn't it?
You get to a certain age where you don't
want to keep dealing with these women's [ __ ] anymore.
Isn't that right, Grezy? Right.
I love this phone, bro. It's so good.
just follow his ace, man.
It's not really an option, is it? No.
No. Still no horror films.
I I will Yeah, but do you know why I do
it? Triple H because it's too easy.
It's too easy, isn't it? It's too easy
to get sex. You
It's too easy, bro.
So that's why I do it. Everyone pays
anyways one way or another.
I have no problem with paying. I I I
don't have a problem with paying. My
thing with escorts is not paying.
It's not about the paying. I don't give
a [ __ ] about paying.
Say you saw someone on the street and
they said, "Oh, if you give £200, you
can do whatever you want to me." I'd pay
it. I don't care about paying, bro.
Paying doesn't bother me.
Paying. It's not paying doesn't bother me.
There's different thing with the There's
different things with the escorts.
There's different thing with the escorts, bro.
I'd pay. I I don't mind paying, bro.
Cuz it's a direct transaction, isn't it?
I'd happily pay, bro. I don't [ __ ] care.
Think of if you could if money actually
worked with normal people, Greavvesy,
you would do it. I would do it cuz I'm
getting what I want. So, I don't mind
paying what everyone's got different
opinions on it. Some people say they
don't pay. Some people think like me and
say, "Oh, you pay." There's no right or
wrong answer. Everyone's got their own
opinion on it. I personally think you
pay either way, whether it's directly,
indirectly, and also there's nothing
wrong with paying.
I don't know, bro. That's the way I've
always seen it.
Look at USA. I paid her
indirectly a steak meal. Triple H.
Isn't that right? Um, Grezy, still paying indirectly.
If I didn't do it, I wouldn't have slept
with her. So, what
there are times when you don't pay. I've
had it where I don't pay where I've
bought a drink and they bought me a
drink. But there are times, but most of
the time you do you do pay.
Obviously, there are times where you don't, but
I don't know, bro. It's too easy.
And you get to stay single as well, Grezy.
You know why women don't like people
using escorts? Triple H.
It's bec and greasy. It's because it
takes away the power.
It takes away the power. If you can't
figure that out, then that's on you.
You understand what I'm saying? And it
takes like they
okay so they be [ __ ] and [ __ ]
because they know that men want sex and
they want them and that they can do what
they want because they know that they
hold all the keys when it comes to
dating. But when someone pays that's
over. It's over. So that's why women
don't like it. So yeah.
What do you mean? Why don't I tell these
women up front?
Again, the the screenshots again, the approaches,
they want to stay single as well.
No. So, that's not So, yeah.
Yeah, I don't pay that much.
I don't I don't pay that much, bro. I
don't pay that much.
I pay like 80 and I just get a [ __ ] normally.
I have paid £200 though before when I
was subleting and that I spent like £400 on escorts.
Yeah. But main I think I've only played
that once and that's cuz she swallowed
my [ __ ] I wanted a very specific thing. But
yeah, but women have got high body counts.
So I mean that New Zealander
that I had sex with, her [ __ ] stunk.
That Sigs [ __ ] stunk, bro. No escorters
I've ever been with have ever smelt.
grievously. No escort that I've been
with has ever stunk.
They have not stunk at all. Normal women do stink.
But I don't I don't have sex. I just get
I just get [ __ ]
Yeah. I just get [ __ ]
normally. I don't normally have sex with
them. I don't have sex. I just get the [ __ ]
and come in their mouth. I don't I don't
really have I don't have sex with them, bro.
I just want their mouth on Peter Belly's penis.
You know what I found strange though,
Grezy, is that it's like I was saying,
do you agree with what I said in the
video, right? They talk about men having bad attitude,
but yet this miss all of these women
having bad attitudes when when people
try to speak to them.
Bit weird, isn't it? I'm sure you
noticed that, isn't it? They say that
men that can't get women have got bad attitudes,
but haven't these women had stinking
attitudes when people tried to speak to them? Grievy. Strange, though. >> [snorts]
>> When I went out about a month ago,
not two weeks ago, a month ago, these
women have bad attitudes, bro. Bad
attitude. I had one that gave me a
thumbs up. Entitled, stuck up, rude. So
what? They're allowed to be all them
things, but women men can't be fed up
with their [ __ ] Bit sexist, isn't it?
Bit weird. What's your opinion on that,
Grezy? So, they're allowed to be stuck
up, rude, entitled, but we're not
allowed to be fed up with their [ __ ]
That's not fair, is it?
I don't really think that's fair, is it, Grezy? You know,
so yeah. What do you think, Grezy? What
I'm saying? Go on.
Yeah, but if you don't use escorts,
you're never going to get laid. Well,
you would get laid, but it means you
have to go out every day approaching,
and I'm not doing that. So, it's either
either way you lose your pride. Whether
you use an escal or you deal with normal
women, either way, you'll lose your pride.
Your pride's spoken for, no matter which
one you you deal with,
cuz say you you you use it at an escort.
what this Triple H is saying and then
you use [ __ ] and then you and then
when you go out and you approach you're
you're disrespecting yourself when
you're dealing with normal women.
No, no, no, Grezy. But you're not
listening to what I'm saying, right?
They talk about men's attitude,
right? But how many women have stinking
attitudes when you have tried talking to
them? So what is it okay for them to
have a rude attitude and be rude but not
men are not allowed to feel a type of
way when they've been through [ __ ]
It doesn't make sense, bro. But either
way, you lose your pride.
Whether it's escorts or normal women.
Nah, bro. Not at all. Dealing with
normal women's worse. stuck up giving
them power. You You lose your pride when
you deal with normal women. Trust me,
you do. The games, the mind. If I If
they said to me right now, "Yeah,
you could either use escorts for the
rest of your life
or deal with women." I'd be like, "Escults 100%."
Boring. Bye-bye. Fantasy stories.
Escorts 100%. 100%. No questions asked. You know,
dealing with toxic women that are not
growing in their head.
[ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that.
You know, that is not normal, bro. That
is not normal. And you could even agree
on that and it agrees with you that
dealing with these women is not normal.
The mind games, um, the [ __ ] the
dickheadness, that is not having pride for yourself.
That is not and that is what you'd have
to be putting up with if you were trying
to find someone or get laid or whatever
it is you want. That's what you're going
to have to be putting up with. No one
should have to put up with that.
Nobody should have to put up with that, bro.
That's bad. That's [ __ ] bad, bro.
They're rude, stuck up, entitled, play
mind games. You can't meet anyone normal, you know.
Yeah, but what? Oh my god. But you're
not listening to what I'm saying, bro.
If I wanted to get with a woman, that's
what I'd have to be dealing with. And
I'm not dealing with it. I'm not a virgin, bro.
I don't I don't have to deal with that [ __ ]
The only time I go out and try is when
I'm born out of my [ __ ] head and I
got nothing better to do and I want to
go out anyways other than that. Yeah.
Cuz I know that there no women are
different. I know all women are the
same. So it doesn't piss me off, bro.
Cuz I know all women are the same. So
well, I'm going to play you this video. there. [ __ ]
Why do you know who the side men are? Triple H.
They just popped up on my [ __ ]
I need to stop drinking Coke, bro. It
[ __ ] your teeth up. One sec.
>> How you guys doing on this Saturday? Um,
I'm going talk to you guys about
something about a comment that someone
left on my um last page on my on my last presentation
to talk about uh you know guys, people
who try to give you false
Um, people that try to give you false
hope, man, they know that it's no hope
for you. They just That's That's that they just
>> Listen, Grezy, can you hear it? Can you
hear it, Grezy?
>> They just, you know, like I never
attention to give me false hope.
That's all BS, man. That's all BS because
>> Can you hear me, Greg Z?
Someone who never lived your life
never been in your position.
>> Like I never understood how you got
other men who think they going to tell
you something when they ain't even lived your life.
>> Yeah, that's true. you been through something [laughter]
another man about his life. >> Listen,
>> endured the things that he's endured in
his life. See, you got a lot of people
that like speaking on things that they
don't know nothing about. And I could
never understand people like that. How crazy.
Just be quiet because you don't know.
We just don't know. See
what you see.
And a lot
of positions need to understand what is
another grown man going to tell you
about your life. When he ain't been your
position, [laughter] he ain't been
through what you been through. What
another grown man going to tell you
about your circumstances?
Somebody that ain't lived your life.
Somebody that ain't experienced what
you've experienced, they just talking.
They just talking.
They your life. You got some guys who
would say that,
you know, these dudes that not desired,
not chosen by the opposite gender.
Some people would say that
these dudes are just negotiable men false
That's that's that's that's their whole
message to get false hope. Tell dudes
that a shot for them when it ain't no shot. See, [clears throat]
a lot of people just like blowing smoke
out of their behind. And you got a lot
of people that like writing checks that
they behind can
[laughter] see somebody that had to live
your life or been through the challenges
you've been through. They don't know
what the hell they talking about.
They don't know what they're talking
about. [laughter] That's why when I say
when people try to tell you about your
situation, they try to tell you about
your life. Don't let no another man tell
you about your life. See, people love
giving people false hope, telling people
that there is a uh a chance for them
when it ain't.
When you've been treated bad your whole
life and done wrong your whole life. [laughter]
>> It's true.
>> They're telling you that there's a
chance for you. No, it ain't.
See, I'm here to tell you, don't let no
another man tell you about your life.
Nobody going to tell you about your life
when they ain't lived your life.
That's why it ain't nothing that nobody
can tell me. I ain't trying to hear it.
You know, you ain't live my life. You
got dudes that'll say, you know, these
dudes that ain't wanted by women, they
just got to learn game. Ain't no such
thing as game. Some men just ain't want it.
>> Is it true these days?
>> Is that true? [clears throat]
>> 35y old man.
Ain't nothing that nobody can tell me.
Nothing. Not even Jesus himself. Cuz I
still probably wouldn't listen to him.
Ain't nothing nobody could tell me.
What do you think of that?
How can you not hear it, you [ __ ] silly goose?
Okay, I'll put it back on in a bit, but
I want to put something else on.
How can you not hear it, man?
It's time. Look.
>> Oh gosh. You need to hold the bundle only 469
secret only £54.99.
Friday deal plus get up to 12 months to
pay with Berry Pay. I'll pay no interest
very let's make it cycle.
>> Are you looking for anything in particular?
>> Yes. I was wondering whether you had any
pirate memory games suitable for
children between the ages of four and eight.
>> Uh just have a look.
Gentleman here WANTS TO KNOW WE'VE GOT
ANY PIRATE memorates
>> name of Linda Williams.
>> Right. So you're looking for a specific
person? No, I'm looking to meet any
woman with the name of Linda Williams. >> Yeah.
>> Not my favorite.
>> No, my favorite name is Katherine Drew.
But in [clears throat] my time of life,
you can't afford to be too picky
because as I always said,
age woman to meet.
>> Oh, really? Anybody between the ages of
38 and 39?
>> You should have them height. Yes.
>> Do you prefer it?
>> No. Any particular length?
>> Anything from here to here.
They can't cast the bet.
>> They can't cast They can't cast the bet
without the slip by going to the
specific store. So, it's not possible.
You can't cash in a bet with just the barcode.
So, that's not possible. They can't You
can't cash in a bet without the slip.
Even if you had the barcode, not possible.
So it would never happen.
It would never ever ever ever ever happen.
So yeah, would never happen. It's not possible.
Absolutely not possible.
Antman's been quiet. Antman's been quiet, matey.
Look, it doesn't work like that. Matey.
Yeah, he can do that, but he can't cash
it in without the slip. So,
yeah, he can do that all he wants, but
he's not going to be able to cash it in
without the slip. So, he'll be wasting his time.
He will be wasting his time
cuz you can't cash it in without the slip.
So yeah, good luck with that one, matey.
Good luck with that one, matey. Cuz you
can't catch it in without the slip.
So he'd be wasting his time.
Yep. I've looked it up as well.
So, you can't cash it in without the
slip. If you lose the slip, you have to
go to the exact bookies that you put the
bet on and know the exact time and I
have to look up on the system. It's not
going to work.
It's definitely definitely definitely
one million% not going to work.
So, good luck with that.
You'll be completely wasting your time.
You've been wasting your time. You might
as well just stay in your little
nesticles at at 7:00 in the middle of night.
So yeah, my sister's boyfriend's lost a
slip, so I know exactly how it works. Yeah.
Why didn't anyone copy that bet anyways?
Why didn't anyone copy that [ __ ] bet?
You [ __ ] bunch of copycats. Oh, yeah.
I'm having fun on my flagship phone. How
many more years do you reckon this
phone's going to last, Greavvesy? How
many more years?
How many more years do you think it's
going to last? This uh flagship phone.
It's not going to work. It's not going
to work. You can do that. It's not going
to work. You need a physical. I'm not
talking about this no more, bro. You're
not scaring me. So, I don't know why you
keep saying it.
It's not going to work. It doesn't work like that.
So, I don't know why you keep doing
this. You're not It's not scaring me,
bro. So, I don't know why you keep doing this.
It's not scaring me because it's not
possible. You can't cash in a bet
without a slip
and it would need to come up on the
system. So, I don't know why you keep
saying this cuz you're not scaring me,
bro. So, I don't know why you keep saying this.
It's not going to happen because
I'm not I'm not even explaining it, bro.
I'm not explaining it anymore. But yeah,
you keep thinking that's the way it
works, but it's not the way it works.
100% not the way it works.
Yeah, there will be somebody cashing it in. Me.
Yeah, there will be someone cashing it
in, mate. It will be [ __ ] me.
No other [ __ ] Oh yeah.
It's going to be very funny when it
comes back to London though, isn't it?
It's not going to work.
That's not going to happen. Bro, that V
is such a loser though, is it? Proper
proper fat virgin loser.
You know what makes me laugh about these
people? You could give them one slap in
real life and you'd knock him out.
Oh my god. Give them one slap and you'd
knock them out the fat ugly mongos. But
they'll never meet anyone. That's the
thing with these these people in here.
[ __ ] sake, man. Tooth again. is that
I'll never meet anyone.
Yeah, good luck. You're not going to be
able to do it. You can't do it without
the slip. So, good luck with that.
Yeah, good luck with that because you
can't do it without the slip. It doesn't
work like that. You can't do it without the slip.
Look it up if you don't believe me.
So you be wasting your time because you
can't do it without the slip.
Yeah. You can't do it without the slip.
Mate, if you lose the slip, doesn't
matter if you've got a picture of it. It
doesn't matter if you've got the a
picture of it. It's not going to work if
you don't have the slip. Any anyone can
have a picture of it. It doesn't mean
anything. You need you need the slip and the barcode.
I don't Why are we still having this
conversation, bro? You're not scaring
me, so I don't know why you keep saying it.
You know what I'm saying? And why is
that V back on? He's such a sad bastard.
I hate that [ __ ] bro. I hate it when
you bring up these little keyboard
warriors to me as well, bro.
Hate these little keyboard warriors,
bro. These little fat ugly [ __ ]
virgins. I hate it when you bring them
up to me, bro. I swear down. [ __ ]
hate it. I do. [ __ ] hate it.
These all fat ugly nerds. Don't know why
you bring on my channel, bro.
Doesn't matter. You need a Doesn't
matter. You need You need a slip. You
can't cash it in without the slip.
[clears throat] So, good luck, mate. You
So, good luck.
cuz you can't cash it in without the slip. So,
he doesn't have the time either.
Good luck though. Anyways, not going to work.
Anyways, moving on.
Being there at 7:00 in the morning, Grezy
being there at 7:00 in the morning.
Imagine that, Greasy. 7:00
in the morning. Yeah.
Yeah, man. Stop bringing up these
[ __ ] nerds up as well, bro. Stop
bringing up these [ __ ] nerds on my channel.
Stop bringing up these [ __ ] nerds.
They ain't got a life.
You remember when that bo pretended to
be USA Izzy for 3 months? Sad, sad, sad bastard.
Don't know if any of you remember.
They're just jealous. They could never
win a bet like that. They could never
win a bet like that, mate. Never. They
could never win a bet like that.
Isn't that right, Greasy?
So, what would have it been if I had
[ __ ] £80 on it? Like a grand isn't Grand.
Yeah, think so.
I don't care to be honest.
What about trying to get free next time, Grezy?
Nah, I think that's pushing it in. Free.
It's hard to get threes.
I've got a little uni brow now. Greasy. Look.
Little uni brow.
I need to go to the barbers, man.
Yeah, but it was a both score. Yeah, but
it was a both score, no draw, isn't it?
I know, but it was a both score, no draw.
Next time, bro. Next time. Don't worry.
Next time, lad. Next time.
Don't worry. We'll get the [ __ ] next time, right? >> Yeah. [snorts]
What do you think, M? You think I'm worth it? Oh,
imagine I had Imagine I had 150 on it. [ __ ] hell. Bad. way.
To be honest with you, if you stick to
the football, you won't.
Football, you won't. Football is all
right, but roulette, you will. That's
why I don't want to do the roulette
again, but I might do it again soon.
Like one like a oneoff roulette session.
like a one off. It won't be like Yeah,
it's like Yeah, but the football you won't
you won't go broke with a football.
It's different than roulette.
Yeah, but not football trip is it? When
you stick to when you stick to football,
you won't go broke on football, guy.
I need to brush my teeth, bro. Brush my
teeth. I need to stop looking at my coat, bro.
[ __ ] up my [ __ ] teeth. [snorts]
If anyone Yeah. gets that B's address,
give it to me. I'll go this [ __ ] door
cuz of the stuff that he's done before.
He's another one a complete keyboard
warrior getting people banned from
casinos. Yeah. Just if anyone ever gets
his address, bro, give me a [ __ ] door.
And he doesn't live in Ireland either. I
don't know why people keep saying that
he lives in Ireland. He doesn't live in
Ireland. There's no way that [ __ ] lives
in Ireland. There's other things that
he's done in the past before. The
[ __ ] little keyboard warrior, bro.
And he doesn't live in Ireland either.
So, I don't know why people keep saying
that the fat mole does cuz he [ __ ] doesn't.
Sad little [ __ ] virgin. Yeah.
But yeah, that's the thing with
gambling, bro. Yeah.
I used to be bad on the roulette, but
nowadays not so much. Yeah.
So, what about getting a what about
getting four both teams to score? Triple H.
What about getting four both teams to score? Nah.
Nah. No way. That is [ __ ] That would
be very hard.
But no, bro. I reckon
I reckon you I reckon you could do it. I
reckon you could. I reckon you could if
you studied it long enough. But even
getting two was hard.
Even getting them two were [ __ ] hard, bro.
I reckon you could put 50 on a treble
both scar. No draw.
That's a good return, isn't it?
Yeah, but we're talking to both score.
No draw, bro.
They're hard. Both score no draw is
Yeah, both score no draw is hard, bro.
No, that's too hard
cuz you can get [ __ ] over at any
second. That's the thing.
So, if I done Darlington, I would have
won as well.
If I'd done Darlington, I would have won.
Dude, I was just going to put 120 on two
teams, but I'm not doing that.
No, I'm not doing that [ __ ] I don't
think I'll do that anymore.
Too risky, isn't it?
No, I'll be having a wank, Triple H.
I'll be having a lovely wank.
So, how do you get money, Greasy, then
if you don't gamble? You can't in it.
So, do you want to see a roulette
session then, Triple H?
I can do one if you want. a lovely roulette session.
If you want a roulette session, I can do one.
Maybe like 250 on roulette.
Yeah, probably put like 250 on roulette.
I don't know when. Don't know when.
Going for that number 11. E. Going for
No, not not tomorrow, bro. I'm not doing it tomorrow.
I'm not I would never get addicted
again. I just don't like the Yeah,
that's why I didn't do the 150 today,
bro. That's why I didn't do the 150 today.
That's why I didn't do it cuz I didn't
want to lose and then be put in a bad mood. Yeah.
No, but if I said I'm going to do 250 on
roulette, then I wouldn't be pissed off,
bro. If I if I've set a video
about, oh, I'm going to do 250 on
roulette, then that's that. I'm not
going to be pissed off cuz I could never
get addicted to it again, bro. Ever.
Never ever ever cuz I don't get as much
money anymore. So,
uh, so it would never happen cuz I don't
get as much money anymore. So, I
wouldn't risk it
cuz I wouldn't want to worry about
money. So, it would never happen, bro.
It would never ever ever happen. Never.
Cuz then if I lose, then I don't want to
worry about money. So, I'm not worried
about money. So, I wouldn't chase. Would never happen. So, yeah.
The bet come in, Steven Howard.
The bet come in. I told you to copy it.
Sometimes it's all right, you know, to
be a copycat.
You should have copied the bet, mate.
You come in. Little copycat.
You little copycat.
I remember when I went to Newcastle, I
snugged three women. Yeah.
Yeah. Little copycat.
Yeah. I went to I went to New The first
time I went to Newcastle, I snugged
three women in one night.
No, but it was annoying losing last week
cuz I could have done with that, bro. I
put 50 in, it would would have returned
200 and something.
No, it's not funny. It's annoying, bro.
[ __ ] Spennymore or [ __ ]
What kind of name is that? Spennymore.
Imagine a place a place being called Spennymore. Huh?
Spennymore. You know, Greavvesy,
imagine you're saying you're Imagine
saying you're from Spennymore.
Yeah, I've been to the Northeast a few
times, actually. So, I'll be going out
next week and hopefully I can find a new mama.
I know where it is.
I got a double both score. No draw.
Steven Howard, I thought I'd never see the day.
What you want to do with that, mate, is
you want to stick about 80 quid on two of them. Definitely, mate.
Yeah. I I I won 90 quid. I I won 110 off
20 uh of 20 pound.
That's what you want to do, mate. You
want to try and study them and and get a
both score, no draw. That's where the
money is, bro. Only had [ __ ] 80 quid
on it today.
It would have been 600 maybe,
but like I said, I was happy with that.
Yeah, because they've clocked on with
the [ __ ] odds, isn't it?
The thing with just both teams to score,
you got a lump on it.
No, the first season, no, the f the
start of the season, I put 80 pound and
I got it to 280. That's good odds.
No, that is good odds. That's good odds,
bro. 80 to 280 is good odds on a both
teams to score. Then I won a week after that.
But then 120 to 380, I mean, you need to
lump. That's the problem. And then if
you lose, you've lost loads of money.
So I think you're best off studying at
both teams to score low draw and really
study it. I've been studying these teams
now for a couple of weeks, so I thought
it had the best chance of winning.
I'd go with that, bro.
Yeah, I think that it's because of me,
bro. They [ __ ] made an odd [ __ ]
because of me.
You need to try and get a both score. No
drawing, mate. That's what you need.
You put 80 pound on three teams. You're
[ __ ] laughing, mate. Even three of
them, you know. I only got two, but it
is hard. They are hard to come in and
they can [ __ ] you at any minute. My
heart was pounding, bro. I swear down my
heart was because like it just did, bro.
I just wanted to win the bet in it. It's
not much money, but it's better than
nothing. But the thing is, bro, my heart
was pounding. I said, I hope these [ __ ] don't score.
How How much did you win, Steven Howard?
Yeah, they've seen me come, bro. I've
been rinsing these bastards the past three months.
I don't think I've been able to buy
[ __ ] traders and [ __ ] jeans and go
out and that been rinsing the [ __ ]
mate. [ __ ] rinsing them.
£80 from 30.
But it's even bad now. Even when you put
if you put £500, you get £1,400 back.
It's not worth it.
It's not worth it, is it? It's not worth it.
If you put £500, you get 1,400 pound
back. It's not worth it.
Cuz it before it was like 17,800, but
it's not worth it.
It's not worth it, mate. It's not worth it.
500 to win,400. Nah, you can modding
that on roulette. It's not worth it.
That ain't worth it, bro.
That ain't worth it.
Yeah, good for you. It's not going to
work. Good luck, mate.
Yeah, you're not scaring me and that's
not going to work. So, yeah, good luck with that.
It's not going to work, summar.
They think that they can cash in the bet
without the slip, but they can't. So yeah,
they they say that they're going to try
and cash in my winning bet because they
got the barcode and I've explained a
million times it's not going to work.
So you can go to the bookies. It's not
going to work. You need a physical slip.
It's not going to work. The only way it
would work is if you went to the same
bookies that I went to and you knew the
exact time I went. It's not going to work.
So you sad little bastard.
It is not going to [ __ ] work. You're
wasting your time.
Trust me, it's not going to work. You
can't cash in a bet just from a picture.
Well, you can, but you know, it takes
like 24 hours.
No, it won't. No, it won't. No, it
won't. We still having this
conversation? Are we still having this
No, it won't. Are we still having the same conversation?
Yes, it does. Yes, it does. If they've
lost the slip, yes, it does. If they've
lost a slip, yes, it does need to be the
same bookies. If they're claiming that
they've Bro, we're not having this
conversation. Why do you keep bringing
it up over and over and over again? I've
already explained to you how it works
and you're not listening, so there's no point.
You know, you can't just go in with a
slip and get paid out straight away
saying that you've lost it. They're
going to ask you questions. It's not It
It doesn't work like that. So So
yeah, it's not going to work.
Madness, bro. Absolute madness.
You need a slip. You can cash it in at
any bookies. Yeah.
Yeah. With the slip.
I'm going to keep blocking you if you
keep talking about this. Anyways, I'm
going to block you, bro, cuz we've had
this conversation a million times. And I
don't know why you keep bringing it up.
You keep bringing it up over and over
and over again. And I said I don't want
to talk about it anymore. You keep
bringing it up. So if you keep bring it
up, I'm going to have to time you out, matey. Sorry. Sorry, matey.
Give it a [ __ ] break. You've been on
about it for the past three [ __ ] hours.
Jesus [ __ ] Christ.
It's not going to work. I will look
tomorrow cuz I've already looked it up.
If you've lost a slip, right, you need
to go back to that exact bookies and
fill out a form. I've already looked it up.
I've already looked it up, mate. I've
already looked it up. If you've lost a
slip, you have to go back to that exact
same books on the system that you've
placed the bet on, which I've explained
a million times. Yeah. And I will see
you tomorrow when I get the money. Yeah,
I will see you tomorrow, bro, when the
money's in my pocket. Yeah, I will. I'll
do a video to you as well.
So, yeah, we will see you tomorrow.
Yeah, we'll definitely definitely
definitely see tomorrow. Yeah,
I didn't lose the slip, Stephen Howard.
I've basically put the slip up and it's
got the barcode. It's got the barcode on it,
right? It's got the barcode on it and
they're saying that they can cash it in
with just the barcode number. And I'm
trying to explain many times that you
can't do that if you don't have the sip.
If you don't have the slip So, yeah.
Anyways, we're not talking about this anymore
cuz I'm going to start banning. If you
keep talking about this, I'm going to ban it. One second.
Right. I'm timing out now. Okay. I gave
you a warning to stop bringing it up. I
don't want to talk about it anymore and
you keep bringing it up. So, people
going to start getting timed out.
All right, I'm going to have to start
timing out. I did give him warnings.
Gave him the warnings, bro, multiple times.
Yep. I told you multiple times, stop
bringing it up. And you keep bringing it
up. So you get a timeout.
Yeah, but it's annoying, bro. Hearing it
over and over and over again. It's annoying.
[ __ ] annoying as [ __ ]
No, I just timed out. Just timed them
out, bro. For 5 minutes. I didn't ban him.
No, it's not banned. It's annoying. Yep.
One second, bro. Anyways,
I'm going. I'll be back tomorrow.