Yo, who the [ __ ] took my [ __ ] winnings, bro?
Some [ __ ] took my took my [ __ ] winnings, bro.
I I the [ __ ] bookies
eight [ __ ] [ __ ] claim my [ __ ]
wins, bro. What the [ __ ]
I bet it was that [ __ ] red star,
wasn't it, man?
Who the [ __ ]
Someone took my [ __ ] winnings, bro.
Yeah, someone took my [ __ ] w
must have done it with a [ __ ] barcode,
bro. I went in 8:30. Yeah, it just it
[clears throat] wasn't even scanning. I
went up to the [ __ ] counter there.
Oh. I said, "What the [ __ ] There's
about Oh, someone's
someone's cash in." I said, "But how?"
But I'm the only one with a [ __ ] slip, bro.
madness, bro. What the actual [ __ ] I
thought they were chatting [ __ ] because
I'm sure I showed a [ __ ] what?
I'm sure I showed a [ __ ] barcode on
it before and they [ __ ] didn't do it.
Could have [ __ ] done [ __ ] 10 quid, bro. Madness.
I have a mad white night story to tell
you all. You're not going to believe it.
You're generally not going to believe
it. Um, you know, because of what we was
talking about yesterday was bad, bro.
These white knights have got serious autism.
Um, and it actually happened today.
Uh, no, I put the thing up and they must
have went in the bookies and claimed it.
They must have claimed it with a code. But
£110. I could have done with that, bro.
It's like [ __ ] It's like four Indians.
Like [ __ ] [ __ ] Indians, bro.
Madness, bro. [ __ ]
Is there a way I can get it back, do you
think? I'm going to have to try and go
back later. See if I can get the 110.
Could have done with that 110. I won
that bet [ __ ] fair and square as
well. I didn't even know people could
[ __ ] do it.
See, it doesn't seem a lot of money to
you, but it's a lot of money to me, bro.
Yeah. 8:30 I went to the one up the road
and it was just void.
I thought Trip H was chatting [ __ ] I
was like, nah. Cuz I always thought you
needed a physical slip. Mad. Yeah.
[ __ ] madness, bro.
It was a It was a uh both score, no draw.
Griezy, I've got a white night story for
you. You're not going to believe it. It
actually happened today.
H crazy. I've got to show you something. Oh,
I've got I've got nothing to do with
that, mate. Nothing to do with that.
Nothing to do with me.
I just wanted to see if I was a [laughter]
I just wanted to see if I was a good actor.
Yep. I stayed up all night. I even done
a little video. Do you? I stayed up all
night. Haven't been bed yet. I think
that tells you how much I hate these
people in this community that I weren't
going to let them have a laugh at me.
Yeah. I'll put the videos up if you want. [laughter]
I do that, mate. I You think I'm a good actor, Gizzy?
You think I'm a good actor?
I think I'm all right.
I'm going to put the video up. One second.
Yeah, I was going to keep it going,
dude. But oh, I've got a mad story to
tell you, Gamsy. You're not going to
believe this, bro. You are not going to
believe this. Really, really, you're not
going to believe this, bro. Oh, you're
really not going to believe this. Since
we're just talking about white knights
and silks and
one second, I'm going to tell you
exactly what happened, mate. I've done a
few videos, by the way. Not I actually
recorded this, but I'm not going to put
it up of me arguing with this woman
because I'm obviously white knights and
bias people. If you want to see it, I'll
send it to you sing singly if you want,
but I'm not putting it up on here
because I learned my lesson with that.
I'll tell you exactly what happened. [laughter]
It's not funny, mate. Uh cuz it just basically uh
it just ruined my whole [ __ ] day to
be honest with you.
Right. Have him in bed. Yo, Gre, are you listening?
You listening? Yeah, captain.
This is sober as well, by the way.
Right. So, I was on the train. I got a
burger. Um cuz I thought of you and I
got myself a burger. So, I went on the train
coming back. I was eating I was eating
on the train and there was this woman
sat next to me,
right? Not like directly next to me, but
you know when there's four chairs and
you're sitting to the back of someone,
but they're next to you and she's looked
back. Feel her look back, bro. And she
gave me the dirtiest look. I said, "What
are you looking at?" And then I said,
"No, no, no, no, no. What the [ __ ] are
you looking at?" Yeah. She gave me She
gave me a dirty look at it. She started
running up her [ __ ] mouth, mate.
Trying to say, "Oh yeah, you look at
your you got food in your beard." No,
no. I said, "Mate, have you seen
yourself? You [ __ ] crackhead. You
might want." And mate, I'm telling you,
Greavvesy. It was bad. Like 10 out of 10
bad. It was worse than [ __ ] Timmy on
the train, me and the Weber Spoons,
broke it. That them things was nothing
compared to this. She was running up her
mouth. She weren't stopping. I weren't
going to back down now, mate. At the end
of the day, if you've had a bad day,
you're not going to take it out of me.
And we were going back and forth and but
I w I weren't giving up, bro. And she
was this like mixed race mixed race
woman. And she weren't stopping, mate.
She was not [ __ ] stopping for love
nor money. Guess what happened then,
Graves? You could probably imagine who
stepped in. Of course she could, Graves.
Cool. Who do you reckon stepped in? Um,
I'm not going to tell you. I want you to guess. Yeah. [laughter]
So, the guy was about to get off the
train and he was like, "Uh, do do you
know what time it is?" I said, "No." And
he's like, "Oh, you can't be
disrespectful to the lady." I said, "Uh,
she's running up her mouth to me, so
tell her." Yeah. You can't run up your
mouth to people and say, "Oh, the lady,
disrespect the lady." We're not We're
not [ __ ] Yeah. We are not told at as
as at adolescence that we can't defend
ourselves verbally mate. So whatever
going on in your little white knight
head, that's on you, bro. Don't bring it
on to me. And you know the thing is
Grezy again only defending the woman for
having a vagina. Everybody heard us on
the train, but we we were both as bad as
each other. Like we were bad, bro. Like
we were both as bad as each other. And
it's not like someone come in grievy and
said, "Can you two shut the [ __ ] up? I'm
having a bad day. The train's packed.
Can you just shut the [ __ ] up, both of
you, and just stop it? No. No. No.
Straight to defending the woman with the
vagina because they think that these
women are going to sleep with them. It
is [ __ ] pathetic. And guess what
happened? You're not going to believe
this. As he was walking off the train,
right, as he and he said, "Oh, you can
get Nick for that." I said, "Really?
Really? I can get I can get nicked for
defending myself?" I don't think so,
mate. As he was walking off the train,
bro, his head got crushed in the door,
bro. He literally got crushed in the
door, bro. It was some bold man. His
head got crushed in the door. Yeah,
that's karma for being a [ __ ] white
knight. Mind your own [ __ ] business.
Yeah, [ __ ] white knights. [ __ ]
simpy little [ __ ] Yeah, they're not
going to sleep with you. Stop defending
them for having a [ __ ] vagina. We're
both as bad as each other. [ __ ] hell.
You know that the way they're stepping
in, Greavvesy. The way these people
Well, this guy is stepping in. It's not
justified. justified is you beating up a
woman for no reason or you picking on a
woman for no reason. You can clearly see
that we're going back and forth, back
and forth, back and forth. Who the [ __ ]
are you, bro? You know, you little white
knight [ __ ] simpy little [ __ ] you
know? No, they're not going to sleep
with you. Women don't. Why, bro? I'm
thinking that at this point now, it's
got to be autism. It's got to be some
sort of disability, bro. You know,
because where does the desire come from
to want to defend someone just for
having a [ __ ] You know, it's like you
you would have thought that it's like
depending on the situation, sometimes
men are right, sometimes women are
right. They they it's like no, it's not
being a bigger person. She's running up
her mouth. I will run up my mouth back
to her. You don't tell me what you do.
[ __ ] hell, bro. These people got
autism or some [ __ ] It was bad though,
bro. and his head got crushed from the
doors as well. Yeah. Because you're not
where you're not minding your own
business, [ __ ] and you're trying to get
involved in other people's business.
You're not seeing where you're [ __ ]
going. So, what you done was you got
your head almost [ __ ] cut in half and
you're still not getting a woman sleep
with you. Yeah. Pathetic, isn't it?
It's [ __ ] Bro, you should I got I got
it recorded. I got It was bad. It was
bad. I'm not going to put it up though
on here. If you want to see it, you're
more than welcome to to to message me on
because these people on here were
biased. And I'm not going to say that I
won. We were both as bad as each other.
But they're defending women again. Do
they not realize that it's it's not
going to make a woman sleep with you?
Women do not like you. They can fend
themselves. Stop buttoning in.
It's [ __ ] mental, bro. I What is it
with these [ __ ] Bro, I I don't even
know. Do you know what I said to my mom?
These men give us a bad name. Yeah. You
know, you know when you talk about that
men that you know are weird. I'll tell
you what gives men a bad name. These
people, they're giving us a bad name, you know.
But no one else on the train said
anything. She was running up her mouth
saying about my beard. There's there's
food in my beard. I said, "Brother, you
looked at yourself, you crackhead."
Yeah. And I'm half asleep, by the way.
[ __ ] I'm still half asleep. And I'm
madness. It's It's why they feel the
need to defend women for just having a
[ __ ] I shall never know.
And she was running up her mouth, Grezy.
She was running up her mouth. It's mad,
isn't it? It's mad. Talk about having a
[ __ ] makes you get away with everything, isn't it?
I think one day, bro, I'm seriously
going to do one of these white knights in, lad.
I seriously seriously seriously No, I'm
not uploading nothing. Nope. I'm not
No way. That's opening a can of worms.
No way, bro. Um,
no. Do you know what? I'm just going to
tell them. No, I basically said, yeah,
like like she's saying stuff to me, so I
will say stuff back to her. She's saying
stuff to me. I will say stuff back to
her. But do you know what I'm going to
say next time? Like I'm not No violence.
I'm just going to say, bro, like it's
you need to stop this now. Like, I don't
know if you've got autism or why you're
doing this. Like, I don't know why
there's so many guys like you, but
they're not going to sleep with you.
Women don't like you. So, no matter how
many times you defend them, it's
embarrassing, bro. You know, she
probably got more chance of [ __ ] me
than [ __ ] you, mate. It's just that
she was having a bad day. Why is it I
I'm really really wanting to understand
why these people And bro, trust me, she
was running up her mouth. Like I
wouldn't even say I beat her. It was it
was it was a draw. It was a draw, bro.
Um but to be fair, I was [ __ ] half
asleep. So, but it was a draw. I'm not
going to say that. Like it but I I told
her about herself. I defended myself.
But she was giving it bad, bro. Giving
it bad. So you can't say anything bad.
Oh, could that a lady? [ __ ] off, you
[ __ ] white knight [ __ ] We're not
[ __ ] taught that. Adolescence. We are
not taught that, you know. We are
actually taught that if a woman puts her
hand on us, we can put their hands back
on them. So, I'm pretty sure if somebody
is verbally trying to abuse us, we can
say something back to them.
These white knights, mate, or and then
he's trying to say I get nicked. Really,
bro? I can really get nicked for saying
that someone looks like a crackhead.
Really, mate? Really? I don't think so.
No, it's not even funny. It's bad, bro.
It just ruined the whole day. And I was
going to and I was going to keep up the
whole like story, you know, where I
didn't get the winnings and stuff, but
that just put me in a bad mood, bro.
It's not even funny. It's [ __ ] annoying
[snorts] about I I can't about be the
bigger person. No, I'm not going to be
the bigger person. I'm not [ __ ]
having someone [ __ ] run up their
mouth to me like that. You silly [ __ ]
You silly [ __ ] [ __ ] You know,
madness, bro. And I was half asleep as well.
And now it's getting worse now. Uh, it's
not even when you're drinking. It's not
even when you're drinking out, Grievy.
It's actually when you're sober. And I
was just going to lad Brooks and back.
But yeah, I didn't sleep. I left the I
left the house at 6:00 in the morning, Grezy.
Yeah, I left the house at 6:00 in the
morning to get to the bookies. Yeah,
very, very early. I was waiting there
for about 15 minutes. I'll wait. I'll
wait. I've got a video of me waiting.
I'll just wait. And I was like, hurry
up. Hurry up. Hurry up.
Hurry up. Yeah, I didn't want these
[ __ ] winning, bro. That's how much I
hate these people on here, Gregy. That's
how much I hate these people on here. I
think you understand it now. So, I don't
know what that white knight why he was
getting involved on the train.
Does it look like someone just took my
winnings? Bro, do you like the photo?
Yeah, I'll put the video up of me
waiting, bro. I'm not putting up um the
video of the train because people are
just biased and they just will just
Yeah. But these white knights, what do
you mean respect the lady when she's
running up her mouth? [ __ ] autism,
bro. You need to go to a [ __ ]
doctor's, mate. You got autism.
[ __ ] mad, bro.
Greasy. What is this, bro? Seriously,
between me and you? Cuz me and you seem
to not be these people. Is it because we
didn't have dads brainwash watching us?
My dad died. Obviously, your parents
died. Whatever. What is this, bro? Like,
seriously, all all jokes aside, why are
these men doing this?
I'm really, really, really wanting to
know why they continuously defend people
just for having a vagina, you know? I I
I want to know. I really Do they think
that these women are going to sleep with
them? Do they think that it makes them
look good? Is it because they've got
autism? Has their dad brainwashed them
at a young age? Like, what is this
thing, bro? I really want to know,
you know? I might might do a podcast.
This [ __ ] mad about, oh, oh, be the
bigger person, don't respect her. I
said, no, she's saying stuff to me, so
I'll say something back. And bro, his
head almost got crushed in it, bro. His
head got crushed in the door, bro. His
face was about to like It looked like
his face was going to split in half.
Yeah, cuz you're not looking where
you're going. You're too busy trying to
defend someone cuz they've got a [ __ ]
vagina. You [ __ ] idiot. You know,
like is madness. I said, "Don't I even
said don't look at me like that." Yeah.
And then she tried like she had like she
had um earphones. I said, "No, don't
look at me like that and I'll pretend
that you can't hear me." Yeah. madness.
No, it put me in a bad mood. No, it's
not funny, Grezy. It put me in a [ __ ]
bad mood, mate.
And it's not even so much the women.
It's the white knights. It's the white
That's what makes it worse is the it's
they're white nights. It seems they're white knights.
They've definitely got autism in it.
They've definitely definitely got autism.
I'll put the video up, bro, if you want.
Um the the bookie one.
Yeah, I left the Yeah, I weren't going
to let these [ __ ] win, mate. I'm not
going to lose.
I've come too far. I'm not going to
lose. You [snorts] know what I mean?
Well, I'm going to have to change the thumbnail, obviously.
I'm going to put this up. Yeah,
these white lights are mad.
It's not like they said, "Oh, can you
both just shut the [ __ ] up? Can you guys
just shut the [ __ ] up? No. Straight to
defending someone because they got a
vagina. Cuz they've got a [ __ ] in
between their legs.
I told my mom about it as well. Mad.
Mad, mate. And they don't think they're
sexist. [ __ ] off, mate.
And then he got his head crushed through
the doors. I don't know if you've seen
it, right? You know London? Yeah.
They've got like doors that crush like
they open and close and and it's on a
timer. So even if like he's trying to
walk out the door and it's crossed his
head. I was like, "You're a tit, mate.
You a [ __ ] tit. You just you just
crossed your head trying to defend a
woman that's not ever going to sleep
with you. She's running her mouth." He's
like, "Oh, what time is it?" And I was like, "Huh?"
Yeah. I didn't want these people to win.
Yeah, I don't know why. Like, you can
clearly tell that she was running her
mouth to me. It weren't like, you know,
Timmy situation yet where the woman
wasn't really saying anything. This
woman was, bro, this woman was mad.
Like, this woman was [ __ ] crazy, bro.
And I was half asleep as well. Like, I'm
I'm [ __ ] arguing with two people and
I'm [ __ ] half asleep.
And it's not like like a Timmy situation
or like, you know, even the one at the
park, right? You know the one in the
like it certain things it it could be
justified. You know what I'm saying? But
that it's not justified, bro. They were
running up their mouth, bro. They were
they really really really were.
Really, really, really, really, really,
really were. And I was giving it back.
They're not going to give me a dirty
look. Don't look at me like that. Simple.
I said, "Yeah, I am eating. Yeah, I've
got stuff in my beard. I'm what? I'm
What? What you going to do about it,
crackhead?" [ __ ] off, mate. Bad. Sounds
funny to you, but it ain't funny, bro.
It's [ __ ] annoying.
It's bad enough you got some [ __ ] trying
to put you in a bad mood. Cuz they're
not going to like it when you're in a
bad mood. Cuz they don't like it when
you're in a bad mood. Yeah, they're in a
bad mood trying to put you in a bad
mood, but they're not going to like it
when you're in a bad mood, bro. Cuz look
look look what happens.
[ __ ] mad, bro. Look what happens.
They're not babies.
They know what they're doing.
Yeah. His head got [ __ ] crushed in
the door. What a dick. What an absolute
dick. You know,
just for defending a woman for having a
vagina about be the bigger person. No.
There's no be the bigger person. No. No.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. You might
let you might want somebody to talk to
you like that. That's not me. That's not
my morals. We don't have the same
morals. Yeah. How you're brought up is
not the way I'm brought up. You're
brought up the wrong way. Obviously,
these people that have got dads are
brought up the wrong wrong way, Grezy.
It seems that they're brought up the
wrong cuz their way of white lighting
and sing isn't the right way. You know
it and I know it. So,
what is it? Is it they've had dads? What
is it, bro? I don't know what it is. I
I really really don't know what.
Oh, you're going to laugh at this,
Grevy. So, you know how I charge I had
this I've had this charger for one day.
I plugged it in the controller and it's
bent where the controller slipped. The
charger bent. Yeah. Typical, is it?
First day of me having the charger, it
does that. Yep. [ __ ] bent. Look, I'll
show you it. It all works. Look.
Look. It's bent. See? Yeah.
She was, "Oh, you don't look like you've
washed for 3 days." I said, "Is that any
of your business?" She didn't call me
She didn't call me that. She didn't say
I was ugly or anything, but she was
trying to um
I don't know. She didn't say anything
about looks, but she's trying to say you
look you ain't washing that. I was like,
"And what's that to you?
Yeah, it's bad though. It really,
really, really is bad. It really, really
They just see women as innocent. It is
bad, bro. It is bad. Especially when
that shit's happening on a train.
No, if a woman runs her mouth up to me,
I'm going to run up my mouth to her in
front of anyone. You You don't You've
got your way and I've got my way. Yeah,
that's that simple.
Um, and everyone could hear her, mate.
Everybody could hear her on that [ __ ]
train, mate. From one cabbage to the
other, everyone heard it. Everyone was
looking, BBC. Everyone was looking, mate.
Everyone was looking, bro. And I
uploaded a video, by the way.
He doesn't understand that, you know,
everyone's got problems, mate. But
you're not the only one. You're not special. Yeah,
there you go.
>> Basically, yeah. I mean, she could
clearly defend herself,
you know. She was just as bad as me, if
not worse. But somehow this guy wants to
try to get involved and then gets his head crushed
like a [ __ ] tit. I couldn't even
imagine getting my leg or arm. He got
his head stuck in the door.
What an idiot. All for defending a woman
that's running up her mouth. But yeah,
we should respect Well, maybe if you're
a [ __ ] lady, you should start acting
like a [ __ ] lady. Maybe you should
you should start acting more ladylike
and start acting more feminine, not
running up your [ __ ] mouth across one
cabbage to the [ __ ] other, you know?
Maybe they should start acting more ladylike.
Is that right, Grezy?
Yeah. I put the video up, by the way, lads.
Just waiting for it to open.
It's a copycat statement. [laughter]
I love you, Grezy. I love you.
She's waiting for a copycat statement to be made.
Yeah, I was going to do that to be
honest, but that woman put me in a bad
mood. I was going to keep playing along
with it. Yeah. To see how many people on
here would lie.
Yeah, I was to see how many people and
they would lie in it. That's what would
have been good about it
because then they'd be like, "Oh, I done
it. I done it." And then at the end of
the day, you can say, "Well, you
didn't." So, you're a liar. And it So,
but I did wait.
It's okay. I'll just Do you reckon if I
went later it would have been cashed into Bre?
That's a good picture of me in it. I like it. [snorts]
I like that picture of me.
You're okay, Captain.
Yeah, these people are [ __ ] nerds on
this community, Triple H. They're just
sad people, Triple.
They're just sad little nerds.
Yeah, they're sad little nerds,
bro. Do you know what's so mad is
they're talking [ __ ] over £100, bro? But
they don't even have a£100, bro. They
don't even have a£100, lad. These little
nerds. you [ __ ] fat nerds on YouTube.
They're proper proper nerds as well,
bro. Have you seen how they type? Proper
proper nerds, lad. But thanks for
telling me about the barcode thing. I
didn't ever think of it, bro. Cuz I'm
sure I'd show I'm sure I showed showed
the barcode before.
I don't know. I'm sure I have before.
Yeah, they're proper proper sad little nerds.
They are little nerds on here, lad.
They're just sad people.
Yeah, I told that woman about herself
that it got really bad, bro.
Yeah, they're just sad people, Triple.
They're just sad little nerds, lad.
Sad little nerds.
Joe said he will be the first in Q
before it. Not to mention he probably
walked over now there back in the
freezer called lightning shorts. Yeah,
but I done that so you didn't get the
last laugh. I didn't I don't need the
money, mate. You really think I need the
money? I'll send my mom £150 right now,
bro. I don't need the money. I done it
so you people wouldn't get it. I didn't
want you get I didn't want them getting
the last laugh. Trip H. You know, I hate
these people on here, bro. Hate them.
Yeah. And I know like cuz we like laugh
and stuff a lot about it. I don't really
say it much. I hate a lot of these
people on here, bro.
No. No. Seriously, Triple H. I I hate a
lot of people on here, bro. If I had 10
minutes with some of these people, bro. [snorts]
Like Fantasy Stories, um, you know, Red
Star, uh, these people. Have I had 10
minutes with these [ __ ] bro? Trust me, lad.
Oh, bro. Yeah. So,
I hate him, bro. I hate these people on
here, lad. Trip rates. Not all of them, obviously. Yeah.
You know what I mean? But you know what
I mean by what I say.
[snorts] Yeah. They They must have knew
they weren't going to beat me to the
bookies, mate. I'm a [ __ ] crazy [ __ ]
I'm a crazy [ __ ] mate.
But yeah, thanks for telling me about
the barcode, mate.
That is mad. I didn't know that.
These little sad nerds.
Why is that aim on Red Star's channel?
She's another weirdo.
She's another freak. Yeah.
Yeah. Hey, Grezy, it's not about the
money, bro. Grievy, it's not about the
money, lad. It really ain't about the
money. I don't need £110, but I'm not
going to have these people have the last
laugh out of me, mate.
And I would do anything to stop that
happening, mate. And I had to travel. I
didn't walk. I traveled. I had to get I
traveled about five or six miles.
Yeah. Five or six miles just to get to
the 7:30 one. That's how much I hate one
of these people. That's how much I hate
these people. So, you can see the dedication.
Oh, look. I'll put another video up if you want. One second.
There we go. Look.
Do you like the picture of me? I think
it looks good. Do you like the little
picture of me, Grezy? It's cute, isn't it?
Give my mom £110. I don't And I said in
a video, right?
Yeah. If it if it was to collect £30, I
would pay £80 in Uber to collect £30
just so they wouldn't get it. That's how
much I hate these people here, bro. I
don't hate you and Triple H and stuff
obviously. And that Tiger seems all
right, you know what I mean?
You know, you know the the you know the
ones I hate, bro.
And I'm serious. Do you think I'd be
going on a train 6 milesi in the [ __ ] cold?
Yeah. [ __ ] that. Are you mad?
I could I wouldn't be able to let it
lie, Grezy. If they beat me, I wouldn't
be able to let it lie.
I won't be able to let it lie. Grievy,
do you remember them [ __ ] were laughing
at us? [ __ ] that, bro. Laughing at us.
I'd never hear the laugh last of it,
would I, Grezy?
So, you waiting for another copycat
statement to be made, Grezy?
Do you want another copycat statement?
Yeah, these simps are [ __ ] crazy.
Okay, so why did Nleg say that Sher, if
you don't like Sher Cole, um, you're gay again, Greavvesy.
Why did he say that again, Greavvesy?
Did you say?
Do you remember? >> [snorts]
>> Dude, do do you remember, [laughter] Grezy?
What did you say it was?
Greavvesy, [snorts] you're too funny,
man. What did you say it was?
What is it again? Grievy.
What did you say it is again?
Was a copycat statement. You're mad. You
are. I can't believe you got on YouTube
again. Soon as you wake up, you silly goose.
You know what? I should have on the
train. I should have just got my I
should have just showed that [ __ ] to my
dick, bro, and told her to suck it. I
should have just took my [ __ ]
trousers off, mate.
Said, "Suck my dick, you silly cunt." [sighs] Oh.
Oh, that's cute.
You like the little picture? That's what
makes it better, is it?
Quzy, did you say Autumn's my mama?
Autumn's not my mama. She's been talking
[ __ ] about me on Red Stars.
She's been talking [ __ ] about your mommy
doesn't do that.
This Smokey Be is another one that's got no life.
They've all got no lives on here. Yep.
So, do you have faith in Peter Belly now?
You have faith in Peter Belly Greavvesy.
Are you a believer?
I like the little picture with the
money. It's cute, isn't it?
There you go. I showed £100. You got to
double it now.
Yeah, I would have went mad if they
cashed it in. I thought, "Oh [ __ ]
they're taking too long." I was like, "I
hope they [ __ ] open.
We need to get to scram before them
Discord [ __ ] Grezy,
we need to get to scram before them Discord [ __ ]
You That was what that was [ __ ] That
was worrying me, lad. That was worrying me.
[snorts] Do you remember? Did you touch
Isabelli's boobies? It's not funny, bro.
It's immature as [ __ ] No, it's not
funny. It's immature.
It's just immature in it. [snorts]
I don't like that Joseph Farra. He's a
snake. He's a nonslover. [gasps]
He's a nonslover. Joseph Farra. [sighs] [panting] Oh gosh.
That's mad that they open 7:30 on a
Sunday, bro. That is a madness, greasy,
is it? They open 7:30 on a Sunday, but
if you wanted to get a pint of milk, you
got to wait until 11:00. I think it's
all wrong, you know. I think it's wrong
that you can't go to a main supermarket
on a Sunday till 11:00, but you can go
in a bookies at 7:30. That's [ __ ] bad. That
That is really bad. I think that's out.
I think that's bad. [snorts] >> [snorts]
>> Dude, dude.
Yeah, Triple H. I told you I don't [ __ ]
around when it comes to these punts.
It's okay. I'll just wait.
You'll wait. Yes. Until it's been made.
I love that little comedy sketch. I
waited. I said, "Come on, Captain.
Captain, let me in." Hi, Captain.
Captain C. I was watching some
interracial porn grievy.
Oh, this black guy was like, "I can get
you off this island. You help me and I
help you." And she was sucking his dick.
She said, "Oh, yeah. You get me off, I
get you off. Suck it, [ __ ] I was dead.
I was dead. Lovely bit of interracial pornography. [snorts] Yep.
Yeah, I'm just on Lord J. It's the same
nerdy fat ugly people.
These fat ugly nerds. Yep. Yeah.
They're little nerds. Onl. They're
little fat ugly nerds. They ain't got a
life. They ain't got no money. They're
[ __ ] skin. They ain't got a job. Gra.
They say they've got jobs on here, but
they ain't got no jobs, bro. Sat on
[ __ ] YouTube, mate. On YouTube all
day, every day. They don't work. These
little bums. These little skint bums.
[sighs and gasps]
Is that right, Grey? These little skid bubs,
you Why don't you want me to enjoy my life, Grezy?
I said that. What if I went out? Can I
go out and get a woman pregnant for a
laugh? And you said no.
You're so controllive. Why won't you let
me do that, Whezy?
or a laugh. You're just mean.
Are you jealous or something?
What don't you want me to be happy?
Why can't I have a baby? You're just mean.
That's all you are greedy. You [ __ ]
mean. You just don't want me to be happy.
You just want me to be miserable, don't you?
You don't want me with anyone? Well, duh.
I'd call it baby Peter. Grezy. Baby Peter.
Is that cute? Greasy. Baby Peter.
No. Why would I run off?
I'd love it. He'd be my little friend.
He would be my little friend. We
No. Run off. Some people's dads actually
do that. You know, they say they're
going to go shop, but they just run off.
They never come back. It has happened.
Uh, Mr. B, I uploaded a video.
You be the judge.
You be the judge, Captain.
It's okay. I'll just wait.
You wait. Yes, until it's been made.
Oh, wait. You know what I should have
done, Greasy? I should have went there
midnight and waiting there for 7 hours
and just done like a 7 hour video. I've
been just waiting there for like 7 hours.
Imagine that. Creepy.
[ __ ] hell. Nah,
only thing is I'm quite sleepy now.
But that woman put me in a bad mood on
that white night
defending women just cuz they've got a vagina.
I could understand if it was like their
girlfriend Greavvesy or like they were
married then I mean like yeah you
understand or it was someone's mother
but they're random ass women that are
never going to sleep with them. Why are
they doing it? Why are they doing it? Or
like yeah the mom or like they're
married then I can say yeah don't talk
to my [ __ ] wife like that.
But they it's not that it's they are
defending them just cuz they are women.
It is mad. It is sad mad. Or if it's
someone's daughter like if it's
someone's daughter. Yeah. You know what
I'm saying? Greasy. That's the only, you
know, if if you're talking to someone's
daughter like that and their [ __ ] dad butts in.
Oh, there was a white knight on the
train today, Mr. Me. I had an argument
with a woman, mate. The whole [ __ ]
train was looking. It reminded me of
you, Greavvesy. The whole [ __ ] train was looking.
That tends to happen when Peter Belly's
in town, isn't it, Grezy?
Yeah, that tends to happen when Peter
Belly's in town. Chaos happens. [snorts]
Stayed up all night, Mr. B. Stayed up
all night to go to this bookies. I
traveled six, seven miles to go to this
bookies, mate. I weren't going to let him win.
My my money. It's my money.
But yeah, they're proper proper nerds on this community.
They are proper proper virgins on here.
That's why like my channel,
they're proper [ __ ] virgins on here,
lad. Mr. be they're proper proper nerds.
Uh, King of Belfast, proper proper
nerds. They need to go get laid, bro.
These people, they need to go [ __ ]
lose their virginity and get jobs and [ __ ]
I just [snorts] put the money in the bank, lad.
I just put the money in the bank.
Oh, I'm so sleepy now, Greavvesy. Oh gosh. [sighs]
You laughed when you saw the picture,
didn't you? Yeah. I was going to keep it
going for longer
and then we can catch the lies out on
here in it and all of what they're
saying would be lies
cuz V would come and say, "Oh yeah, I've
cashed it in. I've cashed it in." And
then in the end you can say, "No, you
[ __ ] never mate
after the whole day in it."
I hate that Joseph I hate that Joseph
Ferrar. He's a snake lad. He's a little nods lover.
He's a [ __ ] nod lover, mate. [gasps]
There's so many white knights.
[ __ ] off you weirdos.
No, I've not been to sleep. Obviously,
I've not been asleep, you [ __ ] idiot.
I'm [ __ ] tired. I'm going to sleep in
a minute. I didn't go to sleep, mate. I
weren't going to let them [ __ ] win.
No way was I going to let them [ __ ] win.
I didn't want them to get the money.
Even if it cost me £110 to get the money.
There we go. I don't want them getting
it. my money.
What chicken ticker and cries?
Who's my mama The bridge.
Man said I can get nicked.
Said I can get [ __ ] nicked for [ __ ] arguing.
I'm so sleepy.
I'm falling asleep.
No, they didn't win, bro. Because I
don't mind staying awake.
It was fun to me, bro.
No, my sleeping pattern isn't Well, I
I'll fix it within today, bro. Not
really. I done it myself. I done it to
myself. If you think about it,
I [ __ ] I done it myself by putting a
code out there. I didn't even realize.
So, in a way, I done it to myself
because if I didn't put a code there,
they wouldn't they wouldn't have
anything. I didn't know. So, at the end
of the day, I did it to myself if you
think about it. So,
No, I done it. I done it to I done it to
myself cuz these people only give get
what you give them if you think about
it. But I didn't know about the code.
And if they would have got the if they
would have got the money, they would
have won. So
if they would have got the money, they
would have won. So either way, I [ __ ]
it for myself cuz I showed the code.
I don't mind saying that, bro. It was a
bit of fun, to be honest.
I had nothing better to do.
I won, bro. I won. Captain
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> launch leg says that Cheryl Cole is
attractive to fit in
fit in with a copycat statement. Triple H copycat copycat.
These people are nerds though. Triple H.
They're [ __ ] nerds on here, lad.
getting little fat jobless people.
They're [ __ ] sados on there, bro. Sados.
They said to you go clean your sheets,
didn't they, Trip Rage? Uh, yesterday
when you commented,
they said to go clean your sheets. No.
Yeah. It's just repeating, isn't it?
These people need to stop the repeating,
lad. They need to think of new things.
It's getting boring, ain't it?
They said I think they said go clean
yourself or something.
Didn't they say go clean your sheets or
something, isn't it? Yeah. It's
repeating. Yeah. Because that's all
they've got on you. You see,
it's like what money says. They only
have what you when they have something
on you, they'll keep going on about that
until they have something else.
Yeah, they're sad people. Triple,
you got you got uh food on your beard
and you look like you ain't washed. I
said, "So what?"
No, I think it's sad.
I think it's sad, lad, that these people
repeat themselves every day. Repeating bastards.
Nah, I didn't like it, lad. I just said
that's what they said. Sad repeat, isn't it?
Yeah, but do you see what I mean?
They're just repeaters in it.
Fat, ugly, sad repeaters.
Triple lad. They ain't got nothing in life.
These people ain't got nothing in life, lad.
These people should break.
Oh, mate. Don't get me started. What
happened today on the train, lad? It was really bad.
I had a bad experience today with a
woman in a white knight.
I'm too tired to explain the whole thing again.
I already explained it.
Go back here.
Go back in the on the video. Go back on
the live stream. I've explained it.
I can't explain it again, bro. I'm too tired.
No, I don't like it.
Monty man lost his kids over YouTube.
[ __ ] madness, bro.
Yeah. And and the guy got his uh the guy
got his head uh
uh head uh crushed in the door. You know
the the London doors. He got his head
crushed in the door. The [ __ ] [ __ ]
Serves him right for being a little
white knight and little [ __ ]
st [ __ ] defending a woman just for
having a [ __ ] Sad bastard. They never
got to sleep with them. So I don't know
why they do it.
I told him I'll talk to her how I want.
Yeah, we know that, bro. That's another
thing. They're opportunists. Yeah, I
know. I know. Or John Cena. Yeah,
they're opportunists. I mean, they're
white that to me, but I tell them about
themselves and they shut up. I said,
I'll talk to her how I want. She's
talking to me like that. I'll talk to
her how I want. That's what I said.
Yeah, of course. Like, they're they're opportunists.
Every man's like that. Yeah,
but then when you tell them about
themselves, they shut up. It's weird. Yeah.
Yeah. They're opportunist. Oppa opportunist, lad.
Defending women just cuz they've got a
[ __ ] Even though women are not going to
sleep with them, they still defend them.
[ __ ] autism, bro. Autism to the max.
They think that these women are going to
sleep with them because they defend
them. It's embarrassing.
[ __ ] embarrassing, mate. Hate white knights.
Yeah. I told her I said, "Who you
looking at?" And then she tried to turn
around. I said, "No, no, no. Who the
[ __ ] are you looking at like that,
mate?" And then we just started getting
into it. We just started getting into
madness. Bro, don't get me wrong. She
was giving it back. She was giving it
back, bro. Nothing like Timmy's one or
the one in the We ever spoon. She was
giving it mouth, mate. Giving it mouth,
mate. Trust me, she was some some mixed
race girl. She was giving it bad, bro.
And then the white knight tried to get
involved and then as he was to walk up
off the train, he got his head crushed.
He got his head crushed. What a [ __ ]
[ __ ] Teach you for being a little
white knight defending women just cuz
they got vaginas.
No, I didn't call her the n word. I
called her a crackhead. I said, "You
dirty crackhead looking [ __ ] Go look in
the mirror before talking about my
beard." She said, "I got food in my
beard and I look like I ain't was I
said, "Have you seen yourself?
Have you seen your [ __ ] self?"
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] off, mate.
I told her about herself, lad. She
didn't say anything about my looks. She
was just talking about my beard. What the [ __ ]
Said, "Have you seen yourself, mate?"
But anyways, let's forget about that,
bro. It's negative.
Yeah, Monty, man. What? Yeah, but he But
Triple H, he had chances to get off it.
He had chances to get off it, bro.
Oh, it's a long story, bro. I'm not I
don't want to get into it anymore, bro.
It ruined my whole day.
And then you got white knights defending
them just because they got a vagina.
His head got crushed in the door, bro.
Like, literally crushed. I was like, I
could have like what?
I've never that's never happened to me
like my arm or my leg. Never. So could
you imagine your head? [ __ ] hell.
Peaching for being a little white
knight, would it? look where you're
going instead of [ __ ] getting
involved with other people's business
when so the whole [laughter]
the whole train was looking like the
whole [ __ ] train was looking
[ __ ] they were all looking triple
you can imagine is it yeah it is a
country designed to annoy you
Yeah, he got his head he got his head
crushed, bro. I was like, "What?"
And he said, "Oh, it doesn't matter.
It's a lady." I said, "No, it doesn't
matter because if he talks to me like
that, I'm going to talk to her like
that." Simple as that. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, mate. Your
beliefs are your beliefs. Don't [ __ ]
project that onto me. [ __ ] white knight [ __ ]
So many [ __ ] white knights, bro.
So many white knights. Yeah, his head
got crushed in the door. What an idiot.
All because he wanted to look like a big
man in front of some [ __ ] ugly woman
that's never going to sleep with him.
Sad, sad, sad.
It's not about about being a bigger
person. I'm not being a bigger person. [ __ ] off.
No, no, no. It's not one rule for one,
one rule for another, you [ __ ] dick.
I'm not sure. Triple.
So what am I going to do when about
finding another mama?
Huh? I'm getting fed up with this now. Yeah,
I was going to put 150 on Kitty Minister
and Slow. I would have lost cuz Kitty
Minister never scored.
Yeah, they didn't score, did they?
Yeah, it is what it is, isn't it, bro?
You get used to it, ain't it?
I'm going out next week with my sister.
Like I said, I could go out this week,
but I'd rather save myself.
Yeah, I'm coping. I still saw some
good-looking women today, but obviously
I didn't approach cuz I can't be bothered.
Maybe I just I'm just going older,
maybe. I don't know. I just can't be
bothered with it anymore. It's just the
same old is it? I don't It doesn't
bother me anymore.
What bothered me was that thing on the
train today, bro. There's no need for it.
No, there's no need for it. I remember when so
you touched Did you touch Isabelli's boobies?
You You asked that, didn't it? Copycat statement.
Did you touch Isabelly's boobies?
No. That autumn can't be my mama because
she goes on Red Star's channel. I
thought maybe she could be my mommy, but no. [laughter] I triple
USA Izzy did die though.
She had lovely boobies win. So and Sig
Sig did as well.
Sig was like my stepmom, isn't it?
Yeah, she was my stepmom
I think. win. So yeah, [laughter]
do you remember old man at the cinema? Oh,
Do you remember old man at the cinema?
Uh, yeah. I had a burger which is what
caused the argument on the train cuz I was eating.
Yeah, [clears throat] they do give you
nutrients. Sig ones. Sigs did and USA is ones did. Yeah,
that's how I get my nutrients in it, Grezy. Yeah,
but I'm learning to live without my
nutrients now. Is it Grezy?
I'm just learning to cope without them.
I mean, I had some steak yesterday, so
that probably helped.
Uh, I could do, but it's pointless. I
just want to move on from it, bro. It's negative.
I already done a video of it.
I actually already done a video of it. I
just need to upload it.
Yeah, I already done a video. I will
upload it. I already did one of it.
Yeah. So, if you have steak and that it
it gives you nutrients.
What would I do? What would I do? Uh,
well, I would do them on TikTok. And
basically, I want to know
why people white knight and simp.
That's what I want to know. That's what
a podcast got to be about. I want to
know why they do that, you know?
I I want to know why they do it. Um, so
maybe people can join and ask why they
feel the need to defend women's just
having a vagina
and nothing else. I would love to know.
It would be interesting.
Yeah. If you eat steak and stuff, you
can get the nutrients that you don't get
from the boobies.
You just learn to live without the
nutrients. They are nice nutrients, but
you can't Yeah.
Yeah. I want to know why they do it. I
don't I don't want to share my experiences nor
tell people what I've gone through
because it's like what Savvy guy says.
What's a grown man going to try and tell
me and they just dismiss your struggles anyways.
So, I'm not having them. I'm not having
I want to discuss him why they feel the
need to defend women just because they
got a vagina,
you know. Don't get me wrong, I like
nutrients and stuff and, you know,
obviously boobies and whatever, but I
don't start defending [ __ ] random ass women.
That's [ __ ] ridiculous.
You know, I would have defended USA, but
that's only because she's my mommy. You
know what I mean, Grezy? That's that
when I used to defend her, that's cuz
she's my mama. [sighs] It's a big
difference. You know what I mean? Grim, [sighs]
there's a big difference.
You don't see me [ __ ] defending
random ass women.
I only defend I only defended my mama in it, Greavvesy. Yeah.
So, who's my dad then, Grezy?
That's the real question. If she's my
mom, who's my dad?
That's That's weird, isn't it?
Yeah. So, we Oh, so we'd have to do the
podcast on YouTube.
We'd have to do the podcast on YouTube
then. Yeah, no problem.
Yeah, they're all simps. They're all
little white night simps.
The only person
woman is your mom, your wife,
or someone like that grieves you. I
don't think that's simp. I think that's
fair. Like if you was defending your
wife or your mother or your daughter,
that's fair enough. But these men are
defending random ass women that are causing [ __ ]
all cuz they've got a vagina. mad.
Only cuz they've got a fishy vagina. No other reason.
Just this this dude's to stop, mate.
Just simp [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] disgusting, mate.
What do you Who do you think was in the
wrong and the Timmy video? the woman or
Timmy. But the thing is that woman
wasn't running up her mouth
on Timmy's that bad. She wasn't even
running up her mouth that bad.
That weren't even that bad compared to today.
Yeah, I'll get you. I'll get you. Yep.
Some New Zealander called Sig.
She smell I was like, "Can you suck my
willie?" She said, "Can you go down on
me?" I said, "No, I'm not doing that."
So, we just had sex.
Yeah. She had big boobies as well. [gasps]
Just waiting for another copycat
statement to be made. We
[ __ ] cats. Hate him.
Why? Because I went down and I smelt it.
Cuz I was thinking her and [ __ ] in it.
I went down and smelt it.
It was really, really bad.
I'd never go down on someone unless they
were a virgin or
Yeah, I was with them for a very long time. Nowhere.
Then it's different.
Would you eat a vagina,
Grezy? Would you like to eat a vagina? No,
you can just use your finger. You don't
need to, you know.
Choose your finger.
Crazy. You're so funny with your little words. Nah,
I was watching some mad interracial porn
from the 70s. Greasy.
So, do you reckon the two people the
porno is dead now? It was from the 70s.
They must be dead now then, isn't it?
Yeah, they must be dead now.
Yeah, some interracial porn.
Yeah, that's like 50 years ago, is it?
It was a black man and a woman and he
was like, she was like, "Can you help me
get off this island?" And he was like,
he took his pants down. He says, "You
help me, I help you, bitch." And she
started sucking his dick. And she was he
was like, "You get me off, I get you
off. Keep sucking, [ __ ]
Be nice to me. I was dead, bro." Yeah.
And then he [ __ ] her twice and then he
never he never got her off the island. Mad. Madness.
So, do you reckon they're dead now? If
that was the 70s, Greasy got to be dead
now, ain't it?
My mom would have been 10 cuz my mom was
born in 1960.
Yeah, they got to be dead in it, Grezy.
But why? How do they put all of this old
porn on these new porn sites, Grezy?
You know, just 80s and 90s porn.
How [snorts] do they put them all on
these new sites then?
They're from back in the day. Uh 30s, 40s.
Yeah. I don't know how they get all of
this old porn on these new sites. We see
it says vintage porn.
Vintage porn. Yeah.
I don't know how they [clears throat] do that.
I weren't even [ __ ] born, lad. Nope.
Yeah, it's crazy.
For the seven is
bad. We weren't even born in the 70s.
Have you seen stuff like that before
then? Grezy old school porn
15 years ago. [ __ ] hell.
Tropical paradise 1796.
that old school porn graves here.
[snorts and sighs] Mad this squeezy.
So, do you still watch Lex now, Grezy?
I don't watch him, bro.
No, I don't watch him because
he dismisses people's struggles in it. Yeah.
Yeah. He dismisses people's struggles in it, Grezy.
You A lot of people complain about that. Is it?
You get me off, I get you off, Greavvesy.
Imagine saying that whilst getting a [ __ ]
So how comes when me and USA kiss was
kissing grievy I felt something in my todder?
Is that normal?
I felt something downstairs. Grezy,
when I kiss and stuff, I feel something
in my toddy.
Am I touchy?
That's cute, isn't it? Greasy feelings dodger.
Yeah, they should do videos about him,
bro. He's a [ __ ] idiot.
He's gay, by the way, as well. Not that
it matters, but he is he is gay. You can tell Gy,
I'll be back later. Yeah, I'm going to
go sleep. I'm tired. Goodbye now.