[ __ ] you.
I am [ __ ]
I'm [ __ ] stuffed, matey. Absolutely stuffed.
Come on. Controller work.
Have problems with this [ __ ] controller. Come on. No [ __ ]
That Indian was [ __ ] expensive, mate. Talking about tip him. What's up Wait, hold life.
It was [ __ ] lovely and it was [ __ ]
expensive. But you see what I mean with
these little mongos on here. Yeah. As
soon as you put something out there,
they write something negative.
Jealousy with these people, bro.
Proper proper jealous. Proper proper
jealous little selfjectors on here, lad.
The account called the battels. Proper proper jealous
saying, "Oh, how's your life? That's a
good life. Comfort eating. What you
think? Eating once a day is comfort
eating." Really, bro?
They're so like forced to write negative
stuff because they're fat ugly people
that ain't got no life. Depressed ugly
people that ain't got [ __ ] all in life.
Weird, isn't it, bro? Weird.
So many There's so many
self-reflectctors on this community, lad.
So many self projectors.
So many [ __ ] self projectors
really bad isn't it
about oh yeah that's a good life sitting
by yourself comfy and what eating once a
day is comfy and I think these people
have got themselves confused with me again
self projecting fat ugly [ __ ] that
ain't got a life to be fair
yeah it was nice bro it's [ __ ]
expensive I'm [ __ ] full up I'm still full up.
I was last. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, it's a bit too early for the
Christmas music to be fair.
Oh, I wish you was with me eating it,
Greavves. I wish you was with me eating it.
Yeah, I wish you was with me eating it, bro.
[ __ ] lovely. It was absolutely
Can't beat some nice ticker.
Can you greasy? No, no, no, no, no. What
do you prefer? The tandoori chicken or
the chicken ticker? I like the chicken ticker.
Yeah, it's December on Monday. Okay, we
are Thursday and we're still nowhere near Christmas.
So, I mean it is it is the 27th of November.
Oh, am I giving you Am I giving you ideas, Greavvesy?
Am I giving you Look what it cost me
[ __ ] £49. That food did £49. But it's
all right, Grevy. It's not a problem, bro.
It's not a problem. I'm not from uh I'm
not from Kent, so I'll be all right.
Don't worry. I've got the buddy, mate.
Not a problem. I'm not I'm not from Kent.
No. Why would I have an Indian for
Christmas dinner? That doesn't make sense.
What kind of question is that?
But I'm not, you know, it was kind of it
was quite expensive, but again, I'm not
from Kent, so it's all right, mate. you know, was nice.
I'm thinking of getting this vest that's
got fur on it. All Saints have got a
sale one, a Black Friday sale. I was
thinking of getting a coat, £230, but
then was like, do I really need one? And
then I was like, should I get a hoodie
with a vest?
[ __ ] knows, mate. [ __ ] knows.
I don't know what to get. Greasy.
What do you think, Captain?
They've got a nice little sale on uh All Saints.
Everything's 30% off everything.
I like All Saints. It's one of my favorite shops.
P It's not the [ __ ] summer, is it?
Then you could wear the [ __ ] um short
sleeve t-shirts are nice in the summer,
but obviously it's not summer, so [ __ ]
Oh my god, that [ __ ] filled me,
Grezy. I done so much walking and I'm
still filled up. It doesn't give you the shits either.
I'll be out next week.
on the old piss.
How much was your little coat, Greasy?
How much was your little coat?
See, the thing I get money and I just
[ __ ] spend it,
man. You get money, you [ __ ] spend it
in the end, you know?
How much was your little coke gy?
Yeah. Do you ever buy new clothes, Greasy?
Do you ever buy new clothes?
By the way, if you've got more money
than someone and you've got a better
life than them, Greavvesy, you're materialistic. Apparently,
if you have more money than them, you're
you're or you're willing to work. You're
supposed to live on their level. If you
don't live on their level, they're materialistic.
They say that you're materialistic.
So, they expect that even if you get
loads of money or you have more money or
they expect you to have the same life as them.
I'm not sure that's how that works,
mate. I'm pretty sure if you was a
millionaire, you'd be in a mansion, wouldn't you? You know,
it's like a footballer. What would you
expect a footballer to have? Primark
clothes. I mean, [ __ ] hell.
What do you think about my Tommy
Hilfiger coat, Greavves? Yeah. I think
it's I think it's too old now. I've had
it for like two years.
I've had it for two years.
This coat is uh £230.
I'm thinking of getting it. Or I could
get the hoodie and the vest. I don't
know. I don't know.
I hate buying new clothes.
H, stop with the skin thing. It's boring.
Oh, you're sending me to sleep, bro.
I can eat out every day if I wanted to.
You don't know how much money I have.
Stop self projecting. You're killing the whole chat.
You need to stop now. It's boring.
You need to stop the self projecting.
It's boring, bro. Really. And it agrees.
It just ruins the chat
with repeating and the self projecting.
Have I been winning what? Gambling. I haven't gambled.
I could afford to eat out every day if I
wanted to. You don't know how much money
I have. Why are you still doing this
[ __ ] with money again, bro? You get
shown money and you still call people
skin. You need to stop this now. It's
boring. Very, very, very boring.
We get it. You people are skin that say
this. We get it. You won £300 a month.
Your life, not our life. [ __ ] hell.
Stop it now, bro. It's [ __ ] boring as
That cost 50 pound by the way. That food mad.
Went out today cuz I was [ __ ] bored.
So I thought let me just go out and eat.
So what do you think of the hill for
good coat grezy? I was going to keep it
until next winter then buy one next winter.
I could buy one.
I wanted to
buy one. But
it is looking quite old though to be
fair. It's like 2 years old.
They're worth the money. I think I paid
150 for that one. It was on sale. So
definitely definitely worth the money.
That coat was definitely worth the money. Yeah.
I'm not sure. [snorts]
What do you think? We
close 230. I might buy it. Not sure.
Oh, I can get a vest and a hoodie.
I don't know. [ __ ]
It's so nice when they're new. You know,
coats greasy when they're brand new. The
coats are so lush.
They're so lush when they're new.
But anything good when it's new.
trainers. So, I've got a new pair of
trainers, new pair of jeans, or only one
twice. So, if I got a coat, I'd have a
new coat as well.
I don't know.
Uh, yes, I can. You don't know how much
money I have.
Yes, I can. You don't know how much
You don't know anything about me again.
Stop self- projecting. I've got more
money than you. You don't know how much
money I have. Don't make me prove you wrong again.
You get proven wrong multiple multiple
multiple multiple times and you still
come back for more. Just like the trainers.
Don't make me buy this coat. Please
don't make me do it. You do not know how
much people have. You only know about
your own life.
I spent over £400 on two items.
Yeah, bro. Stop talking about people
that you don't know.
You'll go far in life.
Yeah, I got about 30 quid left. Yeah,
cool story, bro. Anyways, Grezy, where
are you, man? Oh [ __ ]
Yeah. You keep telling yourself that, bro.
You keep telling yourself that.
Yeah, that's very very specific, bro.
what you just wrote there. 30 quid.
That's interesting because I get money every week.
30 quid to last a month. Whoa. Really?
Very very very very specific thing to say.
You sure you're not talking about yourself, bro?
Very, very, very specific. 30 quid. I
could never have £30 to last me a month
because I get money every week. So, how
is that how how how do you work that one out?
Strange, isn't it? Very very strange. Oh, [ __ ]
I've actually put my car in the wash.
I've never washed it before. This is my
first time watching it. Washing it. Sorry.
Yeah. I've never watched it before. Yeah. Really?
You said I had 30 to last me the month. Really?
£30 to last me the month. That's not
possible though. How could I have 30 to
last me a month? And no, I went to the I
went to the bookies so you people
couldn't get the money so you can have
the last laugh. Like I told you,
[ __ ] if the if I if it was £30, I
would spend £80 to collect the £30. It's
just so you little skint [ __ ] ugly
little mongos didn't get it cuz I didn't
want you having the last laugh. And
yeah, I would do anything to stop you
[ __ ] having the last laugh, mate. It
could be £30 and I'd spend [ __ ] £200
if I had to. Not a problem at all.
Not a problem at all. You little mongos.
You not going to get the last laugh. It
could have been 2030, 30, bro. You
weren't getting that money. I don't need £110.
Yeah. Pretending I'm buying a £230 coat,
mate. We're not all skint. I don't know
how many times we have to say this to
you. We're not all skint people.
Why do you keep thinking that people are
skint like you?
I'm asking you this question. I want you
to really really answer it. Why do you
think everyone's got your skin life?
Why do you think everyone's got your skin life?
Because the things that you come out
with is ridiculous.
£30 to last me a month.
What the [ __ ] are you talking about?
No, you know yourselves are skint.
That's why you call people skint because
you're skint yourselves.
No, you you know yourselves are skint.
No, no, no, no, no, no. It's you people
that are skint.
It's it's you people that are skin.
That's why you call people skint every
day cuz you're skint yourselves. That's
why you sit on YouTube every day
projecting because you haven't got
anything. No life, no money, no hope, no
future. That's you people self
projecting. And you're gone now. Bye-bye. Bongo.
So many self projectors on here, man.
So, I might get this code anyways. N
let me go back on it.
These people are proper self projectors, lad.
He said I had30 to last me a month.
That's not possible.
30 to last me a month.
Where the [ __ ] do these people come out
with this [ __ ]
Where do people come out with this
[ __ ] bro? £30 to last me a month.
Yeah, I've had this coat for 2 years and
it's beginning to take its toll now.
I'll just put in the washing machine though.
So yeah, I might just buy this coat.
They've got a black sale on so Black
Friday sale 230 quid.
It's like a car key coat.
It's quite nice to be fair.
Well, obviously otherwise I wouldn't be
considered buying it, would I? Yeah.
Show you if you want. One second.
Yeah, I did. I put it on a on a 20.
I was either going to get the coat or
get the vest with the hoodie.
I mean, I'll be going out a lot drinking
in December anyways. So,
uh, it'll be a good investment in it.
I'll show you the coat.
I think it looks nice, man.
I saw it. I saw it in the shop as well. Yeah,
I like this coat, bro. It's got a bug on
it as well.
I'm going out drinking next week. Anyways,
I could wear that with the jeans and the
trainers. [ __ ] lash.
That's what you call [ __ ] lash, mate.
That's what you call [ __ ] lash.
Oh, so that's when they have their Black
Friday sales. Everything's on sale as well. Yeah,
think I'm going to get it.
See, we can afford £230. Not like these skin flints.
Not like these [ __ ] skin flints.
I had a Tommy Hill forgot one, but it's [ __ ] nah.
[ __ ] naft. It is
you wear to like walk the dog and [ __ ] in it.
When you go walk the dog or
they don't have it in black.
They don't have it in black.
Nah, I'm not a copycat. I could get it
if I wanted to. A Canada Goose. Yeah,
but only copycats wear that.
I'm not a copycat.
See, all saints, they don't really uh
people don't really wear it. Obviously,
people wear, but not as much as that cat.
No, [ __ ] off.
I'm not a copycat.
No, I'm not a copycat.
It doesn't matter how much it is. I can
afford it, but
I'm not paying that. I'm not I'm not a copycat.
Yeah, of course I can afford it.
Let's see how how good this Tommy
Hilfiger coat comes out.
I don't think it's going to come out
very good. It's [ __ ] like two years old, bro.
I could have got a coat today cuz I was
near the thing, but I could order it
or I could get like a black vest and a
hoodie, but the black vest looks kind of
cheap. So, I think I would just get a
coat to be fair.
I'm going to treat myself for a change. Hey, Grezy.
Oh, no. I can't afford it. Actually, I
got 30 to last me a month. Yeah,
I got 30 to last me a month, bro.
30 to last me a month. What am I going to do? One sec.
No, I'm not getting that, bro.
That's what [ __ ] copycats wear.
I'm not a copycat
like some people.
Not mentioning any names. Copying the crowd.
Talking about shovel go [ __ ] copycat.
You little copycat.
You little copycat. You little copycat.
Yeah, you copycat me.
Hate copycats. Always prefer dogs.
Yeah, I might buy this coat. It's £230.
I buy a new coach approach. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. So, yeah.
But I can just get the coat online
because it's I can buy it in stock. But
if you buy it online, you get free
delivery and it's more fresher when you
buy it online. So you might as well just order it.
It's just All Saints Co. I've had my
coat for two years
and then I need I could do with an upgrade.
So when I if I get this coat that means
I I'll be wearing like 700 pound just on
my body. Rainers jeans coat. [ __ ]
hell, bro. [ __ ] hell.
All right for something that doesn't
work in it, matey.
Like [ __ ] um Yeah.
Coats are all right though cuz you pay
money and they do last about 2, three
years. But trainers
next week cuz I planned it with my
sister. I'm going to go out next week. I
could go out this week, but I'd rather
wait till next week. I'd rather wait until December.
Makes more sense. Wait until December, I think.
Yeah, makes more sense. A lot more Oh yeah. Yeah. Pointless.
[snorts] Pointless drinking in November.
Waste of time. Waste of time. Waste of money.
Whoever was [ __ ] today as well. Yeah, probably.
You're a little copycat. [clears throat]
You little copycat.
Triple H. You're a little copycat.
That's what you are. Triple H. You're
nothing but a little copycat. Nothing but
Nothing but a little copycat, mate.
Nothing but a little copycat, matey.
Are you a little copycat?
Are you a little copycat, Triple H?
>> I don't know, but we need to stop now.
Anyway, it's bringing up these weirdos.
No, I can't, bro. I'm skinn. I got 30 to
last me a month.
I got 30 to last me a month, bro.
[snorts] Even though I get money every week. Bro,
these people in here were [ __ ] proper self projectors.
There's a lot of There's a lot of self
projectors on this community. Triple H.
There's a lot of self projectors. [laughter]
There's a lot of self projectors on here, bro.
30 to last me above. [ __ ] me.
Nope. I'm not telling you. It's none of
your business. But I get money every
week. End the story. You don't need to
know how much money I get.
Some guy come on here and said that I
get 30 I have30 to last me a month.
What the [ __ ]
30 to last me a month.
Where the [ __ ] would you come out with that from?
What the actual [ __ ] bro?
Who? Bro, who would even [ __ ] say
something like that?
It doesn't matter how much I have. You
don't know how much I have or you don't
know how much I get. None of your business.
I never go out out anymore. I literally
told you why I don't go out.
I haven't been out for two weeks. And
I've literally told you the reason why I
haven't gone out for two weeks.
I can go out every week if I want to,
but I told you why I'm not going out.
You don't know how much money I have.
I don't go out because I literally told
you why I did not go out.
And I I do the same thing every year, no
matter how much money I have or how much
money I get.
I could literally go out every week if I
wanted to. Month in month out, month in, month out.
Yeah, there's months where I do not go
out like January, November.
No, I don't go out because I don't want
to go out because I wanted to save the
money for December. It makes sense. Just
like January, people save money because
it makes sense. No, I don't go out
because I don't want to go out until December.
You do not know how much people have and
you don't know how much people don't
have. Stop talking about people that you
don't know. I don't know how many times
you have to be proven wrong time and
time and time and time and time and time again. You know,
I don't want to go out [ __ ] every week.
I went out three weeks in a row. I
haven't been out for two weeks and I
went three weeks in a row.
You don't know. You don't know how much
money people have and what they don't
have. Why do you keep doing this? It's embarrassing.
You tell people they can't afford
trainers, they buy trainers. Why do you
need to stop self projected
and or being nosy? It's [ __ ] weird.
How much money do you spend when you go
out drinking? What? 150 200?
Once you've had your haircut,
how much do you spend one?
Is it 150? Is it 200? How much is it you
spend? Say 150. You know
what? What do you spend? What is it? 150 200 pound.
No, I could go out right now if I wanted
to. I could go out right this second if
I wanted to.
Literally, I could go out right now if I
wanted to. Is 10 minutes to 7. There's
nothing stopping me other than I don't
want to. There's finances are not stopping me.
Okay, I couldn't. Whatever you say.
Anyways, moving on now from these self projectors. Anyways,
is he? Well, if he's got anything to
say, Triple H, send him to come. Tell
him to come in here.
Is it, bro? Let me have a look.
Well, if he's got anything to say, bro,
he knows where I am. I'm here.
Yeah, I think I'm going to get this coat. Is it?
Where is it?
Elaine hates me. Good one.
Tell him if he's got anything to say. I
have him blocked. I don't have this come
blocked. Do I? One second. No. No. No.
No. No. No. No. No. No. I don't. I don't
have this come blocked. One sec.
One second, bro. One second.
One second, lad.
Do I have him blocked? I don't think I do.
Oh, I do. Why do I have him blocked?
That's weird. I didn't know I had you
blocked. Well, you're not blocked now.
So, come on here.
I don't know why I had him blocked.
Oh, I remember why. Cuz you was coming
on talking [ __ ] and being biased. That's
why I blocked him. Well, you're
unblocked now. So, didn't even realize I
had to come blocked. Well, you're not
blocked now, so you can come back on here.
But yet yet Joseph was gambling his money alone.
He was gambling his money alone.
Well, you pe you people on here are just jealous haters.
I went out three weeks in a row.
Three weeks in a row. Yeah. Was
it three weeks in a row? I think it was.
Yeah. Three weeks in a [ __ ]
Three weeks in a [ __ ] row. I went out, bro.
I'll be out a lot next month, though.
I'll be out a lot next month because of um
Yeah, that'll be it until [ __ ] like
February. So, we need to make the most
out of last next month. do baby cakes. Oh, [ __ ]
So, yeah, I could go out every week if I
wanted to, matey.
Yes, I could. You don't know what people
have, what people don't have.
It was [ __ ] lush.
Yeah, it was [ __ ] lovely, man.
[ __ ] lovely. It was
Why do these people get jealous when
people people go to restaurants? Triple
H. Jesus Christ.
I think that just tells you how they've
got no life. the way they react to
somebody going to a [ __ ]
to somebody going to a to a restaurant.
I think it goes to show how like
skint they are, you know. Yeah. Yeah. Cuz
he's an absolute virgin.
Is that right, Steven Howard? Because
he's an absolute virgin. That's why.
So, how much do you go out when you How
much does it cost to go out drinking?
What? 100 pound 120. Steven Howard, what
is it? 20.
I think it's like 120
max, which is let's say 600 a month.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure
I I could go out drinking every week if
I wanted to, mate. Pretty sure I [ __ ] could. Yeah,
these people on here are [ __ ] idiots,
lad. They're [ __ ] idiots.
Yeah, bro. It was nice though. It was nice.
Yeah, it was nice though.
It was lost. [sighs]
One second, bro. >> [snorts]
>> Virgin boy.
Yeah, they ought to be fair, lad. They
ought to be fair.
They ought to be fair. Yeah. No, never.
I don't want to go out because it's November
and it's dead. Not that I need to
justify myself to these people, Steven
Howard. Not that I need to justify
myself to these [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] go out as much as I [ __ ] want.
The [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
It's just toxic as well when like I've
said a million times before when you go
out it's toxic isn't it
with like the women and [ __ ]
it's toxic. So,
just cuz people don't want to go out
dealing with it, it doesn't mean people
ain't got the money to do it.
You don't know what people have, what
people don't have.
Yep, pretty much.
Bless you. Bless you, Grey. Bless you. Greezy,
are you skinting skin? Flinty
skin fus skin blimp.
So, what do you think of the coat? It's
[clears throat] nice, is it? Greavves.
I like the I like the coat with a bug on it.
230 [ __ ] pounds.
I'll buy it, but obviously I have to run
it by uh
I'd have to run it by Greasy first,
you know. I'd have to run it by Grezy first.
Trying to get more of that [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
Let's see how this coat comes out.
No, I don't need to win the bet, bro. I
can afford it.
I don't I already won I've already won some bets.
I won that 110.
Another one [ __ ] I've won bets and
[ __ ] I can afford it, bro.
Not a problem. I can afford it. I need
to win money.
And I ain't no [ __ ] virgin from
[ __ ] Kent either.
Know what I mean?
I'm going to have to start [ __ ] working soon.
I say about working soon, but I actually
live a pretty good [ __ ] life
for someone that don't work all the gums
and get to do what I [ __ ] want. And
grievy, I haven't been out the past
couple weeks because I haven't wanted to
[ __ ] go out. I can [ __ ] afford it.
What? You think I can't afford to get my
[ __ ] haircut? You think I can't
afford to [ __ ] Of course I [ __ ]
can. I just don't want to. You know,
what do you think, Grezy? What's your
opinion on that?
All right, Timmy. You all right?
You all right, Timmy? Captain
you get paid. [ __ ] all. We wasn't
talking about cycling.
I wasn't talking about that. And you can
actually make decent money with that.
You can make £15 an hour. So, I mean,
it's pretty like enough to [ __ ] build
a [ __ ] nest egg. And I wasn't even
talking about that either. But even with
that, you can
you're not going to make fast money, but
you're going to be able to make enough
to be able to [ __ ] save, spend, and save. So, yeah.
Your legs don't get sore because you're
on an electric bike
and you don't get a backachche either.
The only thing that hurts is your shoulder.
Why? Yeah, but why wouldn't you do that,
bro? You got nothing better to do.
Still better than nothing. And you don't
get uh your you don't your legs don't
hurt because you're on an electric bike.
So you rent an electric bike.
I'll [ __ ] do it. Even if even if I
don't need to do it, I'll [ __ ] do it.
Even if it was just for like a month
just to build money up, I'd [ __ ] do
it. You ain't got anything better to do,
then why the [ __ ] not?
It's there if and when you need it to be honest. So,
but it's um I don't think a lot of you
people in here would be able to do it.
It is uh it's tiring and boring.
I would 100% do it, bro, with the gym.
I would do it just to build funds up.
Just so just I'll do it enough to like
build funds up.
Um and then yeah,
you don't do it all your life obviously, but yeah,
[ __ ] it is tiring though. It's
[ __ ] tiring. That's the only thing with it.
Better than most jobs though. [ __ ] at
least you don't get you don't get told
what to do.
You can probably make like 160 170 a day greasy
doing this bike thing.
That's quite a lot to to to make just
cycling around if you think about it.
You need to be doing that [ __ ] around January, mate.
That's when you need to start. You know,
there's You need a month.
You need a month for saving money.
You need a month for saving money, bro.
Doesn't matter how much money you get.
We always do this [ __ ]
So, I'll probably work I'll probably be
working in January, to be honest.
ready for midFeb March and the summer mad
and it graves.
You sound like a pretty good [ __ ]
I think we'll get on just fine. Yeah.
That Indian was [ __ ] lush.
Can't believe these people are so
jealous of [ __ ] people going for an Indian.
Apparently Elaine hates me. Really,
Joseph Farer? Is that why I live with Elaine?
I mean, I live with Elaine. How could
Laney hate me? You [ __ ] stupid old man.
Stupid old man, mate.
Over there to be fair.
Well, this Joseph Ferrar is a proper
gambling addict, isn't it?
Back at it. Back at it. Like I said, I
was down like if I like back at it,
back at it, if I said I was down to 40,
you would pro, you probably wouldn't
believe me. And I was in big, but profit is profit.
That's mad, bro.
This guy's a proper addict, isn't it?
This Bro, this guy's a proper gambling
addict, isn't it?
Oh, that virgin boy is mad.
That virgin boy is mad.
He's [ __ ] mad. [snorts]
So, Grey, can I buy this coat
or do I need to see if this Tommy
Hilfiger one comes out good first? All right.
So, I have to think I have to run things
by grievy first, you see.
It's good spending money on yourself,
isn't it? Greasy.
What is Virgin boy? Is Virgin boy excited?
Oh, that virgin boy is mad.
That virgin boy Greavves is [ __ ] mad.
There's a uh there's a lot of Mongs on
this community, isn't there, Greavvesy?
There's a lot of [ __ ] Mongs on this
community. Would you agree? [snorts]
The hill finger. You call it a hill
You silly goose.
You're a silly goose.
Bless you then greasy if you get £,200 a month.
Is that cute greasy that you get £1,200 a month? a shot.
Yeah, I think that coat is [ __ ] cat, bro. Honestly,
230 on the car is not that bad because
because the grievy,
as I always say,
and then he says nothing. That's what
they say in Little Britain. They say as
I always say,
but then he doesn't say anything.
Grezy, as I always say.
Oh, no. Do you know the funniest one?
Grezy. I'm looking for a Linda Williams.
Uh, we've got a Lindsay Williams.
Absolutely no way, [laughter]
Grezy. Absolutely no way.
right? We're going to wait until the
coat comes out. Yeah.
However you [ __ ] get money, you've
always got to bloody spend it on
something, Grezy. It's [ __ ] in it.
It's [ __ ] [ __ ] isn't it? Grezy,
but as they always say,
as you always say.
So, yeah, I'm actually spending money,
but this time it's on myself this year.
Greavves, are you proud of me?
Are you proud of me, Grevy, that I'm uh
spending money on myself this year?
One second. They've got some other
They've got some Tommy codes. One sec.
because as I always say,
Triple H, [snorts] why do I cuz uh
Greavves is my financial advisor,
so I have to um ask him, you know.
Because Because Triple H's, as I always say,
Triple H, as I always say,
no, you know what made me laugh, Triple
H? Yesterday you said that you're having
a tea and digestive biscuits and we said lovely.
He said it to you, not me for a change. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't know. That just made me laugh, bro.
What's planned? Well, I'm going out. Oh, [ __ ]
Well, I'm going out next week. Yeah.
Nope. No chaos on this channel. Anything
that happens, I'm not putting it up
there because of these little mongos. Remember?
No, bro. Because these little mongos, remember?
Do you remember
these little mongos? one half.
No, I am. Yeah. Mr. B,
you all right? Captain, Mr. B,
you all right, Captain?
are you all right? Captain K.
You all right? Chapter come.
The wash should be finished soon. Yeah. Heat.
We had a car.
So I have to buy a new [ __ ] car.
It's [ __ ] [ __ ] it. Yeah.
I want to buy this car. I think.
Skin on a [ __ ] skin flint.
Skin a [ __ ] skin flint.
No, but we're not But the thing is, bro,
we're not [ __ ]
we're not um
we're not from Kent, Steven Howard. So,
we we've got the money to do it because
we're not from [ __ ] Kent.
Are we mate? We're not [ __ ] skin
tanks from Kent.
No, I'm joking, bro. I probably won't
buy it. I probably won't need one until
next [ __ ] winter, to be honest.
But next winter, I'll definitely
definitely have to buy one.
Like, next [ __ ] um like [ __ ]
like [ __ ] um
like [ __ ] um next um October.
Definitely definitely October. I'll have
to buy one though next October 100%.
That'll be his third year. So yeah.
Why is that indigo Why is that indigo
trying to say I can't afford to go out every week?
Yes the [ __ ] I can.
Yes the [ __ ] I can go out drinking every [ __ ] week.
Yes the [ __ ] I can, mate.
Yes the [ __ ] I can. You don't.
Yeah, but I do need to buy a phone though 100%. Yeah.
Just a self projector, in it. Just like
when they're like, "Oh, you got £30 to
last you a month." Yeah. They're just self projectors.
You know that you know
just little self projectors. Just
Yeah, they're self projectors, bro. that. Yeah.
What it is with these people and this
Steven Howard is that they're just self projectors.
You know what I'm saying, lad? Like
that's that's all they are in here is
just serial serial serial
serial self projectors.
That's what they are.
That's what they do. They talk about
their own lives. Yeah.
30 to last me a a month.
30 to last me a month. But that's not even possible.
If I had done all my bollocks in, if I
had done my bollocks in, then I would
have £320 to last me the month.
Let's say I had no money and I just got paid
and I had done all my money and then I
would still have £320 to last me the month
cuz that's how much I'd get every week.
Like well for the month it would have
calculated to that for the for the month.
Yeah, they're just [ __ ] self-p
projectors, bro, on here.
Self projecting fat, ugly life losers
with no hope.
Hit a nerve when I say that, is it, lad?
Really? It's a nerve because it's the
truth. It is the [ __ ] truth. Let's be
real here, mate.
Yeah, proper proper self-projecting idiots.
But yeah, next summer, sorry, next winter.
But saying that though, I should get a
couple of All Saints t-shirts now for
the summer whilst they're on sale.
I think that would be like a good idea.
Put them away for summer.
Now they're on, you know, they're not
going to be on sale again.
You can probably spend about £100 on
worth of t-shirts
for like the summer.
Wouldn't be a bad idea to be fair, you
know, for the summer because obviously
Black Friday starts now, is it? So, you
could put them t-shirts away.
You could put them t-shirts away for the
summer, couldn't you?
Well, I bought a couple of t-shirts,
spend 100 pound on them.
Um, then obviously be good for the summer.
That's not a bad idea, you know. That
ain't a bad idea. To be fair,
it isn't a bad idea.
cuz I like their t-shirts. Their
t-shirts are good quality. I like their
t-shirts. I get like gray, white, black.
If you spend about 80 pound on t-shirts, it's uh
it's a good investment to be fair
for the summer.
Trust me, it's worth it. I'm going on
holiday in the summer as well. So, let
me see how much they are. voice is t-shirts.
No, they don't.
Some of them t-shirts made from brush cotton.
Yeah, they're made they're made from
brush cotton. So, £35 ones or £24.
So, you see what I'm trying to say? If
you buy a couple of them,
that's what 4400
that's pretty cheap to be honest.
They're like 20. Yeah.
Let me see.
So, how much do you pay for your plain
back black t-shirts?
Not enough, huh? 2 pound50. Really?
You little copycat.
You little copycat. Yeah, I used to get
them from the pound shop as well.
They're all right. Yeah, they're all
right in the pound shop, aren't they?
You little copycat.
Yeah, I I I've worn them at the pound
shop. Yeah, the pound shop ones. Yeah.
Yeah, they're good in there. Yeah.
So, when do I need to buy more clothes
again, Steven? How would you think?
I'd say maybe 7 months.
Never you mind. What's the youngest I date?
No, you're not going to wear it once and
throw it away, you idiot.
Yeah, all Saints t-shirts are good
in the summer.
You can buy white, gray, and black and
just switch it up in the summer.
Yeah, they're good t-shirts. I like the
white one as well. in the summer.
They're good in the summer, the white ones.
So, they're like three for £70, but
they last forever.
Yeah, I didn't really watch it, bro.
What What are they saying?
Yeah, I get what you're saying. Yeah,
when you put it that way. Yeah.
I like all s t-shirts
with a bug on it. It's not even a bug,
but we just call it the bug. Been
calling it a bug for years.
Yeah, I know. But we already know about
this, bro. I knew I was right.
They're [ __ ] I'm going out with my
sister next week. I'm not looking
forward to it, bro.
It's so peaceful not having to deal with
that [ __ ] anymore. So nice not dealing
with toxic women leading you on, you know?
I'm not looking forward to it, bro. I'm
dreading it to be fair. I'm actually dreading it.
I'm actually [ __ ] dreading it, mate.
Oh no. Do you know what coat I'm going
to get? One second. I'm going to get
this Air Jordan coat. The beige one. Do
you remember the beige air Jordan coat I
had? That's the one I'd get again, I think.
Oh yeah. Do you remember that beige
coat? I had the Air Jordan one.
Oh, I don't know if they still have it.
Yeah, that's my favorite one, bro. I had
it a few years ago.
But obviously, bro, I'd still be willing
to wear it, no problem, and not care. Do
you know why? I'd be willing to wear it
and not care.
Do you know why? I'm not a copycat.
You know what I'm saying? I'm not a copycat, lad. Yeah.
That one's a lot better. £122. That's
more like it. £130.
That's a lot better.
No, I won't be. And yeah, I will be
going out. Yeah.
Yeah. Post 130. That's a lot cheaper.
I used to have that Air Jordan car. It's
so outdated. Um, Triple H that you can't
even get on a normal website now.
You're probably wondering why I would
still buy it.
Cuz I'm not a copycat.
I'm not a copycat. So I I I wear
outdated [ __ ] You know what I might
triple? I wear outdated [ __ ] I'm not a copycat.
I'm not a little copycat.
What's the plan? Just chilling.
Yeah. How much of that? How much of them
How much of them coats?
Yeah, I think this Hilfiger coat can
last until October,
but then I then I'll definitely have to
buy another one.
I prefer to spend the money going out
and getting pissed.
To be honest, I'd rather just go out and
spend money on food than [ __ ] getting
drunk to be honest.
What is this? Yeah.
Oh, I'm still full up from that Indian, bro. Lush. [ __ ] lush.
Yeah. You don't get hungry straight
after again, bro. No way. I'm [ __ ] bloated still.
And I've done a lot of walking too as well.
Right. Let's see how this cloak has come
out. Should be finished now.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. One second.
Having a little wee wee. [snorts]
All right, let's see what this clutch
looking like. Okay, Captain
might need to go on another spin.
What the [ __ ]
going on here?
This car cost me 150 about two years ago,
but the one I was looking at,
that's all right. I think this is Yeah,
I don't think this is that bad. This color
if you want
just a bit. Yeah,
it definitely looks a bit whiter.
It is a bit quiet. One sec.
I think it's all right.
This is the car I got. It does.
What do you think? I think that's all right. But
that's whitened up a bit. That was a bit
yellowy. This is a bit discolored, but
I think it's
it's all right. I do think there's no
holes in it or anything.
Why is this gone all bobbly though?
I don't think I could have washed that,
you know. I think it's [ __ ]
No, I think it's [ __ ] bro.
I think I [ __ ] it.
Oh my god. I think I [ __ ] this coat up, bro.
No, no, no. I think I [ __ ] this boat up, bro.
I put it on 20, bro. I put on the lowest.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] The boat's [ __ ] Look.
Oh no, that's not good,
bro. That's not good. What the [ __ ]
Look, why does it all come apart?
Look, it's all [ __ ]
And I put it on a 20 as well. Why is it [ __ ]
I literally put this coat on 20, bro,
which is the lowest you can put it on.
And it's [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] it. Look,
the coat is actually [ __ ]
Look, bro. Look.
Yeah. Completely [ __ ]
Yeah, the code is completely [ __ ]
Well, I'm not buying another one this
month or next month. So, that's that.
That's that start in it,
bro. The coat's [ __ ]
Look, it's probably Look, look, it's all
come up off. Look.
Stupid coat's [ __ ] bro. No, it wasn't
meant to be dry clean. It's a normal
coat. It's the first time I've ever put
in the wash.
Yeah, it's the first time I've ever put
it in the wash.
No, it's a normal coat, bro. It's just
It's just like a normal coat.
The coat's [ __ ] now.
No, the code's [ __ ]
>> Yeah, it's actually [ __ ] lad. Well,
I've got a body warmer, so
I'm not buying I'm not buying an ar that. So, yeah.
Yeah, burnt arms when it was on a 20. It
was on a [ __ ] 20 and the arms are
Do I have another? I don't think I have
another curtain. Nope.
Oh, no. That's not good, is it?
That's not good.
That's really not good, bro.
But it was on a 20. I put it on a 20,
which is the lowest.
And I had to wash the coat, bro.
It wasn't meant to be. So yeah.
What the [ __ ] lad?
What the actual [ __ ]
Oh no, that's not good, is it?
So I guess I'm not going to wear a kite now.
Not going to wear a coat. I'll have to
wear a body warmer.
Oh no. That's not good, bro.
That's really not good.
I did wash it inside out, you [ __ ]
idiot. I did wash it inside out. Didn't
you see it? It was inside out.
You [ __ ] [ __ ] I washed everything
inside out. Socks, t-shirts, boxes. It
was inside out.
I don't know how that went like that.
So, I did wash it inside out. [ __ ] sake.
It isn't. It was inside out. I wash
everything inside out. Every little
thing I wash is inside out.
You know, I even got a [ __ ] coat.
Now I don't even have a coat.
Well, at least the coat at least we know
the coat was the coat was [ __ ] old, didn't it?
Yeah, at least we know the [ __ ] coke
was [ __ ] old, I guess.
Oh no, that's not good.
It's not wearable. The arms are [ __ ]
I'm not wasting money on another coat, bro.
Let me see if it's still wearable. I
don't think it is because the arms are [ __ ]
So, you can't wear it because the arms
are the arms are [ __ ] There's nothing in it.
No. No, it's not wearable, bro.
I don't think it is.
Let me see.
No, it's just saggy. It just sags. Maybe it
Let me try it on. No.
No, you can't wear it, bro. It's too
saggy. You can't wear it. It'll sag
somewhere else. And try it on. Try it Let's see.
Maybe it is.
I think it Yeah, I think you might be
able to wear it.
I think so. This is what it looks like.
Let me dry it. Maybe it might, if we're
lucky, it might shrink.
Yeah, if we're lucky, it might shrink. [laughter]
Oh, look. This is it. Look.
So, it's all like
I guess it's Yeah, I can try and shrink
it in the dryer and see if that helps.
Put it on and try and shrink it. Maybe
that might help.
What do you think now?
It is [ __ ] though because it's
supposed to be puffy but it ain't. Let
me shrink it anyways. Put in a dryer.
I'm going to shrink. I'm going to try
and shrink it.
I don't want to waste money on a [ __ ]
new coat, bro. Be fair. I need another [ __ ]
Let me see. Yeah, maybe just add see.
Yeah, let me just put on a standard heat
in it and see. [laughter]
Not good. That
hopefully will be all right then. That's
You reckon it will be all right this
coat or no boy.
You reckon it'll be all right that cut? Yeah.
Well, I'm not buying another one, so
that'll be that in it.
So, I just have to wear a body warmer.
I don't know how that's got like that on
the on 20 Celsius, but yeah,
it's not a coat that needs to be dry
cleaned either. It's a washable coat.
Dry clean that dry cleaning coats are
like leather coats, leather jackets. Mad. Hello. Yeah.
So, why did Virgin Boy keep saying Sher
Cole was attractive again? Steven Howard,
why did he keep saying it?
Yeah. Completely on its own. Yep. Little copycat.
It's the name.
So, what are we going to do with the
coach [ __ ] I'm not buying a new one.
cuz it needed to be washed. I never
washed it ever.
It's not good, is it, bro? Yeah.
A few talks. Yeah.
I'm not buying another coat. [ __ ] that.
No way. Am I buying another coat mate? Double call.
What a copycat.
One little copycat.
Anything to fit in with a crowd.
Anything to [ __ ] fit in with the crowd.
Want to fit in with the crowd. I would
Yeah, I couldn't have tipped that guy
today anyways, lad.
Yeah, it's going to have to be something
like that, matey, cuz I'm not spending
money on a coke. [ __ ] that. So, yeah.
I'll buy a cheaper one.
Yeah. Your [ __ ] are coing it.
Let me start looking on Amazon then cuz
that's what it's going to be. Eh. Yep.
But you can get one for like from for
like £40 when River Island or something. Yep.
Not River Island. Sorry. Zora.
No, you can probably get No, there's Oh,
no. No. There's another website called Sick Silk.
Yeah, there's a site called Six Silk.
One second, lad.
Yeah, there's a sight here. One second.
Yeah, there's one here. 90.
One second, lad. No problem.
down from 120 and that. So, I'll
probably just get a coat like that. 90 quid bargain.
I don't want to have to look at that
[ __ ] one ever again. It's [ __ ]
disgusting, mate. It's [ __ ]
disgusting. It is.
There's one here. It's a lighter one and
that's 90. There's some good coats. I
used to I used to have this I used to go
to this brand before.
I'm looking at this one, bro. This one lush. Yeah.
You got two colors.
You have like the plum color or you have
the white color. [clears throat]
Yeah, there's black ones. I can get a black one. Black. Yeah.
Hoping they have a platform.
I look like they do.
Nope, they don't have black.
A lot of black. Um,
I'll show you the two if you want.
Don 90 pounds. One sec.
This is the first one.
That's the first one.
And this is the second one.
I kind of like the the cream one to be fair.
It's uh actually be
Yeah, I'll get a small.
What color? I think the beige one, isn't it?
Should I get the beige one or should I
get the other one?
I think the beige one looks good.
Yeah, I'm a small. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, I'm going to get the white
one and take a risk with it. I'm going
to get the white one. Yeah,
stick with the [ __ ] jeans and that
just get dry cleaned.
I get a small or medium.
Yeah, I could get medium and it's too
big. That's the thing.
Okay, I'll just get a medium one. [ __ ] it.
I want to see that [ __ ] code again,
bro. It's [ __ ] disgusting.
Yeah, I'm going to get that car. One sec.
Yeah, I got the beige one. Only 90.
got [ __ ] [snorts] bro. Got [ __ ]
That's going to be nice with the
trainers and the jeans. We lush
One second. Let me order this coke, bro. Yeah,
why are you asking that? Why would I overturn it?
Yeah, but I'm not going to do that, obviously.
Don't know whether to get medium or small.
I think small, you know.
I reckon small.
I'm going to go small.
I think small 100%. I'm not going to get
medium. I'm going to get small.
No, I'm getting small. I know my size definitely small.
And if I need to return it, I'll return
it. But I'm definitely sure I'm small. So, yeah.
I'm not happy with this, mate. I have to
spend my savings on this [ __ ] coat.
But at least I'll be looking good for next week.
I'm sure I'm a small.
I'm not that big. So, I'm sure I'm a small.
I'm going to go with small, bro. Right.
Let me just get this small bar.
Right. I've ordered a I've ordered a
car. I've ordered it. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. I got it.
Right. So, it should come.
Yeah, it's coming. It says it's coming
the next day. Next day. I got free next day delivery.
Yeah, free next day delivery.
Yeah, that's not bad, is it?
90. That's less than £100 for a next day delivery cart.
Pretty good, eh?
That means I would have only saved 600 this month.
Still good though, is it? Yeah, whatever.
I know, bro.
I know, dude.
It's madness, isn't it? It's [ __ ]
madness. Well, at least we got a new
clo, new [ __ ] jeans and new trainers
to go out next week. [ __ ]
know. [ __ ] Yeah, it's [ __ ] over.
That's almost £200 we spent today.
Yeah, it's bad, bro. It's bad.
It is [ __ ] bad, is it? That coat is
annoying. That coat just annoys me
looking at it, lad.
I need to be saving money. But to be
fair, I did need a new coat and that was
a good deal. So,
I've used this type before. Six silk. So,
it's not funny, guys, but it's bad.
Quite bad, to be honest.
Quite [ __ ] bad. Yeah. Heat.
It's a nice coat though, is it? It is a
nice coat. 90 quid. That's a bargain,
bro. For that coat.
It's a bargain.
So, I'm not that pissed off about the
Tommy Hilfiger coat because
um it is quite old, isn't it? So, we
would have only had another couple of
months. Bro, looking forward to that new
coke coming, bro.
I need to be careful, bro. I need to
save some money, bro. I keep saying this
and I keep [ __ ] pissing money away, lad.
Just keep pissing money away every time.
That's good though. 90 car, isn't it?
Yeah. 90. That's cheap, bro.
I don't give a [ __ ] It's a coat in it. So,
I'll be looking sexy, bro. [ __ ] next week.
Marty jeans, nice paper trainers. Yes.
90 on a coat. Yeah, it is cheap. What's it?
Yeah. Looking at that coat, bro. Pisses
me off, bro. That's why I just [ __ ]
bought this one. It's pissed me off, isn't it?
[ __ ] annoying, bro.
Yeah, I'll get a dry cleaner like
get a dry clean in like [ __ ] 3, four months.
Yeah, my jeans were 190.
Yeah, mine were [ __ ] 190.
What are these replay jeans? I've never
heard of them.
Never heard of these [ __ ] replay
jeans that you're [ __ ] going on about.
So, I spent over £150 today.
Yep. But I got30 to last me the month. Oh, really?
Yeah. Interesting. I didn't know that.
You learn something new every day, don't you?
110s. What are they? Well, obviously I
know they're [ __ ] trainers, but what ones? Oh, them ones.
Yeah, I know them 110s. I've had a pair before.
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah. I know that ones I had to stop
wearing them cuz they hurt my feet. Yeah.
Yeah. I got a coat for 90 quid. Triple H.
90 quid, lad.
Big up six silk.
[ __ ] hell, bro. I need to get on a
piss again, bro. Next week. 100%. Next
Yeah, I know the trainers you're on about.
I like Vapor Max with me.
>> Yeah, I like Vapor Maxes.
Nice black t-shirt under that
coat as well.
Yeah, bro. I woke up at 11 today. I told you.
Yeah, I woke up at 11:00.
Yeah, I weren't going to let them have
that [ __ ] money, mate. Well, was I?
Nah, I going to let them have that [ __ ] money.
Show my jeans. Triple my ones.
These are my jeans. Yeah. 190 lad.
190. I've only worn him a few times. I'm
going to wear this shirt on. I'm going
to wear this next week. Counting down
the days, mate. Counting down the days.
Going to wear this
with these, bro.
Look at that. Triple H. Oh, mate. I
can't wait till this coat comes.
Look at this, bro.
Yeah, look, they're brand. I've only
worn them and I've worn these twice. I
can't wait. I can't wait.
I can't wait. Seriously, bro.
Can't wait, man.
No [ __ ] No horrors, man. No [ __ ] horrors.
Yeah, these trainers and jeans are
[ __ ] fresh. I'm going to [ __ ] wear
these, bros. Next Saturday.
Next Saturday, lad.
For this new coat that's coming, I pay
90. Just pay 90 for it.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, lad.
Life [clears throat] is expensive, bro.
[ __ ] get money and he just goes,
"How the [ __ ] have I spent 150?"
I'm just going to go to a local pub with my sister,
but I'm going to go out again the week
after that. I'll be going out a lot next
month cuz it's December. So, I'll be
going out every week
or maybe every two weeks maybe. Well,
I'll be going out a lot. Feel that way.
[ __ ] sake, man.
I need to start saving some money, bro,
as well. But I can't because every time
I try to save, something crops up, you know.
Every time I try to save, bro, it's annoying. Oh, wow.
No, I can't be doing that, bro. I can't
wear cheap trainers.
No, I'm not like the Skint Virgin. I
can't be doing them things, bro.
I can't stop buying insane trainers.
We're not all skin like the Virgin.
What does she drink,
baby? Guinness and vodka. Normally, I'd
go out to the city in it, but we're
going out, so we're just going to stay
local, but it's still busy.
>> We'll still get busy. Yeah.
Yeah. Virgin boy can't afford them trainers.
You know why Steven Howard? Because he's [ __ ] skin.
You already [ __ ] know, bro.
You already know that he's skint [ __ ] skin.
All right, let's check this [ __ ] coat
in a minute. I think it's [ __ ]
Well, it is [ __ ] but we'll see if it
if it's no longer [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] Well, it's old anyway, so
Jesus Christ, bro.
Any job. Any any job, man. Any job. Any
job. Any job. Any job. Any job. Any job.
Any job, mate? Any job? Any job? Any
>> Any job?
>> You know he's not working. You know he's
not working. You know he's not working.
>> Any jumping? He's [ __ ] jumping.
You know he's not working. He's [ __ ]
stupid. He's [ __ ] skipping. He's
[ __ ] He's [ __ ] stupid. [ __ ]
>> Bro, can you just shut the [ __ ] up now
about his [ __ ] daddy savings? Don't
know about [ __ ] daddy's [ __ ]
savings. Daddy's life savings.
He keeps going on about daddy's life
savings that he showed 100 years ago.
Steven Howard, lad. Madness.
Is [ __ ] madness, isn't it?
What? These [ __ ] the coat. It needs
to leave it a little bit longer, bro. It
still ain't dry.
Coat's [ __ ] Basically,
coat's completely [ __ ]
Oh, he's he's a mad virgin. He's a
[ __ ] mad virgin. Yeah. They ain't
even got a [ __ ] grand.
That [ __ ] ain't even got a [ __ ] grand, mate.
Yeah, he's [ __ ] He's skint, mate.
He's skint [ __ ] skimpling. I told you
this million times.
I bought my mom Uggs this month as well, didn't I?
Yeah, I bought my mom Uggs this month. So yeah,
they were 165. Yeah.
Still need to buy a phone. Always
something you got to buy, bro. I'm sick of it.
I'm [ __ ] sick of it. Always something
you got to [ __ ] buy.
You're a [ __ ] skin.
You [ __ ] virgin.
[ __ ] virgin. [ __ ] virgin.
You [ __ ] virgin kunga. Yeah.
Yeah. Next year um Steven Howard is
going to be about me me.
How do you feel about that, lad?
How do you feel about that? Me me
me me me me me me me me me me me me me
me me me me me me me. Simple.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] [ __ ]
Stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] coat.
You know, Virgin Boy is obsessed with um
people being materialistic.
Yeah, he's obsessed with people being materialistic
cuz he's too scared to buy anything himself.
cuz he's too much of a skin [ __ ]
and coat. I needed a new coat, bro. I
haven't had a new coat in two and a half years.
It's something that I needed.
So, it's not something I wanted. It's
something that I needed.
Trust me, I wouldn't be buying it if I
didn't need it.
I don't particularly want to be wasting
money, but yeah,
believe you me, I don't particularly
want to be [ __ ] wasting money.
I can afford it though, Indigo. I can afford it.
That's the difference. I can afford it.
Virgin, but I can't afford it.
I can afford it.
virgin by car it because he's [ __ ]
skin [ __ ] skin flim. SK. Yeah.
I can't help myself. Indigo, leave me alone.
I can't help myself, mate. We're not all
skin like the [ __ ] virgin.
We're not all skin like [ __ ] virgin
are we, mate? We're not all skin by that virgin [ __ ]
So just just just just you know allow it
be nice to us you know.
Well, that's going to come
virgin boy skin and a [ __ ] skin. Flint
have a cup of [ __ ] in a minute.
I think Virgin needs to get a little job.
Indigo, what do you think?
I think he needs to get himself a little jab.
Just a little jab.
Nothing wrong with a little job,
is there? Nothing wrong with a little job, mate.
Nothing wrong with a little job. You get
You get a
You'll get very far in life with a little job.
It's just a little job, mate.
Just an old job.
I always you say just to [ __ ] virgin
boy. Why don't you get yourself a little job?
It do you the world of good. Working.
Working will do you the world of [ __ ]
good. It's what I used to say to him.
Indigo, working will do the world of good.
as I had a little smile of a face, you know. Yeah.
Right. Time to look at this [ __ ] coat.
You want to see it, Steven? Yeah. Oh gosh. Grazy.
I don't know. One second. Legend boy. Oh no.
I hope it's not feeling all right now.
It's feeling a bit better.
Hopefully it's not, mate. I just ordered
a new [ __ ] coat.
I just ordered a new [ __ ] pipe. I
have two pipes now.
One sec. It is stupid. But
I think it's all right.
Yeah, I think you can kind of wear that, bro.
Well, I just ordered a new coat.
It's just a bit better now.
final because I put it in a thing.
It is [ __ ] though, but you can still wear it. Look.
Yeah, it's not that bad. You can still wear it.
I've just ordered a [ __ ] new coat
cuz I thought it was [ __ ]
It is still [ __ ] It's not how it was,
but it seems still wearable,
huh? And I just ordered a new [ __ ] coat as well.
Oh, well, we'll have two coats.
Well, it seems a bit better now. The the
the the [ __ ] coke.
No, it's [ __ ] No, no, no. is still
The coat is still [ __ ] lad.
No, the coat is still [ __ ] It is
still [ __ ] but you can wear it like
Yeah, it's still wearable.
Yeah, the coat's still wearable.
But I bought a new one anyways. [ __ ] SC.
>> I just ordered a new [ __ ] car.
I just [ __ ] code.
A lot of
I just ordered a [ __ ] new one.
It's all right though.
We're not skipping obviously Howard.
So it should be fine.
Not we're not [ __ ]
That [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] huh.
Yeah, seems better now. But
you want to join Timmy? Yeah,
he's on the virgin side. The blades. >> [laughter]
>> I'm a happy.
>> Oh, [ __ ]
>> All right there.
>> All right, lad.
>> What's up, man?
>> Nothing. I just bought a new car.
>> Yeah. What what make was that?
>> Uh thick silk. If you ever seen it,
>> you've seen it in it.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Have you ever worn it? >> No.
>> Where did you see it then? >> Online.
>> Yeah. They used to have it on in JD
years ago, but they don't anymore.
>> Yeah. Um so when you going out on next Saturday?
>> Next Saturday, son. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yes, lad.
What about you?
>> Um, I don't know when I'll next out. Maybe.
>> Next weekend.
>> Maybe tomorrow. >> Really?
>> Yeah. Just for I feel like not mad.
Don't know what I'm doing yet. [snorts]
>> You are.
>> You're going to be on the pool lad. >> No.
Just going to play D in there. I like
play I like to play pole as well, mate.
>> Yeah, lad.
>> All right.
>> Where am I supposed to go?
>> Get the train.
>> Yeah, but to where? >> Durham.
>> Well, the train station.
>> All right.
>> Yeah, I've been I've been I've been
there. Well, I haven't been there. I've
been past it on the train before when I
used to go Newcastle in it.
>> It goes past there.
>> Mhm. Yeah,
>> we could Why don't we just do Newcastle
play and play darts there?
>> Good idea.
>> Maybe I might not have darts there. Is it?
>> Yeah, I love that everywhere, man. What
you having now? A cup of
>> Yeah, copper [ __ ] with free sugars. >> Yeah.
>> So, okay. I I'll go
>> and you'll meet me.
>> Well, Hi. Hi, man.
>> Oh, I love I love your little accent. It's cute.
>> Yeah, man.
>> Oh, what did Timmy say? His his penis
was hurting, isn't it?
>> The woman bit it, didn't she?
>> Yeah. Bless you. You know, um I was
going to say there um
that's what I do now, Peter. I don't um
I don't play on them like blueprint
machines and the in the uh pubs me I
like I play d
or something you know so just that I'm doing something
>> so I'm not
>> I don't I don't do gambling me like in the pubs
>> yeah man
>> [ __ ] um so did you like that football
bet win I had the other day was sick of
it bro no draw
>> yeah it was a good little win lad
cuz it's hard to get them in, you know, [ __ ]
>> So if you want to do if you want to ban
more on Saturday, right, do slow in Enfield Town.
>> Is that what you're doing? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, but you can do the same teams every week.
>> I can.
>> Just one minute. I'm going to get a can of coke.
>> Oh, bless you then. Well, I can do the
same teams every week. Just one minute, bro.
I do what I bloody want.
Is that right, Grezy?
Is that right, Greavves? I'll do what I bloody want.
You don't [ __ ] tell me what I can and can't do. Enfield Town.
Yeah, Enfield Town. Oh, I bought myself
a 90 Coke Grey. Is that okay with you, boss?
Yeah, it cost me £9, Grezy. I know
you're my um financial advisor, but
yeah. Is that all right?
>> All right, son.
I got 24 cans for 12 quid.
>> [ __ ] bargain.
>> But why I
>> [ __ ] bargain. Do you like my trailers then? >> Um
>> yeah nice and bit max. Yeah.
>> [ __ ] expensive though.
>> So what you going to wear for the night
out? Obviously you jeans your friends.
What are you wearing? Like a jump or a t-shirt or
>> I'm just going to wear the coat.
>> Oh you wear all right. You got your new
coat to go out. I didn't know. All
right. All right. All right. Yeah, with
a black with a black t-shirt in it. Just
like a black t-shirt, you know.
>> Yeah, it was quite a good deal. Grey 24
can 12 like 50 a can in it. We buy that.
>> What you saying [ __ ]
>> So, have you bought anyone presents for Christmas?
>> No, I'm starting next week. Me, lad.
>> How much you looking to spend? >> Uh
about 4 500 quid. [laughter]
>> No, really. Yeah.
>> No, but on who? On who?
>> I've only I've only got me B to buy, haven't I?
>> Your what?
>> I've seen I've only got me B to buy.
>> Your bird?
>> Ben, my me son.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. Oh, is that what you
call your son?
>> A b. That's what you call That's what
the burn. Yeah.
>> I've never heard of that.
>> It's northern slang life.
>> So, you're going to Okay. So you you're
spending £400 or £500 on him. >> Yeah.
>> Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
>> Yeah, bro.
>> Cuz I'm not buying anyone anything.
>> What about your mom and sister?
>> I've already bought my mom boots.
>> Greasy. B A I R N. Ben. >> Yeah.
>> What you saying, Peter?
>> I said I bought my mom Ugg boots. Do you
know how much they retail for?
Um, they're not cheap. I know that.
>> Yeah. 165 quid. You know, how did you know?
>> Cuz I used I bought me ex-girlfriend not cheap.
>> What color did you get?
>> It was like a like a brown color. Like a light brown.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> What What color did you get your mom?
>> Gray. Gray.
>> Gray. Hi. Are you getting your sisters
out like Peter?
>> No, that's all. I can't afford it.
>> Do your sisters get you anything?
>> No, only one. [snorts]
>> Well, Charlene get you.
>> Yeah. Has it ever happened to you one
year where you couldn't afford
Christmas? Yeah, I think it's happened
to everyone, isn't it?
>> No, it's never happened to me. I've
always wrecked me.
>> Yeah. Well, I So, it's never happened
where you couldn't afford it this year.
Do you remember? Huh?
>> No, not actually. Never. Never. No. No.
I got paid. Yeah, it could happen though
because you could do your balls in in
December and then you're [ __ ] in it.
>> Nah, not really. Nah, I don't play the
machines anywhere now. I don't go to the
betting shop me. I don't even don't even
step foot in the betting shop.
>> Yeah, but [snorts] I'm saying it can
happen to people don't it? Yeah.
>> Oh, can happen to a lot of people. I
guarantee it probably go to try and win
money for Christmas and then lose it, would it?
>> Yeah, but yeah. Yeah, probably.
>> It's not funny, is it? It's um sad
really when you think about
>> Why does Timmy lie so much, man?
>> What's he doing now? Like
>> about lying about sex and that. It's
ridiculous, isn't it?
>> He might not be lying.
>> Yeah, he might go him.
>> What do you think, Rey? Do you think Tim
lies about having sex?
>> Just a me can of Cork, lads. next year.
>> I love kind of coke me. They're no good
for your toothies. They're no good for
your toothies, you know.
>> No, full of sugar around know
>> bad, bro. It's bad. It is bad.
>> These people repeat themselves every
day. Now I'm getting sick of it.
>> Yeah, there's a lot of repeaters on
here, Grezy, on this community, lad.
>> It's all the last page.
How much did you You said you get 500 a
week, don't you?
>> Just averages between five to six. All right.
>> Nice. Is it nice? I' had I've had eight
eights in that me and sevens on the time. But
>> that's long though. Is it
>> [ __ ] no good working man? >> Huh?
>> Working kills you, man. I'm [ __ ] me back.
>> Bless you. I just I get I get the old
[ __ ] pains and that
>> when you get an old man it will start affecting you. >> I
could you live off £500 a month?
>> Obviously not.
>> What do you mean obviously not? People
do. What do you mean? People do it.
That's what I was [ __ ]
[clears throat] There's people on
Universal Credit isn't there who get
like what is it? I think it's [ __ ]
>> 300 a month.
>> 340 a month. Like how you meant to live
off that? They do, don't it?
>> They don't. They spend on the first week
and they struggle on for three weeks.
That's what happened there. No way.
Happened last year. It's like 85 quid a
week. What the [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but like
>> But there's some people.
>> Could you live off 600 a month? >> No.
>> But why? What do you spend the money on?
>> I pay rent. I [ __ ] I
>> No, I mean like without rent. No, no, I
mean like without rent. Oh, I spend I
spend money every week for me son. I mean
>> I like to go I like to buy clothes and
friends and I like outing at me
>> and out. Yeah. Did you see my video
today? It was lost, bro.
>> Yeah, it did look nice to be fair, lad.
>> it cost a lot of money, bro.
>> How much? >> £50.
>> 50 quid. What'd you get?
>> Didn't you? >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] hell. Do you know that what you
had there up here, right? They do specials
>> for 15 quid specials where you get a a
start a main a right
and a [ __ ] n bread for like 15 quid.
It's cheap up north.
>> Yeah. Up north they do multiculture
buffets as well which we don't have
here. They do have north but we don't
have it here.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> So could you what about what about 800 a
month? You could live off that in it. Uh >> maybe.
>> Yeah. Why are you a spoiled brat? [laughter]
>> No, I just I don't know. People just
depends. It's Some people live different
to other people, though. They like
people lot most people gamble and they
like the lot. Loads of people like to
drink every day and things. But that's
never been for me. I have to be honest. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, man.
You're you're rich, in it.
>> No, I wish.
>> So, what they do they do they pay you
they pay you weekly? Not monthly. Is it
>> weekly? Yeah.
>> What? Like midnight? Isn't it?
>> I don't know. I just wake up. Me wages
are in the bank, lad. >> Like,
>> yeah. You probably spend all of it as
soon as you get in it.
>> No, I don't. I used when I was a young
lad. I used to Yeah. He used to uh he
used to go to the betting shop and he
used to finish work and then do me
sacking but when I grew I've grew out of
it now like I don't go now anyway. >> Yeah.
>> I have a few points on a Friday after
work me but I've even knocked that on
the head now.
>> Why? To save money or
>> no cuz if I get if I cuz I don't know I
just like to just have a few points me
it's all out for me and I end up spend
all or nothing is it? [laughter]
>> Yeah I can't just have two pints. I'm
not normal. Like I have to mix.
>> Try mixing Try mixing your spirits.
Yeah. Try mixing your spirit. Try mixing
spirits and then go to work the next
day. It ain't happening, bro.
>> And it Yeah.
>> I've had a few work.
>> Yeah. Like two days in it.
>> Yeah. Like even when you've had a good
session, man, it takes me a good few
days to recover, lad.
>> So, how much all them 110s?
>> Uh 175. The ones
>> I have had them before. Yeah, I have had
them. They're like a Yeah, I have had
>> I like them like them.
>> What size are you again? Trainers >> 10.
>> Yeah, same as me. I'm Well, I'm like
nine and a half 10 to be fair. I think
my feet are shrunk, but I just get 10. I
just wear the tens. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I like them on cloud train
as well. I've got a pair of light blue
ones. Lovely. But
>> did you like Monty's boss ones? Um
>> I can't really remember them to be honest, fella. >> Really?
Yeah. What? What coat? What coat did you
say you got? >> Bagos.
>> How much are they?
>> Don't know. Mom bought me for Christmas. Um, >> nice.
>> I was like, it's a black one. I think
it's a black one. She got like a
windbreak ones are nice. I like I like
the co I don't like the ones.
>> Yeah. See, even if you Yeah. Even like
if you get like 11,200 pound a month,
that's even that's hard to live off if
you want like a really like good
lifestyle and drinking.
>> I could live off 1,200 quid a month. Easy.
>> 300 quid a week. I don't really do much
anyway. Yeah, I could live off. Yeah,
definitely live off,200 quid a month.
300 quid a week. I could probably live
off. Yeah. Yeah,
>> I get that. And I and I and I still like
get more just to like be able to do it
like wins and [ __ ] in it.
>> You should be able to live off that,
man. that just when you gamble
>> bro there's been time Yeah but bro
there's been times Listen there's been
times where I've had £1,000 in my
account listen I've had £1,000 in my
account bro and I've gone out on the
[ __ ] Friday and then by the Monday no
gambling mind you I've had like £500 left
>> it can happen it can happen like cuz cuz
I'll get like a takeaway like I don't
know what it went on well like escorts
and I'll get I'll drink get an escort
and then go to like a restaurant and
then buy the and uh probably spent about4500 pound.
>> Well, that's not all the time.
>> All the time.
>> No, last last time I went out, bro. Last
time I went out two weeks ago,
>> I went for an Indian and drink and all
in all it cost like £100. It only cost
100, but so I don't know how that's
happened before, but it has happened,
bro. It has happened and it hasn't been gambling either.
>> Yeah, it's a mad lad.
>> I think it's when I've got like a
haircut and [ __ ] Maybe like when I've
got my haircut and it's all added up or
something, you know? I don't know.
>> You You pay 50 quid for your IMB cut.
That's tragic. That like I only get 20, mate.
>> Yeah, but I get like a face mask and
stuff. I get like everything in it.
>> I get I get me haircut. I get me beard
done. I get oct towel. Nose and ears. It
nose and ears whack. 20 B. [ __ ] mint that.
>> I need to come I need to come to your
bar. I might come to your barbers this week then.
>> You lad. Yeah.
>> What do you think of that, Grezy? Me and
Triple H having our haircut together. It
would be cute, isn't it?
>> How the [ __ ] did you have a child at
such a young age? That's crazy, bro.
>> I didn't think you would ever. >> Huh?
>> You what?
>> I didn't think you'd have a child at
such a young age.
>> Yeah, man.
>> Yeah, bro.
>> That's crazy, isn't it? You only got
one, is it?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. You don't want any it? [ __ ] that.
No, I probably won't ever have abnormal.
I don't want no more, man.
>> Did you know when when you found out you
having a child? Yeah. Did you want it to
be a boy or a girl? >> Boy.
>> Yeah. A lot of people want boys.
>> Do you know what happens, bro? Some
people want like a boy and they can they
have girls and they have like four girls
before they have a boy. I know some guys
got like six sisters. >> Mad.
>> Yeah. Six sisters, bro. Cuz obviously
they would keep trying for a boy in it. Obviously. >> So,
Bless you. Bless you, Triple. I still
don't know your name.
>> My name is Toby.
>> Yeah, right.
>> Actually, actually, it actually is. >> Toby.
>> Why would I lie about my name? Yeah,
>> because Triple H, as they always say,
>> for Toby. Triple H.
>> Is that right, Greg? As I always say, [clears throat]
Triple H, as I always say, you know, [laughter]
I love that sketch. I love that comedy
sketch. You was watching Little Britain
yesterday, weren't you, Triple H?
>> Yeah, I like the Margaret scene in
there. And where [clears throat] goes Margaret? Margaret?
>> I like the Fat Fighter one. Have you seen that?
>> That's good. Yeah. Yeah.
>> What's that, Van? What's that?
I love it.
>> You have one.
>> Did you have a wank over Little Britain?
>> No. No.
I like to describe one. I like to
describe where they describe them. Do you remember?
>> Um, no.
>> They start insulting them. They'll
describe them and then start insulting
them. Like, hi, this is Linda. We got
someone here. And then they start being
nice and then start insulting them.
>> Oh, yeah. I know what you mean. Yeah. Yeah. [laughter]
>> I like that one.
>> You saw me. Did you like the betting
shot video I did? Well, I waited. Green.
Well, I waited H.
>> Yeah, it was crazy that I can't believe
you had no sleep over it, man. That's a mad.
>> Yeah, I didn't cuz I didn't cuz cuz if
they if they had cashed it in Ron, they
would have been laughing at me in it.
>> Yeah, that would have been your finish,
lad, wouldn't it?
>> I was going to have that, mate. [ __ ] that.
Bethany, also known as the bomb,
screenshotted your barcode, lad.
>> Yeah, I didn't know about that. I'll
never [ __ ] put another I would never
do that again. I'll never make that
mistake again. [ __ ] that.
>> Don't post the barcode. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. [ __ ] that.
How much you putting on a footy on Saturday?
>> Probably 20.
>> God bless you then.
>> Probably do a do a do a free um both
score no draw. You should get like 250 back.
I'm going to have a look. Yeah, I'll
have a good I have a study on a Friday
night. M I'm going to do
>> Yeah. So, what do you think of the bets
that I that I've done in the past where
I put like 120 on two teams and it
returns back 360?
>> They're good wins then. [snorts]
>> Yeah, but it's a lot putting in though, is it?
>> Yeah. London good loss in it if you
lose, but paid off, didn't they?
>> Yeah. Stuff like that, man. I don't bet
massive amounts of money. I just think
it's just pointless. Yeah, that's what
Ant Ant Ant Ant Ant Ant Ant Ant Ant Ant
Antman says, "Yeah, Antman says the most
you'll ever put on is like 10 or 20."
Like that's it. Yeah.
>> Yeah, he's right.
>> He says no. He says there's no point in
putting 120 on it. Is that true?
>> Yeah. Anyone can beat anyone. Yeah.
>> So there's no point putting 120 on it.
>> Like last weekend, um who let me down?
Liverpool against [ __ ] Not Forest got
paid three. Like that's all crazy.
>> But you know if you put 500 pound on a
double both teams to score it can return
like 16,700. You know that
>> if you do what? Sorry.
>> If you if you put £500 on two teams
Yeah. and they both score,
>> it returns 16,700 back. But obviously if
you lose, you lose 500 quid.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Normally about 45s and
stuff. I thought it was Nick.
>> It's a lot of money to lose, isn't it?
Just on a football bet. No.
>> I've got an tip for Saturday. What I'm
going to have a bet on if I've been
giving it as a tip. Have you ever Have
you ever won a lucky um 15? Antman did.
He won five grand off like
>> You want to tell me to tell you a story
about a lucky 15? >> Sure.
>> I just had a 50 p one. So it was a £750
bet obviously for horses lucky 15 and I
was at work and I just went on me I went
on me for me
>> and the first three horses won it was
for the grandest bet right
>> and offered me 340 odd quid. I was
[snorts] waiting on a two to one favorite.
Two to one favorite in the on the last
one. I just cashed out and I just put
the 30 quid in it and I cashed out well
cuz the last one came the last one came
second. That was that was not like that.
>> You lost what?
>> I I cashed out 330.
>> Yeah. [snorts]
>> And then uh I put the 30 quid on the
horse I was waiting on for the lucky 15,
but I cashed out so I just put the 30
quid on and it never got 300 quid but
got 750. How's happy lad?
>> All right, in it. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Decent, >> captain.
>> I've got I think I might start doing
them lucky 15 fast goal scorers as well, mate.
>> I think I think you should start doing roulette again.
>> No, I'll never play that again, lad.
>> Three zeros on the wheel. H. [laughter] >> Yeah.
>> Three zeros on the wheel, bro.
>> Not not in the not in the lads. Not in
the global draw one, I don't think. in
it only like patty power and that
>> friend in it.
>> Yep. But I remember I walked in there
before£50 I come out with a grand
>> like last last summer. Yeah. >> Yes.
>> It was good times, isn't it? Why don't
you go to the Stoke um Why don't you go
to the uh Stockton Casino? Have you ever been there?
>> Shut down, I think. Really?
>> Probably because I don't have money to
keep the [ __ ] thing open obviously in it.
>> Stockton's a [ __ ] all as well.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying. So like do
you know where I want to go gambling?
Blackpool. I've never been bro. Yeah.
>> Yeah. But go Blackpool. Like I know. I'd
like to go there. Yeah.
>> You never been in it? I've never
>> I've not been to Blackpool. No. No.
>> No. Michael Basset hasn't it?
>> Yeah. Don't know ladies
in this ch I remember all the time I
used to go past it.
>> Yeah, is a dive as well.
>> You should go there.
>> I used to work in Darlington, mate.
>> I'm surprised you never saw Toasty.
>> He lives there.
>> Yeah, he's Darlington. Yeah,
>> he's Darlington based triple. I wonder
if he goes to Darlington footy games. I
don't think he does.
>> Do I met him? It's funny, isn't it?
>> Yeah, man. Yeah, I remember when he met Martin Eldridge. [laughter]
>> I sometimes watch like you know every
every [ __ ] so every
like watch it once a year or something.
It's good that video.
>> Yeah. Why do these accounts come on here
Triple H and say Peter Belly needs to
find his mama and stuff? Is it you?
>> Why would I do that? Ma,
>> I don't know. Like, it's some guy. Yeah.
And he keeps coming on like different
accounts. Like he'll go on account and a
week later he'll be on a different one.
He says, "Peterbelly, you need to find your mama."
>> Probably be Harry Fraud.
>> It's weird though, isn't it?
>> Yeah. The weird man.
>> Think about it. It's probably It's
probably an old man behind the account doing that.
>> It's some shadow in it.
>> Oh, do you remember the Buzz Lightyear
account? years ago.
>> Yeah. My member Isabel Eldridge.
>> Yeah. You Why did you find it funny though?
>> It's funny though.
>> Well, the Buzz Lightyear one.
>> Both of them.
>> Yeah. But they they're old making
[ __ ] accounts, isn't it?
>> They've got no better though, lad. It's
what these people do.
>> You remember Pat Mustard?
>> Yeah. He was a qu lad. [laughter]
>> What you called him a quick hunt, didn't
it? Yeah, he's a hate.
>> Who? Who do you hate the most on here? I
hate that fantasy stories and that
[ __ ] V, bro. But I love to get my hand.
>> I don't even know them to me. Um I don't
hate anyone. Me I come. Come on for a
laugh, mate. Like the problem is when
people on here it's took over the life.
But to me it's a [ __ ] laugh. Like
>> it's like when people get it's when
people it's when people get docks and
then they still But I got docks me. I
just [ __ ] off. I probably wouldn't come
back m you know. Yeah.
>> Yeah. He's not been seen, has he?
>> Yeah. But Brad is a coward, though,
because he actually would troll people,
bro, badly. And then when he gets
stocks, he ran away. You see what I'm
saying? That's different, bro. He's a coward.
>> Yeah. But you've been you've been
attacked off these people before and
they found where you live and they've
done all sorts to you and you still
won't get off. Like, I don't understand it. [laughter]
>> Yeah. You laughing about it?
>> Yeah. Same with Monty. It
>> Monty, man. Yeah. He's he he he's he won
they've done all
>> who's edited the worst Monty in it. And
Monty's head well I don't know you want
Monty I think no probably Monty anyway I
think Monty edges up but what they've
done to that Monty man is mad >> YouTube
they call him a nonsense the Manchester
groups on Facebook and everything and
he's still on there [laughter]
>> it's funny is it
>> I wouldn't say it's funny not it's
[ __ ] sad what they're doing but [laughter]
what these people want you but imagine
that though losing your kids over YouTube.
>> Yeah, but he still won't get off. I have
no sympathy for the Monty man.
>> Why? Because he's had chances and he
still he's had chances and he still
won't get off of it.
>> Yeah, they've bullied him on here for
years. They've written letters. They've
they messaged his mom. They've they've
said he's a non. They've done everything
possible they can do to Monty, man. He's still on.
>> It's mad, isn't it, Grezy?
>> It's absolutely crazy.
>> Yeah. They sent letters and they done it
to me as well. >> Yeah.
>> Mad at it. Mad.
>> You do realize this. These are grown men doing this. >> Yeah.
>> But I think you like Lord J.
>> Um I think J was all right actually. But
>> he's a [ __ ] Hey, do you remember when
he done that bindaloo challenge and he
could only afford the Iceland one cuz he's skin? [laughter]
>> Yeah. And he was
>> [ __ ] skin is it? He was sucking the
life out of that [ __ ] nice lolly.
>> Yeah, like he was sucking a dick in it.
>> That money m said drink milk. You fat
[ __ ] or something. [laughter] >> Yeah.
>> Right. I'm going to dive in the shower
anyway, bro. So, I'll pop back on if you're on.
>> All right. Catch you in a bit.
>> In a bit, lad.
>> Good old Triple H. He's a pretty good
[ __ ] isn't he?
What do you think of our triple our Jordy lad?
He's a pretty good [ __ ]
What you even said to him, lovely, in
it, that he had um
he had some nice uh
he had a tea and some digestive
biscuits. Greasy, you you were saying
lovely to him, is it? Yeah. You even say
to him as well. Lovely. You said that
yesterday, didn't you? Lovely.
Oh, we haven't spoke about women today,
have we, Grezy?
I wonder why that is. >> [cough] [snorts]
>> It's because I've had my vitamins, isn't it, Grezy?
Yeah, it's because you've had it.
It's because I've had my vitamins greasy.
Don't start going on about it. Why do
you hate it, Grezy? >> [snorts]
>> What did you say, Grey? It shouldn't
affect your Christmas. You said it
shouldn't affect your Christmas [ __ ] it grieves the
It shouldn't affect your It shouldn't
affect your Christmas budget. [laughter]
Yeah, it shouldn't affect my Christmas
budget, should it, Grezy? No,
90. Yeah, my other coat. I thought it
was Yeah, I just bought another coat. [ __ ] it.
Not that bad. 80 90 is it?
You wouldn't pay much more than 90 for a
coke, would you, Grezy?
You wouldn't pay much more for one, would you?
You better not be [ __ ]
Yeah, mine was 90. Not too bad.
You make me laugh greasy with a cat
waiting for a copycat statement.
You're how [ __ ] [ __ ] up you are.
Wait for a copycat. David Grecy, what
what even made you come out with that?
What would make you even come out with
something like that?
Just sounds like a copycat statement.
Sounds like a copycat statement.
know all about the copycats, don't you, Greasy?
This is the coat I got, Grezy.
It looks all right, doesn't it? With it,
it would look good with the jeans.
The jeans and the trainers.
Nice beige color.
I can't wait.
That's my kite, matey.
We'll do so.
Yeah, that's why you got to be careful.
So, you can take it to the dry cleaners.
I mean, it's actually beige, not white.
But, I mean, you could just take it to
the dry cleaners.
So, that happens. the dry cleaners will
be able to get rid of it
if that was to happen.
Right, Grezy? So,
and yeah, it was 90. So, I don't feel
like I need to be extra careful with it
cuz it wasn't that expensive.
But it looks the nicest in it, Grezy. Beige, white.
It does look the the nicest, doesn't it?
You have to admit.
Yeah, if the car if the car gets built
then the dry cleaners will get rid of it.
I can't believe I got called gay for not
finding Sher Co attractive. Greasy,
you said it. What was it again? Grievy,
a copycat statement.
What was it again? Gra a copycat statement.
Just sounds like a copycat statement.
You're [ __ ] mad, Greasy. You need to be sectioned.
Yeah, I got my vitamins today. I'm still
not hungry, Grezy. I'm still not hungry.
I'm more than happy with my little
vitamins that I got. Yep.
So now I don't need boobies to latch on
to, do I?
All right. I said, do you remember I
said to do remember I asked Trip Grey I
said can you live off £500 a month and
he said obviously not. [laughter]
Do you remember Greavvesy?
[snorts] What did he say? Obviously not there. [laughter] [clears throat] Yeah,
you're jealous of me. What makes you say that?
Why would you come to that conclusion?
This charge is [ __ ] annoying, bro.
But yeah, this coat's going to be coming
and it's going to be lush.
The coat is going to be absolutely lush.
We done good with the football bets, isn't it?
So, yeah. What did Triple 8 say? He
could live off £1,200 a month. Could I?
Not really. I haven't lived off that
money, bro. That's the much money I get.
But I've had obviously more money,
obviously. Is it? I don't know, bro.
It just depends what you're doing, is it?
What do you mean what I have? What do I
have? Apparently, I've got nothing.
Apparently I'm skinn
£1,200 a month. Yeah.
Well, you won't starve. Put that way.
I have loads. Do I What's that?
Yeah, man. Thank you, bro.
Yeah. Thanks, man. Yeah,
but bro, that's that's not what they're jealous of.
That's not what they're jealous of, bro.
You think they're jealous of people
having loads of friends, your own
property, and a fit girlfriend?
Bro, they're not jealous of that.
You I think you're going I think you're
going to the extreme, lad.
Younger and better looking. That's all
it takes. Well, no. There's three
things. Younger, better looking, and not
hopeless like them.
Yeah. You're younger than them. You're
better looking than them. And you're not
hopeless like them.
That's the end. So, yeah. Yeah.
Younger, better looking.
Younger, better looking. and not
hopeless like them. Yeah,
you've already seen me with friends. So
why are you trying to troll when we've
already seen me with friends?
So this self projection is not going to work, lad.
Because it's just self projection. It's boring now.
Like go back on Laur's channel and tell
everyone that you got no friends and stuff. [snorts]
Stop asking me questions, mate. It's
boring now. You know, go back on Lord JS
and go self project. You're boring.
Boring as [ __ ]
You just tell people that they ain't got
things what you ain't got. It's boring
now, mate. Come on. It's almost 2025.
Yep. It's almost 2025, by the way. And
you're still doing this?
It's boring now, bro. You need to come
up with some new stuff. Isn't it right, Grievy? Probably. Yeah.
I'm a time travel.
A time traveler. You're funny, bro.
Yeah, he is out gambling.
So, what's the solution? Grezy, lad. Bye-bye.
Trip 8 said that you can live off 1,200 a month.
You're trolling. You're [ __ ]
trolling. Triple H.
Do you know where I fancy going again?
I fancy going Manchester. You know, Grezy
aiming for ages. I touched some boobies
and stuff. You remember when I first
went to second time I went to
Manchester, I got a one night stand. We
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
I been there for ages.
I used to have Manchester all the time.
You remember Grezy?
I agree with you. Monty blocked some
people on his chat earlier because they
kept bringing up rice and stuff.
They kept bringing up [ __ ] rice
when the next escort.
[ __ ] knows, bro.
I can't be asked with them to be fair.
He blocked them because they kept
bringing up Rice and [ __ ] Timmy. They
said, "Stop bringing up these idiots. Yeah.
Do you remember when that I call that
Hugh talking [ __ ] about me, lad?
All right. This fantasy stories is going
to make me end up going to island grievy.
And it ain't going to be funny, bro.
I'll just go to [ __ ] island and
[ __ ] just do the [ __ ]
You know what I'm like, Grezy, mate. You
know what I'm like, mate. Don't greasy.
I end up [ __ ] going there, mate.
[ __ ] doing a [ __ ] tant in mate.
You know I'm [ __ ] like, mate.
Add it up to here with the [ __ ] Yeah,
[ __ ] Northern Irish bastard.
I'll go to the Guinness factory in
islands and [ __ ] do them alling. Yeah.
No. Hopefully I find someone here. Grievy.
No. Grievy. I'm hoping I'll find someone here.
What do you think?
Yeah. fantasy stories. You said sorry to
Pat Mustard and he ran you off of YouTube.
Stop it now.
Stop it. You're not going to do
anything, bro. You got bullied by a fat
old man and he made you say sorry
without even meeting you. Just just just
stop it now, bro. Just stop it. And and
and you know what, right?
This is how I know that the Irish are
cowards, right? Because anybody, mate,
would have cut off their [ __ ] left
bollocks to [ __ ] get Pat Mustard,
right? They would have cut off their
[ __ ] bollocks to to to meet Pat
Mustard. A lot of people on here was
after that [ __ ] for a very very very
long time. Yeah, this [ __ ] bastard
made every single excuse not to meet him
and said, "Sorry, bro. You're a joke.
You're you're a joke. You could even
meet a fat old man that has been
harassing people on the internet for
years. You know, it's it's you're not
about that life. You're not about that
life, bro. Sorry, Pat Mustard. You win
and then you ran off of YouTube for two years.
Stop it. It's embarrassing now, kid.
It's very, very, very, very, very, very
embarrassing. And you know I'm right.
That's why you can't join a hangout
without talking over people because you
know I'm right.
You [ __ ] fat ugly Northern Irish
little [ __ ] bully victim. You [ __ ]
Irish [ __ ] bully victim. Little
[ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. You little single little virgin little [ __ ]
There you go.
You need to stop calling yourself a bun,
mate. I'm a million times better looking
than you'll ever be. You need to stop
calling yourself a bun, mate. You really
need to stop bullying yourself. I mean,
Pat must have already done a good job of
a good job of it, lad. You don't need to
keep bullying yourself. You need to stop
calling yourself a b.
You really, really need to stop calling
yourself a m lad.
That mustard already done the bullying, bro.
He's already done the bullying. He's
already done the bullying, lad.
You know, it's [ __ ] I knew it was you as well.
When are you going to stop calling
yourself a m? It's embarrassing, mate. [ __ ] >> embarrass.
>> Stop calling yourself a m. Stop bullying
yourself. Pat mustard's already done a
good job at that, lad. Stop it now.
Stop it. You said sorry to Pat M and you
ran away for two years. It's
embarrassing. Stop it.
>> Hey, that's your name, though. What
should I call you?
>> Oh, really?
>> Well, do you know what? Put your camera
on and show your face.
>> But you're known as the mon.
>> Okay. Okay. Put your Put your Put your
camera on and show your face.
>> But mon, why are you offended? People
call you mon if that's what you're known as.
>> Put your camera on and show your face
and we'll see the M.
>> Yes, you.
>> You. You are the M. You are
>> You are the M.
>> You are the M. Yes. You're single.
>> You're a virgin. You've never been with a woman.
>> Is you
is the Irish woman that must you are
known as the bully victim.
>> Bro, you said sorry
cuz you're panicking.
>> Can't have a conversation. >> Pat
over you and say you're a bully victim
[ __ ] but I want a regular
conversation. So you ran away from You
can say that, but everyone know that you
ran from Pat Mustard. That's why you
talk over me. You talk over me. I'll stop.
>> You talk over me because you ran away
from Pat Mustard and you don't
>> Every time you talk over me, you I've
won. So you keep talking over me. You
said sorry to Pat and he made you run
away. So keep saying what you want to
say. I don't care, bro. You think a fat
ugly man could ever make me run off of
YouTube like he did you? Have some
[ __ ] pride coming back on here
showing your [ __ ] ugly M Iris face
after being bullied the way you did. You
want to talk about prime, bro? Guess
what? At least it was in real life. At
least it was somebody bigger than me and
younger, not some fat old man that made
you run off of YouTube. You know it's
the truth. You can laugh. You know it's
the truth. And you know the thing is
that your question how many people after
>> you have a question yourself a bun
you calling me a bun is not going to
change the fact that you're the actual
it's not going to change it's not going
to change the fact that you're the bun
so you can keep you can keep okay bully
I just told you what you done
>> but you haven't told I just told you
what you done
>> your friend from school joined Lord
Jay's and said you used to get bullied
that's a fact did Did he?
>> Yeah, he did. He got bullied on school.
>> So why? Okay. So why did
>> you online to try and find some friends
and you got bullied online as well?
>> So why did you run away from
>> then you met Prime and Prime bully?
>> He's not answering. He's not answering the question.
>> Why Why did Pat Mosed bully you off
YouTube? Why did he make you say sorry
without even being you?
>> Why did he make you shut that Iris mouth
and run away like you are? Again,
listen, bro. You want to answer my question again?
>> Stop calling yourself a bun. It's not
going to change the fact that you're the
bun and not me. You need to call you.
I've had more women than you've had hot
dinners. Is you is you bastard.
>> Women call you is the Northern Irish
bastard that run away from Pat Mustard.
It's this bastard. It's the Listen,
listen. The M is the Northern Irish
bastard that run away from you. [ __ ]
Pat Mustard. I'm not no m I didn't run
away from Pat Mustard. I'm not some
[ __ ] Northern Irish [ __ ] that
can't talk properly. Are you almost crying?
>> [ __ ] You're near crying, PJ. Relax.
>> You [ __ ] Northern Irish [ __ ] bully.
>> That's your family. He bullied you. He bullied YouTube.
>> That's your girlfriend. He bullied you.
>> I can't control you.
>> You want So you want to meet me? Is that
what you're saying?
>> Yes. Come to Northern Ireland. When I
take you seriously when a fat old man
bullied you. You see the problem bully victim.
>> I would see a problem bully victim. When
a fat old man made you say sorry without meeting
you beat me. Yeah, if you do, I swear if
you come to Berious,
let's be seriously
put your camera on and go live for more
than half an hour. It's as simple as that.
>> Okay. Okay. Where I
>> Anywhere in Banganger. Anywhere you want
>> Well, where? I don't even know where
that is. So, Belfast.
>> It's near Belfast. You're scing the
train. Save all your money.
>> I've got more money than you. I've got
more money than you will ever more than
you will ever listen.
I'll go anywhere in Northern Ireland. If
you give me stuck in your mom's basement
with anxiety, you're a keyboard warrior.
The fact that you
running away from Mustard, you run away
from Pat Mustard and you still No one
can take you serious. No one can take
you serious. No one can take you seriously.
>> Stop panicking. Are you going to come or not?
>> I'm trying to talk over.
>> I'm trying to talk over you, bro.
>> Can you afford a plane ticket? Yes or no?
>> I'm trying to get a word in.
>> Bro, listen. Can I afford a plane ticket,
>> bro? We're not skint like you. I'm not
skint like you. So, of course I can, you stupid idiot.
>> So, come this weekend. What's your excuse?
>> Okay. Come this weekend. And and you promise
>> anywhere in Northern Ireland. Anywhere.
>> So why didn't you meet Pat Mustard?
>> No, no. Don't back out.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no. Why did you meet
Pat Mustard? Why did Tell you Pat
>> But do you want an answer? >> Yeah.
>> I tried three times.
>> No, [laughter] you did not try three times.
>> But I did mother idiot. You
>> That's the reality mother. But I won't
need three times for you because unlike
Pat, you don't have [laughter] to hide
your stinking face because you already
know you're stinking.
>> So you go live,
you go live and you put the camera on
you. What's the excuse about that life?
You said you come from
people love these bro. You're not coming.
A lot of people
felt like mon
He was the most person on here and you
ran away from him and you ran away. You
ran away. Why you backing out? You just
[ __ ] weak. You have your kid. You're [ __ ]
chance to [ __ ] beat that harasser.
You being the Irish [ __ ] that you are ugly
from Northern Ireland.
Come here. I will smack your mother face.
You ran away from anytime you want. Come
over to take you serious and I'll be there.
>> We can't take you seriously.
>> You said the same thing to Pat Mustard
but you didn't meet him. You said the
same thing to him but you didn't meet
him. Not there.
>> Yeah, exactly. Bye-bye bully victim that
ran away from Pat Mustard. Bye-bye. See
how he talks over people cuz he knows
I'm right, mate. You think anyone could
take that guy serious, lad? He ran away
from Pat Mustard. Do you know how many
people was after that guy's ass? And he
had his chance to meet him and he ran
away. He ran away from Pat Mustard.
That tells you all about the Irish.
They're [ __ ] [ __ ] The Irish are
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
really really bad [ __ ] you know.
He ran off of YouTube, bro. The guy ran
off of YouTube. Yeah,
the guy ran off of YouTube
because of Pat Mustard.
Imagine that, bro. And he comes back on
here like nothing happened. We can't
take him serious.
His accent just annoys me, bro. He's
just one of them people that you could
just slap up, you know? He's just like
V. Just a little nicky geeky little
[ __ ] [ __ ] that would never say
anything to anyone's face, you know?
Just a nicky geeky Irish little [ __ ]
that ran away from Pat Mustard and he's
trying to act like he's a [ __ ] man,
bro. [ __ ] out of here, man. Yeah,
like I'm going to come to Ireland so you
can [ __ ] run away. If I have your
address, I'll come on your [ __ ] door,
mate. If I ever get your address, I'll
come on your [ __ ] door, you [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
Yeah, if I ever get your [ __ ]
address, I'll come. We You're not going
to meet anyone. Stop it. You're not
going to meet anyone. You [ __ ] pushy
Irish little manta. You're boring. Get
blocked. [ __ ] off. See you later, [snorts]
Yeah. Ran away from Pat Mustard.
Oh, that's [ __ ] mad.
That's mad, bro.
How much would you say we're up now? All right. [clears throat]
I don't know how much I'm up, lad.
maybe 400 and something. But don't
forget, I bought jeans and Uggs and
trainers and [ __ ] So, I don't actually know Yeah. Really?
How comes you can't bet on the Northern
League in William Hill?
Why is that? Right. Let me see the odds
for this week.
Have a little look. Virgin boy. Oh. Oh.
Oh. That Oh, that virgin boy. Oh, that
Oh, that boy. Oh, that version.
>> Yeah. Do you want to go for a pint or do
you want to do it bad
or do you want or do you want to do it dirty?
Steven Howard, why did Nons keep denying
keep denying the escort stories when I
would tell him about the escorts? Why
did he keep denying it
when I was telling the escort stories?
Why would he keep denying them Steven Howard?
Back to what I was saying before I was
rudely interrupted. Greavvesy about the
Thailand thing. Um, I'm hoping that I
can find someone here.
What do you think are the chances? Maybe
I could find someone here to be with. By
here, I mean in this country. Oh,
yeah. I'm thinking I can maybe find
someone here. Greasy, what do you what
do you reckon?
Maybe I can find someone interested in this country.
I was reading up why people don't watch
porn greasy and a lot of them say that
they don't watch porn because it's
degrading women. What do you think of
that? Like the porn degrades women?
What do you think? Ant-Man
said, "You watch porn from the 70s? That's weird."
He said, "It's weird that I watch porn
from the 70s."
He said, "That is strange."
He said, "It's strange." He said, "I've
never known someone watch from the 70s.
out of all the people he knows that
watch porns that watch porn. So here, he
said that he's never met someone that's
watched it from the 70s.
Where is he? Yeah. 70s,
man. I ain't a [ __ ] skin virgin, am I?
Some [ __ ] skin virgin from [ __ ]
out of London. What do you think about
that, Grezy? Some skint from [ __ ] out of London.
Love it, lad. Love it.
Yeah, he was probably scared of a will
to be honest
because he didn't want to be a virgin by
himself. He wanted you to be a virgin with him
cuz he's a [ __ ] virgin.
Yeah, it's probably because where he's a virgin.
He wanted he didn't want to be the only virgin.
Well, he is the only virgin who will
die. [ __ ] virgin. [ __ ] die one.
He needs to stop going on about that 13
grand as well. That 13 grand is his
daddy savings that he can't show now.
You need to stop going about that 13 grand.
Look at this self-p projection. Look at
this self projection. Poo ho. Look at this.
Self project him. His only comeback now
is calling you a copycat. Ever since you
destroyed him at the money game. He
never destroyed me at the money game. I
destroyed him at the money game. Um, and
he showed an old video from years ago,
which he can't show the money now. He's
never destroyed me at the money game
ever. That was daddy's life savings. He
never recovered from that. He stayed up
all night. These people are such nerds.
He stayed up all night anxious and went
to the betting shop at 7 halfway in the
week so nobody could cash in the
pittance because he's completely again
self-p projection. Um, his existence is
living off CLA. Never used CL in my
[ __ ] life. I've never ever paid off
for clothes in my life. Ever. Never
have, never will. Um, gambling. I don't
gamble that much. Again, self-p projection. Refunds.
Not had a real refund in well over a
year. Self-p projection. Free food for
the mosque. Again, self-p projection. I
won't be going to Thailand in December
5th either. Skin. Self projection. I'm
sure these people just look in the
mirror, right? I I'm sure these people
just look in the mirror and get
themselves confused with you, Germany.
Clana, what the [ __ ] Kana?
Well, I've never used Cler in my [ __ ] life.
I've never used Clana in my whole
[ __ ] life. Never have, never would.
We're not all skint. I know it's hard to believe, right?
you little nerds.
But they're proper nerds on here as well. Absolute [ __ ] nerds.
[ __ ] they're absolute fat, ugly,
nobody nerds that never made it in life.
I'm telling you, Steven, that's what they are.
Self-p projection little attention seekers.
That's what they are, bro. Fat, ugly
people. They get bullied every day.
[ __ ] Colana. What the [ __ ]
I've actually got receipts for all my things. Um,
one second. One second. Listen to Hold
on. I've actually got receipts for all
my things cuz I bought all of my stuff
online, but I'm not showing you
anything. And the reason for that is
because how many times did I say to
these people Steven Howard to put their
camera on and show their face and prove
they're not fat ugly bongos and they
haven't. So I've asked you to show me
something. I've not proved myself to you
little fat ugly nerds.
It's called Kana.
I don't do Kana. Yeah. I'mma prove
myself to you fat ugly nerds. Little low
lives. I've asked you plenty of times to
put your camera on and it will prove why
you fat ugly people do what you do every day and
you didn't want to do that. So,
you know, shut the [ __ ] up.
Why would anybody need to get anything
from Kana? We're not all [ __ ] skin
like you little mongos. You middleage
little fat ugly people.
Yeah, I'm going to do a video on this.
I'm going to do a video on this, bro.
Yeah, [ __ ] this. I love this [ __ ]
Greavves. You know what I'm like in it.
I've never used Colada in my life.
Never used that in my whole life.
They've got to be self projecting again.
What is it with these skint people on
here keep self projecting? Even when
even when you show these [ __ ] people money
like you didn't beat anyone at the money
game, [ __ ] That money. Yeah. That
money that you showed was a 100 years
ago, [ __ ] Yeah. You can't show the
money now. Yeah. And you won't show the
money now because you can't. Simple.
Yeah. Every single time you got shown
thousands, mate. Yeah. You ran away. You
[ __ ] ran away. Shut the [ __ ] up.
Nobody destroyed me at the money game.
You [ __ ] fat ugly nerd. And before I
start [ __ ] asking people to start
showing [ __ ] receipts, you [ __ ]
little lowife nerd. Yeah. Show your ugly
faces and prove that you're not ugly.
But you can't do it cuz you're fat ugly
people that ain't got a life. Simple.
Fat ugly mongos that ain't got [ __ ]
nothing in your [ __ ] life.
I'm not [ __ ] showing you receipts,
you some [ __ ] my life. I was not put
on earth to show a bunch of fat, ugly,
middle-aged, ugly losers receipts of
what I bought. Get that in your [ __ ]
head, you [ __ ] bongos.
You show that you're not an ugly fat
[ __ ] right? And then I'll show you
receipts. Simple. I've got all my
receipts on my emails. Simple.
That [ __ ] did not [ __ ] destroy me at
the money game,
you know? And you're calling pe you're
calling people skint because you're
skint yourself. I don't know how many
times you need to keep looking in the
mirror to realize that you're the skint
one and you need to stop typing out
about yourself. Yeah,
but I'm younger than you. I'm better
looking than you and you're trying to
talk about someone that's a [ __ ] Do
you know what I'm trying to say? Madness.
These people, they've got to be on the
bones of their ass ass to come on here
every day, Greavesy. Right. Calling
people's skin. They've got to be on the
bones of their ass. They've got to be
living their worst life.
Like [ __ ] disabled little [ __ ]
mongos that ain't got a life. Bro, it's
almost 2025 and these fat ugly people,
these little nerds are still on here
repeating themselves. It's almost 2025.
It's December next month.
It's December next month. Yeah.
It's December next month, Grezy. Yeah.
What's after December? January.
You did definitely definitely did not
destroy me at the money game.
You 100% did not beat me at the money
game, mate. You showed an old video of
daddy savings, which was not even
counted out about 100 years ago. And
then when you got asked to show it again
and you got shown 50s, you run away. You
did not beat anyone at the money game.
You did not beat anyone at the money
game, you fat ugly little nerd. So you
might want to right actually give your
[ __ ] head a [ __ ] wobble and sort
your [ __ ] brain out.
It's almost 2025.
Look at this little A s. E a s.
He's just said he he had a loud shouting
match with a woman on a train this
morning which reminded me of a story you
told of him arguing a woman at a train
station. This the same repeating fat
ugly people in it. Years later we still
doing the same thing while this woman
was on a train going to work and was on
his way back home. Listen, [ __ ] The
woman's never going to sleep with you.
Yeah. So, all of this you trying to
defend a woman, she's never going to
sleep with you. Ugly fat nerd. She's
never going to sleep with you, bro. I
swear to God, whenever I get my if when
one of these people's addresses get out
there, bro, I'm going for him, bro. 100
fucking%. When one of these people's
addresses come out there, I I'm breaking
in their [ __ ] house.
I'm breaking in one of these fat, ugly
little nerds house and I'm exposing
them, bro. 100%. Yeah, 100%.
When any of these fat, ugly little
stinky little skint nerds that can't get
off of YouTube get exposed, bro, I'm
going on their [ __ ] door, bro. Hold
me to it. Hold me to it.
Yeah. Calling someone lowife [ __ ]
scum. Mate, you're not going to do
anything to a low life scum. So, at the
end of the day, stop being a little old
nerd that can't get off a YouTube cuz
you're too much of a [ __ ] that you
got the brain power to get a life. And
stop writing behind the keyboard. Yeah.
[ __ ] little Mongs.
These little mongos. They're [ __ ] You
know, would you believe Grievy that
we're the youngest on here? You know
that? You know, we're the youngest on
here, lad. We're actually the We're the
youngest on here. You know that?
All these people in their 40s,
would you believe it, in their 40s doing this? [ __ ] [ __ ]
Why would Why the [ __ ] would someone use
[ __ ] Colana, bro? That's a wild
statement. What? Because we're not
on£300 a month like you?
What? Because we're not on £300 a month
like you? some little skint nerd that
can't get off of YouTube.
Why would anyone use Kano or Clear Pay?
Because what? Because are we supposed to
be skint like you?
No. No. See, what it is with the these
little fat ugly people is they try
bringing people down, but they don't
look in the mirror and see that they're
talking about themselves. They're fat,
ugly, spasticated, nerdy selves that
ain't got a life.
And that's what triggers a [ __ ]
reaction when I say this [ __ ] because
it's the truth. Fat, ugly little
hopeless nerds. That's the word. You you
say to these people, Grezy, they're
hopeless and they go mad because they
know they're fat, ugly, hopeless
little nobodyies that have got [ __ ] all but YouTube. But YouTube
hating on people that they don't even
know. And think about it. These people
are in their [ __ ] These people are in
their [ __ ] 30s, bro. No, they're not
in their 30s. They're in their 40s, lad.
And it's And they're doing this in their
40s every day. Imagine. Think about it, bro. You know
that completely skin,
mate. The these people on here are
[ __ ] skint. That's why they sit on
here [ __ ] every day doing this [ __ ]
because they are absolutely skinn right.
We will see. I'll show you Grezy. Right.
From next month I'll be going out. So
from next week is the next month I'll be
going out every week and I guarantee you
you'll be seeing these same skinned
people on YouTube that ain't got no
life, ain't got nothing. 100 [ __ ]
million%. I can tell you you'll see the
same people, right? Because these people
are the skint ones. These people have
got nothing in their nobody life.
Because we all know that if these nobody
lives had something, they wouldn't be on
here. It's simple as that. Simple
as [ __ ] that. So, at the end of the
day, lad, you show your ugly [ __ ]
face and I will show you receipts. I've
got them all on my email. We're not skin
like you fat, ugly, wrinkly, little
lowife old, pathetic men, right?
Pathetic old men that ain't got a life
but being a [ __ ] every day on the
internet. Yeah, remember that.
You know, if I ever get one of these
people's addresses, bro, I'm telling
you, I'm going on their [ __ ] door, lad.
Now, he blocked me on Facebook, bro. He
blocked me on Facebook.
Do you remember when I always used to like
say about, "Oh, yeah, addresses and stuff,
not addresses, something else." And I
say, "Can you show your face? Can you
put your camera on?" You can't do it,
bro. So stop asking other people to
prove stuff to you fat ugly self [ __ ]
projecting little mongos if you're not
going to show your face
you know watch bro whenever I get yeah
whenever I get my hands on one of these
people like their address I'm I'm going
to keep quiet Huh? Simple
[ __ ] mongos, lad.
And stop going on about nowhere near
[ __ ] 13 [ __ ] grand, bro. You
showed 13 grand [ __ ] years ago. Your
daddy savings. Stop trying to [ __ ]
flex it. Right.
Let's play the money game now, you
little [ __ ] How about that one, Grezy?
little [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, let's play the money game now. And
then do you know what what what it's
going to be now as well? Who can show
the most for longest? And it's going to
go in longest now, Grezy as well. Yeah,
you showed your daddy's savings 100
years ago, mate. And you can't even show
1% of that now. Stop trying to rinse it,
mate. It's boring now. Yeah, very very
very very boring.
These people go on about people being skint
cuz they're [ __ ] skint themselves.
How the [ __ ] do these people seem to
know how much people have and what they
don't have? It seems that they live off
their own lives. Yeah.
>> Self-projecting fat [ __ ] Tell this
guy to put his camera on. Yeah.
Tell him to put his Tell these little
fat ugly little mongos to put their
cameras on, bro.
I'm going I'm doing a video to this
little [ __ ] One second, bro. [ __ ] this.
Not that people need to prove themselves
to you fat ugly bongos, but anyways.
One second, Timmy, bro. I'm going to
[ __ ] own this [ __ ] One second.
This charge is a big dodge.
[ __ ] little [ __ ] Little self-reflector.
Talk about self-reflected. E. Yeah,
this is this is fun content for me,
Grezy. You know why I'm like that?
This charger is [ __ ] bro.
talking about pittance. Bro, you ain't
even got £100. You [ __ ] little skint
[ __ ] [ __ ] You ain't even [ __ ]
got £100. You ain't even got £100 to
your [ __ ] name, lad.
Watch. I'm going to go on this channel,
bro, and I'm going to and I'm going to
reply to it as well.
You [ __ ] little [ __ ] If you want
to play the money game again, we'll do
it if you want. If you really want to
get embarrassed again, just like last
time I made you run off, I'll do we'll
do it again. You stupid little [ __ ]
We ain't all got the same life as you, bro. Yeah.
I said you're a copycat because of the
Cheryl Cole thing. Yes, you're copying.
You didn't want to feel left out. It's
ridiculous. It's being a copycat.
Somebody can't be gay for not finding
one person attractive.
That's a copycat.
That's what copycats do. Yes, it's a
copycat statement, isn't it, Grezy?
Because it's a copycat statement, is it not Grezy?
It's a [ __ ] copycat statement.
What's funny, Grezy? Yeah, because it's
copying. Not wanting to feel left out,
you know. It is copying. That is
copying. Saying that if you don't find
one person attractive,
you're gay. That is copying. It's not
wanting to feel left out.
You know, you know it and I know it.
There's nothing funny about it.
And you did destroy me at no money game,
mate. [ __ ] out all. So [ __ ] off, you
stupid little [ __ ]
You [ __ ] stupid fat ugly nerd. Ain't
got a life to stand on thinking that we
need to prove ourselves to you fat ugly
people. Fat ugly low lives that can't
get off the internet. [ __ ] off, mate.
I said on multiple Red Star videos,
"Show your face. Show your face." And
you can't do it cuz you're fat and ugly.
Don't start [ __ ] thinking that we're
going to start proving ourselves to you little nobodyies.
Little you little nobodyies. Firstly,
they said I had I had [ __ ] credit. Now
they're telling me that I used Kana.
Make up your [ __ ] mind.
Bro, do you know why I'm responding to
it? Because it's so funny. It's actually
entertainment. Entertaining how stupid
these people could actually be.
How stupid do the do these people like
how they actually are, bro.
How [ __ ] [ __ ] these people are.
These people are insanely insanely skint.
Every time they get shown money, they
run away. I mean, bro, it's almost 2025
now. You need to stop talking about
yourself like that, you know.
Don't make me embarrass you again at the
money game, mate. Please do not make me
embarrass you again.
never recovered from that, bro. You did
not win at the money game. You showed an
old video years ago of your daddy's
savings. Of your daddy's savings. That's
what you did. You didn't beat anyone at
the money game. You can't show no money now.
You're going to love this video, aren't you, Greasy?
You're going to [ __ ] love this video, aren't you?
I think that just goes to show you how
skint these people actually are, bro. If
they think that people need to use
colana to buy jeans and trainers,
I think it goes to show how skint you
really really really are basing your
your life of of other people.
[ __ ] sat on YouTube. [ __ ] ain't
got a life. Yeah,
it's like, do you remember when Monty
man said it greasy? There's a lot of self-reflectors
in this community. A lot of self-reflectors.
What about that? Um Yeah.
A lot of self-reflectives of this community, bro.
Isn't that right, Gre? A lot of self-reflectors.
Would you say there's a lot of
self-reflectors in this community?
Yeah, I bought another coat, bro. I
bought a beige six silk one. It cost me 90 quid. Yeah,
I ordered a new coat, lad. Yeah.
Yeah. You want to live? Yeah.
Never forget me.
Hey, Grezy. Reddit keeps banning me,
bro. It's definitely a power thing,
isn't it? With these mods, Grezy.
Agree. It's definitely a power thing
with these mods, lad, isn't it? It's definitely
All right, Gregy. It's definitely
definitely a It's definitely definitely
a power thing, isn't it? With these mods.
When you show your fat, ugly asses, then
start asking people to start proving
stuff. Your [ __ ] little [ __ ]
Sad little mongos ain't got a life. Yeah. Madness.
Nah, the mods are definitely power hungry.
I call them power hungry. Greavves in me.
Yeah, I call them power hungry.
[ __ ] knows, lad. [ __ ] knows.
Do you remember Franklin Grezy? Franklin Greavesy Franklin.
You said Autumn was my mama. Is it Greavvesy? Nah,
you said she could be my mama for the
winter in it. Nah,
I said you're a [ __ ] copycat cuz you
kept going about Chev car and people being gay
because you wanted to fit in with the
crowd. Nothing to do with you showing
your daddy savings 100 years ago.
Nothing to do with you showing your
daddy savings 100 years ago. It was you
copying the shovel co trend
cuz you didn't want to feel left out.
I don't know why that makes you laugh so
much when I say that.
It's true though. You didn't want to
feel left out. We [snorts]
Yeah, I need to cancel that. I'm going
to cancel it. One second.
One second. Don't want to cancel it, lad.
It doesn't let me cancel it, bro.
You private debits.
Yes. But it's not I have How do I cancel
it? It's not letting me do it via the bank.
Well, on the Xbox. Yeah.
bill as well. It's £32 a month.
I don't know why I'm paying it. I don't
even use it. I just use Wi-Fi. I don't
even use minutes and stuff.
But maybe I'll get a contract in the
future, so I'll keep on paying it.
I use it on Wi-Fi, don't I? So, I'll
keep on paying that one. Yeah. How do
you do it on a How do you do it on a console?
Oh, I guess you do it on the Play Store.
Uh the store, don't you?
You don't find Co attractive, you're gay. Copy.
You little copycat.
The control is [ __ ] bro.
I keep the Oh, here we go.
You little copycat.
You little copycat. She's hot. She's attractive. Little copycat.
Little copycat. [snorts]
Yeah, I'm on the settings
account. Okay. Payment and billing.
Okay, here we go.
Yeah, it doesn't let me
complete it. 22.99.
You in store? Maybe you have to go to
the store and cancel it.
Oh, there you go. Manage, right?
Okay, here we go. Cancel subscription.
So, I still have a month of it, don't I?
So, I still have a month for Franklin
and then I have to buy it. And it's not £15 either.
It's Yeah, it's not £15 either because
I'm using a discless Xbox.
I should have
Yeah, I should have a month left of
Franklin. Is that cute? Usually a month
for Franklin, then I'll just buy it on
the store in it.
Oh, that virgin boy is mad.
I didn't say he's a copycat for showing
his daddy's savings 100 years ago.
Yes, Scriezy, but I'm on a discless
Xbox, so I can only use the Xbox store.
I can't use discs. It's only digital.
You silly goose.
You don't find channel, you're gay.
Which makes someone a copycat. I've had it confirmed.
So, how much would a disc be, do you reckon?
Let me have a little look.
Grezy, are you sure it's a copycat statement?
If someone says if uh you don't find
Chev attractive, you're gay?
You sure it's a You sure it's a uh copycat statement
before I do this video?
Are you sure it's a copycat statement?
Cuz I don't want to feel like a tit when
I'm doing this video, lad. [sighs]
You sure it's a copycat statement? Yeah. Okay. Sir,
Yeah. Yeah. Non Sleg said to me, "If I
don't like Chev car, I'm gay." Oh, it's
£17. Grand Theft Auto uh premium edition is £17.
Yeah. Okay. Sorry. Yeah, it's a cop.
Yeah, that's what I was saying. I was
saying the same point. Yeah, it's a
copycat. It's a copycat statement.
Of course. Yeah, that's what I was
basically saying. I was saying the same thing.
Yeah. So, it's a copycat statement.
Yeah. It's a copycat statement.
Anything to fit in with the crowd, isn't
it, Grezy? Anything to fit in with the
crowd. But I said the same thing about
the boobs and stuff. Yeah.
I said the same thing about the boobs
though. I said exactly the same thing
with like big boobs or even black women,
but nope. Gay. Gay. Yeah, copycat. No
mind of his own.
Yeah, I said the same [ __ ] thing. I
said somebody could literally like
African women or [ __ ] blonde women or
[ __ ] brunette [ __ ] women with big
boobs. But he said straight away gay
just because her name is Cheryl Cole
because you're being a copycat.
No mind of your own.
It's the name. It's not the person,
Greasy. It's the name. Would you agree?
It's the name. You got no [ __ ] mind
of your own, mate. No mind of your own.
You little copycat. You little copycat. Little copycat.
I'm not greedy. I'm just a little copycat.
I'm not Do you remember Grezy? You said
that I'm not Grezy. I'm just a little copycat. Oh,
I'm not Grey. I'm just a little copycat,
bro. I bought this Xbox years ago, lad.
I bought this Xbox years ago.
Years ago, lad.
Douglas, is that is that you, Kieran?
Is that you, Kieran?
Please tell me. Yeah.
Is that you, little KK? That's you.
Yeah. I hate copycats.
I hate cats. I [ __ ] hate cats. No, no, no.
I want to get an Xbox 360 and play
Smackdown versus RAW 2009. Grezy, I'd
love to show you all the glitches.
I'd love to show you all the glitches, lad.
I won't be able to stream it. That's the thing.
I love to show you the Smackdown glitches.
I do a little tutorial for you.
You little copycat.
No, Sh is attractive. Attractive copycat. People
that say sh is a copycat. [laughter]
A copycat statement.
I said the same [ __ ] thing. Reevesy,
you're copying me now. I said the same
thing about the blonde eyes with the big
boobs. But nope. Gay. Gay. Copycat.
That's what you need to do. Oh, hey
Grezy. Anyone who says that yeah in
school as soon as they walk in the
classroom you have everyone has to step
this up right and point and be like copycat.
They all need to like point
and say copycat.
No, he was being serious. No, he was
being serious, lad. He said it when I
met him as well. He said, "No, you're
gay. If you don't find Sher Co
attractive, you gay." Nope. He said you're homo.
Nope. He was He was being serious, lad.
I said, "You're just a You're just
copying." That's what I said to him.
You're just copy You're just a copycat.
No, it wasn't a joke, lad. It was He was being serious.
It's back when I used to meet the [ __ ] virgin,
you know? He was being serious. He said,
"If I don't find her attractive, I'm gay."
I said, "What the fuck?"
Copying copying the crowd.
If I don't find someone attractive
that's got no ass and no tits,
apparently I like dick.
No ass, no tits, no nothing. Yeah,
you're a copycat.
What's the cat waiting for, Grezy?
What's the cat waiting for?
All right, you need to give me time to
make another copycat statement.
You know that [ __ ] skin mode you might
I'll play the money game again and beat
these [ __ ] again if you if you want me
to. But there's no point because they just
they're just they're just going to run away again.
Who? Virgin boy. Yeah, cuz he's nothing
but a little copycat.
Because Grevy, as I always say,
you can't afford to be picky at my age.
I'm looking for somebody with the name
of Lindsay Williams. Age range, uh, you
know, anywhere between 38 and 39.
Because, as they say, at my age, you
can't afford to be picky.
Yeah, you copycat
these people. I'm leaving this community
next year, lad.
I'm leaving this community next year. Fresh start.
Same repeating [ __ ] people.
Yeah, but it's the same repeating
people. G we
how many times do we hear that word on
his skin? It's [ __ ] boring. It's not
even triggering, lad. It's just boring,
is it? You know when you watch like the
same film over and over again? It's
boring. It's not even triggering. It's
boring, lad. Same fat self-projecting
[ __ ] ugly people, bro.
Yes, I will.
Yeah. Waiting for a copycat statement to
be made. Bro, why is there so many nerds
on this community?
You know, a lot of these people on here
rates are on nerds.
Have you seen their comments? They're
just little nerds. Little virgins.
I didn't know you could get colad on bad
credit. You need to make up your mind.
I don't need anything, Uncle Anna, mate.
I'm not skint like you.
Yeah, we're not skin like these people,
are we, lad?
I'm a little copy.
That is [ __ ] mad. Greavves is a mad
You little copycat.
Is Virgin boy a copycat, [clears throat] Douglas?
Oh, have you ever watched Triple H? You
watch the Sideman, don't you? Have you
watched the Sideman story on Netflix,
Greasy? There's a thing called the Sideman story.
You ever watch the Sideman story?
Do you know who they are? The side men
Do you remember Monty? Greasy.
Greasy. Monty. Monty.
Monty. Monty was like, "There's a lot of
self-reflectors in this community."
B. That was funny, isn't it? There's a
lot of self-reflectors in this community.
Remember when I went to Birmingham and
had a night out with Monty? That was
funny, isn't it?
No, there's a lot of self projectors in this community.
There's a lot of it. Yeah.
No, I didn't hear about that.
I reckon. Do you reckon the coat is
going to look nice when it comes?
Greedy. The nice coat.
Do you think it's going to look nice? Yeah.
Yep. You know Douglas, don't you? Mick
Jonathan Robinson. He thought by [ __ ]
off to [ __ ] Australia they wouldn't
find him, but they [ __ ] did. They Yep.
So why would did did did did he say that
I was gay if I don't find she car attractive Douglas
I don't find that [ __ ] attractive no
ass no tits no nothing nothing
I find other people attractive but
apparently I was still gay
I was still considered gay Yeah.
Yeah. That was his stepdad.
Philip Campbell from Leed. Yeah. That
was his stepdad.
The one that had him up against the
[ __ ] wall and strangled him.
Yeah. He was from Leeds
was his stepdad.
Yeah, you remember these things, don't you, lad?
Philip Campbell of Lead. Yeah, he's from Leeds.
He's even got Facebook. I showed you his
Who's my mama, Douglas?
See the account's back, Grezy. The
account's back. This is what I was
telling you about. [laughter]
They're coming for a laugh, ain't it?
Uh, is Virgin Boy stepdad?
Yeah. You know Virgin Boy when he had a
stepdad? The one that had him up against the wall
and gave him a punch in his [ __ ] face.
Yeah. Do you remember? Yeah, bro. Mad. Oh gosh.
Grezy, can anyone say it as as like the
way I say it?
It's Friday tomorrow. Yay. Friday. Yay.
I haven't played Frankie for a long
time. You know,
anyone fancy a Frankie fishing frenzy session?
Nope. Not tomorrow. I'm not doing
anything tomorrow, bro.
I'm not doing anything till next week. Uh yeah.
Anyone want to see a fishing frenzy session?
No, I'm not doing anything this week. Wireless. Yeah.
Get version boy.
How much do you get a month again? Steven Howard
from the benefits.
I'm only joking, bro. I'm not going to
actually play it.
No, I'll be working soon, lad. I'll be working soon.
I'll be working soon, mate.
I'm self-employed. I can work when I
want. I'm self-employed.
I can work when I want. Uh, triple. Yeah.
Starting to feel a bit hungry then now.
Nah, not quite. That Indian really does
feel you, don't it, Griezy? It really
does feel you that Indian, huh? For like
the whole day.
Why do you think that is, Grezy? I think
it's because of the um
the heat in the food. Maybe that's why
it fills you up for longer. Cuz if you
was just to order it, it wouldn't fill
you up for that long. Maybe cuz it was
fresh and warm. Maybe
where was like hot like really hot maybe. Maybe
that's must be what it is. Greavves know
cuz if you just ordered it, it wouldn't
be I can't believe that cost me 50 quid.
£49 for that food. Mad. >> Yeah.
Do you remember in Virgin boy used to
say a grand a month decent? A grand a
month decent m. Yeah. Yeah. Grand grand
a month's decent. Grand a month's decent
grand decent m grand's decent version [ __ ]
He used to say grand month's good money.
Nice amount of money. Nice amount of
That's what he used to say. Conver.
I'm talking about that virgin [ __ ]
Oh, but you don't mind watching his
channel when he keeps going on about me. Same stories.
Oh, you don't mind that though, do you?
You don't mind going on his channel
going on about the same stories.
Bit bit weird, isn't it?
You said that you watched the same
episode before, right?
But you've said that you've gone on his channel.
You know about the same stories about me.
You're not an onlover, are you? Triple
H. You're not another Joseph Ferrar, are you lad?
Please don't tell me you're another Joseph Ferrar.
bloody Joseph Ferrar.
cuz that ain't good. Yeah.
[ __ ] copied my holiday. Copycat.
Should have been [ __ ] born a cat.
Cuz all you do is copy.
Yeah, because I don't like copycats.
Triple H. That's why I went I keep going
on about it is because I can't stand
people that copy and have no mind of
their own. You know,
you know, Triple
Yeah, because I don't like copycats.
I don't like people that copy. Triple H. Little copycat.
You little copycat.
[ __ ] can't even [ __ ] go on holiday
without some [ __ ] copying me, Douglas.
I can't even [ __ ] go on holiday
without some [ __ ] ugly rat looking
virgin [ __ ] copying me.
I have to keep everything private now. You know,
no, he's not talking about me, bro. He's
talking about nonslegs.
Douglas is not talking about me. He's
talking about non legs triple. He ain't
talking about me.
Yeah, they're trying to Yeah, it's repeating.
Yeah, it is repeating. It's the same [ __ ]
I don't even remember that [ __ ] It's so made up.
What? The Chinatown thing. Yeah. Yeah.
He's been saying the same [ __ ] for about
10 years, bro. 10 years. Yeah. 10 years.
He needs to [ __ ] get off this
YouTube, get himself laid, [ __ ] not
be a virgin anymore, and [ __ ] [ __ ] off, [ __ ] Obsessed virgin.
Oh yeah, where apparently I [ __ ] myself.
Yeah, made up stories. Completely made up.
Don't even sound believable, mate. Yeah,
apparently I put my finger in the in my
ass. Yeah, completely made up.
He can't even say it without laughing
because it's made up.
He makes up stuff. Apparently, my dad
apparently my dad
got hit uh my hit me and my sister.
It's just made up.
Just made up stories.
Completely made up.
Yeah, I used to love Air Jordan shorts.
I still do to be fair, but they don't
make them as good as they used to.
Uh, I almost shot myself. Yeah,
but I didn't [ __ ] myself when I was with
that Virgin. Yeah, I used to love Air
Jordan shorts, lad.
Yeah, they they used to be £45 and they
used to last years, bro. Eden short. Yeah.
Yeah. It never happened. It never ever
ever happened. It's made up stories.
You would never tell someone that. If
that happens, you would never tell
anyone that. It's just made up
cuz he's a s.
Yeah. He's a s. That's why. Yeah. He
used to make up stories about women
beating me up.
Made up stories.
Yeah. Made up stories.
Made up boring stories that you can't
keep a straight face. Yeah. Yeah. Cuz I
I let some woman slap slap me. Yeah,
bro. It would never happen.
Yeah, another madeup story. You would
never tell someone this.
You would never ever tell someone this.
Also, Monty Man made up a story.
Apparently, I asked him for a [ __ ]
Another madeup story. What is it with
these people making up stories?
Why is it with these people making up stories, Douglas?
completely made up. It's funny in a way.
I always used to tell him um that you
should be an author with these stories
that you make up,
these madeup stories. You'd be a good author,
you know, like you know, uh Stephen
King. He'd be a good author, you know,
with all these stories that he makes up. [ __ ] virgin.
No, I didn't see it.
Yeah, he's he's he's he's made up,
man. I can't wait until his dad dies.
I'm going to throw a party. The most
expensive bottle of champagne. I'll be
like, worm food. You never see that [ __ ]
again after all the [ __ ] you said about
my dad. Watch what these when these dads
said. I'm going to be like f never
seeing him again. And I'm going to show
my face and I'm going to be a nasty
little [ __ ] And we're going to be like,
you're never seeing him again. Never.
He's [ __ ] worm food. He's with Jimmy
if he's with Jimmy Savile and you'll do
nothing. Maybe that might prompt the
virgin to meet me so I can [ __ ] slap
his ugly head in.
Yeah, he used to um he he used to meet
this guy called Christian.
Christian and they stopped meeting and
he showed me a picture of him and
Christian saying, "We think that you're
gay." I said, "You two look like absolute virgins."
No one can [ __ ] say it better than
me, can they, Douglas? Two absolute virgins.
[ __ ] 1990s little gay boys that need
to [ __ ] get their dick sucked. Bunch
of [ __ ] packer virgins.
He He used to He used to dress the same lad.
Nah, it was someone else.
Y talking about Jack the Ripper. He was
a [ __ ] freak, bro. Yeah.
You know, he was crying before. Yeah. He
met someone on Tinder. He was speaking
to someone on Tinder when I [ __ ] up
for him. He started crying, you know.
He started crying. [ __ ] virgin.
Should have known then he was a [ __ ] virgin.
Yeah, he's a virgin. Proper virgin, lad.
I don't want him. [ __ ] virgin.
[ __ ] virgin. Virgin virgin virgin
virgin virgin virgin virgin virgin virgin.
[snorts] Yeah, because he's an absolute virgin.
Yeah, he he said that he tried to kill himself.
He said he tried to kill himself over
some [ __ ] girl that [ __ ] never wanted him.
Do you remember?
Stop going on about some girl that don't
want you. I'm not.
Stop going about some that don't want you. I'm not.
I'm not. Bro, that was mad.
Yeah, it's a madeup story, Triple H.
It's made up.
Completely. Completely made up.
Because if that actually happened, you
wouldn't have kept beating someone.
If that actually happened, you wouldn't
have kept meeting someone if they had
[ __ ] on their hands, would would you?
Would you? It's made up. The stories are
The stories are [ __ ] completely made up.
You know, he started telling me about
his dad towards the end.
Yeah. He told me about his dad. He's got
a very, very dark past.
Mick Jonathan Robinson.
Horrible, horrible bastard.
Born uh 1st of September.
My mom's the 2nd of September and his
dad's the first in September. So I remembered it.
It was a horrible horrible pedo.
Horrible pedo. His dad was his.
He he met He was 32 when he met his mom
and his mom was 17. Dirty pedophile.
Dirty dirty pedophile.
Dirty dirty nons. Yep.
Mick Jonathan Robinson. Horrible [ __ ]
Even even changed his name as well.
Yeah, he changed his name.
He went prison. Yo, he got done for it.
He's even said that his dad's been prison. Yeah.
Yeah. I lost everything. Job lost a lot
just from being a nons. He He's dad was
a brick layer.
Yeah. His dad was a brick layer. [snorts]
Nothing. I just don't like Dr. Pepper. Yeah,
he's a copycat.
That's all he is a [ __ ] copycat. Copycat statement.
Yeah, that's a copycat statement.
I know. I've I always told him, bro. I
always told him, "You should be an or
only one packet of crisp left." What the [ __ ]
there only one bloody packet of crisp left.
I tell you what's really nice here. Crackers.
Cream crackers with cheese. Oh, lovely. Look,
I want to make some cream crackers. Is
that okay with you, boss?
Is that okay with you, boss?
Yeah, but I was laughing at I was like
this absolute virgin has got no chance
cuz it was I was laughing out of embarrassment, bro.
I was laughing. I was so embarrassed.
I was like, I look at this absolute
virgin. I was thinking to myself,
yeah, virgin [ __ ] up by Douglas.
I I I I wanted to go to a gay bar when I was 17. No,
no, I don't think I wanted to go to a
gay bar when I was 17, mate. Another madeup story.
Why man are blame for this? Yeah, I met
this virgin [ __ ] cuz of him.
Joseph is a nons.
I never call Joseph Far a nons. I said
that he's a nons lover.
He is a nons lover. He loves nons cuz
he's a nons lover. Yeah.
Yeah, it is funny, bro. But all the
stories I'd say about him is the truth.
None of them are lies about him, about his dad. Yep.
You can tell he's a pedo as well because
remember when you said right oh about
six about oh you can't get with a 16y
old. He says it's this ain't America.
This ain't America.
There was one there was one woman said
to me oh don't go for any women that are
below 25. I said uh if I want to go with
an 18y old I can. Not that I would
because uh well it's legal and you're
legal at 18. Well, you're an adult at
You're not an adult at 16.
I'm not [ __ ] I come with who the [ __ ]
I want above the age of [ __ ] 18.
He used to hate that as well. The 16
thing. He used to be like, "Oh, this
ain't a marathon." That's how you knew
he's a [ __ ] nuts, mate. Proper pedo. Propedo, mate.
Proper pedo. That gun.
Why won't he leave me alone? I don't
want to know him. I don't want to. [ __ ] off.
You [ __ ] pedo [ __ ]
I wish I never met that P dog.
I I play Do you know how I met him? Good
Rage. I met him through Monty Man
or made myself some cream crackers. Grezy.
Yeah, I met him through Monty Man,
believe it or not.
Through [ __ ] Monty Man back on
[ __ ] PlayStation Triple H. I [ __ ]
met I met him through [ __ ] Monty Man.
Trusted to be through Monty Man, eh?
Yeah, I met him through Monty. They used
to be friends.
They fell. I think they fell out over Britney.
Oh, people just used to bully him.
Yeah, people used to bully him.
And I felt sorry. I was like, "Oh, this
kid's getting bullied.
I thought I'd give them the benefit of the doubt,
but no, they don't. No, they don't
happen. No, everyone moved on. But it
was good though. PlayStation was good
though. Like, cuz there was no
repeating. There was no repeating. It
was always No, PlayStation was good, bro.
PlayStation was good. You can you can
even ask Monty. PlayStation was good.
But it's not good on here because it's
just the same repeat.
It was different. It was a PlayStation
was a lot different, bro.
No, there was no repeating. It was just
B. It was just drama all the time. But
it was fun drama. No repeating, no nothing.
But people used to put their camera on as well.
But it don't happen no more. No.
Everyone moved on.
Everyone moved on. I was a lot younger
back then, but I was [ __ ] like 16. Yeah. Absolute virgin.
I used to think maybe like
He was just not unders he was misunderstood.
But people used to bully him, bro.
People used to bully him.
And he used to tell me that I live with
my mom. I said, I mean, yeah, I live
with my mom. I'm 19.
I mean, yeah, I live with my mom, bro.
I'm 18 years of age and I live with my
mom. Yeah. I'm 19 years of age. Yep.
Is that you, Kieran?
No, it wasn't funny. I remember the Izzy
days with Craig Goodson.
No, I I remember them days, bro. [ __ ]
they weren't funny, bro. They were depressing.
I wanted to get off YouTube back then,
Triple H, but I was in it too deep with
the Isabelle thing.
Yeah, I think I was like 22.
But then I met my other mama.
USA is that's my other mama.
That's when I met my other mama.
How was your eggs?
Ruby had eggs for lunch.
break. Remember me and Isabelle?
She was playing me and Craig in it. Do you remember?
That's when Mr. G was on here. Do you
remember Mr. Grip Rage?
Weird fellow, ain't that Mr. G? Yeah.
Yeah. It was only a few months ago that Mr. G.
I was in it too deep, mate. I was in it too deep.
He was on here a few months ago. He
still comes on occasionally, lad.
He still comes on here occasionally.
You remember the picture, Triple H? Do
you remember the Mr. G picture?
a picture in it.
Yeah, it was like three men in it.
Hey, I was thinking of becoming a porn star lad.
What do you think of that? Like, no, no
[ __ ] Becoming a porn star.
What do you think of that? No, seriously.
Would you watch me in action, Triple?
Would you watch me in action?
Right. I need to brush my teeth. One sec.
I still piss in the sink. Yeah. One sec.
Oh, I've just been talking to my [ __ ]
self. I was just talking for 2 minutes
and I had the [ __ ] thing muted.
I was saying, "Yeah, I got arrested for
breaking my own door."
Criminal damage. Yeah, it was my own door. Yeah.
Yeah, I remember that.
Yeah, I was talking to Bar Quest a while
ago. He blocked me on everything again.
So, he must have went back with that
Lee, I'm guessing. Uh, no. Yeah,
you need to stop that buy [ __ ] It's
really boring, bro. Yep.
One second, bro.
Anyways, I'm gone. Yeah. See you later.