Oh Jesus [ __ ] Christ, bro.
I am [ __ ] levered
on them few Guinnesses.
I can take it now at some [ __ ] stink
burden that has to say Cheryl Cole's
attractive to fit in with the crowd. I
don't need to pretend someone's
attractive and they're not just to fit in.
I'm not a little copycat.
I'm not a little copycat. I'm quite big actually.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
I am [ __ ]
I don't know what takeaway I'm going to
have yet, but yeah.
Going to have a hunt. [ __ ] I was
playing some drunk ball. It was a laugh.
It was a good old laugh.
Good old laugh.
You [ __ ] virgin.
That did pop up in my mind a few times.
You [ __ ] virgin can't
you know I'm like that
[ __ ] drunk as [ __ ] bro. Maybe
Chinese. Maybe maybe Chinese.
Don't underestim Don't underestimate.
[ __ ] Guinness. Oh [ __ ] There we go.
My eyes [ __ ] twitching, bro.
Yeah, nice nice bit of P. Nice bit of P. Oh, mate.
Sleepy now though. I can't lie.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm [ __ ] I'm so steaming, bro. Sorry
that joke. And I think for about six [ __ ] Guinnesses, mad.
I don't know what take what tasty
takeaway to get. Lovely.
Although some digest
some digestive biscuits too. Ba.
That's the only word I know. Bloody.
I had some pie and mash. I had some pie
And then I had some drink and I played
some pool with someone.
I would have stayed up, but I never have got
the last time I played Paul as well. And
you know what the funny thing is? I
actually remember the last time I played Paul.
It was actually the day before I met
USA. Is it? I actually remember it. Yeah,
I actually do remember exactly the last
time I played Paul except from today.
[ __ ] hell. Well, at least there won't
be no uh there won't be there won't be no hangovers.
Well, they like to
likes to play his darts. I like to play pool. Lovely. Yep.
[ __ ] it up, bro.
That was mad. They were like5 pound a
pie. So I thought5 a [ __ ] pie, mate.
It's not that bad, is it, man? [ __ ] bro.
I've just gone out. I was drinking and
playing some [ __ ] pool back now, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, I already went out drinking
Guinness and playing pool with someone.
So, yeah. Yeah, I've already been out.
the proper proper thing is next week.
Proper proper thing is next week.
I need to go get some food, mate, from somewhere. Uh,
how much money have we spent the past
couple [ __ ] days, mate? [ __ ] hell.
It's getting ludicrous now. Lo the
[ __ ] grist. Yeah.
I don't know if to get like five guys or what knows.
Getting psyched though. Definitely getting sank.
Well, I'm not a little copycat.
So, I'm not a little copycat. You got
mind on my own bills.
I'm not a little copycat.
Hey, Gravy, I've just come back. I was
drinking Guinness and I was playing pool
drunk as [ __ ] I had some pie mash earlier,
some lovely pie mash.
And then I got drunk and I played some
pool. Now I'm looking at some nice uh
and I got some digestive biscuits as
well, Greezy. They're going to be lovely
later. So I don't know. I might get a
Chinese today. I'm not sure. I'm not
getting an Indian. I've already had Indian,
bro. It was like5 a Guinness [ __ ]
dirt cheap. I was just drinking them,
drinking them, drinking them.
Next week though, definitely we'll get
[ __ ] bro. 100%. I didn't even have
my haircut today or anything. I It was
just like a chilled one for next week. 1 million%.
Oh, [ __ ] off. Give me a break, Grezy.
Give me a bloody break. My mom actually
bought them. Actually, you actually got
me going with the whole thing about like
when you said that it was lovely.
Bloody copycat. [ __ ] off. At least I
don't say Chevel Cole's attractive. You
don't like her. You're [ __ ] gay. At
least I'm not on that level of copycat
yet. Am I boozy?
You don't find her attractive. You gay hobo. Copycat.
Everyone point at the copycat. Boozy.
When the copycat walks in, point at the copycat.
Copycat. That's what we need to do. We
need to say to Virgin boy that we're
having a Halloween party and you we all
need to dress up, right? So every
obviously he's the one that's going to
dress up. No one else is going to dress
up, right? And he walks through the door
and you have to shout copycat and point
your little copycat and tickle him.
Copying to fit in with the crowd.
cuz you want to fit in your It's like
today. Um Grezy, right? I went I went to
have a I went to have a beer. I went to
have a beer while just got the bird I
was with. Yeah. He's like, "Oh, I'm
going to have a beer." I said, "I don't
want I didn't want to feel left out,
Greavvesy. So, I want to have a beer
with you." Cuz I didn't want to feel
left out, Greavesy. I didn't want to
feel left out.
Like Virgin Boy when he talked about
Sher Co. He didn't want He didn't want
to feel left out.
You know, it's it's it's a thing for a
lot of people not wanting to feel left out.
You little copycat. You little copycat.
Little copycat. She's attractive, is
she? Yeah. Everyone's gay if they don't
like her. Copycat. [ __ ] copycat, mate.
That is definitely.
What if you like big black women with a
bony boobs? What if you like blonde
women with blue eyes and big boobs?
Would you still be gay, mate? Would you
still be home, mate? [ __ ] copycat.
Little copycat. Like you said, Grezy,
it's a little copycat statement. I'm
looking on the menu. What to have to eat today, Grezy?
I had some pie mash. It was lovely.
Oh, what? I need to update it before I can order.
Oh, bugger off.
Little comfy cat.
Yeah. Is that all right if I had a few Guinnesses today?
Yeah, it was fun, bro. It was really fun.
Yeah, it was a fun day, bro.
Next week though, 100% we're going to
get on the [ __ ] up, bro. Proper.
When I have one grievy, I can't stop.
I see some guy that I knew. He was
working at the place from uh when I used
to live in Stratford. I was like, "Oh, I
remember you. You used to work in
Stratford, is it?" And we was talking
and stuff. Yeah. Peter Belly gets
around, bro. Peter belly gets around.
Peter belly gets around. Grievy.
Oh gosh. You would have loved this. You
would have loved this pie mash. SC,
why don't I talk about women much
anymore now, Greavvesy? Is it cuz I get
my vitamins from other places?
Yeah, you get your I don't fancy pepp. I
don't fancy Pizza Hut.
I might I don't know what I want, bro.
Chinese. It It's got to be Chinese, isn't it?
Maybe some cheeky fish and chips.
I don't know.
I don't want peppies, grilled chicken.
I don't know what I want. Maybe like
some fish and chips. Maybe don't know. Uh
What do you think? Chinese are fishing ships.
>> Yeah, I was with my sister. I was with
my sister and yeah, we just had some
drinks. But this isn't the proper
session. The proper session is next week.
I don't know. I might get Chinese. I
fancy like a beef chowine, you know.
I might get a [ __ ] Chinese
cuz I like the beef chain.
Yeah, my mommy bought me pie mash today.
Greasy. It was lovely.
Yeah, I can't just go and have one,
Guinness, I can't have only one.
Nope. I can't have only one.
I can't have only one Guinness, bro. I
had about six Guinnesses, love, mate. I
had about I had six Guinnesses. I was playing pool.
Wait until next week, brother. I'm going
to pull some [ __ ] bro. Watch next
week. This week I couldn't be bothered
by my haircut. I just want to chill one.
Watch next week. Well, watch watch what
watch. These can't ain't seen nothing yet.
Cole's hot. J Cole's attractive. I
couldn't stop thinking about that when I
was in the in the pub.
I just don't understand why somebody
feels the need to copy, to want to copy someone,
to feel the need to have to copy another person
just to fit in, you know?
I think it's got to be Chinese, bro.
Who does Douglas? Who? Who does dogless?
Uh, I'm trying to think, man.
You all right, Captain? I've just come
back, man. I've been on the Guinness and
I was playing some pool, so I'm a bit
drunk. I'm not having Indian again. No way.
I don't know why people need to copy
though, Douglas. She's attractive. Oh,
so what if what if you like big what if
you like big black African women with
big boobs? Does that mean you you're
still gay? What if what if you like
blonde women with blue eyes and big
boobs that are curvy? Does that mean
you're gay, mate? Yeah. Yeah. Does that
mean you're hobo? Does that mean you
like Pekka? Does that mean you like Peppa?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Peppa, mate.
Yeah. Yeah. So, mate. Yeah. Yeah. Gate game.
Yeah. Little copycat. You little
copycat. You little copycat. You little
Uh just some guy I know.
I was just playing with some guy that I
know and I and I recognize one of the
bartenders from when I lived in
Stratford. I said, "Oh, I know you from
uh last year." He we was talking and
stuff. It was quite a good day.
Nah, she doesn't work there anymore. But
this isn't a proper session. The proper
session is next week, bro. We're getting
on the [ __ ] bro. The Guinness is only a
Fiverr there. The Guinness is only a fiverr.
I won. It was 2-1. Two to him and I won
once. No, it was three. It was two. It
was 32. We played three games. What am I
talking about? 3-2. And I remember the
last time I played um uh Paul Douglas. I
remember the last time I played Paul
from except from today. It was when I
met my mama. It was actually the day
before I met my mama
when my sister was working in the pub
few years ago. That was the day before I
met my mama.
So I I know exactly when was the last
time I actually played pool. And it was
a couple years ago cuz day before I met my mama Douglas.
So I know exactly when the last time I played. Yeah.
You have Yeah. It was a few years ago, bro.
I was decent at it. But
Triple H likes to play dot. I like to play pool. Uh right.
Should have had a bet on it. It was like
150 a game.
It was fun though. I enjoyed it.
And the Guinness was £5 which is cheap
consider considering the atmosphere and
the place was good for £5. And if you go
central London, you're spending £8 in
the [ __ ] Weather Spoons, mate. So
there's a big difference. You can get
[ __ ] for like 30 quid.
So there's a big difference, bro.
Yeah, I think it's going to have to be
Chinese, man. It's going to have to be
grieved. I thought my [ __ ] TV packed
up. It wasn't turning on, lad. And then
it's because the battery is [ __ ] dodgy.
It's because the batter is dodge. I was
like, there's no way a brand new TV
could have packed up. No way.
No. Yeah, it's 1 pound50, which still
ain't that bad, bro. You can have a lot
of fun in that place for like 30, 40
quid. It's cheap. Uh,
I'm going to get a beef, man. And yeah,
looking for my next copycat statement. Yeah,
we have a Lindsay Williams. Absolutely no way.
No, we have a Linda Williams.
Absolutely no way, Grezy.
for the name Linda Williams.
We have a Lindsay Williams. Absolutely no way. Mad.
Yeah, this was 150. [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I get my vitamins from other
places now, so I'm happy.
It was the vitamins all along, wasn't
it, Grezy? Because I wasn't getting the
vitamins. That's what it was.
It was all because of vitamins.
Greasy trolls me hard and I don't see
it. Yeah, bro. I totally don't see him
trolling me. Yeah, I totally don't see
it. Of course I [ __ ] see it. I don't
give a [ __ ] It's all a laugh. I don't mind it.
He He would even admit he trolls. That's
fine. He admits it. It's not a problem.
It's only when you get these [ __ ]
idiots that think they're clever and
they think they're good at trolling.
That's the [ __ ] that pisses me off.
Yep. I just get my vitamins from other
things now. So, I don't need women.
Why do I need them?
Greasy. With me and Grezy, it's just banter.
Yeah, like you said.
So what? He's Yeah, he's trolling as as
he's taking a piss. So what
Triple H does it as well?
So what, bro?
Not like the virgin [ __ ]
See, I'm so happy when I get my vitamins, Grezy.
I'm so happy when I got my little vitamins.
It's them tickets. They filled me up.
You know, Grey, the little chicken tickers.
Yep. I don't need them. I keep getting
my vitamins from other places. A greasy
Yeah, bro. Got my nice new coat coming
in a couple of days,
so go out on a piss.
So, I went out today and I enjoyed
myself. I didn't speak to any women. I
could have if I wanted to, but I never
cuz I don't need my vitamins. I have
less vitamins. I don't need them. So, yeah,
I don't drink water. I have
Let me ask lady if she wants anything
order of this [ __ ] Chinese. Lady,
you want anything for the Chinese? Mama,
>> you know what? Nothing at all. Mama,
>> I was going to get fish and chips, but
it's a bit too greasy. So, I think I'm
going to I'm going to eat the Chinese.
You know what I'm going to get?
What did you say the other day when you
looked at the beef chain?
>> So, what happened to all the beef?
I scoffed all the beef, ma. Yep. See?
So, what? You just happy with the digestive biscuits? Okay. Ma,
what are you going to Yeah, but you got
me the pie mash today, Ma.
I thought I could repay you. >> Yeah.
>> So many. >> Yeah.
You like your hugs? Okay, ma.
That's all right. Huh?
>> They cost a lot of money, ma. Yep.
Well, lady's been doing it for years,
James Johnson. So, okay. Seriously? Yep.
But guess what, bro? You people in your
40s and you self project every day.
Imagine that. You people like double my
age and you and you act im more immature than me.
Oh, that Simon is fantasy stories, by the way.
The sad [ __ ] that ran away from Pat
Mustard. We don't entertain that
Northern Irish bastard.
We don't entertain that [ __ ] A sad old [ __ ]
Ugly little virgin man with a [ __ ]
ugly accent. He's trying to kill the
vibe. We don't want people in here
killing the vibe. [ __ ] off.
wouldn't be good enough for me.
These women, I'm looking at these people, bro.
I'm looking at these people and I'm
thinking, how the [ __ ] are they happy
with these women?
Really, they've got no there's no nutrients.
They've literally got no boobs. They've
got nothing. What the [ __ ] That's boring.
That's bloody That's nothing. That's no
good. Without the nutrients, they're
boring as [ __ ] They're just whiny
[ __ ] and [ __ ] you know,
we don't even need them now cuz we get
nutrients from other places. But, you
know, even back then,
boring as [ __ ] That tells you how
boring they are.
You could see all of the women I ever
went on dates with, they all had big boobies.
Well, most of them the solicitor,
you know, all of these people.
Otherwise, they're no good to me without the vitamins
to help them get me through the winter, right? Laney.
Right. We're going to get some
We're going to order some food in a bit.
Yeah. Let's get some nice
Pork. They have pork chain.
Pork chain. No thank you. Pork chain. Barbecue sauce.
Okay. I want a small I want a small I
want a small beef charm with spice cuz
I'm a big strong Turkish man as you know.
I'm not some little virgin that lives
out of London. You know what I mean?
We got beef curry.
What? What about the balls?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, where is these balls? I like these chicken balls.
USA is boobies were tasty, but this food
is even better. Greasy. It's just
obviously it's more expensive, you know.
Yeah. I'm going to get a small chicken
fried rice. Yeah.
Do you like ribs? I don't really I'm not
really keen on ribs.
You say is his boobs. Do you know they
tasted like greasy? They tasted like chocolate. Yep. Chocolate. vesticles,
right? No, seriously. Where's this uh
we need? Where's the chicken fried rice?
rice. This is Okay, here we go. Chicken fried rice.
I'm going to get that hot as well.
Wait one second, lad.
No, it's here. One second. Hold on. Add
oil chili. One sec.
Add oil chili. Add Wait, wait, wait.
Please let me think here.
Yeah, here we go. Add. Yeah. So, it's £14.
No, it's £19.
Should I buy that?
I'm not a skin virgin in a bedsit, so
should be all right, mate.
I'm not a skin virgin in a bed, am I?
So, I should be all right, mate.
I don't know where I don't know how you
can get the chicken balls, lad.
I had this problem before trying to get
these chicken balls.
I'm [ __ ] drunk, lad.
I am [ __ ] drunk.
Where Where were these chicken balls?
What's better, Greasy? What's better
vitamin? Do you say is his boobies or the Chinese?
Well, the Indian is way better than her boobies. Grezy,
you know. Yeah. That Indian. What would
you prefer? The Indian Grezy or USA is his boobies.
I don't know where these chicken balls are, bro.
But this is hot. So lady won't be able
to have any
lady won't be able to have any
cuz it's hot.
I just want these chicken balls, bro.
Where are these chicken [ __ ] balls?
I love chicken balls, bro. And I can't
find these bastard [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] hard to get, bro. I
swear to God on this online chicken dishes,
beef dishes. Where is it? Ribs, roast
pork, squid dishes.
No, I don't know where it is, bro. Side dishes.
No, it's not here.
Well, let me ask lady to try and find
this cuz I can't [ __ ] find it. One second.
Yeah, I got it.
[snorts] I got it. Graves.
Got to order it in a minute. Yeah. cat.
A little copycat.
I like copycat.
He knows he's a copycat.
I'm [ __ ] I'm so drunk, Steven Howard.
But I'm not a copycat.
I got a mind of my own.
Got a mind of my bloody own. Oh,
I'm getting some more vitamins before bedy.
I don't need that. USA, is he? I've got
my own vitamins.
Isn't that right?
These women are boring.
They're boring, mate. Drunk of Guinness. Yeah.
What? Why? Why wouldn't you get drunk of
Guinness? It's It's alcohol.
You think it's unbelievable to be drunk of Guinness?
Yeah. I mean, it's got alcohol in it. So, [ __ ]
Greasy said that if I had a baby, it'd
be whisked straight into the care system.
It'd be whisked straight into the care system.
When am I back on a [ __ ] never, mate?
[ __ ] that. When I go out next Saturday,
I'm not drinking anything but Guinness.
You can get [ __ ] mate. The hangovers
the next day is not worth it. I'll sleep
like a baby today, Greasy.
I'll sleep like a Bubba.
How does that make you feel, Grezy? That
I'll sleep like a baby.
I'm not touching that, Captain Morgans.
[ __ ] right off, mate.
Nah. No way. [snorts] Who's that?
You little copycat. Them little cats.
Them little copycats.
Them little cats. Grizzly. Them little
No. Don't get some like 98s because that
would mean you're a copycat.
That's what copycats do.
No, that's what little copycats do.
Isn't it greasy?
Only if you're a little copycat. Bless you.
That's okay with me, boss.
I'm going to order this food in a minute.
She's good. She's attractive.
Chev is attractive. You find Shevil Co
attractive, Grezy? She's so attractive. So good-look.
She can't deny. Can't deny.
Can't deny she's attractive.
You can't deny she's attractive, lad.
dismissing my struggles. Grievy,
I'll explain to you how they dismiss my
struggles again. Right? So, you'll show
them messages, you'll show them
approaches, and then if you do something
that they they agree, they disagree
with, they'll be like, "Oh, well, maybe
that's your problem." And I'm thinking,
"But what about the approaches? What
about the messages? Yeah, they they
dismiss people's struggles.
Does it bother me now? No, not really.
Because I know that people are always
going to dismiss struggles when it comes
to women. So, it's just like, oh,
really? Yeah, whatever. That's fine.
They do dismiss people's struggles.
Definitely definitely do. Triple H has
done it as well. Triple H has dismissed
my struggles as well.
They even resort to making stuff up and
assume and assuming greasy.
They will even they will even make up
stuff and assume things if that makes sense.
Mad, is it
They do dismiss your struggles, Grezy. 100%.
100%, Greasy. Because why would Triple H
be saying them things if I put
approaches and messages up there? So,
would you say that that is that is
dismissing people's struggles?
They do dismiss people's struggles.
What do you think, Grezy?
>> Yeah, it's
What do you think, Grey? Is it
dismissing people's struggles or what?
Yeah, it is.
It is because Triple H was saying about
how, you know, I'm immature and I can't
get a woman because I'm immature.
Somebody that doesn't dismiss people's
struggles would see the videos that I
put up and what they've done and the
leading on. So, the fact that they don't
acknowledge it, it is dismissing
people's struggles. I know you might not
like I know you might like Triple H. I
do as well. I like a good Triple H and
his little Jordy accent, but it is
dismissing people's struggles
and it is cuz they're a woman as well.
So these things need to be pointed out.
I don't know why why they do it.
Look at this. I said you kept me
hanging. One second, Gre. I said you
kept me hanging. She said no, not my
fault. I have a life to you. Maybe this
your first red red flag. You don't have patience.
Right. But I've shown you approaches and
I've shown you messages. Completely dismissed.
That's why you can't take these things seriously. Grezy,
do you know what, Grezy? I'm going to do
the social experiment tomorrow and they
better make these excuses for men.
Because if they don't make excuses for
men, Greavvesy, I'm going to have a go at you.
I'm not going to be happy with you, lad.
I'm going to have a bone to pick with
you. I'm going to talk [ __ ] about men.
pretending to be a woman tomorrow. And I want
Yeah. No one cares about yourself
projecting sim comments, lad.
No one cares about your little white
knight comments. and Greavves they I I
if they make excuses for men then I'll
be like okay whatever
Douglas you're probably a virgin and
you've probably never been with a woman
mate no one cares what you think
no one cares about your little negative
self-p projected hopeless comments
you're writing it to the wrong person
lad wasting your man. Anyways, we listen.
I just want them to make excuses for men.
If they make excuses for men, I will
never say anything ever again about Grezy.
I want them to make the same excuses for
men as they do women.
Can you promise me they're going to do that? >> [snorts]
>> Yeah. Why Why are you writing stuff like
that anyways, bro? That's a weird thing to write.
Another one that dismisses people struggles.
Why do they keep dismissing people's
struggles? I don't know why they do it.
I was speaking to a transgender yesterday, Grezy.
Grezy, listen. I just want them to make
the same excuses tomorrow for men. Yeah,
I'm going to be a woman and say I've had
bad experiences with men. I've met men
on dating apps
and I want them to make the same excuses. Greasy. >> Yeah.
I just want them to make the same excuses.
So if I'm really wrong, Grezy,
then people will tell me I'm wrong when
I pretend to be a woman, right, Grezy?
If they really believe I'm wrong,
then they'll make the same excuses
tomorrow when I pretend to be a woman.
Isn't that right, Greavvesy?
They will make the same excuses when I
pretend to be a woman, will they not?
I don't mind being wrong, but the
problem is I'm not wrong. And the only
reason that they're defending them is
cuz they got a [ __ ] in between their legs.
So, if I'm really wrong, I want to be
told I'm wrong tomorrow when I'm
pretending to be a woman. Crazy. Yep.
In a minute. I'm ordering it in a minute, lad.
I'm ordering it now.
Is okay if I order it now, Captain?
Can I order it right this second?
They're not normal women. These women
are not nor they're not normal. They're narcissistic,
evil people with unrealistic standards.
So they're they're not normal. These
women are not normal. Are you talking
about the women in the messages and
stuff? Yeah, these women are not normal.
They're narcissistic, suckup [ __ ]
with unrealistic expectations.
They're not normal, lad.
These women are not normal. So, I don't
know why you're saying that they're
normal. E, a s,
a wild s appears
and he floats. A normal wh normal women.
These women are not normal.
Appears out of nowhere. [sighs]
Wild simp appears out of nowhere. These
simps appear out of [ __ ] nowhere.
These women are not normal.
You know, when I was out today, Gres, I
was actually paying attention. They're
all stuck up. I didn't even speak to any
of them. They're all stuck up their own
asses. They're definitely not normal,
mate. They're all NPCs.
Anyways, let's change the subject now.
[snorts] anyways, let's let's change the
subject now. Anyways, right onto this Chinese.
Right, Grezy. [snorts]
This is where it starts becoming
unhealthy, isn't it, Grezy? This is
where it starts. This is where it starts
becoming unhealthy. Right, Grezy?
We're not interested in white knights
that dismiss people struggles. Waste of time.
Right. So, we got Oh, it's actually the
same price. That's weird. Right. I'm all
the way in now.
Uh, anything to add?
Yeah, these women are definitely
definitely not normal.
Definitely definitely definitely not normal.
I don't think I've ever come across a
normal woman in my life.
That's an insult to people that are actually normal.
They're not [ __ ] normal. They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
Evil narcissistic [ __ ]
The [ __ ] that they do is not normal.
Right. I'm ordering this £25.
How much did yours cost?
Yeah, mine was 25.
How was I spent today? I can't remember.
Where is he?
>> Where's the copy?
You little copycat.
Why did you copy me? I'm in Chinese. You little copycat.
I felt so much better. You know, Grezy,
not dealing with women. I This has been
the best three weeks of my life, Grezy.
You know, when I gave up. Yeah. Every
time I give up, I feel so much better.
So much better. Does that not tell you something, lad?
that the moment you give up, the moment
you don't have these problems anymore.
I think that tells you that's how how
toxic it is. Yeah. Yeah,
I need to put this coke in the freezer
cuz I like a really cold coke with my
tire like I'm mate.
Who am I? Oh my
I feel [ __ ] bro. I feel [ __ ] [ __ ] man.
I can't wait for this Chinese.
Is it too early to have Chinese greasy
though? Is it
going to have a nice [ __ ] Chinese?
Nice cup of [ __ ] and digestive biscuits
and then go to sleep. Mom,
how much was the digestive biscuits?
How much was the digestive biscuits?
No, sorry. Um, how were they? >> Oh,
they put this in the
>> Yeah, I've ordered the Chinese. So, we
got double chicken balls, so you're more
than welcome to. Huh?
I've added some oil or some chili oil
into the char and fried rice. What's it?
You can have some as well.
The chicken was nice and empty, didn't it?
[ __ ] you hell, mate. That was lovely.
What am I going to do after I eat?
You know me in it.
Do I like sleep?
You're a little copycat. [ __ ] hell. Jesus Christ.
My beard is long now. on it.
Definitely going barbers next week. [ __ ] hell. [ __ ] me.
Beef Char is my favorite. M. [snorts]
The beef's nice, isn't it?
I like chicken balls as well. The pie
mash's nice. You don't have it often, do you? Double check.
>> That's nice match. [ __ ] chocolate
though, is it? >> Yeah.
>> Well, you never really see people going
to Five Guys, do you? Huh?
Yeah. You should do your ears out when
you come out the shower. It huh? >> Yeah.
>> My ears are not really dirty. Why is
that? I don't do them. Huh? >> No.
No. No. Dirt comes out of it.
Weird. Is it
me when I go in the shower or something? Hello there. Huh?
Hands going over my [ __ ] is annoying.
I want to get the haircut shorter. Annoying.
I'm I'm a little copycat.
You're a copycat, boy. You copy people.
You copy the crowd.
You don't look all left out.
Strong homo vibes.
Sounds like greasy. The Chinese is
coming. The Chinese is coming, lad.
Sounds like a copycat statement.
I don't like you, Gregy. I think you
take the piss out of me.
Sounds like a copycat statement. Why
would you even say something like that?
Cuz it does sound like a copycat
statement because it doesn't even make sense.
Sounds like a copycat statement. [snorts] Yep.
Just looking looking for the next person
to copy Greasy.
No mind, no no mind of their own, no substance, nothing.
Just copying copying the crowd.
Greavves is just copying the crowd, isn't it? Winner winner.
Winner winner. Chicken dindins.
Did you like that booking video, Grezy?
You didn't You didn't think I had it in
me, did you?
You didn't think I had an image in your last >> [sighs]
>> Come on, food.
Oh, you get deleted.
Oh, so it says deleted when the mods ban you.
So you you have to admit that with these
Reddit mods, it is some kind of power.
They get off on banning people, Grezy,
because it's strange that there's no
other site that just bans people but
Reddit. No Instagram, no Facebook, no
YouTube. It only seems to be Reddit. It
does seem like a very power hungry
power hungry website
and they have to feel in control. It
does feel like a control thing to me lad.
It does feel
Yeah, but a lot of people have been
banned on Reddit grooves. A lot of
people have been banned.
I think the mods are creeps. Little
creep little low lives.
Why do you think Steven the mods ban people?
Why do you think the mods ban people?
Is it Do you reckon it's to feel in
control? I think it's the power thing
where they've been bullied all their
life. They want to feel a part of something. Yeah.
Ru, you need to go to the dentist.
Yeah, people on Reddit say you can get
sex whenever you want. Just go on the
dating apps, they said.
Grezy had a go at Lex for dismissing my
struggles, didn't you, Grezy?
You nasty virgin.
Griez you nasty virgin.
You nasty virgin. Boom.
You nasty skin virgin. Lay me. Yep.
Yeah, I get you, Gre. I get you.
Bless you. Then
would you say USA is is a uh narcissist? Grezy.
He doesn't talk about that [ __ ] Sh
thing anymore, does he? Where is it?
Because he knows he's a copycat.
He knows that he's a straight up copycat.
So, he can't even deny it.
Why would I make it up, bro?
What? Make up. Make it up. I put the
messages out there, Grezy.
What? What? What do you mean making it up?
What do you What do you mean make it up?
I put the messages out there. Griefs [clears throat]
when it first happened. What do you mean
making it up? Huh?
No, she led me on and then blocked me.
And then when I got my friend to message
her, she started making up stories that
I grabbed her and [ __ ] I mean, that's
what the [ __ ] said. Just that's what Yeah,
but who cares? I'm just a little copycat.
Grezy. I'm not I'm not Grezy. I'm just a little copycat.
You little copycat.
You little copycat. I can't stop saying
it. Grezy, you little copycat.
Little copycat. She's attractive. She a good-look
[ __ ] is [ __ ] ugly. And I'm not
[ __ ] insecure about my sexuality.
Yeah, I wasn't making up.
Where is this [ __ ] [ __ ] in Chinese?
I'm hungry. I'm hungry. Greasy. The
Coke's in the freezer. Oh,
I'm feeling a bit [ __ ] now cuz the
good old Guinness This squeezy.
Oh, I'm [ __ ] tired, bro.
I am [ __ ] tired. Oh Jesus.
You remember a couple of weeks ago,
Grezy, when I was drinking, I was sick.
when I met Adam.
Remember that's what I grab.
What do you think of Adam Graves?
Do you do you like Adam?
I really don't know.
Adam from Brighton. Adam,
I don't like posh people. Greavves. Do
you like posh people?
like really posh.
I don't like posh people cuz they think
they're better than people.
Adam seems kind of stuck up.
I mean, Adam kind of seemed a bit stuck up
like kind of being awkward. I can't explain it.
Like I said to him that you know if you
really like [ __ ] it's a fetish
fetish and he's like oh it ain't a
fetish if you just like it. But I said
well it is a fetish because if you have
a if you prefer [ __ ] than sex it
becomes a fetish.
It becomes a fetish. If you would rather
have a [ __ ] then have sex. If you can
have a [ __ ] without sex then it is a
fetish. Would you not agree?
Because most people would just prefer sex.
I think it's a fetish. She didn't think
it was. I think it is.
What's your opinion?
But it's still in [ __ ] progress.
So, what's your opinion, Grezy? Would
you say it's a fetish or would you say it's not?
Brighton is a stuck up place.
I've been to Brighton many times.
One second, lad.
Happy New Year, Carla. This is Adam's
brother. Is this your daughter? I assume
that one on the right is your son, but
boy, the lad at the back looks like
Mark. Yes, Ben is Mark's son. He lives
in Shanghai with his girlfriend Lola. My
daughter M was next to Adam's son.
Thanks, my dear.
They seem like a pretty uh pretty strong
family to be honest.
He actually does live in
He does that guy actually does live in
China then. That's mad mad. Copycat.
I just saw your community post. Copycat.
Everyone's going to wait for you to walk in.
in now and call you the copycat. You are
You little copycat.
You delete it, lad. I was just about to comment.
just about to comment on it. You silly goose
You don't find cheerful car attractive
at all, Grizzly?
Like at all? At all? You're trying to
tell me you don't find her attractive at all?
You're trying to tell me you don't find
her attractive at all. Gy,
you must be gay, lad. You must be [ __ ] gay.
You must be gay if you don't find her
attractive. Homo vibes. Homo vibes.
Still waiting for my Indian. I'm sorry.
I'm still waiting for my Chinese. But it's okay.
I'll just wait.
Must be gay then, Grezy. You must be [ __ ] gay.
Must be homo.
If you don't find her attractive, you're gay, lad.
You literally can't deny that she's attractive.
You must be gay, mate. Must be gay.
Must be a homo.
You literally can't deny that she's attractive.
Yeah, you must be gay, mate. I'm with
nonsense on this one.
I mean, even if you liked
big black women with big boobs, Reevesy,
you not liking Sher Car makes you gay.
That makes you homo. Makes you
homosexual. You might like blonde women
with blue eyes and big boobs, but you're
still gay. If you don't like Cheryl
Cole, you're still gay. I mean, you
could even have kids, Greavves. You
could have a children with a woman. Kids
But if you do not find Cheryl car
attractive, you're gay.
Even if you got kids with a woman, still
gay, mate. Still [ __ ] homo. Oh my,
mate. [ __ ] homo.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say that's a copycat statement.
But you agreed. If I didn't know any
better, I'd say it was a copycat statement.
Copycat. No mind of your own.
Yeah, it's definitely a copycat statement. Cubby cat [clears throat]
crazy. It's not the fact that somebody
finds them attractive or doesn't find
them attract attractive. It's the fact
that they say that you're gay if you
don't find her attractive.
You understand me, Grezy?
That's what makes them a copycat.
That's what makes them the copycat, you know. Yeah. You okay?
Order is on its way. My order is on its
way. Grezy, it's on its way. It's on its
Are you Huh?
going to take for the next um
for the next copycat statement.
How long does a statement take to uh
generate grievy? What' you say? Okay.
So, what what what's Elephant and Castle
got to do with me, Greasy?
What's Elephant and Castle got to do with me? I'm tired.
You lose it.
How [ __ ] knackered I am, lad.
Elephant and castle. Grezy. Elephant and
Do you think it was weird that my mom
was staying there?
I'm still waiting for the food. Greasy.
It's okay though. I'll just wait.
You'll You'll wait.
Yes. Until it's been made. Joseph Farra.
Joseph Ferrar is a gambling addict.
Have you noticed that about this
community, Grievy? There's a lot of
nerds on here. I'm sure you've noticed
that in it.
where they were going to kill themselves
because they lost four grand.
Is that what you mean?
>> Wow. Oh, really?
There's too many nerds on this community
though, Grezy. So many nerds.
Would you agree there's a lot of nerds on here? [ __ ]
Now, Treasure Far is a proper gambling addict.
Now, he's a proper proper gambling
addict. He put £700 in a FBI. A fy.
I put 500 pound in FB a few times when I
used to be depressed.
I'm waiting for this food. I'm trying to
stay awake, bro. I'm tired. Virgin boy.
What's your favorite WWE finisher, Grezy?
What's your favorite WWE finisher?
O where you at? Let me let me send you
something funny. Yeah, look at these little copycats. Ew.
Grooy, did you watch it?
Why? What's the cat waiting for? Why is
he just sat there waiting looking? Grezy,
why is the great Why is the cat just sat
there waiting looking? person said
this person said it is valid that you
feel betrayed for you felt that they are
leading you on
and you know what I replied we
said I didn't feel that they were
leading me on they were leading me on
they dismissing struggles are they
dismissing struggles Yeah.
Are they dismissing struggles again? war.
What makes you say that?
Why are you saying that they're
dismissing my struggles?
I'll do it to my own.
Now they're talking about preferences.
I hope this they don't make greasy. I'm
do I'm going to do the experiment
tomorrow. I promise you. But
Grezy, I just hope that they make
excuses for men tomorrow.
I just hope it's equal to my Grezy.
What's your prediction? I got hiccups.
What's your What's your
What's your prediction for tomorrow?
I think that they're going to make
excuses for men as well. Hopefully,
I'm going to say that I'm a woman and
I've been led on by men.
And I'm also going to pretend
I'm a gay man that's been led on by men. And hopefully
it's the same thing.
No, but No, no, no. I'll private message
people. No, but I'll private message
Why are they going to ban me?
What's your prediction?
What's your prediction? Yeah, we'll see.
But what's your prediction?
I reckon they're going to make excuses
for men as well. Hopefully.
Hopefully, we'll hear the same excuses
that the men change their minds and
stuff. Hopefully, with a bit of luck, we
hear the same excuses.
But what do you think, Grezy?
No. What about when I pretend to be a woman?
Yeah, but I'm going to pretend to be a woman.
boded and complaining about men as well.
I'm going to be a woman and I'm going to
complain about all men and say that
they're all [ __ ]
and I'm going to moan about men.
Hopefully I get called for it. What do you think?
I've done this experiment before. um moves here.
I done this experiment before on Reddit
where I was a woman moaning about men
and everyone felt sorry for me.
Everyone like oh maybe it's the men that
you're going for.
They were like they were saying to me
maybe it's the men that you're going for
and stuff. They said it's nothing to do
with you. It's probably the shitty men
that you you know that that keeps going
for you. And then when I was a man,
there was like you [ __ ] insel. It's
your mindset. It's your personality. Big
bit of a difference. There was a bit of
Yeah, there was a bit of a difference.
They like it's your mindset. You [ __ ]
insult. But when I was a woman about
men, they felt sorry for me.
Bit unfair, is it? No. Bit rude.
I mean, if they can't even admit they've
let people on, I mean, what would they
admit? What can they admit? We I mean,
it's not even the worst thing ever.
But they can't even take accountability
for leading people on. So,
this is all right. Then stop to those
people. Go with your life. You can be
angry and mad and angry again, but move
forward. I know it's wrong and they're
awful for it, but it's your job to it's
your job to heal. That's what they
should be saying. Stuff like that. Not
dismissing it. You know what I mean? Grezy,
again, please tell me you're not
bringing this kind of again. You're
making up stuff.
You're making up stuff. See, this is
what I'm saying.
This is what I'm saying. It is It is
dismissing struggles because if they
weren't dismissing your struggles, Grezy,
they wouldn't be saying that. Okay,
Grey, how many how many approaching
videos have I watch have you watched,
right? Where I have tried starting a
conversation with someone and they've
said straight away, you're not interested.
One, two, three. I don't know. Did you watch any?
I mean, I'm sure you watch some that
said that. No.
So, my whole point is would that not contradict the whole
women go for personality and stuff?
Wouldn't that surely contradict it?
I I'm I mean I'm asking you would that
short would that
surely contradict everything that
they're saying about personality and stuff?
I've ordered it. Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no, no. It's not leading
on Grezy, but wouldn't it contradict
everything that they're saying?
Go out, be confident, have a good
personality, but yet you can't even
finish a sentence without someone saying
they're not interested. So surely to God that would
that would that would contradict it.
But no no we're not talking about
leading on but surely it contradicts the
personality thing though
because they say that women go for
personality right but how many videos
have you seen where people have said
straight away you're not interested.
Surely it contradicts what they're
saying to you. No, a little bit maybe. So
this woman was like, "What do you want
me to say?" I said, "Again, you're
making up stuff. Dismissing my
approaches. I showed you my approaches."
She said, "What do you want me to say?"
I said, "Well,
maybe just don't dismiss my struggles. I
don't care what you say.
They definitely dismiss your struggles.
Definitely, definitely. 100% they
dismiss your struggles.
But if they went for personality grievy,
wouldn't they give you a chance?
And then we go on to the whole thing
where they don't owe you anything again.
So you just go around in circles.
Just same old conversation.
Same old repetitive, boring, depressing
conversation. Right, moving on. Anyways,
we're not we're not going to know about this.
Sorry I brought this up, bro.
Right. Yeah, move on. Anyways,
well, dating apps don't work, so
we don't have anything else, lad.
Yeah, but bro, I know what you're
saying, but we have to code approach. >> [laughter]
>> We have to cold approach.
If you want to meet someone, you got a cold approach.
If you wanted to meet someone, you have
to code approach.
You know, in if you're in my situation,
but they do dismiss your struggles 100%. Cuz
if they went for personality, they
wouldn't be saying straight away they're
not interested if they went for personality.
So I don't know where my Chinese is.
But yeah, it is definitely uh Yeah.
It is dismissing struggles.
All they keep saying is my order's on
its way, Dad.
But I still haven't received it. Chinese
So, Indigo, what's your prediction for
this social experiment tomorrow? Captain,
what's your uh what's your prediction?
Actually, I might do it today early
hours when all the little S mods are asleep.
I'm going to be pretend to be a woman
complaining about men.
I'm going to say I hate all men. They're
scumbags. I can't find anyone. And I
want to know if people are going to
start blaming my mindset and my personality.
See what the crack is, as Irish would say.
I'm going to pretend to be a woman
moaning about men. Then I'm going to be
a gay man moaning about men and see if
they make excuses for these men like
they make excuses for these women. Yeah,
it's a very very
This woman was like, "You know what? I'm
done talking to you. I'm really sorry,
but I can't help you." So, I sent her my
two approaches. I said to her, "Right,
let me remind you of the approaches." is
I sent her two approaches. She said,
"You know what? I'm done talking to you.
I'm really sorry, but but I can't I
can't help you."
Why do these people hate taking
accountability for women's wrongdoings?
I've done videos, no one answers it. I
don't understand this. I've done videos
a million times, but no one comments.
No one bloody comments. Squeezy.
They hate taking accountability.
They dismiss your struggles.
So would you say this person's
dismissing my struggles? Grezy,
it's not tiring, bro. It's depressing.
It's not tiring, it's depressing, lad.
So, is he dismissing my struggles? Greasy.
Who cares? [ __ ] them.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] that, bro. Just move on. Yeah.
I'm waiting for this Chinese.
Is it here?
The Chinese is here, mate. I didn't hear
it. [ __ ] hell, mate. the doorbell.
>> Well, I got the good boy.
I got some chicken bows.
You ain't got the skills to do
Have some food.
Look at this.
Look at this, mate.
I need a bit of beef in me, mate.
Bit of beef in me, mate. What's a beef, mate?
Why, mate? You got all sorts of
>> What do you mean?
>> You know, not this one. The chicken fried bison. Sorry mate.
>> What did you get then? You could find as well.
>> Yeah. And the chicken.
I should have done good.
>> It's all right. I'm about good.
But you said you >> probably m M lovely.
He should be working on losing his V cards. valid. [snorts]
You could be working on losing that recon.
What do you reckon? You could be losing that replay.
Well, what's this?
>> Is it bad?
>> No, it's just a >> mine. Have some.
>> Oh, [ __ ] hell, mate. really mate.
Where's that [ __ ] virgin?
Where's the skin version? You been
[ __ ] awfully quiet.
When I was on my other account, right,
she didn't reply. Then as soon as I made
another account, she replied straight
away. Was she being an ignorer?
She wasn't being a [ __ ] ignor. She
know she had a long day.
She wasn't being a [ __ ] ignorant.
I don't like ignorers.
Love your vitamins.
Not as good as the Indian, but still lovely vitamins.
So, if I don't get vitamins from this,
how am I going to get vitamins? H
How am I going to vage? [cough] [snorts] Oh gosh,
the beef is lovely. Oh gosh. Mhm.
No, you didn't answer my question. H [snorts] [ __ ] off.
He's mugging us off. He's on the channel
with Steven Allen.
Please don't skin virgin shadow. Oh,
I don't trust you. Steen Allen.
He's going on the virgin's channel virgin.
He's never had sex. He's a virgin. Big
virgin. Big virgin boy.
He's not one of the bubs anymore.
I think he's trying to [ __ ] us over with
the skin bird in those juven Howard copycat. Copycat. Never mind. Nothing.
You're laughing by copy.
He knows you're a copy.
You stop my Chinese copy that
left out your virgin. Mhm.
>> [clears throat]
>> The virgin [ __ ]
Come on, Ch.
Launch your version. [clears throat]
I'm a little pupp.
I want to do a video to virgin boy after
why it's such a proper
it doesn't make you look big. It doesn't
make you look clever.
It doesn't mean you're going to lose
your virginity any faster by simply a copy. Hm.
Why you need to copy the crowd? Why? Huh?
I want to know why you need a copy.
And it's my right to ask.
Pop it out. Oh, cop out. All right.
I want to know. I just got some beef
noodles and some chicken and fried rice.
And you have to rise tomorrow. You saw. You're not
flopping in the ground.
One is a bloody well fit. your burden.
Why you say anything to fit in with a brown
[clears throat] and I'll explain the
story. I brought her up to bloody puppy.
I saw it in between us as well. Then you
started saying it
in your little virgin bed. [snorts]
Your little virgin bed out in London.
I don't want to know why you such a copycat.
Nothing wrong with being a copycat.
We usually got a copy today.
What if you like big what you like big
[ __ ] big black women?
What if you like big black women or big
blond women? That still make you gay. Boy,
I'm doing a video, mate. Because I've
been wondering all day, why you keep copying
copying the clouds? It doesn't make you look good.
Call them people that have had more
women than you guys because they don't
copy the crowd.
Why am I going copy?
Cuz I got mine in my [ __ ] hand.
The students need to say to each other.
I'm not letting this lie. I'm doing a
video, mate. I'm doing a video.
I'm sick of these little copycats.
No, I'm going to do a video upstairs.
I want to know why he's such a copycat.
Why he has to fit in with the crowd?
You little copycat. What if you like big
[ __ ] demon women?
What if you like Jamaican women? What if
you like white women with freckles? That
mean you're still [ __ ] gay, mate? [ __ ] copy.
Doesn't make you look good. Just makes
you look like even more of a virgin and
you always will die once.
No, I want to know why virgin boy says a copycat. M
even even if you got kids, even if you
even if you're in a relationship, you're
still gay, mate. Copy.
No, I'm not I'm not leaving. I'm sick of
this little copycat
copy in the crowd, you know.
Copy in the crowd. The loser cubby.
You little copycat
playing it all day. You little copycat.
No, I just want to know why he he he
feels the need to copy.
He's copied the crowd.
He said if you don't See,
you didn't say anything about
all the other women that I've been with
and stuff and women that you've seen cuz
that they didn't have the same name. You know, copy
classic 20 [ __ ] 12 trend.
Pull someone gay.
Call someone [ __ ] gay.
>> No, I want to do a little video to a
little copycat. [snorts]
A little copycat.
Virgin boy hasn't posted, but he hasn't responded.
Why does he feel the need to copy?
Why does he have to copy the crowd? Be
original. Be unique. Don't be a copycat.
Hate copycats, man.
You don't understand how much I hate cats.
I [ __ ] hate cats, man.
Look at this.
There we go.
That's what coming saying. Yeah. Copycat. Copycat. Copycat.
I I want you I want you to walk in.
Yeah. I want you to walk in. Yeah. I
want him to walk in tomorrow
with a Halloween costume.
With like a little Halloween costume.
And everyone can shout him being like this. Copycat.
What do you think? Copycat. Copycat.
Steven Howard. Why did you say if I
don't find her attractive that makes me gay?
What a weird thing to say.
Uh, on my end, it seems you already know
what to do. You're just afraid to do it.
If you really want someone, then pursue them.
Why do you keep just missing my
struggles? [ __ ] all you bastards. I'm
going to do this little experiment cuz
I've had a bloody enough of it now. I'm
going to do this experiment
cuz everyone just keeps dismissing my
bloody struggles. So [ __ ]
do it to fit in with the crowd. Yeah.
Is that funny how everyone says the same
[ __ ] as you copy that? They don't say
about anyone else. Look at that.
I'm sick of these people.
Sick of these people dismissing my
bloody struggles. I've had a bloody
enough. I'm in my little nest now. Oh gosh.
Don't be crazy. Never.
I like to walk out.
Of course you do. You little copycat.
You little cupcake.
Yeah, I did.
cops. [clears throat] Yep.
What do you think of Sher K leaving out?
She's so attractive. Oh my god,
he's so good looking. Oh, what do you think?
So good looking.
Had about 100 wanks over her today.
So attractive. Oh my god.
What do you think?
So good looking. Oh my god.
Would you get with a
If you don't like her, you're [ __ ] gay. homo, lad. People
that say that are copycats
My name is not greasy. I'm a little copycat. Yeah.
Well, I'm gone yet. I'll see you tomorrow.