You all right? You absolute virgins.
You know who you people are when I'm
calling you, mate. Yeah. You absolutely.
You know who you are.
You know who you You [ __ ] are, mate.
You absolute virgins.
You absolute virgin.
That's my favorite saying now, matey.
Did you pull it up, mate? Yeah. Good,
mate. Oh, thank you, mate. Good, mate. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah. You all right? You absolute virgins.
All right, Triple H. I was out yesterday
a few beers playing a game of pool if
you don't mind. It reminded me of you
with the darts. Yeah.
even do a football bet today?
No, I didn't do
well. Bless you. Well, I went out
yesterday. I didn't go out today. I I
was only out for like a couple of hours.
Only spent about 30 quid. I didn't go out today. Yeah.
But yeah, I'll be off this uh community
next week cuz it's December and I'll be
going out. I'll be going out more. So
yeah, detox would have been full. I had
a drink yesterday. I had a couple of
Guinnesses yesterday and yeah, I won't
be on it for a while cuz I'm going to be
busy. So I hope you people are not on
YouTube. I don't want to see you people
on bloody YouTube when I come back.
No, I just said I didn't have a football bet.
>> I woke up at like 2:00 and I couldn't be
bothered to go to the bookies. I would
have lost anyways. So,
I don't live near the bookies, bro.
That food was yummy. Oh, that food was yummy, bro.
I was absolutely starving. Starving, Marvin.
Little ky cat. [snorts]
when he was live then he deleted it. [snorts]
It's nice man. It's nice. Yeah.
Yeah. I was on Reddit yesterday. They
were dismissing my struggles again as usual.
Dismissing people's struggles is their
favorite thing, isn't it?
Used to it by now. Delayed. Yeah.
But I don't even feel like I've even got
the energy to go out anymore drinking
and approaching. Bro, I swear down. I
don't even feel like I'm not looking
forward, bro. I'm not I'm not forward
I'm not looking forward to tomorrow,
bro. Next week. I'm not looking forward to it.
Toxic Women. Oh no. I've been enjoying
my break so much. I'm not looking
forward to it. The mind games are leading on
road man. I'm not looking forward to it.
Oh, you know the Reddit mods, apparently
they don't get paid, you know.
>> Yeah, apparently they don't get paid.
Don't p I've never had that. Yeah,
apparently they don't get paid.
That's what I heard. They don't get paid.
I'm thinking what? They don't get Yeah,
apparently they don't get paid.
Road man, you know, um Reddit, why do
they ban people so easy?
You know, like Instagram and Facebook
and YouTube, you don't get banned
easily, but on Reddit, they'll just like
ban you and then IP ban you and be cryb
babies. It's so easy to get banned off Reddit.
[clears throat and snorts] But yeah,
they don't even get paid for it. If
that's true, they really have got no
life. If they really don't get paid for
that, they really have got no life.
I think it was just a bunch of people
that's been bullied
that um take their frustrations out of
you. A bit like this community with
these little self injectors. There's
people that's been bullied.
Hope there's people that have been
bullied. I think it's similar to Yeah.
Yeah. That's similar to here. This community
remind myself a couple of come
little self projectors. Yeah.
Self projecting fat ugly people.
[ __ ] Did you see what I had for tea? Grezy.
Oh, my coat come by the way. My lovely
coat come. Grezy.
Um, well, to be fair, there was two
people that blamed me.
Yeah, no one cares about that virgin.
Don't bring them up on this channel,
bro. No one cares about these little clowns.
Stop bringing it up on this channel. No
one cares about them.
Um, so two people did.
and another thing is trip uh grezy is
also that it's not what people say, it's
what people don't say. So if you post if
you post right about like men, a lot of
them just won't reply. Like a lot of
them just won't reply. But if you say
stuff about women, they will.
Someone on Reddit was dismissing my
struggles again yesterday. Grezy.
Triple H also dismisses my struggles.
That's their favorite thing, isn't it?
Just ignorant people in it, Grievy.
They're just ignorant people.
Very ignorant. But yeah, they definitely
just You know what? I f I fancy an Oreo
milkshake. You know,
an Oreo milkshake. Oh, can't beat a nice
Oreo milkshake. I only get it from certain places. Oh, we
Oh, I've been having a lot of milk lately,
corn flakes, coppers. I'm addicted to milk.
I feel like I'm addicted to milky like a cat.
Now my quote is sick. You won't find
somebody with the same brand. Yeah, I
can buy Canada Goose. Yeah, I can afford
Canada Goose. But everyone wears Canada
goose greasy. And I'm not a copycat. I
was born with a mind of my own. Unlike some people
unlike some people. That's the copy.
Not mention any names, but you won't
find anyone with that same brand and
that same color.
You won't find any anyone with anything
that I wear because I'm not a copycat.
So bless you, Grezy. Food is always on
your mind. When I when I was picking up
the food tend uh the tandoori chicken, I
went to order it, Grezy, and my belly
was rumbling. My face was my my eyes
were on the oven. Wait, I was waiting
for the tandoori chicken to come out. I
was so hungry.
My belly was rumbling. Oh gosh.
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up. You know,
my eyes was on the oven.
Yeah. Oh, yeah. Milkshakes. Nice.
Now I fancy some cornflakes. I'm
addicted to milky. What is it with me and milk?
It's milk teas. [ __ ] what is it with
me and milk, bro? I can never be a
[ __ ] I can never be a [ __ ] um
vegan then, can I?
I love milky.
Why do you think that is?
Don't know why. I just love milk.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, man. I was in my
little nesticles today, Grezy.
I was in my little nesticles.
It was so cozy. I don't want to get out of it.
You know what's nice? A can of Coke with
a meal. You can't beat a can of Coke
with a meal.
I need to stop drinking Coke. I need to
change my diet though, bro, cuz my teeth
are going to get [ __ ] My gums are
never going to get better. If I don't If
I don't stop drinking Coke and sugar and
stuff, my gums are never going to get
They're always going to be [ __ ] But
I'm surprised it never happened sooner
with all the coke I used to drink every
day. To be honest,
I don't think you understand how bad
Coke is for you. Very very very very
bad. Very bad.
I have to drink water and vegetables for
a little while. You know,
[ __ ] you up. That will, bro. But I'm I'm
addicted to sugar. Greasy. I'm going to
make I'm going to make a I'm going to
make some bastard cornflakes.
Hi, UK silent. I've been drinking a lot
of milk lately. You know, cornflakes,
teas. I don't know why I love milk.
I don't know what it is with me and
milk. I feel like a baby.
I feel like a bubba. I just had a I just
had a [ __ ] whole tandoori chicken and
I fancy some bastard cornflakes. You know,
yeah, I'll be doing some approaches next
week. UK asylum. What do you reckon is
going to happen?
Do you reckon it'll be any different next week?
Oh, you never guess what, Grey? There
was this person on Reddit
and she was like, "Oh, anything can
change at any time."
I said, "Really? I mean, this has been
going on for years." Then she said, "Oh,
yeah. I've been homeless." I mean, be being homeless.
But I found out a million times before
UK asylum, and it's always the same old.
I mean, being being uh being uh
uh being homeless and getting yourself
out of being homeless is a bit different
than dealing with toxic stuck up women.
I mean, I think there's a big difference
because I've technically been homeless
and I've lost everything and it gets
better within 3 months. So, what's that
got to do with dating? I don't
understand what's that got to do with
like it's this has been going on for
years, you know, [ __ ] years. You know
what I mean? Grievous.
They're going to be telling you the same
thing when you're a 50y old man. It's ridiculous.
It's really, really ridiculous. I don't
know why they
why they dismiss people's struggles, but they do.
But yeah, they definitely definitely do
dismiss people's struggles.
It's so obvious
to break dismisses my struggles.
People on Reddit do.
But when I was pretending to be a woman,
some people saying that I'm a female.
I'm a female um version of an incel, but
that was one person. So yeah, you might
get one person that's impartial, but for
the most part, people will either feel
sorry for you or they just won't say
anything at all.
Probably won't say anything at all, to
be honest. But if you're a man
complaining about women, boy, you better
run away, mate, because people will be
going after you. So,
they just won't say anything. If you're
a woman that complains about men, they
just won't say nothing really.
They'll just say, "Oh,
do this, do that, or work on yourself."
But they won't blame you like they will
blame you if you're a man. If that makes sense. So, yeah.
You even get people inboxing you.
So anyways, yeah, did you put a bet on today?
A lot of it is. Yeah.
She was saying to me, this woman on
Reddit was like, "Oh, you got to think
positive." But I said, "My experiences
have been bad for years and years and
years road man things.
Like I've had bad experiences for
[ __ ] years and it doesn't stop.
And they're still telling me to be positive.
But then if you're positive, you're
going to get let down.
Cuz if you're positive, then the same
thing's going to happen again and then
you're negative. Whereas if you think
the worst, you're not going to be let
down, are you? So would it make more
sense to think negative than positive?
Because if you think positive, negative
is going to happen. At
least if you're negative,
then you you know you know
it's never going to change. I don't know
how these people on Reddit think it's
going to change. Red M road man,
they seem to think one day you're going
to go out and it's going to be different.
That's why I don't go out, bro. It's not
because of this [ __ ] indigo saying I
can't afford it. Of course I can afford
to go out. I can go out whenever the
[ __ ] I want. Got the money to do it.
Nothing to do with that [ __ ] all,
mate. I'd rather stay in Esticles and
not have any more bad experiences. Logical, right? It's logical.
I think so. Anyways,
I can go out whenever I want, mate.
It's not worth it any It's never worth it.
It's not It's not worth it. It's never
worth it, bro. It's always going to be
the same old.
It's not worth dealing with westernized
women. I went out yesterday. I played
some pool. I had a few Guinnesses and I went home.
I don't want to.
You get so used to the peace and quiet,
you just don't want to change it cuz you
know exactly what's going to happen
again when you start talking to women.
You know exactly exactly what's going to happen.
And I don't really want to put myself
through it again.
You know, that's what I'm saying. And it
will never be different. Despite what
people say, despite people saying that
they're not all the same, we know
different. But we no different. So that's that. Yeah.
50 a night out. Really?
Not for me. It's not.
I do one 150. I don't spend 250 on a
night out. What the [ __ ] 350 on a night
I've never spent that all one night.
Only when I booked a hotel and I was gambling.
Only when I was gambling and booked a hotel
spent like 700 night.
Well, yeah, I don't do cocaine.
That's maybe why
it's just so toxic. That's the thing.
It's not even a pressing road, man. It's
just toxic. Trying to date is so toxic.
The lies, the [ __ ] the leading on.
It's [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Every time, you know.
It's bad, isn't it?
Just sick of it. Yeah.
It's so expensive for that as well. Road man things
people on Reddit
people on Reddit seem to think I've got hope.
Yeah. What makes me laugh is all the
people that make excuses for them
just for having a [ __ ] in between their legs.
That never gets old that loud. That
never gets old. People that defend women.
Just for having a [ __ ] in between the legs.
It's comical, is it? Really, bro?
Not because they're wrong, not because
they're right. Just because they've
simply got a [ __ ] in between their legs.
Mad, isn't it? [ __ ] mad.
They had an argument on a train the
other day, road man, and this white
knight tried to get involved and his
head got crushed in the door. Madness.
All because he's trying to defend a
woman that's never going to sleep with
him. They don't like him. that started
it as well. Mad. Yeah.
They defend women thinking that these
women are going to let them hit. Mad.
>> It is mad, isn't it? That
What makes me laugh when they say that
women aren't all the same road man things?
They say women aren't all the same.
I can't believe people are still saying
that women aren't all the same.
That's mad how people could even say
that to be honest.
They're definitely all the same.
Definitely all the same.
They're all [ __ ] They're toxic.
They're narcissists. They're time
wasters. They've all got the same
attitude as well. But you'll notice that
with these women, bro, that they've all
got the same attitude for people that
are apparently not all the same, which
again, I can't work it out. So maybe if
you ever do, they're they're not all the
same, but they just say the same stuff,
have the same mannerisms, and have the same attitude.
But they're not all the same. Mad.
I'm dreading next week, bro. I'm
dreading next week.
Absolutely dreaded next week.
It'll be my first time out for like
three weeks a month. I just gave up with it, bro.
I just gave up with it.
I don't know, man. I don't really want
to. I might not, to be honest. I said I
was going to go out with my sister and
stuff, but I don't know, bro. Maybe I
won't. But I have to, cuz I can't let people down.
No thoughts on what I've just said the
past 10 minutes or did you completely dismiss it?
People seem to love dismissing my struggles.
I do you know what? I might have to go
to a doctor's and see if they can hear
my voice properly
because you don't seem to hear what I'm
saying. So maybe maybe there's something
wrong with my voice or something, you know.
Warm up for what?
To warm up for what exactly?
I'm I'm not scared to approach. Why am I warming up?
I don't even like talking about this.
This is depressing, bro. I might not
even go out next week, to be honest. I
don't know, man. It's too depressing.
We've been planning this for ages, but I
don't think I will go out next week,
bro. It's just too depressing.
I honestly would rather do nothing.
That's how bad it is. I would rather sit
in bed and do nothing than than date again.
I'd rather sit there and do nothing.
I'd actually at this age now where I am
now, I'd rather sit and do nothing
cuz it's just depressing
and the hope is already lost. You don't
need to lose any more hope. The hope is
already lost. So there is no good women
out there. There's no women out there
that are different. You've been giving
people the benefit of doubt for years. So yeah,
I need to change my diet as well cuz my gums,
not my weight, but my gums. Otherwise,
it's never going to get better.
No, but I fancy one. I might get I might
get a milkshake, you know. I do fancy one.
Yeah, I might get one, you know.
But I really fancy a milkshake.
I'm going to order one of it. I think uh
what's the point of being born with No,
I'm going to get a I'm going to get a
peanut butter milkshake. road man.
What's the point of being born with a
dick if you can't use it? Pointless, isn't it? Mom,
are you getting a milkshake? Do you want one? You sure? All right.
My coat come by the way. One sec.
Oh, it's here.
One second, please. Bro, I need to do this.
I get Oreo, but I prefer peanut butter.
I don't want cream on it.
But I'll probably put cream on it. But
it doesn't matter anyways
because I'm not a little copycat. You're
not a little copycat. No, I'm not a
Yeah. You sure you don't want one?
You sure you don't want one, Captain?
You sure you don't want to milkshake? Chocolate one.
>> All right, mama. >> Yeah. Boy
[ __ ] with a bed of [ __ ] money in it. >> [snorts] >> Right. Okay.
Right. I got the coke come by the way.
Yeah. I got a nice milkshake.
Yeah. The clock come. I'll show you it.
Yeah, I like it. Me
You're probably wondering what [ __ ]
what brand is this? What brand is this?
What brand is this, lads?
The quality is okay, but it's hard to do
the sip up some reason.
It's good. I like it, man. I'm not a little copycat.
You know, if I was a little copycat,
I'd be getting can I'd be getting Canada goose.
I'm trying to sip it up, but it's hard
to sip it up.
Nah, it's so hard to sip it up, bro. I
don't know what's wrong with it.
Might be a bit stiff.
Jack Jones. Uh, no it's not Jack Jones.
You [ __ ] It's actually six silk. One second.
It's hard to sip it up, bro. I don't know why.
Never won Jack Jones in my life.
It is hard to sip it up though.
Don't know why.
Yeah, she done it for me earlier.
Doesn't tip up.
Might be a certain way of doing it.
But my hands are clean.
Well, this kite was
90 pound. So,
here we go.
No, you can't even sip it up, bro.
We done it earlier, but I don't know why
it's not sipping up.
There you go. See,
I like it. But I'm not a little copycat.
>> Yeah, I don't I don't wear I don't wear
Canada Goose. I'm not a copycat.
I'm not a little copycat. I've got mine
on my own.
I like it, mate. I've got a mine on my
own. I'm not a little copycat. I don't
follow the crowd.
I'm not a little copycat.
Obviously with the jeans
um with the jeans and the trainers and
obviously I'm going to get my haircut as
well. So yeah, but again I'm not a little copycat.
I don't sit there and say, "Oh, I like
Sher Cole cuz she's attractive." Cuz I'm
not a copycat. I've got a mind of my own
and I'm not insecure.
You don't find Sher Cole. You're
attractive. You little copycat. Only
copycats say that stuff. Road man things.
It won't stain, bro. Because I I'll take
it to the dry cleaners every couple of months.
It won't, lad. There's a thing called
Vanish. Trust me, it will stay white
with me, lad.
It was only £90. Yep.
I just don't feel like ever trying
again. Doing the approaches road, man.
I just can't be bothered with it anymore.
Indigo is trying to say cuz I don't have
money. Of course I've got [ __ ] money.
I can do what the [ __ ] I want.
But I'd rather do nothing.
I'd rather do nothing, bro.
Stay in bed and [ __ ] chill and watch
some [ __ ] Why is it coming undone now
with it, bro?
My fingers are got tandoori chicken on
it, but it's like dry. Okay, here we go.
I thought it was unusual. It was nice.
It's so unusual. That's nice, you know.
That's why I bought it.
Oh, the Hilfiger coat's perfect by the
way. Steven Howard is perfect. Laney
done something to it. It's perfect now.
But oh well, I got another coat in it. She's attractive. >> Copycat.
Everyone needs a point when he walks in.
Yeah. Everyone needs to point. Copycat.
No mine of your own. Copycat.
Everyone needs everyone needs to do that
cuz you got no mind of your bloody own.
He's saying that to fit in with the crowd.
To fit in with the crowd.
Do you remember that um shovel cold
trend road man things? If you don't find
shovel co attractive, you're gay.
They're little copycats when we used to
copy each other.
Do you remember that one lad
when they all used to copy each other to
fit in? They done it with Beyonce as well.
That's where the skin virgin got the trend from.
I I I said to him, "Have you heard about
this Cheryl car?
People keep copying each other, saying
that she's good-looking." He's like,
"She's attractive. You can't deny that.
You're gay." The little virgin was
trying to say I'm gay.
Why? Because I'm not a copycat and I got
a mind of my own. Unlike you, you skin virgin.
Doesn't make someone [ __ ] gay.
It just makes them got a mind of their
own. Someone that's not a copycat.
>> Some transgender looking [ __ ] average
looking woman with no tits is not
attractive to is not attractive to me,
mate. And again, I'm not a copycat.
I don't say things to fit in like that virgin.
You know what I mean? Like gay.
You gay. That's what he said. He said I was gay.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> Yeah, road man.
Um, it's £5 a Guinness. The place I was
at yesterday was5 a Guinness. That's a
bargain cuz I normally pay £8 a Guinness. So,
yeah, that's not too bad to be honest. 5
pound of Guinness. So, yeah.
All right. Five pound of goodness, mate.
I can't wait for this milkshake. Little copycat.
You little copycat.
You a little copycat.
You little copycat. Little copycat.
You little copycat. I need to start
using escorts again though. Road man.
There's no point being born with a dick
if you can't use it. Is it?
I'm going to have to start using these
escorts soon, bro. I don't want to have to, but
What's the Highlands in Scotland though?
What's the point of being born with a
dick if you can't use it? Road man,
what's the point being [ __ ] born with
a dick if you can't even use it?
Never understood what was the point of
having a dick if you can't use it. >> [snorts]
>> It'd be even worse if he was a virgin.
I see somebody delivering food in
Edinburgh. I watch some um delivery
channels and this guy was delivering in
Edinburgh and it looks nice, bro. I've
been there a couple of times. Yeah, it's
nice Edinburgh. The Christmas market
look good as well,
but I'll never go back to Scotland. No need.
Nope, it was the other one.
It wasn't London each. It was London
Hustle. But yeah,
there's two of them.
Yeah, there's two of them. And what I
don't like about that London Hustle is
he doesn't say
he doesn't say how much he earns.
Yeah, his name's London Hustle. It's not
London Eats. London Eats is another one,
but he doesn't say how much he earned.
Whereas London Eats says that says how
much he does earn
which is [ __ ] because the Ginger one
doesn't say how much he earned, which is
which he should do because that's like
he doesn't say how much. So it's like we
don't even know how much he earned.
There's London Eats and London Hustle. I
just watch London Hustle.
Yeah, he's No, man.
Yeah, there's two of them. There's a few
channels that do that. Yeah.
How old do you think he is? Do you think
he's older than me?
Yeah, maybe the same age as me in it.
Yeah, he was living in Edinburgh. He
drove up there as well. That's mad.
[ __ ] drove up there. [ __ ] that, bro.
This milkshake has cost me 8 quid.
Why did this indigo say that I don't
have as much money? Because I don't get
as much money. I can't afford to go out
now. Of course, I can afford to go out
every week if I want to.
I can afford to go out every week if I
want to. Road man. Yes, I absolutely can.
I absolutely can if I wanted to. Greasy.
I absolutely can.
Yes, I [ __ ] well can if I wanted to.
This is the problem with people in this
community, bro. They they talk to pe
they talk about people that they don't know
and they get proven wrong every time and
then they still think they know about
other people's lives. It's just a proper
spasticated community really. That's why
I don't go out cuz it's not worth going out.
Why Why are you telling me to send it
when we've just been speaking for half
an hour about what women are like?
We've literally been speaking about what
women are like for the past half an hour.
So why are you telling me to send it
when you know exactly what's going to
happen when I do?
You already know what's going to happen.
Oh, okay. Yeah, that's different. Yeah,
I might just work, bro. To be honest,
I'd rather [ __ ] work than go out
drinking now. To be honest, it's [ __ ] dead.
It's [ __ ] dead, bro. The last time I
went out was like [ __ ] two and a half
weeks ago. [ __ ] that [ __ ] bro.
But I can go out whenever I want.
Once you get your haircut, you're
spending what? 150 a week going out drinking. Yeah,
it's not worth going out. You might as
well Yeah. Just Yeah. Like you said, travel.
Sure. I like to go out rarely, like rarely. But
I didn't go out cuz I wanted to save the
money in November as well. It made more
sense not going out December uh November
to save the money for November.
It seems to have made it seem to have
made more sense.
I need to buy a phone as well. That £250
phone. I got a few things to do do
before I can really save properly. Yeah.
I'll be out on Saturday anyways. Next
Saturday. So, we'll see.
You can't deny she's attractive. Attractive.
>> I can't get out of my head, bro.
You was born your own person. Why copy?
Why copy the crowd? That's what losers do. Copy.
Come on here and and explain why he copies.
I just want to know why somebody feels
the need to copy
what someone gets out of like copying.
You know what I'm saying? Triple H. I
would just love to know why somebody
would feel the need to copy
to copy the crowd.
Why copy the crowd?
Why not just have a [ __ ] mind of your
[ __ ] own, little copycat?
You know what I'm saying? No, Triple H.
Like, why not just have a mind of your [ __ ] own
and not be a copycat?
You know, come on here and explain why you copy
why you copy the crowd.
Boozy, can you comment on the channel, please,
and ask him to come on here and explain
why he's such a copycat?
I'm not [ __ ] being friends with that [ __ ] virgin.
That skin out of London virgin. [ __ ] out
of it. I'm not [ __ ] I can't be
friends with virgins.
You need to go crazy, can you do it?
Please go on the channel and just say,
can you come on here? cuz I think he's
got everyone blocked. And explain why
you're being why you're such a copycat.
Uh, Grezy, please. Please, mate.
And just ask him why he's such a copycat.
No, it's he said that if you don't find
Cheryl Co attractive, you're gay. That's copying.
That's copying the crowd.
That's copying the crowd. That's
anything to try to fit in with the crowd.
That's what I'm saying.
You little copycat.
You little copy. I [ __ ] I I'll
I [ __ ] throw you, mate. I [ __ ]
throw you, you little copycat. I [ __ ]
throw you. You little copycat.
You little copycat. I was going to do a
Kitty Minister and Enfield Town today
and guess what? They both scored.
But Slow never scored. So
Oh, [ __ ] hell, man.
You need to stop trying to troll cuz you
suck at it. Triple H.
You need to stop trying to troll because
you suck at it.
Even Dusty Showiz is better than you. Yeah,
you need to stop. But you're bad at it,
lads. [ __ ] bad at it. You know what?
I don't even think there is anyone on
here that's actually good at trolling.
That could actually psychologically [ __ ]
with someone's head. I generally don't
think there is.
You need to stop trolling, bro. You're
bad at it to the point where I'm trying
to like I'm feeling sorry for you.
Okay. Well, moving on anyways. We're not
getting into that.
I've told you a million times I don't
date disabled people.
I don't date disabled people. Disabled
people don't count as girlfriends.
And I've been laid more times than
[ __ ] you, lad. So yeah, you need to
get laid as well.
Anyways, we're going to have to block
you soon. Anyways, bro, if you keep this
up, Chipper H. You're doing what they do
on Monty's chat,
bringing up people, bringing up idiots.
So, if you carry this on, lad, you might
have to get blocked.
I want him to come on here so explain
why he's copying the crowd.
Don't talk about [ __ ] nonsense. I
want to know why he feels need to be a copycat.
Can somebody tell this copycat to come on here?
They're still being [ __ ] prepared. Nope.
Nope. I wouldn't.
Yeah, I'll put them box out later, bro.
Where's this [ __ ] milkshake? Uh, you
little you little big big virgin.
Why do you keep bringing up these
idiots, Trip H? This is why you get banned.
Bringing up [ __ ] idiots all the time.
That's why you get banned because you
bring up idiots. Yeah.
No, it's all right. Can you just tell
him to come on his channel, please, and
discuss why he's such a copycat? Triple
Yeah. Can you [ __ ]
can you [ __ ] um
get this copycat on here and explain why
he copies people,
why he thinks that people are gay if
they don't find a transgender looking
[ __ ] with no tits attractive.
Doesn't make you look good. It doesn't
make you look clever. It makes you just
look like someone that has to copy and
people people don't have respect for
them kind of people really.
Not anymore he doesn't.
Not anymore he doesn't. Anyways, are you
going to get the copycat in here or not?
The little copycat. >> Triple.
>> Triple H. Triple H. Triple H. >> No. Ow.
>> He tried calling the police on me the
other day. The police told him to [ __ ] off.
[ __ ] virgin. [clears throat]
The police told the [ __ ] little
virgin to [ __ ] off.
They said [ __ ] off. Basically, in other
words, they said [ __ ] off.
But I need to go out next week cuz me
and my sister's been planning it for
months and months and months. So, and
it's only local, so I don't mind.
But then I think I'm going to go out New
Year's Eve. 100% I'm going out New
Year's Eve. I don't know where yet,
but that will basically be it now. It
will only be like special occasion occasions.
Yeah, New Year's Eve, I think, will be
the next time.
I'm definitely going out of London. Like
I said, I don't know where, but I'm
definitely going out of London 100%.
Well, New Year's Eve, I definitely am
getting out of London, bro. I've been
saying this for ages. Years. I've been
saying this. New Year's Eve. Got to go
somewhere else New Year's Eve. I'm going
to go somewhere else.
And I'd love to just spend somewhere
else New Year's Eve. You know,
I've always wanted to do it. Greasy.
Yeah, I'm out New Year's Eve, lad.
I might go Nottingham. I might go
Cardiff. I might go Liverpool. I might
flip a coin where I'm going. I
definitely want to go somewhere out New
Year's Eve. Definitely always wanted to
do it. Always wanted to do it. So, I'm
going to have to book these trains soon,
I'm guessing, because it's going to be Choa Block.
Even if it's just like Nottingham or
somewhere, just anywhere but London.
would just be lush.
But then it's getting back in it. Can
you Can you come back the next day?
I'll have to look. I'll have to look.
I'll have to look. But I'm sure
even just like Cardiff, even Cardiff is
fine. New Year's
I've always wanted to do go somewhere else. Yep.
Is that is that all right with you greed
if I go somewhere else New Year's Eve?
Okay with you, boss.
Is that okay with you, boss?
Okay with you, Captain.
Oh, I'm waiting for my little milkshake.
Doesn't have to be too far, Greavves. It
could be anywhere. Cardiff, Nottingham,
Manchester, just somewhere else.
I want someone to be wishing me a happy
new year when I'm out out the city, you know.
I would go Scotland, but it's too far.
It's too far.
One second. I'm having a big poo.
Scotland's too far greasy.
That London Hustle said that's his first
time in Scotland. I've been there a
couple of times. Not for years though.
You got a lot of tips up there in it. Yeah.
No, I'm not going to Scotland. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that, bro. What day is it? One
second. What day is
But no one's going to see. It'll be good
if See, if New Year's Eve is like a
Saturday or Friday, it'll be good.
It will be good because you can go out
the two days. One second. Let me look up
what what day it is. It is
It's a Wednesday.
Yeah, it's a Wednesday.
Yeah, it's a Wednesday. Oh, see, if it
was like a Saturday, you could have went
out the Friday and the Saturday. You see
what I mean? But I mean, it's going to
be busy either way, ain't it? But it's a Wednesday.
Do that [ __ ] virgin.
trip. Do you remember can you live off
500 pound a month? He was like obvious obviously not
you remember that he was like obviously not
obviously not it. [laughter]
I'm [ __ ] still waiting on the can.
Obviously not in it.
He was like obviously not in it. You
said because you buy your son stuff isn't it?
>> Yeah. You said because you buy your son stuff.
All right. One second, bro.
It's still saying it's being prepared.
It must be busy today.
So, I had a whole tandoori chicken
today. Now I'm having a lovely milkshake.
Where did the milk come from?
Did it come from boobies? Grezy.
There we go.
It should be on way, bro. What the [ __ ]
It was only a milkshake.
Cost me£8 quid. They're normally6. So it
was only like two pound for delivery.
That's all right though, mate. We're not
skin. We're not a Skint virgin from out
of London. Should be all right. Should
be all right. Should be all right. Yeah,
we're not a skin virgin from out of London,
so it should be just all right. Yeah.
8 quid, which is how much I could find
the Guinness, isn't it?
I'm not going to [ __ ] Asda. I'm tired.
[ __ ] tired, lad.
I'll be playing some pool next Saturday again.
Can someone get this copycat on here?
Come on. Can someone get this [ __ ]
copycat on here? I'm going to unblock
him. One second. Can someone get this
[ __ ] copycat on here, lad?
He's unblocked. So, can you get him on here,
Triple? Can you get him on here?
I've got I've No, no, no link. Type in.
No link. Type in, mate.
I want to know why he copies. He doesn't
make you look clever. He just makes you
look like a copycat virgin that you are.
She's still a virgin.
You still you still can't get anything
normal. No matter how many times you
say, "Oh, S's attractive." You can't
deny that. You know, you know you know.
Why do you say that I've got money to
burn Steven Howard?
>> Well, we have been winning a lot on the
football, haven't we? So,
we've been winning a lot on the football. So, yeah. [ __ ] hell.
Come the [ __ ] on.
I am guilty. Steven Howard. Guilty. I
know. I am guilty. I'm not denying it.
I'm not denying it. I'm guilty. Guilty,
mate. Guilty. Guilty, mate.
But obviously I'm not from Kent, am I?
I'm not from Kent, so I can afford it. Yeah,
I need to stop, bro.
coat, takeaways, trainers, jeans.
It's nice to have the money. It's nice
to have the money to
do it, you know.
Should have about 1,500 smackaroonies, mate,
with all my bills paid for.
And all my bills paid.
Yep. All my bills paid as well.
Also get And I also get carers allowance as well.
So you all right?
You'll never beat me. Red store. Peter
Betty will always have money. Oh, is
that funny, mate? I just ain't been
going out because I ain't been wanting
to go out.
You didn't [ __ ] my income up, mate. You
never beat Peter Belly. Never.
S little bastard.
Yeah, I know, man.
Red Star definitely definitely
definitely didn't stop my income, mate.
But serious, um, yeah,
nice little 1,500.
But I need to buy I need to buy some
food. I need to buy buy some food. I
need to buy this £250 phone,
the one I had before, brand new. So
yeah, man. So it's not a problem.
I don't want that [ __ ] virgin join
in. I want him to come on here and type
and explain why he's such a copycat
that says Sher Cole was attractive to
fit in. I want to know why he's such a copycat.
Why are you such a copycat?
Such a little copycat.
Yeah, I'll do some approaches on
Saturday. Not a problem.
Not a problem at all.
And that's me done for New Year's Eve. So, yeah.
Yeah, he's pushing her about saying,
"Why can't you give me no sex? I've been
with you for years and I'm still a
bloody virgin and you won't sleep with me." Virgin,
you remember when he stalked you and
say, "Is he the virgin, Steven Howard?
Such a virgin."
That Joseph Ferrar is a [ __ ] little
[ __ ] Little nons,
he's an absolute little [ __ ]
Oh, so go back to your [ __ ]
boyfriend's channel, you little nods
lover. You little biased nods lover. No,
it's on its way now. It's out for delivery.
You [ __ ] little nods lover.
I don't like cream on it, but there's
probably going to be cream on it. It's
not a problem. It's all right.
Joseph Ferrar is a non lover road man. I
never said he was a n. I said he was a
nons lover. If you actually heard me
properly, I said that you're a nons
lover. I didn't say you was a nons. I
said you were a nons lover. Cuz you are
No, he wasn't. Because when I was
calling that [ __ ] n a virgin, he
would go to his rescue like, "Oh, how
can he be a virgin when he's got a
girlfriend?" But he's got a girlfriend.
But then when I've proved I've had sex
on the video, he doesn't defend me. So I
said, "Fuck off, you little biased nods lover.
See you later, mate."
No, he's a nons lover, bro. He's a
non-slavver. He's a biased little nods
lover. Us brothers are not like that.
Didn't Didn't come to my rescue. No,
didn't come to my rescue when that
virgin was talking about me. So,
you don't think it's possible someone
with a disabled girlfriend could be a virgin? No.
Right. But, but what about me proving
I've had sex?
Right. But what about me proving I've had sex?
Uh, okay. But what about me proving I've
had sex? I don't see you on my channel.
I know he's absolutely not right. He's
never had sex. He's an absolute virgin.
And he's never proved he had he's had
sex. I have proved I've had sex. I have
proved I've had sex. He has never had
sex in his life. He's still a virgin.
He's He's a [ __ ] He's an absolute
virgin. Disabled girlfriend or no
disabled girlfriend. He's never had
[ __ ] since [ __ ] had him. I know all
the signs of a virgin
and he's the biggest one going. And him
showing a disabled girl does not prove
he's had sex. I'm not buying it. Unless
you actually prove that you have had
sex, you ain't, mate. I know a big
virgin when I see one. I know the
biggest virgin when I see one, mate. You
know him saying that I've not had sex
when I have. It's all cuz he's a big
virgin. Big virgin. and his dick don't
work because people that have have sex
with people don't sit there stalking
other women. It's all signs of a virgin.
I know all of these things and I don't
give a [ __ ] if he's got a disabled
girlfriend. He's not allowed near her sexually.
And disabled women don't have nades. And
he said, "Oh, don't you think people in
relationships have sex?" They do, but
you don't cuz you're still a virgin. Is
that is that is that a good Is that a
good impression for you, mate?
The escort stories
that you kept denying it was because he
was the biggest virgin. He's the
absolute one. He's the absolute little
dick virgin that's never had sex.
Didn't know at the time cuz I was only
[ __ ] 17, 18 cuz I wasn't the smart,
you know, I wasn't mature as I am now. I
said, "Oh, he's calling me a virgin
because he's one. He's projecting his
ugly face little dick onto you with his
notch stand. Oh, I got it now.
No, it doesn't trigger. It doesn't It
doesn't trigger me because he's talking
about himself. He's calling himself a
virgin cuz he's the biggest one going.
No, what triggers me is the biased
people like Joseph Ferrar, a biased
biased biased [ __ ] [ __ ]
And he needs to stop his [ __ ] bro,
because I'll just end up going to
[ __ ] Newcastle and calling the [ __ ]
out, mate. I might go Newcastle New
Year's Eve, actually. Oh, that's another
one. No, no, no. Actually, do you know
what? I might I might go Newcastle New Year's Eve.
Yeah, that's a good plan. Do you know
what? Scrap it. I might I'm going to go
Newcastle New Year's Eve. [ __ ] it.
That's the new plan now.
I'm going to call that Joseph Par.
I'll be like, "Come on, you fat ugly
man. Let's go. Let's Let's [ __ ] go, mate.
Even if I am a virgin. Yeah, I'm a
virgin, bro. Even though there's a video
of someone sucking my dick. Even though
there's videos of me in women's beds.
Yeah. I mean I mean I am a virgin. Yeah.
So what? Nothing wrong with being a virgin.
Yeah. Nothing wrong with being a virgin,
bro. I've never had sex. What does it
feel like? Is it good?
Yeah. You said that you're going to meet
me. You're not going to meet me, mate.
You're not going to meet me. I've been
to Newcastle three times and you never
met me. I've been to Newcastle three
times and you never met me, lad. I don't
think you're going to meet me, mate. I
really don't think you're going to meet me.
No, no, no, no. I've been to your city
three times, mate, and you didn't come
out. No. And neither did Cory, to be
fair. Cory never either.
I don't think you're going to beat me,
mate. I don't think so. I really don't.
I really don't, mate.
Yeah, I'm a virgin, bro. I'm a virgin.
Yeah, I know, bro. I'm a virgin. Can you
get me laid? Yeah,
I'm a virgin, bro.
Even though I proved I've had sex, made
a porno video. I'm a virgin, bro. Yeah.
What does it feel like? Sex.
Does anyone know what it feels like?
I've never had it before.
I'd give him a hug and a kiss.
I say, "Oh, I like your channel. I watch
your channels. I give him a hugle and a kiss." Yeah.
What makes me laugh is that these people
on here say they don't like nons, bro.
But they like nons. I'm not talking
about you. I'm talking genly. They say
they don't like nonsers like body man,
but they they support the biggest nons going.
Oh, you will, will you? All right, then.
We'll see about that.
I'm waiting for this milkshake. Oh gosh. Please. [clears throat]
So, Roadman, what is what's the point of
being born with a dick if you can't use
it? Road man seems pointless, isn't it?
Seems pointless, doesn't it? You know,
haven't had a bloody date since April.
No, man. I played I played
I haven't had a date since April.
basically does. Really
basically does. What's the point of
being born with a dick if you can't use it, you know?
Yeah. It does seem pointless.
People on Reddit say I'll meet someone. Don't
Yeah. People on Reddit say you'll meet someone.
What the [ __ ]
Why isn't this working? Yeah.
Yeah. But even the women they make Hey,
there was this woman on Reddit, Road
Man, and she said that she can't get
with me because I'm not Muslim and I'm
28 and she's 23 making up all of these
excuses. But then I found out that she'd
been with a 28-year-old before that
wasn't a Muslim. And I told her about it
and then she called me a stalker. Yeah.
Do you know what you'll find with women
um road man is that they're very um when
you speak to one they're never the same
the next day. For example, you could
speak to someone on Reddit on Instagram,
right? And you're talking right and then
they'll be saying all of this that and
then the next day you never hear from them again.
Strange, isn't it?
Yeah, I'm not a troll. I showed them my
I've got a main channel, you know, with
all my approaches on it. I showed them
it, but they keep dismissing it.
Yeah, they just miss people's struggles.
Yeah, they just miss people's struggles,
bro. I don't know why, but they do.
Yeah, they definitely definitely
definitely dismiss people's struggles.
100% they do.
They seem to ban your device. I use my
my mom's phone to uh I use my mom's
phone to go on Reddit.
I use my mom's phone to go on Reddit.
So, they seem to actually ban your
device from using it.
What is this strange?
They ban your um
they seem to be able to ban your device. Grezy,
I really hope this is not true about
these mods not being paid.
Nah, please don't tell me it's true that
these mods don't get paid.
Please don't tell me that it it's true
that these mods don't get paid because
at least if they get paid right
you know you can say okay if they earn
decent money then okay whatever
they're still losers but like please do
not tell me
they don't get paid Grezy because that
is sad as [ __ ] you know
but look at this Jamie Thompson loser
[ __ ] stalking me. Fat ugly bastard.
Have you seen him? That stalker? That
Jamie Thompson little failure. Stalking
me every day cuz I'm younger and better
looking at him. Sad [ __ ] bastard.
Sad [ __ ] ugly bastard.
Life's a loser in his 40s. Fat and
uglier. And look at me, bro. Younger
than him. Better looking than him. Mad [ __ ]
fat ugly monga.
Yeah, Triple H. Fat ugly [ __ ]
See, if I had a child, my child could
get on with your child, Triple H. But
it's too late now because the age gap
will be too will be too big. Me, you,
and LT's child. We could all have ch
children and our kids can play together
and be friends.
Oh, what a lovely sight, Grezy. If I had
a baby Peter, we could play with Triple
H's child. They could be friends. Oh, lovely.
And LT's child as well. Oh, lovely. Lovely. Really?
We could be best friends. Huh?
And uh my son could tell uh LT son how
his daddy almost killed me one day over YouTube.
Isn't that right? He could he could tell
him all about it.
Grezy. Oh, I could have I could have got
killed that day on YouTube.
Yeah, it's about 6 minutes away approximately.
Yeah, it's approximately 6 minutes away.
I hope this has got USA boobies milk in it.
I've been I've been drinking a lot of
milk lately. A lot of milky. Gosh.
Oh gosh. Oh,
come on. I want my bloody milkshake.
We're looking forward to this.
Yeah. Have you ever had a peanut butter
milkshake, Grezy? They're [ __ ] lovely. Yep.
Elephant and Castle is where you met
your mama. Grezy. Elephant and Castle is
where you met your mama.
It's where you met your mama.
Is that where you met your mama?
Yeah, it is.
Elephant and Castle is where I met my mama.
Because he's already found his mama.
That's so immature, is it? No, that's
immature, bro. You don't think that's immature, Grezy?
Cuz he's already found his mama.
Sig is not Peter Belly's mama.
Sig not Peter Belly's mama.
right, it should be here in
approximately 3 minutes.
In approximately 3 minutes. So Greavvesy,
so if that car wasn't famous, right? Say
that she wasn't famous. Yeah. And it was
just like a normal person.
He wouldn't. So you don't think nonslegs
would be saying that I was gay if I
didn't find her attractive then? Do you
think it's the name? I think it's the
name, is it? Not so much the person.
It's the name that uh created the trend.
I don't think it's the actual person.
Why? Why would nobody [laughter]
Why would nobody grievesy?
Why? Why not? Because if the person's
attracted, then it doesn't matter what
their name is. No.
Because if you saw that Italian person
that I went on a date with, I thought
she was quite good-look.
And no one says, no one said that if you
don't find her attractive, you're gay.
And she's better looking than Shel Co.
I'd say that Italian person. So why did
no one does no one say that then?
Are they actually copying each other?
Greavves, are you just trolling me?
Are they actually just like copying or what?
Yeah, when I was in this play share the
other day at the pool table, there was
Frankie there. There was Frankie.
Frankie pool table.
Must be a lot of winning money on that.
Yeah. So, they're copying each other though.
So what I'm saying is do they mean it or
are they copying each other
should be here now?
>> Yeah. So what they Yeah. So
where is this captain [ __ ] There he is
with my milkshake mate. Hello mate. Here
we go mate.
What the [ __ ]
Oh, I can open the door there for a second. You good?
>> 16. Yeah.
Hopefully it's not come all [ __ ]
>> I actually
hope it's not all slushing.
>> No, it looks all right to be fair.
It seems a bit smaller. I think that's
just because of the lid. M m.
No, that's lovely. Nah, it's not
squatch. It's lovely.
From five, guys. Not McDonald's. M.
Oh, I love peanut butter. You know what?
I love peanut butter, you know.
I love peanut butter, mate.
You know what my sister said? Trip H. My
my sister said that she remembers
holding me as a baby,
but she's only three. She's only 3 years
older than me. Is that Q remembering
holding me as a baby? I was a cute Bubba.
I come out of boxing. Oh gosh.
Yes. You can remember holding me as a baby.
Yeah. Five Guys is the best.
Money doesn't mean anything to us.
Steven Howard, I keep telling you this.
I'm not from Kent. [clears throat] I'm
from London for [ __ ] sake. M.
Oh, that is lovely. M
peanut butter and oil milk is my favorite. M
That's lovely. M
I think it's USA Izzy's milky.
I think they put her milk in there.
So if I started traveling again,
Greavvesy, and doing traveling videos,
people wouldn't come on and troll me in it.
So people wouldn't come in and troll me, would they?
Saying, "Don't let these [ __ ] women
win." Is it? Nah. I think if you change
I think if you change the topic of that
and start doing other content, I don't
think they'd mention it, isn't it?
Cuz there's an account that comes in
randomly, normally it's on like a Friday
and it'll be like, "Don't let them
[ __ ] women win.
They were laughing at you trying to egg
me on and [ __ ] But I think if you
change I think if you change the content now
they're only saying it greasy cuz I say
it in it.
They only say it because I say it
in it. They got all of this from me.
Have you noticed that? taking a baby
away from his mama. Yeah.
Women are hypocrites about sex. Crey,
would you agree that women are
hypocrites when it comes to sex?
They're hypocrites because they pretend
that dicks are nasty and they don't like
sex and they're all squeaky clean and
they don't need men. And then the next
thing they're having a baby.
Yeah, of course they're hypocrites. A
lot of people are hypocrites. But but
it's not just women. There's loads of
people that are hypocrite with things.
But they're definitely definitely hypocrites.
See, there's this woman that we know and
she's like everyone knows that she loves
sex. She's an older woman. Like she's
older and you think it's weird her
admitting that she's a sex freak, but
it's just being honest, isn't it? You know,
would you agree that they're hypocrites
when it comes to sexy?
This milkshake is the business.
That's the business.
I'm going to have to start using some
escorts again, lad.
No point having a dick being young if
you can't use it.
Absolutely pointless. Greasy. Hm.
Some of these people on Reddit, some of
these women on Reddit, Grievy, right? Say that.
Say that. Um, what do you what do you
expect me to say?
That's what Joe used to say. He used to
say, "Oh, what do you want me to say?"
They say, "Well, what do you want me to
say about the situation?"
I said, "You women are [ __ ] cunts."
in it. Really? Yeah.
Oh, he's a he's an addict. You know that
Joseph Far Steven Howard, he's going to
end up on the streets.
He put £700 in a [ __ ] FBI.
700 in a FOBY, bro.
Yeah. He's going to be on the street soon. H.
I love this milkshake, bro.
Do you like that, Gre? I've been eating
curry since I got separated from the umbilical cord.
You're putting £700.
You're putting £700, bro. In a FBOT tea.
Are you [ __ ] mad?
In a [ __ ] FOBY.
That's mad. He's He's going to end up on
the streets one day, bro. I'm telling you.
I've been eating curry. I've been eating
curry since I come out the since I come
out the womb.
Since I come from Laney's stomach,
that's cute, isn't it? Oh gosh.
Yeah, I am a Turkish man. I come from Turkey.
Uh Joseph Ferrar,
he was £700 in and he got it to a,040. I
said you put £700 in the fsy
then he took out a,040
I don't play them I don't play them machines me
I might play next week maybe 20 pound I
might put 20 pound on Frankie yeah
I probably would to be Yeah. Yeah,
probably. I've been thinking about it, but
I don't know about risking that kind of
money, matey. I was thinking about it,
but imagine it loses. You just lost
[ __ ] 700 [ __ ] quid.
Yeah, they didn't score today. I was
going to do Kitty Minister with Enfield,
but then I was thinking of doing Slow
and Enfield. So either way, I think I
would have got [ __ ]
Slow don't score unless they're home. Remember that.
If they're home, they score. If they're
not, then more chance they don't score.
I've been studying these [ __ ]
What do you think, Road Ma'am?
What do you think, mode man, the most
you should put on a double football bet?
Both teams to score? I No, honestly, to
be honest with you, I think the max I
would put on it is probably 150. Maybe 150, bro.
I could put 500 on it, but yeah.
Yeah, Adman said there's no point putting more.
They just taste like [ __ ] USA is
these boobies. These milk this milkshake.
Yeah, Antman puts 20 pound on. He said
he would never put more than 20 pound
on. But them kind of bets hardly ever win.
You need to try to win a double. both
teams to score like three weeks in a row.
Then you're laughing.
They taste like USA is boobies. These
they're very tasty. I don't gamble that much anymore. Here's
another double standards.
Oi Grezy. Here's another one with double
standards. You want to hear another
double standard one.
Here's another one.
I think women since you want them for
sex, just a prediction. I turn around
and said, "Isn't there women out there
that only want sex?" Double standards. I
mean, there's been people before that me for sex.
Yep. That's double standards. That's
definitely double standard
because there is women out there that
just want sex and want to meet people
straight away. Double standards. That is
definitely double standards. Mhm.
That is definitely definitely double standards.
What's your opinion, Grezy?
Yeah. Well, women out there that want
sex that just want sex,
they don't get called for it. Which is
ironic because they get called for being
a slag. That's that's the whole thing is
they get called for being a slag. uh if
they want sex, no one says, "Oh, um
oh, uh yeah, you're trying to use men
for sex and stuff." But when if you said
that you wanted sex, you'd be called for it.
Is that double standards, Grezy?
Grezy, is that one double standards? or nah.
When they say that like you if you only
wanted a woman for sex,
isn't that double standards?
Would you say that's double standards or no?
What's your opinion, boss?
Gregy, what's your opinion on it?
But here's the thing though, Grezy, that
doesn't make sense.
But Grezy, that doesn't make sense though.
Right. Anyways, moving on.
So, what? There's people that's just
uh I haven't been out for a while,
notorious. I can't be bothered.
I haven't approached in ages, lad.
I'm sick of it, to be honest. I'd rather
chill in bed. I'd rather chill in bed.
Yeah, I'd rather chill in bed. Me, lad.
I can't be [ __ ]
I can't be bothered with it all.
How you been?
I'll be out next week though.
Oh no. What was you in hospital for? Oh bless.
Sorry to hear that.
I unblocked the virgin. So I don't know
why he's not on here. Oh, bless.
[ __ ] this charge is [ __ ] now, bro. It's [ __ ] [ __ ] off.
Hate it, bro. It was my fault this time, though.
Why Greasy? Do you know some women?
Someone was like, "Oh, um, they were
asking women, do you like giving
blowjobs?" And one said, "No, it's disgusting, Grezy."
They said, one said, "It grosses me out."
And then the other one was like, "No, it's disgusting."
What do you think of that, Grezy?
They said sucking Willie grosses them out
and the other one was said no, it's disgusting.
What's your opinion on that? Grezy,
before you leave, what's your opinion on that? Yes.
I can't wait to get my haircut next
week. Oh, lush.
They've all got [ __ ] Tik Tok brains.
Oh, that milkshake was lovely. It was
worth the £8. It cost a lot of money to
keep Peter Belly and vitamins and stuff.
Oh gosh. How did that fall out? Triple
H. It cost a lot of money to keep Peter
Belly in the vitamins and stuff. I think
I'm going to go bed in a minute.
Going to go sleepies. Yeah. Gosh,
I need to start using escort soon. Like
I say to him, bro, there's no point
having a dick if you can't use it.
You was meant to, you know, you was
meant to [ __ ] like in porn. What's the
point of having a bloody dick if if all
you do is pee with it? Might as well
have a [ __ ] vagina.
What's the having a dick if you if you
can't use it? I've got a couple of
escorts on my phone. I'm going to have
to start seeing them.
Make the most out of, you know, my PCO and stuff.
I'll go to work every day and spend the
money on an escort if I need to, lad.
Because there's no point having a dick
if you can't use it,
even if it's just for [ __ ]
Well, we're going to do some traveling
videos soon. Yeah, I got my sleeping
pattern back. Triple,
do you remember trips? I'm going to jump
in the shower, right? I'll jump in the
and I and I'll talk to you later. Do you
remember when you used to say that Triple H Isabelle
is belly? God bless.
So, Trip 8, does your son Does your son support Newcastle?
If I ever meet your son, I'm going to
give him a West Ham t-shirt. I'm going
to make him support West Ham.
The next time you see your son, he's
going to be in a little West Ham
t-shirt. Na na na na na.
Yep. He's going to be in a West Ham top
the next time you see him. Yep.
He's going to be in a West Ham t-shirt
and you'll do nothing.
Nope. He's a He's a He's a Cockney lad.
Nope. He's a Cockney lad.
I do remember when Seaside Mark said
bomb sniffs his daughter's knickers.
with wage. [laughter]
He's a sick pop pupp puppy that Mark in
it. He's a sick puppy that Mark. He's a sick puppy.
He said, "Bon, go and sniff your
daughter's knickers." Do you remember? [laughter]
Do you not remember that [ __ ] sick?
He's a sick puppy. Poppy Mark Edwards.
He's a sick puppy Mark Edwards.
Yeah, he's a sick puppy.
That Joseph Farah needs to stop gambling
before he ends up on the street. I was
going to comment on his um thing saying,
"Your gambling is out of control, Joseph Farah.
It's out of control. Joseph Ferrar where
Mark said bomb sniffs his daughter's knickers. is
There's no point having the big this
lovely big dick if you can't use it.
I've got a really big pecker, you know, Triple H.
So, yeah, there's no point having it if
you can't use it. Absolutely pointless.
I did the other day. He commented on my
video. I told him to go away.
You and LT should meet up. Triple. You and Lt.
Do you remember the hangouts when it was
me, you and Jane? Triple H. Me, you,
Jane, and Monty.
Lovely site, isn't it?
It's funny, is it?
Yeah, I need to go to bed in a minute, lad. Oh gosh.
What's going on with this? One second.
But I thought my bloody my phone packed
up. You want You want Monty man on?
Okay, one second. Sorry about that.
Oh, I can't man on. He blocked me on Facebooky. He's
calling Adam Thomas.
I was I'm trying to get Adam on the
panel. Adam Thomas.
What a lovely fella.
He's all right, Adam, but he's a bit
stuck up. He's a bit o and stuck up.
He's a nice kid, though.
Oh, Bonny man's just gone live.
I'm going to watch Bonny Man. I'll catch
you all tomorrow. See you.