Oh my god. What is it with these [ __ ]
Reddit [ __ ] Reddit moderators keep
banning people to feel powerful?
They feel so powerful being able to ban
people and they don't even [ __ ] get
paid for it. [ __ ] nerds.
They don't even [ __ ] get paid for it.
Would you Would you believe?
They ban people and they don't even get
paid for it.
S those absolute nerds.
Absolute [ __ ] nerds.
They still have to ban manually, by the
way. These little nerds. They still have
to ban manually.
Even if they're flagged up on the
system, they still have to ban. They're
[ __ ] losers, bro. Absolute losers.
Absolute losers on Reddit
just woke up me.
I woke up thinking where does where does
the passion come from to want to copy to
want to copy the crowd. I thought I
would have got thought I would have got
a response but I didn't.
You [ __ ] copycat. Copycat. That dude
that performed proved that you was a
copycat all along. Copying the crowd. Virgin [ __ ] virgin. Yep. Copycat.
Make them Make them [ __ ] dress up as
Mario and Luigi. Yeah. Say that it's a
fancy dress. Lie to them, get them to go
and then it's pun them saying you copycat.
And then you move on to someone else. Copycat.
You little copycat.
That's so [ __ ] I can't stop saying
it. You little copycat. No mind of your own.
No [ __ ] mind of your virgin own. Yeah. virgin.
But yeah, these [ __ ] Reddit mods are
[ __ ] sados. I I didn't know they
didn't get paid.
I thought, well, at least if they got
paid, then, you know, I mean, still sad,
but I mean, they're getting paid, but
well, they don't even get [ __ ] paid.
What? Sad bastards.
It's all about power, Reddit. That's
what people need to understand. It's all
about mods having power. It's a power
site. It's a power trip site.
I don't want to stop using it.
They're [ __ ] losers.
Proper proper losers. What am >> [snorts]
>> S losers in it.
Sad little losers. These Reddit mods, [ __ ] nerds.
But to be fair, there's a lot of nerds
on this community as well. Little virgin nerds.
There's also a lot of nerds on here. So,
ain't got a life.
So, you know,
I'm off from next week anyways.
Definitely off from next week. It's
December, so I'll be off here for a long
long long long time.
But these people won't be cuz they can't
take one bloody day without it. Day
without YouTube. Not even a single day.
Sad, is it?
I got banned off Reddit again.
Got banned off Reddit again, lad.
They banned people to feel powerful,
Bob. They ban people to feel powerful.
Let me guess. How's the women's
situation? Same as it will always be
before you ask
cuz you like to ask the same thing. Same
as it was 6 years ago. Same as it will
be for eternity.
So yeah, to answer your question if you
wanted to know.
Same as it will always be. Yeah.
They ban people for no reason. The mods. Bob.
Oh, sad bastards.
It makes them feel powerful bastards.
I genally design it is a site designed
to push you off. I generally think it is
it's a site designed to annoy you.
Someone else said that before as well. I
think it's true as well.
[ __ ] simps. Yeah,
see the video that I done on Bob Bills.
So, he was definitely saying it to fit
in with the crowd, wasn't he? Definitely
was saying it to fit in with the crowd. Another
question is, are you gay? Copycats?
Told you it was a copycat trend where
they all copy each other.
Got no [ __ ] mind of their own. I I
can tell you, bro, even back in the school days.
I never ever done anything to fit in.
I've always had a mind of my own,
unlike the Orington virgin. Absolutely
no mind of his own. See, they all copy each other.
No man of their own.
Yeah. What do you think of it? But Bill
was bunch of copycats in it.
What do you think of it? Bunch of
[ __ ] copycats. No mind of their eye.
[ __ ] bunch of copycats with no mind
of their own.
With no mind of their own.
What I say of the builder.
With [ __ ] no mind of their bloody own.
Oh yeah, I don't know when I'm really
going to try approaching again, Bob. I
don't want to deal with them anymore.
I don't want to deal with these scumbag
all the same toxic women anymore.
Same old, same old, same old.
And if people didn't dis and if people
didn't dismiss my struggles, they would
say it's the same old, same old, same
old. And as usual, people dismiss your struggles. So
that's never going to change.
I don't know why you seem to think it's
going to change. I don't know why you
come on here and ask me, thinking that
one day it's miraculously going to change.
No. My mom was cooking me a gaming, but
I don't want it cuz it's from Iceland,
so I don't want it.
I don't know what I'm getting today. Copy. Copycat.
Better question. Are you home? Copycat. [ __ ] copycat.
That [ __ ] told me he had a mind of his [ __ ] own.
What? Cuz you wear some [ __ ] stupid
gay virgin secondhand virgin clothes.
That means that you got to buy them your
own cuz you wear absolute virgin clothes
from the charity shop.
No, mate. You're definitely definitely
definitely a copycat, mate. Definitely
definitely a copycat.
If you don't find that [ __ ] below
average looking transgender attractive,
you're gay with no tits and no ass.
Makes you [ __ ] hobo. It makes you
[ __ ] hobo. Does it? Does it make you [ __ ] hobo? [ __ ] copycat. Copycat.
Copycat with no mind of your own.
with no [ __ ] mind of your own.
No mind of your bloody own.
It doesn't make you look good, you know. Uh cola coke. Yeah.
Oh, I just shouted for no reason. I just said coke. Yeah. Um,
just get a big one.
Just get a mediumsized one.
Yeah. It doesn't make you look good
after copy the crowd.
What happens to copy cloud?
You're a little It makes you nothing but
a little copycat.
It makes you nothing but a little copycat. Somebody could Yeah.
So, uh, this person was like, he says,
"Oh," I said, "Oh, you can be annoyed
because you've tried and you've put a
lot of effort in." And when people say
no one owes you anything, this is what I
say. I said, "Well, what if you worked
right? What if you done a job, right?
and then your boss didn't pay you or the
company didn't pay you and they turned
around and said, "Oh, well, I don't owe
you anything." What What would you say?
It doesn't wash. That excuse doesn't
wash anymore. Um, and it's not
different. It's the same. It is
literally the same thing. Um, effort
means you get something out of it. Time
means you get something out of it. So,
then the boss doesn't owe you paying you
any money then, does he? Or the company. So,
or if you won money and then they didn't
pay you out. So, you you wouldn't accept
that they don't owe you anything.
So, same thing with women. If you put
effort in, they do they do owe you
something. Just like a man would owe you
something. I don't agree with that at
all. I don't agree with that. Not for
somebody that puts effort in. No, no
way. They of course they're owed
something. Everyone's owed something. If
they put effort in and time in, of
course they're owed something. Everyone is.
Of course they [ __ ] are. That's the
whole point of getting up your getting
off your ass and [ __ ] doing
something. Don't agree with that at all.
They do owe you something.
They [ __ ] well do. If you go out
there and you approach every [ __ ] day
and [ __ ] they do owe you something.
Just like if you went to work, you'd get
money. Just like if you went to the gym,
they do owe you something.
As I was saying before I cut off, it
annoys me when people say that it's
about money. When they say it's about
status and looks or whatever, you're
like whatever. But it's annoying when
people say it's about money when it
comes to women because it isn't. Cuz
even if you have money, you're still not
going to meet anyone. Even if you live
by yourself, how do how would I know all
of these things? How would I know these
things? because obviously I've had it.
Obviously I've done it.
So I don't know why these people on the
internet say these things
for the sake of saying it.
Like you could have money. You could be
loaded and you're still not going to meet anyone.
Why do they say it's not about money
when it comes to women? Why do people
say it's about money? >> Nope.
As you know, I don't gamble that much
anymore. as you know.
So, it's not about money.
I've been loaded. I've lived by myself.
I've worked. Still don't make no
difference. I don't know where people
come up with these things from.
Don't know where they come out with
these things from, bro.
This got to be excuses for these [ __ ] women.
I think they just make excuses for the
fact that they're just [ __ ] and
just say stuff maybe. I don't know. Who knows? Yeah.
Triple H dismisses my struggles.
Proper, proper dismissing your
struggles, mate, when it comes to [ __ ] women.
Don't mind me. I need to change my diet, lad.
What about the approaches where they
said straight away they weren't interested, Bob?
Wouldn't that contradict what you're saying?
What about my approaches where they said
straight away they weren't interested
and led me on? Was it about providing that time?
That's the whole point of dismissing
struggles. This is what I mean by you're
dismissing struggles. Because if you
didn't dismiss people's struggles, you
wouldn't be saying that.
There's plenty of videos out there that
I've got on my channel where I've tried
to speak to people and they said
straight away they weren't interested in
the past or they said straight away they
have a boyfriend or they've led me on.
So surely it would contradict everything about personality.
Surely that would contradict it. No,
they're just stuck up [ __ ] That's
all that's all they are. It's not about
you. It's not about what you have or
what you don't have. It's just them. They're [ __ ]
You know, you see Ed Matthews [ __ ]
guy. I was watching him again yesterday.
Same old [ __ ] Rejected. Rejected.
It's not about money though. It's
definitely definitely not about money.
The only time it would be about money,
bro, is if you're a [ __ ] billionaire.
If unless you're a billionaire, then
it's to do with money. I've been very
comfortable. I've had loads and loads
and loads of money in the past. plenty
of money never made a damn bit of
difference. It's not about money, bro.
Unless it's in the billions or millions,
you know, millions. And I mean a
multi-millionaire. Unless you're a multi-millionaire, then
yeah, that's that. So,
don't know why people would say it's about money.
I used to think it was about status and
followers, but it doesn't even seem like
it's about that because it's like even
when you have that, you still get rejected. So,
but I think it's well and truly
finished. I don't think you'll ever find anyone here.
I think that's that in it. That's that.
You ain't got no chance really.
[ __ ] depressing, bro.
Depressing, bro. That
You [ __ ] virgin. basically. Yeah.
Yeah. I quit ages ago, bro. Weeks ago.
They're so negative and toxic.
>> Depressing. Well, not depressing, just toxic.
Same result, same women. Once you've met
Once you've met one woman, you've met
all of them.
So, like, yeah, once you've met one,
you've basically met all of them cuz
they're all the same. So, they've all
got Tik Tok brains. They're literally
all exactly the same as each other. But
once you've met one, you've met them all.
Unless you go to some [ __ ] tropical
island where there's no [ __ ] social media. Um
um you go to a tropical island where
there's no [ __ ] social media sort of
[ __ ] then maybe. But
it's all about [ __ ] power with this Reddit.
They tell people to feel powerful.
[ __ ] bing [ __ ]
It's all about power on this Reddit. Okay.
Yeah, message is this person. So,
I'm at my bloody wits end.
at my bloody wits end with it all, matey.
These people on Reddit lied to me, Bob.
They said I'd meet someone.
Depressing life here in England, is it? But
proper proper depressing life.
People on Reddit lie so much. They say,
"You're going to meet someone." Yeah,
that looks like was lost yesterday.
What is the lady situation? Um,
what do you think?
I've seen you talk [ __ ] about me as well
on someone else's channel, which is
fine. What is a lady situation?
It is almost 2025. So,
what would your guess be? Was it was it
supposed to change or
I didn't I didn't know it was it was
about to change, bro. In almost 2025.
I mean, it's the same old as it would always be.
I mean, that's it's like it's it's like
saying to you, what's the [ __ ]
what's the color of your hair? It's
never going to change. So, why why are
you asking that? Is it suddenly what
what you suddenly suddenly what is women
going to pretend? Stop pretending they
got boyfriend. Stop leading people on.
It will never happen. It will never change.
Why would you want to know what this
situation is when it never changes?
Never changes. Never will change. It's
been going on for years.
These [ __ ] Reddit moderators are
[ __ ] sad bastards.
They're [ __ ] sad bastards. They ban
people for no reason. They don't even
get paid. These Reddit moderators don't
even get paid.
But yeah, the situation is the same as
it will always be.
It will never change, ever.
I don't even go out anymore. I'm going
out next week.
Don't really want to, but I have to cuz
I've made plans with someone. So,
I'd never go out again if I had if I had
it my way, bro.
Yeah. It's depressing. It's toxic. It never changes.
That's why I gave up
because it was too depressing. Yeah.
I've dealt with a lot of white knights
lately. I had a I had an argument with
someone on the train, Ben.
Some white knight tried to get involved
and his head got scrushed. His head got
crushed in the door.
And I have respect for the lady. I said,
I'll talk to her how I want. She's
talking to me like that. So, I'll talk
to her like that. [ __ ] white knights.
Next time a white knight gets involved,
I'm going to be like, "Dog, they're not
going to let you hit." That's what I'm
going to be like. I'm going to be like,
"Dog, they're not going to let you hit.
So stop it and they'll know exactly what
I mean by that. They're not going to let
you hit doggy. So why why are you
defending them? They're not going to
sleep with you. Too many too many
diagnosed uh too many undiagnosed
autistic people nowadays is is is insane.
They defend women thinking that the
women are going to [ __ ] them, but the
women don't like them. It's mad. They're
so autistic. They don't even learn from
each other. Bro, I'm surprised. You know
what? I'm surprised people don't learn
from each other. Men, women,
mad. Did you see my copycat video, Ben?
Nothing but a [ __ ] copycat. That kid.
Yeah, his head got crushed in the door.
His head got crushed in the door, bro.
Mad. I've never seen that happen before.
All four defending some just cuz they
got a [ __ ] in between the legs. Madness.
Oh, you know Virgin Boy, you know when
he was trying to say that you're gay if
you don't like Shervel Cole. It's a
copycat statement. He copied it. He
found a trend and wanted to and wanted
to fit him. He said, "If you don't find
Cheryl Cole's active, you're gay." He's
a copycat. He wanted to fit into the
crowd. Other people say the same thing
to each other. So, if I don't find some
below average transgender looking [ __ ]
with no body attractive, that makes me
gay. Copycat. He's the copycat.
He's the weekly copycat. He's got no
mind of his own.
If you go if you go on the student room
form, they all say the same thing to each other.
They all copy each other. He's got no
mind of his own. I bet he's got no mind
He's a little copycat
with no mind of his own. No integrity,
no substance, nothing. Just copy. That's
why he loves That's why he loves cats so much,
you know? [ __ ] mad. Yep.
What a copycat.
What an absolute copycat.
You can't ain't even good-looking. [ __ ] copycat.
But yeah, the ladies situation is the
same thing, Ben. I've not had a date
since April. I've been out lots and lots
and lots and lots and lots
recently. Uh yeah, I've been out lots,
bro. I went out three weeks in a row.
Same old. I have a boyfriend. I'm not
interested. Give you their number. Lead
you on. The end.
One of three things happen. That's
literally all that ever happens. And all
will ever and will ever happen.
Nothing changes. Nothing. You don't even
get dates now like you'd get like a year
ago, year and a half ago.
Yeah. You'd get like dates and stuff.
You get like buildups to success. Now
you don't get nothing.
I went out not last Thursday.
Not the Thursday before. I think the
Weeks ago, bro.
I haven't been out for weeks, bro.
I was in Liverpool Street. It was kind of dead.
Same old story.
Balling, bro. Balling.
So yeah, that's that. Shut up.
Yeah. So, it would never change.
You will never change.
It's like telling someone, it's like
what I said yesterday. It's like telling
someone they're going to win the lottery
after 10 years. I mean, what's the
chance that someone's going to win the lottery
or win anything on the lottery for that matter?
It's so depressing.
But people on Reddit say you're going to
meet someone then.
People on Reddit say you'll meet someone then yeah
man lives in Thailand. Bro, you don't
need to tell me some stories.
He tells me all about it. He lives in
Thailand. He moved to Thailand.
Also, women are compulsive liars and
bullshitters as well. them.
I feel sorry for people that even trust
women. Even people that in
relationships, you actually trust them.
They're nothing but [ __ ] liars. I've
caught that multiple times. You actually trust them.
[ __ ] that. They're [ __ ] Billy bullshitters.
They're [ __ ] Billy bullshitters. I
don't know how people can trust them.
I know all about it, bro.
I know all about it. That man tells me
all the time. But what he did tell me
was that uh it's harder to get people in
their 20s. He said you can get 30 year
olds easy, but trying to get 20 year
olds now and 21 year olds and 22 year
olds, they're very westernized and stuck up.
But he said you can still get people in
their 30s, which is good cuz here you
can't get nothing. You can't even get a 40-year-old here.
You can't get nothing. I could go out
today, spend £300 and get nothing. Not
even a date. I know today's Sunday, but
I mean next next week I'll go I can go
out and spend £300 and get [ __ ] all get
absolutely nothing. Not even a date. So
someone in their 30s is still winning in my opinion.
Yeah. You can't get laid here. You can't
get nothing here. It's depressing, bro.
It's a depressing country. Never changes. Yeah. >> Yeah.
He's told me all about it. He's never
coming back either.
But he said in 10 years it's going to be
the same as here in 10 years. He said,
"Yeah, you can't get anything here."
Here, you can't get [ __ ] all here.
Yeah, you can't get anything here, bro.
Other than I'm not interested. I have a
boyfriend. Same old boring [ __ ] Do you
know what? That [ __ ] doesn't even bother
me, bro. You know what bothers me, Ben,
is the leading on by text,
you know, and these people sit there and
defend these women like these women
can't do any wrong. It's madness. Absolute madness.
Yeah. [ __ ] depressing it is, bro.
I can see why people go on killing
sprees, you know? People that's not had
people that's not had sex. I can see why
people would go on killing sprees, bro.
Cuz they done the wrong thing. They
should have left and went to Thailand. I
mean, people do all sorts of things.
They can do [ __ ] that gets them locked
up. I can see why people do it,
you know, if they be on these forums
all, you know. I I can see it if they
were virgins. I can actually I mean, I'm
not a virgin and it pisses me off and it
[ __ ] annoys me. They piss me off, bro. So,
they're just [ __ ]
So, yeah. I'm not really asked to going
out anymore, Ben. I'm only going out
next week cuz I've planned it with
someone for ages and I let them down
before otherwise. Yeah, I don't think
I'd be out for
I I I don't think I'd be out again, bro.
Not for a very very very long time.
And then you see this Ed Matthews gets
the same old [ __ ]
Tik Tok famous. The guy's got money. The
guy's good-looking and he can't even get anyone. So
what, bro? What you think? The next time
I go out, what it's suddenly going to be
different? Why? How would it be
different? How the [ __ ] would it be
different? Bro, this is what I was
trying to explain to this guy yesterday
that you can't even get a date. I
haven't had a date since April. April.
We're [ __ ] almost December.
That's pretty much
it's almost a year really, if you think
about it. Couple months will be a year.
So, what makes you think that the next
time you go out? [clears throat] It's
weird why people think that all of a
sudden it's going to change after all of
these years. Yeah, I'm I'm in the
minority of 10%.
You know, I'm in the minority as well,
mate. They're stuck up everywhere
though. It's not just London. It's not
just London, though, is it? It's Wales.
They're all the same everywhere. Liverpool,
it doesn't really matter. They're all
the same everywhere. I see these Tik
Tockers go to America, from England, and
they can't get nothing. But you remember
all them guys saying to you, "Oh yeah,
they love the accent. They love the
accent. They love the accent."
It's not just about people from London,
though, is it? Because they're like that everywhere.
Absolutely everywhere. They're all
[ __ ] Even the ones that come here,
they're all [ __ ] They're all lion scumbag [ __ ]
same as Manchester. They're all the same
everywhere in the West. [ __ ] America,
they're all the same as well. I used to
meet loads of Americans time and time
again. They're all the same.
I went out, Ben, I went out uh about I
think it was about a month ago, a bit
over a month ago, bro. And I had to
approach 50 people to get one number.
I'd been to the dentist. Yeah. I went to
the dentist. I had to get fill in and I
was like, "Oh, I'm bored today." It was
Friday, so I was like, "Oh, I don't want
to go to sleep. Let me go out and
approach people." Bro, it took me 50
people to approach to get one number
sober. It was so It was sober to be 50
[ __ ] people. And the amount of
attitude I had to deal with as well. And
then you you think to yourself, well,
you get these people on the internet
that think it's going to change and
you're going to meet someone. Yeah. All
the people that you come across have got
stinking attitude. Well, not all them,
but most of them did. stinking attitude
that need telling about themsel.
Obviously, I didn't tell them about
themsel cuz it's not my place to do it.
I don't care. But, you know,
Yep. I I hurt my feet by the end. But
these people on the internet say it will change.
These people on the internet say that it
it will change and that
I'm not sure where they're getting this idea from.
Yeah, it was a lot of work, bro.
Especially sober. It makes you hungry as
well. That's why I don't do it anymore. Because
even if it would be nice to have
someone, Ben, my logic is that it's not
worth dealing with their [ __ ] their
attitude, their their lives, the
toxicity just to find someone. It's not
worth it to me. It's not worth it.
It really, really isn't worth it.
Obviously, I only done that for a joke,
right? Like the approaches cuz I was
bored. Like I I just done it to see what
what the score was. Um and um yeah,
a man really has no respect for himself
if he's willing to constantly put up
with that [ __ ] It's all right when
you're younger and you're a virgin and
you know, whatever, then it's it's a
different story. But
it's crazy, bro. The amount of attitude
that they have. They all say exactly the
same thing as well for people that are
not diff that are not all the same. Ben,
you get these people that will sit there
and say, "Oh, they're not all the same.
They're not all the same." But they do
and say and act exactly the same way.
Get [ __ ] They've all got [ __ ] Tik Tok brains.
They've all got Tik Tok brains, lad. Of
course they're all the [ __ ] same,
bro. What the [ __ ] They literally do
all the same [ __ ]
Like they're not all the [ __ ] same.
Of course they [ __ ] are.
There's not one good one out there at
all at all.
You can't even find someone that's
mature and doesn't lie.
And that's why I took myself out of the
game cuz it was just too toxic, man.
I took myself out of the game pretty
much a long time ago, bro. Cuz it's just
depress toxic and depress. It is. It
toxic. Yeah. Toxic and depressant.
I got 10 numbers about two months ago,
bro. I hadn't been out for a month,
right? And I didn't even get a single
day out of them 10 numbers. And after
that, I was like, "Yep." Whatever
happens now, it's like, "Yep, I'm used
to it. Yep. I'm used to it now. Yep.
Yep. Yep. Yep. I'm used to it now. Now
it doesn't affect me. If I like when I go out
um when I go out now I expect it to happen
cuz it would always be the same Thailand.
>> Yep. That's how Ant-Man does it.
Yeah. It's like£500 return. Yeah.
Yeah. It's like£500 return, isn't it?
And also, it's not cheap going out as
well, Ben. It's not cheap going out either.
It's not cheap going out. There's been
times of weekends where I've spent like5600
just to get nothing, just to get [ __ ] off.
But Ben, people on Reddit say that
you'll meet someone.
People on Reddit say that you'll meet someone
and they're liars as well, bro. They're
liars as well. Absolute liars.
You'll never meet someone in this country.
So, I don't know why people tell you
that you will when you obviously won't.
It's been proven multiple times you won't. So yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Antman told Yeah. Antman told me
that uh Antman told me that you can uh
you can get like
Antman told me you can get um
you can go you can drink beer all you
want from like 5 to 8. It's like 5 to 8.
It's like an all you can it's like an
all you can drink beer. Yeah.
Yeah, he told me all about it, bro.
Yeah, I'm staying in.
I'm staying [snorts] in, bro. Oh,
I'm staying in. Saving my pennies.
That's what I'm doing. I'm going to make
a bowl of corn flakes in a minute. Yeah,
I might go get some chicken and chips
later, maybe. But yeah.
Yeah. Hand man told me there's like all
you can drink
here. It's like £8 a pipe. B
I went to a local place last Friday. It
was £5 a Guinness. I thought that was a
bargain. £5 a Guinness cuz you're
normally paying like £8 even in a
[ __ ] Weather Spoons in central
London. You're paying like £8.
I don't know what's the point of Weather
Spoons in um central London because it's
not any cheaper than the [ __ ] actual
places that are eight pound a Guinness.
It's not any cheaper than £8 a Guinness.
H strange, isn't it?
Yeah, it's not any cheaper.
Yeah, I [snorts] won't be going out.
I'll be chilling.
It take a lot for me to get bored.
See, the thing is, Ben, I'd rather be
bored than deal with their toxic [ __ ]
and their their attitude.
That's why I don't see it as being bored
cuz I'm I I I'm sick of dealing with
their [ __ ] attitude attitude problem.
So I'd rather sit there bored, bro.
That's how bad it is. Yeah. Than deal
with them [ __ ]
Let me see if there's anything in the
cinema. I don't think so.
>> Yeah, I am.
How's speed dating going to work, bro?
What woman needs to go to speed dating?
Why would a woman go to speed dating
when all she's got to do is jump on a
dating app? Think about it logically.
Why would a woman go speed dating? >> [snorts] [clears throat]
>> Oh [ __ ] Is there a new Toy Story coming out? No.
Toy Story 5. Nah,
really can't be. [ __ ] [snorts]
I hate June though, man. I hate that month.
There's actually Toy Story 5 coming out.
But how was that when there was only
when there was a three? There weren't no
four, was there? >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, it's out in June.
I hate June. I hate going to the cinema
in June. It's [ __ ] hot.
Oh, Woody. We're going to see Woody and Buzz again.
I'm going to wear myself for all the corn flakes. One second.
No, no horror until next month. >> Yeah,
I just looked on that.
Otherwise, I would have went to the cinema. No heat.
There's one coming out next month.
There's one coming out next month. I
think it's called the Maid.
I think it's called the maid or the bride.
>> Yeah, the maid, the bride.
>> Yeah, the maid or the bride.
There was this woman on Reddit. Um, then
she said she doesn't date um people that
are not Muslim and people that are 28.
And I went her post and I found out that
she has. That's what I mean with these
women. They're constant bullshitting liars.
They're constant bullshitting [ __ ] liars.
Absolute [ __ ] bullshitting [ __ ] liars.
They're all the same, man. They're all
the same. Every single last one of them
are all the same.
say the same stuff, act the same way. Um, [snorts] probably orphan the ring.
Orphan the ring
and talk to me, I think. Yeah, that got
me the ones.
I'd love to go cinema today, but there's
no horror films on. Spider. Yeah.
What's your favorite phrase?
You're nothing but an awesome virgin then.
What's your favorite freak? This charge
is dodgy as well. Yep.
Why the [ __ ] are you not responding?
I can't shave my beard if I'll be
[ __ ] I'll be bullied.
What do you mean virgin boy? I can't
show my beard. Beard being bullied. I've
never been bullied. I'm not the one
saying shovel codes attractive to fit in that.
There was an Australian one. Did you
watch that horror film called Bring Her
Back? That was quite a good one.
That was a good one. was called Bring
Her Back. It was an Australian one.
Quite new. Give it a watch.
Yeah. Do you know Australian horrors are
quite good? Australian horrors.
Let's see them.
I love cornflakes. M
m. Lovely cornflakes. [snorts] Anyway,
I'm gone. Get